This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 374.
The David Head Show is pleased to announce the first in our sensation audio series.
The Adam Curry relaxation tape.
Listen to the soothing sounds as Adam unleashes his calm and serenity.
You're overweight.
You're fat.
You're only in the free cage that lives in your mind.
Hear the beautiful words of a man focused and centered in his own being.
It's a lie.
It's a fucking lie.
You'll drift in a tranquil ocean of peace and windless calm.
What is your fucking problem?
Relaxation.
More than just a word.
To Adam it's a state of being.
It's a fucking word.
Okay.
It's a word.
And how does he do it?
Because I switched it off in my brain.
I think, ah, well, whatever.
To achieve this state of perfect peace.
You must ask yourself these five questions.
Do I take it up the ass?
Who would I fuck?
Who would I kill?
Who would I marry?
Why haven't Keith in the girl been signed a pod show?
Let's explore.
Lesson one.
Adam's key to breaking from your hectic life.
If you keep getting stuck in this stupid bullshit,
you'll never get anywhere.
Lesson two.
Adam teaches health sensuality.
Can be brought about by sexuality.
I've explored all the limits of my sexuality.
I know where I stand.
I'm very comfortable with where I stand.
Not afraid to talk about it.
I've had my ass kissed in a sexual fashion.
I really didn't enjoy it and explore your own sexuality.
Explore the parts of your own body.
Some parts are worse.
Some parts are better.
Some parts are...
Hmm, kind of...
That's the way it goes.
Lesson three.
Learn the art of touch.
And how it can ease the senses.
It's beautiful when men hug.
It's beautiful when women hug.
And kids.
And cuddle.
And make love.
And have sex.
Lesson four.
Look not only to the good and peace in your own life.
But also to the world around you.
Look at the world around you.
There are kids who are killing themselves.
Young girls are starving themselves to death.
We have hundreds of thousands of kids who are fucking homeless.
By the final lesson, you'll be so empowered.
You'll feel as if you could take over the world.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Oh yeah.
I'm afraid you're going to take over the world.
Even after you listen to the entire series.
Who make you feel so at peace?
This is if you hadn't listened at all.
You didn't listen to it.
Okay?
Nothing more.
Nothing less.
Go back and listen to the show.
Prepare to be led in the journey of your psychic path.
What right do you have to call anyone a psychopath?
What right do you have?
Why does Adam take the time to teach others his method?
Because he cares.
I don't care about anyone.
What they say.
What they do.
Who they have sex with.
How they have sex in their private lives.
I don't care.
Johnson, a prominent Swedish doctor who deals with sleep disorders says this.
Adam's lessons on relaxation do a great deal to shed light on the issues in this community.
Wow.
That's the community.
I got to grow up in without asshole.
I'd shut up about it.
You better believe it.
By the end of this series.
You're not only no more about yourself.
But you'll know so much more about Adam Curry.
Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Now I'll sudden you know all about me.
You know what I've been through.
You know my life.
Adam would not only make you feel relaxed.
He'll make you feel special.
All of a sudden you're fucking special.
No way, mother fucker.
You're not special.
If you find that the Adam Curry relaxation tape helps you.
Please, right to him.
And let him know.
You want to hear from you.
One paragraph, not a long email.
One paragraph, the Adam Curry relaxation tape.
Get some sleep.
Get some peace.
Get some perspective.
All right.
I'm done with this.
I've nothing left to say.
Find out more at the davidmatchow.com.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strap to my ass.
Do the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking trees.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm fasting.
It's so curry.
We have clearance clearance.
Roger, Roger.
What's our vector, Victor?
How are you?
That's a clearance over.
Over.
Roger, Roger.
Almost to lovely.
I'll say it to you again.
You want to grow from my friend.
Well, you said you'd say goodbye.
Just try and prove you right.
Was I wrong?
Tell me I'm on it's gone wrong.
You're nothing.
I'm wrong.
You tell me I'm lost.
I'm gone.
Say you belong.
Go.
Almost to lovely.
Baby, I'll go.
Baby, you've been there.
Baby, you know.
Here's a preaching.
Looks like a hole.
And you never said it was a pleasure
when I served with it.
Just so I thought it was wrong.
It wasn't you.
You rewronged me to myself.
And I knew this was wrong.
I'm done.
I know the more leaders
The more I hate my head taller.
Oh, Mr. Lovelay, I'll say yes to you again
Oh, Mr. Lovelay, you want to grow my friend
Well, you're active in the middle and can't wait
It's a slave in the morning, it's a sworn in prayer
There's no sin in the ring, there's no love in the day
Oh, man, Mr. Lovelay, Beth Thorne Lee
On your daily source code, it is
What is it? Wednesday, coming to you from Curry Cottage
In the affluent suburb of Syria, Gilford and Surrey
Man, I love that song, Beth Thorne Lee
She's from California, she's from LA
And apparently a lot of her songs have been heard
in TV shows and films and now on the pod save music network
God, that was just an actual, you know, when I'm playing a song on previewing it
Patricia walks in and says, hey, then you know it's got something going on
It's Patricia approved, the only thing though
The only thing I felt this song was missing
Oh, man, you know what it is, come on, it's clearly
He needs a little bit of cowbell
Now watch it kick it
And now I'm feeling extremely bad because I forgot who gave me the cowbell
Was it Paul? Was it Neil? Oh, man, I feel bad now
Oh, yes, that by the way, it was not a mistake, I played that song
I got a recommendation from Douglas Pilgrim
And when he sent that to me and I played the song, I recalled and he
He played the song on his perfect head addition of digital flots
And thanks Doug or Pilgrim as you call yourself for doing that
You know, I've put on a pop filter
It's not even this isn't enough for the plopping
I do. Basically it's a professional version of a wire coat hanger
With a pantyho strapped over it
It's a double sided
And probably 300 Dernier
So hopefully the plopping should be a little bit less
Okay everybody, so sorry about yesterday, no show
But it was absolutely impossible. I knew that was going to happen
Which of course will tie writing to our long versus short
Five or three days a week conversation coming up in a bit here on the daily source code
Because we were in the city pod show in the city
On a mission seeing if we can get all the right partners lined up
And really of course podcasters are our partners
But we need a distribution partner or we need to kick you know kickstart some advertising
Or preferably a combination of both in order to get it going
Because we just don't have enough pod show money in the coffers
To fund a rollout
In the UK without you know some form of cash flowing in
Or at least some opportunity of cash flowing in
So we were pound in the street got up at 615
We met at 715
And we were off and I don't want to tell you it's just not appropriate
For me to tell you the people that we met
But we did meet with potential distribution partners
We met with the potential
Partners in advertising
And it was just it was great
It was a lot of fun
It was great meeting
All these different people
And what's kind of cool
You know this does fit into our
Brits versus yanks
And that's not really a versus because
You know we all kind of stem from the same place
But you know there is a definite cultural
Brits versus yanks thing
And it's so apparent to me
That we love each other
Who you really do
Even though we crack joke and I actually I'm in the middle
So I don't do it in fact when
When either Ron or Chris would make a joke
Usually about the language
And that would only be the three of us
And I found myself saying hey you know
Chill out come on
And vice versa I can totally you know
I hear all the jokes on TV
In fact I seem to be noticing more of them
Maybe just because I'm paying attention to it
But
You guys love us for certain things
And we love you guys for certain things
And personally I just got to say
I love living here
Even though it's not the amount of it's not 100% of my time
You know we do have kind of a
Well we definitely have a home base
And seem to be shooting some route
Our daughter is shooting route
Oh man I should get her to speak some some
Speak some English on the show you'd be amazed
She can do at least five different accents
Most of them based upon little Britain
But she can and a lot of what she hears at school
And she can do her you know her regular
Called regular American accent she can do Dutch
She can do flimish
But really when she's talking to her girlfriends
Like I wouldn't know I wouldn't have no idea that she wasn't born and raised here
But I'm digging it and London is so pretty even though even it rains
It doesn't matter and there's a lot about it is called it's about the people it's about
And I think this is directly related to media
Excuse me because I think that a huge commercial
Media landscape the way it exists in the United States is probably not very good for the public health
You know and there's and by the way NPR and public radio and public television
That's just an I think just another version of commercialism it works in different ways
And I don't think we have to get in a whole conversation
But you know whether you call it sponsorship underwriting whatever
It's it's all commercialized and it's understandable
And yeah you go on your
On your listener drives but a lot of the money is coming from big corporations
It doesn't matter
I think that what we have here in the UK is pretty darn special
We still have a culture of listening and because the the network the radio and television network spawns the entire island
Which is 60 million people by the way
There is still a lot of you know cultural communal listening and watching going on where you know people in the south of the country are hearing the same
At the exact same moment as people in the north of the country and and that is a pretty important community aspect
Something that we really don't have on radio in fact, you know, I was a part of that
We did have some kind of a national radio
It's still done a lot with syndicated satellite shows where local stations will pick up a feed
I did a show called hit line USA which was on it was a lot of stations
It was like two or three hundred stations across the US so we had pretty good coverage and it was a calling show
With with an artist and we'd always have a band or an artist and they met a lot of really cool people
Last in an hour and I have co-hosts in Los Angeles not being New York and so it was really good to field all the questions and
And have you know really a community of listeners the bummer of course is that
Whether you're on podcasts or whether you're a stream or whether you're live television or live radio
You still all got to kind of do that at the same time to make it work
So I have a feeling that
That we may just
Really settle down here
Like for good for good and what is forever and what is for good, but
Yeah, like in it a lot and of course
I'm in a very fortuitous position to be able to
Be in America a lot and I thoroughly enjoy as you know
There's a lot of things about the United States that I enjoy
Something that I'm enjoying immensely has been watching the tally of the bitties
the Lasivius bitties
Walk their sponsored walk for multiple sclerosis
CC Chapman joined in
Check this out they were hoping to raise $10,000 by
Requesting for donations on their podcasts both on the bittie cast
Of course an accident hash
We've talked about it here on the source code there are many other podcasts who purchase who put to part of the
Hey participate it in it
But check this out they raised a total of over
$22,000 and I asked specifically and yes, most of this money came from people listening to the podcasts
That
blows me away in just a years time when we raised $1500 for Lee Wilkins and is his lovely girlfriend
Jenny to get their dogs out of
You know basic isolation imprisonment
Which happened very quickly as well now we're up we can get we can raise $22,000 this is fantastic and thank you everybody
Who participated whether you walked whether you
Told other people about it if you're
able to donate money yourself. It's just that's great and and kudos to the bitties and CC for really driving that
It's what power what power remember training wheels people. This is just training wheels
All right, let me hear you with a promo here
Who knows what you should expect from midlife menagerie?
This is not a show about nothing but it's not a show about anything in particular
Nor is it a show about everything a guy has to draw the lines somewhere, right?
I'll talk about interesting stuff I'll tell him using anecdotes
I might review a movie or a restaurant and I'll play music that I like
And if you're a middle-aged Midwestern guy with very tastes you'll probably like it too
And if you don't well then maybe you're weird
tune in it just might not be awful
www.kelvind.com slash podcast
The music in this promo is from the pod show pod safe music network
Check it out at music.podshow.com and while you're at it stick it in your ear
Do you believe anything is possible? We do. Where are flink?
We believe in an internet that's safe from virus hidden scammers. We're earthlink
We believe your personal information should be just that personal and we believe your internet should be a friend not a fo
We're earthlink
Make this smart choice visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you earthlink
We revolve around you
So on Monday show I asked for some specific feedback about the frequency and the length of
this program and
I kind of gave you two choices purposelessly
Because I didn't I didn't want to really preset and you give you any preconceived notions
I said would you rather have five short shows one each day of the of the week of each day of the week work week or
Would it be okay if we did three longer ones?
And I so I didn't say how long I didn't say how short which is pretty interesting because what people find long and short is also very subjective
I did ask specifically for listeners to send in feedback and thank you very much
Most of the feedback I got was from listeners although also many from friends acquaintances and of course podcasts
Which is totally valid. I just wanted really I just wanted to I said that so that people would identify them
selves as a listener so I can put some perspective into the survey. It's all very very scientific stuff of course
overwhelmingly people want
five shows a week and
overwhelmingly they feel that they should be
About 40 minutes that's the average most people said under an hour
But the the number 40 came up very very often it seems to be a perfect time and it's kind of logical when you think about it
That you know if you think about a commute which could last an hour or a commute that's maybe half an hour
how you can actually
Massage the cast into fitting into your commute maybe you start just before you walk out the door and then you finish while you're you know
You're right enough the elevated to work or if you have an hour commute you might fiddle around a bit
And of course if you know, this is all based upon the original time of Dave winters walk which was 40 minutes and it just seems to be kind of a human clock thing
So a couple of you said yeah, you know
Make them as long as you want that definitely makes sense now. You know I do have one specific time restriction which is the satellite window
You know, order to get as many different pod show
Podcasts and then not all pod show podcasts actually on to serious
We've chopped it up into bits. We only have four hours. So what you're listening to now and stars
Only last 24 minutes and 30 seconds and then there's all kinds of I think this commercials and stuff and promos and what have you
In order to fit all the other stuff and sometimes I do 49 minutes which would be two half hour blocks
PW and I do that sometimes just to shake things up or just to you know
She switched stuff around make it a little fresh put some excitement into the into the lineup
But it typically it's 24 30 and this isn't that there's nothing I can do in 24. I can't finish
I just can't finish enough of what I want to do so it has to be more than 24 minutes and think about it
You know you've got a song it today. We had that great opening bit
The relaxation course. I was four minutes and ten seconds. You know, so before you know it with the
What is it what's missed to lovely? Mr. Lovely's another good form. It's just like eight or nine minutes gone, so that's almost half the show
you know
That alone I want to play a longer audio comment. So I think what I'll so obviously it's done when I'm done
But I think I should try and keep it
Definitely five days a week. There is hardly anybody who said
Give me three everybody wants it to be daily and they also of course feel that it shouldn't be called daily source code if it's not daily
Jamie says Monday here in second life or
High May I guess depending on
Your pronunciation. I like the daily source code to be daily
anywhere from
24 and a half minutes the satellite window to an hour
But definitely every day
When you're at the college I get them in the morning usually and it's great via the i-trip via fm in the car
And when you do it from the condo, it's usually afternoon in the home office when I listen I'm in the US Eastern time
So you know what Adam do him whenever he can for as long as you want just do him. I need my daily source code
Jack Elias get jacked dot hontemus dot com
Okay, so that was from my podcast or but I also got some interesting feedback from a listener not from the US by the way
Which also made a difference in my survey?
Hi Adam this is how you're from Mexico City
Well on DSC 333
You're saying that you like to receive a feedback from
listeners
Especially those of us that doesn't have a podcast
So I said hey, that's me
So this is my contribution for you and
Well, I wanted to
Comment a couple of things one of them was
Regarding the length of the show for me
Appesiate not very long shows
Especially since I try to listen to as many podcasts as possible, but
When you have a show that lasts more than an hour, man
It's it's difficult to do that and
Sorry, it's rather small texting here and
Yeah, I would appreciate if you make a
shorter shows
Maybe I don't know for a minute. It's a very good standard and
Well we understand that maybe sometimes you will have to make shorter shows sometimes
Longer shows okay
Exceptions can be made that's that's not problem
But if you aim to to maybe for the four minutes will be really would be nice
Um, all the things that you said
Regarding the feedback from listeners
Especially for the I would say the technology impaired
Man, God did switch it and all that stuff
I don't think that's the easiest way
I was thinking maybe you can do what others do
Which is to have some hotline
So the listeners can't call at any time and you don't have drums
So you you have you can have a voice mail system
Maybe like Skype so
Even you can have a number in the US another number in the UK
So depending where your listeners are can call to the number which is
Communined for them
And give you a message the rest of us that which are not in the US or the UK
Maybe can call by a Skype and I think that will be a very easy way to give you
All the feedback
Well some ideas that may help you
Well just to let you know that there's a listener who doesn't have a podcast
Right here in Mexico City that tries not to miss a show
What it's been a good talking to you and well take care and hope to keep listening about you
Best regards have here for Mexico
Bye bye right on have you well thank you very much for number reasons first of all because you confirm the
The whole concept of it being daily and around 40 minutes and if it's longer shorter that's okay, and I took your advice
And we've got a phone number
We have in the states
201 625 635 7
when the UK
020 7 6 8 1 3 7 5 3 satellite folks on 102. I'll talk to you tomorrow. Okay
So I've actually had those no had both those numbers for a while
It's a J2 connect or something whatever which I've always found to be quite reasonably useful in the past because it'll actually email me
The audio file as soon as it's recorded which now that I like there's another part that I really like the audio files are in a g in the gsm
Audio format which is very good quality and of course you'll never get anything better than what the phone is putting in
But I've tested it with my own cell phones and stuff and I like the quality of it and
The file size is very very small so again the numbers are 201 625 635 7 if you want to call in a voice comment
So it saves me in my Gmail inbox it saves you the hassle of having to record something if you don't know how to do it
And of course if you want to do something like Matt and Dave did with a pre-produced bit, you know that the we you know how to get it to me
Why the 201 number because I'm from Jersey of course 201 625 635 7 in the UK
That's a plus four four so the UK country code if you want to dial from somewhere else
the number is 020 7 6 8 1
375 3 and then finally on this topic because I don't want to dwell on it too long
Something that is also quite important as Tristan
Ppo or Ppo pointed out
Hey man
My car iPod adapter has been knocked out of commission and your shows are getting a bit too long to burn on a CD
In the future if you could take some pity on those with broken car adapters and make the show small enough to fit on a CD
One hour 10 to 15 minutes would be great. Thanks. Yeah, you know what I'm also someone who often does that
I'm a way to the if I'm my one my way to fair Oaks or oh one second
We've got a red dash out from message in three parts who's sending in
Okay
Oh, it looks like this is a from P to digital flot some server appears to be down use and it gives me a different
email address to use
To tell me when Charlie is up problem A involved all of West Coast pod show is slow too. Hmm. I don't know if that's a network thing or if that's a
Pod show thing
We're getting into that area, you know, as we we started to bring I think today we we bring the developers in
They all have some kind of info in their email box more about that on the devcast devcast.podshow.com
But there could actually be something just whacked out on the west coast. I've seen that happen before and God remember
Back in the day in the in the late 80s early 90s this happened all the time. Oh, someone put a backhoe through
some fiber near Virginia the entire eastern seaboard is down
Oh, yes, the good old day. So yeah, but I'm also a guy who will you know take off for the airfield and I'll burn a
A show onto a CD and take it with me. It's I really become accustomed to that, you know
I I always have a stack of CDs and a felt it magic marker always right down what's on the CD by the way
I'll you'll be sorely disappointed or you could get a CD
CD rewriteable of course if you just want to have one one for the daily source code whatever
So yeah, I am I am sensitive to that as well. Although I must say the burner in my Mac
It'll say it won't fit on one CD so we put it on two so that's not bad
So okay, so I guess we're going to keep it around 40 minutes, which I don't think I'm going to make today either, but there's so much cool stuff to do
You'll back to that bridge versus yanks
um
I find British women as an American speaker for something about it, but
It's fun to flirt with with British women and it works really well if you have an American accent and it's and to me
It's it's really sexy to flirt with with English women
It's something that's something about it
Has anyone else noticed this? I know there's a lot of Britian combos a couple of them at the the drafts and darts meet up we had
Maybe it is maybe it is the line maybe we just find each others
Accent very sexy for very different reasons and I can't really pinpoint what it is, but maybe maybe British women are just
Flirts I like it though don't stop
Okay, what do we have here oh yeah
Mark Smith I just wanted to
Read a bit of his email here
He says really nice to see surface
To see surface you're interested in what listeners are thinking especially in your last couple of shows
I'm a listener having for a long time since listening to your show
We nearly got your laptop swipe by some teenagers down at the BBC. Oh, wow
That is a while ago. That was a fun that was a fun day
I got myself down to the draft and darts after new the brick layers on Sunday not really knowing what to expect
They had a great time
I hadn't gotten myself a name stick and at some point in the afternoon someone I was kind talking to kindly made me
Made me one with a word for your on it. Yeah, I remember you
It wasn't done to be nasty or anything in fact at the time
I found it quite amusing. It's funny though as the afternoon progressed
I realized that the word voyeur did actually encapsulate in some way how I felt
It's a very weird thing to know such a so much about a person from listening to their shows yet
They know nothing about them. I would have I would have said hi and had a chat
But what on earth do you say to a person to whom you have listened to for nearly 200 shows?
Well, you say hi
Trying to keep the podcast in community a non-cliquey affair. I think is really important. Listen up podcasts
I have no plans to become a podcast to myself but love being a listener and want to be involved
So it's cool to hear you're thinking about this. Thanks for suggesting the gathering
I'm at lots of really interesting people someone which I will meet again, and though no darts were thrown
I thoroughly enjoyed the beer maybe I'll see you in second life. Yeah, Mark cool man. Yeah, that's I agree there
Now of course this was a very specific
podcast or afternoon. I was so happy that we had a listener there were a couple more people who were quote just listeners show up
But it's easy for for us as podcasts to get caught up in ourselves and what we're doing and
And so you know again, this is why I'm really trying to
Understand a lot more about my audience about you as a listener and hopefully you'll pipe up once in a while
And phone in on the on the numbers I gave earlier
Got another dev cast I'm gonna do today. I just want to bring people up to date if you if you want more of the geeky talk
About what pod show is doing. We've definitely moved that over to dev cast as in dector dector
Delta actor Vico Charlie alpha Sierra tango dot pod show dot calm
10 golden tickets had been issued 10 have been claimed
We're going to do another round today
For those of you who want a golden ticket
I saw posting from K1 Kevin
of Strauski on
Well, by the way
Shipman just as as we're getting this thing going his grandmother passed away
So he's gonna be out for the rest of the week. We knew she was ill and Kevin had been back to visit her several times and
It's just sucks so he's he's on a plane now and he's he's gonna go visit with his family
I think it's in in Chicago
So I'm gonna try and talk to Aaron
This afternoon or it'll be more like this evening
Early early to late morning San Francisco time Aaron is our database wizard wizard dress
I should say I haven't gonna talk a bit about
Well, what she's you know what she's I think she has a very important role everyone has an important role, but man
Data-based stuff that that's not science. Okay. It's sure there's some science but a lot of it is
Art and sorcery and all kinds of witchcraft and Aaron is just perfect for that
So we'll be talking to her more tickets to be sent out it again as if you want to go and take it
Sorry, I have a bit of you know what I don't have this in sale. It must be this different coffee
I'm drinking
But she's gonna get some new new pods for me today
Okay, so you should have in your email information and we just had to get some some stuff cleared up and we want to make sure everything was set up with appropriate
Appropriate docs et cetera, so look for that
And let's just clean it up some stuff here. You know, this is my problem. This is why these shows gets so long
It's because everyone sends me this cool stuff. I don't want to miss out on anything
I did a pretty poor job of explaining what mags are
The magnetos, uh, which I thought one was broken when we were on that flight, but it turned out to be a spark plug
Well, you know, you can always leave it up to the Charlie audience and then a cha cha head will bring you the real low down
Get out of him. This is Peter Bailey a listener from Australia and until recently an aircraft maintainer for the Royal Australian Air Force
In Charlie 373 you seem to a little bit vague about magnetos in the ignition system for your aircraft
Hopefully I can help out a little bit
Most if not all civilian piston engineer craft have two magnetos each magneto feeds an entirely independent bank of spark plugs
So each magneto feeds one spark plug on each cylinder
That way if you have a magneto that dies in flight your engine isn't going to die with it
When you select for example left magneto
You are electrically shorting the right magneto out and effectively killing it
Which leaves you running on one good magneto. That's what you do during a power run-up checks
Is to make sure that that ramp magneto that's still selected is going to continue to feed you with enough spark to keep the engine running
Hope that helps
Oh as for the duration thing that you're asking your listeners to give your feedback on
Personally I'd like to see it the Charlie kept it around an hour for the simple reason
This is how long I commute for and it's the best way I know of well
Second best way I know of of finishing a day's work is to just sit on the train and enjoy listening to the Charlie
There's not a radio show around that can beat it
Thanks and keep up the good work cheers. Dude. Thank you very much. See now there you have it from a mechanic who hopefully
No's exactly what he's talking about
Man
Yeah, how about really add something to it, don't you think?
Had a major metro sexual moment I wanted to share with you guys if this is our little corner where we
We sit around and complain and bitch and mowing about stuff that we never talk about it face-to-face because well
It's just not naively right
So I'm staying in the Sheraton, Bulgaria via hotel. There's no more spot at the at the luxuries
Buckle where Ron was saying in fact Chris wasn't staying there either he was at the at the york club or something like that
And the Sheraton, you know
There's there's two this
There's a couple things that really bother me about the standardization of Sheraton hotels one is
The hairdryer okay now when I check into any hotel that is costing more than a hundred bucks a night
I expect there to be a decent hairdryer on the premises
If there's anything I hate is that vacuum tube that reverse blows
Luke warm air out into a vacuum cleaner attachment
They are supposed to be actually actually be able to use a functional hair blowing device now remember
I'm not just using the hairdryer for blow drying the hair for actual drying
But for styling and it's
It's
Especially the magnets we click it back into place and you can't move around because the tube is too short
And then the lights the lights in the bathroom are so bright and of course you can't dim them that you know you're looking right through your hair
And to your scalp you can't get any idea of
What you're doing so then of course I want to go looking for another mirror and
Restricted by the hose so that was just a just a minor little annoyance
But because I've been subject to a cold for the past couple of weeks and I have a I have a lot of minor cold just now nasal stuff
I blow my nose a lot
It's been quite frequent as of the past week or two and
You know when you do that when you have dirty hands before you know it you can get a little
Infection under your skin anywhere on your nose, of course, and that started to turn into a nice little sit that was kind of bubbly under
You know
And here's another annoyance
I thought I was going to be smart by jamming only only what I needed into a roller bag
Which man I didn't have my life bag and you know we really are like women guys
You know at least I am I have all things I need in my bag. I've got you know
And acid should it happen
Sometimes it does on days like like yesterday
aspirin but also I have this
Marta gave this to me when I was doing the
Interview for the Spiegel magazine
She gave me this great cover up makeup and
Normally I have that right in the side pocket because
You know, it's if you have a sit. Okay, but to be able to to cover it up just lightly so you don't see it
And I admit for me it makes a big difference with myself consciousness
Particularly when I'm in a meeting and when I have to present stuff and so I didn't have that with me either
So it was not a very good Metro day to say the least hey Adam
This is the rubber head here for a rubber room for radio.net
I'm here in the bathroom, which is where all Metro sexual males go to a crimp and prune and prod
Get their selves together about to do my hair and I've got a product for you and
I don't have as much
Lowing hairs you can affect my hair is kind of short
I need it to stick up sometimes and I need to lay just right and
This is stuff you can only get it in salons
Not in a salon but salons. It's redkin fifth avenue
New York City you're rough paste
Working material you know it's kind of like it's not gel. It's not
Moose it's kind of it. It's paced you know it kind of like that stuff in
Kindergarten that you would
Well, I don't get next to you. I wouldn't even
But here's the thing you can't just go to like the
Public's
grocery store crubber or something like that and pick up a bottle you can only go to a really expensive
Salon and
I said once
My wife when she was gonna go out of town. I said hey can you
Can I keep the rough paste she said no, no, I need that there's only one bottle left and she said
Do you know how much that stuff costs and I said no
$15 a bottle and it's all
Tiny two and it's up and like a week
You know why can't they make
Stuff that is good and you can use it and be meant for sexual
To our full potential and then have to pay
$15 a bottle. I don't I don't get it anyway
I got to get ready to go
I got to go to work
Hi
Radio
I've been
Remember head and
Thank you once again first. Let me get that off my chest. Yeah, no problem. Well, I'll tell you why
You know what this is why I'm so confident we're going to get a sponsor for the metro sexual moment because
We're subject to the same crap that the women are my friend
The cosmetics industry. Yeah, we may not be using it quite as much yet and we may be secondary users by being first
And buyers and passing stuff on but
No, no, no, no, that's that is the cosmetics industry for you and you know what we'll get into stuff that we don't want to use
Because it's tested on animals, etc. It's said to you watch just stay tuned to the metro sexual moment
In 1775 it was the shot heard around the world and the revolution was on today
It's the podcast being heard all around the world and the revolution is on
Listen to some of the finest podcasts in the world at new England podcasting.com
New England podcast the revolution is on
From America
It's
The podcast with a mission to expose Jesus for who he really was
These guys are awful and we would never do that if we're giving the chance world
Well, Jesus loves some sexuals. I don't want fat people in my club
I would be as much ass as I could in response and I probably wouldn't feel bad about it
Christians prove that they believe in something a little bit weird
Check us out on the web at wTF-wjd.com
This has been your announcer speaking
They paid me to do this. I have nothing to do with this guy. Jesus loves assholes
I thought I'd roll that promo out for you to
You know have some different airtime for different perspectives
What was it's what thought was Jesus doing show interesting? I don't like the that's so
Old fashioned though the old they paid me to do those so I have nothing to do with them. That's too bad
Some I used to say they paid me to do this but not very much
So I want to wind it up today with a little bit of talk about second life because I actually spend some time there
So it is a part of my life just like my first life is or RL as we say on second life
You know what I've noticed. I've noticed that
Yesterday when I came home
I left the sea I was on the five o'clock train from Waterloo to Guilford Station and I called ahead of time
I used to call the the car servers say I'll be there at 530 because it takes about half an hour pick me up
And we were there late because we had some electrical thing that had we had to wait five or six minutes four
So I was there about five forty and the car wasn't there so I called up and I was ready to apologize
But the guy started apologizing to me saying
Oh no no no no I'm just curious really busy and it was it was crazy
I think it would probably take 10 minutes just to get from where a car would pick me up
To go around the station to the stop to the stop light, you know to get back on to the road
So I understand that you know
I understand how it worked with cabs and with drivers and traffic and crap and managing a business
We really have too much demand for you always have more demand than cars if you're lucky
So I'm cool with that, you know, but I waited another 20 minutes so by now the cars an hour late and I'm like fuck it
I'm just gonna walk and you know why not if you have I've been in cabs all day and the trains and tubes and I'll just walk
Which is a good 30 minutes from home, but it was great and what I noticed is that I'm paying a lot more
Intention to my surroundings and I am convinced this is because of second life in fact
Sometimes I actually catch myself saying oh wow, you know, I should jump on that balcony
Very quickly, you know, just a flash. I'm not in total not totally delusional
But architecture is is
Starting to become very interesting again to me clothing the people are where behavior is how they walk
This is all the stuff that you're you're very focused on in second life and and as I was thinking you know walking along
I'm thinking wow this could be a great educational tool
To have kids build stuff in second life when when learning about history and understanding
Understanding things like architecture and behavior and you could program that in and these toolkits
And become more plentiful and and more easy easier to use and I was just I just wanted to make a note of that that
It's really doing something to my brain, which I am enjoying completely
The guys from Lyndon Labs also gave a presentation at Google at the Googleplex
During their tech talks. Oh, man those guys are so square over there
I'll put a link to to the Google video in the show notes because it's great. It's cool if you want to because they do
They do the the talk with the two of them and one guy is showing stuff on the screen
Well the other guy's talking and it's cool. You should definitely check that out look for the link in the show notes
data source code dot com and it curie dot com
And Greg Hoffman says
Give me a link to a forum on second life. You have to actually be I think a member of second life to read the thread
But he says something something interesting here. I'll just I didn't quite understand what he was saying
And I figured if I put this in my in my notes for today, and I talked about it
Maybe I would figure it out. So you could put you could put your comments or wait into the discussion on what would be
Doing virtual podcast and video podcast from within second life
Imagine getting virtual cameras and microphones and a mixing board then you can control these and then out
Pops and audio or video at the other end and I have seen people do this
For me when I think it would be very compelling is a second life video podcast and then the avatars can actually show all
The second life gear or I presume anything else that they're doing. I got to figure this out if it's easy to record a camera view point
It probably is
The maybe a maybe I will do that. Maybe I'll do a video podcast of the castle which I've now I figured out how to lock it out
So the people kept just jumping by and landing on my roof and stuff and you can find my castle pretty easily
It's got a
Whitesacorsky s 76 helicopter on on the roof
Which I bought the other day and that I've been flying around it behaves
Amazingly
Life like I have to say
Not in the real controls because if you let go of the controls, you know, it just hangs the hangs there continues on its journey
But without a doubt good stuff in second life
Catch you there, right? Oh, there. I don't know she's Barry Burbs from the Burbs podcast, you know, we have some pretty distinguished listeners
You know, I got an email about the Burbs. It's a listen to it. Oh, yeah, I really like that
So anyway, I just thought I'd send you a voice mail to
Try and calm you down from
Again everybody excited about second life
I'm not quite sure I haven't checked it out, but I don't think you can do podcast and in second life
And you don't want to kill off the podcast in industry just yet Adam so a little less of the second life stuff
All right, bit more of some great British music and you know where to head for for that
Code UK slash pod
Cheers Adam. Yeah, all right me that now that's a that's a guy who's excited about doing stuff
And he's been doing this burbs thing for a long time to check it out. I did look at the site man. This is great
And we definitely got to talk about how we can do things together for sure
I don't have an English band lined up although, you know, I'm I'm happy to play anything from anywhere
This was something
That is not pod safe
In that respect that it's not on the pod safe music network. I was given permission specifically to play it
I'm not gonna tell you who it is until after the songs. I want you to listen. I want
I want you to tell me
We listen to this piano who's playing the piano
It's also the same person who produced the record by the way
I'll tell you who the the band is as well
Have to listen to it. Let me be the one on the Charlie
We've all the girl I love before
Down the hard time baby, I'll be the first bit it
Oh, you're down. I'm gonna let that count when I'm low
No, no, they stop the wicked deal about it
I do my best on the answers to your questions
But I ain't gonna promise that the way it won't come again
And if all I'm dealing is baby, it wants you from your hands
Let me be the one who makes you again
Let me be the one who's always there for you
When you feel us but with an alcohol sound and you're only just
And if all your way, let me be the one who makes you stay
I want to be the one
Gotta be the one
I don't want to be the one who's always there for you
When you feel us, let me be the one who makes you stay
I don't want to be the one who makes you stay
You know, don't break skies and get rid of it
Baby, I ain't here on my him and not here
Oh yeah, I'm all but I'm that hard to let them walk right here
I do my best on the access to your questions
But I ain't gonna promise that the way won't
Come again
Just let it wash away his sense
Let me be the one who makes you care
Lord, let me be the one who's always there for you
When you feel alone, where's the love you're saying
I don't want to just take it away
Let me be the one who's always there for you
When you feel alone, where's the love you're saying
I don't want to just take it away
Let me be the one who's always there for you
When you feel alone, where's the love you're saying
I don't want to just take it away
Let me be the one who's always there for you
But I ain't gonna promise that the way I'm over here
But I'll try how it is
You'll make up and let me make it
You'll make it everybody
You'll make up and let your words do me make it
You'll make it, you'll make it
You'll make it everybody
Tattoo, rodeo
Let me be the one by permission
The track was sent to me by
Okay, did you figure it out yet? Who it is?
We were in London yesterday and I've known Ron for 12 years
And still don't know everything luckily about him and vice versa, I hope
And we were talking and he reminded me that he had written some, I think he wrote some of the songs
But he definitely produced Tattoo, rodeo's album, which is great because I used to have a Tattoo, rodeo leather jacket when they were out promoting
I think it was Atlantic Records
And I believe I interviewed them in Los Angeles even at the same James Club or something weird like that
And Ron at the time apparently was living in LA
He had to produce this record and played piano and some of the guitar parts
And he actually sold the entire master to Atlantic Records
And I just thought it'd be cool for you to hear some of the work he's done
Although it's impossible that he can give me full permission to play that
He said he would he would stand up in court if any problems, any problems occurred
So a cool idea that let me be the one Tattoo rodeo
Okay, so we're over our 40 minute mark but I'm gonna keep it under an hour
We're gonna say goodbye to you now first of four
And I now have a new version
Beta 067 so it should be even better in its communication with with the PDN more about that on the dev cast today
As I said, we post a new one devcast.pot show dot com portions of the show brought to you by go daddy
If you want a great deal on a domain name how about $6.95
sense just on check out use the promo code
DSC has in Delta Sierra Charlie
One and you'll get the domain name for 6.95 and of course portions brought to you by
Ancue of you check out Heather and John L's podcast at download.acue.com
That's it animal curry dot com
One more time the phone number like you couldn't have paused it and written it down, but
It's fun to say it 201 65 6567 or in the UK 0207 681 3753. I like the US number a lot better than the UK number
So I'm looking forward to hear from y'all daily source code dot com. I'll see you tomorrow. Bye bye
Show podcast
Stick it in your ear
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from pod show and lime light networks