This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 379er.
Hey, whatever happened to his name moves.
Adam Curry, he's our wife.
And now he lives in the place called Jerry.
Can they give any other one?
About $60 million worth of airplanes trapped in my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Yeah.
You've got no comment.
Got you found out with your man.
Yeah.
You've got no go down.
You've got to give it all out your care.
Yeah.
I am not a winner.
I am not an ass.
I love it, man.
But you keep trying to put my love to the tears.
Yeah.
You're not the one in the world.
You're not too bad, man.
Yeah.
Well, if you're on a naked, you're mad to give it all out your care.
I'm gonna tell you why.
But you can't take it.
There's always someone else who you care.
I ain't trying, don't put your trust to the taste
Just keep on going and you're about to have the taste
Yeah, but all the money in the world
Just don't know how what I will do
But I've had only made a deal
All the money in the world
Those up there have to know
All there have got to do is it
All the money in the world
Don't know how what I will do
But I've had only made a deal
All the money in the world
Still I've had to know
Hey everybody, welcome to the Charlie
This is going to be a fun show
See how many times you laugh at all this shit I say
On the show today, Lady Patricia
Let's drop by
Hello
This is not just because we love each other very much
And we like doing stuff together
But it's all about ratings
Oh is that so cute?
I don't like that
Well that's not honest
What do you mean is the most honest thing I can say
People love it when you're on the show
They all love it
I just do it because sometimes I like to talk to you
No it's okay
Yeah, Patricia was complaining about the sound
It's right
I gave Christina my headphones
Yep
So that's how they got busted
Yeah
And I like it
So anyway, due to popular demand
I'm trying to get Patricia on the show
Nice underwear on
Shut up
This is not it is nice
Adam is in his underwear
Not in my underwear
Oh yeah
At my black for say slacks on
These are my for say
Yes
And my Russell and Brumley
Crumley shoes
Yep
And this is this you gave me this is my Italian wife beater
That's what they call this like a wife
Oh is this
Yeah, except my other ones are really wife beater
I said are you going to beg the bread?
Yes
I'm making a pasta for you baby
Come here
I'll make your pasta rise
So
We had a lot of things we wanted to talk about
Hmm
Today on the show
And I figured I'd start it off
Because we got some feedback specifically for you
About
Maybe we're talking about the Beatles
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, it was the Beatles
Yeah, yeah
Because Frank Sinatra is in a playroom
Is he in a playroom
Is Frank Sinatra in a playroom
Is he actually in it?
And he's not in it, is he?
No, he's not in it, at all
I don't even think
He has any talent
No
Now he's a conductor
He is
Yeah, I'm sorry, he got to be pretty talented
He worked with his dad
Watch, I'm waving my stick
Yeah, he worked with his dad
And I think he does arrangements or something
Okay
But I don't think that this is the way he reacted
On TV
I think it's not his production
It's got to deal with his sister
Oh
Little bit of nastiness
Yeah, so that's maybe
And they invited him to see the show
And that's why he said
I was amazed
And he was actually thinking
I was going to play
Because I see my dad
So that's not important
But the way he reacted
Mmm
Are you a bit jealous?
A bit jealous of the success of your sister
Yeah, yeah, yeah
He had a very grumpy face
So
I'm just going to close the door for one second
Because our next door neighbor
Better known as our daughter
Oh, do you?
He said not my radio may be
I don't know that she has it on the shower
Oh, okay
He has that shower radio
So now
So now, you know what you were saying
It wouldn't be great
If there would be
Something similar with the Beatles
Yeah
And check this out
Listen to what I've got here for a second
Hi Adam
This is Bat
Also known as a French lazy Bastard
This is a new guy
I love this
I was talking about the French being lazy
Bastards
That one of the works that I'm going to protest
I love this guy
Keep sending stuff
It's the French lazy Bastard
But I'm going to play that again
I love it
Okay, but listen, he'll be
He'll be standing in more stuff
I'm sure you'll hear what
I had done
This is Bat
Also known as a French lazy Bastard
I can't really talk to you right now
Because I signed a contract with Syracuseolise
Oh, you're before
So
I'm not able to
Tell you that I'm one of the characters
They're a new show called The Love
I'm going to take place in Vegas
Really soon
But I can tell you that you will be always welcome
And also all the listeners and podcasts
To come here
It's always a pleasure to visit
Especially in Vegas
Really strange city
So I hope I will see you soon
And by the way, I will stop my podcast
Ready soon too
At FrenchFamilyat.com
And you can be sure that no beaters music
It's going to be played on my podcast
See you soon
Bye
I think you should call it
The French lazy Bastard podcast
That'll be quite much more commercial name
So he's a player
In this production
Called Love
Which is exactly what you want
And it's going to be in Vegas
And it's about to beat him
Yeah, here's the details
That was not very clear
When he was saying
Well, he was saying he because he's under contract
He can't talk to you about it
It's a bit early
But well Paul Barry Jr. sent a Gmail to me
The show is called Love
Here it is
Preview performances June 2nd through June 29
7 p.m
Oh, we have to go
Dude, totally
During performances
The creative team is in the very final stages of production
The audience has reaction and participation
It's an important step in this process
The artistic director of Love
Reserves the right to interrupt their performance
To make any adjustments
Very blah, blah, blah
He's even given me a ticket line to call
Wow
I'm thinking what we do is
We asked the French lazy Bastard
If he can hook us up
Oh, what did he just say?
He says something
I'm sorry, let me just see what
Only you
For me
Bye
The chemo
Watanabe
From the potsafe
Music network
Okay
Club for the song
Very good
I say, why don't we ask him to hook us up
Yeah
We're not going to sing Elp
Elp
I need somebody
I don't know if he's singing
Hello
I am the French lazy Bastard
Elp
No
But yeah, I feel very close to the Beatles
Songs and the Beatles
Time area
Because
You know, it was my time
When you were growing up, absolutely
My time I was there
Yeah
Yeah, I was there
You were there during the original
Love End
Yeah, the Love End
That we did
That was a world
It was not a worldwide telegraph
It was the first satellite broadcast
Yeah
And the stones were there
It was 69
I'm going to guess
I could be
Could have been
Yeah
And so it was done at the BBC studios
That was where the main location was
The Stones
No, the Beatles were there with the Stones
Stones and a couple other
I think a Marion Faithful
And all those...
Marion Faithful?
Faithful
I said it right
Yeah, you did
I know
The Dutch have a travel
You don't haunt, by the way
You're not really Dutch anymore
The Dutch have a problem
We're pronouncing this
Yeah
So the safe face
And we literally heard a guy on a TV show
Yeah, Marion Faithful
I'm more like
But she had her face full
Help me, help me
That time she had her face full
Oh yeah
But so yeah
All around Europe
And I think I don't know if in America
No, I think it was Europe
Probably European thing
And you were in the Dutch studio
Yeah, it was in the US
And in the US
It wasn't that the studio that I used to record my show in
Or was it a different one
You were in the recording
Yeah, could have been concordia
Yeah, it was only two
So we had the stars from Holland there
Which is you
And the Femco to was there
The man behind the Golden
Golden Earing
And Venus
And Chuck and Blue was a little bit later
No no no
Willem was the man behind the show
Oh that's what you mean
Okay
Chuck was the Golden Earing
Hearing motions
Q 65
Qb and the Blizzard
Probably
Qb are stars
I think about it in the crowd
Uh-huh
Who was our Bob Dylan
Yeah, a couple
And maybe Bozura
Bozura
No, I don't know
Well she wasn't being
Never heard that name ever before
So the Dutch
Marin faithful
Oh
Okay
But and she was
She was produced by the Golden Earing
She was very beautiful
Very beautiful
Beautiful girl
Um
So we were also
So you all sat around
Set around with flowers
Love love
To do
Love love love
So we were sitting
It was amazing
Yeah, yeah
There were a couple of
Um
Uh
Tv's
A hanging around
Isn't we could see the other people sitting in there
Okay
And they said
Hello Holland
How are you?
Can you all wait
Are you all there?
Here we go
Holland
Yeah
I don't know if they have a
Still footage of that
Oh yeah, of course they do
I've seen lots of times the black
And white footage
Yeah
I want to see myself
See that
There's so much that you and I
And when it comes to footage
And photographs
And recordings
We don't have any of that
Shit
Oh by the way
I told you I got this guy who has your entire
Every single song you ever released
That's why I wanted that daddy
CD from you
Yeah
Because I'm sending that off to him
That's the only thing I know
I'm sending it off to him
Notice my grammar was correct
I am
I'm in the process
Look
Yeah, it's on the stack
It's on the outstack
Because that was the only one
Didn't have because that was never
sold in stores
It was only available with the
Approaches
That through your
Lepy cosmetics
Yeah
So I said no problem
There's four tracks on
I'll send it to you
But would you be so kind
As to send us every single
Collective
Would you be so kind as to send
Every single song
Patricia has ever done
And he claims to have them all
He sent me a list
I'll have to give you the list
Every single one
Including all the heart stuff
You name it and he'll send it to us
Yeah, there's a bunch coming out
For people who want them
Yeah
But this will really be everything
Yeah, I mean so there's
That's what EMI
Oh, no
But I think they have everything
It EMI
No, of course they don't
No, no
Half of it is a red bullet
Some of it's at
It's around
Oh, they didn't use
They don't own it
No, they don't own it
They're not going to use
What they don't own
That's that's what's so fucked up
About the music industry
Is they bring out a box of your stuff
But it's only stuff they own
So it's none of the other stuff
So it sounds from some other
I checked it on really
And I...
Yeah, somebody has to do it
I look at that stuff
Yeah, yeah
Especially because they just do it
Without even involving you
Which is fucked up
It amazed me when I saw
The
The amount
Well, how much is going to cost?
No, how many
How many
Singles I had
Oh, dude
Singles
Yeah, back when Singles meant something
EMI
So I don't know the rest
It's not even the stars
This isn't all that shit
So 40
And EMI
Yeah
In 10 years
10 or 12 years
Yep
That I was singing for EMI
It's amazing
So we're doing something fun tonight
At, I think it's seven o'clock
I hope we don't know that
We were watching Joan Collins
On Jonathan Ross
Two, three weeks ago
Yeah
And you like Joan Collins
I like her
She's a feisty lady
Yeah
And how old is she now?
She's got to be pushed in seven days
She's got to be very close
She's already seven
She looks amazing
And you know, you can say anything about her
But she's well-preserved
She's well-preserved
Whatever she does, she looks good
She's
And she's...
But that's going to...
I think, even though there's
Something very sexy about her
Yes
I really, really, really
I'm curious
What
The rest of her looks like
Why?
Because I just want to know
I mean, would it be like a
What her head stick out like a sore thumb
About the rest?
I think no, no, I think she takes care of her
First skin is not bad
She's still with that guy
Didn't she have some younger guys?
Yes, she has a younger guy
And those guys, those guys will keep you moving
But keep you going
She said that she's very happy with him
She tried it a couple of times
I mean, with her
She's been interested, she's been married
She's been married to some interesting guys
Yeah, but didn't work out
But she's a strong woman
Did it come on?
There was some famous guy she was married to
Wasn't there?
No?
I thought so
And some waxed out guy
That didn't work out at all
Peter or something
Yeah, yeah
He turned out to be some kind of
Of course, of course
Yeah, you know what's going to
Show up at her doorstep
So she's doing a tour
A small theatre tour
Yeah
And evening
And evening with Joan
Call us
And I can't, you know, and so
We're lying on this
And now we're looking at the
John and we're saying, what is she going to do?
Yeah, and I grab a blackberry
I'm like, yeah, let's order some tickets
Yeah, so we were very curious
What an evening with Joan Collins
Yeah, it's about 35 miles away
It's not in London
She's not in London at all
It's a nice, nice trip
I hope so
Yeah, so it's to the south of here
So it's about
Why are you doing that?
Why?
Well, we don't have to go
You know, if you don't want to go
We don't have to go
Why not?
Just, you know, to do a lesson
See, yeah
Yeah, I thought it'd be interesting
How my future will be
Oh, please
This is your future
Right here on this show
This is your future in show business
When Jonathan asked her
You know, why she did this
She said, well, I need the money
Mm-hmm
That's what I always say
I need the money
People think that
I can always use more money
People always equate celebrity status
To wealth
Don't have to do anything anymore
Ah, it's so not true
Look at us
You know, because she wanted to show
She was all that
You want to live like a star
If you want
Once you are a star like she is
People expect her to live in a beautiful house
She can not just live in a little
College, it's like we do
Of course she could
No, people expect her to live in a mansion
And she lives
She has a beautiful man
I got to tell you, I am so beyond that
For myself
Oh yeah
And why are you building
Castles in second life?
Why a castle?
Well, why just because I like what a castle looks like.
Why not a bunker?
For exactly the way you just said a bunker.
And besides, curry bunker
does not have the same cachet as curry castle.
So what I mean is, everybody would like to have their own castle.
Let me just say, well, we've had a castle
and I miss it still very much.
Yeah.
That's part of it.
Because the castle I'm building in second life
is a great place for entertaining.
Oh, OK.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
OK.
You want to get into second life now?
You want to talk about that?
Although, you know, I see that it's very, very interesting.
And it's brilliant.
And I see it as a game.
But I don't see the purpose of it.
You don't see the purpose of it?
No.
I mean, people can hardly deal with the first life.
And now they're escaped to, they want to escape to second life.
And then, and then probably somebody that they're not.
And then, probably be a girl a chick with big boobs and a very extremely eye-eels.
Have you seen me in second life?
Are you the girl with big boobs?
No.
And I've seen you.
So everybody's good.
Of course.
Somebody that they actually are not.
Well, you, you can.
Is that the fantasy?
Well, the first of all, let's just step back.
See, I am the girl with big boobs and the extremely eye-eels.
Yes.
Exactly.
And all the girls in all the girls in second life who look anything like you.
I immediately have a crush on.
The only thing is they're about six feet tall.
That's the only difference.
And if you were in second life, if you were in second life,
the only thing you change about yourself is you make yourself taller.
Right.
True or not?
Yeah.
Okay.
Now, let me just step back for a second.
Because I said this to you last night.
You said, who has, in fact, you did want a real Patricia.
What time for this?
You're really.
And I said, this is.
People have hardly time for each other.
No.
Before you get into that, let me just step back.
It's replacing television time.
It's replacing all that other time that is spent on other entertainment.
I don't think that it's in addition.
So we spend time fun of the TV.
If we watch television together, you know that we always, you know, or argue about it.
Or usually about, had you made comments during the commercials?
Have you?
Yeah.
Or, you know, a discussion.
Or you talk about it.
Or you enjoy it together.
You know, with me, you do something together.
Together.
Right.
But that's what second life.
You have lots of people do second life together.
Koso and Joe.
So I need to sit there with my laptop and play with you together in second life.
Well, you don't have to.
Well, first of all, I'm allowed to have some personal time to do whatever the hell
I want to do.
Right.
You know, like you don't do that.
Well, I take advantage of that privilege.
And this actually is, if anything, this is cutting into my flying time.
I might have decided to fly instead of sit on second life for two hours.
So, but it's a choice.
And that's what I think is so interesting.
Why are people choosing this?
Don't give me that's, that's smart.
You think I'm talking out of my eyes?
I'm not.
I'm serious about it.
I'm serious.
But here's what I think is fascinating about it.
And then you can say whatever you want.
And I really want to hear it.
I want to hear it.
I'm interested in it.
What are you interested in?
No, but here's what I find fascinating.
Is the crossover between real life and second life.
So, first of all, I had no idea what I'm sorry.
My phone is.
I don't know.
I thought I heard a big bumblebee or something.
That was money.
Your ass.
Okay.
I had no idea what would happen.
Because basically, anyone who's in second life has a different name.
And you don't usually know them.
So, I said, I gave up my second life name,
which is about the darkest name I could find.
Adam Newman.
Yeah.
Why?
Well, you can't choose your last name.
You can only choose your first name.
Okay.
For some reason.
And I said that on the show.
And then people started showing up.
And last night with the night before,
50 people partying on the roof of the castle.
But you know, people want to play with you.
No, it's not about that.
I totally disagree.
No, it isn't.
I mean, first of all, if you watch and you could see it,
then you'd see that it's not true.
People want to chat.
They want to talk.
They have questions.
They want to meet other people who they've heard of.
Maybe on the show.
It's a sort of playing.
Okay.
But it just makes it sound so infantile when you say playing.
It's not.
It's socializing.
It's a game.
It's not a game.
This is my point.
There is no game over.
The game never starts.
It never ends.
You know, the definition of a game is not what second life is.
It's it's more a virtual.
It's.
Look, people are on MSN all day.
Look at your daughter.
Yeah.
All day.
She's on MSN.
It is exactly the same thing.
She only instead of having to come in every time.
And I say to her, who are you talking to?
Her body.
Why are you talking to these people?
Well, why not.
Isn't that.
It's not.
They open the door and there's somebody who is selling something.
Oh, come in.
I want to talk to you.
No.
Because you can.
First of all, who said they're not selling you anything?
No.
They're not selling.
But it's the same thing that somebody comes to my door.
I just got to go.
Hello, Ms. Curry.
I just want to talk to you.
Hold on one second.
Okay.
Folks listening to us on serious satellite.
One, two.
I'm sorry.
You're going to have to download the rest of the show.
Go.com to get to everything that we're going to talk about.
PCH is next.
Why would I like to speak to strange people?
It's not straight.
It's not strange people.
I hardly time for my own fan.
Hear me out.
So I talked to, and you know, you've heard of Andrew Grommett, Andrew Grommett, who
I've worked with on podcasting for two years.
And he now works in San Francisco.
We talk in second life.
We're talking in second life.
Why don't you just talk to him on the phone?
Because no one talks on the phone anymore.
If you can avoid it.
It's instant message.
It's just like MSN.
Only instead of having all these different windows open.
You're in a place.
Now listen.
Yeah.
Listen.
What I'm trying to say.
So normally we'll be on on Skype.
It has instant message.
Yeah.
So we'll be Skypeing back and forth.
And it's just it's so that it's so you don't have to have a full conversation.
Like hi.
It's Adam.
I'm calling you to talk about this.
I'm interrupting.
He can do 15 different things while in some messaging.
And I can do.
I can have 15 different conversations.
It's multitasking.
This is what people do now.
That is a huge shift.
Is it a different way of phoning each other?
You don't phoning each other.
It's just not.
No.
I mean, it is a different way of.
It's communicating.
And so, so communicating is what it is.
But it's socializing.
And the socializing part is where Andrew would be in second life.
And then he turned around.
You say, oh, by the way, Adam, this is Scott.
Scott is from, you know, so and so.
Party line.
You're equating it.
You're equating it to old metaphor.
I'm teasing you.
I'm not fair.
This is for people like me who don't get it.
Okay.
I do.
See, I, of course, I try to understand it.
And I try to, you know, I wonder if Ron understands it.
I get into it.
But there are people just like me.
Same age.
They think, why?
What are we doing?
We have, you know what I mean is we have hardly time for you.
You've hardly time for your family for your loved ones.
You forget to call your mom or I don't know why.
I called my mom.
Yeah, you did.
I spent time with you.
You know what I mean?
I'm going to go into joke columns with you.
People spend a lot of time being in this second life.
While they don't even, you know.
Well, you don't know that.
I'm sorry.
You just don't know that.
You don't know other people's lives.
Why?
You're presuming that.
You're totally presuming that.
Here's how I look at it.
Now what I want to say is because I'm a bit slow.
No, no.
It's okay, baby.
They can even resolve their problems in real life.
Now they have a second life.
Okay.
All right.
So let me, let me just,
I'll, here are the things that I find interesting.
First of all, the fact that when you're,
when we're on the roof of Curry Castle in second life,
and there's people who I know,
I don't know them personally,
but, you know, they're in Chicago,
they're in San Francisco, they're in Tokyo,
you know, all these places.
And here's a way to, to get together
that is not just a bunch of text command line
based stuff.
And we have general, you know,
we have interests.
We should, in some cases, podcasts,
you know, the pieces, music.
So it's life enriching to get together
and talk about stuff.
Now the problem, of course,
is that Curry Castle was kind of set up,
not to be a party place,
and, you know,
and everyone who's coming in
is kind of new and testing shit out.
So, you know, one day,
the things on fire,
the next day, there's, you know, like,
well, and by the way,
the nicest person,
the most respectful in second life,
comic strip blogger,
will not come over to the castle
without an invitation,
even though he has a lighthouse right next door,
because he feels that's not proper.
I'm telling you, this,
I gotta, I gotta get,
I gotta get the lazy French fucker on too.
Alright, so,
um,
but then Dawn and Drew show up,
or Dawn,
I didn't actually see her,
there were so many people.
Yeah.
And then listeners,
fans of Dawn and Drew show,
they're like,
wow, it's Dawn, you know,
and it was the same reaction,
as I've seen it at a personal meeting,
great,
except no one had the travel
all this way to go and hang out with,
all people want to do is,
I think what it's proving is that
even though the physical aspects are very important
of real life,
no doubt about it,
but we've never had the capability
to fly somewhere immediately.
You know,
it takes a lot of effort,
a lot of time to get somewhere.
So I think it enhances people's lives,
by being able to,
you know, meet Dawn and Drew,
or maybe they'll be able to go and listen to it.
I think it's not you,
it is me,
it's me,
of course it's me.
I mean,
when I have clothes on,
am I still me?
Yeah,
okay,
you flesh,
what do you mean?
Flesh and blood and real?
I understand,
it's not the same thing,
you would never get the real thing
because of,
time, distance and all of that.
So isn't that a plot?
It's more nice to see.
If you're chatting on the internet,
but then,
but you have a body
that people can see,
and you can,
you know,
it's more than that.
That's what I'm trying to say.
We've all been chatting on the internet
on an instant messaging for years.
We've been doing that.
Email is chatting.
Yeah.
But we chat on email.
What are you talking?
Excuse me, you do a hell of a lot of one-line emails to all your friends, your family,
people you work with, you do that all the time.
Now, I know that second life may seem a little bit geeky, but what if you just put on a
pair of glasses and you saw a hofer right there and you saw your sister and of course it
wasn't easy.
But it's not my sister.
It's your sister speaking.
It's a drawing.
It's a rendering, huh?
I understand, but isn't that better?
Okay, so here's how it works, so you see your sister, because you do this and you have no idea
how sophisticated you're using the internet already.
You find a handbag that you feel that she should buy for the store.
So you're sending her, what?
A drawing, a picture, pixels on a flat screen, not sending her an actual bag.
She's looking at it saying, hey, that's pretty cool, and eventually the real bag should
be stored.
I don't have a conversation with a bag.
You have no-be you have a conversation with Ivn about the bag.
Thank you, Ivn.
Why are you doing that?
I didn't.
You crazy.
It's working, okay?
It's more oscillations.
It's wonderful.
Have fun.
No, it's great.
It's great.
I think it's going to be shot at all.
I'm not defending it.
It's going to be a big success.
I know that.
I'm not defending it.
I'm just trying to
Feel it, it's my guts.
Then why are you pointing there?
My guts.
No, I feel it's going to be a great success, it's fine.
Anyway, so I
What I'm doing.
I want to use this in conjunction with what I'm doing.
I have other hobbies.
This is not a hobby for me.
I'm building a palace.
I showed you a picture of it yesterday.
How does it look?
Yeah, gorgeous.
Thank you.
And it's going to be the place where you can see podcasts, music, bands, perform live.
It's going to be classy, right?
What is it?
No cool-aid.
Look in guys.
Here that beef cake.
So no one blowing up to the size of a cool-aid jug.
No flaming arrowheads.
You know, black tie made when you're classy.
I want to classy.
We'll have black jack.
We'll have poker.
So we'll have
And you really you play for real.
For money.
Yeah, but you're actually really play, which is cool.
Yeah.
That lay
You know, that lay service.
We have hosts and hostesses.
And, you know, so from time to time, we can have
You know, someone still
People are just going to disappear in this world.
Possibly.
Wow.
But think about it.
For people who cannot leave the house, it's wonderful.
It's not just about it look.
It's not just about leaving the house.
It's, you know, you can't go to San Francisco just
Oh, let me go to San Francisco because there's a cool band playing.
Yeah.
I guarantee you, if I told Christine any one of her favorite bands was on in second life.
She would love to be on second life, except she doesn't want to be on the dorky teen grid.
She wants to be on the adult stuff.
It's too old for her.
Yeah, it's definitely too old because
Yeah.
Because, and then, of course, there's that.
Because at the end of the day, at the end of the day,
everyone in second life is going around having cyber sex with each other.
Oh, that is so sad.
Please don't tell me that.
That's sad.
God.
It's not it's not sad.
Oh, I was afraid of that.
No.
It's not sad.
It's
I think it's an and
Either it's
It's a human thing.
Yeah.
I think it's
It always ends with
Fucking for some reason.
Exactly.
For some reason.
Okay.
And I've talked to a couple of the escort girls.
Yeah.
In fact, just about every cute girl in second life has it one time or another worked
quote worked.
Well, they will love you Adam Newman.
Yeah.
If I give them a thousand lindens, they love me a long time.
Lindon.
There's a lot of really twisted fantasies.
Yeah.
Oh, that I believe I know about that.
Oh, yeah, really?
Yeah.
How do you know?
Well, it's been, you know, it's been for years and years and years.
And yes, people are very extremely strange fantasies.
Yeah.
But, you know, I think the brain is still the largest sex organ we have.
So, if you're stimulating the brain based upon some visual images, I have to say
I can see already because I've seen the figures that those men have in second life,
with those big baskets and, you know, walking around with
Boy and boy.
Big muscles and everything.
Yeah.
Well, that's a part of it.
Well, of course, mine is a true representation of real life.
Yeah.
Particularly my arms.
I have arms like tree trunks.
It's a second life.
It's an expensive skin.
18 tackles.
10 tackles.
Yeah.
No, I think that
I think there's
That's not an area that I'm interested in delving to deep into,
but I think that the way people have sex in second life is something
new.
It is definitely something new.
It is something
I'm very safe.
Very safe.
Yes indeed.
Yeah.
But it's fascinating.
And so anyway, so with the palace, which
And they're building it, and I'll put some pictures up somewhere.
I wanted to show you that this morning.
It's phenomenal.
This is going to be so beautiful.
And we have actually
We hired people to work in second life.
We had a meeting on our land.
I mean, if you get in
Of course, it's all
It is a game.
But then again, isn't all of life a stage, and each of us must play our part?
Love is a game.
Okay.
We're playing.
No.
We're talking to no.
You're done.
You're bored with it.
Yeah.
Okay.
So let me just finalize by saying
So of course, we have to kind of start small just to see how goes.
I can't run this thing.
Someone else has to run it eventually.
It has to run the palace.
And we're going to give away golden tickets in the podcast, which will have the code
to get into the palace for like the opening night and stuff.
So that's the kind of stuff that I like experimenting with.
Am I invited?
In second life, you can absolutely your invited.
In real life, no.
Okay, dear.
Hey, I just wanted to
Bring it one last thing before you go.
Yeah.
I love you.
Oh, thank you so much.
And then there's one other thing.
Yeah.
You've been doing a lot of research recently for arthritis on the internet.
Yep.
Because you have is it in your lower back?
Yeah.
I've never had anything like that because you know
It sure's not the same from time, right?
It's not the cell phone type.
I still have my doubts about it.
You know, I'm very sensitive for these sort of things.
And I'm a great mover.
My muscles are, you know, like elastic.
Yes, they are.
Yes, you know, baby.
You are so flexible.
I'm a great dancer.
Mm-hmm.
I'm going to get me one of those poles.
I'm a mover.
So it's strange.
It's very strange.
But really hurts, right?
But I'm not telling me how much it hurts.
It hurts sometimes.
But all the time constantly, or is it better sometimes?
Yeah, it's all the time now.
And it starts actually from the moment we came to England.
I'm telling you.
It's not the weather because it's the same weather.
Well, unfortunately, you didn't have any problems.
No, but I didn't do anything.
Here's the thing.
I lay down in the sun, you know.
Yeah, but does that really make all the pain go well?
Well, if you move around, you can feel it.
That it's, you know, sometimes it's stiff.
Sometimes it hurts.
I mean, I know what that feeling is like.
It's like my accident.
I know where it is.
Yeah, yeah.
That's what I looked it up on the internet.
And it's in the internet.
On the internet.
40 million Americans have it.
Oh, yeah.
And they're going to be another million to get at this year, probably.
Yeah.
It's a normal thing.
It was when they checked, for example, the,
the mummies and everything and examined them,
that even in the days of the Egyptians,
they already had that problem.
So it's a human thing.
Oh, yeah.
Don't worry about it.
You're not abnormal.
Don't feel bad about it.
No.
But the question was, since we know that lots of doctors,
and well, and it's people much smarter than us,
listen to this show.
Because, you know, I don't feel old.
And I didn't want to read, like,
Oh, now, you know, this is your problem,
because you're getting older.
That's not the, that's not the problem.
Because, you know,
you know, even younger people,
and even kids can have it.
Yeah.
But it suddenly came.
And I want to get rid of it.
So I read a couple of things.
I read some newsletters from doctors.
And so I'm going to cure myself with
a metal tea.
Yeah.
Devil's claw.
You know, these sort of things.
I told people you're a witch.
They know that.
I don't have to.
Just my, my eating habits,
because these are, I think, already.
So when does it kick in?
When does it kick in?
I don't know.
It takes a couple of weeks.
I'm going to try to mean, see, and, uh,
glucose a minute.
How come?
So here's what I'd like to test.
Is there a way for us to test?
Um, if it has to do,
I think the way to test it,
but it has to do with the cell phone tower,
because I'm still not completely convinced.
It's strange.
So when we go somewhere else,
it doesn't bother you.
Even if you sleep in a completely different bed,
even if it's in Rotterdam.
Yeah.
I feel a lot better.
So, but then when you hear,
it's because I'm moving on,
doing stuff.
So why don't?
I thought maybe because you know,
I'm carrying it.
You can see bags and, and, you know,
I'm my basket.
I'm carrying you around.
So why not for, like, a week or so?
We test it.
And you sit on your ass for a week.
And, uh,
No, I can do that.
Yeah, you have to.
We had, it's for science, baby.
Yeah.
Now, you know what I also do.
I don't sit down the whole day.
You should sit down now, then.
Even, yeah.
But would you be willing to test it?
So that we have, you know,
we can, I can help.
Christine, I can help.
Yeah, I know.
No, no, no.
Because the best thing in any case.
Roger Smalls will be happy to help.
No, the best thing there is is just moving around.
Just keep on moving.
Moving.
Can we test it?
Can we take one week out of your life and test it?
Just to see.
No, no, no.
No, I'm not going to do that.
Okay.
No, um, let's play one song.
No, because when you sit around,
don't do anything.
I'm going to be fat.
So that's another problem.
I, you know, I'll love you.
You get fat.
unconditionally, whether you're fat or whether,
you're fat, you're fat, you're fat.
Yeah, you don't.
You don't.
You're going to go to the second live and play around with those beautiful.
You better believe it.
Six feet six to some of that.
Tell big boobs, high heels are girls.
No, that's not a good problem.
Another good idea.
Play one song.
No more wrap it up, okay?
Think you like this song.
This is John Nicholson.
Love is all right from the podcast.
Music.
Then I used to follow in strangers.
Lookin' for the girl with the flowers in her hand.
Music.
Love is out right here
I don't be the one to reach out
Save you, maybe it'll come in a twig
Let's not lie
Baby, you can save me in return
Each of us could give the other way
It's the fly
You never know it might be the perfect thing
Might even turn around
Stay the whole and me down
Don't bother telling me
Love is all right
Love is all right here
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's why I love so much about you.
I don't have to say anything.
You get up, your earphones in, you're ready.
You know, the song's ending.
Nice.
Such a professional podcastI bunu.
He's aremth, yes, you are.
John, Knickers and John with no H.
He's from Tennessee.
He's when he's like in that hole.
Hey, Tennessee, Nashville.
Right from Mafia.
Yeah.
I got some good stuff going on.
Oh, OK.
Remember, don't mention a name.
And I told you that one of our clients that we had it think new ideas that they've signed
up for, you know, we're going to do stuff with Podsafe music around the country.
Yeah.
Remember I told you about that.
It's happening.
It's on.
Yeah.
I just saw an email this morning.
They got the go ahead.
Dude.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's wonderful.
I said yesterday I said, when I die, the only thing I really care that people will
say about me is that I helped in this in the Podsafe music revolution.
Yeah.
And I said, you know, burn my ash, burn me to a crisp and, you know, what's so much more about
is that so many, so many bands, they get another chance, you know, or they get a new chance.
Oh, dude.
You should hear that.
Or band said or and and tell us that never get a chance.
I put, remember I played, you want to crazy about the song, let me just go and find it.
I played, uh, crap.
Let me just, um, just get this.
Um, I played a song from Leslie Gore.
Yeah.
Because she's now in the Podsafe music network.
Mm-hm.
I'm just, uh, stupidity.
For me.
It's my party.
No.
I'm sorry.
Not Leslie Gore.
No.
Yeah.
Now you can have me confused for a second.
Um, so, uh, Marc Eosho motor Nemkov, hold on, you know, from Pacific Coast,
Highway.
Mm-hm.
He, uh, have to change this from a guy I hate doing.
So, stupid.
It's a change it from a, uh, dot M O V file to a MP3.
Sorry.
Mm-hm.
This is very unprofessional.
But I wasn't preparing on doing this.
So, we interviewed Blake Morgan, who, uh, is the owner of the record company.
And also of a couple other, uh, pot-safe artists that we've played.
Listen to what he says.
Undeniably, every single time, um, any of our music has been played on, on your show,
or on Adam Show, and Adam playing, uh, ever since, um, from Leslie's record, we saw a gigantic
hit instantly.
Like, we saw a huge spike instantly, and it's not like a coincidence or anything.
It's, it's absolutely clear.
You can see it on iTunes.
We know it happening off of our site.
There's no doubt about it.
Podcasting works.
It's the new radio.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, I wouldn't go so far, say it's the new radio, but for those guys, I always say
it for the music.
Well, for the, for the people from traditional music business, yeah, it is, it is the
new radio.
It's the new promotional vehicle, and they're selling on iTunes.
So wait until we finally get everything open up, and the MP3's will be available in
all the positive music network.
I think we can actually break some of the shit that's going on.
It's going to be phenomenal.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right, baby.
So, uh, I'll check on the, uh, on the navigator.
We probably have to leave around, what does the show start 730?
I think it was early.
Yeah, 730.
So probably have to leave around 6 something like that.
Yeah.
And we'll tell the list.
I was going to say more.
What it was.
Yeah.
Tomorrow you'll pop by.
And we'll talk about it.
Yeah.
What are you going to talk about?
Portions of the show brought to you by Earthlink.
Stay tuned for the Pot Show Challenge sponsored by Earthlink.
It's going to be cool.
You get to make stuff.
And when valuable cash prizes.
I'll give you.
Check out Heather and Janelle show download.accu.com.
And finally, if you want to register a domain name for the lovely lady Patricia, such as the
lovely lady.
There's a great idea for arthritis.
Hello.
Trisha's arthritis.com.
Then you can get a great deal of code to add a 695 for your domain.
If you check out with the promotion code DSC number 3 and people are actually doing
that.
And I appreciate it.
Yeah.
Okay, baby.
Well, thank you, Mr. Newman for having me.
Thank you, lady Patricia for being on the show.
I really appreciate it.
I have this.
I know.
This will continue.
This is 20 years of this.
I'm okay.
Okay.
I can handle it.
Cracky.
All right, baby.
I love you.
Love you, too.
See you tomorrow, everybody.
Another Pot Show Pot Cast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this Pot Cast and more great ones like it on the high performance Pot Cast delivery
network from Pot Show and line white networks.
I love it.