Delta Sierra Charlie 3-4-4
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass
In the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into the future
When the sheriff found the plants
They were eight feet tall at least
Growing in a grassy little urge of the highway
To the east
Who owns this land
The sheriff had to know
He said someone's got to pay the price
For letting these plants grow
The land belonged to God himself
The records clearly showed
So God went on the one at least
The crimes he and it got removed
God himself showed up in court
The answer for his crimes
The calling goes early in the past
He may have deserved some time
Mother nature managing
Whatever you do
To make the world so bright
And we're a little wet all black on you
The call went wrong again
We're a little dry to your sleep
He's just in the eye
The job is playing
This call is the greatest
According to the accused
We're a little wet
God said
But you are crazy
I send this as a gift
To ease your stress
And worry little mind
Just your spirit to sigh
Would lift
So you and it
The judge is going
To committing such a crime
So although I hate to do it
You're gonna have to serve some time
So that one got up in the federal pen
For his lifetime, no approval
The words were passed to dust
And the judge fears poor soul
Now the law to his little tail
In case you couldn't tell
Don't try to make it clear
And if they can't sell it
There's a group so well
Mother nature managing
Whatever you do
To make the world so bright
And we're a little wet all black on you
The call went wrong again
The legal drug loss
He's just an eye
The judge is playing this court
The greedy kids
According to the accused
He's just an eye
The judge is playing this court
Shhhhh
Mother nature of Merid Jane
What have you done
The Court of Breetingers
Val Davis from the plain情 es Nietzsche
object
I'm music.podshow.com.
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
It's Wednesday, halfway through the week back
at the cottage in Gilford, the affluent suburb of Surrey
in the United Kingdom.
It's a beautiful day today.
It is very, very cold, but it's one of those days where
you can see for miles and miles and miles, the sun is shining.
There's a little bit of wind, which would actually be beautiful
for flying today.
Wouldn't it?
I got to call the wind commander.
See, when I can pick up the delta-share, delta-share.
So, boy, I'm pretty wrecked.
I'm tired.
It's been a lot of travel in the past a few weeks.
And now, finally, I have a good stretch where I just
get to sit here with the girls.
That stretch will last for about 11 days, then
it's back on the road, more about that in a bit.
And yesterday, of course, the big lawsuit held at the court
in Amsterdam, the Netherlands,
plaintiffs, being myself, my wife and my daughter,
against the Outdox Publishing Corporation,
the gossip rag weekend.
And the two editors in chief,
because there's a co-ed leadership there, personally.
And I thought, you know, if we're going to discuss this
and tell you what went on and what went down and what happened,
what better way to do it, then, to do it with my co-plaintive,
the lovely Patricia Pi, who was up here during the,
during the, during the weeds, so on.
And that you had a cup of tea, and I said,
well, you didn't bring any from me?
Not meaning she'd have to go and get some,
but there you go.
That's the kind of, that's the kind of gal she is.
She'll be back in a couple minutes and we'll talk about that.
Lots of other things I want to try and get to today.
Let me see, what should we do?
Okay, just because this is time sensitive.
Let me get this out of the way right now,
because I promise Steve, I would do it.
Here we go.
In three, two, one.
Hi, this is Steve Webb with the Lightspring podcast.
Lightspring is a podcast that answers some of the questions
that everybody has about God, Jesus, and Faith,
whether you're to believe her or not.
In three, two, one.
So if you don't normally listen to Godcast,
I'm extending this invitation to you.
Yes, you.
You can find the show at lightspringpodcast.com
or search iTunes for Lightspring.
Two, one.
In this week's episode, I answer the question of whether or not
there's power in prayer.
What do you think?
Is there power in prayer?
Take a listen to the podcast.
My answer might just surprise you.
Of course, life's spring is happy to be a member
of the pod show podcast network.
And I've been hitting you right between the years
with a message of hope, love, and good news
since October, 2004.
Two, one.
I dare you.
Take a listen to the lightspring podcast.
This week at lightspringpodcast.com.
All right, Steve.
Come closer.
Psst.
How are you, baby?
Oh, you're getting situated there.
Okay.
Yeah.
Do you like the stool?
Is that good for you?
That's the one that our fans and brought over,
remember?
You weren't here when you brought it.
It's an lovely stool.
Yes.
Yeah.
Move the thing.
You want to use your headphones?
See?
Yeah.
Let me just everything for you.
You used to be a singer.
Yeah.
I'm adjusting my.
My grabbing.
Grabbing them.
My grabbing the shaft of the stand.
It's a very professional grab there, baby.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
And it's the headphones a little shitty ever
since Christina Barnum.
For the work.
Yeah.
They work.
I'm not touching them.
Yeah.
Don't touch it.
No.
Hey, baby.
How you doing?
Yeah.
I heard it snowing in Holland.
Oh, yeah.
Yesterday in Holland, it was, she was crap.
It was so cold.
I had, um, I had Eric, I told you that I had one of,
Eric had one of his guys got and get me a delivery.
Yeah.
For Michael Jackson and you of Michael Jackson.
Excuse me.
George Michael Jackson.
I wish he did.
No.
George Michael.
Yeah.
Eric supplies George Michael as well.
He does international deliveries.
Just tell me where you're parked and we'll bring it to you.
Um, RB wrote me an email.
Said, Adam, I just listened to your show before going to court.
Sure.
Hope you weren't lighting up a split before your court appearance.
Didn't I ask you?
Exactly what you asked.
Didn't know, baby.
I'm clear.
I'm completely clear.
I, uh, he says.
I used to do a magic act a year ago and lit up before opening for the,
for the Steve Miller band in Pasadena.
Man.
What a mistake that was.
Everything went wrong.
And I have no idea what I did on stage.
But the band really liked it.
Yeah.
Do you think they're on the same level perhaps?
I think so.
I think you functioning very good.
Yeah.
Why?
I don't see a difference.
Mm-hmm.
But that's because I'm always this way.
Less, lesser aggressive.
Less aggressive.
Yeah.
But, but friendly.
And, uh, well, maybe I, you know what, maybe I shouldn't.
The frames are wide open.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
Maybe I shouldn't consume before doing a show because people like it
want to get really pissed off.
That's what they said.
Yeah.
That's how it's turned got to famous, you know.
No.
How it's turned got famous by putting lesbians on a show.
Ah.
That is the clue.
Yes.
That is the true clue to ratings, but an answer.
Daring to used a word to life to be a.
Lovely.
Yeah.
You know how Americans love that.
Ah.
So, um.
I said last night, when I came home, I said, you got to come on the show because that's the best way to talk about about the lawsuit.
So I can explain it because you weren't there.
Yeah.
You did a good job.
How do you know?
Well, because my family was watching TV.
Oh, the news reports.
You had a couple of quotes there.
Yeah.
So, you want to get into it now?
Yes?
Or should we, um.
How far do we get into it?
Oh, baby.
How far do you want to go?
No.
I think that's probably best.
Yeah.
It's not necessary to throw it mod.
Throw it mod.
Translation.
Very nice.
Wait.
But first, first, you know, he doesn't call often, but when he does, I have to put him on the show.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Oh.
Come on.
You ready, young?
Here's another message from the Rages of the Rages of the Rages of the Rages of the Rages.
Hello, I'm Roger here.
I just think catching up on your tele messages.
And I thought I'd like to mention, I don't actually drive a car or a mini.
I used to drive a box so now, there.
But I had a nice next step and now I'm found.
So I have to work everywhere.
and also take the bus, but that's even very expensive these days.
I'm not quite sure who's been hanging around outside your house, but it's not me.
I think you've got to be very careful because there's lots of sensory people out there
and there's only so many covers in the phone book.
You never know who you've got out there, it's probably that comic shit blogger
because he seems a bit involved in writing all those nasty things about you.
He traces all those pictures of you on his website
and I don't think that's very normal behaviour.
But the great careful with Jacket or where his name is
is looking at his blog, he seems very obsessed with you.
He knows this kind of person he drives and many as well.
Anyway, everything goes well with those nasty magazines
and it's some consolation.
I have my picture in the local newspaper a while ago
and my solicitor made the mission a form of a policy.
But please I do the same for you too.
Although they'll probably say sorry in the small print at the back.
Anyway, I'm a phone now, can have been out for the evening.
So, made the wincey with you.
Roger, are you stirring the shit up here?
Yeah.
What was that knife of Paul McCartney to do that jingle?
I was just thinking.
Yeah.
Mac and me, you know, like this.
That's the Jeff Smith.
We did that.
Okay.
My blog Barry's going.
Excuse me.
Hold on.
Let me just see.
Talk amongst yourselves.
Oh.
Okay.
When I hear that guy on the phone,
I have to think about Betty.
Remember?
Yeah.
Hold on a second.
There we go.
Okay.
Here we go.
So, the lawsuit.
Yeah.
Let's just set the stage real quickly.
Everyone knows we're talking about.
Yeah.
A Dutch magazine took pictures off of this two parts to this.
Took pictures off of my flicker, strut, my flicker sight, which by the way.
Let's just say one thing.
Yeah.
In the Netherlands, the word flicker has 99% of the population.
When they hear the word flicker, they think, homosexual.
Yeah.
Because the word, you know, the derogatory term, as we would say, Fag, is flicker.
So, even though you spell it differently.
But an English flickering flicker.
Yeah.
Well, the spelling is F-L-I-C-K-R, which is, of course, very web 2-O hit trendy.
But so, it's kind of funny.
You know, all these people talking about flicker this and flicker that.
Yeah.
There were some snickers in the courtroom, by the way.
And by the way.
Yes.
That magazine is not just a nice magazine.
It's just a gossip magazine.
It's a flicker magazine.
So, did you know that?
You know, it's not even okay or hello or in style, for example.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's a really, it's, you know, it's a rag is what it is.
Okay.
Supermarket.
Right.
Now, let's just preface this by saying that you and I have been together for 20 years.
We've been very, very well-known in the Netherlands all that time.
That is not stopped.
So much to our measurement, by the way.
We lived in the United States for 14 years, and we came back and we were still well-known.
Well, escaped it also the first time, because when we got together and we went out together,
that was a big thing.
Because no, because you were a scorned woman, because you had an affair with me.
You had an affair with me?
Divorced.
Yes.
Not even when I found you.
It's horrible, horrible, horrible, but bad, bad, bad, bad, bad.
And you were younger 15 years younger.
So, that was a big thing.
We had the paparazzi sitting in the garbage cans.
Yeah.
It was kind of like a dame more ashton-coached cushioner.
I just had a visual for a second there.
I was doing dame.
How would you like, do you like ashton?
No.
I don't see it.
No, no.
No.
We were.
Okay.
Anyway, they took pictures off of my flicker side.
And here's what they did.
They followed Patricia around and Christina apparently.
Yeah.
And they took a picture of you.
And you know, I'm sure they took many, many pictures of you.
You were shopping at Saintsbury.
Didn't know anything.
Right.
So, it doesn't matter.
Even if you had the most beautiful clothes on, we're completely ready for a photo shoot.
There's always a shitty picture.
So, they're looking for a shit.
That's a new thing.
They're looking for the shittiest photo that they have.
So, they can say, look.
She looks like shit.
And you didn't even look that shitty.
Hey.
Don't break the studio.
Yeah.
That's shitty.
I thought it.
I did.
No, it wasn't that bad.
You know, when you normally actually a normal person who does.
Looks like that.
No.
No, look.
Look like you and you look shitty.
Who carries the grocery bags in her car.
And you were looking down.
Pools faces.
Yeah.
You pulled us a face.
Put that on.
Okay.
So, that face, you know, was.
That's the poop face.
On the cover.
That's it.
That's when you're trying to pinch one off.
Yeah.
Okay.
And that face was on the cover of the magazine.
Yes.
Correct.
And it was full page.
And the gist of them of the article was, you know, they say that everything is all
Hunky Dory, but it's really all crappy.
No.
Look at Patricia's face for Christ's sake.
I'm happy.
It must be poopy.
Very unhappy.
And so, to prove this contrast inside, they took these pictures of our trip to America.
Yes.
Well, we were in New York and San Francisco.
When we were sick actually, and I took a picture of the three of us in Central Park.
You had the flu.
Yeah.
Boy, that's bad.
Well, remember that.
Bad hair day.
Yeah.
And, and quite honestly, of course, these are great pictures.
You know, that's why I published them on the on my family.
I put a muffler.
And on the knees.
Did you just broke?
No.
On this show.
You know what happened.
What do you have to say?
Did that burn?
Yeah.
What do you have to say?
Excuse me.
Well, senseo.
Oh, senseo.
Thanks for listening.
Oh.
For the past year and a half.
But I'm not a coffee drink.
No.
Okay.
But from now on, whenever you hear a book,
the day I've been didn't go down very well.
But anyway, and underneath these lovely holiday pictures,
I said, yeah, look, they're playing like it's nice, but it's not good.
No.
It's horrible.
And they're sitting in a limo.
No.
He can afford a limo.
Okay.
But that doesn't matter because in 20 years that we've been together,
we've never sued a magazine ever.
Never sued a gossip magazine for anything.
Never.
Because we think, you know, you are out there.
We did our things.
We did our appearances.
We were famous.
That's what we were working for.
And sometimes these sort of things.
You know, that's the other side.
Yeah.
I mean.
So.
That's the way it works.
That's the game.
That.
Silicier.
Hmm.
Okay.
So that isn't the game.
No.
No problem.
And they've said some shitty things about us.
And they've told lots of untruths and lies.
Of course.
But these are gossip magazine.
And on the other side, we use them to sell things.
You know.
Absolutely.
It works both ways.
Yeah.
We know how to play the game.
Let's be honest.
However, there are rules to the game.
Yes.
I think so too.
One of the rules is people can stand outside your house and take as many pictures of
they want as they want.
But they cannot take pictures of you while you're in your house.
If you're in your house, they can't take it.
Well, they can take it.
But they can't publish a picture that has been taken through the window.
Yeah.
Now, if you're in your back garden.
Or if you're on your balcony.
It's, you know, there's jurisprudence that says they can publish that.
So, so really your final privacy is easy.
Even if you're in your bare butt, they can take the picture.
Yeah.
So that is preferred, of course.
Yes.
Of course.
Now, just in normal publishing terms, well, before I get to that, they also followed
our daughter Christina.
Yeah.
And we know that because written in the text of this article was the name of her school
and how she is transported there every single day.
How do they know that?
Of course.
How do they know?
Because they've been watching these editors or one of these editors ordered some
guys.
Some greasy ass guy in a trench coat is the way I envision him with a fucking lens to follow
my daughter.
Yeah.
I don't care who's following my daughter.
She's 15.
That's not okay.
No.
That is just not okay.
So, that is endangerment of a child.
Unless we say, can you follow my daughter?
Yeah.
Well, there's some guys that, that's not a story.
There's some guys that I told not to follow my daughter in case some other
motherfuckers shows up.
So, no worries.
Yeah.
It's all good.
Now, so that of course is subject to how you want to interpret the words, what is danger,
you know, there's all kinds of things that can be taken into consideration, but any parent
will agree.
That's not okay.
If you, if you, if you are a parent, you know that's that doesn't feel good at all.
And it's just wrong.
It's wrong.
Okay.
Follow me.
Do the same as Barry.
Doesn't matter.
Yeah.
Take my ugly face and put it on the cover.
It wasn't ugly, huh?
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter, but don't do that to my daughter.
Right.
Now, they took these pictures from my flicker feed and every single picture that I have
up there, public, is marked as creative comments, share a like, non-commercial attribution.
Yeah.
So, the, the important part here is the non-commercial part of the license.
Now, this whole creative comment is not a small thing.
You know, this is set up by Lawrence Lessig of Stanford University.
It's, it's adopted globally.
People rely on this for protection for their intellectual property.
Yeah.
And the, the, the, the, the magazine and the editors, they basically had to come into court and explain
what, you know, why they felt justified to take those pictures and publish it.
Exactly.
Because they can't read English.
Because it's clearly, well, the part of that was the part of their defense.
Yeah.
He set the stage for a second.
Okay.
So, I have taxi Eric who's all dressed up.
He, you know, of course he takes care of all the logistics for us in Holland.
So, he's dressed up and looks like a secret agent.
Totally James Bond.
Yeah.
Exactly.
You know, he's overcoat, little oversized, overcoat, you know, he's kind of walking.
Yeah.
He looks, he looks perfect for the posse.
Gold rings.
Yeah.
And what's that?
What?
He has the walk.
Yeah.
Exactly.
So, we have our lead attorney, Christ from Popula Stain, Abibushnach.
Christ is, he's a, he's a pretty scary guy.
Yeah.
He's like partially bald.
And he always has like, that shitty ring on his face.
Yeah.
You know, you just want to have him on your son.
Don't fuck with me face.
Yeah.
And then we had young villain who was an associate who actually, you know, wrote a lot of the stuff.
So you had two.
Yeah.
And young villain was my size and, you know, kind of a big, like, all off-looking guy.
You know, so it's all right.
I think we had a pretty good posse.
Yeah.
Now, what was interesting is the news organizations that will news.
I mean, the, kind of like the entertainment tonight news organizations.
They had requested to film to record video during the, during the session during the, during the suit.
Two programs.
Yeah.
Exactly.
And so they asked me to, do you mind?
I don't care.
I mean, that's fine.
Yeah.
And stuff like that.
Can be very helpful for other people.
So when we get there, the camera crews were there.
But it turns out that the magazine and the publisher refused.
They didn't want any cameras in the court.
I mean, a gossip magazine, you all, I mean, this, I was blown away by that.
Oh, they were shy.
Yeah.
All of a sudden they were shy.
You know, what's, you know, what's a real bummer?
Yeah.
I'm just thinking you're car right now, listening to this on serious satellite stars 103.
And you're not going to hear the ending of it because the satellite window closes and, if it's, if it goes to Hellway, it comes up next.
So, so, well, but when they get home, when they get to the office, go to dailysourceco.com, download the show.
And you can hear the rest of it.
Yeah.
Oh, you know, that podcast, and you should look into it.
It's pretty cool.
Okay.
So they're gone now.
Where was I?
Oh, yeah.
The judge, then, before, before we started, the judge called in the, my two lawyers and their one lawyer.
It was as geeky looking.
If you put two, two bolts here in his neck, he was totally frank and stunned.
Yeah.
Yeah, but it's like a lurchy guy.
Sometimes it doesn't matter.
You know that.
Yeah.
But it may be feel good at the time.
I know.
Okay.
Of course, it doesn't matter.
It makes no difference at all.
But as it turns out, anyway.
I had geeky guy a couple of times in the courtroom and defending me.
And I lost.
Yeah.
No, exactly.
And I was telling these guys.
I'm like, hey.
It's true, but you never know.
I was telling, I'm saying, okay, guys, listen.
Let's do this right.
You know, let's just sit there.
This is always so dry.
These Dutch court cases.
Yeah.
You know, you watch TV.
You watch Boston legal.
You're like, you know, besides the fact that the office is filled with groovy, you know,
by sexual chicks.
Yeah.
You know, there's all this like.
There's professional suits on.
Right.
Yeah.
Exactly.
So I said, listen, guys, I want some Danny Crane.
Danny Crane.
Yeah.
And in a couple of times during the, during the case, I went, I.
Danny Crane.
Yeah.
So, and, and, but, help, they really hit.
It made a difference.
But they, they knew that you meant be cool.
Yeah.
And it's psychological.
And they were very cool.
And these guys are pros.
They're really good.
I've done this a couple of times before.
You know, it's very good because we have American listens.
And listeners, and they have no idea how it works in how it works.
Oh, let me, yeah.
Let me just say.
And I've mentioned this before.
But there is no jury system in the Netherlands, not for criminal or civil court.
It's just a professional judge system.
One judge.
Yeah.
So the judge is going to listen.
It reads the documents, listens to the arguments, and then makes a decision.
That's, that's how it goes.
And he's stomach hurts.
And he has a fight at home.
He's in a bad mood.
Well, no.
You're fine.
Let me just say one thing.
I do believe that the professional judges who are in the system really believe in the system,
and really work it.
I mean, I just don't believe in the system.
That's nothing against judges.
I don't think they use their gut feeling.
Yeah, but they're not supposed to.
No, that's why the line.
So you always get something different.
They're not well.
And then the Netherlands, of course, is always.
Why don't we just come to a compromise.
There's always a compromise.
It's never a clear cut winner in it.
I think it's too much about the rules or the rules.
Yeah, but they look at it exactly.
Well, we can argue this for a hundred, a hundred years.
But I mean, the way the system, I don't like the system.
I think it's a bad system, but I do think they try their best to make the system work.
So let me just, let's just say that.
That's true.
Okay.
And this judge, a woman.
She's known for intellectual copyright about intellectual property cases.
Yeah, she's probably somewhere between my age and your age.
I guess.
I think somewhere on that.
Maybe younger.
No, I think she was older than I was.
But somewhere in between.
Laskar.
Yeah, but, you know, I like the, oh, so she overruled the.
The request by the magazine to have no cameras in the court room.
She overruled it.
And talk like, oh, that's kind of cool.
And you know, I hadn't met her yet.
I thought that was a very interesting.
Of course.
So these schmucks, they record everything.
And you know, what do they use like, you know, us walking into the courtroom?
It's like Christal mighty idiots.
Yeah.
Okay.
So I showed up, of course, representing us with with our attorneys.
And this guy, Mark Funderlinda, who was the, who's the editor, who shares this co-editor
ship with this other girl, Peter of Boats.
He wrote the whole piece.
Oh, I don't even know who wrote it because there was no buy line there.
Yeah, but then I know that it was him.
Well, usually it's him.
So he didn't show up because he apparently had a fall in luck.
And left where he was slipped.
He was, you know, following celebrities around.
He was leeching and left.
Yeah.
He was following them around and then he slipped.
Yes.
And he slipped and he couldn't make it.
Okay.
So the better boats can.
And you know what?
She should really change her hair color because she's giving the whole dumb blonde thing
like too much.
Yeah, credit.
Too much credit.
I mean, I'm sorry.
You know, it's just, she just doesn't seem very bright.
She didn't say anything throughout the entire court case.
Throughout the entire case.
Not one word.
No.
You know, and I was talking on doing all kinds of stuff.
You know, you know me.
Oh, let's just say the best news of the entire day.
No Donald Trump hair.
Ah.
The hair.
I actually got the hair pretty good now.
Lucky luck.
Look.
You saw the hair.
Look pretty good.
That's the hair that I always say.
Right.
And Donald Trump hair.
Right, but I didn't have that did I do.
No.
You did your best.
Okay.
Because what I said was a jury.
He said fine, how was your hair?
She didn't ask about my hair first.
And it's not because he needs good hair,
no, because he makes he just cannot do his hair.
But if I have the hair, then I have the confidence.
It's my main. It's my armor.
If I let you do your hair, then you look like a sort of blonde,
Elvis Presley.
Yeah, you just put a little bit of water in it.
No, throw it back.
Stop about the hair, okay? Enough about the hair.
That would, people know that you don't care about your hair.
It's nice to know.
No, I do care about my hair because I want it to look right
because that gives me confidence.
Of course, of course.
Okay, so I care.
Yeah.
On top of that, instead of my regular blue contact lenses,
because I thought it would be stunningly beautiful.
It turns out that the guide gave us the wrong ones
and had green contact lenses.
Yeah, what was that?
Which made my eyes look like two black holes.
Yeah, very dark.
But I didn't want my glasses on because of it.
No, I know.
Because I think this stuff is important, you know?
Yes.
But again, whether you're appealing to a jury or a judge,
I mean, I know.
I'm taking this shit really, really serious.
That's what I wanted to say.
Everything needs to be out.
That was the statement.
Yes.
So then we read our whole thing, right?
And here's what I liked about the judge,
because the lawyers get up and then first the plaintiffs,
you know, we had this brief of like 46 or 47 different points,
which is, you know, what we claim,
what the law is, jurisprudence,
what the conclusion is.
And so, you know, our guy actually reads that.
He reads it from the paper.
Well, I'm going like, denny crane.
But the judge, the judge, even though she's given a copy,
she didn't read it.
She actually put her glasses on top of her head and just listened.
And as she listened, she was looking around
at different people's reactions during different pieces.
Very, very smart, very smart.
And so then they go woman.
Yeah, oh yeah.
Very good.
So then the other guys get to do it.
And oh my God.
I brought it home with you.
It's just so funny.
Yeah.
So let's just on the pictures for a second,
because that's where the real legal stuff happens.
They claim that when you move your mouse over a picture on flicker.
Yeah.
They claim that something pops up a message that says,
this photo is public.
Now, that's true.
It's public.
That means it's public too.
You can look at it.
And underneath it actually says under certain restrictions.
And it has a concrete created creative comments logo.
The seas with a copyright is very internationally acknowledged stuff.
I know.
But they know that, of course.
I mean, let's not kid each other because they're professional.
Right.
But well, this is what the judge said because they had printouts and screen grabs.
And they're just proving that it's confusing.
And that and they had no idea of your happiness.
And you should go boost.
All that stuff.
Yeah.
It's an important thing for them on their list.
Little list was all disgusting things.
They're asking for it.
Hold on.
No.
Stop.
You're telling the story the wrong way.
Oh, is that so?
Yeah.
But that comes later.
I'm way ahead.
Yes.
Stick with the program.
Hold on to my co-tails, baby.
So they had all these different explanations for why they didn't see it.
They also said, hey, look, it's available.
All these pictures are available in multiple resolutions, including very high quality, which is
plainly, definitely intended for magazines.
That's what you said.
And flicker is only full of promotional pictures.
And it's just fun.
And it's just mucking about.
Mucking about.
And.
And so, you know, so then we kind of go back and forth.
And I say, you know, you're on her.
And I was I had all the right word.
You have to say eight left butter for our own and all that stuff.
You know, I really tried to respect her position.
So I really was very.
I thought it was quite polite and correct.
I said, you know, I don't take this.
I don't see this as fun and games at all.
I mean, this is really serious stuff.
This is a part of our company.
Our company, our media company, the personal Adam Curry Patricia Pi, media company, which
is registered as such.
Yeah.
You know, spans across web logs, online stores, which you've had.
Pictures, podcasts, video podcasts.
It's a part of the new media.
Yeah.
And we need to respect the same intellectual property rules.
In the new media as as the old media respects from us.
You know, this is this is this is critical stuff.
And you can't just go taking it.
It's stealing.
And so this this debate kind of went back and forth.
And I got into it and I said, look, you know,
first of all, any editor who respects himself after making this huge intellectual
property violation knowingly should resign.
So I'm not only want any money from this, just make the guy resign.
We have to send a message.
We have to send a message that there is a line in the sand.
And the the genesis of this is that when I when my lawyer first sent the letter to them,
hey, you violated our copyright by publishing our pictures.
They said, oh, well, here's 1500 euros, which is like three times
the going rate and you should just shut up and be happy with it.
We offer them money, which is a very common occurrence, by the way.
But it's it's not right.
You can't steal something knowing that I'll just pay them off later.
I mean, you're still stealing.
Then it's done.
Yeah, you're still stealing.
And of course photographers who just take pictures and sell them for living,
you know, they'll take that.
I mean, they're part of the problem because I'll take that three times the amount.
You know, go ahead, steal my pictures all you want.
I didn't offer them to take care.
No, of course not, of course not.
So, you know, that was kind of their their whole defense saying, well, it was hard to
hard to figure out what what the license was, you know, and pictures are they
actually literally said, once a picture, once something is put on the internet,
it has no value.
It has no value.
And I said, well, that's really interesting.
Say, my podcast does pretty damn well.
Thank you very much.
And I gave it away.
Yeah.
And I let people copy it.
And I said, but you can just download this stuff.
It's available for download for everyone.
I said, yeah, absolutely.
You can download my pictures all you want.
There are rules.
But you can't publish them.
Now.
Downloading is not the same as publishing.
So, I started to use some pretty big words like theft and, you know,
violations of intellectual property.
And the judge said, well, Mr. Curry, say, you're using some pretty big words here
for, you know, the crime that has been committed, the taking of a picture.
She said, you know, what exactly would the damages be?
If she's trying to get a numb, because she knows that she's going to decide that they,
I think, that they violated the rules.
The thing here is, what is the value of those pictures?
You know, and so there are two ways I could have gone.
I could have gone and said, well, you know, we've sold pictures in the past,
which I don't think we've ever done.
Oh, one Christina was born.
We sold, actually we didn't sell pictures.
We had pictures made.
And then they wrote a check in Christina's name.
But I mean, you could come up with ways to measure it, but I'm not interested in that.
So I wouldn't answer the question I said.
But I was expecting, I was expecting it.
Yeah.
And here's what I said.
I said, these are the exact same terms.
Theavory, huge loss of income that are used by the RIA, the MPA, the, I used the Dutch,
Bhuma Stamina, ASCAP BMI, said the business software alliance.
And she was nodding her head because, you know, she's done these cases and I said,
Yeah.
So you're telling me that a song that you buy for 99 cents,
when someone copies that illegally and put and shares it with someone else,
why all of a sudden can they get a $150,000 lawsuit?
And I can't.
No.
Yeah.
And that was the tipping point.
And I saw her brain go, oh, click.
Yeah.
Hold on a second.
So I'm just here as the guy who was only hearing about,
we can't rip off the big companies because they're going to take, you know,
they're going to take you down and then you get, you know, look,
the housewives, you know, moms who don't even use the computers,
kids have shared some file and they get, you know,
the $150,000 lawsuit, but they can settle it for 15,000,
and not go to court.
And it's fucking crazy.
Yes.
And she got it.
So what I basically said is all I'm asking for is a signal.
And the signal has to be very clear that it has to stop the idea of
grabbing it and taking it and using it and then paying someone off.
It stops with me.
And if you, if you're going to, you know,
find them 5,000 euros, they're just going to go do it again.
And I'll be back here next year.
And the year after that, and someone else is going to be here.
Yeah.
And it's a stupid waste of time.
It's stupid.
And it's wrong.
It's like getting on the train and not buying a ticket because, you know,
if I get caught all I have to do is pay the ticket.
But the whole thing was that they think they can do that to us,
because no, I'm just in a second.
So those are the facts.
Yeah, I know.
Okay.
But they think that we want that.
Yes.
Okay.
So a part of their, a part of their whole defense and argument there,
was that throughout the years, we have always sought publicity.
And that all we are about is about publicity and making money.
That's what I said.
Yeah.
Which, of course, is true, but not in this context.
But come on.
We always did it in a very professional way.
Of course, we're professional.
Professional.
Of course.
And if we do something to start a new magazine or, you know, something that
people want from us and we say, hey, you're going to earn a lot of money from this,
let's talk.
Yeah, because we make money with our brand, with our, with our face, with our talent, with our voice, you know, whatever.
We have something to sell.
And we're not supposed to have any business sense.
I guess that's very foreign to the people like this.
I don't think that we can have any business sense.
Wow.
So.
I think we did pretty well.
Yeah, on the, on the picture stuff, definitely.
I mean, if I were, if I were to, I'm just thinking, because these, again,
the judge may be going for some kind of compromise.
I mean, what would be great is if, is if they came up with,
if the judge came up with some kind, I mean, something to send to signal.
If it's money or whatever it is, but something that really hurts, you know,
something that makes a difference to that company.
They have to do something.
And I'm not looking for money for us.
I'm just looking for a, you know, that's why I said, just fire this guy.
Fire the editor and then the next editor will think twice about doing that shit.
Is that simple? How hard somebody is to start with this?
Yeah.
About the Christina stuff.
I don't know.
They, I think they'll get a, a reprimand.
I don't think they'll get anything else.
I don't think they'll, I don't think they'll be any other.
Any other sanctions there, anything, anything happening.
Okay. But, you know, that's our feeling.
And it is a scary feeling.
Oh, yeah. No, totally. Totally.
But, you know, what they said there is that, well, you've continuously put her in the limelight.
And so, therefore, he's fair game.
All right.
Well, she belongs to us. You know, she walks next to us.
Yeah.
It's, uh, it's crazy. But then then.
And it's not going to stop us from doing nice things that we want to do.
You know, that we like.
But this guy blew it this, uh, this Mark guy. He blew it.
Uh, when we were talking last night.
Finally, what, what his name is, is, uh, he hates us.
And I don't know why.
You, you don't even know him.
No.
Did you ever talk to him?
Uh, once.
I met him, uh, when I came home, I remember I came home from work.
One day, and you were being interviewed by him.
And this is 20, you know, there's eight, 17 years ago.
Was that him?
In New Jersey.
We just lived in New Jersey.
Yeah.
And 1718 years ago.
I think Christina was, uh, just about four years old, three or four years old.
Oh.
And, uh, well, then he called me only 11 years ago.
And he said, we're going to start a new magazine.
Uh, or a new, we'll give it the new phase to avant garde.
Was it?
And do you want to do it?
I have a feeling we're going to get to the bottom of why he hates us with this story.
No, no, not at all.
No, not at all.
That's where I say, and I know him just a little bit.
Okay.
And, and said, who are you?
Because we lived in America.
I didn't know him.
And he said, well, I'm actually a very good.
I'm a real journalist.
And I write books.
I said, oh, how interesting.
And what kind of book do you write?
He says about the royal family.
And I thought, well, that's nice.
That's right.
He's a royalty expert.
Yes.
And of course, it's why he follows us around.
I just have a new book out of about, uh,
Beatrix, Queen B.
Queen B.
And I said, well, that's nice.
Sound for him.
And he sounded very nice.
And I invited him.
And I said, well, let's sit down.
I have a nice, uh, uh, uh, interview.
And we did.
And I was a bit disappointed about it.
Because all the things that we agreed on, uh, he didn't do.
You know, I always ask, uh, can I read it?
And if there's anything that's a little bit cold,
it's a little bit wrong or not my way of saying it.
Can I change it?
Sure.
Never sent it, right?
Well, he sent it.
And I.
You changed it.
I remember that very clearly.
Yeah.
And they never changed.
You remember what it was.
And then it came out.
I don't know.
Well, the way a Christina was actually, uh, conceived.
He said, in such a horrible way.
And then I'm the cover.
Wait a minute.
What did I do?
Well, what did I do?
How?
I said he's with Christmas.
And he made a horrible sort of terrible line.
You know, remember that?
And that line was on the cover.
Uh, just above Christina's head.
Who was having, like, shag on Christmas.
Created this.
Something like that was really, really.
You don't say that, especially above.
Well, there you go.
He doesn't understand what you ever know.
No.
He has no, if it's about Christina, he has no feeling.
He has no idea about family life.
Oh, my God.
About family fail use.
And that's how I know him.
Right.
And so you're pointing at me is freaking me out.
And I called in and I said, why is that on the cover?
And why did you pick that line and put that above my, my daughter's head?
And, and he said, well, that's that, that is not my job.
I didn't do that.
It's got nothing to do with me.
Oh, what an ass.
And he was very nasty.
And I started to cry.
I was so disappointed.
I don't remember that.
I felt, I was in.
Did you tell me that?
If you told me that, I would have kicked his fucking ass.
You didn't tell me that.
I was in the studio with, uh, ho for the rose.
He still knows that.
Did you tell me that?
Well, and I cried because I felt so.
You humiliated.
Yeah.
And I felt stupid that I fell for it.
And, uh, so maybe he's just a mean nasty guy.
No.
So, um, that was the last thing I spoken to these years and years.
It is about, uh, maybe 17 years.
Yeah.
What'd you said?
18 years ago.
So Christina wasn't born.
That's not possible.
She's only 15.
So I couldn't have been that long.
I think it must have been 12 years ago.
12 years ago.
Okay, that's it.
Let's just play a song and then we'll get back to us.
Let's just regroup for a song.
And I never talked to him again.
That was it.
Should we wrap this up?
Play a song and then we'll wrap it all up?
Yeah.
Or do you want to, or do you want to continue?
Depends on?
What do you guys listening want?
What?
I'm asking the listeners what they want.
Oh, what they want.
They're like, don't play another fucking shitty song from your
Dampod Podsate music network.
Yeah.
What?
But you'd like this one, huh?
Have you asked Rock Chick?
She'll like it.
Hey, hey sister.
Laura Clap.
Hey, the moment that I knew
I'm over half the screen
Just sent a bad decision
I'm home.
Quick to anticipate
Which body punch do you need
It's while she puts her fake eyelashes on
Every morning say,
Reaction
Have soon, I'm sad,
It's fashion.
Hey, hey sister,
You can let your head down
You ain't done nothing bad
And nothing up to feel so guilty
You're just the partner
Of the world and the rush
This crazy life will be the end
It's all a part of the way
Up.
She's under self attack
Can't do this, can't do that
Or she might lose her precious hands
Watch your figure, watch your weight
Clean out that empty blade
Throw you know that ain't no way to live
Time for social intervention
Listen girl, pay close attention
Hey, hey sister,
You can let your head down
You ain't done nothing bad
And nothing up to feel so guilty
You're just the partner
Of the world and the rush
This crazy life will be the end
It's all a part of the way
Up.
She's under self attack
You ain't done nothing bad
And nothing up to feel so guilty
You're just the partner
Of the world and the rush
This crazy life will be the end
It's all a part of the way
Up.
She's under self attack
You're just the partner
Of the world and the rush
This crazy life will be the end
It's all a part of the way
Up.
She's under self attack
You're just the partner
Of the world and the rush
This crazy life will be the end
It's all a part of the way
Up.
Crazy life will be the end
It's all a part of the way
Up.
She's under self attack
To get kept in the trap
Up.
With up.
That's like the sheets in your ass.
Oh my god.
You know, this would, I'm so sorry.
This would be very good song for Charlotte Church.
Right.
Oh, right on.
Yeah, but she pulls it off, man.
I mean, she sings it well, but.
But screw it.
Charlotte Church has nothing on this.
No, but she could.
No, no.
Look, she's cute.
Look.
I know.
But if she wants to sell the song.
I like her.
She looks badass.
Charlotte is chunky.
I know.
I don't care.
So what do you think Laura should give the song to the chunker?
Look at her, man.
She's great.
That's all I say.
That's old school.
We are pod safe here.
And we support the artists.
Yes.
And their careers.
We don't need no stink and mainstream.
Charlotte, chunky church.
But she's not the England issue.
That's what I'm saying.
I'm bringing Laura Clapper.
If she wants to sell, you know, if I put Laura Clapper on Jonathan Ross,
Man, immediate overnight.
Nobody knows her.
So you wouldn't have to.
I mean, to get on the show.
Yes.
To get on the show.
Okay.
But I got contacts.
I'm connected, baby.
You're talking about it.
Okay.
But she's great.
True.
Wonderful.
And what a song.
Let me just see if she wrote it on the show.
I think she did.
Let me say music.
If she wrote it herself.
Whoa.
Oh.
Hey.
Sister.
Shapo.
I guess.
What is simply?
No.
It doesn't say.
Well, I mean, I don't have liner notes or anything here.
Okay.
She's got.
Oh, man.
Okay.
Anyway.
Very cool.
You can find that the pot saved music network.
I heard it on the pot show.
Music rewind actually.
That's where it's heard the song.
It's a great place to pick up music.
So to end the whole thing.
Yes.
To wind it all up.
Somehow we pissed this guy off.
Yeah.
This guy.
I don't know.
I'm going to have to make him cry.
Yeah.
I have to make him cry.
That was so disappointed.
So I can cry.
So stupid to fall for it.
But anyway, after that,
I actually never talk to him again.
Because that's what I do.
If I'm disappointed.
Oh, well.
He's just trying to get your attention.
No, no, no, no, no.
He doesn't.
You know that.
You know there's a whole different side on this whole story.
And he just hates us.
And he uses his magazine.
You know, to get back to us.
Or into irritators.
That's all.
Right.
And which is fine.
Because we've got podcasts.
We've got all kinds of ways to do that.
By the way, I don't spend a lot of time doing.
Because we have other fish to fry.
But that's fine.
You can do whatever you want.
But he can't break the law.
And you know.
And let me just tell you, wouldn't it be funny if the judge says,
Well, it was confusing.
I mean, this is a Yahoo company.
I mean, this would be big fucking news
if the creative comments doesn't stick.
I have to get that.
Well, she can be legendary.
She can be legendary by saying, you know what?
This shit has to stop and it's important that we send out a message.
And we, and we listen, we do it.
We do it.
If we're Warner Brothers records.
If we're, we're universal pictures.
We do it.
If we're Microsoft.
Yeah.
But what if those guys do it to us?
Then all of a sudden they can, they can get away with it for just a pay off.
No, no, no, no, no.
This, this is a legendary case.
Legendary.
If she does it, this could set big, big jurisprudence.
And Europe, at least.
Now it would be really important.
Seriously.
Let's make a picket line outside the point.
Okay.
Why don't you go start hammering the signs.
You start drawing them and I'll hammer up the wood.
Hey, baby.
Thanks for coming on the show.
I love it so much when you're on the show.
Thank you.
Yes, today.
You did a good job.
Oh, well, it's my pleasure.
That's my pleasure.
Because it's big too much.
Fuck it.
That's not for, that's his man's job.
Men gotta go out.
It's like, you know.
It's not good for my heart.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Not good at all.
No, I mean, it's a pain in the ass, but I do with a great pleasure.
Because I gotta defend you guys somewhere.
And I have to defend.
I have to defend intellectual property across the vast internet.
Well, everybody.
God bless the internet.
And the freedom for which it represents.
It stands or something like that.
I gotta work on the speech.
Okay.
I love not.
I need a break now.
Yeah, no.
Okay.
Let's have a cup of tea.
I love you, baby.
I love you too.
Another pod show pod guest.
Stick it in your ear.