This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy.
Delta Sierra Charlie 401.
A $16 billion worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Where is your boy tonight?
I hope he is a gentleman.
Maybe he won't find out what I know.
You were the last good thing about this part of town.
When I wake up, I really need to take my chance.
Who about the game, if you hate him more than you know.
Is I love this for you?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I should be there.
This morning I can stay for him.
Where is your boy tonight?
I hope he is a gentleman.
Maybe he won't find out what I know.
You were the last good thing about this part of town.
Why are you upstairs?
It's
That's my sin, and that's what I did, I can't drink for him
That's what I do, I can't drink for him
When we're so bored and I know it's a gentleman
And maybe we'll find out, I know
You wouldn't ask to be the bad fish for the town
Where is your body?
I hope he is a gentleman
Maybe we'll find out, I know
You wouldn't ask to be the bad fish for the town
Where is your body?
I hope he is a gentleman
Maybe we'll find out, I know
Oh, you wouldn't ask to be the bad fish for the town
Grab that bottom, where is your body?
From the pod safe music network
And this is yet another one of those nexus that we've talked about
Followed boy, man, I think they have a record deal
Don't they? They've been around for ages
Now their music is playable on podcasts
I think this is really big
Another band that I'd heard of before
Panic at the disco, also uploaded yesterday to the pod safe music network
This is great
This is really cool, kudos to
I think Michael Butler persuaded them coerced
I don't know, Michael, how hard was it?
Or was it easy?
I just want to step back and say that
It's not that I'm impressed that we have
Big names coming into the pod safe music network
What I'm impressed with is these are people who are already
Definitely at a plateau, worldwide even
And they're seeing the advantage of getting your music played on podcasts
That's what's very, very exciting to me
Hey everybody, how you doing coming to you from the curry cottage is the daily source code
I want to be happy but I can't really be happy
Because the morning only about an hour and a half ago
We went to check out Patricia's palace
Her project
This is the house that we saw that if we could do the work that we wanted to do to it
Then it would be not only livable Patricia would turn it into a beautiful palace
Now it is a listed home, grade two listed
Which means the council has put it on a list of important buildings
So there were a lot of changes and really one of the most important ones for me
Was raising all door frames by six inches
So I could actually actually walk through the house
And so we met the lady from the council there
And we had a list of maybe seven or eight items
None of the minor I have to admit
But right off the bat at the door
Non-starter
Honor you there
Honor
No, yes not
Huh?
I'm trying to find hunt in case you had noticed
Yeah, so non-starter and it was interesting because the reason she gave this council
A woman from the, I don't know the council
The man it was a woman
Is that it would ruin the ratio of the doors versus the panels
And I said you're not talking about the golden ratio R she said yes exactly
I put in mouth of course
So you understand the importance of the ratio of the doorways versus the panels
And it just went downhill from there
Even the banister we went a lot to do anything to raise it to change it whatever
Patricia and I had pretty much agreed with each other
Even if one thing was off the list and quite honestly
I was prepared to accept the doorways
That's a really tough one in the UK to find doorways that are tall enough for
For me to walk through
I was prepared to accept that
Although I said the alternative was of course
It's you know she could just get a different husband
Yeah, I'm so thankful for the life and a hard podcast
And I just looked at the really social number 400
And discovered when you played the England song
Wait a minute
We don't have any conversations
There are very many podcasts
Patriotic students for the sport that's alive
We need to have some more podcasts with which I use
You know you can't play R or C in the USA because that's all right
I don't know why
So we need to have more music that we can play on the podcast
Do the footage of life
It'd be really nice if you could help that
Yeah, that's a good point
Although I'm sure if you looked you'd find a lot of patriotic stuff in there
If you find anything let me know about it
Send me an email at Maccurrey.com
So I can check it out
Because fourth July is upon us
It's going to be a very special day
A very special fourth of July this year
For a lot of people that I know
So myself included and some I don't know
40 50 people who are very close to me
That's all I'm going to say about it
Hey Adam it's Jeff South and Nashville
Just calling I was just listening to your show from the 6th of June 6th
And I guess I'm one of those few people that actually enjoy it when life is not on the show
I've said to say
Don't give me wrong
She's beautiful
I love her voice she's gorgeous
But I prefer listening to you take out on stuff
Talk about second life
That's something you're into
Talk about the computers
All the fucking problems they have
Because that's going on
Don't let her get you down
Don't let her tell you what not to talk about
Magnetic crap
Anyway
Just a
A little advice I guess
Somebody can do a listening to all the GP crap
All right
Thanks
Alright dude thanks
Yeah I love it when I hear from listeners
It's always a little harder when someone's a podcast
Because they have a set way of the way
They think a podcast should be
Or how it should be constructed or whatever
I love it when just just plain old listeners
Who are actually the top of my list
Honestly
We got to voice mail phone lines for you to call into
If you're traveling in your car
You should just put it into your cell phone
You know just punch the number in now
You won't have to actually dial it
But just punch it in so you can program it into your address book
In Jersey
So it'll be plus one
6256357
And then we have a number in Europe in London
Specifically
O2O
So it'll be plus four four two o
Yeah man
Talking about you know
No, I just want to make it very clear
I have not migrated to the PC
See was this Ian Richards
Excuse me Ian Richards
Left a comment at curry.com
Now let's see what he said here
Oh this was about the window blind
Yeah about customizing it to look like OSX
Yeah
I must say another
minor
Advantage
Of at least
Not having a Mac power book
I can't speak to the new Mac books
But I had one of those aluminium ones
Or titanium or whatever the alloy is
And it was much harder to receive Wi-Fi signals
I noticed at the hotel that I stayed in last night
The night before in London
Of course apologies that we didn't have a show on Wednesday
But more about my day in a second
I noticed that
You can just pick up many more Wi-Fi signals
In fact I didn't have to use the cranky as
Expensive hotel Wi-Fi
I'd jacked into someone's net gear
Point that was just apparently near by work perfectly
I was able to download a whole bunch of podcasts
And chill out in the room
Of course
I don't know if you ever seen one of these
She reported Jay's very light
I mean 2.6 pounds
Now of course you have to carry an external CD drive
If you want to use it
But the sound that comes out of this machine
The actual speaker
It's like a
Like play school
It's really childishly stupidly
Tenny and tiny
It's like okay
The people who use this laptop
They'll be using it for everything except audio
So let's just throw a little thing there
Like a little transistor radio speaker
And there's really really poor
But there's still advantages
Right now
As I said earlier
I'm getting so much
Service off of the web
That I really don't need much more
Than a browser
And of course cast blasts
Which I was using already
Say Adam Curry
This is columnist
Who have been seen to your versions
About episode 10
I'm 16
From Essex
Just how to say that I love the show
And listen to it every morning
On why I take round
So keep up the good work
Thanks a lot
Bye
Yeah dude
Right now
So if you were listening since episode 10
Then you were listening when you were 14 or 15
Because it's almost been 2 years
Krike
Continuing story about night sweats
Which of course actually does believe in the
Belong and the what is it
It belongs in this category
Right so the Metro sexual moment for those of you who are new to the program
Is intended entirely for water cooler talk
That guys just never really get around
To because we're too embarrassed
Or I just want to be a bunch of guys
We don't want to be seen as two feminine
You know stuff like that
So night sweats has been an ongoing topic
Night sweats is something that I suffered from
So nearly
Until a listener actually came up with a wonderful idea
And said why don't you wear boxer shorts
And why she said we shouldn't sleep naked
Not much for pajamas
So I wear the white beaters and the boxer shorts
Night sweats have almost completely stopped
I mean sometimes I wake up and I'm on the verge of being damp
If you know what I mean
But in general it works
Now I got an email from Freddy Avalos
And he sent in and I'll definitely put this link in the show notes
A link to the bed fan
Which I'm sure it would help tremendously
It's essentially a fan that is designed to blow air up out of the top
It's very thin you put it right in front of the bed
And the presumably you switch it on
And then cold air just blows from your feet
All the way up through the blankets
I don't know so far so good with the
With the clothing
And I'm not even sure why that works
Maybe the combination would be even better
But I don't feel hot like I thought I would
You know temperature wise course
So we continue to keep our eye on night sweats
Tragedy of tens of thousands
Yeah
Yesterday spent the entire day in London
And wow what a first all beautiful weather
Could not ask for a more beautiful London day
And we have three guys in from San Francisco
We got moody mark and Chris
And they brought over codes and umbrella
And like man what's up with this
You know what I was going to rain
It's like dude that's I told you
It's a bad rap
He went has beautiful weather
Another fine example today
In fact it's going to get very hot soon
And as you know we're in the cottage
Which is a rental
And it has no air conditioning
So that means we'll be breaking out the
What is the name of that thing again?
Oh yeah
The con there
It's still in the corner from last summer
I figured I'd keep it nearby
Just in case I needed
So it was just a fantastic day
And we spent most of the day meeting with producers
Creative people, writers, technical people
A couple people who I'd already met
And I was
Not just myself but
Mark and Moody and well as well
And we were doing most of these meetings
Just astounded
Flabbergast
Literally by the amount of creative talent
That we saw
And I'm presuming that there's much much more of it
And I'm not sure what it is
Maybe first of all there's not a lot of
A lot of television channels
Really if you look at it
What people can receive here in the UK
Maybe really only six
You know big TV channels
Cable is not very prevalent
There's only I think 3 million cable subscribers
I believe I could be wrong
I think sky digital
There's 60 million people in the country
And I believe
Maybe only 8 or 9 million have
Have satellite television in the rest
Well
They get their BBC 1, 2 and 3
I think it's kind of it
I could be wrong
Correct me from wrong
So if you just do the math
And we know how many
What kind of great tools there are
On PCs
If it's an audio
It could be pro tools
Or audacity
If it's video
It could be Final Cut Pro
Or Premiere
Or Windows
And people have just been honing
The creative talent
But there hasn't really been an outlet
And so we're seeing this outpouring
And I saw pilots and demos
And ideas
And it's just completely blew me away
The level of quality
That is bubbling around
At least London where we were
I mean some people came from the north
By the way from as far as Manchester
Totally astounding
And then as we discussed this
We said wow you know
It's definitely
An example
We met two guys
I'm not going to say who any of these people
We're going to met with two guys
We met with two guys
Who came out from Bournemouth
They're in a college in school
University
Film school
And the ideas they had
And what they showed us
And what I've already seen
Of them
It is influenced by
I believe a much richer
Culture of
Media
And I think that's really where the
Difference lies
If you think about it
What are the kids
Today in the US
What do they grow up with
Well
They've been growing up
15 to 20 years of prepackaged
Playlisted
Completely controlled
Crap
And so their influences
You know
Thank goodness for the internet
Because now they're being exposed
Other stuff
And I think that's one of the most important
And we have no art
School anymore in the States
Do we?
Is it even an hour a week
That's left of
Art Studies
I'm pretty sure that was on the outs
So
It's just
A blown away
And so
I came home
I was dead
Dead
Tired
Home around nine
And she looked at me
And she saw how tired it was
And I don't know if she could tell
What Muda was in
And she's like
Carefully says
How was your day
And I'm like
Wow
I'm just bold over
So many good ideas
So many talented people
It's going to be so incredibly exciting
And we're building a great team
For our UK office
One thing I did want to clear
Because everyone asked me this question
Is it going to be like
You put a different skin on
Podcast Ali
Or launch pod show
Plus with the UK flag
So the answer is yes and no
First of all
The folks we want to have
Working here in the UK
They got to be bright
Right
They have to understand
Much more about the culture
Than any of us do
Myself included
And of course it'll be for a worldwide audience
Obviously
But yeah
It's going to be its own entity
Closely tied to the mothership
We'll have sales here
And when advertising
It certainly really only works
If
You know on a local or regional basis
Very few companies will buy
Advertising from one source
In the United States and another country
That just rarely ever happens
So in all I'm just
I'm chaffed as we like to say over here
Really chaffed
Hey Adam
This is Doug Money
And one time chronicler of it
Hey Doug Money
You gotta tell you who he is
Doug was I think the first
He looked I think
Did he work for the register I believe
Hmm
I don't know
I think he was the first one to actually write
About podcasting on the internet
The first article
That actually got any traction
Before slash
I think then slash dot caught onto it after that
Adam
I'm kind of scared
I think I'm suffering from
Charlie withdrawal
Uh-huh
Let me describe this sentence for you
Okay
I've had listened to the Charlie and I know
The past five or six days
Over the past two nights
I've dreamed about you
On the first hearing
Uh-huh
I dreamed you were running around
Making these kids are like drop down and do push ups
Oh man
Wait man
I was running around naked
And I occasionally drop down and do push ups
Doug
This can lead nowhere good
I'm sure
On the second night last night
I
Dream that we were hanging out at the
Creeperop cottage
I know somewhere out in the woods
We're talking
It's Doug and me out in the woods at the
Crap cottage
Doing push ups naked
A bunch of people
You call me my brother
Oh yes, how it starts
Hey my brother
And then we'll move in from it
I don't understand what's going on there
Anyways
I have a good day
Charlie fixed him
Pretty quick
I don't know what to do
It's unstable on the road
And the problem
I don't have time to listen to the Charlie
Oh, maybe a cricket is in sale
No, tied me over
And it was
Tell you have to dream about you tomorrow
I have a really critical show up as well
Naked
Yeah exactly
Doctor
I'm a brother
Okay my brother
Watch where you swing that thing
You know, I think about it
You may be deprived of a Charlie tomorrow as well
Oh crap
I hadn't even figured that one out yet
I'm going to do
I have a meeting at a huge ad agency tomorrow
But they're in Canary Wurf
Which is not convenient
From anywhere I think
But actually if anyone can tell me
What's the fastest
Or what tube do I take to get from
Waterloo Station to Canary Wurf
I really appreciate knowing that
So we have like a
A 10 30 or 11 AM meeting
So there's no way I'm going to be able to do a source code
Before that
We're going to be done around one
Which will probably be too late for the satellite window
So we'll have to do something different on serious
But then when I get home
Then I promise we'll do a show
Patricia and I will both do a show together
For the Friday festivities
But it will be later than usual
And tonight I'm going to
Engineer
And shut up because everyone's told me I shouldn't be
Giggling or laughing
Even though it's very hard to stop
What my daughter is doing her pod save the queen show
So she'll be doing that this evening
So that she'll have a show out on time
And that'll be episode number two
What else is it going to say?
Hold on
What do I have here?
Oh, this was about the fried nuts
About the, you know, of course
I don't really have the problem right now
Because the power book was getting so hot
When I left it on my lap
But they would fry my nuts
Whether to Shiba is very, very cool
Unless of course using it to run second life
And then it's like full blast
This is from M. Josen
As a Windows
Since it meant I usually recommend IBM
Thinkpads to everyone now Lenovo
Which is what they're called now
Still same quality
Over the years I've been using it myself
A lot in the same very stable
I carry mine around constantly
Wait a minute
What was the thing about the fried nuts?
Here it is
You also talked about your fried nuts
Well falling asleep
Trust me
I know how this feels
Yeah
Guys, we know what that's like
And there's a lawsuit waiting to happen right there
You know what I'm saying
And if you can get three million dollars for spilling
Hot
Coffee from McDonald's on your lap
We certainly should be able to get some dough out of frying
Our nuts with our laptops
Laptops tend to become very hot
Cooling is essential
Especially if you play games on them
Ooh, that would be second life
In your processor and video record
Really have to get to work
To prevent it
And this is a good one
I always have a thick newspaper at hand
It also relates great
Keeps the airflow going smoothly
As it's not stuck to your trousers or anything
Also works great in bed
And you can find a thick newspaper everywhere
So no need of carrying around other solutions
Also think pads have a separate AC, DC, power converter
The adapter also becomes quite hot
But it's not built into the laptop itself
Like some other models
Yeah, that could be a part of it
But not with the Mac
Because it also has an external power supply
Good one
I like that
Well last night
I had to go back and just
I didn't even do email man
I just chilled
And we watched some big brother
Why?
You know what?
For those who listen to the podcast
Just stay tuned
We're going to continue with that story about big brother
If you're listening to serious stars
102 Pacific Coast Hellway is next
As the pod show line of continues
Wining up tonight with a new digital
Flotsom and Michael Butler, Cedar Maro
For the Friday festivities
So the Tourette sky
I really like him
And I think he has a strong chance of winning
This is kid in there
I think his name is Pete
And he has Tourette's
And being a mild sufferer myself
I can really recognize some of the agony
He's going through
But his best take if you will
He just keeps saying
Wanker
And a wanker
You can almost hear everyone in London
Replicating him now
But he's really really sweet
And quite intelligent from what I even saw last night
But something
I don't know if I missed this
But two of the kids in there
We're talking
Well first I didn't
I called Christina
Because I said what is this
And then we're speaking Welsh
And I'd never heard about it
Although I
Spoken to people in the past
You say that Welsh is really making
Resurgence, it's coming back
People are starting to speak it again
And it was the most funky language
It was almost like
It was like listening to the
Clingon
That's what it was
I could neither make heads
No tails of it
I'd be like
I can't go back
Schoolboy
I hate me
It was funky man
Hey Adam
It's Jamie here
Long time this to see
Source Coast
I must have just been listening to
And I've got to say
You're Welsh accent
Cracks me up
I was listening to you
I'm trying
Some of that from water
And people were just staring at me
And just thinking that I was having
Sort of problems
Please if you get it out
But I'm just by the end
Could it just it
I'm the only gain of it
It's Welsh
Is that Welsh?
Welsh accent I've ever heard
Really?
I can't wait
I'm the only gain of it
You know
I'm the only gain of cottage
David
That's Welsh
It sounded a lot different
I'm big brother
Yes of it
Tell you that
About this whole Mac window
By the way
I'm not
Frank Barnico
wrote a piece
He writes for CBS
Marka Watch
I think he wrote it on his own
Blog saying
It was actually quoted me correctly
Which I appreciated
You said
I'd said I hated being a
Propetual data tester for Apple
Which I have been
You test the machine
You find the bugs
The next one comes out
While you only have yours
For six months
And presto
Those problems are fixed
It's probably the same with any
Line of hardware
You know
I'm not trying to kid myself here
But I'm just a consumer
I'm just a guy who just needs functionality
And I just have no time to deal with
Going to the genius bar
It's just for anything
You know
And if this to sheep or brakes
Well that's being repaired
I'll buy another one
Maybe that's just the endless loop
That we were caught in with
Stuff that we really really depend on
But it's not a Mac versus
We know it's thing
Not at all
I'm just very interested to see
There's less and less importance
On changing
Or on the operating system itself
Because there's so many web services
And that's another thing
Barnico got absolutely right
I used Google Calendar
I used Gmail
I'll use rightly
I don't have a beta account
But I'll use that
I know I will
I've been an open office user for a long time
I despise the amount of money
That's being charged for
The small, just really just for a small, small piece of the functionality
That I use of office or of word
Excel
Only to read stuff
I don't think I ever created an Excel sheet
On Google
Didn't they also release their Google spreadsheet
Big debate about that
Do you know that a lot of people use this spreadsheet
Just kind of to keep records
Just like they use it as a poorman's database
And by the way, Excel was a very powerful program
But I think that's going to be one of the uses for
Not for real number crunching perhaps
Or not initially
But just to store some shit like your record collection or whatever
Yeah, I'm pretty sure people will use that
So all these things are what we call web services
That is the web 2.0
My friends
That's it
It's coming true
It's not like we didn't know it
You know
And that's where
We'll do that in a dev cast more geeky crap like that
Just a consumer
They'll just try to figure it all out
Oh, this is
I received an email about this podcast
Which I'll tell you which you'll hear a promo for
And it was a very long email and very detailed
And I was like, oh man
They just sent me a promo one of these days
Because so much easier and so much more fun to hear
Different Voice and low and behold, my prayer has been answered
Hey Adam, good afternoon
This is Tey Officer Robert Kern
The United States Navy
Currently stationed at the Command Navy Reserve Forces
Command Office in New Orleans, Louisiana
And I'm proud to announce the launch of the official podcast
Of the Navy Reserve Force
This is the first podcast of the Navy Reserve Force
And it can be found at navyreserve.navy.mil
And I had to say
That the Charlie was inspirational in the development of this
Again, my name is Putty Officer Robert Kern
And my personal podcast can be found at RobCastin.com
But that's not important right now
We're here to talk about the official podcast of the Navy Reserve Force
The United States Navy Reserve
Good luck as the show continues
And I hope to hurt you at DSC 400
Hope to hear you get a DSC 800
Take care
Anchors away man
Yeah, that you go anchors away
That's a good one
I guess I'm not allowed to say that
Not being a sailor man
Dude, very cool
Congratulations
I will check that one out
Over the weekend I'll put it on my list
I wonder how that works
Did you have to go through
You know all kinds of channels and get approval
Or was it just kind of like you just did it on the slide
Or was there some, as there's a missive
For better communication
And of course we'll find out what's in it
But congratulations
I'd love it when we get different types of programming and content
Yes, speaking of that
I've been telling you about this earthlink ad challenge
Where earthlink and pod show
I've decided to put our money where your mouth is
By enabling you to create the actual commercials
For the earthlink service
That's pretty interesting that
We're getting tons of submissions
But I'm also seeing a lot of podcasters
Submit stuff which I like too actually
It's very, it's no different
Listener, podcaster, podcaster listener
I guess it's all the same
But they have some experience
They have already have some experience
And have the tools and know where to upload stuff
And even it said
What was it?
Add challenge.podshow.com
I'll put a link in the show notes
Let's listen to it
I just pulled up a couple of submissions
Let's see what we have here
Whether you're just starting out
Or your season traveler
Let earthlink
Or your bridge
To the world of the internet
Like an old friend
That you can always depend on
And will always be there for you
Earthlink
Always
To the internet
Wow
We'd call that a positioning branding
Spot, I guess
You should re-cut that
But then use Doug Monies thing
You know
An old friend
Earthlink
It's like an old friend
Running around through the woods
At the cottage naked
Doing push outs
We're doing the earthly clues
That's right baby
Right on
Earthlink
Bombastic broadband
Delicious dialogue
That's your thing
Earthlink comes home to you
And brings it home to Mama
That's our assistant
That's what I'm talking about
In Earthlink
We'll help you out with all your internet needs
It's just good at Earthlink.com
Let them know that Papa sits in
Yeah
That's your baby
That's what I'm talking about
So that would be perfect
In combination with a website to go to
Was it Jay Donnelly did that from Mad Pod?
Very creative dude, love it
And you know it's a cool about it
That wasn't 30 seconds
It was like 44 seconds
You know that's fine
That's what's cool about this stuff
How many seconds you need
You know we'll make it in
It's long as it entertaining
We got plenty of time
Not a problem
So it can be like that
We can be
Funny
Sad, esoteric, experiential
Whatever you want
Check it out at challenge.podshow.com
The prices are pretty big though
I think if you
I believe it's listed
Thousands of dollars that you can win with this
And of course really
Just the coolness of
Practically creating a commercial for
Relatively big company
You know that's
Screw it man
I'm going to get into this game
I'm going to do one
Troy Rutter from RutgersRamblings.com
Hey Adam just wanted to give a public thanks
Make and bury over at castblaster.com
For some great help in getting my
Mixer configured correctly for
Castblaster earlier in the week
They were very responsive
Replying several times throughout the day
Definitely a great experience
Now I'll have to do a figure out
Where the increased room noise came from
Well actually I started right after
The recycling guys came today
I was ready to go and they rolled up
And I figured out what
Wait until they were done
It happens
It could be compression or whatever
The type of microphone
I'm sure that the forums and
Indeed my can bury will help you out
We got a new module that I'm testing
Now on castblaster which I really like
And the idea was developed right here on the
On the daily source code which
Just makes me so happy
Because it came through
Forget who sent it
Something about
You know I'd still like my WordPress web
Log to post my show
And honestly I always cross post
The daily source code to curry.com
Which is not the official home
You know daily source code.com
Is the official place with the official feed
etc
But I always cross post it
And it takes time you know
Because you got a copy and paste
And you know if you got different fields
And then copy the link URL
For the direct link to show
And all that stuff
And so I talked to Andrew Grumman
And I said dude can we just do this like
Castblaster just do it all in one
And now I have like a million more ideas
Because actually it worked
When I post this show
It automatically puts in the direct link to the show
Link
It puts it up on the podcast
Lover network
It shows up in pod show
Plus with all the show notes
Which you can't see yet
But remember I talked about important dates
Um
You know then it cross post
Post the entire thing
Plus the entire thing
The entire show notes
Plus the the enclosure
The podcast over to curry.com
And I'm pretty sure that's just going to become a configurable module
But I'm really really really dig in this
Anything that saves me time is great
Um you'll add them
This is Johnny Kay calling
Long time listener
Johnny Kay
Look I I've got a confession
I I've got a confession
I I'm a long time
Charlie I've been listening for about a year
Wait a minute
Awesome dude
Charlie Ite
There you go
How about Charlie Ite's dot com
Perfect
Oh that's what you should use your go daddy
DSC 3 code for
When you check out get it for $695
First one to get it wins
Charlie Ite's dot com
I've bought us some sale
I um
I've got under second life
I've um I've done I have
I haven't listened to Christina's podcast
And I've bought some some music from from the band that she played
I've done everything you've asked
But I just can't just can't switch to windows
Don't make me
Wait a minute
First of all I don't think I've actually told you to buy anything
Yeah the MM50 speakers in the eye dog
I didn't tell you to buy a sense out
I didn't ever tell you I don't think to buy a Mac
In fact I've said quite the contrary if you want to run cast
Blaster but I do appreciate it
And I see this happening all over the place with podcasters
You know if if a podcaster
Um has something or like something
And it shows then it actually works people go out and buy that
Like a recommendation from the friend you know
While you're running around the woods naked doing push ups
Some back with all of us here in the apple world
Once you're back
So please don't make me do it
Don't make me go do windows
I'm not going to do it
I'm not going to tell you I'm not
I promise you I'm not going to do it
No matter how much you talk about it
Anyway thanks for the show
You're hot ladies
I hold on man
Hold on to that dream my friend
Just hold on to it
What do we add right now?
Oh perfect
We're going to end up at our golden ratio time for today
Oh by the way
Charles Fleischer
We're moving ahead with him
We had a great phone meeting
Phone call
We got pod show LA involved
And he's going to do a video podcast
I think it'll blow you away
All right
I've played this girl before
And she shows up
With a new song
And the pod save music network
From the UK
Kelly Mueller
It's a gentleman
My friend
As we run around
To the woods naked
Doing push-up
I've got my face
To the sky again
And I've got my small and full blue
Housing ain't used to a different beat
Now that all my thoughts are with you
You give me such a fashion
You make me feel like I'm perfect sure
They can't keep on pushing me down
But I've got the whole thing I'll never need you
I'll take my keys
Take my keys
I could be all in no longer
And I would be the richest I've ever known
I've got my eyes wide open now
And I've got my vision to clean
Housing ain't used to a different light
Now that you are right here
You show me my potential
You become such an essential
Like the sun you throw my eyes in moves
And it's something that I never ever want to do
Take my keys
I'll take my keys
I could be all in no longer
And I would be the richest I've ever known
Take my keys
Take my inkle
I could live on them
How long?
I would be the richest
I've ever known
I've got my keys
Take my keys
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh
oh yes Kelly mur oh yeah oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh yeah oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh yeah oh oh oh oh I
I mean, listen to this, it's so good, and it's becoming more apparent to me that we need
a couple other positions filled in not just the Podsay for Renet, well, Podsay for Renet,
but also in Pod casting in general, we need the internet version of publicist, you know,
not the, you know, usually a publicist is a semi, I'm just, oh, I'm really generalizing here,
okay, so don't get me wrong, but they're, you know, very connected, you know, hip
happen in people, they got cell phones, you know, but that's for the old media, for the new media,
it's, you know, the bloggers, they know the podcasters, they know, to really help, I mean,
Kelly can't do everything by herself, I mean, look, she's, she's busy, you know, working with her
blessed four and a half octave soul voice and using her weapons of choice, the piano and her songwriting
skills. Now, so she's creative, she needs people around her to help her and we can do that now with the
internet, and we probably need people to help manage their careers as well, you know, so it doesn't
necessarily have to be, we can recreate a whole new version of show business, which will be a
hell of a lot more fun, a lot richer and experience, and open anybody, you know, but we do need to
fill a couple of those, a couple of those gigs. I think I can bring something, you know,
who goes out and really actively promotes to all the podcasters, you know, not all bands are
just capable, you know, look at some of your favorite singers and artists, they're not always
capable of doing the business side or the promotional side, so there's definitely room for that.
All right, that's stuff to think about. As I said, tomorrow we'll have the Friday of activities,
lady Patricia will be on, it will be a little bit later than normal, but it'll be worse.
Or 20 tailwinds, see you, bye. Another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear.
Yet this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from
Podshow and line-white networks. I love it.