This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 360
Metro, Metro, Metro, Metro, Metro, Metro, Metro.
It's Adam Curry's Metro sexual ringtone.
Adam Curry's Metro sexual ringtone.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding.
It's Adam Curry.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
It is the longest running reality show at the business.
It's funny everybody coming to you from Northern California.
San Francisco.
Curry Condo.
Daddy's first code is on.
Come on, you Charlie had this weekend.
First days.
Electricity.
When you walk in, you set my circuit tree.
Back it up.
We've gotta do it.
When people swear that out, you always play cool.
I think I know you.
I'm going a bit.
And you lock through with you.
And don't get it.
Bet your queen fix!
In my car!
You gotta sweep to the damn you switchlebee.
$19 President!
No! No!
Can you just pop on my feet?
$20 President.
No!
$Phone It Right?
$20 President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President President Set President President President
Cause I do, cause I do, cause I do, cause I do, cause I do, cause I do
New y'all, I'm the catwalk, I like to play it to the screen
You don't want to show, spray paint your tagging zone
And cool yourself, don't be wrong, don't take a chance
Give me your shot, you think I'm bluffing, I think I'm not
Give me your OK, I got a question for you, suééééééèéèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèè
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
We're gonna do all the things all the couples like to do.
We're gonna go to Wolfie, we're gonna have some dinner, take a walk, look at the moonlight and if thing you wobble, baby I gotta question.
Do you kiss all the first names?
Let's do it all the first names!
What do you do all the first names?
Thank you very much, Jersey Todd, for sending that in this suggestion for kickoff of the
weekend festivities on the thank god it's Friday edition of the Charity Daily source code.
only guy from Jersey could really understand exactly what song you want at the beginning of
a show like that. Thank you, dude. Appreciate it. Hey everybody, it's the last day. The last
full day, last show day for me for this trip out west. Tomorrow, going back home, can't wait.
Gotta be really honest about that. Although it's gonna be pretty busy before we take off on
vacation for Portugal. So I'll still have shows all next week and I haven't quite decided what to
do in my absence. I know I want to do at least one, probably one or two shows from vacation.
I mean, of course, I'll be checking in, but I do really need to take a break.
For example, just last night as I came home. That was a long day yesterday and I stayed
late at the office because I was working on some video stuff which I'll talk to you about in a second.
So I'll come home and it's like nine o'clock and nine o'clock is like, you know, you could, yeah,
you could order some food if you want, but you know, so you probably won't be eating until nine
45 or 10. I wanted to prep today's show, but I just wanted something to eat and, you know,
hey, look, I'm a bachelor out here. You know, I got the complete tricked out bachelor pad. Right
now, I was funny. I was looking at last night. I got three high-end computers running here all the
time. This, you know, just gadgets plugged into every available wall outlet. Man, when Patricia
comes along with me in May when she's coming over. She's just gonna hate it so much.
But I don't have anyone to, you know, I don't have a lot of stuff here to cook. You know, yeah,
I've got my pantry filled up with stuff. And of course, you can always make some pasta, right?
And it's real easy. I like making the sauce and I've got all kinds of stuff herbs and stuff around
the house. Really easy to to whip something up. And that's always, you know, that's, that's like,
it's almost like nature's fast food. Let's be honest. So here I am and I've, and I got my pot and I'm
cooking up my, my pasta, angel hair pasta. And I have this, you know, this sink, which is really
this whole area. I really should take a picture of that shooting. I should publish a picture. So I've
got, I'm on the kitchen, open kitchen bars where my computers are, where the studio is. And then,
of course, there's a dual sink, you know, with garbage disposal. And so I've got the pasta. I'm
gonna, I know, what I didn't have is a strainer. I thought I had one, but I guess I don't. So I have
to get a strainer. So what do you do is you, you know, you grab the pot with the lid on and you
try and strain out the water carefully. So the, so now it's now it's 930 that I've got the finally,
I've got the pasta going like, okay, I'll just have, I'll just eat something, then I'll, you know,
I'll chill out and I'll go to bed. And, and I start pouring out the water. And I can, some of
you already know what happened. Yeah, exactly. All the pasta went right down into the garbage disposal.
So I'm still hungry. If you know what I mean. God, man, this video stuff is hard. I've been,
I've been working on, on figuring out how to, hey, how to get video stuff just right, you know?
And Apple is not very helpful in this because, okay, so what's very easy, if you just want to
make something and publish it to your iPod or, or make it compatible with the iPod, it's easy,
because there's an actual button there tab, a pull down menu that says iPod. So, you know, I did that
a couple times and of course, lots of people said, hey, I don't have quick time. I'm running Linux.
It doesn't work for me. I use a different player. And the consensus that I could see pretty much
was, you know, get yourself into the habit of creating real MPEG for video. Let me just see, I had,
yeah, for instance, super, right, that's a different one. And, and that's not easy. You know,
you try MPEG for and then it, it won't even play back properly on my machine for some reason.
It's almost like you're being forced towards an Apple way instead of something that would be
universally useful. And so, yes, I tried, I did the MPEG for, I did the, I used several different
settings. And, and, of course, when I put it into the podcast feed, it didn't make it in,
which means you may have picked it up, but not, if you were using iTunes, you didn't get it.
So, you'd actually have to download it and then you'd have to recompress it with the iPod.
You know, so mysterious what those settings are with the iPod setting so that it then will go into your iPod.
So, this, this means that unless I can figure out one setting that will also work on iPods,
as well as any other MPEG player, and I have no idea, now I'm really lost, you know, because I thought
I did it all right. I chose the MPEG for compressor anyway. And then, of course, as a question
of putting it into the feed. Now, this feed, my podcast feed for the daily source code is,
and that's a pretty valuable property. You know, anything I put in there is guaranteed to get to a
lot of people, or at least if I'm using the proper video codex. But not everybody likes it.
For different reasons, let me see, here's an email from Frederick. I want to say that a second
feed for the videos will be a good idea. I have a fourth generation non-video iPod, and my iTunes
set up to only copy the latest episode and delete the older ones. So, if you send out a video,
iTunes don't copy anything on it. Well, I mean, hey, look, this would happen if I did a whole bunch
of audio releases, too, your stuff would start to get deleted. In fact, Frederick does say that,
you know, this actually could be a bug on his system that iTunes won't copy anything to the iPod.
I don't know, man. I thought the iPod would take MPEG for an any version, but apparently not.
And then another piece of feedback about that from Andrew Stanley Jones. You mentioned no
and complain, so I thought I would. This always nice to have someone who will step up to the
plate, isn't it? I haven't since I think it's actually a bug in my feed fetcher. I don't
want to fetch the videos automatically. I can't see them on the nano and have a meter to internet.
I can only get 500 megs a day, yeah, that does suck. But that's life on the satellite internet
in BFE, middle of no rural Indiana. But anyways, it would be easy to limit what type of
enclosures it should fetch versus automatically fetching them. So, after all, I blame the software.
Okay, well, it is all kind of software, software issues. So, working on it, trying to figure it out.
And everyone has sent me different ideas and suggestions and different settings. And, you know,
we're going to figure it out one way or the other. And meantime, we'll just keep making the videos.
People seem to like it. You know, this was a very interesting test. And I think I really
have to document how I did it, because people think now that I have some awesome,
the software switching video, which it really was much simpler than that. Although,
Casplaster Mike did check in with me. He's on his way. He usually goes off for a couple of days
to go program and like the woods. It's not really the woods where he's going. But it's like the
woods. Which means he's getting ready to do a final release of Casplaster, I presume.
And of course, he's already been thinking about the video version of Casplaster. And,
and the other first pop up is what are we going to do about formats, because, you know, Windows,
the Windows Media format is much more prevalent, which also should be able to just create a simple
MPG. Anyway, if you've got info, if your tech heads, please let me know. But try and
and whittle it down because my eyes fucking glaze over at the stuff some people say. Oh, I'm
extremely stressed. Can't start a weekend without him, you know.
Comics trip. Comics trip. Comics trip. Comics trip. Comics trip.
As our friend, Comics trip blogger can't finish up a week without him, you know?
Ciao, ciao, I'm Kerry. Once upon a time I lived in Italy and spoke Italian. And I remember saying
once to my palpfabizio. But I don't know how to say it today. And he replied,
what funculo is cosy? Maiono, I begoto, Ilca, Ferrancoa. What could be translated as,
how are you today Fabrizio? And, fuck off, I haven't drank coffee yet. So, you see that for some
people coffee is important, but not for me. I don't drink coffee at all, so I am not digging
here, since I'm a belching advertisements. Sorry. But when you announced it now,
naturally as a deal with Go Daddy, I was happy I am very often good customer of Go Daddy,
and when I needed to add additional demand to my collections, for example, with blogger in the
main name instead of blog in the main name, I just go to www.godaddy.com and or the new domain
and they even have a very nice feature of privacy protection. So, you can buy internet domain
in the same time, hide from the word that this domain is released by yourself. Cool stuff.
Yo, dude, thank you so much, and then actual comic strip blogger endorsement for Go Daddy,
I love it, man, and it is true because I got an email from, was it, no, this was an email,
this was a comment that I saw on curry.com. Low and behold, someone has gone out and actually
done me a service by registering a domain name for me with GoDaddy.com. Yes, if you type in
bighairedfag.com, you'll see that it goes straight off to curry.com. Yeah, you know, these are
great gag gifts and they can be great love gifts and well, and I consider this one definitely to be
the latter. This is for generations of the government and the electorate have had an uneasy
relationship, a relationship based upon the politics of fear, power, and and harmony. The
media has often neglected its responsibility as the four branch of governments. As citizens
we can no longer tolerate this, but it is time for us to remain what is ours.
You can even use an independent politics with groupy sweet shows, college without affiliation
with a head of curry and an odd show network. Though some may snuff, groupy sweet and
perfectly boldly, that the others in the media have advocated its responsibility to a more
ordinary electorate. This is a journalism, this is the future, because we can no longer
lie among a government to tell us the truth, and because we can no longer lie among the
needs to help us make informed decisions. It is up to us to pursue an adverse
responsibility to join our show and release it as our audience support.
Oh man, right, dude, I'm expecting quite a lot from you now.
Nice, nice boots, jack boots in the background.
Okay, the pod people are coming creepy sleepy show in the pod show pod has not worked great to have in the board of course.
And there's so much love, so it's such an outpouring of love and it comes in all forms.
As you know, this is really one of the prime examples of a user generated program.
75% of the show is put together by the people who are actually listening to it.
And that's what I love so much about it because I can wake up in the morning.
And people who heard that, you know, I had problems during yesterday's show and, you know,
and I couldn't get the complete line out out in time to tell the folks who are listening to us on serious satellite that,
you know, that what else is coming up.
And it's just because I don't have a producer, it's shoot man, it's 730,
I'm sorry, 630, 630 in the morning.
You know, it's hard.
And then my friends come up and stand next to me and say,
we're going to help you out and we're going to help you get through the Charlie.
Hey everybody now, you know what that means?
Oh, the window! He's over there by the window!
He's a satellite repair man, what's he gonna do?
He'll fit your misconceptions and answer questions too.
He's turned nothing in the universe and he can't do for you.
A satellite repair man.
Woo!
Hey, I just beat him!
Everybody.
Alright, beat up, come in!
Beat up, you out of me.
I saw one that I saw.
I saw a satellite line up, are you ready to copy?
Ready?
After the daily source code, it's a specific code's hell-weight,
followed by East Radio.
And it's gone and grew, followed by Steve Gilmore's Gilmore Daily.
And we wrap up the satellite transmission with Wichita Rottenford's
Groove Crash Show, and our newest music show, the scene scene.
Have a good weekend at him on a tape trip home.
Coming up on Lawson Signal.
Thank you.
Let's do that one more time, man.
It just maybe feels so happy, especially for fun.
You know, we bet everybody, he's known as the EU.
The satellite repair man.
Coming after you.
What's he gonna do?
He'll fit your misconceptions and answer questions too.
Learn nothing in the universe,
and he can't do for you.
The satellite repair man.
Woo!
Here I go.
Alright, honey, we've got to get some airtime on the DSC.
And I've got some ideas.
I was kind of thinking that I could set him a spot for the Metro sexual
moment.
How does this sound?
Hey, Adam, I just want to give you some of my skincare ideas for your Metro sexual.
No, no, no, sweetie.
Sweetie, sweetie.
Okay, you are so not Metro sexual.
I mean, you don't have any hair to put mousse on.
And as far as I know, you've never removed any hair from any other part of your body
besides your face and hair.
I saved my legs one time for a swim mate.
Does that can?
No, sweetie.
Alright, um, that could be like a stalker.
The new Adam stalker.
A stalker?
Yeah, well, I don't know.
Just hang with me.
Hey, Adam, I saw you in Trinity this last weekend.
You were looking pretty good.
Ew, Robin, you did not see Adam in Trinity this weekend.
He doesn't know that.
And I'm an airline pilot.
I can be in San Francisco.
I can be in New York and be in London.
And is there something that you're not telling me about your layovers?
Uh, no.
No.
Uh, I sense you're getting a little tense.
You know what, honey?
We can talk about it.
Hey, easy on the psychology stuff, honey.
This is about Adam's show.
Not about me.
How about if I start bitching out of like,
Madge?
No, no, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, hang on.
Adam, you f***!
Get your hair!
You f***!
Why f***!
And the nair in the Netherlands, I don't f***!
Get it!
No.
Oh, that went well.
You think?
Mm-hmm.
Honey, I think that we should just speak straight from our heart
without any tricks or gimmicks and just say something like this.
Thanks, Adam, and Ron for inviting us into the patch of family.
No, try it.
Hey, that's not gonna get it.
Okay.
Thank you, and bye for now from InsightWorks.com.
That's Ion as YTWORKS.com.
Wait for it.
Here comes.
Tailwind.
Oh yeah.
And Robin is one of the people who definitely definitely can say tailwinds
because my plane is such a thinking to Ion compared to the ones that he flies.
Great to have you guys in the patch of podcast network as well.
Very nice.
It was InsightWorks that, you know, first, actually I got a lot of benefit from listening
to the show.
When they told me not to accept other people's baggage, it really made a difference in my life.
So it's much appreciated.
And great to have you guys, you know, your voice out here on the network.
Let's see what we're talking about.
Oh, you know, it's actually, it's interesting how much feedback I've received
on the Metrosexual moment, which we did the other day, where I talked about using
narrow on the other regions, narrow in the other regions, everybody.
Gosh, you know, Americans are freaked out by that.
What is it with, you know, is this a homosexuality, you know, homophobia type thing?
I don't know.
I mean, I just think that it looks so much cleaner and nicer and, you know, shit,
we're not in the 70s anymore.
And I go back to the porn.
Look at the porn, guys.
You look at women in porn movies.
Yeah.
And if you are watching that with your, with your woman, with your,
if you're watching it with your men, with your partner, doesn't matter.
Someone's looking at the guy.
And your wife or your girlfriend, your partner's probably going,
yeah.
But not if it's all one big bushy mess down there, come on.
Jesus, Jesus, Louise.
It's like everyone's like, oh, well, that's really weird.
I don't think it's weird at all.
But it only seems to be Americans who think that's really weird.
Yeah.
Anyway, just wanted to make that observation.
And we were talking about the album covers, and when we're talking about potsafe,
music, network, how I used to love that double album cover.
See, you had Frampton comes alive with a double album.
There was Stevie Wonder songs in the Key of Life, was a great double album.
We just folded it over and had all these great, great bits in it.
And then, of course, there was the Greece soundtrack, which had,
really, I remember looking at that album, a lot, the double album.
It all, you know, pictures of little fifties, trinkets on it.
And in the comments, curry.com, comments on the show.
Jimmy, Jimmy Crackhead said, speaking of albums,
did you have a favorite for getting seeds out of the bag of weed you just bought?
I was used Frampton comes alive.
There it is.
It's absolutely right.
Frampton comes alive, baby.
That was the best one.
Yesterday, the, the podpim came to me.
The podpim, Aaron Bersel, who does all our PR and marketing.
He's a pimp.
He's our podpim.
And he has, in his hand, a copy of the latest edition of Playboy Magazine.
And on the cover of this is the Go Daddy Girl.
And so here's the message I got.
He says, and it's beautiful, by the way.
Very voluptuous.
If you haven't seen the videos for it,
I think you can find it at GoDaddy.com.
Madge Weinstein played some of the videos.
Cali played some on Geek Brief TV.
So you can find them around.
She's stunningly beautiful in sexy.
And Aaron says, well, you know, this came from GoDaddy.
And it actually came from the GoDaddy girl who wanted you to have it.
And so, of course, I said, yeah, right bullshit.
And he said, no, no, it's really, really true.
The GoDaddy girl wanted you to have this.
And I'm looking at that.
And so the first of all, I say, hey, wow, that's cool.
Of course, I say, podpin.
Get her on my show.
Now I want to talk to her.
And she said, yeah, yeah, that's a great idea.
And then I'm looking at this picture.
And I'm thinking to myself, this girl is worthy of the list.
Now, don't tell me that if you're not married,
you don't have a list.
Because I think every couple has at least discussed the list.
You know what I'm talking about.
The list is the list of usually celebrities
that either one of you was allowed to have sex with
if you should happen to bump into them.
So, you know, we've talked about my list, right?
Angelina Jolie.
Patricia's list has Brad Pitt.
Oh, shoot.
People on the satellite.
You're not going to hear what happens.
You left to go to dailysourcecode.com.
Sometime over the weekend to hear the rest.
PCH next.
See you guys on Monday.
Okay.
Glad you're still here on the podcast.
So Patricia has Brad Pitt on her list.
I got Brad Pitt on my list.
And I'm thinking, I bet you.
If it's really true, if this girl want me to have the,
want to be to have that playboy, there's a message there.
I bet you I could swap Angelina Jolie for the Go Daddy girl.
I bet you.
I'll get back to you on that one for sure.
You know, dealing with most domain name registrars is like this.
Oh.
But dealing with GoDaddy.com for your domain registration needs
is like this.
Oh.
Yeah.
And using our promotional code, PCH3,
when you check out to get a.com domain name for just 6.95 a year,
is like this.
Oh.
What are you doing?
Can I help?
Oh.
And with your domain registration,
you'll get hosting free quick blog complete email.
And so much more.
Hey, go get your piece of the internet at godaddy.com.
As we start to upgrade advertising to advertising 2.0,
this is our GoDaddy promotion part of our one brand many voices campaign.
And that's you're hearing this all over the pod show podcast network now.
I once coming up with different ways different advertisement ideas.
And I'm really, really digging it.
Unfortunately, the show also, of course, brought to you by earth link.
And by acu view, check out Heather and Janelle at download.acu view.com.
And I've got a couple more pieces of feedback for you today.
No, not a sense.
Oh, just a nice cup of tea.
Adam.
Yeah.
Mr. Curry.
Yes.
I think you're the only man on a first name basis with the entire world.
Good morning.
Good afternoon.
Or good evening depending on where on the planet you are.
This is Al-Lock or aka Uncle Normie from a hate the radio.
Today I want to discuss networking.
Not the, hey, how come these email servers keep crashing?
So I know what?
I'm sorry.
You know what?
This is a really long comment that actually deserves a lot of comment for me and thought.
So I'm going to save that until next week if you don't mind.
Because it's Friday.
We got to move through to show you.
Yeah.
Adam.
It's Brian from the Procrastecast.
Yeah, Brian.
At the Procrastecast.com.
And I've been playing around trying to get into this podcasting game and I'm having a lot
of fun actually.
I had the audacity to put up the first eight.
That was in the last few weeks.
And audacity works pretty well.
I don't mind the program.
It's actually quite easy to use.
But the problem is once I get the music tracks down and once I get the, you know, the
show opener thing and whatever you call that, I don't know what the hell I'm doing on this
stuff.
But I'm modeling through.
And I get ready to do my comments.
I've sort of lost the mood.
It's like it's like having to put on a condom just when you're, you know, ready to do it.
It just kind of loses.
It just kind of fizzles.
And I'm afraid I, you know, anybody who's bothered to stumble on that show probably
fell asleep in the middle of it.
And that's not really what I'm going for.
I love playing the music from the pod safe music network.
And I, you know, that's kind of what I want to do.
Just play a few tunes and make a few comments and get it up, right?
And so my problem is, you know, the flow.
So I decided to go get cast blaster and, you know, the thing works.
I figured it out.
I was able to put some shows together.
Two programs or so I put together with cast blaster.
I was able to get it up really fast and really well.
And, and that's a good thing, right?
I mean, you, when you're ready to, to get it up, you want to get it up.
And so I'm not doing that.
That boring thing.
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
I think you're really hot at him.
I really do.
But not that.
You know, while anything can happen, I doubt it's going to happen between us.
All right.
So are you going to interact with this cast blaster question?
Mm-hmm.
I know that you use it at least as why I've heard that you use this cast blaster software.
And what I would like to know is, while you can get it up fast, I'm missing some volume.
So the program just doesn't have the volume that I need.
And so that's kind of my question for you.
How can I get more volume out of cast blaster?
Do you do it?
Yeah.
You know, I was standing in front of the mirror yesterday, coughing and I said, damn it.
I need more volume.
Give me more volume.
I don't know what the, what the problem is.
And you need to basically turn it to 11.
So you got to crank your mic up so that the meters are hitting almost hitting zero
at the very end of the scale there in the reds.
And the same for the music.
And then it should be working.
And I don't know if you're talking about the volume that you are recording or the volume.
That you hear in your headsets.
You have to be a little more precise about that.
But I'm using it now.
And I got plenty of volume.
In fact, sometimes I have too much volume.
It does happen.
So yesterday we turned on portions of D-gap dynamically generated.
What do we call it now?
We change the name dynamically generated asset placement.
Ass placement.
And it's cool because now you can have multiple segments to any podcast that can be configured
dynamically through the network or through the individual podcast very soon.
And eventually I believe the listener.
And so we have these, we have the ability to insert a tag.
So you probably heard the beginning of this show.
And it, you know, it's all randomized.
And we have different grids.
So you'll hear P-dub doing a tag first.
And Brian, no.
We'll do a tag later.
And there's a whole logic to it, which is very cool,
a whole management system that we've created.
And so we started with the GoDaddy ads, which, or the GoDaddy tags,
I should say, which was it like you want a badass domain name for your killer content.
A rather short-sighted on the networking side from my point of view,
because I should have taken into consideration.
And of course, now we've automated this.
That should have taken into consideration that some podcasters may not like the term badass.
And in fact, Steve Webb, of life spring, as I told you yesterday, said,
Oh, man, you know, this won't go from my show.
He wasn't alone.
I had him into the Danny Caster lab rat beta tester from 100.
One uses for baby wipes with some audio feedback.
Hold on, it's Bita.
You're a beauty attesta.
Yeah, I've been attempting in vain to upload a show to the PDN,
since I was invited to join the network way back in February,
which, you know, in podcasting terms, like half a century ago.
Now, I've been very patient.
And my patients was rewarded today.
I was finally successful in uploading a show.
Woo!
Later that morning, I listened to the Chuck E 359er,
and heard you talk about Steve's dilemma over at life spring
and thought, I wonder, did that happen to me?
Now, I can cast bad enough to make a sailor blush, okay?
Enough said.
I just don't do it in front of my kid,
and I wouldn't want someone else's kids to hear it.
Now, the PDN is already asking if the show is explicit or not,
so just cue off that to decide which ad to attach,
so that we don't have to listen to bad ass.
Okay?
Bad ass.
Can you help a fellow podcaster out,
and then, you know, fix my one and only uploaded show?
Please?
Okay, okay.
I'm going back in my test now, see ya.
Oh, dude.
Totally appreciate that feedback.
And you know what? Great fucking idea.
Don't play that, what I just said to your kids.
Great idea.
So we immediately implemented that,
because yes, when you, when you create a show,
and you put it on the podcast,
the library network, you could say,
is this particular show explicit or not,
and that, of course, shows up in the tags
that are useful in other places, like on iTunes, et cetera.
And also, for our own internal system,
if it should you wish to filter by that.
So, first of all, I'm really glad that you got your stuff uploaded
because we've had, like,
I think, three of the beta testers have had issues,
and you were one of the final ones.
So it sounds like we got that fixed.
And yeah, as you know,
after he sent out this comment, he realized
that we had changed that, and we put the,
actually, you get PWM and Brian
cut some special new ones really quick.
This is what it takes man to figure out a real network of shows.
And so what we've implemented now,
what Andrew Romitt is doing, is indeed that simple.
But explicit, yes, then you get all the great ads,
or for that particular campaign,
or no, would be the PG version of the campaign.
So that's a great idea.
I really appreciate it.
Fantastic feedback.
Really works.
And the golden ticket idea, which I told you about,
we're going to try that.
I think Tuesday, Wednesday, next week,
it kind of depends on the timing.
Now, this is just going to be a test.
So the way it'll work is on a designated daily source code.
You'll either download it from the website,
or your iTunes will get it, or juice receiver,
or it's something, however you normally get the show.
And I think we'll do it this way.
The show will start off probably with a network tag.
And then before I actually start with the show tag,
you know, DeltaShare Charity, whatever,
you will hear, either I'm sorry,
you did not win the Golden ticket,
or you'll hear, congratulations.
You won the Golden ticket, call this number now,
with this, you know, with whatever password or code,
or whatever I'm going to use for that.
Because we'll be able to insert into one,
only one of the thousands and thousands of downloads
of this show.
And we're only testing it on daily source code.
One of the people who downloads it,
will actually win a prize.
And that's the thing that Sam Leaven hooked up
that iPod remote with the power remote,
the AV thing.
I'll get all the details on that Monday.
So be on the lookout for it.
One of these shows that's going to happen.
Now, of course, what could happen is that that show
will have been downloaded, but someone might not listen to it
for a day, for two days, for a week, or at all.
So it's going to be interesting to find out what happens.
And it'll just be at random.
So it doesn't matter if you're earlier late.
It'll be, you know, a rather large random generator
thing, because there's a lot of downloads of the show.
But we'll make sure that it will definitely be downloaded
within the first day, because that we can kind of figure out.
You know, knowing how many downloads there will be,
and we'll make sure that the numbers lower than that.
So, what else did I have?
You know, we could wrap it up now.
You know what, there's time, there's enough time for.
Should we just do one more?
I don't know.
I'm feeling kind of.
Yeah, well, you know, this was such a nice piece of feedback
from Greece.
And I don't think we've ever had a Greek charlie head on the show.
And also, full of really good ideas about the ID3 tags
conversation that we've been having on the pod safe music network.
Now, for those of you who don't know, ID3 tags are little pieces of information.
You can put into your MP3 file when you make it available to the world
or to your friend or when you make it public.
So that your player can actually, you know, display information
about the song or that file itself.
So if you look at your player right now,
you'll see that it says daily source, Adam Curry's daily source code.
It'll have some numbers there, maybe even the show notes appear.
All that information is baked right into the file.
And you can do some pretty interesting things with that.
And besides that, it's just, I said, I said,
Panayotes is just interesting to have on the show.
Hey, Adam, this is Panayotes from Greece.
Recording this message on my way to the office,
as I'm driving on my mobile phone,
here are some thoughts regarding the ID tags on pod safe music network.
I don't understand your approach that, you know,
we just provide the space and the community where it's our system market
and promote his songs or his songs.
And they are responsible to make sure that the customer gets the best,
how is the worst in some cases.
On the other hand, since the artists already provide
all the information needed,
such as artist name, song name,
sometimes record name too.
It would be pretty easy to embed these information
in the MP3 files automatically.
What would be nice if you do that?
Well, there are two places where you could automatically
add the ID tags, ID3 tags.
One place is when the artist uploads the songs.
So you do that once, and the MP3 file has all the ID3 tags it needs.
The other place would be just before someone download the song.
This might seem a bit more with those consuming
because you will have to do this every time.
But on the other hand, this opens up a whole new space for promotions.
What I mean is that if you embed the ID tags,
I'm just listening to this and I'm thinking to myself,
isn't it amazing what we're doing here?
I mean, you take it so for granted what's happening.
But I'm sitting here in my kitchen in San Francisco.
I recorded some stuff and some thoughts about independent people's music.
And here's a guy in Greece on his way to the office,
recording something on his mobile phone,
and able to send it off to me and it's within our community the next day.
This shit just freaks me out.
Well, just before someone downloads the MP3 file,
you could say that every 100 downloads take your...
It sounds like the golden ticket idea.
Eggs of the songs.
And if you see the promo code, you have this gift.
Or an artist could add additional ID tags,
for example, what's his concert schedule for the next couple of weeks or months.
Or I don't know.
I think it would be a pretty interesting advertising space.
Or at least a nice tool to promote things.
Well, what was it?
I hope I helped.
Well, I do have a podcast in Greece,
but I won't mention it here since very few people will be able to understand Greek.
If someone knows Greek and understand Greek,
they can visit www.repa.net.
We are YPA.net.
And find the link for my podcast there.
Goodbye, Adam.
All right, buddy.
Thank you very much.
Patricia's Greek, part Greek.
Her mom is, her mom's side of the family is Greek.
And Christina also has a lot of that Greek blood running through her.
Hot tempered, I have to say, but love the Greek.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
By the way, although a really good idea,
I don't think it's a good idea to start altering ID three tags,
because that, for me, falls under the publishing of the,
excuse me, under the publishing and the copyright of the creator of that.
So that's probably not a very good idea, unless you, you know,
agree to it beforehand.
But for artists, yeah, that could be kind of cool to create a system
and dig up can completely do this.
And that's what I liked about your idea is not only on pod safe music,
but it could also be a part of the podcast,
where when you put your show up on the PDN,
we could make a space available for you to type in a message,
which would then be added in, and you could change that message.
So you could say, for every show that goes out for this week,
I want this message to scroll across an ID three tag,
and the description or whatever of the MP3 file.
We can totally do that.
So that seems like a great step for us to implement for podcasters.
I think it'll be very cool.
Now, the big problem is of course that ID three tags,
it's not consistent.
You have 15 million fucking different versions.
You know, Silicon Valley really fucked this stuff up.
The only thing that's good came out of Germany,
and that's the MP3 format,
because that's the only thing that's really pretty much consistent.
Everything else is so goddamn incompatible.
It really pisses me off that it works like that,
like that in computer land.
It's stupid.
Everyone trying to wall off everybody else.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, let's wind it up with a song from the pod safe music network.
This is another recommendation from my favorite frogcaster,
Arnau Uber.
Adam's email,
I found a great talent on the PMN,
who just uploaded it to stuff,
Justin Winnerker.
So we're going to play Justin.
I just played him on my latest French language podcast,
De Genouille, don't, am I saying this right?
De Genouille, Genouille, don't le valet.
De Genouille, don la valet.
Bonjour, les bonjour Monsieur le professeur.
Great stuff, he's difficult to find as far as it's sound,
but who cares, it's great music.
Let's see, God, he wanted to hook up for a drink.
Shit, man, next time I'm out, we'll definitely do that.
And I really appreciate the recommendation.
There's nothing more fun than having someone give me an idea
of what to play instead of me having to choose
that every single day.
He's Justin Winnerker.
You would crawl at me and mother chance to be.
I love to know you're home.
I love to be the way I do now,
every single day of the week.
I'm happy to sleep around.
Up in shows, trips across the sea.
It's just go out with me.
If you're just go out with me.
If you're all kissing your lips,
I do just have a red rocket shot.
All for each day of the week.
We fly up to base on romantic,
we can dream, and we show you how good it is to be.
I love to know you're home.
I love to be the way I do now,
every single day of the week.
We're happy to sleep around.
Up in shows, trips across the sea.
Just go out with me.
If you're just go out with me,
I can fly around.
Justin Winnerker, just go out with me.
Two date songs in one charlie.
I mean, does it get any better than that?
The hell is this more to the song?
The kid made.
No.
What is that?
That's just like the band played on as the Titanic Cirque.
Just a two quick after thoughts here.
One is about to go daddy girl.
It just kind of hit me that Patricia might want to go daddy girl on her list.
And maybe what we should do is we should both just take Brad Pitt off our list.
Hmm.
Everybody had a great week.
Thank you very much for hanging out.
DailyStoresCode.com.
Adam at curie.com, although you may not be able to send me any email until I get back in the cottage
because Gmail is full once again.
Google, I will pay you.
I will pay you any amount of money to give me more space.
Please, please, please, please, please.
Another pod show pod cast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this pod cast and more great ones like it.
On the high performance pod cast delivery network from pod show and line white networks.
I love it.