Delta Sierra Charly 345
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do. Where are flink?
We believe in an internet that safe from viruses and scammers.
We're Earthlink.
We believe your personal information should be just that, personal.
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe.
We're Earthlink.
Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net
And discover what our internet experts can do for you, Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
We're 16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Can I ask me this?
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky ingredients in it.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Fantastic.
It's Adam Curry.
Music
In the morning sun, I rolled a fat blood
Just to wake me up.
Sometimes I find it hard to understand the way it can.
From your point of view you'll find this true.
And you'll just roll your eyes.
But in your mind you'll see.
It's not all that she thought it was.
It's just all that she thought it was.
It's not all that type.
It's not all that she thought it looked like it was.
It's not the outfits you covered on front and no blame for that.
It's not because it's just the dress design.
It's just the dress design.
It's not a pics of for themselves.
Now feel it flawless.
It's not this style of clothing that we look kind of like.
But its not the fashion Chocolate in body but it doesn't match taste.
Yeah.
And tell me all the things that you do
The things that says I'll be rings
So grab the tubes, they just send a message
Just not stay in the room
In the morning sun, the lignus
I don't!
From the pod save music network everybody
How you doin' welcome to the Charlie episode 3-4-5
Always nice when you have sequential numbers like that
Another beautiful day in Gilford in the...
Well, it is the sunny affluent suburb of Surrey
Better known as Gilford
Now cold this morning, man
It was minus two degrees Celsius
When I took Christina to school this morning
But just nice and sunny and no wind
So it's really good everyone's in great spirits
I was up way too, I don't know what happened
I woke up at like 6.30
You know, it was an hour before I even had to wake up
Must be some form of internal clock mechanisms that aren't
Aren't exactly ticking correctly
And thank you all by the way
Oops, what is this?
Oh that's interesting
Thank you all by the way, so much for sending in all these different ideas
And, oh no, what the hell happened there?
Good
Sorry, little mac issue there
All the different ideas and remedies for jet lag
It really doesn't bother me all that much to be quite honest
It's kind of interesting that I woke up so early this morning because I know I'm really tired
I have no idea
It'll get better as we go along
So looking forward to a really nice weekend hanging out here at the cottage
Of course, we'll have a thank god it's Friday edition of the show tomorrow
Looking forward to that lots of great stuff coming
It's really interesting all the all the feedback that's coming into this show
It comes in through so many different avenues
And also I think the show really extends beyond just the podcast
If you look at the comments on curry.com
Now that we have the new server, we're using wordpress now for the show site
Not for the show site for
From my personal weblog
We're also do post
Every source code as well. It's a crosspost thing. Yeah, I'm a crossposter
The comments there really started to heat up
And it looks like we got a little light of the stalker is going on between
Roger Smalls and comic strip blogger and somehow I don't know
I got some stuff to to play for you in just a couple minutes
Then there's the the the user show notes which is the wiki show notes at show notes dot info
There's lots of stuff that gets fed back there and then of course still tons and tons of of
email
Coming into Gmail and at 99% today. Let me just double check. Let me see my percentage is correct
The minute you hit 100 you can still receive some mail 99% yet 4056 megabytes of your 4096
So someone sends me a 40 meg file
Toast
Please don't do that. It does so many horrible things particularly to the blackberry
That's even I've completely given up on the blackberry push email by the way now. I'm using
Gmail's mobile email. It actually works pretty well now that this new blackberry have has the edge
Services which is really really fast and it has a faster processor internally
It's actually worth it just to use Gmail's online interface I found and you can and it does have it still doesn't it let you add a star
Doesn't let you add a label. I don't understand why not. I mean if we can do a star let's do a label
Because now if I want to tag something for the source code instead of applying a DSC label to it
I have to add a star to it and then come back and search for the stars search for the stars
And then convert those into
Into DSC labels otherwise the searching goes well even the most frequently used emails email addresses
Of course it doesn't pop up in the same Java script
You know, what is it to Ajax kind of way that that it does in a web browser but you it does remember which ones
You can select from a list that enough about Gmail
Let me see
This is something that was I had a whole bunch of stuff that I didn't play yesterday of course because we had the lovely Patricia pie on the show
This was kind of interesting though because it shows this next comment shows how podcasts are being used internally
Within businesses and not just you know for business talk, but they also want to make it entertaining and there's nothing against making
You know business information entertaining
But there are some issues when it comes to the pod safe music network
It's crystal in daily source code three for three you played the feedback from Martin who is an internal or internet podcast
Like I am and you don't get the problem
Which is basically that we cannot complete the registration process or our podcasts are never getting verified
So we never become members at spotcasters of the
Pod safe music network since our feeds exist behind our firewalls in our
Internet so
There's no way for us to get the access to the pod safe music and
I think it's a shame since podcasting is such a great way to bridge the
The gap between cultures and between people in a highly
Distributed environment so we'll be great if you guys could provide some sort of checkbox
That allows us to indicate it's an internet podcast and there's no way for you to verify it
And the rest certainly is something we can do provide feedback and group or report and
Usage, but we simply cannot pass this hurdle
So maybe something for you guys to consider thanks a lot and take care
Right, okay, so now I finally understand that I guess there's some form of verification
When you sign up as a podcast or to the pod safe music network that checks to see if your feed is actual for real
Actually for real so that it I guess it validates to whatever. Hey, what's that?
The bad phone ringing
Okay, so this makes sense it makes sense that you can't validate it and it makes sense that we should have a different verification procedure
Absolutely, so we'll we'll get on that. I'm not quite sure what we're gonna do or how we're gonna do it
But there is absolutely no reason whatsoever that you know an internal
Podcast which is not for the general public shouldn't be able to use pod safe music network as long as you just keep to the rules of reporting back to the network and
Putting a link in your show notes to the to the page. That's fine. In fact, I expect that to be a great resource of new listeners
Holy cow
Okay, so I know Chris Rockwell's listening to the show and we had some some conversations yesterday about
Pod safe music network
You know the the really the only final thing that we're
That we're waiting on for you know for rolling out our beta across the board for any artist that wants to participate
Is this damn email thing that I've been talking about and for those of you who missed it or didn't care the first time
It is kind of important
Because if you just want to open up shop right and just set up your own company or service or anything that
Requires email communication quite honestly. That's just about everything unfortunately. I'm not you know, I'm not a big fan of email
You have a very high likelihood of getting caught in the spam filters of ISPs
Most notably hotmail and MSN
Webmail
But also America online and others and now I I'd never really heard of this and of course we we have a couple of
What I call
Social engineers or virologists who we've hired Mark and Steven also known as the emo guys
And and they've dealt with this before and they say yeah, you know you got a sign up for a subscription to one of these
Services that contacts every single ISP and make sure is that make sure that your email address
Once they verify that because of course, you know, they're not gonna just say I come on in and
You're on the white list now if you're spammer. So there is a verification process and it's really a service, you know
And the service and I have to correct myself the the standard fee for the service from from the leading provider of these services
Comes with a hardware as well now so you could lock a definitely lock a large chunk of money off
But $80,000 is like the pre-negotiation price which
And and I'm and obviously if you want to be in business you got to pay for it
But you know the alternative is is to hire someone to go and and deal with that on an individual basis and I'm pretty sure that by now
Most of these larger ISPs
Don't even want to deal with it. So it does create a two tiered internet and what I'm seeing with this whole AOL email thing if if you haven't
If you haven't heard about this this is I think it's a part of this issue and and no other is this is not about spam
This is about
Opening up their own service to allow
Corporations to pay
For to have their email passed through now. I have a lot of thoughts about this
Um, first of all, I think that if we do have to pay to get your email
Even if it's just registration email or email that is
Shit, you know, whatever it is
Um, in fact, let me just you know, I just attend thoughts went through my mind. I mean, obviously
The future of communication with your customers is through a published subscribe mechanism like RSS
So let me let me just say that upfront if I want to communicate anything
It would be much easier and I guess we'll just have to start doing this. This is a good idea
Much easier to publish things through RSS. Okay, and that can even show up in your email box like outlook has
Excuse me. I am drinking one
You know, they're that what is it news gator or whatever it is you can get the plug in and and then the RSS information shows up in your email box almost as if it's email
so that would be the smart way to continue
You know to continue any type of conversation between a company and its customers
But there is that critical moment where you need to confirm someone's who they say they are and
I guess this is the whole you know central identification
Thing that we don't have in place anywhere yet which was
Microsoft's passport was kind of supposed to do that
So the only way we can really do that is through email and low and behold it's the same companies Microsoft who are now you know kind of making that difficult
So from a from a company perspective
I think it blows and it's and it's it's really open to
It's open to fraud, you know, I mean how easy is it to say oh well our spam filters trap your email and not that company's email
So you have to start paying us a quarter of a cent per message or $80,000 with a ongoing service fee of like 20% of that's as like
You know easily
15 to 20,000 dollars per year just to have your emails delivered. That's fucked up ladies and gentlemen. I'm sorry
That is just not okay
And this is not about protecting the consumer. They're still going to deliver shit to you
So you know, and I think it borders on unfair practices. It really does now
For pod show although this was not budgeted and believe me we run on a budget
You got to run a company on a budget
We had not now there's always miscellaneous stuff and there's always you know the budget is there to as a guideline to be reevaluated
So it's not that big of an issue, but come on. I mean this is just it's outrageous. It really is and I think that the internet
Particularly email
You know we should fight spam, but there should be a very easy way
To authenticate
Email that you're expecting if you register for a service and you and you're expecting a registration email you should be able to get that
I think your ISP is doing you a disservice in fact how interesting is this going to be for Earthling?
I got to talk to Earthling about this. I wonder what their policies. I have not seen them on any of these lists actually
It seems to be much more the the MSNs and hot males of the world and the AOLs
Interesting, but if you've probably seen this happen before and I've gotten tons of email from people saying wow
That's really funny because now I understand why I thought my software was broken my email software wasn't working
I registered for something and then I never got the registration email
Food for thought for sure
Oh boy, I'm gonna fit some stuff in today. Let me get this roll in first
Oh, yes, everybody
Feel free to sing along if you know the words to this jingle
As right it's time to talk about the biodiesel industry alternative fuels and of course my lovely vehicle
Which I didn't even start this time around the weather was so nice in San Francisco. I never fired Trinity up to see if you still work
Hopefully she is
Just one topic in today's Trinity segment. I Adam says Charlie Thompson discovered thanks partially to our local
Musical resident Willie Nelson that biodiesel is readily available for $2.84
Sense of gallon here in Austin, Texas, so I'm mixed up a 30% biodiesel mixture
Tail on the water so to speak and filled up my diesel tractor
Here's a link to my biodiesel sound seeing tour with the tractor
Thank you very much for getting me on the biodiesel jacks
So I'm gonna because it's a sound seeing tour I'm pulling down the music so you can really fully enjoy this because it's a good one
So crank up the earbuds jam it in your ear and check this out. Oh, it's a beautiful day to walk to the barn here in Austin, Texas
Okay, we're out here in the barn
With my three horses
And what we've done
Can you hear that horse
Yeah, give a big snort
What we've done is we've mixed a 30% mixture in the kabota 2500
tractor hands climb up on it
Turn on the fuel
So warm day probably don't even need to glow plugs
Sure, we're in neutral
Preflights complete
Let's see if she'll start
Oh
Marvelous
Okay, if you will cut there you go, okay Adam
So we're running biodiesel in the tractor around here and it smells much better
And we only use probably 30 gallons a year so this will do it
Okay, Adam, I'd just like to say in closing thanks for getting me on this jag of biodiesel and
We're gonna run a hundred percent a summer draws near and
Really enjoy the fact that the diesel just doesn't smell as much and that we're doing something good for the earth out here at the microarrange
So so long from Austin, Texas. Thanks over and out
Good free flight and post flight my friend excellent
Oh
You know what you said it was nice smelling and good for the farm and all that and good for the environment
But it's also good that we can know that we don't have independence on oil
Isn't this exactly what our president said?
I'm so proud of you. You're not doing this just
For Austin, Texas, not just for the farm not just because it smells good
You're doing it for America, my friend, and of that you should be very very proud
In a thank add-on for booping in her take
We got a podcast fight a war we've got the war of this what I call that was the war of the stalkers
Now it's a stalker throw down let's put it that way and I when I say stalker
I mean that really only in the virtual sense of people who show up on
Message boards and send in audio comments. Okay. I don't really well. I'm not too sure about Roger
So I played this bit from Roger Smalls yesterday who was talking about I think he said the comic shit blogger
But I'm pretty sure he meant comic strip blogger and boy CSB really went off on that on the on the comments on
at curry dot com you got to join in and see what's going on there
He's talking lawsuits and actually let me read this posting from
From the web blog Adam Curry you are just a mean nasty guy you play audio comment
I'm just I'm reading it verbatim obviously
Comics for blogger. I think it's from Poland lives in Germany, so his English kind of drops uh something here and there
But I understand totally so you you play audio comment from Roger Small
Comment that is slander about me, but you didn't play my totally innocent audio comments besides
Rogers accusations are pure lies of a retard the last time I was in the UK was January 1st
2006 and the only countries in which I was staying lately was Germany in Spain
I couldn't therefore be anywhere near your house which is in the UK Adam Curry you are utterly unfair
You obviously are not what you pretend to be on your podcast frown face frown face I hear by officially request
That you will issue a apology to me in your podcast stating that these accusations were false
Otherwise I will sue you due to violation of British laws racial and religious hatred act and the public order act in the UK
Oh
Man comic strip blogger chill out dude chill out
I'm and so what I did is I said you know dude why don't you just send me an audio comment
I guarantee did you make it the equal equal air time here? I'll make it the same length as
It's where Roger Smalls did I'm even gonna include it in the serious satellite stars cast
It's a new one we came up with the stars cast
Since we have a couple minutes to go
Ladies and gentlemen in the interest of equal time in the stalker throw down here on the Charlie
This is your um in the left in the red corner
In the blue corner we had Roger Smalls yesterday ladies and gentlemen in the red corner
In the red corner it is coming strip blogger
2006 and the only countries in which I would stay clay to a German and Spain
I couldn't therefore be anywhere near your house the UK
So for fuck's sake behave and I'm curious
I should have actually preface that by telling you that it was not family safe, but I think this show was pretty much
obviously not very family safe
Interesting tune there comic strip bloggers that pot safe and if so can you get someone to put that on the pot safe music now work?
I love to me. Did they have an old album of that stuff it reminds me of like
Durwood douche a dig at man very very cool. Oh no
There's another message round
Roger Smalls
Hello I've been Roger Hayer
I'm just so think out as scheduled for work at the moment and there's one thing when you want to meet you come around the cafe
Thank you
Badger
Okay
You know Roger I'm really busy this week and I think it would yeah, it's best that we that we meet on neutral terrain if you don't mind
So instead of me coming to your crib or the other way around I suggest you know what
It's it's interesting
Roger is getting quite a bit of notoriety around around the podcasting circles these days
And he showed up in the second
publication of podcast user magazine
He he wrote an entire article about his how he podcast and about him. I don't know if he wrote it specifically for a podcast user magazine
Or if they you know asked him if they could take that off his site
It looked like it was a screenshot of his Roger Smalls dog blogs bot.com website
So Roger
I thought it might be kind of fun since you're becoming such a celebrity for you to come and hang out with me at the Guardian Media Conference
Which I think is at the end of the month the March 27th I believe
I'm gonna put you on the guest list
You know almost like Elvis right you know Elvis is on the guest list at many many rock shows
So if you want to show up I'm make sure you're on the guest list as Roger Smalls just you know bring some bring a photo ID
And I'm I'm doing a panel there and we'll we'll hook up we'll hang out and it'll be kind of a neutral territory and we can you know kind of get to know each other
I hope you're okay with that
Those of you checking us out on serious stars one oh three soon to be one oh two Pacific Coast Hellway is next
Madge Weinstein follows that dawn and Drew and it's Thursday
So I think it might be Brian know with the Frank truth that's all coming here on the pod show on serious and I'll see you guys tomorrow
Those of you still hanging out here. Thank you very much got some more audio feedback a nice block for you coming up with some and also a celebrity
A celebrity podcast that I hadn't heard of yet, but I stumbled across yesterday email here from
Franco
He's from the rock cast Italia
Adam S. I. E. that is the Italian version of Ask Cap came out with a licensing scheme dedicated to podcasting fees changed depending on being
Commercial or non-profit length of podcast percentage of show time dedicated to music here the fees it's kind of interesting
And I'll also read Franco's response to the fees if you are non
If you're non-business that means non-promotion if you are non-business what does that what the hell does that mean?
Okay, so if I guess that means if you're non-commercial up to 500 downloads per week
If you use 25 if 25 up no more than 25% of your podcast is musical content you will pay
120 euros a year just add you know like 10% to make it dollars
If you have anywhere if you use oh my god
If you use excuse me if you use between 25 and 70%
Between oh god I'm butchering this if between 25 and 75% of your podcast is musical content
You will pay 440 euros a year now if you have up to
15,000 downloads a week and you're using no more than 25% musical content you pay 65 euros a month
And if you're in the 25 to 75% musical content range it's 85 euros a month
Now this apparently is for the non-commercial podcasts and there are limitations podcasts can not last longer than 60 minutes
You can't have more than 15 songs per episode or more than 75% musical content and you must separate songs with spoken words or comments
So Franco correctly says I'm a non-commercial
podcast or get between 701,000 downloads a week so I should pay 1,020
euros and of course there's 18% VAT on top of that a year
Just for the privilege of promoting Christina Aguilera. I would rather buy a PR 40 and valve compressor
Actually the PR 40 I just bought the compressor I will be buying soon and I'll continue to promote Matthew
Ebel the Bitties and Bro low they at least say thank you when I play him right on my brother
I'm fighting words and we love it in Italia rock cast Italia very cool man. Thanks
Feedback from Hank just listen to the court case podcast you know it gets me the most
You can't make the fact that Christina is endangered as the focus of the lawsuit
You had to get them via business copyright issues where did humanity go?
I know I know even alcohol had to be judged on tax evasion instead of murder
Racketeering and stuff like that so it's nothing new but it does make one thing. I hate it
Why can't you get the bastards on the thing that really matters? Well it would to me if or my child
I'm pretty sure as yours and Patricia's priority is well indeed Hank anyway
Just had to fire the thought off even if it probably gets lost in a few thousand other males
Take care fight the good fight
Thanks buddy
Didn't get lost. You know what's interesting though?
There's this organization called the EFF the electronic frontier foundation and they build
themselves or at least they have the image that they are an organization that fights for the rights of
Really a fights for online rights that have to say all digital and new media
They fight again. They petition and fight a lot and lobby a lot against stuff like the digital millennium copyright act
But you know twice now
I think that I've been in a position where there was something very important that was at hand
For the internet at large and the EFF is completely silent the first one was the MTV dot com domain name dispute
And I have I'm not going to go into it now, but I will say that I spoke to jump Harry Barlow in person
He is no longer with the EFF I believe and and I said you know dude
I need some help here
Yeah, well, you know, I'll bring it up somewhere and I'll talk to somebody and and you know the end of the day was they wouldn't help me
They would not it it cost me I think 4 450 thousand dollars
That one freaking lawsuit that MTV brought against me
And now with this lawsuit, which I think is critical particularly when it comes to creative comments and it's usage and and interpretation by
Mainstream or old old world media
You know where where's the Cory doctoral articles, you know, where's the outrage from the EFF?
It's not there because I don't believe they're on the same agenda as you and I my friends just wanted to point that out
A couple of Charlie's ago and oh great now it's being used as a time reference if you Charlie's back
We had a discussion
Where I
Said you know if you really want to create some outrage and I believe we should have some outrage if you want the same type of outrage about the war
Against terror being held in Iraq
In Iraq sandbox if you want the same type of outrage that we had in the United States that we had with Vietnam
The two wars are often compared to each other and for some very correct reasons and some very not correct reasons
But I understand the comparison the main difference is the main difference is that the media
Actually showed our young men and women
slaughtered on battlefields and
You know that is when the shit really hits home. That is the real truth. That is what war is about wars not about
IEDs in surgeons and numbers
Show what's really happening
That will that is going to change opinion and and and I'm not talking about the opinion of the American people
But of their representatives because
No-one wants bad PR and that would be considered the worst of all possible PRs and we know that
the government I'm not even sure who
tried to restrict the publishing of photographs of coffins of
Service men and women with flags draped over them arriving back in the US which eventually did get out
But that was the extent of it
So I'm so outraged that I feel everyone should see what this is really about
I'm old enough to remember the pictures and the the film reels that were was were sent in
very very different and I think very important to show it
And some people agree some people disagree and some people sit right in the middle of that
Hi Adam this is Rebecca with training rec radio
Yes, I know I don't have the ideal radio voice by the way your voice turns me on
many times if you've been told that by a train social woman and yes, I am the real deal
Anyway, I just wanted to comment on the discussion you started in Delta Sierra Charlie 338 about
Photos of soldiers getting killed being printed and released in the media
I would agree that photos of soldiers getting killed would be appropriate to be released only after the journalist has received
Consent from the family. Otherwise, I think it's just bad taste and
Disrespectful to the family of the fallen soldier
So anyway, that's my little two cents on that issue for those of you that want to see she mail porn
Do a Google search for the rest of you visit my website
Trannywreck.com
That's training with two ins at a y later beaches
Is that one word or two words?
She may
Thank you very much for the feedback. I like your voice by the way. I think it's enthralling
And she mail porn. Hey, you know
So I'm subscribed you got an opinion a dig it now something I came across
Two days ago and I it just blew my stack when I heard not just the fact that this guy is doing a podcast
He I don't even think he knows what a podcast is. I think he's calling it an audio blog. He's blogging his ass off
I really like that
I don't think I've met him personally, but I have played his music and his videos
over and over. I mean, I can do
I know all the lyrics. I'm sure that shit just is embedded. It's it's burned into my fucking brain because of wearing headphones cranking it up
Known the world over and unfortunately because of the image that he had and and what happened
He gets ridiculed a lot which I think is unjust because I think he's a very intelligent guy and I'm gonna play this is a two and a half minute clip
of
Not just an audio blog or a podcast, but also
The reasoning behind him starting a weblog and starting to do
Podcast. I'll just call it a podcast, but I don't even think there's an RSS feed for it. So
I'm happy to help him out
Happy to to get him rolling with you know feeds and items feeds and all that stuff and anything he needs and anyone like him
Because I think it's great that he's come into into our world
Ladies and gentlemen, MC Hammer
I recently spent some quality time with the
Very famous Hall of Fame football player. It was actually at the birthday party
Another famous Hall of Fame football player and he actually made a speech and what he said in his speech was
Really significant and profound. He said that he has been his entire life
Trying not to make any waves
You know trying to appease to the status quo and
Although he had achieved greatness in football and looking back at his life
He wished at the time that he had
Command of the spotlight and all eyes were on him that he also
would have said some things and done some things
That I will they would have called some waves
They may have made a difference in the lives of his people and in society
And what that being said and it's stuff with me and I I really applaud him having
You know the the courage to even say that but what that being said
The power of
blogging
We'll look back at it and it is a paradigm shift and unprecedented and
To be able to utilize a blogging to help further change
peace
to help
Fight against injustices and things like that. I
Want to be able to look back at all the blogs
I will do
And years to come and say that not only that we have fun with baseball and life and
Family and God
But also when some things needed to be addressed and needed to be said
That MC Hammer stood up and said them and
With that being said
I invite your comments
On history I won't give up on my life
Because I respect the comments and your thoughts
God bless MC Hammer
Cool is that that's a guy. I want to work with man
MC Hammer out
Wow, man excellent
Very very cool
Ha ha all right MC MC Hammer or just say hammer. I think what is he back to MC Hammer is this name Stanley?
I don't give a shit dude. We're right across the bay right across from Oak Town
Let me know. I'll drive Trinity up. We'll hang out
We'll pop some bottles. We'll make some plans. We'll save the world my brother
Welcome back to the Bank of America Stadium here in beautiful Charlotte North Carolina
Skip the details old Kirk here along with Sami slim gym McCoy
That's right skip man and what a humdinger of an energizer first half the panthers are up by one after a beautiful
Dr. Pepper power plant he get into the cocoa coal in zone
Then we'll just 10 seconds left on the energizer first half motorola clock and unbelievable toastinos two pointer to squeak past the cowboys
What an amazing Taco Bell moment and the incredible must see TV second quarter by the bias and the toastinos two point are also made the
Remington close shave play of the energizer first half
I can only hope that the dirt cell third quarter kicks off as exciting a McDonald's second half is the toastinos two pointer
Fitter's the must see TV second quarter of the energizer first half. I couldn't agree more
Skip and who looks like we need to wrap up the bull's ball half done report as the players are taking the ruffles turf here at Bank of America
Stadium to start the dirt cell Macy's McDonald's second half brought to you by Honda
Honda's 2006 accord hybrid more power less gas Johnson said to deal from the texipo diesel
Season that's the national comment podcast. I actually if you subscribe to the pod finder, which I think
I don't know if it kind of will release it today, right? Maybe we'll release it Tuesday. I'm not sure
I put that one in actually Chris McIntyre put that one into the into the pod finder episode number 17 just cracked me out
But I think it's actually broadcast on terrestrial radio, but they make this available as podcast and like yep, that's the mainstream media for you
And the amazing Kevin says hey Adam, I was just listening to the chart of this morning three four four and all about your chord case
What boggles me is it seems is the amount of celebrity you possess over there and you're up mind you
I live in Florida and I'm 35 so I'd recognize you if you walked down the street just from MTV in the afternoon
I didn't even remember your stint on head bangers ball Ricky Rackman occupies that space in my head for me
Hmm, I can see that you have a certain amount of celebrity even here, but I don't see enough to warrant
Abloid coverage this is what I don't understand unless Europe holds your past televised accomplishments and current
Untelivized and much bigger regard than America
Perhaps it's not necessarily you was Patricia celebrity or former celebrity that I'm unaware of
I'll be know her as your wife mother of your child on the occasional coho so help me out
Oh help a brother out here. I'm completely clueless now don't think I'm slamming you
Okay, I understand
Absolutely Kevin. Yeah, I should explain Patricia is
He's a little bit older than I am. I'm 41. I'll be 42 this year and should be 57 this year
She's currently 56 and she started her musical career in the Netherlands with a Dutch language-based hit very important
when she was 16 so that was 1834 and
She was just an amazing overnight celebrity success
And the Netherlands very very small country. I think they're probably only 11 million people living in the country at the time
And they are really constricted
Not by borders because they you know that borders on well if you cross the water on the United Kingdom
Belgium France Germany if you go up high enough Scandinavia, but by language
The only other place in the earth where Dutch is is a spoken language is well two places
There's a there's kind of a version of an in Belgium which would be flenish and there's a version of it in South Africa
Which would be South Africaans and all of us can understand each other, but it's it's definitely dialect
Then within the country itself there's huge dialect differences
So that's why
Local celebrities, you know really kick around a lot particularly for years up until the
Man up until the early 90s they only had two television stations
Two all government run radio stations with the same and then they opened that up and
Well, you know all the so my wife was just well known throughout when we
Hooked up so to speak in my space talk and we hooked up in
1982 no later than that. I'm sorry 1980
Should I don't know mid 80s mid 80s
She was still married so she was of course that we talked about that yesterday and I was on television and so it was like
It was like a perfect thing a perfect scandal to famous people age differences height differences all kinds of differences
And people just love that shit and when you have a very small country you need you know to sell magazines
Particularly if you got 10 15 of them now we have 15 commercial television stations same with radio
You can't just fill it up with stuff that you buy from entertainment tonight people want to know about local celebrities
We just don't have that many and it's a lot of them actually get created that probably don't deserve to be on television
But that happens everywhere these days and
What was amazing is even though we live in the US together for 14 years and rarely went back to the Netherlands
When we came back we found that our celebrity was still as large as ever
And we did what most celebrities do we
We tried to turn that to our advantage instead of running away from it and that of course
But gets only more and that's really one of the reasons why we left a year almost a year and a half ago is we're tired of it
You know, so we just want to come here and hang out and
They got our address and started publishing pictures of our house and well the rest of course
You know by now so that's what's going on there
But I would have to say that really it is Patricia who is the celebrity she has
Real credibility she has an amazing amazing bunch of different talents
She's done duets with everyone from
Tony Bennett to
Joan jet, I shouldn't do it with Joan jet. She was on Joan jet's album. She's been on you know all kinds of really hard rock albums
used to do those with the
Was it Babylon AD and stuff like that did those with the panties
And she's had her own TV show. She's been in these you know in the the European song contest
She's you know she's from the old school music business
Of the really 60s seven these and 80s and even in the 90s and she's also beautiful
Google Patricia pie and you'll see one of the
Four times she was featured in playboy magazine
The last time being when she was 50 and when you see it you'll say shit. Okay. I get it
Just briefly a couple things before I check out it here for today
Ricky Jervais the
Pay per play from audible and iTunes
Is apparently already available on bit torrent
That's kind of disappointing. I wish that the people would have respected
Respected that when I got a presumed that it's only a few people who are ripping it off but I hope that
The Ricky Jervais show will be just as forthcoming with the success of their show behind
The DRM firewall
As it is
As they were you know for their Guinness Book of World Records entry. I hope oh
And then a beautiful email from Laura clap Adam heard a rumor you played a little tune of mine on your kickass podcast
It made my universe. I would be all snazzy and send you some sort of audio. Thank you as per Matthew evil suggestion
But I'm still learning this whole podcasting thing bear with me. Oh, and thank you. I probably should have mentioned that first
I would come to Gilford in a heartbeat by the way. Oh, she did listen to the show didn't she?
I'm from Gilford Connecticut. So perhaps it would feel a bit like home
slightly colder and less yuppies but home like nonetheless. Yeah, so I'll be in Germany at the Frankfurt
Music Mesa from the 27th of March through April 2nd Patricia has performed there
She told me this morning when I read your email tour come hang out and watch me demonstrate a cool little toy called voice live
Or send some pod love my way. I'm so new to all of this but Matt is slowly showing me the light
We're playing two shows in Kansas City this Friday and Saturday at Bar Natasha
As a matter of fact, it promises to be mayhem and wonderment
You are fucking swabulous and I am in awe of your kind words for hey hey sister, which I did write with a wonderful writer named
DeVinson Williams
Hope to hear from you soon major props to your wife who tells it like it is and probably keeps your ass in line. Uh-huh
You bet Laura
I'd really love that song. I'm gonna maybe apply that play it again on tomorrow show it was and Patricia
I were actually singing it this morning and
You know, I did make kind of a little faux pas shouldn't have said
Charlotte Charlotte church has a chunky ass. That wasn't very nice of me kind of a big fan of Charlotte church too actually
So pathetic and then finally one of the
The new pod show network podcasts is getting a lot of heat recently. I've been following the strip
Which is the strippodcast.com
Let me see
On February 15th last Vegas more the this the strip podcast is about Vegas and it's
Produced in Vegas and there's a lot of shit going on in Vegas apparently
So on the 15th Steve win he's the big mogul in Vegas announced he was closing Avenue Q after nine months surprise move
But the strippodcast guys interviewed him
They have they have they're also reporters. I think Steve is a reporter so he wrote that for newsweek's website
But then
They post that a special edition about the interview in the strip there were a couple of big
Revelations in it including discussions of future plans for developing his property in Vegas
And all of a sudden this makes huge waves in the mainstream media
Local newspapers a grabbing up and basically this was a scoop from a podcast
New York post picked up the story and
Then they had these guys just keep going. This is really cool
In the in the episode after that of the strippodcast they had Las Vegas Congresswoman Shelley Berkeley on they asked her about her recent plastic surgery and
She went on at just a great length about her facelift last summer
But the story that took off
Check this through roll call the Capitol Hill newspaper
It did a big item on Monday because they noted and they compared the dates that she had skipped a vote on
Katrina relief in September
Because she was recovering from her surgery
So the strippodcast.com is definitely making some waves very proud to have them on the network and and creating all these scoops
They're showing up on like drug report and all kinds of crazy places so
Way to go guys. Hey, let's play one more pod save song before I get out of here, okay
I
Let me go, I'm not here to get a baby
Give me help, I'm gonna wear the water past the tree
And it's time you look at me, I'm gonna feel guilty
Because I'm bad, it's bad, it's bad
I won't let you touch me, it's bad, it's bad
I'm gonna be a little miss, it's bad, it's bad
I'm gonna be a little miss
It's never bad, it's bad, it's bad
And I hope that you can put the sand on me, I'll be coming
I won't let you touch me, it's bad, it's bad
I'm gonna be a little miss, it's bad, it's bad
I don't know man, I don't know, it's gonna go
And baby, baby, it's good, it's good
I won't let you touch me, it's time you look at me, I'm gonna feel guilty
Because I'm bad, it's bad, it's bad, it's bad
I won't let you touch me, it's bad, it's bad
I'm gonna be a little miss, it's bad, it's bad
And I hope that you can put the sand on me, I'll be coming
And you don't know, it's bad, it's bad, it's bad
And I hope that you can put the sand on me, I can feel guilty
And I hope that you can put it on me, I'll be coming
Even like that, if I figure out Adam and his life
Come on
Spring
spring
You can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you can't bear it, you
Yep, all types of music available on the pod save music network, if you're looking for cool tunes for your show, just sign up, cost nothing, just got a report back to the network, that's all, we even reported to the artist for you, and as we start to roll out the unlabel, there's even more ways for you to help support your favorite artists through the sale of unrestricted MP3s, use it.podshow.com, that's it everybody tomorrow, we will have a full blown thank god it's Friday edition of the show Metro Sexual Month,
and the moment will be a part of that daily source code.com is where you can find the podcast feed and where you can find new episodes and anything else, check out curry.com and of course there's the show notes, wiki, show notes, that info, add them at curry.com is where you can reach me if I can wait through all the crap that I get in my Gmail, I'll see you tomorrow everybody, thanks.