Delta Sierra Charlie 34-0.
The $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
The next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic, it's a battle curry.
Hey everybody, it is time for the Charlie.
Some different today.
You've probably read somewhere in a newspaper or more likely you've seen on television.
The bird flu is coming.
But I don't know much about it.
I was lucky enough to find out that our investors are one of our investors in pod show and
smaller burkins.
Can tell us a lot more about it and are actually doing something about it.
So I thought I'd share that today with you on the source code.
And we're going to get to that.
Well right after we hear from our friends over, or a think of course.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
We're our flank.
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers.
We're Earthlink.
We believe your personal information should be just that.
Personal.
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe.
We're Earthlink.
Make this smart choice.
Visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
Joining the conversation on the Charlie now
is bookbires.
The B in cleaner perkins.
Callfield and buyers.
And Dr. Beth Sidenberg of Biocrist Pharmaceuticals.
Both are on the board of directors of the pandemic preparedness and bio defense fund, which
was announced last week.
I thank you both for taking the time to talk about this.
So I was in New York last week.
And I read the announcement in New York Times.
And it blew me away.
Mainly because all of a sudden this thing became real for me.
We're talking specifically about avian flu or the bird flu.
Here's a group of very smart people who I guess believe that something is probably going
to happen or it's inevitable and putting their money where the mouth is so to speak.
Maybe I should start with Brooke with you.
Can you just explain, what exactly?
This is a $200 million fund.
What does that mean?
Is there already?
Is there $200 million that you are now starting to invest?
Does this money already exist?
How exactly does that work?
What is an investment fund, I guess, is what I'm asking?
Sure, Adam.
So yes, our firm, client-approved, and call to the buyers, is a venture capital firm based
in Manlo Park, California.
And we have raised and completed that process.
$200 million fund specifically targeted toward what we call pandemic preparedness innovation.
And the reason we're doing this is to call attention to the severity of the problem.
And our belief that more attention needs to be paid to innovation gaps in preparing for
pandemic pathogens and global public health issues.
And by innovation gaps, what we mean are vaccine, any viral, and diagnostic products that are needed
by the world that are just not getting developed quickly enough.
So this is the thing that almost troubles me when I think about this.
And clearly when you get into the business of investing, other people's money as well into this area,
that means that you are expecting this to work.
I presume that that's kind of funny.
Will the fund be successful if the flu actually breaks out, or if we actually need something,
or am I seeing that a little too short-sighted there?
Well, the innovations that are needed in vaccines, any viral drugs and diagnostics,
are ones that are platform technologies.
So we hope a pandemic never happens, even a mild one.
If it does, the world is going to need these innovative products to make it as less severe as possible.
If a pandemic does not occur, these kinds of innovations, these kind of products,
can be applied to other infectious diseases as well.
And it's very fortuitous for our firm that last spring, Dr. Bestseinberg joined us as a partner here at
Clienter Procus, Coffield and Buyers.
And she brings the background of 25 years of product development experience at the
National Institutes of Health, Mer, Crystal Myers, and Amgen.
And so Beth, one or two come in on this.
Okay, great. Thank you, Brooke.
Yeah, Adam, I think that it's important for us to recognize that influenza is a great example of what we call emerging
or an emergent infectious disease, meaning something that occurs and can change on an annual basis
and create disease in millions of people.
In order to really understand the disease that's developing,
you need to be able to see it coming in the environment, you know,
so in a specific country, be able to diagnose it with rapid tools and then treat it and prevent it.
And technology needs to be flexible, needs to be able to be applied quickly,
and made available to people around the world.
And flu gives us an opportunity to focus on those types of innovations and technologies,
and apply them to other infectious diseases if they were to occur.
Okay, so a lot of the media talk now, which I actually despise it because all they're doing,
I feel is just freaking people out and not even talking about possible solutions other than this so-called
stockpile of Tammy flu or whatever it should be available.
Actually, I lived in Belgium for about five years, and I think it was two years ago,
what they were calling the bird flu, swept through continental Europe,
and actually we were only one kilometer outside of the quarantine area,
and we actually had officials come by and investigate,
we had a family of like six black swans, and, you know, they were ready to quote,
call them if necessary, and one of my neighbors was working on a lot of the calling,
and he actually got, I guess, the bird flu, which I presume that, you know,
that is indeed possible that you get this from birds, and he was really quite ill.
He, you know, he was okay.
Are we really talking now about the, you know, a pandemic or the one that everyone is talking about,
and I'd love to talk about some more, you know, just bio-defense in general,
is it, is it the tipping point where it spreads from human to human,
and is that something that is a reality?
You know, Adam, I think the way to look at this is,
there, if you think about the birds, whether it's, you know, swans or chickens,
or just any kind of migratory bird, consider them the natural reservoir for influenza.
It's not uncommon that these birds carry flu,
and the key question and what we're worried about is, will the virus change
when it replicates, when it makes more of itself, will it change to a form
that will allow it to be infectious, not only from birds to people or birds to pigs, for example,
but from person to person.
And the only way that that can happen is when it's making more of itself,
the virus, and it's called replication, it has to make a mistake,
and change or mutate that virus to a form where then it becomes highly infectious
from person to person.
Is it possible for that to happen?
Absolutely.
Can we predict when it will happen or the probability of that happening?
We can't predict that.
We do know that annual flu often goes through that process.
Birds, or the reservoir, it goes into what you consider a mixing vessel
or another kind of intermediary species, which is a pig,
and then it can be transformed or mutated into a form that infects person to person.
So KPCB is really known for a lot of its technology investments
certainly in the recent decade.
The technology, as I understand it, of creating vaccines,
is actually antiquated, maybe not the right word,
but you still use chicken eggs to actually develop anti-virus matter?
Well, that's right, Adam.
The way vaccines are made today are in eggs.
I mean, literally tens of millions of them.
And that's where the vaccine that we all get, hopefully everyone,
listening gets every year for what we call the seasonal flu.
And that vaccine contains the best guess by public health experts
each year of three strains that were probably going around the world.
But that technique has not been replaced.
So that's part of the innovation gap set that we were talking about.
And so what we're doing with this new funding is we're searching worldwide
for innovators, young companies, inventors, and scientists,
who are developing ways of making vaccines and cells.
So, so-called cellular production.
Or even beyond that, not in cells, so a DNA-based vaccine.
And the advantage of these is, first of all, they don't use eggs,
which would be problematic, a baby, and flu breaks out human human.
And secondly, these production techniques allow a shorter time
of response, what we call surge capacity.
So instead of the current six months it takes to scale up a lot of vaccine doses
for the world, it could take literally six weeks,
or maybe even shorter.
And then also new vaccine production techniques
and product development techniques, formulation, and so on.
We call it would allow vaccines that are more exquisitely immunogenic,
which means less can be given to a person to protect them.
In the antiviral space, there is Tamiflu, which is a good drug,
but we don't know how will it would work against
really strong new viruses that come out.
It works okay against the seasonal flu,
but against avian flu so far in Southeast Asia.
It hasn't worked so well in humans.
And so there is some new antivirals that are being developed.
We want to invest in those and encourage the development of them
by our capital as well.
So, as a broken obvious question is,
in the grand scale of preparedness and defense against anything
in today's world, you know, $200 million
with all respect is chump change.
If you just look at what we're spending on the war against terror.
Is this, I mean, is that enough?
If it's, and if it's only $200 million,
why isn't the government doing this type of funding
and working hard or NGOs or any other organizations
besides venture capital?
Well, they are as well.
So, there are a lot of people working on this problem.
The United States Federal Government works on it
from a variety of points of view.
The National Institutes of Health has an allergy and infectious disease
division that funds research.
But, and so does the HHS and the CDC,
Health and Human Services and Centers for Disease Control.
But, their role as government is to encourage research
to fund some of it.
Government doesn't develop products.
The private sector does that.
And so, our $200 million will go to that
to developing the products that then go out
into the public health system.
Now, as your question of a quantitation of that
or size of it, generally when we invest in a company,
there are other investors who will follow our lead.
And so, usually, there's a four or five
to one multiple on that.
So, we estimate that.
So, our investing will probably lead to about a billion
dollars of investment in these companies.
So, then, there's two obvious questions that arise.
One is, so let's say the fund produces one or more
technologies or products that actually are effective.
That has the capability, of course, of making the investors
and the fund in these products wealthy beyond their wildest dreams.
And there's always the question of, well, is it made affordable
for everyone can, you know, will it only be a certain segment
that then kind of access to this technology or this medication
to actually survive an outbreak?
Is, you know, how do you look at that?
Well, it's way more complicated than that.
First of all, I don't think in infectious diseases
or anyone gets wealthy beyond their wildest dreams.
Because there's a desire just as you said
to get these products out to everyone.
In the developed countries, the drugs like this
would be priced at a rate, what we call a reasonable price.
And then it's our goal to have these drugs available
in the less developed countries at cost or some other method
of getting it to them so that this can be a worldwide phenomenon.
And it's important to think as Tom Friedman says the world is flat.
It's especially true in infectious diseases
because with worldwide travel and how people move around today
and infectious diseases starts in one country
really is local to every country in the world.
Beth, I believe that part of the fund has already been allocated
towards your work.
Could you tell me what you're doing?
Yes, sure, Adam.
So one of our first investments is in a company called Biocrist,
which is a drug discovery company that has an important
antiviral agent called Paramavir.
We believe as Brooke mentioned that it's very important to have
multiple options to choose from when if there is a diagnosis of flu
in your ability to treat patients.
Paramavir is a similar mechanism to Tamiflu
and it can be given intravenously.
So in particular for patients who are very ill and in the hospital
parameter we hope will be a very important therapeutic option.
Now let's just say there's no pandemic or maybe just a very mild one.
I presume we don't lose.
I presume the investments are for long term and not just a short term.
Oh my gosh, the black death plague is coming.
Is this all for the long term?
Yes.
This is not dependent upon anything bad happening.
Sure.
Yeah.
So venture capital is really a 10 year horizon on investing.
That's true in all technology and science areas.
It's especially true in this one.
And as I mentioned earlier, so a new vaccine production technique for flu
or avian flu or new strains of that would be applicable to new vaccine technology
production methods for hepatitis and herbysimplex and many other kinds of diseases
respiratory viral diseases that are around today.
It's important to remember that there are over 20 new infectious pathogens that have emerged
since 1970 in the world, HIV being one, of course, that's been devastating in this tragic.
We haven't talked about diagnostics and that's another area that's very important.
There is, for example, today, no rapid diagnostic test that can be used point of care
to determine if someone has avian flu.
It's possible to go in right now and get a rapid test to see if you have the annual flu, but not avian.
What's the incubation period of the avian flu?
What's the incubation period?
Well, that's an interesting question.
The incubation period, it doesn't show symptoms so far on avian flu for at least seven days,
but the person can be infectious by the second day.
So a person could be walking around in the infectious state, but not be symptomatic.
So there's a need for a test that could be done by an untrained technician with agricultural workers
or at an airport check-in facility or something like that.
So the sick people will know that they're sick and healthy will know that they're okay.
And then you would know who to give like aggressive antiviral therapy to.
If you read the paper today when they take the samples that you read about in Turkey or Iraq or India now or wherever,
it takes days to get confirmation.
So that's a second diagnostic test that's needed.
There would use less technology of instruments in a special lab and more out in the field.
Well, that does sound like your first line of defense is identification within timely manner, I agree on that.
Just moving on to the bio-defense part of the fund.
Whenever I read the word defense, I immediately think of aerospace and defense and I think war.
Is that how I should interpret that?
No, the way we think of that is that these are infectious pathogens, regardless of the delivery system.
So what works for public health works sort of across the board?
Excellent.
Well, I guess the only thing that's left is to stay close to you guys and real happy.
Because if something breaks out, you know I'm going to be living in your basement.
Well, you're welcome too.
And just break that car.
Yeah, we'll we'll turn it by.
But so I just in general, just as a final question, should we really be,
I mean, this is great to hear.
I'm really happy to know that there, you know, at least understand some of the work that's going on,
and even understanding about, you know, the identification in a timely manner,
and knowledge of if someone is infected, is all the fear that is being built up now,
particularly on television.
Is it warranted?
And I guess that's the best question.
Is it really warranted?
It feels like this thing is just around the corner.
And now in the United Kingdom, it's like, you know, bring all the birds in because it's coming.
It just feels like, you know, it's being whipped into a frenzy almost.
Well, Adam, I think that there's reason to worry because the virus that we've seen that's infected people directly from birds.
Is a very, very, very, very severe type of infection that develops in people.
And so there is reason to have careful evaluation, increased surveillance and diagnosis,
whether it's in the birds or people.
And I think that, you know, the silver lining for us here is being prepared,
and moving innovation forward in this area of emerging infectious diseases is going to be a very good thing for the population at large for the global,
for the world, whether we have a pandemic from an avian flu or not.
We're going to modernize with vaccine business.
We have an opportunity to have better diagnostics and better therapies for people.
And we think it'll make an important contribution.
Well, I appreciate both of you taking the time to explain some of this to me today.
And definitely, you know, keep me updated on progress.
Brooke, if someone's listening right now and thinks, you know,
Wow, you know, I have an idea or I have a plan.
I mean, how do they reach out to you?
Oh, they just go to the our website www.kpcb.com.
Okay, and then I'd like to know if you've ever considered doing a podcast,
because you've got a great voice, Brooke, you'd be perfect for one.
Well, I'm just trying to be like you.
Got to grow the hair man, that's all.
Best side in Bergberg by us.
Thank you very much.
And let's definitely keep in touch on this and see where it goes.
I'm sure the audience would love to be updated as well.
And if you feedback, I get from all past on you guys.
All right, thank you.
Thanks, Adam.
Well, I don't know, but you guys, are you freaked out by that?
Or not?
I'm still a little bit confused about how I should feel about this pending pandemic that is upon us.
And by the way, this was the first time that I used Cas Blaster with Skype.
And I'm pretty happy with the result.
I mean, we did all in one go.
No glitches, everything sounded pretty cool.
Although, you know, a lot of room noise, man.
I never noticed that when I shut up and when someone else is talking,
it's like you can hear the whole condo kind of breathing, breathing upon you.
And a couple of lighter clicks there in the background,
but considering the topic, I think it was necessary.
So this is just a temporary format change for the Charlie.
I just wanted to mix it up a little bit.
You know that I'm working on getting my Uncle Don in.
I don't think he'll fit in 20 or 30 minutes,
we'll probably have to do a series of Uncle Don conversations,
which I might have to edit, because you know,
what is it?
It's like 50 years of life in Washington and in politics,
and not just in Washington, but in Asia.
Gosh, I should have asked him about the avian flu as well.
Anyway, so that turned out pretty successful.
Those of you interested, the way I did it with Casplaster is using two sound cards,
and I just routed Skype through a different sound card,
and it went through the mixer,
and came back into Casplaster so that worked out perfectly.
If you're listening to us on serious stars 103,
soon to be moving to channel 102.
So I think that's coming up in a week or so,
as we move just a little bit closer to God,
as we can move closer to the Stern channels on 101.
You've got Pacific Coast Hillway coming up next.
After that, it's a Madge Weinstein Donandru Gilmour Daily.
Today, maybe, DVD weekly, or which at all.
I'm not quite sure what's coming up.
And of course, I'm pod save music.
We do that every single week,
after noon between 6 and 10 Eastern 3 and 7 Pacific.
Tomorrow I'll be back right here with more daily source code.
We'll get back into some music.
And we'll finish out the week,
because I'm hurrying up, getting a lot of stuff done.
So I can go back home.
I'll see you, everybody.
Bye-bye.
Another pod show pod guest.
Stick it in your ear.