Delta Shara Charley 3-1-8
He very careful with this podcast, experimental technology is in use
And change your life again
But we're doing it more
And I think it is because
We're all times like your turn
It's for you
I don't know what I'm doing
I don't make it hard
But I don't want to know
It's for you
Let it go go go go go
Let's see what this should matter
It's for you
Let's see
I don't want to go no more
But if you're getting better
All right
You're close my heart
Oh
Everything I want is for you
It's for you
I don't make it hard
But I don't want to know
It's for you
I don't want to go
Everything I want is for you
It's for you
I don't want to go
I don't know
It's for you
Because of the reason you stay and get married
And everything I wanted is for me
And some of the mistakes and everything
I don't what I'm doing, I'm making less
But I don't want no face to live
Because of the reason you stay and get married
And some of the mistakes and everything
I don't what I'm doing, I'm making less
But I don't want no face to live
Pot's safe, my little radio waste another night
From the pot's safe music network, hey everybody
How you doing halfway through the week
It's Wednesday
And nothing better than a hump day to start
Experimenting with some of that pod show technology
Let me explain what I'm doing
You know that we've got all the new stuff rolling out
We're going into beta and lots of products and services
And lots of cool stuff that's going on
That's right, radio stations in your laptop
Broadcasting by the pot casting
Let me start off with a couple of audio comments
And then I'll get straight into what I'm doing today
First one from Peter Snakers
Let me see, I hope I'm not bothering you with this
But I noticed on your podcast the sound of your voice sounds watery
Like something's wrong with your vocal cords
The distortion in the sound in the mids through the high range
I'll say not too high
It's really noticeable when you say something with a long eye sound
Or when you
Other sounds, Brahms and music seem to sound fine
I've heard the compression might cause this
In this case, probably only in the frequency range of your voice
Well, I hope it's me or my setup
Still enjoying your show and the Brahms
Keep it up, Pete Snakes
Well, wait, let me read the second one
Hold on a second
I'll tell you this is from Chris May
I'll just move this window over just a tad
That's actually
Hold on bear with me now
You'll find out what I'm doing here in a moment
I must be one of the rare listeners that is not had any problems with your feed through iTunes
And I've been listening since late spring
However, I've noticed that every now and then you play music on the DS
The audio will skip forward through that throughout the song
The most recent example was today's episode 317 with my life
During the 34th minute of Delta Sierra Charlie
The audio skips no less than seven times
Think about it further
Just happen while you were talking a couple of weeks ago
Something else to look into, I guess
Hopefully someone else has reported it
I'll try to send you another note if I notice it again
You're pushing me closer and closer to starting my own podcast every day
Especially with the car testing podcast idea
Man, that would be fun
Totally
Especially since there's an absence of information for what cars
Tall people would enjoy
Well, that's interesting
That's very true actually
Tall people like myself
Vertically challenged as I like to say
It do have problems with automobiles
If I have to take new and use cars out for spin on some of the back roads around Virginia
And I think I can make that sacrifice
Yeah sure, gotcha
Okay, so I got so fed up with all these audio problems
Which were I'd have to say
I'm not all necessarily the fault of the Mac
But the shortcomings of the Mac that I was using
And let me just preface by saying
I've been a Mac user all my life
I love Mac and Tosh
I love Apple
I actually I love my new power book
But I was really really hating these sound problems
Now the first problem
Regarding the audio
So there's really this three problems
First of all the the warbling of my voice
That could very well be compression
I've done some testing with this new setup
Which I'll talk about in a second
And it may be better
We'll just have to work on that
But that is probably a combination of
What MP3 can do with sound
Because it remember it's not a lossless format
It's compressed so you are losing stuff
And it's probably chopping shit out of my extremely low vocal cords
Skipping of recording
Well we've had a lot of that
That's the audio hijack pro
And when you're reading and writing to discs
And doing all kinds of stuff
It's sometimes it actually reported
It'll say skipping
But that is definitely a problem that has occurred
And of course the infamous now infamous audio skipping
That Apple does acknowledge
But they're fixed so far as being to run
Only one audio application at a time
Which is just a non-starter when it comes to podcast
Because you have to have at least two open on your machine
One to record
And one to play back audio
So I was
A combination of things
First of all I wanted to really do a full end to end test
Of our podcast delivery network
Anyway I did
I went out this morning
Right after I got up and did my things
And I drove down to Best Buy
And bought me a new PC
That's right
I got a Windows machine here
Slap top
This is a Toshiba Portage A
And it's ultra ultra thin ultra ultra light
All I was looking for really was something that was reasonably small thin light
Then I could just pack away
That I wouldn't care about too much
You know I'm not going to use this as my main computer
But I am going to use it
For cast blaster
Because I'm back on the cast blaster
Got to tell you
And I'll actually have to be honest
I have not looked at cast blaster for quite a while
Because you know the craplet
Really was the wrong purchase
I bought it at the time for cast blaster
It's a
A vera tech I think is what it is
Piece of shit basically
That's simple
The shitty sound card
So I was looking something with a good sound capability
With a PC slot
Because I knew that I would want to have an additional sound card
So I got a creative lab sound blaster PC card
Which just looked right into the slot
And I've been playing with this thing
A little bit today
But really for the past hour configuring everything
And wow it's really cool
Because you can set it up now
Cast blaster mic is on a whole bunch of different things
You can set it up
We're using an external mixer
As I'm doing
It has an emboard limiter
There's no latency when you listen to it
And it's almost impossible to overmodulate
Now it is possible for me to overmodulate my mixer
So we have to I'm kind of keep my eye on all different
View meters and making sure that everything's kind of staying in the safe zone
But it still could happen
But the limiter basically stops you from being able to distort the sound on the recording
Now the cool thing about cast blaster is that it ties into the podcast delivery network
So now you enter your show notes in cast blaster
You record in cast blaster
You describe your show
And it actually if you're logged into the podcast delivery network
You can have multiple shows on the pdn
And it'll let you select which show and it'll change all the values automatically
And you just hit one button click and you're done
It sends off show notes to your show site
It sends off the MP3 file
Kind of does despite everything automatically
It truly is one
Well there's no step three
Let's put it that way
One record two
Publish there is no step three
Yeah go check your shit
See if it worked
That's really it
And so far I've been playing with a little bit and I really digging it
I think now cast blaster mic is on vacation
He's packed away and some shed in the UK where he always goes
And he's completely income unaccado and unreachable
Which is cool
Everyone's entitled to a vacation
But it's too bad he couldn't witness this
I know he'd be jazzed
So the only thing left for cast blaster
As far as I'm concerned
I'd love to have a MIDI control surface
That would be so cool
Because you can control all the faders and everything
Through keyboard commands
But it would be very cool if we had
If you could just have
Maybe three faders
That you could control
What's going on on the software through MIDI
And we've talked about that before
Maybe he's ready for it by now
But I'm pretty jazzed with what I'm seeing
When I bought a new license myself
Am I owned a
Of course, I couldn't reach him
I couldn't get a free license key
But it well worth it
Oh man, fantastic
So the way I've got it routed now
Oh actually I figured something else out
This is where my tea here
I figured out how to record Skype as well
And you can do it with two sound cards
So there's of course as a built-in sound card this thing has
But then with the additional sound card
And the mixer
I found out how to record Skype calls
And I can actually send a mix of
What's being played back down the line
To the person on the other end
Listening to Skype
So they wouldn't actually hear me through the microphone
In the PC or an external mic
They actually hear the output of the mixer
So
Kudos to mic
And everyone had cast glass at our calm on the forum
And the forum moderators
And everyone providing feedback
I guess what are we up to now
Beta 51
Getting very close to what I would say
Is something that's spot on
Just a quick
Administrative note
For those of you who thought I would show up in Atlanta
Yesterday or today, sorry
Yesterday the day before actually
It didn't happen
I'm really sorry
I was able to email a couple people back
Who would really wanted to hook up
If we had gone, it would have been a very short turn around anyway
But the meeting has been postponed
So
Which was actually good
Because it was Martin Luther King's birthday
It was the wrong day to have any type of meeting
Now of course, I was also
Wigning about wanting to
Meeting to go to Australia yesterday
This is a bit
How many thousands of you just thoughts in sale?
Let's see
In Delta Shara, Charlie 317
You talk about going to Australia
This immediately reminded me of a guy who's built his own
747-400 cockpit
Powered by that simulator I told you about
PS1
Every year, this is from
Mr. Meers
Every year in November a couple of guys and girls apparently
Meet there to do world flight Australia
Assimulated flight around the world to raise money for the flying doctors
Maybe you could get
Matt to put you on the pilot roster for a flight pilot roster
To fly a leg or two
Okay, I'm going to get in the 747-400
Sim and fly this thing
Also, there's sound seeing flights over Antarctica
From a few cities in Australia
Around New Years
Very cool
He says, I don't think that alone would be worth a long flight
But unfortunately
What was he saying?
Oh, he would love to go to the Antarctic flights
Antarctic flights, but doesn't have the dough
Okay
Um, that's not really a business reason
But it's certainly an interesting one
That's for sure
I got another
Australia comment here from Jack Sauer
Uh, excuse to come to Australia
And excuse to come to Australia
Sorry, and a business reason to come here
Would be to come over to Adelaide to check out the podcast
Magazine
Uh, try promoting podcasting in Melbourne, Sydney, and Perth
If it's worth it, let me know
We should catch up for a Sensei
Uh, Jack, are you the guy that's putting together the podcast magazine?
Uh, definitely let me know what's going on with that
That could be, that could be almost construed as a business reason
If you can get one or two more business reasons
Then I might be able to make that trip
It would be nice, you know, Sydney, Melbourne, Perth
And then I guess I'm already halfway home, right?
Check this out
Well, I guess our good buddy Roger heard the call
Uh, heard the jingle, the Jeff Smith put together for him
And he sent in this little ditty for us
I was just wondering what you smell like
You're thinking
Uh, let me smell
Hold on, Roger, let me smell myself for you, baby
I actually smell pretty fresh after
After only a few hours of this day
Um, but to be quite honest, Roger, I think you would much more prefer
To come over to San Francisco and walk the hallways of the condo
Because you know, it's only me in the curry condo
And then in this building, there must be 300 Asian women
And they all walk up and down the hallways with damp hair
Because of course, we have a spot on a pool and everything
And they walk around a t-shirt with damp hair
Because I'm so much taller than they are in the elevator
And I just kind of hover above them and
I gotta tell you, it smells really, really, really good
Yeah
Hello, Adam and friends, this is Michael Odee from the most people are DJ's podcast
And soon I'm going to be part of the Pod Show Network
I podcast is a show where everybody's a critic and most people are DJ's
That's a lyric by the great band, the whole study
And that's also a description of being a music and media fanatic
After doing zines in the 90s and making countless CD compositions
With podcasting, I finally found a way to let people know about great indie music
And fringe pop culture stuff
And I've been doing it for nearly 30 shows
I'm excited about joining Pod Show and maybe even quitting my day job
So look for most people or DJ's on the podcast Network soon
By the way, the music in the background
In what track are you called, looks on tape
Right on
Most people are DJ's joining Pod Show, congratulations
Great to have you on the network
And you too will soon enjoy the luscious sounds of cast blaster
Connecting everything
Oh man, good times for sure
I guess every single day this week we're going to be able to announce a new podcast
Joining the Network with this is very cool, we've been doing a lot of stuff here
Hello, that's a spike on the mic
And you're listening to Adam Curry's daily source code
Okay, one drawback is if you don't listen and remember exactly what everything is
Then you just might miss the cues
There's got these little jingle I actually should have put that in a different player
In cast blaster, you can basically put anything anywhere you want
But the longer players have a countdown timer and the short ones
Which are really meant for jingles and effects and stuff
Have no countdown timer, I kind of wish they did though
Although I understand I do kind of also understand what Mike is saying
That that does mess up the interface somewhat
Okay, got to think about that, got to work on it
Well, you know what, let's just do it again and pretend it never happened, okay?
Hello, this is Spike on the mic, and you're listening to Adam Curry's daily source code
Hey Adam, this is, let's just say Louis
I'm the producer of the quasi-to-week connection podcast
Hey, thanks for playing our promo the other day
Anyway, I want to offer a little tech tip to your audience
Particularly those folks who use iTunes to aggregate and listen to their podcasts
Let me first say that iTunes is on sure you'll agree broad podcasting the masses and for that
I plot Apple
I will say however that once you search subscribing to more than a handful of podcasts
Listening to them with any efficiency and iTunes becomes a chore
I thought I'd offer a tip for setting up what I like to call a podcast radio station in iTunes
What you want to do is create a smart playlist in iTunes
Name it whatever makes sense
I call mine podcast playlist
On the first line of the smart playlist dialogue
Select podcast and then select is true
Over to the right click the plus sign to add another rule
On the second rule select play count
And is and then enter the number zero into the final field
Lastly at the bottom of the smart playlist dialogue
Make sure that the live updating box is checked
That's it
Once you've done that
You'll have a smart playlist you can listen to every day
And it will only contain those episodes that you've not yet heard
Once they're played they drop out of the playlist like magic
Now you can of course add more rules to this playlist for the refinement gets added
Or take specific podcasts out of the daily rotation
Anyway, thanks for your time
And be sure to check out the closet totally connection at
www.closetoolie.com
Or look up closet holy and iTunes
Later
Thank you very much
Yeah, that's actually how I do it
A smart list that I created which I call the podcast list
And and I like it because it gives you reverse chronological order if you sort it by date
Which by the way you have to select under views
You have to add that as a
As a column in your in your iTunes view
It's too bad that isn't on by default
And they don't even have a
I agree I've subscribed to a whole bunch of podcasts and so much easier just to go
Start at the top, you know, so what's going on now
I don't have the play count set in
Because I believe well first of all I stop and I start stuff all the time
Well actually
I wonder
If you stop it midway
Will it then still give you a play count?
Probably when you probably have to listen to the whole thing before it gives you a play count
I'll have to look into that
If you're in the Bay Area
And
Looking for some fun work
Today
Had a meeting with
Just Sue
And we've got a job opening
And we can take you right now
If you're a flash
Programmer
We have people who can program flash and design and flash
But I guess that this is like a hot
Hot area or something like that
There's just a lot of requests
It must be the whole web 2.0 thing
Everyone's hiring flash and java script
Developers so anyway
Looking for a flash programmer
Action script
To expert
Proven experience using
Using action script to core classes
Ability to create new classes
Wow
Experience using
Action script to components and events
And create clips that interact with dynamic content
Examples are PHP XML
And oh also if you have any experience with creating
Streaming media players
Then you're in luck
But you got to hurry up because we'll be closing this
Opening very very soon
Just fire off an email to Sue at podshow.com
I promised I was going to broadcast her email address
Because
She hasn't filled this job like she said she would
Damn it
Sue with podshow.com
Let me see
Actually so we have a pretty big day ahead
Got a board of directors meeting
And oh man
So it sucks so bad
We had everything all set up
Because the office is almost done
You know the doors are in and you know
Miner stuff like that
And we had the conference room which has doors
But no panels in the doors yet
You know nice lighting
And we got the coffee machine and everything's kind of ready
And we were going to have the board directors meeting
At HQ this month
But word came down from the mountain
That Muhammad just ain't going to move
Yeah, it's like coordinating
What is it six people seven people
I don't know it's usually pretty big meetings
Just wasn't possible
So unfortunately we'll have to drive to Sand Hill Road
It's kind of funny because I'm threatening to take Trinity
In fact I want to take Trinity
And I but
No one seems to want to let Ron and myself
Both drive in Trinity
To any meeting because you know
They're afraid that we won't drive
Which is so unfair although I did get a warning light
As I was pulling into my parking space in the garage
Here at the condo
I got a warning light and I looked it up in the
It looked like a break light but it was amber
It wasn't red
And it looked like I guess the front break pads are wearing thin
So break pads will be needed
Very soon
Maybe the bio bio basis fuel guys
And bio fuel oasis guys
And Berkeley can hook me up with that
Can you imagine
I just want me to just go to a number of satis garage
Just pull in
Sound seeing two of the whole thing
And say hey man here I am this is my rock and ride
It's just a thought
Hey you got something new for
The satellite folks a new sound
Which means we're leaving y'all
And we'll be back tomorrow
Pacific Coast Hellway is next for you
Listen to us on serious stars 103
Yeah
Oh man
The sound was kind of indirect
Because
As a mistake on my part
It's routed to the other sound
The other sound card and it went out to my
Logitech MM50 speakers
But you got the idea right
So now it's just us all of us on the podcast
Do you believe anything is possible
We do
We're our flank
We believe in an internet that's safe from virus
His and scammers
We're Earthlink
We believe your personal information
To be just that personal
And we believe your internet
Should be a friend
Not a fo
We're Earthlink
Make this smart choice
Visit earthlink.net
And discover what our internet experts can do for you
Earthlink
We revolve around you
Alrighty
A couple more emails here
I had to go back into Gmail
And delete a whole bunch of stuff
Unfortunately because I hit my max
And I just didn't have the balls to
Going big for more
So I'm already I'm already using four gigs
And what is kind of cool though is in the search function
You can just say
You know show me everything from
Let me see
What I have a search function
Has attachment
Subject promo
Contains the words
MP3
And also I selected for
You know a year ago
So I was able to
You know basically get rid of a whole bunch of junk
That won't have junk
But stuff that I'm pretty sure I won't ever use again
But
Then again
It's a shame
I love Gmail so much
I wish I could buy unlimited space
That would really make it cool
Chris Ali Villardo
Right to me
Says been meaning to write this for a while
Back on New Year's
I got drunk off my ass
And when I was puking
From 1215am until 5am New Year's day
All I could think of
Was the theme song
To Trinity
Trinity
The quintessential luxury
Oh
Trinity
From the biodes of industry
Yo
So it's not really like I have a long Trinity segment
In fact we already discussed a little bit about Trinity
But I just wanted to see how it worked
Transitioning from the
The Jeff Smith composed Trinity track extended theme song
Into the tag and see how that worked on cast blasters
Or see if it did a good experience
But do you have one email
Oh shoot it's something that we can't use here
Yeah
Can't underwards at me a picture of
Biodes of t-shirt
I was pretty dumb I guess
Should have prep that a little bit better
Okay let's see if it works
So basically I would finish up my Trinity segment
And then I do something like this
Oh wait a minute
Sorry a little bit of pilot error
Here we go let's try one more time
By the way when you download cast blaster
Comes pre-installed and pre-populated with a couple of pot safe music tunes
Like my little radio waste another night
Which I've played at the beginning of the show
And chance
We go now to spin around to the leaders of the follow
Wave the light and for some kind of say
So spin around to the leaders of the follow now
The death president's game
See the cups is everywhere
In the street has the unfair
Look around you already now
The Nixon land takes his own land
So fill out the question
Then jump into a hip-hop
Oh yeah
We go now to the leaders of the follow
Wave the light and for some kind of say
So spin around to the leaders of the follow
I'll be demoing for our board, I'll be demoing a purchase of song on the podcast music network.
Unfortunately, the next step I'm about to make in my process here today, you won't be able to
witness.
Well, the fact that you're listening to this means that it worked.
I'm going to stop recording in a couple of seconds when I'm done, and then I'm going
to hit publish.
No, actually, I'm going to just tighten up the show notes first.
Hit publish, and then it should all work.
And if it does all work, then you won't notice a thing.
Now, what I might have screwed up, although I don't think so, is in the description,
the ID3 tags.
I think I did it pretty consistent with what I've always been doing up till now.
So hopefully, all of that works.
If not, I'm sure you will let me know through adamantcurry.com.
Of course, you can subscribe to this podcast and listen to new episodes as they come online
at dailysourcecode.com.
And, oh, don't forget to drop a promo into promo.podshow.com.
You can actually drop it right into the site there, and you can actually subscribe to
the feed there if you want to, if you're a podcast, and you just want to get some cool
promo.
So, enjoy that.
And thank you very much for participating in the first of what I'm sure will be
many, many tests over the coming weeks.
Take care y'all.
Only cast blaster mic would make lighters.
Another pod show pod cast.
Stick it in your ear.