Think Advertising sucks.
Think you can do better?
Pod Show and EarthLink are willing to put our money where your mouth is.
Listen to this podcast or go to adchelens.podshow.com to see how you can win big
in the EarthLink make advertising better challenge.
Delta Sierra Charlie 410.
It's Friday!
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm guessing it's time to carry.
I got it.
Sit tight.
I'm gonna need you to keep time.
Just snap, snap, snap.
Your fingers for me.
Good good.
Now we're making some progress.
Come on.
Just tap, tap, tap.
Your toes for the feet.
And I believe this may call for a proper introduction.
Well, don't you see?
I'm a narrator in this.
This is the floor.
It's Friday!
It seat here's Studio.
I can't fly there.
I know everything today.
It seems the artisan days are NOT too you think.
So we'll take back up on that on another page.
I believe this may call for a proper introduction.
Well, don't you see?
I'm a narrator in this.
Interest is the floor.
Tracer.
It indeed not been test…
Well, don't forget to turn your systemic reaction.
If you can't do it with you, I won't try again.
Class satisfaction!
Stop theping you've got three, four, ten, scissors and I-
Erm, four, ten, to say!
I!
To me, to rest, to be boys, to be wise
You're going to see me, I'll be the kids
We're gonna listen, we're gonna listen
So you're going to test, we're going to test it
I ain't to be, to rest, to be boys, to be wise
You're all ready to come on tonight
You're on great road
You're going to certainly come
In luck we're going to see you
If I want to see you, I never let you think about it
If I want to see you, IK assure you
If I want to see you, I will warn you
If I don't capture you, I'll be happy
If I want to see you because I'm coming
Don't kill me withoutentes
You're all ready to use me asILLI
Love me
I've grown up with , Are steel
I'm here
your eyes shall be模oused shall be wise
smokes you get beneath the wall
ah
Abbey Friday everybody, welcome to The Daily Source Code
northern california last time for this trip panic at the disco the only difference between
martyrdom and suicide is press coverage and ain't that the truth it's on the pod say music
network brand new upload from uh panic at the disco great to have those guys on pmn hey everybody
it's beautiful in the city but as I look out over uh over the hills i see nothing but fog i'm not
quite sure if it's coming towards me or going away uh there's a lot of wind and now we've got
a really funky climate uh here's San Francisco you know with what comes out you know from the sea
and from the valleys and the hills and the mountains and the who i don't know how it works everyone
here seems to know i don't but man it's been beautiful it's been like eighty ninety degrees in
San Francisco it's just been fantastic and it's time for me to head back home uh yes i can't wait
for a number of reasons some of them you can guess right away but i really also besides just missing
my girls just because they're my girls i miss Patricia on the show i really do i need someone
else to bounce off of and talk to once in a while and just knowing that she's next door in the bedroom
doing her makeup in the morning when uh when i'm doing the show is enough to know that she could
walk it at any time and correct me for my miss assumptions in life so we've got a really full show
today um when i woke up this morning quarter six is usual i had twenty two voicemails i don't
know what happened all of sudden you guys turn on to the voicemail system and some good feedback
comments so we'll get to all of those and i've got to kind of keep it moving today because at nine
thirty rosy from the office is coming to pick me up i have to go to DMV that's right figured
what we're fixing Trinity will fix everything else um there's been really you know i think the car
was in Ron's name because i can't register it here because i don't have a California driver's license
and they say well uh you can just take the test and i don't want to take no driving test again
that'll suck severely i'm sure i could pass it but um so we sent away to New Jersey and
New Jersey said hey no problem we have a copy of your old license which of course had been expired
for many many years that's since we've been away uh i shouldn't i shouldn't let those things
expire that's just handy to have man so i i have no idea what it's going to be like at the
the California DMV here in San Francisco but we should find out and uh let's see let's get all the
soccer stuff out of the way right off the bat because um we have some things to clear up about well
about the name soccer first of all hey Adam it's Dave the guy who left you that yeah woo woo woo
message on your answering machine you didn't get it it was a hockey reference you said on Wednesday's
Charlie i think was the only person in America interested in hockey what went wrong there how
can we don't care about hockey in the US hey there's one place in America that still cares about hockey
North Carolina home to yours Stanley Cup champion Carolina Hurricanes yes Canada
Rally North Carolina is a hockey town except it and move on anyway on this whole soccer versus
football thread you said on Tuesday's Charlie yeah what should we do we have to call it soccer
I guess we have to i'm just gonna keep saying football you'll know what i mean well if you want to
avoid all confusion why don't you call it by its full name association football see back in the
19th century all these English public schools form their football clubs but each school played by different
rules some schools kicked the ball some schools picked up the ball and ran with it Cambridge school
for example played a soccer style kicking game with a fair catch rule you could catch the ball
market and get a free kick from that spot they still do that in australian and gaelic football actually
but i digress in october of 1863 the first meeting of the ball was held and all these clubs got
together and decided they wanted to play by one specific set of rules and that set of rules became known
as association football and some players abbreviated it to soccer in the 1880s
to help differentiate association football from rugby football okay so how do i get soccer
from association football that the the the source i got that source so sock but then what is the
curve come from that's what i'm that's what i'm missing i i totally take you word for but i'm
where's the curve they uh got rid of the fair catch rule too so there you have it the origins of the
word soccer by the way i happen to have a lot of this useless football trivia floating in my brain
so if you ever need any more history lessons about football you just let me know in the mean time
for the latest in american football check out days football blog dot com and if you'd rather play
Canadian football hey for twenty they appreciate it dude i this is the comment that got missed
up the other day and uh i was my fault i guess somehow i'd uh downloaded only half of it and
loaded into cast blasts and it blew up so i still not quite sure where the curve comes from but
that is a very good uh background on on on on the rules and how we split up into all these different
types of football i'm just gonna keep it at football though if you don't mind because that to me
is the real name and if you're wondering why uh football has been so slow to catch on in the u.s
we had a big conversation about this yesterday at the office my theory is fairly simple the game
does not lend itself to commercial television you know you they play for forty five minutes at
minimum there's no uh look how many sports do we have now that have a television time outs
excuse me since sao this and sao moan brought to you by
open source sex with violet blue
there's more about soccer for you hey Adam it stays here from ragging sorry just on the road
suburb of gulfed got a couple of points for you um about soccer and about snake bite
first of all soccer um the word derives from association football so there you go there's the answer
that one and regarding snake bite my wife Rachel asked me to let you know that in in
Surrey and West Sussex snake bite was banned when she was at school made illegal when she was at school
because the kids were drinking 10 or 11 points of this nectar at a time
it goes to a lemon and also you need to drink if you're drinking snake bite the classic is
snake bite and black which is snake bite and black current which destroys your brain
and leaves you with a purple moustache in the morning so you're good anyway date signing off
yeah I've done other things that have destroyed my brain and left you with a purple moustache in the
morning my friend you can find our web development company shameless plug at www.projectcommer.co.uk
cheers peace of mind bye bye yeah dude appreciate it okay so I don't know if it's still banned in
gulfed and by the way why does your wife Rachel know so much about it huh
as she a party girl do you think she's still parties which you'd like to get some snake
bite and black with the pod father right down the road hi and this is Phil one half of the
soccer show podcast available from soccershout.com once again he's a quick world cup update
there's some superb games over the last few days let's start with the U.S. when Demsy last
up all into the back of the net I thought the U.S. would go on and win but their second half of
formus was just unacceptable of the calls for these three games that just didn't do enough to
justify moving on to the next round they definitely got some bad calls against them particularly
in the match against Ghana but to be honest they weren't worth it and it's good to see at least
one African team move through to the next round yeah I'd let's not say they weren't worth it
but it was a start yeah this was the first time I've seen so much excitement for
excuse me for football in the United States of course it worked out very well
with the timing because if it was in prime time would have been a huge problem as I just mentioned
with the commercials and thank goodness for ESPN too and other stations like that who carried the
games it all the Spanish stations who carried the games so I'm just really happy and proud of
our guys they you know they next next next competition they'll do even better because now they've
got the fans behind them I also thought Australia vs Croatia was a great game crazy refereeing
committed play and some good goals and one of my favorite teams Australia moving on the next round
as well I had to look forward to Holland vs Argentina but they pretty much cancel each other out
it was a bit of a disappointing game I forgot to build up but I think they were just saving
themselves for the next round the second round starts the side day is eight games four days
single elimination with overtime and penalty kicks every quiet to quickly run through the lineups
on Saturday we have Germany vs Sweden and Argentina vs Mexico Sunday we have England vs Ecuador
in Portugal vs Holland a Monday we have Italy vs Australia and probably Ukraine vs
and I say South Korea those games haven't been played yet to decide he's gonna be in that game
and on Tuesday we have Brazil vs Ghana and I think it's gonna be Spain vs France to finish off
the line up there my pick of the weekend is the game the sun sunday three p.m. eastern on ESPN
that's Portugal vs Holland Tuesday I think is gonna be two great games Brazil vs Ghana
and what I expect to be France vs Spain over at the soccer show podcast Tony and I are hitting
foam just at the right time so for a daily 20 minute two blocks in a pub style podcast about the
world cup check it out soccer show dot com this concludes our soccer moments on daily source code
410 only 10 more till 420 what are we gonna do then get your audio comments in quick
and your audio productions please yes today I told you that we're gonna have big news
regarding second life on today's show at 12 o'clock SLT which is the same as Pacific Coast
time PST Pacific's so-st to time we open up the pod show island that's right been working
very very hard now of course you know that we've had parties every single day people have been
hanging out yesterday we had was the blue the blue party at the at the brothel what am I talking
about this is about second life the virtual world it's a it's a game you can download it's
second life dot com but what's nice about it is it's a game where well a lot of listeners hang out
a lot of podcasters hang out uh people get to get together and chat about stuff and do stuff
so uh I got pretty frustrated with just you know all the limitations of second life in general
the only way to really fix that is to get an island so uh got the team together let's me in
Brittany Brittany Mason you'll find her of course uh today at the party there's ex-dark ex-alora
magic squeeze magic star squeegee squeegee squeegee squeegee squeegee and we put together this
island and you're gonna love this place it's gonna be a great place to come and hang out we've uh
got a lot more control over what goes on in the land so of course the brothel move there yesterday
you probably saw that right after the party everything got ripped out and taken away
the palaces now there and it's it's it's the palaces been expanded it's beautiful we got swimming pool
we've got all kinds of great games Texas hold on roulette of course the podshow princesses will be
on the island dancing contest I'm moving there uh I think that's so I will be moving out of the
castle to live there not quite sure we're gonna deposit the castle there not because uh I have
a pretty nice place to live just look for the red car so it's gonna be uh it's gonna be high end you
know it's gonna be much much classier we have a lot more control out of keeping people out who we
don't want in but I think I think we're gonna have a really good time and you can also buy land
there you can rent a place uh so let's see if we can uh let's see if we can really get a community together
if you want any more information just to look for Brittany Mason online if I'm not online
and she'll be able to help you particularly when it comes to the real estate
oh man another chapter in my second life yeah yeah yeah yeah it's speaking of chapters in my life
you know that before I got the delta Sierra my my airplane I was flying helicopters
in fact I have about 750-800 hours on the turbine helicopters as piloting command
and uh it's you know so I kind of went from helicopters to uh to regular fixed wing
where most people go from fixed wing to helicopters and it usually happens after an experience
like Misha had AC how are you it's Micah from let's shoot I mean Micah I've done that before I'm
sorry Micah the chopper so over at LC choppers.com and uh I just want to say you
roadograph pilots man you guys are nuts you see my wife and I we just went to Alaska on a cruise
and we took a glacier tour and you want to talk about scud running and not being very far off
the ground and looking up out of the helicopter to see the top of mountains it was just crazy but I
tell you it was quite the adrenaline rush now I'm an air traffic controller over in Toledo
Ohio and we were helicopters all the time and I'm a fixed wing pilot myself with about 400 hours or so
but I tell you after the helicopter ride I'm seriously thinking about going back to school and picking
up those roado wings right on anyway take care and have a good week we'll talk to you later brother
and and tailwinds dude you suppose to say tailwinds how you really apply
yeah Micah used to have Micah's minute which was great there was him recording stuff from
from the tower as he was doing ATC in Toledo and I really loved it but I guess they they found
upon it so Micah's minute passed and now he's doing the chopper podcast which is not about helicopters
but about two wheel choppers. Let's see uh yesterday talked about uh was it yesterday talked about
hugging a long tall Lisa at the pod show HQ about me being vertically challenged oh I have not
alone hey Adam this is David from New Jersey call the tell you just uh working about a
day behind on the latest B.S.E.s. one of the shots and I'm sitting at a restaurant here on the
Jersey term bike and I thought I'd give you a call I too have vertically challenged just had my
20 second anniversary of this test weekend with my wife um 64 she is only five two so I kind of
know where you come in from bro uh was looking through my wedding album this past weekend and I
started the chuckle I have forgotten during the wedding they made my wife stand on a box so that the
pictures look more normal know where you come in from keep it up bye bye guys so what Patricia usually
makes me do is uh whenever we're going somewhere where this potential for us to be photographed
together for like uh newspapers gossip rags etc so usually when we're in the Netherlands because
it's a really the only place we ever get bothered with that stuff she'll make me walk about three or four
feet behind her and then if the people say oh yeah let's take a picture together and I literally
have to like spread my legs out I had this whole way of doing it so you can't really see what I'm
doing but you know particularly in perspective if people are taking pictures right from the front of us
so kind of like spread my legs forward and back and and just kind of squat down and that usually
works out okay and all the besides you know people often ask me if there's any other disadvantages
to such a height difference can you say pinwheel?
Hey Adam it's dead zero from the area of 51 group the weather middle listening to Wednesdays
usually sort of code your thing on that neutrality and I think you're missing this a certain amount
of perspective free lunch there's no such thing nobody is getting a free lunch we're oh wow this
is great yeah I've got like a couple uh two pieces of feedback uh to share with you regarding net
neutrality this is the thing that's uh coursing through the veins of the internet right now everyone
talking about it like we're getting ripped off SBC is gonna blow up the internet it's gonna suck
so I'm gonna just let you hear a couple of different sides of this and then uh hopefully give you
some more information all paid for that then with Google is saying a massive amount to SBC or
whatever the hell they're called by AT&T and whoever else who are those things these networks
we're paying for all that stuff to what they want they want to get get paid twice they want to
maximize their revenue streams they want more money more money more money more money that's our problem
they want to make it the glory of the internet has always been that anybody can prosper if
you've got a good idea and maybe some technical chops or you know somebody you can get a website
up and you can make a million dollars all of a sudden now you got to pay the ferryman before you
can actually stand a shot it's been a ruin it if you're not fair it's not legal and there is no competition
they're in collusion there's about three bandwidth providers that cover the United States
and everybody else is using them they're definitely all gonna charge the same amount and that
amount's gonna keep going up together and they're not gonna get charged as weeks as long as this
is made for the city office it is not going to be what you're imagining is not gonna be worked
out in the market there is no opportunity for anybody else to make any even networks maybe
she's for Google but if watch them get stopped with galleries they have a it's not a fair
system it's not free market and it's not a free lunch you know what are you getting it for free
see you later okay so this is pretty much the typical attitude that that is coursing through the
veins of the the internet right now that it's not fair it's double dipping there's no competition
now this is a subject that I happen to know an awful lot about having owned a data center
and really understanding how the internet itself works on the inside that's the big cloud that
you always see on the power points when people are talking about these great things with the
internet and they say on end is cloud in here all this stuff kind of happens okay so I happen to
know a lot about that and before I get into it I want to play more because now here's a a different
viewpoint on net neutrality hey and this is Chris Thompson so it helps you and he go apex of that
come I was just listening to so talking about net neutrality and it has two cents to offer
awesome Louisiana I was talking to internet engineer a network engineer who works for a
streaming media company for like music videos and got the scoop from him so basically it's all about
fiber optic um for years uh FBC and AT&T have been putting fiber optics to the nose level which is
you know your neighborhood so you individual neighborhoods would have fiber optic connection
and this this means they sent a lot of money on infrastructure and all this other nonsense
and the plan is to bump up everyone's bandwidth so all of a sudden now you have you know a huge
pipe coming at your house and they want to offer content on that they want to offer uh
voiceover IP they want to offer you know content distribution stuff and if they're going to have
competitors come and do the same thing without paying for that's that's what their beef is and
doesn't make too much sense for me um but also there was a um a bit about having this you know a huge
fiber optic pipe certain packets will also be time sensitive like voiceover IP and streaming packets will be
preferred and if your network is preferred then you just get you get right through in preference to a
packet which is not preferred so you know it's getting voiceover IP even better and stuff
and it makes very much sense you make a lot of sense if you're doing this but you basically have
monopoly over these fiber optic connections you can name your price there's not much I'll choose I mean the
telco's own the internet I mean combined um so I don't know too much about I don't know too much about
this issue but that's just my uh my knowledge that I can add to the conversation um personally I'm
looking at um getting uh dumping contest I don't have a only in my phone I want to get the um
the neighborhood wireless connection all right so he goes on for a little bit more and I really have
to stop because if you want to know all about net neutrality and you're listening to this podcast on
serious stars 102 you're gonna have to download the whole show a daily source code dot com to find out
my viewpoint on that PCH is next for you guys I'll talk to you on Monday so okay
I'm trying to think if I should get now you know what there's one because I did a lot of research on it yesterday
because even though I'm pretty sure that I know what I'm talking about I did go out and do some
more research on net neutrality and low and behold I uh found I'm trying to launch this now
I found a uh a video of uh hold on open up here we go of Tim Berners Lee the man widely credited
for um yeah essentially uh coming up with the concept of the worldwide web
you got to listen to this it's you know it's it's short but it's Tim Berners Lee
who I obviously high and got him in very high on the radar and on the uh respect scale
but I don't think he understands either quite honestly uh he did invent the worldwide web as you'll
hear him say in this video piece I'm just waiting for it to load or actually streaming this uh over
the net coming I think this is a hopeless streaming and over the net oh what is this
to help protect your computer windows firewall has blocks and features of this program unblock okay
could you please get to it it was unblock yesterday why did y'all sudden decide to block it now
here comes Tim here's Tim Berners Lee and listen to what he's saying this is Tim Berners Lee
from MIT I invented the worldwide web without having to ask anybody's permission
I invented the worldwide web hundreds of millions of people are using it freely today
I'm worried that this will end in the USA I've blocked on net neutrality before
I'm so did a lot of other people but since then some telecommunication companies have
spent a lot of money on TV ads and PR and the US house seems to have wavered from the path
of preserving net neutrality there's been some misinformation spread about
so here are some clarifications net neutrality is this if I pay to connect to the net with a given
quality of service and you pay to connect to the net with the same or higher quality of service
then you and I can communicate across the net with that quality of service
that's all it's up to the internet service providers to interconnect to make sure that happens
and they've shown they're very capable of doing that
net neutrality is not about asking for the internet for free
net neutrality is not saying that we shouldn't pay more for higher quality of service
we always have and we always will there have been some suggestions that we don't need legislation
because we haven't had it these are nonsense because in fact we have had net neutrality in the past
and it's only recently that real explicit threats have emerged
control of information is hugely powerful
in the US the threat is that companies will control what I can access for commercial reasons
in China the threat is the government controls access for political reasons
there is a very strong short-term incentive for a company to grab control of TV distribution
over the internet even though it is against the long-term interests of the industry
yes regulation to keep the internet open is regulation and mostly the internet has thrived
or lack of regulation but some basic values have to be preserved the market system depends
on the fact that you can't photocopy money democracy depends on freedom of speech
freedom of connection with any application to any party is the fundamental social basis of the internet
and now is the basis of the society we've built on the internet let's see whether the United
States is capable of acting according to its fundamental values or is it as some people who have been
saying run by the misguided short-term interests of large companies I hope Congress can protect net
neutrality so I can continue to innovate in the internet space I want to go on seeing the
huge number of innovations which are happening out there and which is so diverse and so exciting
I want to see that continue unabated okay timbernously I got a disagree with you even though
I hold you on high regard for inventing the worldwide web as you say yourself
you did not invent the internet we all know how guarded that and that's really what this is about
this is not about the web in fact you timbernously even said there you know this is about controlling
television through the internet which I thought was kind of weird for him to even use the word
television because we don't really have television on the internet okay what happens on the internet
and this is something that has been brewing for a long long time and it is not only something
that's that's happening in the US it's going to happen worldwide because this is about peering and
peering agreements when now when when when Al Gore invented the internet as basically when the
DARPA net was turned off and commercial networks took over the backbone functionality of the net
and we saw this happen from you know 94 95 so for the past 10 to 15 years we we yeah for the past 10
12 years we've literally seen this grow before our very eyes now because these were telecommunications
companies they're used to handing off phone calls to each other on a you know on a billions of
phone minutes a day I guess and they do this at exchanges and at the end of the month they have
something called settlement which basically is when they all the computers run and they match everything
up and they say okay I sent four hundred million minutes to you so you owe me an X amount of money
because I passed those phone calls off onto your network but you also passed phone calls off
on the mine network it was 490 minutes million minutes so I owe you 90 million minutes that's what
the settlement is all about now when the same wires the same fiber optics the same pipes started to
be used for data and as they started to you know convert that and there's all kinds of technical
stuff behind that but essentially the existing pipes you know just like our phone lines were
our first access to the internet there really wasn't an efficient way to track the cost and in fact
if that had started a long time ago then we probably wouldn't have seen the explosive growth of
the internet that we've seen so they came up with a concept of peering and you have these exchange
points and I know a lot about this because I had a data center called the data barn which was
directly connected to the m6 the Amsterdam internet exchange and in order to become a member
you have to have a certain amount of traffic for peering which means you're on peer with
other networks that connected this exchange this is where these networks come together and where
traffic is passed off so as an example the podcast delivery network the pod show runs in conjunction
with line light is really a whole bunch of data centers that have copies of the content around the
globe excuse me the other sincere moment but I'm not going to sponsor it now so since there's
not a very efficient way to count packets and people aren't used to being charged by the packet
necessarily these at these interchange points the networks basically say well I'm handing you
you know 500 million terabytes your hand and me 450 million terabytes it's almost the same next week
maybe I'll have more you'll have more so we'll call it a wash we'll call it peering and there
these peering agreements which are contracts which literally say that saying you can charge me money
I can't charge you money as long as we stay more or less within the bounds of equal traffic
so I'm sending as much to your network as I'm receiving from your network okay so when you look at
the podcast delivery network let's say you're on comcast okay and you want to listen to the daily
source code so you just click on a link or your iTunes or some other podcast you're like juice
says give me that file the file literally comes from a server that is probably only 20 feet away
from comcast network because it's in the same data center and because we have a peering agreement
between and really that's a lot of this limelight infrastructure we have a peering agreement
it gets sent over gets put right on to the network and this happens almost everywhere we're
you know so you remember we used to talk about hops how many hops away is this server from me
well what happens is if you if either side of the equation whether you have an ISP
that may not have all the all the direct connections into the exchanges because they don't have
enough traffic by themselves which means they're basically buying someone else's pipe into the
exchange or whether you're a content provider right who is providing the content onto those into
the exchange perhaps through an external ISP or such as pod shell were right in the exchanges
um I lost my train of thought this is a very complicated crap yeah so essentially you
request it and it comes out on the other end if if you don't have those direct connections you
have to do something which we call transit you have to buy transit so if as an example it could
happen although unlikely that the podcast delivery network is in exchange and there's a huge
network let's just call it SBC and they feel that for this new network they've put in place
which is really high speed you're not sending them enough traffic or you're not able to receive
enough traffic back from them for whatever reason they say we don't feel like we're peers then
I would have to literally buy access and it could only be a five-foot cable to a different network
that does have that amount of traffic but I would have to buy that connecting access to the other
network called buying transit which can become very expensive but at the end of the day the concept
of the internet is that no matter what happens your content will eventually get to the other end
it may have to go through several hops because they're peering agreements aren't in place this
has been going on for years in fact eight or ten years ago you could really tell the difference we
would do trace routes anyone done a trace route or you know to see oh where's this traffic going
through my gosh it's unbelievable this is not coming directly you know I'm in California and I'm
trying to get to a server in New York but I'm being routed through through Germany through Frankfurt
I mean that happened quite a lot and this is all because of the peering agreements or lack of them
and the purchasing of this transit bandwidth so because these peering agreements are basically
set on you know people shaking hands and saying I agree either party when they come to the table
with a new network or something and some upgrade of course has the right to say you know what
you want to you want to drop this stuff they could say pod show you want to drop this stuff right
onto our network this new high speed network which essentially will allow you to deliver television
quality images to anyone on our network that's fine but you can have to pay us for it and that's
that's what's happening it doesn't mean it doesn't mean that I can't get there through another
means but it would still cost me money I would have to buy transit to a network that did have that
agreement with SBC this is huge political stuff that has been going on for a long time and it's
not about of course at the end of the day the consumer always pays the bill for everything but it's
it's not about never going you're that you're not going to be able to have access in fact SBC
would be it would be suicide for them to say oh I'm sorry you can't get to that server because
X, Y, or Z they'll never do that this is about a much higher network which really is almost
not even a part of the internet it's their network so if they want to charge people
to peer directly onto their network then people can have to do that and if not then there will
be networks and other parties in between who will aggregate all of this traffic to come up with
the right peering number or whatever the agreement has to be and so maybe that maybe pod show and
Google and Yahoo would all have to get together and buy transit from different parties to still
get on the network you will get on the network but it's going to cost money so and this is what
I truly believe is that SBC is just saying you know we're putting billions into the ground in
fiber and routers and switches and all kinds of stuff if you want to utilize it with all this
additional traffic you're going to put on a network then you know you're no longer a peer
you're in fact you're overloading us so you have to pay for it but the internet is not going to
die because of this I'm sorry it's just not going to happen this is the thing that was supposed to
withstand the nuclear attack and still work you know and so some stupid thought that a powerful
party can take over if look if SBC could really really take and hold the internet hostage
they would have done so a long time ago when they when they actually could have done it and I don't
and even if if they wanted to I'm still doubt that it was possible 10 years ago to really they
they'll try it essentially they try to own the internet it's just not how it works
study and see how border gateway protocol works it's it's it's real high-end techy stuff but
personally from a from a commercial standpoint I think it's great that they've put all this
investment in it still remains to be seen what they're going to charge for basically hopping
onto their network and and making use of it if they make it to expensive guess what we're just going
to continue to compress our videos and keep it nice and tight and you know and then it'll just
progress slower so there are market forces here at work it has nothing to do with with anti-competitive
behavior and even though I was the one of the first to identify some very strange
remarks made by Whitaker the CEO of SBC corporation I just don't see the threat and I think it's
a lot of pile jumping that's going on and I really do know what I'm talking about so maybe we'll
just all check in in two years and and see if I was right but you know this is not legislation
is not going you think legislators understand this stuff I can barely understand what it's about
and I actually had a business that was in this business so I think it's just an upgrade of the
internet and it will probably take 10 years for all you know all parties involved all ISPs and
everything to shake out and reshuffle and create new pairing agreements but man if anyone thought that
this day wasn't coming we're pairing agreements would be busted wide open then then crazy we all knew
this was coming this has been something that's and these contracts are you know 40 pages deep of
all this crap you can and can't do I mean we've been skating on thin ice for a long long time and maybe
just maybe everybody's been getting a pretty free ride ever think about that it's really expensive
stuff we've been we've gotten used to cheap access and you know now we're paying the bill for
essentially but it doesn't mean that any company in my opinion that any company can
can go and hijack the internet and and make it so that individuals can't communicate or that
you can't start a service of course you can and you will get exactly what you pay for you know
it's not like your current standards are going to cost more it's going to cost more if you
want to jump to the next level oh hey and to be honest if that's if you know look I'm a commercial
guy everybody knows that and but I also love the the the the free and openness of the net and I
I've built a career on it and I've become very successful through it and I and I don't intend to
stop now so if I really was concerned you'd be hearing a whole different noise coming from my
piehole which of course is surrounded by lots of growth of hair yeah and this is really from
what you're talking and this is just gone about your your growth you had mentioned in the
day on the metro sexual moment you're wanting tips on how to groom that I don't think we're all
so if that's part of the deal man I think if you're going to let it grow you're going to just have to let it grow
no nothing no clip for no trim and none of that stuff man you're just going to have to go to
blue bush maybe that one's fire you to get off the end you get that two-man working man I don't
I don't think you should be driving at or anything else I think you're doing that boat to pictures
it could I do it and just let it go on there they're a little bit of rail then it stopped
reaching and just anybody now that's your energy that's good work bye all right man you got my
sexy SOGF to thank for that for the pictures of of course another update of the it's getting
it's getting thick and dark now that they take my picture dmv and what happens when I go back
to London will they let me in the country will they look at me and say this doesn't look like
your passport picture in fact that beard kind of makes you a kind of terrorist look and you know
I'm saying hi Adam this is Jeff Groucho Marx in second life what morning I got an elephant in my
agenda oh you got my agenda I don't know I've been enjoying listening to your story about growing
your beard in the pictures in 2000 I was a CEO of a public dot com and I too while waiting for
our new development platform to be launched announced the staff that I wasn't going to shave
until you guys finished and we launched and the news to say I went through many months
scratching and itching and looking ridiculously grubby and so finally they were ready to launch
and at the launch party I came out in my scrubby beard congratulated the team then I ducked off into
the bathroom and shaved off half my beard it came back into the room and into the party with
one side of my face clean shaving and the other side filled bushy and that was good for a few
laughs and a bunch of embarrassing pictures so you might want to consider that when you finish with
the you are impending launch and any event keep up the great work good to hear from you to
and see you every day and as Groucho would say that's the most ridiculous thing I have always
yeah you know I didn't like that too much that that comment because you know you said that
you were a CFO of a dot com company and it took months those are like a whole bunch of things
that just really didn't make me feel good at all about this whole beard thing I'm not planning
on waiting a couple of months I hope the company you were CFO of still exists so there's no bad
home and with this beard stuff this is really just to remind me about how much hard work is going
into creating this thing it's been eight or nine months people are really I mean I've been at the
office almost every night until anywhere between eight and ten p.m. and there's tons of people
still work and they're still just because they want to because they want to get this done they
want to get this out and the demand is so huge so take it for me I'm not planning on having this
beard for very long I'm just wary of giving and we have a date of course we have a date I'm just
very wary of giving it to anybody but believe me when I say the Patricia hates a beard she likes
the way it looks but she dislikes the way it functions and she will be giving me grief about this so
this is this is more to remind me of whatever one's going through trying to get all this stuff up
and going and it's going to be beautiful when you see pod show plus when you see my collection
in the channel guide and then you see the the pdn that's that's that's available for anyone for free
to use I think you're going to like it you're going to want to join the show you're definitely
going to want to be a part of the show hi Adam I was listening to daily source code six twenty one
or six I can't I'm a grand lover I don't know if that's why it's not but anyway I was driving home
away from working um Pennsylvania from Central Pennsylvania to Philadelphia on U.S. one and the
career song came on and I was a little tired to go to about one in the morning coming home
from the TV station that I work at and that song came on and we said hey listen to this song
and imagine it's a video and at that moment I really woke up to listen there were two
years in front of me I don't know if it saves my life but it definitely saves my car so thanks to the
daily source code he kept me awake you're doing a good job keep it up and I love your daughter's
pod show okay and I hope this is clear thanks to all right take care of Adam oh yeah so you
probably also save the deer don't you think you didn't mention that what all right daily source code
known for saving lives all over the world and yeah Christina's getting ready to do her next show
she can't wait I she might even make me do it on Sunday when when I get home which will be
fine with me I mean I I want her doing to voice mail numbers over the weekend you might be
listening to the show over the weekend in New Jersey which is probably the best number for you to call
if you're using Skype 2016256357 we also have a London number we the Royal Wii 02076813753 and
that comments were Patricia's well because you know she's gonna be on the show Monday okay just a
couple more bits here but oh they're very important ones shoot I'm used to using two different
computers for this stuff here we go let's try that comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip
comic strip you use the man with a plan hello madam carry as you maybe know I am a mobile phone expert
and not just because I was working three years in Finland at Nokia but because I'm writing the
bug mobile phones on the internet since 10 years and I visit personally major treasures including
the biggest mobile phone treasure in the world 3GSM so let me tell you and DSC listeners two things
firstly some wireless carriers indeed offer flat rate mobile internet where you pay on
six price without limits it is so in USA Japan Germany and East Europe but not in UK unfortunately
where still it's come and titled unlimited one gigabyte is practiced secondly I would like to say
that there's no oh I just got to stop you there C.S.B. you know this is so true talk about net neutrality
and bullshit my phone bill my singular bill I should say is about $2,500 a month and so Rosie
came to me yesterday said you know what are we going to do about your phone bill and I said well
you know crap you know this is what happens I you know we've tried two phones having a UK phone
than a US phone and I miss out on a lot of calls because people are calling the wrong phone number
this one's on that one's anyway or I got to walk around with two phones a tremendous logistical
nightmare but the funny thing is it's not the actual phone calls you'd think and I talk a lot
and I'm basically roaming when I'm using my US blackberry in in the UK but those costs are
relatively low maybe only a couple hundred bucks what is the actual charge for the charge is for
reading email it's for the bandwidth I consume reading email while overseas because yeah you get one
gigabyte and after that no actually you get one gigabyte if you're in the US and the same goes for the
UK by the way you get a gigabyte which is more than enough for the gigabyte okay just a gig
it's not a huge amount of data by today standards you get a gig to do your email is more than enough
for email however when you are roaming they charge you about a buck or maybe it's a buck 50
per megabyte that is transferred that's bullshit that is total crap and bullshit and it is directly
related to the peering issue and it's and but in this case it's price gouging it is totally
intended to rip off the consumer when he goes outside of the regular coverage area phone would
had this good you got as a bribe it's quite good for the recording thanks to wifi and
3G but it has no stereo audio of a bluetooth so it is missing the crucial thing anyway
and I'm carry why couldn't you give me interview about mobile phones now when you see that mobile
phone industry seriously is entering put casting let's do it made over Skype or in person come on
here you'll like that podcast creator okay see as be I don't know about interview
I'm not I've got nothing to say I don't know anything about mobile phones you know everything
about mobile phones so this Nokia N91 you heard it there from the expert in fact the guy who left
Nokia and does not like the company at all he says it's a pretty damn good phone
and I have to agree you know what thank you offer sending in all that information and emails about
finding the tracks so I was indeed incorrect and I guess it's just an interface issue that I
and I'm not I'm I'm blonde but I'm not totally stupid but I thought that music would be under music
but no it's under tracks okay so I found all the tracks that came pre-loaded on this N91 which is
as CSB just said I received as a bribe to talk about it yeah hell yeah let me see let me see
if I can find it here because they pre-loaded it with all kinds of cool stuff is he Kevin Reeves in
there let me see where is now of course I can't find it I had it all set up for you there was
these ringtones oh man don't tell me I can't find the ringtones now oh wait no tracks that's
what I want tracks there we go okay let's go it was kind of cool the way they set that up here
they actually yeah so they contact it Jeff Smith the Roger Smalls ringtone is on here
comic strip blogger oh wait they even I guess they they contacted and hopefully contracted
Jeff Smith to create this ringtone for me check it out see is it playing yeah should play now
oh wait that's not the one we know that one that's Metro sexual Adam oh Adam's ringtone
shoot where is it okay you can hear me tapping through okay so the so I did this one for Ron
wasn't there to receive his free phone but this is the one for Ron that's pretty funny
can you imagine actually being in a meeting and that going off yeah here's my here's my hip hop ringtone
check this out this is funny I can just see me walking around with this oh yeah oh yeah
Adam is she phone Adam Curry oh you get the idea as a music machine it's great it's fantastic
I'm I'm just bummed about the keyboard I can't use that to it just won't work for email that's a real
bummer okay so I just wanted to correct that from yesterday we almost done here no Marcus
couch or something to say hey what's up it's Marcus couch pot show music rewind and the scene's
aim and I'm actually calling to talk about rewind right now hey if content clips were you know
recreational activities I'd be down to sticks and stems right now are you music podcasts is up there
point your browser to rewind dot pot show dot com click on the submission tab on the right side
and give me a clip just send it to hot show music rewind and gmail dot com and you're in
it could be on the show totally appreciate that hey speaking of appreciate and thanks for the link
to the scenes video podcast yeah my pleasure man plugbell here the scenes theme dot com totally
appreciate that and I'm actually going to two more in the can and each one is like technically
harder than the last so having a lot of fun doing that but I tell you it's a lot different than
audio because instead of just hitting the play button to listen to the thing it takes about 20 minutes
to render every 30 seconds video to all about it the time shifting is definitely a huge lag factor
in video podcasting all right Marcus couch monitor you know all right buddy if you haven't seen
that I put a link on curry dot com yesterday to uh Marcus couch's video podcast I you got to see
what he's done it's fantastic it's really really cool great use of the medium but yeah it's not
that it's not trivial it's not like audio where you bang them out one after another you know it's uh
it takes actual work involved yeah we've been doing some stuff for for the show over in uh in England
for for BT uh sorry I'm supposed to talk about that I'm supposed to tell you who are partners
for a hot show UK for a big launch it's going to be great we've been putting lots of cool
video stuff together finally um just uh quickly regarding my uh temporary switch to windows
first of all all the people who say that I shouldn't be getting a Sony via because of the route kit
fiasco you're probably right but I'm just a dumb consumer and I just want a really good machine
so I can still hate Sony for doing that but yeah people and companies make mistakes
so it is also divine to uh to forgive particularly if you get a great kick-ass computer out of it
but I was missing really I I'm not missing much on on on how it works and how it functions you know
and of course the beauty of the of a Macintosh is that the hardware and the software are pretty much
tightly controlled by the same company so they you know it's like you know there's only so many
types of monitors that are going to be hooked up to it so you know uh uh the the operating system
knows exactly what capabilities the uh how many people you how many people how many if you're looking
at well listen to this on your computer just look down to see if you receive the Skype message
that's Raymond Ford's Skyping Me Raymond I'm in the middle of the show um so you know there's
there's there's there's we don't have that tight integration on windows so there's some things that
you know that that are just a little funky but the one thing I've really been missing
is the ability to do an apple key age which is hide and that came out with OS 10 I don't think it was
even in the uh in the initial release or maybe if I recall correctly it was in the initial release
and they took it out of the second release and then brought it back because people love it so much
and it's nice because it's control which is the left-hand side of the keyboard and age which is right
in the middle so you can tap that with the have long-hand long fingers so I can tap that with one hand
or I can use my other hand it's and I become accustomed to it for you know six years now
I've been using control age as control age all-tab that's kind of my the way I navigate around
and it's just nice to control age to move something out of the way if you want to have it back
and all-tab and it's back and uh I've been looking for the equivalent of that and I of course
receive lots of email and a and a voicemail feedback about how to do that.
Hey Adam how's it going this Kevin reads uh and a couple quick things first of all um an easy way
to do hiding in windows with a keyboard and unfortunately it's a two-step process but it's a lot
of easier than what you've been doing is when you're in an application hit alt space and then
and for minimize it's kind of weird you'd think it was M but it's not it's November
so alt space and then N that will minimize the application and bring it to the next one
so that's that's the first thing second thing and then he goes on to talk about being on the
Nokia phone which already mentioned thank you Kevin so yeah that's not very handy because it's
two-step process this is all about speed you know by the way um you know how you may have
used spotlight on the Mac to find something or I used uh was it quick keys or quick silver quick silver
I think it is uh which gives you a quick short cut command you type in the first couple of letters
of whatever it is you're looking for whether it's a document or an application that's the way
I don't navigate you know to my applications folder or down to the dock you know I like using the
keyboard my hands are already there I don't have to move it away from the mouse it's all about
the speed of navigation for me shoot I'd probably be one if I could if I ever learned e-max I'd
probably still be using e-max I definitely still pop open a VI editor once in a while
but it's not it's not the same thing so I really wanted to control H and Anders Kerson
I thought hope I'm pronouncing that right heard the call and he created a beautiful little
application for me you just drop a shortcut into the startup folder and it's hidden you don't see it
and it basically maps control key and the H key that combination or any other combination you
want you can reset it it basically maps that to the minimize the foremost application command which
would be the equivalent to the alt space bar and then the n which is nuts it's the n for no
member I mean how stupid is that minimize hmm let's make that an n command they must have had a
long meeting and redmin about that shit so anyway Anders thank you so much I love this new app and
if you think it's bug free dude I think you should totally put that out there and let people enjoy this
use max and also use windows and just missed that one little wonderful piece of functionality
I think they'll be very cool and again I really really do appreciate you putting that together for me
dang we've been at it for an hour I got to get to the dmv and even better I got to go home
I want to go home and see my girls
shows
have sex with my wife
god I need it
I'm going home
the long time now I'm home
I'm gonna see my friends
don't see my friends
don't see my old family and my friends
don't ever care too much about money
I like it
don't ever care too much about her
don't think about mulls and don't care if I miss me hey
the time to live is now and I'm on my way
I'm going home
the long time now I'm home
don't see my friends
don't see my family and my friends
don't think about mulls and don't care if I miss me
I'm going home
That's why my friends, going home tomorrow, can't wait so much is gonna happen.
The unleash will happen when I get home, pod show UK is gonna open when I get home and
I'm gonna have this wild-ass jungle sex is what's gonna happen when I come home.
Alrighty everybody, okay?
I gotta get ready, that's a lee metaphor by the way.
I believe he's from Switzerland looking at his email address and he put that up on the
pod safe music network and send me an email about it and said, hey, what do you think?
Maybe for when you're going home.
I said, yeah, that's great.
That's fantastic.
Boo-boo.
Adamaccurry.com for your feedback, dailysourcecode.com for the latest show on the podcast feed,
of course, and Curry.com for the ongoing conversations about all kinds of stuff.
I'm sure I'll get lots of net neutrality comments.
Alrighty everybody, thank you very much for sticking with me throughout the past two weeks.
Oh, I'm choking up.
Throughout the past three weeks here in San Francisco, Monday, Lady Patricia on the show,
no doubt about it.
You can count on it.
420 everybody, talk to you on Monday, have a great weekend, bye-bye.
Another pod show pod cast, stick it in your ear.
Get this pod cast in more great ones like you on the high performance pod cast delivery
network from pod show and limelight networks.