Delta Sierra Charlie 3-5-3
For giving me pot father, for I have since saved
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Fantastic, it's Adam Curry.
You're looking for a better man.
For want to make the sadness go away.
Taking everything you can.
Tears of falling sooner every day.
Waiting for your lucky break.
Laying on your bed for days.
No it was your last mistake.
You keep on dreaming every day.
I want to know.
Do you feel this way?
Are they all the same?
I want to know if you can feel the pain.
Staring at your TV screen.
Knowing that the TV is your one and only friend.
But things are looking up.
From down in the hole.
Things are looking up.
They can't know us.
From down in the hole.
Things are looking up.
They can't know us.
You're waiting for a better man.
Someone to make the sadness go away.
Doing everything you can.
The drinks are flowing sooner every day.
Now it was your last mistake.
Laying on your bed for days.
You're burning but you're never a break.
I still you keep on dreaming every day.
I want to know.
Do you feel this way?
Are they all the same?
I want to know if you can feel the pain.
Staring at your TV screen.
Knowing that the TV is your one and only friend.
But things are looking up.
From down in the hole.
Things are looking up.
They can't know us.
From down in the hole.
Things are looking up.
They can't know us.
American heartbreak.
Michael Butler's band.
Everybody, how are you doing?
Coming to you from northern California.
It is bright and early.
It's 10 minutes.
The time that I'm making this podcast.
But we're here in San Francisco.
And once again, my little commute went very successfully.
Let me just say a couple things about American heartbreak.
As I said, that's Michael Butler's band.
It's brand new.
They have a record coming out on April 18th.
And they're starting a tour next Wednesday on the 22nd March in Las Vegas.
And I believe they're actually.
I don't know if it's the whole tour of it's just this particular date.
But in Vegas, they're playing with the helicopters.
I'm told are pretty damn good.
So has Michael said here.
The song is things are looking up.
It's no Matthew evil, but it's okay.
It's very, very, very much okay.
Ah, yes. Well, let me tell you a little bit about the past 24 hours.
Actually, it was really interesting.
For me to have recorded the show, the Daily Source code for Tuesday.
Now, I recorded that Monday night, but it actually didn't go up until Tuesday morning.
So I got on a plane. I flew like 9,000 miles.
It was a long flight this time was 10 hours and 26 minutes.
Which was, you know, that's like a four movie, a four movie flight right there.
And then I arrived at the condo, say, I was in like 230 something like that.
And then I flipped on serious.
And then I could hear the show.
I actually got here before the show got here.
It was the weirdest thing because, of course, on a serious satellite,
we're on a star's 102 channel 102 now.
So we were, so you got Howard at 100 101 is the Howard News channel.
And then 102 is where you can find us every week.
After noon, between three and seven Pacific six and ten Eastern time.
So it was, it was just, it was twisted, as weather was.
Okay, movies on the flight. Let's see.
Good night and good luck.
Now, it was actually bad luck for this movie that it was the first thing I watched because, you know,
I got, I left it, you know, 830 in the morning.
We'd had a really long busy weekend. So I was pretty tired.
And of course, they offer you that come when you got on the plane.
It's like, would you like champagne?
Just like, I want champagne to live in the morning.
Or do you want orange juice?
Well, why don't you throw the two of them together.
Some of us call that a mimosa in the UK.
It's called a boxfiz.
So I was kind of loosen relax.
I think I fell asleep five times during that movie.
I just couldn't get into it.
For some reason, it just didn't work for me.
And I saw the movie with 50 cent, 50 cent.
What is it to get rich or die?
Get rich faster die or die trying something like that.
Actually, pretty damn good movie.
Yeah, it was really, I think, really gave it pretty good look into the hip hop culture
and where a lot of hip hop and rap artists come from.
And got, I can't remember the third movie I watched.
I'm fuzzy.
And the reason I'm fuzzy is because after I got it, and by the way, the apartment,
I don't know what happened to the cleaning crew,
but they went through this place like the white tornado.
Unbelievable.
They washed my bathrobe.
My toilet paper was even folded in a nice little, you know,
pointy thing that you get in hotels.
The silverware.
As you know, when we ordered all that stuff for the condo,
Patricia got 100, 100 knives, 100 forks,
and hadn't even unpacked half of them.
They were still in their plastic sheets.
Well, guess what?
Every single one was unpacked and organized in the draw.
All the draws were reorganized.
But it was fantastic.
I guess there's more women in my life now
that I don't even know about who we're doing a great job.
I love it. I love it. I love it.
So today we'll talk a little bit about pot-saving music network,
because we got to, we'll do that after the satellite window closes.
There's just some stuff that I wanted to catch up on.
Oh yeah, so I went to the HQ after enjoying the lovely fresh apartment.
You know, I figured you stop buying, say hi to everybody around 4 o'clock.
And it was jam, you walk in, it was just one big,
bubbling, lukewarm,
peachy dish of creativity.
You know, it could just feel it oozing all over the place.
It was fantastic.
You know, so I hung out and said hi to everybody, try to catch up.
And then around 6 o'clock everyone went next door to 21st Amendment,
which is like a bar restaurant that is literally next door to a pot-show HQ.
And so I thought I'd go hang out.
And you know how when you're, when you're,
I mean, after a transatlantic flight, you know,
I was hungry, but not really hungry.
You know, I still don't know where, you know,
I don't know my ass from my elbow, basically, at this point.
But then you think about having a martini with some olives,
you know, a gray goose, vodka martini, dirty olives.
And it almost makes you feel hungry for some reason.
When you're hungry, you can feel like, yeah,
that old, that kind of filled me up a little bit.
And as you know, I'm not a drinker at all.
So I think I had, I'm sure I had two.
Maybe I had three.
Whoa, oh man, it made like a ton of bricks.
I came back.
Actually, I didn't come back.
Richard Brewer, hey, brought me back.
He dropped me off and I came upstairs.
And I unpacked the rest of my suitcase,
which meant I literally threw all the elements of the studio,
which I carry with me through them down on the bar here,
and just went to bed.
You know, I was asleep by nine o'clock.
And just completely out.
I couldn't walk straight.
And I woke up.
I didn't even set an alarm.
You know, I woke up at, oh, was it?
Four o'clock?
Yeah, four, 15 a.m.
And even though my brain was completely awake,
and I'm ready and rocking and rolling to go,
like, okay, I'll get up.
And you know, I'll start prepping the show,
and going through just tons of email,
because when you travel for 10 hours,
you lose track of every email thread,
it's just so much incoming.
And I was still, who see I was still like walking around.
Oh, he's a,
I gotta stay away from drink.
It is not my poison.
Let me tell you.
So, on the show today,
some interesting feedback,
and this first one,
I definitely want to take a little bit of time
going through.
It's, it's from,
well, I'm not even going to tell you who is from.
It was from Vasily.
And I know Vasily.
In fact, he sent me this email,
said, do you remember your trip to Moscow in 1989?
I do.
I was there.
We met.
We worked together.
Now, it, of course,
you know, this doesn't immediately spark off all kinds of,
oh, yes.
Of course, I remember Vasily.
That was a very, very weird trip.
He says, I hope you find this bit of audio feedback entertaining.
Is anything I can do for you?
Let me know,
all the best to you and your family,
keep podcasting Vasily.
Okay.
So, let's, let's just go through this email.
Let me just set the stage for you.
This is 1989.
The Berlin Wall still firmly in place.
Doc McGee, manager of Bon Jovi,
Motley crew, Skid Row, and a couple others.
He had been busted for, I think,
he had a plane, a private jet or something
that had been confiscated
because it had, I don't know,
a couple tons of weed on board
that they were flying into Miami.
And anyways, a part of his get out of jail free.
He had to do a number of anti-alcohol anti-drug events.
And so he put together this Moscow Music Peace Festival,
which was, of course, a great idea
to take a whole bunch of rock and rollers.
Musicians, over to Lenin Stadium in Moscow
and put on a show.
And of course, MTV went along.
The whole show was, and these were the days,
I think Billy Joel had just been there two weeks before.
So there was a lot of stuff happening
in the East Block and it was really an interesting time
for musicians from the West to come in.
And so we actually took a plane from Newark.
And see, on the plane in Newark,
Ozzy was on there.
You know, the Bon Jovis, Montley Crew, Skid Row.
I don't remember everybody.
Giza Butler was on, of course, with Ozzy
for a mini black Sabbath reunion.
And it was just a regular chartered flight.
No first class, all kind of like an airbus,
like an easy jet idea.
And then we first flew to Germany to pick up the scorpions
and then from Germany went over to Russia.
It was a pretty long flight.
And I think I've talked about some of the things
that went on on the flight over there.
Then we arrived in Moscow.
And this was really the time when your passport
were confiscated upon entering the country.
And it was really, it was kind of weird and intense.
And then the hotel that we stayed in, in the middle of Moscow.
You know, it was a luxury hotel,
but this is pretty rich, rich Russia.
And the rest, excuse me, the rest, we really,
with the hell was that, oh, I guess I did set my alarm.
What is that?
What?
Hold on.
Oh.
Don't go away.
It'll never shut off if I don't do it.
Hold on a second.
Okay.
So that's how the vodka Martinez worked.
I don't even remember setting it alarm,
but it makes sense that I set it at 6 a.m.
to get going.
All right.
Let's continue.
So this hotel, which was the luxury hotel,
the mattresses were basically straw filled with straw.
There was warm water, but that was only because they turned on the warm water
in that particular section of the city just for us.
And it was weird because, oh, God.
How many alarms are going to go off here?
Stop this already.
Jesus Christ.
Interrupting the flow of my show.
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay.
I set two alarms.
I'm telling you, I should not be drinking martinis.
All right, continuing.
So you can imagine that this was a really, really weird vibe.
And I'm going to play this audio comment.
I'm going to interrupt it here and there to just give you some background.
What's some of the things that Vasily is talking about.
But now, of course, I do remember.
And he remembers my trip a lot better than I do.
Hello there, Adam.
This is Vasily Strunnikov in Moscow.
You might remember me from your trip to Russia in 1989
when you and MTV were here for the big music and peace festival
at Lenin Stadium with Bomb Jovis Cinderella's Skid Row and others.
I was your Russian-American translator.
Baby sitter.
Now, that's when I remembered.
Oh, yeah, I do remember we had a guy with spoke excellent English.
And the English he's speaking now is even better than I recall it.
And he was our guide.
Of course, there was no MTV Russia at the time,
but we'll get into that in a second.
Remember all the vodka and the late night parties at Gorky Park?
Yes, not just Gorky Park, but I think we went to the red square as well.
Now, you have to understand.
This was an anti-drug and anti alcohol concert.
And Vasily was completely trashed on the plane before we even,
you know, were out of the outside of US airspace.
I think I've told you that story where he was standing in the,
standing in the aisle next to the laboratory,
which someone was, you know, was occupied.
And he's just standing like,
Sherrad.
I got it.
And he didn't help.
And he just wet himself right there.
It was the most embarrassing thing.
Not just for him.
We were all embarrassed for him.
Okay.
So, yeah, lots, I remember lots of vodka,
Comrade.
I certainly, isn't that a coincidence that I had all the vodka last night
and we're talking about vodka again this morning?
A big boat with a KGB hookers.
There indeed, I don't know if it's still there,
but there was a boat.
And this boat was basically a horror house.
And there was also a bar and any Westerner could go,
could go to this boat.
And you walk a gangplank.
Oh, man, I'm starting to remember this now, gosh.
And there are all these little births and bunks and little doors.
And maybe 20 or something like that.
It was a reasonably sized boat or barge or whatever.
And they were all hookers.
But of course, they were all KGB hookers.
And at least that's what we were told.
It's like, whatever you do, man, you do not want to have sex
with any of the hookers over there because they're all affiliated with the KGB.
And what they'll do is they'll blackmail you.
And then before you know it, you're going to be an agent.
You'll have to be spying on your own country because they'll blacken out.
It's like, whoa.
And by the way, let me just say,
not that I would do anything like that anyway.
But there was nothing there for me, my friends.
Nothing.
Or the time Kurt Loader got so loaded that we almost blocked him
at Red Square.
In fact, he's sin along a picture,
which I'm going to post along with opposite on curry dot com
along with the show notes.
He has a picture of Kurt Loader completely hammered on a chair
with some woman hanging over him.
I don't remember who she was.
But yes, I do remember we lot.
We couldn't find Kurt.
He was gone.
It was gone for hours.
This is one of our like three a.m.
Hey, let's, it's a great idea.
Let's go drink some vodka on Red Square.
Yeah, that'll be fun.
Which, of course, it was.
And at that time, oh my God,
the Moscow Hell's Angel showed up.
Completely outlawed group of guys,
you know, driving Java motorcycles and popping off,
popping wheelies and flipping off the back.
And very, very intense scene.
So yes, I remember that particularly Kurt getting so loaded
and we lost him.
Picture will be on curry dot com.
Check it out in the show notes for today.
The stories, the memories.
You know what's interesting?
You and I have quite a few things in common.
Like you, I spent my childhood in Maryland.
I've been in broadcasting for over 25 years.
I am a former MTV VJ.
MTV Russia, that is.
And like you,
I advocate and support podcasting.
In my case, Russian podcasting.
About a year ago, while listening to your show,
I thought, why not start podcasting in Russia?
So we launched Russia's first and only podcast directory site
at Russianpodcasting.ru.
Now, the local press are having a field day with this.
They can't get enough of the fact that there is something
strange about XMTVVJs that makes them engage in such activities as podcasting.
They mention you and their articles all the time, Adam.
Anyway, we're celebrating our first anniversary with a big conference,
and a big shout out to all Russians around the world,
listening to your show to check us out at Russianpodcasting.ru.
And speaking of Russians around the world,
remember the time in 1989 when you were bored in the production office at Lenin Stadium?
You know, there was a lot of boredom during that week we were there.
I'll tell you that.
So yeah, I remember some of it.
And you grabbed a polaroid camera and started taking pictures of yourself.
Well, another famous Russian in the international podcast community,
Marc Yoshimoto Nemtsoff has my exclusive on that story.
But if you play this bit of feedback, I'm willing to renegotiate.
Hold on a second, you think a comma, commie dickhead?
What do you blackmailing me now?
Like, you're some KGB hooker on a barge?
I'm not afraid, man.
Actually, when I heard this, you heard this audio comment.
And then it got to this point, I'm like, oh, man, you know, the voice, everything.
It's a joke.
It's a specific host to Hellway joke.
But it isn't because this guy is for real.
Vasily is for real.
Russian podcasting.ru is for real.
The Kurt Loder picture I put up is for real.
The stories are for real.
And we should really do a Skype conference because I've been feeling that Vasily will remember
a hell of a lot more than I did, but maybe when he recalls some of the things that
that happened during that trip, I might be able to chime in.
But, you know, man, don't go blackmailing me.
Just some of the damn pictures I'll post him.
There's nothing I can be here for.
I'm ashamed of absolutely not.
Come on, man.
And I played your thing anyway.
Thanks for all good luck and dolls.
Vidanya.
Don't come red curry.
Rosridania.
Hey, there you go.
Come red curry.
That's a good one.
It's come red curry in the curry condo.
Coming to you from Northern California.
And it's actually looking outside.
I think it's going to be, um, looks like it's going to be overcast.
There's no sun coming up yet.
Man, there's so many people going to work at this time in the morning.
There's already a traffic jam almost coming off of the Bay Bridge.
And I noticed that the Coca-Cola sign is broken.
It just says enjoy, which is kind of nice.
The Coca-Cola piece never appears.
It just says enjoy.
And it stays there all night.
All right, Vasily.
Very cool, man.
Good to hear from you.
I really appreciate the Kurt Loder pick.
And I appreciate you reminding me of some of the things that some of the things that
the took place during that infamous trip for the Moscow Music Peace Festival, which I guess
the whole concert was, uh, was recorded.
I remember MTV aired.
I don't know if they still have it or if they'll ever aired again, but it was,
it was definitely good times, my friend.
Good times.
And, uh, well, kind of staying over in that region of the world, way
Yantan, send me an email.
Adam, hope that podcasting will kick off in China.
My thoughts are that it will.
But as soon as a comment is made about the country values,
perhaps communist or otherwise, the government or the internet police.
Hmm, I didn't know they had actual internet police, but wouldn't put it past them.
They will ban it.
We are talking about a country that changed the title of Despert Housewives to Crazy Housewives
and censored all the sex scenes because they thought it was too promiscuous.
Oh, that's interesting.
If you take out all the sex scenes out of Despert Housewives, what's left of the show?
I wonder how Pacifico's hellway or East Radio will even get to air in China.
I would really love to hear what you have to say about that at a future daily source code way.
Yeah.
Thank you very much, way.
Well, it's going to be interesting, you know.
I think, I guess that you're in China.
So you obviously know about Pacifico's hellway and East Radio.
I think that, you know, that's one thing.
And what's probably much more interesting and exciting is to see what the Chinese are going to do with podcasting.
And what are they going to be sending our way?
I think that's the stuff that is exciting and interesting.
There's enough ways for the Chinese to understand what's going on in the culture in the West,
but for us to understand what's going on there is a completely different story.
And with all the millions and millions of portable devices and cell phones,
I think that we're going to be able to learn quite a lot about podcasting from portable devices.
And we certainly hope to reach our 100 million mini screens in China as we're going for 100 million listeners here.
In the US and in Europe.
And actually today, I have a meeting.
It's going to be a good meeting with British telecom.
Out here, all their marketing mucks are here for some conference or something.
And they've asked Ron and I to come over and talk about podcasting.
Could this finally be the kick in the pants that the United Kingdom needs to really get it all cranking?
I think it's very possible.
These guys definitely have a hold on a lot of the broadband market.
And I think determined a lot of what is taking place in the UK as it pertains to alternate forms of media.
And now the BBC is getting very, very close to releasing a lot of shows as podcasts.
In fact, people send me a couple of links to shows that haven't been publicized yet,
but our podcast, there's a daily news podcast that I like a lot,
that's kind of a collection of all the BBC radio news shows.
And it's about, you know, 15, 20 minutes perfect to catch up on.
If you just want to know what's happening in the world of, of onty of the BBC.
But they still don't actually talk a lot about podcasts and they talk about web casting or alternative radio.
And so, you know, there could be something going on there.
Those of you listening to a serious channel 102.
This is the daily source code part of the pod show line up.
Up next, we will have Pacific Coastel way.
Followed by yeast radio and Dawn and Drew.
We'll take you up until 10 o'clock eastern time, 7 Pacific.
And I'll see you back here tomorrow.
Bye-bye.
And for those of you still hanging out on the podcast, let's continue, shall we?
I've got a few things that I wanted to catch up on.
I just didn't feel right about, you know, dropping the topics of,
let's see, internet surcharges.
It's one thing that we've been talking about.
I've got so many different pieces of feedback.
So many people, you know, weighing in on what this means and how it's going to work.
And it seems to be actually still quite confusing.
Here's a comment about it.
Let's see what this is.
Hello.
How many are you so soft?
It's a Charlie 340 last night and heard the comments by the listener.
Pretending to tear your internet, the stemmed from your discussion of DSC.
AT&T's proposed acquisition of Bell South.
There seems to be a lot of misconceptions running around the internet,
especially in the podcasting community of what the R box true intentions are.
Unfortunately, they do not articulate those intentions very well.
Their management, they're well, their dinosaurs, frankly.
And they're not very good at communicating with their customers,
the public.
Unfortunately, that's not their fault so much as a problem that exists in the,
in the environment they've been brought up in as they've risen through the ranks.
What they're really talking about here is a differentiated service,
not shutting off any or blocking any potential services of people that don't pay the ransom
or giving any crummy services because you don't pay this so called ransom,
but providing a better quality service for those people that want to provide
a specific time-sensitive services.
I'm just going to stop this right here, hold on a second.
I'm going to reconfigure everything, oh man.
I don't buy it at all.
You know, what's happening is it's happening all over the media landscape
and telecommunications landscape.
We've known for years and years that all the things the telephone line does
can be done through IP through internet protocol traffic.
This is what we're seeing with all these voiceover IP services.
I literally think that we're at this point now where voiceover IP and people
using Skype or Vonage or what have you is really hurting the telecos business.
They're seeing all this money they're pouring into backbones.
They're seeing basically that they're not a part of the content piece.
This is what's happening.
Now whether I'm making a phone call to you over the internet,
or whether I'm making a podcast, or whether whatever it is,
they understand unlike the Dutch court system.
They understand that that content has a much higher value than the roads that it
travels over.
And they want a piece of it.
That's basically it.
They're looking at Google saying, oh shit.
You know, these guys are making money.
Thanks to our pipes.
Yeah, we'll not just your pipes.
Thanks to a whole bunch of people's pipes.
And now that I'm investigating this situation more,
it's going to be very hard for them to do any of this,
this metering or this prioritizing of packets.
And less everyone is full, I think.
And this is just a layman speaking here.
And less everyone is fully, what is it?
IPv6 compatible.
So version 6 of the internet protocol.
And so maybe it's just a lot of talk.
Maybe they'll try to do it through legislation.
But whatever happens, it is definitely in my mind,
not the way to make this, to make this all.
I'd rather pay more money just for my monthly bandwidth bill
than have, you know, services being taxed.
And maybe services that I'll never get to because, well, low and behold,
a small company or a bunch of entrepreneurs who just want to get something
going can't actually afford to do it anymore,
which is not the spirit of the internet at all.
And not the spirit of all these tools we've been building to make it
very cheap and easy.
You know, these are people trying to build walled gardens.
Same goes for the email tax.
Let's just call it a tax.
I mean, but it's not a government tax.
It's like airport tax.
In fact, airport.
It's very like airport tax.
You know what you go somewhere.
And you know, you, the tickets, let's just say,
to take it costs 100 bucks and then your hotel costs 100 bucks.
At the end of the day, you wind up paying 300 bucks for the vacation.
And they say, well, you know, it's all these airport taxes.
Well, airport tax is basically a landing fee.
It's what the airport, the airport charges the carrier to take you there.
It's not, when they say tax, you immediately think,
well, that means it's a government thing and it was nothing we can do about it.
Bullshit.
It's just money that is the cost of doing business for an airline.
And it's been, it's very much like these ISPs and email.
If you want your email delivered, then you're going to have to start paying a tax in
future.
Check this out.
You know, it's not just, oh, there's a whole bunch of shenanigans going on
with email between large email service providers.
Let's call on that.
So if you have a hot mail account, you're pretty much screwed on all
things because you're, you're not getting a lot of mail.
And of course, interestingly enough, hot mail delivers the most spam to you,
than any other, any other email service.
Chris says, I don't have an Apple dot Mac account.
And I cannot email people at Yahoo.
My email never shows up in Yahoo mailbox as when sending it from my dot
Mac account to large companies.
And they can't figure this out.
Come on, not to mention I pay $99 for my email service.
Well, that is, of course, an outrage.
And of course, it's all, I think it's illegal to stuff that's going on.
This is illegal.
So we have our email stuff set in place.
It'll be up and rolling next week sometime.
You know, we've got the, the way we got the strong mail service.
So you get like boxes, you know, hardware and software and then the service.
And apparently now we should have, I mean, even castblaster dot com is getting
crap now in registration emails.
It's just, it's a freaking outrage.
So even though this is one I'd like to fight, we also have a business to run.
So I guess all I can do is keep talking about this horrible precedent that's being set
as companies now charging for delivery of email.
And you should just not stand for it.
You know, if you're paying for email and you're paying for sending email or receiving email,
you know, you should be receiving email.
And you should be sending email.
It should be working.
And they should put the owners on your, on your ISP.
You'll see.
You'll see before too long, you're going to notice that some of your emails aren't showing up.
Excuse me.
I get so excited about this stuff.
So we're just keeping our eye on it.
I think there's a project called Goodmail.
I think it's goodmail.
I'll have to look into it.
But, you know, the end of the day, all these individual ISPs.
So if you leave, you have your email through Yahoo or Hotmail or MSN or Gmail or Apple.
However, you get your email, Comcast, perhaps.
They are the ones that are supposed to deliver the email to you.
And they're basically not.
Sure.
They're saying it's for spam.
But, you know, to some people, spam is desired.
And maybe that's something you still want to handle on the client end,
actually when the email comes down to you.
You have to be in continuous conversation about this stuff.
Because without a doubt, I'd say most of it is wrong.
Ah.
Yes.
Of course.
The network continues to grow.
I'd love this, too.
Unfortunately, it's not a happy mood, doesn't it?
Hello.
Coming to you from the Pod Show Network.
It's the all-creator show with your hosts.
Everyone's favorite, that Nurian, Dr. Lee, Quarbridge,
and I'm his wife, Robin.
When you see an alligator in the wild in Florida, go the other way.
Yeah, this is not a bad thing.
It's time for animal stuff where you have fun and learn something too.
Animal sound of the week.
Can you guess what it is?
This is the breed of the week section.
That was it.
Uh-oh, uh-oh, pick me, pick me, pick me.
Yeah.
It would be really cool.
It's animal trivia time.
This is the part where you get to see how much you really know.
All critters were talking Robin.
Everything animals from medical conditions to just chat.
We covered all.
Have fun and learn something too.
Find us at all critters.pot show.com.
Hi, Adam. This is Doc.
Hi, and this is Robin.
And we just wanted to say thank you for inviting us to join the Pod Show Network.
We're extremely excited to be a part of the Quit Your Day Job Group.
We feel honored that you chose us,
and we just wanted you to know that we appreciate it.
We're looking forward to our long journey together.
Pod Show Rocks.
It was still in the pinch me stage that we're a part of it.
We also wanted to say that we love the daily source code,
and we're totally addicted to it.
Keep up the great work.
Thanks again for having all critters on the Pod Show Network.
And thanks for playing our promo.
Hey, I wonder if Adam is trying to guess what animal sound that was.
Should we tell him?
Nah, let's keep everyone guessing.
Then we'll have to listen to the show.
Animal sounds are so cool.
To go line that with the animal trivia,
a medical conditions we cover.
We just wanted everyone to have fun and learn something too.
How critters experience it at all critters.podshow.com?
I think it was a go for.
I'm pretty sure of it.
Hey, some interesting stuff going on in France.
France is considering a law that gives consumers the right
to break digital rights management.
Better known as DRM.
Just going to pull up the story here.
A couple people emailed this to me.
I just want to tell you what the deal is.
This is pop up from silicon.com.
And here we go.
A law currently making its way through French Parliament
could see Apple's fair play DRM opened up.
Now, this is the way that Apple protects all the songs
that you purchase from iTunes and use on your iPod.
Change it to the French Dwatt Delta copyright law.
Currently being debated in Parliament
are expected to be voted on this week.
Among the changes, the controversial legislation
will bring in will be measures to effectively dismantle all types
of digital rights management, including the technology
that prevent content from Apple's music stores being played
on Microsoft devices and vice versa.
Check this out.
The law will enshrine the right to interoperability
between content and devices.
Which, of course, is really a great idea.
Effectively allowing consumers to break
or otherwise circumvent DRM and play music
on the MP3 player of their choice.
This is really exciting stuff.
In a recent parliamentary debate, Dominic Rishard
a diputee from the UNP coalition described the law
as instituting interoperability
that will stop content being the hostage of technology
and authorized creativity using free as in speech software.
The law will also overhaul the country's legal system
with regard to music piracy giving those convicted
of downloading-pired music a fixed 38-year-old fine
and those convicted of illegally making music available
for download a 150-year-old fine,
which I think is probably much more in line
with the value of what is being stolen
if someone steals music basically.
So I think what's happening here is what they're saying
is you would be allowed to reencode
something you bought off of iTunes for your iPod
into another open format if it's for personal use.
And of course this is very exciting.
Who knows, what a thunket man coming from the French.
I think this is great.
So let's keep our eye on that one
because it's definitely definitely something cool
going on in France when it comes to licensing
and digital rights management.
And if you can break it there,
well, I guess you can break it to anywhere, can't you?
Hey, I'm as Jay Mac from producer and webmaster slash
whatever of the hoody.com show
calling you from warm Detroit.
I wanted to call and say thank you very, very much
for your continued support of the hoody.com show
and our movement, everything we do
and I really, really appreciate that.
And it's always good to hear that you're actually
listening to the show.
I thank you for that.
So I'm also leaving this voice message
to ask you about pardon me in driving and kind of out there.
I wanted to ask you about licensing with ASK at BMI.
And I said you an email, but I don't expect to reply.
So I'm hoping this voice message will be even better.
So here's my question.
We interview obviously some good artists,
some big artists in the industry of hip-hop.
And it's getting better.
I mean, like coming up we have, you know,
boss derirons was coming up in April and, you know,
we're going to be interviewing TI and people like that.
Some pretty big names, so I mean,
but the problem with it is is that a lot of these artists,
they don't really want to do the interview unless
you're going to be playing their music.
That's the whole reason they're doing the interview
is for publicity.
So here's, you know, obviously here's my issue.
We want to be able to play some of their music
and we don't want to necessarily play the entire track.
I mean, we're cool with just playing
their instrumental behind the interview
and then maybe playing a 10 or 15 or 20 second clip
of their track after or during the interview as well,
like of one of their singles or biggest single or something like that.
So, I mean, my question is, you know,
do you necessarily need a ASK at BMI license just to do that?
I mean, because it doesn't seem necessary
if you're not playing the whole song.
If the whole song can't be taken,
then why should you get to pay a licensing fee?
We're helping them promote their music.
You know, I mean, it's a trade, you know,
it's a hit-for-tat type of thing.
So, I'm really curious to hear if there's a way around that.
It's really frustrating.
I mean, I actually talked to somebody over at ASKAP
and the second I said podcast or internet,
they started getting skittish.
They started weirding out and they don't want to talk about it
and you need licensing.
You got a license.
You got a white license.
Internet license or whatever the fuck they call it.
You got to have internet license.
You got to have it.
You know, I read about it.
It's like $300 a year.
And then there's like a per-download fee,
which is bullshit to me.
So, there's got to be a way.
I will provide and read and you'll know the way
is to get the actual person who holds the master's
like the label or the artist to sign off.
I'm letting us play their track.
You know, which is like, come on.
I mean, in the mainstream industry, there's no record label
that's going to sign, you know,
some sort of contract like that.
There's no way.
You know, they're going to want to get the ASKAP
BMI fees.
You know, if there's any to be had.
So, I'm hoping if there's anybody out there
or if you know the answer to this,
I'd really appreciate it.
And I'm hoping it works in our favor
because we really, really, really don't want to get
a license through ASKAP to do this shit.
We'd really like to handle this without paying that money.
I mean, it's, we figured it's a fair trade
if we're promoting the artist.
We're getting, you know, we get to play a clip of their song
and play their voice on the show.
I mean, it's to trade off.
I don't know.
Okay. So, he continues on a little bit
and leaves his cell phone numbers.
So, I won't play that.
You know, this is a question that I get asked a lot.
And I'm not a lawyer, of course,
but the official answer is yes.
I mean, you need to have a license
to be able to use any type of license music
through the RIA or otherwise
or if it's licensed through ASKAP BMI.
You have to have a license for the performance,
which means you're basically using that
as a part of your podcast.
And then just to cover all the bases
because record companies, I think the lawyers
are the record companies pretty much
feel that, you know, this is a mechanical distribution
because you're actually downloading something
and it's going on to a disc of some sort
so that the royalty has to be paid for that as well.
So, you're right.
And the fees just don't make sense
because, you know, I was even looking at the UK,
MCPS, NPCS, PRS, whatever the combined license
we talked about the other day.
And even though the licensing is now starting
to get worked out, you know,
and of course, that's to pay 12% of my gross profit.
Yeah, do I got a blow job with that?
You know, you start looking at it
and then all those strictions
and the money it's going to cost you to think,
oh, why won't I do it?
Why won't I even promote that industry?
Now, of course, for hood hype,
you know, it is great to talk to people
like Buster Rimes and, you know,
and they're always working with lots of independent talent.
And I think in reality,
if you interview them and you use 10,
15 seconds of a track, you know, behind him,
I don't think anyone's going to sue you,
but they could, you know,
so you're definitely taking a risk
and again, I will say to the record industry again.
This is the stupidest way
to try and license your music.
It's not going to get you any value
because very few podcasts are kind of for it
and the ones that can,
I think most of them that can.
I mean, I'd much rather promote
Michael Butler, Matthew Ebel,
a lower clap or brother love.
You know, these are, these are people
who do appreciate it,
and are trying to charge me
for the privilege of playing their music.
You know, it's true that.
What you should do is have a special button in iTunes
or wherever you want to make your music available
for download.
And if someone is going to download it
for use on a podcast,
charge them five bucks.
You know, it's a one shot deal.
There's plenty of songs.
I would just love to play.
And I bet you I would play a five dollar song
every single day.
So what would that be?
150 bucks.
You're talking almost,
probably around $2,000 a year,
you would make for my show.
You know,
let's talk about the hit test,
which I would love to bring back.
I'll pay for three.
So I'll pay 15 bucks for a hit test
to be able to put a hit test together.
You're not, of course, I will.
That's the way to do it.
I'm not going to give you 12% of the gross revenue
of my show for that privilege
for playing your back catalog.
So, and by the way, musicians,
you're the ones that should be revolting
against this stupid behavior
of your record companies,
stupid, it's just stupid.
Okay, a couple more pots
of music network things,
just as I said,
to catch up on where we are
and some of the conversations
because by probably by this time next week,
we'll have our email registrations working fully
with the strong mail.
So that means we'll be able to open up
full sales across the network.
Had some great conversations about this last night,
I was sitting with Chris Rockwell,
Sue, Kevin, Matt Oliver, Richard Brueher,
and we were really just shooting the shit
about all kinds of stuff and feeling
just feeling the love.
And the fact that we're going to be integrating
a lot of the Podsate Music Network
into the whole, you know, Pod Show Plus
or Pod Show PDN.
So what all kind of have a very consistent look
and feel everything all flow into each other
and, of course, Andrew Grumman is working on
API so that any other service
will be able to integrate the Podsate Music Network
into their service as well.
But I believe that,
well, we were talking about
actually opening up
both the podcasting and listening side
of Pod Show, the network,
sometime next week.
And I think we're ready.
Now, of course, it'll be super beta
because shit's just going to break
and shit does happen.
But I also think we'll be able to,
show real fast growth every single, you know,
day almost after that adding new features
because we've just gotten to the point
where we're so far ahead with all the features
and things we want in there
that if you look back to what our goals
were for release,
I think we're there.
I really do.
And it's funny, you know,
Ron and I were kind of like,
looking at the development team looking
for a signal from them to say,
okay, we're ready to release
and I think they were waiting
from a signal for us.
And somehow I felt that
and that's what, that's what three
vodka martinis will do for you.
Really brings you closer down to reality
as what has to be done.
So maybe Wednesday, maybe Wednesday.
And this means that all kinds of shit
is going to be funky.
It's going to be broken all over the map.
But this is kind of how it works.
You know, this is the way
development is done these days.
You get something out there
and just keep improving it.
We'll keep the conversation going.
We'll do a lot of it through
the daily source code and other pod show
podcasts to get feedback.
Already I've gotten several emails
and people saying, hey,
what's up with the funky URLs?
Turn it back to the original way you used to do it.
No, I can't do that right now.
We're working on all of these aspects.
Everything is, you know,
if we're trying to get it all
come together simultaneously.
We've got a huge promotion
starting up a network wide
with the single sponsor
that'll also and every single show
that wants to is going to be involved in it.
There's just a lot of goodness on the way.
And as I said, a whole bunch of great improvements
for the pod sake music network.
Adam, it's Russell from the Dark Matters podcast here.
Also from Brisbane Australia.
So that's at least two of us here.
So I think you're also a trip
when you come down under.
All right, mate.
You know, I see you like my recommendation
of Bob Ferry for DSC339
and we must have similar tastes in music
because I put out episode three
of Dark Matters yesterday
and I want to be held when I listen to
DSC this morning.
You had the same song
Do the heavy mouth in heaven
on episode three
for eight of the Charlie.
You know, and that is really coincidence.
I mean, I listen to, as you know,
tons of podcasts and that's where I got
a lot of inspiration,
which of course is the whole point of the unlabel.
You know, there is no central spot.
So in this case,
I didn't hear your show
and I wasn't influenced by it,
but I would probably
was influenced by some other show.
And that's how it works.
You know, I'm continuously amazed
at how many plays
some songs are getting on the PMN.
I mean, it's in the thousands.
It's just, it's fantastic.
You know, I thought I'd just ring up
and let you know,
I finally got around to trying out
the click and buy purchase of
Putsay for Peace.
So I've been in Australian
credit card holder.
I went through the click and buy process
and because of the first time
when I somehow missed putting
Australia in the country,
which really mucked me up,
I went back and tried again
and when I got the details right,
everything went through sweet.
So I never have
my own purchased copy of
Putsay for Peace
and Australian people
can use it successfully
apparently.
I don't know if they've improved
since the last listeners tried.
That seems to be up and going there.
Just though you might like to know
and if any of you listeners
would like to visit my podcast,
you can find it at
Astronomy.podcastfilmet.com
and until next time,
thanks guys.
What kind of skies?
Dark skies.
That didn't say dark skies.
Yep.
So just want to let you know
that it is working in Australia.
But again,
I think it does depend on
the type of credit card or something
that have been some
funky results for some folks around the world.
Oh, you know,
I wasn't that hammer to remember
last night.
Chris Rockwell was doing
some of the math with me.
And he says,
So what if podshow
would only make about
four or five cents per song
that was sold through the podset
music network?
He says,
that doesn't seem like
it's really worth it
and maybe we shouldn't even take
that money at all.
Of course,
which I said is,
oh great.
So how about if we,
if every song sold,
we deduct four cents
from your salary?
And you know what?
He said,
yeah, no problem.
I'll do it immediately.
And so that caught my attention
because I was just being
facetious.
But if you do the math
and you think about
if we were to sell
a million songs in a year,
which I think would be quite
a lot.
That would be what?
$40,000.
Because there's also taxes
that go into the purchase price
and we want podcasters
to be able to.
They don't have to.
They can donate it back to the band
or wherever they want
to be able to take
an affiliate fee.
And the more,
the more I think about it,
the more I think that he may be right.
You know,
maybe just having people
sign up to the network
is enough value
for podshow.
It's definitely something
I'm going to discuss today
at the office.
And I do want to leave all
options open.
But you know, as we said,
certainly during the whole
date of period,
which will be months,
we're not taking a dime
from any of this.
We're just going to have
the click and buy
transaction fee,
which is nine cents.
And we do want to put the
the affiliate,
the affiliate stuff
into place,
which I think is already
in there.
And I guess the songs
that you can now purchase
as of today are American
heartbreaking, including the new one
that I played for you today.
Podsafe for Peace
and some Matthew Eble,
so I'm Matthew Eble has been selling
quite crazy.
I'm not at liberty to tell you,
but he's sold,
I really a significant amount
of songs.
It's definitely beer money,
definitely beer money,
very beer and some gas money.
So extremely pleased to see
that happening.
A couple more things about
PMN here.
Hi, Adam.
This is Tom from the
fog view podcast.
I've been doing a few podcasts now
and has some feedback
for the Podsafe music network.
The first couple items here
were mentioned by listeners,
a few shows back,
but I think it bears repeating.
The first one is to bring back
the music ratings.
I think that was a very useful
feature.
And I know it got replaced
when you added the pay button,
but it would be nice
to be able to bring that back.
You know, that's interesting
that you say that.
It didn't really get replaced
by the buy button.
It did on the page,
but there was so much feedback,
particularly from artists
who said they did not want
the ratings feature there.
And I have to agree with you
that from a podcaster perspective
and perhaps from a listener perspective,
I thought it was kind of handy
because, you know,
if I'm surfing through the
PMN,
it's at music.podshow.com,
by the way.
You know,
and I'd find a song
that maybe I'd like the sound
of the voice or whatever.
I'll click on the artist link
or I'll go to the artist page
and there would be,
you know,
definitely some feedback.
And it either has all three stars,
which I think,
maybe that's part of the problem is
you start off
and you're always right in the middle of
three stars.
And some of them would actually
have a higher rating
and those would be the songs
that listen to right up front.
So maybe we take that out
or maybe it's configurable
or I don't know.
But it's definitely something
to think about.
I'm not completely an agreement
that they're gone in their entirety.
So I think that,
yeah,
maybe the artist hated it
because they don't like to be rated,
which is another thing
to take into consideration.
But from a podcaster perspective,
finding the song that you want
and having some form of feedback
is important.
Now,
when we unleash the podshow
and the podshow PDN,
you're going to see that we do have
some a lot of interactive pieces
that we've put into place.
So people can let their
feelings and comments be known
about podcasts,
but also about other listeners.
So you're going to see
some integration of that
into songs and artists.
So it may not be the star's rating system,
but we are bringing something back
that I think you'll like
and we'll satisfy your needs.
Second is
with more and more record companies
uploading music.
They're putting their name
into the artist's field,
and then they're forcing the song
artist and title into the title field.
In some cases,
they're only putting the song title
into the title field,
which makes it very confusing.
Yeah, yeah,
you're right about that.
Another thing that will be solved.
So labels,
and of course,
the concept of what is a label
in the unlabel world,
will be able to have a collection of
favorite artists.
So actually,
I could be a label.
Now that when we integrate
all these pieces together,
and I could say here are the
ten artists that are on my label.
Of course,
don't really have a label,
but they are artists
that I'll play on my podcast.
They are artists
that I want you to as a listener
to my show to check out.
And I'll also be helping
to sell some of that music
and as a podcaster,
or as a listener
who has a collection of artists
and songs that you'll kind of
call your label,
you'll be able to participate
in the proceeds of that.
So that will also be solved,
but not in the way you're seeing it today,
but anyone will be able to be a label,
which also means, of course,
actual labels will have the same functionality.
As if it can create another place
to put the record companies name done,
and then use the artist
and title for what it's intended.
The third one has to do with some
strange song names, song titles.
I see titles like Delete the song,
I remove this file.
And I think what's happening
is that artists are trying to remove
something from the network,
not able to do it,
and then they end up renaming it
and hopes that somebody will go through
and see that and remove it.
So looks like that means it will be cleaned up.
Yeah, you're right.
And that's because it's very easy to upload a song,
but not very easy to remove it,
which is kind of stupid on our part.
So that, of course, will all be fixed.
You'll be able to totally manage that.
And I'm just going to skip over the last bit,
and the next comment actually,
because the next logical piece is the ID3 tags,
and you know that the entire pod show,
HQ, listens to the show,
so they're already on it.
When you upload a song,
you will actually be forced to fill out
a number of pieces of information of metadata,
and those will be written into the ID3 tags,
if they're not already there,
of each song uploaded,
so we'll have great ID3 tag information.
We'll have a much richer database of information.
Oh, we just hired this new guy,
he's a search specialist.
God, man, it's nice to have a search specialist
in the house.
So, sod just hit the ground,
running, I think, this week,
and we're going to have some great search opportunities,
both for pod state music,
as well as for podcasts,
really integrating the context
and relevance of show notes.
And obviously, also search on different users.
So, that's all in the works.
Now, let's see a couple more things
I just wanted to catch up on.
Thank you to everyone who sent in
the information that the cube product
that was talking about
is part of the email tax solution,
was the cobalt cube,
and later they came out with the RAC, RAC cube.
And of course, that was bought by son,
and I think it pretty much died
a very short, effective death,
because it was just way too cool
and cutting into sons,
core business for some reason.
So, thanks for that.
Phil Walker, just a funny one here.
He says, I'm listening to Chuck 350,
and you're throwing the Roger Smalls MP3
into the soundtrack.
I leap up to answer my mobile phone
because it's got the Roger Smalls ringtone on it,
and then I realize it's the Charlie Pump
and through the office speakers.
So, I sit down and the bloody mobile
fires up with Rogers again.
Is it the phone or is it Adam?
Is it Roger?
That's what you get in there
and for using Roger Smalls is a ringtone.
All right, final song for the day,
and then I'm going to take a shower,
get dressed and get ready to go to the shop.
I'm actually going to bring this up
because this is a new addition, new entry,
it was put in,
how can I can't find pods,
if music network here is so long.
You know what? I'll play the song
and then I'll find the information.
It's a Dutch band from the northern part
of the Netherlands from Croningen.
They call themselves Tunebone.
And this is a real,
very popular type of music in the Netherlands.
You hear a lot of it more on the eastern side
out towards Germany in what we call the back corner
or the Achterhook,
with dance like normal
and you'll think it to food or beetles.
And just whenever I hear a tune like this,
it's such a combination of almost like Scandinavian influences,
really heavy accents that only belong
to the north or the eastern parts of the Netherlands,
and just plain whole goddamn good rock and roll.
I'll be the neck.
This should wake you up.
Certainly doing it for me.
I'll be the neck.
And we're gonna sing!
That's what I know for real.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know, I know I've been here.
Lacks on the river, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on
on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, in accordance with the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot, on the spot
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, okay, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, any of us, A  is broken up, ah, there has no time left for you, I am still on the way, there have to be sorry Ye comunic for you. You know,, Swane, I want to show off your keyprocessing that you come back from a very schoolship, start in there. Pick yourtus forgot yesterday, you know, what are the trains take at all all but they think about you, we are running a.
Once you don't live there anymore, I really do like the songs that these guys do.
And as I said, there's a couple of bands in Holland that do it.
They never get mainstream radio or rarely get mainstream radio aeroplane.
And if it is, maybe it's one song a year or something that'll make it into the charge.
So happy to share that one with you.
Okay, it is light outside now.
I don't think it's going to be a very nice day.
I see no sun coming up over the bay.
I just see clouds and concrete.
So nice show, damn, over an hour.
All right, we'll see what happens tomorrow.
You know, Cali Lewis is going to be up here in San Francisco.
We might be doing some video stuff together.
There's always people stopping by.
There's still a chance that we might be going to South by Southwest.
I mean, I don't know what's happening.
I'll let you know tomorrow.
And hopefully you'll be back then.
DailySourceco.com is where you can find this podcast and
subscribe to its podcast feed.
Adamacrui.com is where you can send feedback.
And I really appreciate your list.
See tomorrow.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast.
And we're great ones like it.
On the high performance podcast,
Delivery Network from Pod Show.
And limelight networks.
I love it.