This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want to hear content with?
That has domain name.
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 377.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Dreaming of the past is all that I have.
To chase away those mundane morning blues.
Feeling like a fool.
Paying by the rules.
Knowing that I can never win.
The fun day born in blues have got me down.
Out of the road from town to town.
Just my day born in blues are all around.
We're real like a the only spot of me down.
Tuesday Wednesday Thursday Friday Saturday Sunday.
I think that my day don't let some day become my day.
And these blues retain.
We've got a penny in my pocket.
When I pay you and you to help me turn to help me.
I've never had these with my day morning blues.
Those mundane morning blues will let you down.
Better run in the night before you can be the man.
Those mundane morning blues are all around.
Johnny Proctor Monday morning blues.
The way I feel today.
How you doing everybody?
That's of course in the pod save music network.
Just picked it up by searching for blues.
Not that I'm really bluesy, but it's a bank holiday here in the UK.
Of course the show coming to you from Curry Cottage in the affluent suburb of.
Sorry, known as Guildford.
It says bank holiday.
We went through that Friday is I think only the banks are closed.
They're just counting their money probably their profits.
So I got up this morning.
Actually, we went out to dinner last night with the neighbors with Jimmy and Marion.
They're retired, but they're very active in local social life.
So it's a good way to find out what's going on in the neighborhood and who's doing what to whom and why and how deep.
And so this morning, I was really really tired because last week was just felt like the longest week in history.
And I didn't.
Patricia, let me sleep because Christine, of course, had it there from school.
Normally I would take it to school in the whole routine.
We'd start around 7, 7, 30 a.m.
And so I'm looking at my watch and I can laugh.
I'm like, oh, yeah, it's nice time to get up.
And then I'm literally just doping around and all of a sudden I realize, wait a minute, it's Monday.
I got stuff to do here.
There's no bank holiday in the US.
I gotta be prepared and by the way, it's a Monday.
There's no vacation, no rest for the wicked.
Not for the daily source code.
I'm really trying to stick to our daily schedule.
Really trying to keep it to 40 minutes.
Really trying to just have some fun with y'all.
Lots of second life stuff going on over the week.
I want to talk about that in our second life talk.
You see now it's SLT in the show notes, actually.
So it's weird.
You know that we're in this time warp.
Oh, yeah.
It's really, really hard to get into the whole Monday vibe.
Hence the Monday morning blues.
Where's that guy from Johnny Proctor?
South Carolina.
And he's had some success.
Four pages of songs upon the PMN.
Excellent.
Okay.
Right off the bat portions of the show sponsored by GoDaddy.
You heard that the beginning of the show.
If you want a registered domain name for the Ultra Super low cheap price of 695,
upon checkout use the code DSC3.
And you'll get that domain for 695.
Been reading a lot in the weekend over the paper.
Actually, over the weekend, the Sunday papers were full of this huge scandal here in Britain.
A minister of parliament.
He's been having not won, but well, at first we thought he'd just been having one affair.
He's been married to his wife for a think.
Was it 20 or 25 years?
And he basically had an affair.
A two year affair with his.
I think I don't know if it's always his schedule.
Secretary.
So the girl who keeps his schedule.
Gee, how convene is that?
Let me just pencil myself.
And an apparent and alleged second mistress.
Solder's story to the mail.
And it was this is just huge.
It's so big.
And so it's kind of interesting to follow the media coverage.
This is very typical stuff here in the UK and the papers are also fighting against each other.
And who has the best story and the juiciest story.
I'm sure that lots of it is not true.
But it's a dude.
That guy had a shitty weekend.
I can tell you that.
Also, what's still high on the agenda here is the BBC.
I'm sure they're bummed out about all this noise about the minister of parliament.
Because they're trying to now really push the pedal to the metal.
They get their money from public funds.
Well, I mean, from public funds, the public literally pays for a television and radio license.
It's a hundred and twenty-one pounds a year.
So, you know, ten pounds a month and you can watch and enjoy all the BBC programs.
If you don't, by the way, even if you buy a television set, they'll track you down.
And the fine can be up to a thousand pounds.
So, but it's good.
I enjoy what the BBC delivers.
And now they want to raise the amount of money they want.
Above standard inflation rates.
So they're asking for, I think, 2.3 percent more.
I'm not too sure on the figures, but it's a hell of a lot of hundred millions more.
Which means that we, the inhabitants would have to pay more.
And so now they're going through this whole review process.
And they're trying to prove that it's going to be worth it.
And one of the things that's very interesting they said,
it's that they are dealing with extraordinary inflation.
Which boils down to the fact, they say that because of the media landscape today,
it's very hard to get good qualified people.
So they need more money to attract these, these high flyers who are already been snapped up by
other broadcast corporations and other production companies.
And I was like, please, would you open up your ears for a second and listen to the
talent that's all around you?
No, no.
They've put that in a separate little box.
And they're saying, we're going to make the BBC.com website.
Or BBC.co.uk website.
We're going to make it the place for user generous.
Content content content content content content.
So they're trying to be hipsters.
And they're also saying it's going to be, this is interesting that they want to be the place for independent music.
Okay.
That's, we'll see what they do with that.
I still find that there's a huge disconnect within the BBC between BBC digital,
who are responsible for all that stuff.
And the program makers, the people who are making radio and television programming,
they really don't cooperate together from my personal observations.
So they're trying to show that they're worth all this extra money.
And I think they're going to be, it's going to be declined, I think.
And justly so.
And so now they're also publishing the salaries of the top TV host and then radio presenters.
And it's just, the newspapers are really going at this.
You have Rupert Murdoch who owns Sky, who has really a competition for the BBC in the marketplace,
and though it's competition for eyeballs, not for advertising money,
because the BBC doesn't have any advertisers.
And so the sun newspaper, which he owns, of course, is slamming the BBC off the time.
So it's just fun to watch.
Got a piece of feedback, which I was very excited about.
Patricia's out shopping, otherwise I'd bring her in to tell her this.
Dennis Belonget, I think, is the way to pronounce it.
Been listening to the Charlie almost since the beginning, like in a lot, all of it.
On DSC 375, you in Patricia, always nice to hear from her.
We're talking about the Sinatra show that Oblua's son is doing with his father's song.
See ya.
Then commented that the Beatles should do that, too.
Well, of course, the Beatles can't really, but whoever owns the rights to it can.
Well, good news, they're preparing a big show in Vegas in collaboration with Cirque de Soleil
and Faun Suap, Perus, a radio comic from the province of Quebec, who worked in France for a while.
So your wish, in a sense, will come true in a year, too.
That's great.
And I don't know how you found out about Dennis or Dennis Benolje from Canada, but yeah, I do.
We'd like buy a ticket immediately to go see that.
That would be so awesome.
Hello.
Are you okay with being okay?
Then check out the Media Ocar shows official debut on Maxim Radio, Serious 108.
Live and unedited with listener calls and a very special guest from burningangel.com.
The Media Ocar Show version 2.0.
It only hurts from, for more info, go to www.mediolcarshow.com.
It all starts Wednesday, May 3rd at 10 p.m. Eastern on Maxim Radio, Serious 108.
You got that's pretty interesting.
That's the first promo I've received for another show on Serious on the soundlight ever.
And I'm not sure if it's a podcast that has now become a show on Maxim or how that works.
But I just want to fit it right inside the soundlight.
We know to make sure y'all heard it.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
Where are flink?
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers.
We believe your personal information should be just that, personal.
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe.
Where are flink?
Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
So Troy Rodder sends me this email.
And ever since I played that geek song,
the geeky song about the MPAA and the RIA,
I'm getting all kinds of interesting other geek tunes sent to me.
I'm really like them.
And this one actually I think is I'm going to dedicate to my partner Ron Bloom.
Because we talk about this so much.
We're in the final throes of designing,
we're really getting the design ready for a full launch of podshow plus and the PDN.
And we're still kind of old school guys, right?
From 12 years ago we were doing HTML and tables.
And of course now it's all CSS.
And we talk about this a lot and it seems to be some,
what I call it,
some constraints based upon some CSS choices that have been made.
And we're just, you know, look, I'm a DJ and Ron's a guitar player.
You know, we're just trying to figure out what this stuff is.
And so I came across this song which Troy Rodder pointed me to.
And I'll put a link to everything that he put in there into the show notes.
I don't, it's not pod save, but I'll take the heat because it's a parody.
And I think it's pretty funny.
It is the love song to CSS.
Which of course are cascading style sheets?
That much I know.
It's a nice, chill tune for a Monday.
Doing whatever you do when you win the Charlie.
You know, we're just trying to figure out what this stuff is.
And we're just trying to figure out what this stuff is.
and we're just trying to figure out what this stuff is.
And we're just trying to figure out what this stuff's is.
Don't tell us that you'll be well said
Tonight I need you to see your steps
Going into the darkness
You'll be well said
So I believe that was from Andrew Rothman who sent to the BOAG World.com podcast and then that got sent on to me tonight
I need your CSS baby. Oh yeah
We've officially crossed a boundary here on the daily source code
We're stuff that you're sending in just may not make it onto the air
I have too much stuff
TMS just too much stuff coming in
So if you don't hear it right away that means I may play it later
Because I do keep it all and I'm coming up with some interesting ways to file stuff away and categorize stuff
Oh, I really really do wish you would do better with your ID3 tags. It would help me so much
If you don't know what that is just go to iTunes open up
Put anything you're sending to me into iTunes
Then do a get info and then fill out the information
Give me a good meaningful title. It's just like email
Put in the comments when the lyrics feel or anywhere
I'll be able to see it put in what it's about
So it kind of helps me with the organization
Yeah, I wish we could standardize that just like CSS
That would be so nice. So and some of it just won't ever make it onto the air. I'm sorry
But I also don't have time to reply to everything and everybody so I hope you understand
These phone numbers are really working though. I must have received 25 different voice mail
Over the weekend and I have to say 80% 70
Now let's say 70% from listeners who've never had an opportunity to send in a comment before because they just either don't know how
Or can't be bothered to
Record something and then send it off to me. So they're really digging it the phone lines if you're in the car right now
We have a US number in Jersey 201 625 6357 or in the UK 020 766 8137 5353
Let me see if they're working hold on
Great evening. This is just a test to see whether the connectivity works under this number from distant Abu Dhabi
I guess it does
There'll be a comment following in the next couple of days. Okay, bye. This concludes our test from Abu Dhabi
Hey Adam maybe this is one for the dev cache, but is
Potual plus an online interface or is it a download program because
To replace iTunes for me it has to be a download program. I'm not gonna crank open the web browser
Every time I want to do something
Oh, that's a very good question
So I think if I and I listen to your question a couple of times
I think the answer is no and yes at the same time
Potual plus will be a place where you manage your subscriptions. In fact, you can manage your iTunes if you want
So you know when when you want stuff to come into your iTunes and how you want it and how you want it categorized
And in what playlist you want it you'll be able to manage that from Potual plus
So that's one part so you won't have to download anything anything additional
If you want to put it on to a different MP3 player
We'll have a special little thing there that you just if you're running windows
And there'll also be a Mac version you just download that and don't think about it
And it'll put the files wherever you want them
But what I think is most exciting
And I'm not really a big iPod listener. I have to be honest
I have I use the dashboard a bit of an alpha version of the dashboard
Which is giving me the exact same in fact a better experience than iTunes
Because I can shoot through all of my subscriptions see what's new see what's updated
Q things up to play next while something's already playing
I can interspersed that with songs and the pod save music network
All kind yeah and of course that that's not a download all of that is coming in streaming in real time
And we're really doing this because I believe
You know there were a lot of guys when you know the was the famous quote by by Bill Gates who said
If you need I really don't remember this it was it
There's no reason to believe you need more than 64k to write a whole program
It wasn't even 64k it was like 640 bytes or something
Some ridiculously low number that you wouldn't need more than that to create any program you could imagine
And so you know folks were programming for the I think the smart developers
We're programming for much more than that knowing that
The capacity of the personal computer would grow over time
And you know we've essentially also been working against the bandwidth barriers
You know saying okay well we can do this when the bandwidth is more and we have more bandwidth
And we will eventually have even more bandwidth
And I'm a true or firm believer that within the not too distant future
I'm gonna say five years because I've learned so within five years
We won't know any different than that every single device is connected to the network and one shape or form
And that'll be anywhere you go including your iPod
It may be interface through your car or whatever
But however you're going to listen to it I'm pretty confident it's going to be
Got through a connected stream
That's not really I'm not really thinking about streaming if you think about an online radio station
But just getting like like Gmail for instance
I don't use outlook I don't use Apple's mail client
I just use a web browser and all my stuff is stored somewhere else
It's professionally managed it works almost all the time
Yes, I could use a hell of a lot more space and willing to pay for it Google
But it's no longer a matter of having all that stuff on your machine itself
So I think that your podcast subscriptions will kind of go the same way
And eventually you won't want anything to download because everything will be connected
Keep waiting, keep open, get my ticket and do some development on it
And very well version of DHB
So just wondering what it's going to be if it's online or
Is it actual program that you download but
All right, keep it to good work
Okay, so again, I hope I answered your question
It'll work with your iTunes so you don't have to to leave iTunes if you don't want to
But I think we're going to make a pretty convincing argument that you're going to be using the
Mashedboard more than iTunes
And a new dev cast went up a Friday with Aaron O'Neill our database sorceress
So if you want to check that out that I don't think we've given out all the golden tickets
I think we set it up for 20 for this for this time around
And at least eight of them I saw we're handed out so you still have a shot if you want to get in
Early on pocho plus and on the pdn
Adam, this is George from Kino man
I'm doing time up here in Kino and we love to listen to the Jatsa
Especially when we're having sex with each other after lights out man
You know I even downloaded a picture of you on the internet that I came to my cellmates back
When I reached him up and writing like a wetted new old man
So hey keep on the good work and hey if you're ever up in Kino
Swing by for a conjugal visit and if you didn't do much trouble
Maybe if you can smuggle a file in your ass
Hey, that would be a big help do man
It's okay Mark
It's that time again for
Time to slap the window down
The sad light repair man coming after you
Sad light repair man what's he gonna do
He'll fit your misconceptions and answer questions to
There's nothing in the universe that you can't do for you
Sad light repair man
Here comes
So as far as I can tell it's a regular line up for this evening with Pacific Coast
Hellway coming up right after this show in just a couple seconds followed by use radio Donna Drew
Gilmore daily and then DVD weekly followed by CC Chapman
I don't know if he's going to do the U-turn cafe tonight or not
That's all going up until 10 p.m. Eastern time on serious stars 102
We're going to continue here on the podcast if if you're listening to your serious receiver
And you want to hear more go to dailysourceco.com
Download the rest of the show because there is some pretty cool stuff that we're going to talk about
That you're not going to hear because the windows closing right now
Bye-bye
Let's get back to our phone calls for sec
Hey Adam Sharon and Tampa or Tampa on as Mad likes to call it
Thanks so much for putting the phone lines up
I've just wanted to tell you thanks so much for podcasting
And because of you I'm like listening to so much
I said it went to my eyes and that is out of the
And you know this story and met some good friends and just love the whole experience
And I love when lady Patricia comes on the show
Because I love when she puts you in your place
Yeah
She's so sweet
Thanks Adam
Bye
Yes she is
Sharon she is so sweet
That's why I've been married to her for 20 years and still feels like the first time
Which I could play that song
Over the weekend I did show Patricia a second life
And I was a little wary to be quite honest because you know she's so smart
She's like online game
Yeah, okay what's it about fucking
I said well there's that
And she said well just don't let anyone see you
Okay
This is why I love my wife she's so incredibly smart and with it
But she was actually fascinated and she's been asking a lot of questions and she has some pretty good insights
And we've been talking about business opportunities for second life and
You know people keep asking when will we see lady Patricia in the castle I said well
That could be one hell freezes over
Yeah, my name is Cody Brownley I'm a podcast or from Oklahoma
And I just want to tell you that I need to be bringing you all a whole bunch of these
But I think what you're doing is a great thing
Podcasting as a second my life in so many ways it's
Actually the story I want to tell you was
I'm a junior high school and I at the beginning of year
I was slated to get into a glass and actually
It was a scheduling error and I put them in the glass and correctly as a broadcast
And class sounds like what the heck I really want to be in the class
And it's also about the time I started a podcast thing and that I had just started having us
It's like so good so successful show and we just and that we got the top 25 of iTunes
It was just really a really big deal for me
I was like yeah, and I ended up using that to my advantage
I showed a point out that I was doing better than shows that were done by CNN shows
Or they're done by ABC news
And I was just showing them that like I didn't have the skills to be in the class
And actually my podcast and skills paid off and I was allowed into the class
So you know, if you were the great workout and my love here in the Charlie every night
I listened to it before I got a bed
So that's also that's the lesson to the next day while I'm driving a school
But I want to say that you're doing a great job, you have the great work
And you know, just keep doing a great job
I want to send some encouragement to you
That's fantastic
I really like that
That's how you're going to hone your chops, man
That really is
That's the way to do it if you're interested
And you're more than welcome to climb a board
You know, it's unfortunate a couple of the voice comments that came in
People making phone calls and cell phones
And it already sounds kind of crudty
Just because of the the resolution of phone lines
You know, which is what five killer hurts or something like that
It's very, very low resolution
So the sound will never sound as good as a recorded comment
But some of them just cutting in and out and sounding shitty
And it's too bad because there were some really good ones about
One guy sent in a comment about his first car
I'd love to hear if you could call in and give me that again
I'd love to hear the whole story
Because it was always I tried to enhance it
I couldn't get the sound right at all
Garbage and Garbage out stuff
So if you have a cool story about your first car
Let's hear it because I think that's something that I'll be fun to talk about
And he actually had a great story so send it in if you want
But again, the quality sometimes just prohibits use of the voice mail
It's unfortunate
Garbage and Garbage and Garbage and Garbage and Garbage
We have a situation
If you're inside of eating your second life property
Help
No, just kidding
It's your neutral neighbor
Comic-Straper blogger known in second life as comic-senior
So it was nice meeting you in second life Adam Carey
Thank you for teaching me how to operate bazooka in second life
To shoot down a star ship
Anyway, I have a question
I have a question to everybody interested in visual realities
How to be sure how to be certain if anonymity must be granted
And that the other person in visual reality is female
And not male who is just pretending to be female
Maybe your listeners could help out
So so see you in second life neighbor
Okay neighbor, that's right next to the castle in second life
And if you're just joining, please check this stuff out
Because it really will mess with your head
And I'll be the first guy to show it to point out some really good drugs that won't kill you
Okay, that's what second life is
Secondlife.com
And so comic-straper blogger purchased a parcel of land right next to the castle
The Curry Castle
And he put this huge lighthouse on top of it
And it was like, okay, when I first moved there I bought the land
There was almost no one around
Now there's a couple other castles
It's getting pretty crowded
I have to make some decisions here
But you know, I'm trying to be good neighbor
So I flew up to the top of comic strip bloggers lighthouse
And he was unpacking
It wasn't a bazooka, it was an atomic RPG
And it's kind of like the unique
Of course, second life is all based on hackers and programmers
So it's very common to help out new people
And show them the way around
Because there's always someone who showed me and showed everyone
The ropes in the beginning
And so I showed them how to unpack it and how to shoot it
I think actually CSB since you own that spaceship
There's a preference you can set
Which is make, was it make damage permanent?
Something like that
I think that's the way you can blow stuff off
Because in the damage actually we'll take place
And you'll have to rebuild you can't just restore
Something like that, I'm pretty sure
So I was hanging out in second life
Quite a bit over the weekend
And it was once again a mind-bending experience
Oh, let me answer that second question, comic strip blogger
It's very, very easy
Now the way second life is currently run
Or large portion of it
Is girls who are online
Typically they become an escort
They make themselves really pretty
They get hit on all the time by guys
And then they sooner or later the pimps come out
And they say, hey, you know what?
You can get hit on by guys
You can live all the time
But if you come over here and dance in my club
And if you want you can become an escort
You can make money
And then you can go shopping
And there's a lot of shopping in second life
It's very hard to find male clothing for your avatar
But there's lots of stuff for women
I've just tons and tons of stuff
You can't, in fact
I think this will be hugely successful with women
Although probably your right comic strip
Probably a lot of the cute women who are in there are guys
Or young boys
Trying to make some linden dollars to go and build stuff
That can shoot other people out of the sky
So there's only one real way to know
And I've done this myself
You go shopping with her
Go shopping with her first
And that's how you know if it's really a woman or not
You can just tell
And so I went shopping with a couple women over the weekend
Actually Angie B
She went with myself
And oh I have a business partner
In second life
This is really cool
I don't want to say her name because I don't know if she wants me to mention that
Or how silent or upfront she wants to be about the partnership
She's an ex escort
She's stunningly beautiful
And she really wants to have a purpose in second life
And I've had some ideas for a while
And she's been on for a couple years
So she knows exactly where to go to get stuff
She knows all the great designers
All the great engineers, programmers, developers
We're thinking about setting up our own sim
Which means we even run our own server
I'm confident we can make money out of this
And you know me
I'm always the guy I was looking for a way to commercialize
Because that's my life
I like doing things that I have fun doing
And make money out of them
That's kind of what I've always done
And I went shopping with her and with Angie B
And they bought me some new hair
And I could tell you know
I know Angie B is Angie B
So I know that she's a girl
And she shops like a girl
It's obvious
So that's the way you tell
She has B
You don't need to know anything else
Just go shopping
See how they react
Usually that'll be a dead give away
Within the first three minutes
Hey Adam
Remember way back on DSC 296
I signed off saying
Which I was in San Francisco
Parting with you pod show guys
And you were like party
Well I'd have to say that logging in the second life
Hanging out at your virtual castle
And smoking a virtual joint
It's just about what I had in mind
Where I thought about parting with you
Dork
Just kidding
You know I love you
See you in second life
Oh that's hot
See you in second life baby
It's true
So I'm hanging out at the castle
Was that yesterday
And there must have been eight
Eight or nine people who dropped by
Many of them listeners
Couple of I know in real life
Angie wasn't there
I guess she was offline most of the day
But castle
And Joe
Who I know from the UK
They dropped in
And so we're just kind of hanging out
And then
It's very hard to explain
But when you're all sitting there
And then I can actually start a song
I haven't figured out how to get pod save
Music in there yet
So it's kind of it's some 80 stuff
Actually in fact we had an 80's
Revival dance off
And it sounds dorky
I know but I can't help it
And so I'm spinning tombs
And then I got the disco lights going
And then we said
Okay let's do a photo shoot
Let's take some
Because you can take a screen
Shot basically
And you can position the angle
Any way you want
And so I gave everyone a pod show
T-shirt
So okay everyone put the pod show
T-shirt on
And then we'll pose in front of the fireplace
And it was just like a real photo shoot
You know someone can't get the T-shirt on
Right and then you have to tell it
When to shut up
And let's coordinate and let's sit here
And then someone else jumps up and moves around
And so finally we got it done
And it was real
I was there
It's frightening
It really is
Now I still believe that
You're going to
What do I believe
You know the aspects of this
Yeah it sucks you in
But I think we can really be productive
There's a lot of things
In fact I wouldn't mind sitting in my office
And having representations of
Other pod show people at HQ sitting in my office
Sitting in the office or in the same proximity
And we can pass stuff to each other
Which would be notes
The way we do in real life
Only I think that this is a much richer interface
And you really do get sucked in
Whereas if I'm on Skype or on I am
Or emailing with people
Then it's still seem somewhat removed
And the reverse is also kind of true
That and I've said this before
Second life is doing something to me in real life
In fact
I actually went out shopping with Patricia on Sunday
And had a good time
And then she's walking along
I'm looking at her saying
To myself
She would really look good in
In a dress like this
It's because I've been looking at all these avatars
And having these exact same thoughts
And it's really giving me some kind of
Appreciation for
For real life
It's hard to explain
It really really is
But emotion
And communication
Melded into one with the visual aspect
It does something to you again
I am the guy
Who gladly point you towards the drugs
That won't kill you
Hey Adam
It's PD love from Love House radio
Also does Dinkin in second life
Hey I was wondering
And this is regarding second life
I think I could borrow your attack helicopter
I've got a date next week
And that's fine
What would it be better to impresser
Than your attack helicopter
So if you don't mind
If you're not using it say Tuesday night
If I could just take it from a ride
I do a little practice STEM
Anyway
Glad to see you in second life
Enjoy the tripping brownie
Then ride it off
And I'll talk to you soon
Bye bye
Yeah, does no poor
PD love
This is a thing this hard is
Because you can't use the same names
In real life
Or
Whatever you have to kind of choose
A last name that's given to you
It's almost impossible to
Remember who's who's who
I'll just say does
That was fun dude
I had the the trippy brownie
So I've got these blunts
I've got some joints
And they all do things
So you have a jar
They make you fall down
And fall over and do funny stuff
Nothing dangerous
Luckily
But then there's this trippy brownie
And you can actually ride on it
And then so
We went outside for a little bit
After doing this photo shoot
Everybody hopped on the trippy brownie
And we just crashed around
And it was
I'm literally sitting here laughing out loud
And the comments people are making on the ride
It was very immersive
A very immersive experience
And then I caged everybody
And just showed off
Some of my fledgling
Second life skills
And it was cool
I don't think you want the attack helicopter to do
Take the Corske S76
And if you want I'll even pilot it for you
So you guys can hang out in the back
I think that'll be much better
Hey Adam
Bob Evans here
Got my real name in second life
I don't know why you couldn't
Compare that you can get your real name
I suspect that Curry just wasn't added to the drop down
From which you select your last name
I never miss the Charlie
Keep it up
Please invite me to the party to castle
When I get more time in second life
I will be trying to find it
I'm still a newbie and having a hard time
Finding time to get in there and just search around
Yeah no problem
Just go to your find
Command and search for curry castle
I listed it now in the
In the search engine
Which cost you 30 bucks a week
I think
Linden box that is of course which is zero point
Was it 30
30 US cents or something like that
Shoot what I'm going to say something about that
Now anyway
What I witnessed over the weekend
Really showed me some of the power of people just hanging out
And this really works
There's no reason why we couldn't have
Pot say music artist drop by
I know this away
I haven't investigated yet
Angie B is actually working on figuring that out
There's a way for
And
Excuse me
There's a way for an artist to perform live
And that to be represented in second life
And I think that the experience will be
Would be that much more enhancing
Instead of just listening to someone performing live
On a stream you actually can see the performance
See their representation of who they think they are
What they want to be in second life
And some podcasts
I think will also be appropriate
Not this one
Because I want you to have your own
Mental image of where I am
What I'm doing and how I'm doing it and what the cottage
It looks like and
You know I really like that
It gives me a much more I think a much more intimate vibe
In the show
But if you take
Heather and Janelle for instance
They could actually sit around and have some of their friends
Who come on the show regularly
Actually come into the show
And they could do that in any environment
They want it to be
And that show of course
He said slightly
Is underwritten by acu view
And you can find it at download.acuview.com
I could understand
That was just
More cowbell
Yeah
Yeah, you're not the only one who responded to the cowbell
I'm a little acen copy
So I'm still working on my cowbell skills
But yeah
Without a doubt
We got to have some more cowbell
So let me
It's been a while since I gave you the time
And about as long as you were on kind
All the by the telephone
If you were separate you
Say no for a rainy day
And do that all the way
Yeah
I don't know what's in it
It's not your idea
But don't wish a new someone
Thank you
I'm working
Don't think it
If I'm only tried
And now you are
We're less than ever
We'll be tried
All right
And for
You suck
I'm done
I could cry
Or I could say
I'm one of the wives
I could talk myself
And together
You're alive
I'm never good
I've changed my mind
If I tried just one more time
But I can say
I'm not alive
That it was me
I said goodbye
Yeah
I'm done
It's not your idea
But don't wish a new someone
Thank you
I'm working
Don't think it
If I'm only tried
And now you are
We're less than ever
We'll be tried
All right
And for
You
I'm done
I'm working
I am working
Because
I'm working
Don't send it in the sun, you're not here, but I don't wish you knew someone that you were me
Don't think that if I only try and know you are real, that you never will be touched
All right, I'm so done with you!
Oh, Beth sent me a nice note over the weekend thanking me for playing her other song, Mr. Lovely, which is another just fabulous song
Where have you been all my life, Beth?
Wow, this is great. She's got three, yeah, like two and a half pages of songs up on pot safe music network of music.potshow.com, link to Beth
Of course in the show notes, excellent stuff. That'll do it for today. Just kicking off your weekend
It's gonna be a busy week Wednesday. Let's see, Wednesday evening Patricia and I are going to Joan Collins. She's performing a
Small theater tour, you know, Joan Collins, Alexis Carrington from Dynasty, so we she was on on a big talk show here Jonathan Ross
Two weeks ago, I think, and you know, let's just go see what she's gonna do like an hour and ten or hour and 15 minutes with about her life
And she's been married to some pretty interesting guys, so there's that. I'm going to the dentist this week. That's always pretty big
And Patricia and I are also planning on having lunch one of these days on the Isle of White, which means we'll be flying there with a Delta Sierra
I'm gonna see if I can get Jason to fly along with us to show us he's probably been there many times
So I just want to get the routing down, you know, so that I can do it by myself in the future
So we may record something on the way and back in the airplane. I'll cut out all and you know, most of the pilot chatter
And so you because Patricia will be on the intercom with us and she can talk along and so maybe you'll get a, you know, but yeah, that'll be a much better
Sound seeing tour because she's very very visually oriented and she'll be looking at the ground while we're looking at the instruments and she can tell us what we're seeing
So that and, uh, oh, Krike, I don't know. There's all kinds of stuff going on and of course more golden tickets being handed out for you to come out and check pod show
Plus and the podcast literally network just just before we open it up to the, to the general public and we're getting pretty darn ready stuff is looking very, very good
Okay, your feedback, Adam at curry dot com daily source code dot com for all the latest and of course ongoing conversations at curry dot com
phone lines once again, 2016256357 or if you're calling from the UK or prefer to use a British number 02076813753
See tomorrow everybody or in second life. Bye. Bye. Bye.
Another pod show podcast stick it in your ear
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from pod show and limelight networks
I love it