This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 409.
It's early morning Thursday in San Francisco, California.
And I'm watching World Cup Soccer.
Right now Ghana is leading the US by 1 to 0.
Not feeling really good about that, particularly this early in the morning.
So what do we do?
Well we play a song that all American males will play when they're feeling a little bit
down and when they're behind because this is the truth.
I take a look at my enormous penis and my troubles start to melt into a bow, I take a
look at my enormous penis and the happy times are coming to stay.
I got a saying and I dance when I glancing my pants and the feeling like a sunshine
I take a look at high enormous penis and everything is going my way.
So what if we can't play soccer?
We got big spouts.
With $16 billion worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation
radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just a kid that I'm crazy.
I got hand in the devil's land on home.
Never had milk and honey that tastes so bad on home.
All I had mama's day behaving about shutting this stuff just the west of the wall.
You never understand, so just take my hand and put it on your mouth again, all your
mama's gone, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time,
all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all your time, all
time, all your time, all your time, just take my hand and put it in hand and put it in hand and put that time and come !
ehhh
I've got to land in the devil's hand on
Never had milk on a hornet that tastes so bland
All the hot momma's day to have a new bowl
Struggling bad stuff just a west of the wall
It made me wonder how strong it is
So does it take my hand
And put it on your mouth on the ground
All your men always laugh
All owns a safe mind
And put it on your mouth on the ground
All your men always laugh
All owns a safe mind
And put it on your mouth on the ground
Oh man, that's a rock and roll song.
The genders and commemorate glands.
I played the genders before on Charlie.
And wasn't till this time that I found this new song that put up
a lot of music network.
I realized they're from Israel.
And if you listen to the lyrics, there's kind of some giveaways in that song.
I love that song.
Everybody how you're doing coming to you from Northern California.
A very stunning San Francisco today.
As I come close to the end of my trip.
And it's this is really weird.
It's Thursday morning.
And I'm doing the show here.
And this is a really strange day because at 7 a.m., US versus Ghana started on television.
It's very hard because I really want to see the US play.
But I also need to do the show at the same time to hit the satellite window.
And it's already kind of depressing because Ghana's how mandate they had a great goal.
They just took the ball right away from our team cap and shot it right in.
I'm trying not to look at the screen over and over in the corner of the condo here.
And just get through the show.
And by the way, welcome to the show.
It is the show.
The show.
You're part of the show.
We're all in the show.
Are you in the show yet?
And what's the deal with this soccer versus football yesterday?
I had a caller calling on the voicemail line.
It was just it was a listener from Germany.
But the quality was so bad.
I luckily, a whole bunch of other people picked up on it and sent in the actual history
and the origin of the word soccer.
And why does used versus the world standard of football.
Hey Adam, it's Dave.
The guy who left you that.
Whoo!
Mess is on your answering machine.
You didn't get it.
That was a hockey reference.
You just hockey reference?
Hmmm.
Okay, sorry, didn't get it.
Not a big hockey fan.
That on Wednesday's Charlie.
I think it was the only person in America interested in hockey
What went wrong there? How can we don't care about hockey in the US? Hey, there's one place in America that still cares about hockey Northcare
No, what was that don't stop? Hey Adam it's Dave the guy who left you that
Woo woo
Messages on your answering machine. You didn't get it. It was a hockey reference. You said on Wednesday's charlie
I think it was the only person in America interested now. Man this sucks. I only loaded half the file. Oh shoot
Oh
Maybe I have maybe I have another version of it
Maybe this one. Maybe this is it. Let's see
Oh man. This is all going wrong. See now that the US is losing my my production is all screwed up whole on a second
Of course I could start the whole show over and get back to that, but let me try this hold on because I know the guy from Germany called in again
Let's see. Let's see if we can find it. I don't know
Oh, man. Oh, this is so horrible. This is so not what I wanted
I okay, wait a minute if I plug this
You're witnessing a complete meltdown here on the daily source code. Okay. I'm now pulling stuff out of the archives
Let's see if this works
Hey Adam, this is Brad Gunther from Berlin. Oh, there we go. You start playing a common I sent in on for a wait and
stopped because it's sound horrible and
I'm trying now a slightly different setup. I'm going to try sending you a succumb instead of through Skype and see if that helps at all
I was talking about the difference between football and soccer and how the words were used differently and and where they developed
I read this in a germ magazine article recently
Basically it said that in the 1870s when rugby was first dying become really popular in
Britain the decision was made between the players who earned favor of of football to continue
Call that soccer as a differentiating is a differentiating themselves from people who were in favor of rugby
So the game two types of football rugby football and soccer football
And actually then few years later when the first time a college championship game was held in the US for football
One of the teams showed up having played soccer and the other team showed up having played rugby
And over the course next year to the US teams kind of came up with a hybrid which we know today is as football in the US
in order to kind of make up for
That's different so
Officially football is right when you're talking about any sport if that's sort whether it's
soccer rugby American football
Canadian football arena football whatever falls into that rough category of having developed in the same place
And soccer is just a way to specify which brand of that you're playing
All right, well, thanks for playing this and take care
All right, so sorry about that
Okay, so the other comment from the the hockey guy was very similar
Only I liked his woohoo with the beginning let's hear that again
Oh, that's a good
Here we go hey Adam
Shoot everything's all messed up
Pay no attention to the guy who's doing a show but really watching television
This is where I get all messed up
Yeah, so so what it sounds like to me is that the word was football in 1870 or whatever
And because of
Issues here in the US we changed it to soccer. I still don't understand what the real root of the word soccer is you know
Who came up with that how do you go from football to soccer regardless it's pretty clear
The origin is of course football and so we're gonna leave it at football and when we talk about American football
We'll say just that day six of the Unleashbeard not everybody real happy about it Patricia is not digging this at all
So and I knew this was gonna happen so I guess this this is what it's supposed to be it's supposed to be a little bit painful
The longer it takes for us to unleash pod show plus in the podcast delivery network the more pain I get at home
So it's my personal suffering. It's not like anyone a pod show HQ cares
Some of the some people hate my beard there too, by the way, so of course if you look at the
Picture art that I've put into the MP3 file for today if you're looking on an MP3 player
They can display that you know iTunes or your iPod would also
Many other versions of the MP3 players do it
Including pod show plus you'll see that it is indeed growing and that idea to do that to put that into the
MP3 album art
Yes, I couldn't I couldn't remember who would told me to do that and boy that I get spanked
Who there was Brittany of course my second life sexy girlfriend
She'll never let me live that one down
So yeah, he's getting there and people are suggesting stuff. You know, he's just put cream in it to stop the etching and I don't know
I just want to have a little bit of pain. It makes me feel a part of the whole process
Thank you all very much also for trying to help me out with the
Windows equivalent of the hide command
This is something I'm still missing severely
You know, it's really cool on on a Mac on on OS 10 if you want to hide an application
You just and this is what and I forgot to mention this yesterday. It's all a left-hand movement because you know my right hand is is doing other things
It's touching my mouse
So with my left hand, I can use apple key H which is real easy
Real even from a right hand because H is pretty much in the middle of the keyboard and the apple key is on both sides
So very handy to just hide one application
so people sent me plenty of
Plenty of feedback saying hey, you know if you hold down the window start key and M it'll
Minimize or if you hold down the window start key and D it'll minimize two problems with that
The first is actually a problem with this particular keyboard that is in the to achieve a portage
For some reason they put the windows start key top right so it's
Yeah, the F12 then I've got the print screen and then I have the windows key
So not only is it on the right which of course is my mouse touching hand
I just don't like removing my hand from my mouse
So you really need
Yeah, you can do it with left but then it becomes kind of tough and the same course goes for any combination
Then includes the windows key
But also that doesn't hide just the top application it really hides minimizes everything hides minimize the same thing I guess
And and it and it
It takes you to your desktop. I just want to be able to hide one application
Because then I can always switch back with the quick all tab which of course does work very well
And that's the same on Mac as on Windows
So still looking for to be able to minimize the top most application with one swift key command
Preferably that would be a key command with a left hand
Score oh it's one one. Okay
While I was talking about touching my mouse. There you go. It's one one fantastic. Oh man in the 43rd minute
Good so I'll feel good as we go on to halftime and then we can just complete this show
Something funny happened at the office yesterday actually it happened a couple days ago
But I didn't really find out about until just the other day now
We're using Bank of America at Pod Show and this is kind of a legacy thing because when Ron and I started the company and we were funding it ourselves
I was very easy
Particularly because we were pretty much based in Miami at the time at least the finances were based in Miami
And we had Bank of America
I got to tell you American banks really suck
ass
And I'll and I'm gonna give you the only example that I have and there are many many more
But I've dealt with all kinds of banks around the world and I have banks around the world and I really think European banks are far superior
Now's have a private bank which gives you all kinds of personal service and a very cute blonde banker
She's a woman by the way
But that's neither here nor the hair. The real issue is credit cards and
You know, I've had a
Mastercard through my bank in the Netherlands for six years and
Never no matter where I was in the world no matter what the price was of the item
I was purchasing or whatever I was paying for or what type of it was on the internet or or hotel
If it was in Asia if it was in
I've used it everywhere but South America I think never have it has it been declined and and I'm not saying
That's because of course I have enough money in the bank, but it's never been declined for any of the numerous reasons that I continuously get declined for
on my US visa card
And it drives me absolutely batch it because there's plenty of money to cover the account
But they have all these triggers and trips and of course, you know, I'm all over the place
You know, so one day I'm buying so I'm getting money from an ATM in San Francisco next day
I'm buying Virgin Atlantic tickets and I'm doing that from the UK
I might be at an ATM in in the Netherlands or or getting fuel at Rotterdam Airport
Continuously this triggers all kinds of alarms and then they declined the world that yeah
They did they declined the card with the police call us and then I got to get on the phone and
It's tedious embarrassing and it's freaking lame and it's not like we don't move millions of dollars through this account
and you know and we we and Cindy bless her heart Cindy who
Really isn't you know like a like a like a financial controller position at Pod show
She manages all this she has to call the bank all the time and and it you know
She'll get a call from me on Sunday saying Cindy. I got it. I got to pay for these tickets
You know, I don't because it just it's so much more effort if than I use my card and then as a reimbursement
It goes back and forth. It's a pain in the ass. It's a real pain and
That's what the corporate credit card. So I'd also ask Cindy who was kind enough to
Set me up. I needed a bank account. He just a private account here in the US. I just wanted checking account
So of course, you know, you've got me the the company line. She got me bank of America
That's fine. I just needed to checking account just to build a pay for some like the calm cast bill and some you know some
Some basic stuff. I mean I do have a household here at the condo
And and so that arrived and of course
I had been gone for a while so I didn't have time to activate the credit card that came with the account
So
So I get the credit card. By the way, this this whole declination of stuff it happens to I mean I was
Having dinner with one of our investors with rom shirom in London the guy is a billionaire
And he was one of the he was an angel investor in Google so it's not about him having enough money
We're having dinner in London just the two of us and he picks up the tab which was nice and
It's card gets declined and it's and it's and it's not because of his money is because you know
Oh my gosh the card all of sudden is traveled to the UK. I'm sorry
I get really worked up about this because
All this crap about it's for your protection bullshit. It's not for my protection
It's for your protection bank of America and it's really pissing me off
Anyway, okay, so
So I had the credit card and you have to activate it. So I call the number on the card and it says oh we can't the card
You're trying to activate cannot be found. Okay. I tried again. I tried again
So uh say Cindy could you just check it out and find out for me? You know whenever you have time
It's my personal card don't worry about it. I have other ones to use and
And so she gives it back to me you know like a day later
It's okay. It had to be yet to call from a specific phone number because that's how they verify and cross-reference the records
So I call and of course the credit card you're trying to activate cannot be found. So I go back to Cindy and I say okay
Look you know whatever just you know let me know when you can figure it out these guys are host
So two or three days ago buying I'm like I wonder and you know as and I say
Hey, Cindy you have my no actually asked Rosie if she had my credit card
She had no no Cindy still has it and then Cindy said that you know she didn't know if she had it and
Well, I got a beautiful email from Cindy the other day where she copped to what it actually happened
It seems uh it was a small accident
She accidentally shredded my credit card
What not what you're how it happened
But it went through the actual shredder and it's in pieces. We're just probably better
Craft credit cards
Stupid in England. It's great and we have Barclays bank
I don't know I said don't give me I don't want a credit card. I'll just take a debit card
It's much easier all they do is check that it was for some reason with debit cards
There's there's no declination of of your charge
They just look at the actual amount if you have enough money. Okay. That's fine
And there is there is a limit that you can go over
In spending because in theory, of course, you know someone if they have your card could take all your money out
So there there is a limit there, but it always works
Crazy
It drives me nuts. It's for your protection and people actually believe that shit smart people
You know, it's a well, you know, it is important that they chase you at the check on that because it is for your protection bullshit
You're insured so one can steal your card can can can spend a hundred thousand dollars
You're not going to be liable for it at least not with any of the credit cards I've had
But just as continuous it's supposed to be easy. It's not easy
And of course, you know people say well, why don't you try American Express? Well, that is not as it is not accepted everywhere
Not every airline will accept it get it together people
And thank you Cindy for helping me out. I know you I know you didn't do from purpose. I know you'll get me a new one
We met with
We met with some dudes from Nokia
Came over. I know comic strip bloggers going to be real happy to hear that
Excuse me, nice company
We met with some guys from Nokia and they're doing some pretty interesting stuff. They they're now listing
Podcast Ali and pod show picks in in there they have a podcast application in their new phones
Which actually works
It's pretty cool. They have a little aggregator and you can
It's nice that they have these lists because you can basically just go in and and twoodle around and find stuff click subscribe
And it and it functions exactly the way you'd want to
And so they they sent me a phone of course wanting me to talk about it
It's the n91
A phone that I would never use for one simple reason
It's it has a regular
numeric keypad
So you know I use my my blackberry which of course is the phone
That I use but it's also my email device and what I do miss on that of course is all kinds of multimedia which doesn't have so this said this n91
has
Has the smallest keys in the world which are hidden by a slide out cover
But what I wanted to share with you today and this is the real bummer is the and I said this n91
It's a it's a real
Music powerhouse. I guess
It has four a four gig drive
Built in four gigabytes of space and
The quality of the sound is so good
That they actually supply you with a cable
That has a mini headphone jack that goes into the into the phone and then it has two RCA plugs
So you can plug it into your stereo system and the sound is phenomenal has a and then the built-in speaker is fantastic and it has a 1.3
No, I'm sorry has a two megapixel camera so all that's really cool. It has
Check this out it has Wi-Fi built in which I was really digging
And it has a and the browser is nice
So they had loaded it up with a whole bunch of songs
And this is the scary thing so
And then not just songs but they had ringtones and they had really funny ones and they had one like like a hip hop ringtone for me
Like Adam Curry and your phone is ringing and then they had a
That of course they had the Roger Smalls ringtone and I don't know if they're pre-packaging on those on all Nokia
N91 phones, but they were kind enough to put it in the one they gave to me
And so and I was like, yeah, this is great. I'm gonna play it on the show tomorrow and and so I put it in my bag
After I'd actually played with these with these files with these ringtones which are just I guess MP3s or AAC whatever they are
There's some kind of format doesn't matter. It's a ringtone and
And now I boot it up. I turn the phone on
And I go to the music and it's like no song so whole things empty
So it's like what happened?
You know, I look I know I didn't delete the entire library of songs something must have gone wrong so
Unfortunately, I can't I can't give you a demo
And quite honestly if if if there's a phone that is going to lose all my shit
I'm not that interested in it. So
Well, maybe the guys from Nokia can figure out what happened or let me know maybe I'm looking in the wrong spot
But I literally see if I press on if I go to the music area. I see was it say no songs right no songs
So there's just no freaking songs crap
Right
So
When you think of Nokia you have to think of comic strip blogger who has his own problems
I just wanted to apologize to all Welsh people if I have offended you in my latest audio comment
So please accept my apology and here let's learn another phrase in Welsh
Siddhartha here Siddhartha here. What means how are you?
Siddhartha here and now the phrase
Very well. Thank you very much
That young Diochen Vauhr
The young Diochen Vauhr and finally goodbyes in Welsh
Holy Vauhr
So I would like to say once again apology to Welsh people and I really admire that
Welsh people have been able to preserve their original Celtic language
As the only ethnic group in United Kingdom
Fulva Adam Kerry yeah, you can suck up all you want csb but I don't know people are buying it
He made some derogatory comment about Welsh folks yesterday
You know the other day before on the show and it became a heated debate of course once again on curry.com
Gosh this was a pretty frightening
Link that I received from Merrill about how dangers it really can be to
Follow sleep with your laptop on your lap
Sent a link which of course will be in the show notes a daily source code dot com
Let me just open this up for a second. There was a conference
And I'm thinking this was this conference in Japan hold on it's a web page from the inquire
Yeah, Japanese conference
So
So they have pictures of what happened
This guy had a Dell laptop and all of a sudden the thing explodes
I mean not just I mean like really explain pictures of this explosion and flames coming out of this thing
Apparently was it was a bad battery
You know one of these they say oh is an OEM battery or something you know some some replacement battery or whatever
Or not an original battery, but man they needed fire extinguishers to put the guys laptop out and I'm thinking to myself
You know we go through all this rigour morale at the airport
You know taking your shoes off and and taking your belt off and letting the you know letting the guy
Feel your nuts with the back of his hand and we got to take our lighters out and we can't carry those and you know I can't bring my weed
But the laptop is a bomb it's an explosive device
And you know if this happens with a Dell dude, it's a Dell it could happen with with any machine
You got to see those pictures it it'll frighten you
Yeah, and you know what I guarantee you before too long
Someone will say oh, we can't have any laptops on the plane because you know they could explode and terrorists could be using that shit
Just goes to show it's just to keep you happy and feeling safe
You know I have this this skin on
Well, I guess it's called a skin on my
On my windows layout which makes the look kind of like a Mac and
Because of that it changes all the window colors and for some reason now when cast blaster has a built in timer
And 30 seconds before the end of the timer, which I've said at 24 minutes and 30 seconds, which is when the satellite window closes
It starts flashing the window
But for some reason with this new layout the flashing it doesn't catch my eye and guess what I missed the satellite window
In fact, I've missed it by about five minutes, so I apologize to Uncle Jesse Pete dub the satellite repairman for missing that and
Let's get back to some comments
Hey Adam, this is listener Jim from Silicon Valley
Hey listen about three months ago before you went to porch of the light proposed the idea of best of Charlie's and
You took me up on that and we had a great time while you're on vacation
You also promised me to the swag and I figured it's been about three months now. You must have forgotten
Anyway, I actually have to be here in the city today when the day I'm just actually listening to
Today's Charlie on the drive up and I'm going to be up here in the city today for a few hours and
If you get this message
Give me a call on my cell phone. You may want to beat this out. Yeah, okay. Whoops. Sorry about that
Yes, I believe that out
We can buy I'll save you some posters and get in that swag
Anyway, still loving the show and
We'll talk for you soon
You know dude, I appreciate it and and I apologize. I was I'm I'm pretty sure that we said that
Well, I didn't send it off to you, but I thought that we had we'd fix that up so
Absolutely man if you know stop on buy we're in the yellow pages come on by hq will hook you up not a problem
And I'll check today with with Richard and Rosie and the gang and see what happened because they've been really good
Attending the swag out so my apologies
Earthlink ad challenge rages on you can win of two thousand dollars by creating your version
What you feel will communicate best
The message of earthlink and to those people who look at my email problems and say oh, you're not using earthlink
My problems are at a different level. This is at the MX record level believe me. It's a whole it's a whole different thing
It's not the consumer level. Here's another entry for the
The pod show ad challenge with earthlink
Would you can find it at challenge.podshow.com check it out
You
The future of communication is earthlink we revolve around you
It's called evolution going from eight man to earthlink user. I love it add challenge.podshow.com
Yesterday Chris McIntyre
Podcast Valley the Prince of Podcast Valley came over. No, I mean, it's like
You know we're across the room and
He received the letter from Ask Cap from the new media department which is pretty interesting
And I just wanted to share a little bit of this with you because I think it means something
Pretty important. Do you miss the McIntyre
Congratulations on having joined the growing number of internet sites which use music as an element of their programming
You may not have considered however that under the United States copyright law the public performance of copyrighted
Music requires permission from the copyright owners or their licensing representative such as Ask Cap
Musical performances present presented by means of internet transmissions are public performances because they are steps in the process by which the music wins
wind
word is that
Because it is what is it because they are steps in the process by which the music wins
It's way to the end users who are its intended audience. Look at this listen the arrogance of that sentence
Yeah, you music lovers you're not music lovers
You are end users who are an intended audience
According to Ask Cap
Now of course we'd ask Cap are pleased to offer you our new license agreement by which you will be able to
Loughly perform all the music in Ask Cap's vast Repetory by means of your internet site transmissions and
Closes your copy of that agreement
Blody Blody Blody Blody Blody Blody Blody Blot a couple things they don't to mention is
You need the actual permission of the owner of the work itself not just for the performance, but for the
download and sync right so it's very very misleading
and
Then they go into some it's just an amazing
I've seen lots of contracts and lots of agreements in my life, but I'm confused by all of page two
But anyway the minimum annual license fee payable on the Ask Cap agreement is $288
And amount chosen so that the cost of the Ask Cap license is well within the reach of even the smallest site operators hey speak for your self-ask app
And here's the best part
So they go through this in order to enter to the new Ask Cap agreement please complete paragraph
1-3 and 5 in the first page sign the agreement in the space provided on page five
Compliment sign the rate schedule report form of your choice and return them all to me
We will counter sign return only one fully executed copy the agreement to you for your files
It is not necessary to send any money at this time. We will bill you on a quarterly basis
So
First of all, I think it's misleading
Because they it gives you the idea
That you can actually play all these songs which is not true
I just categorically not true because there is a dispute over whether there is a performance or is it a
A download and believe me, you know, if you're paying for if you're paying Ask Cap and you play any one of their songs the RIA
Can and probably will come after you'll ask about that
So thank you very much Ask Cap, but we're we're quite happy with
The pod safe music network because they're the artists grant all the licenses and there's no money changing hands except when
listeners
fans music lovers
not users as you state when they love it and want to support the artist and then they go and give them some money
99 cents if they do it to the pod safe music network, but they might buy the t-shirts they might go to
Go to their concerts the buy other swag. I think we've got a system that is routing around
These have truths that you were spreading
But the fact that this letter went out my foot my friends is very clear
It means that lawsuits are soon to follow so if you're podcasting please please please be very careful
What you're doing
I guess it's only really one song we can play
Top of the world
You probably walking down the street with your earbuds champs so deep in your ear
Yeah, you go and damn you probably found this little mp3 for free
We're looking play this but not on the radio made this just so I could let it go
Does anyone around here? Still have a radio and anyone here at all?
Anyone here at all?
You should go and see a mountain kubernetes
No, it's way cooler out there
Yeah, I think so, but maybe you just like it in your cozy little world
We can play this but not on the radio made this just so I could let it go
Does anyone around here? Still have a radio and anyone here at all?
Anyone here at
Maybe I'm just literally what you say
Leave a front of my head
Maybe I just like it if you turn it off now turn it off now
Don't forget about a sound reeling West Virginia we can make it on our own
Do it just fine, I can't afford your record, but it's outside
We can play this but not on the radio and make this but not fall the radio
Hey now switch off your radio
You can play this but not on the radio made this just so I could let it go
Does anyone around here? Still have a radio and anyone here at all?
Anyone here at all?
The Jeff Smith latest in gentlemen not on the radio that's right you can play these songs anywhere not on the radio
You could find Jeff Smith at the Jeff Smith dot taunt dot com Jeff is G E O F of course links in the show notes depressing news
It is now two to one for Ghana, so I guess I just got to end this show
Oh, by the way for those of you who've been wondering what I've been doing in second life
Not a lot for the past two weeks because well, you know been out here and the time is all different and I really just don't have because I'm basically doing the show in the morning
And in the cottage when I get up in the morning and I've done the show then I still have time before San Francisco is actually awake to to mess around
And
We got some pretty exciting news. I'll talk about that tomorrow a little more in detail, but we've basically started a
New community the founding members of this community myself Brittany
ex-dark ex-alora magic star names you probably recognize if you've hung out in second life and come around to the castle
I've learned an incredible amount about how this game works
Because I do have to say
Having been in second life for a while
All the promise of you know how can crossover into real life and I was very interested in the financial aspect of it
You know, it's a game. It's totally a game because they've they've got it all messed up with
with
exchange rates and inflation and
Yeah, it's it
I have to say remains a game. However, it still has an interface that is some very very powerful
Asmodio that will take us to eventually a new paradigm of computing and the way we share files and the way we share
Information online. I'm convinced of that
But there's a lot of downside to what's going on in there and also I did I understand correctly
That there no longer going to require a credit card or PayPal when you sign up
I think this is a huge mistake because what I like so much about second life is one thing you knew for sure
Pretty much everybody in there is an adult because
You know not only had to you have to give your age and you have to be over 18 I guess or 17
But you also have to have a credit card
Which I thought was a real nice, you know factor and I believe that they've taken that requirement out so now and you know any
13 year old can go in and lie about the rage and still sign up and sure they may not have any
Any linden dollars to work with but guess how they're going to go get their linden dollars
Well if you've been in second life, then you know how a lot of people make money there
So
Here's all I'm going to say I bought an island
Okay, and
These founding founding members were we're trying to do something different and you'll be invited you can come in and you can join too
And I think it's going to be a lot of fun
You know a little more laid back a little more relaxed a little less hassle because now
We really control a lot more of where goes on on the land
Because you know the entire island is ours so more about that on the tomorrow show
Loved to hear from you. We got our voicemail feedback lines wide open
We've got a new jersey number which is probably the best if you're going to use Skype
20116256357 or any UK number in London
O2076813753
Still to one
So maybe they can pick that up by the time you hear this you'll know the final the final score and yeah
Hopefully USA will do good. I really really and I mean I know people who are actually
At bars who went to the bar this morning at six a.m. to be ready for the seven seven to clock game and are already
You know cheering our team. This is unheard of in world cup football unheard of that this happens in the U.S
So by the next time which will be in four years from now although I have to say
There's a lot of talk about doing it every two years
I think U.S will be a real true contender and they've done fantastic so far and I'm really proud of the boys
Yesterday, of course, I watched the Netherlands against Argentina
Went next door to
21st Amendment with Richard Brewer hey who's
He's a young he's an officially a young but you know he's kind of a UK boy
And that was a tough game. It was tough to watch it was a draw as you probably know
But I guess now the Netherlands plays Portugal which they were not looking forward to no one wants to play Portugal
Daily source code dot com adamant curry dot com and if you want a great deal on a domain name go daddy dot com
If you use the checkout code dsc three you'll get that domain name for only six dollars ninety five cents
I'll be back here tomorrow with a Friday festivities last show before I go back home
I can't wait to see my girls and you'll be along for the ride take care everybody bye bye
Get this podcast and more great ones like you on the high performance podcast delivery network from pod show and lime light networks