This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 381.
Hmm?
Friday.
Not family-say.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky drinks, man.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Pod Show.
I think it turns me on.
Because you want to wish the killer hisfather?
Maybe I am a little fucking crazy.
That's right, maybe Jerry is a little nice.
But this isn't about me, but i'm a little cool cool.
Pop声 coming from around.
Hide滿 it, take the knock to run!
I'm surround in myself a negative TV,
Memes it sounded like i'll never breath,
and I'm drowning.
I don't want to leave, I hate work, give a cat shot, it was the G.
This makes work, give a time for my family, my soul's hurt, in the same mind as the G.
That's what's hurt, it's not what it didness, in the world only God can fill me up,
what is love, but the temptation is strong, I need to pray, if you want to change the path you're on,
just say, I need to wake up, I forgot what's important now, wake up, come to money, ain't never day,
wake up, all my dues bring all day now, wake up, I gotta do it for my family, wake up,
all my God was important now, wake up, I'm a loser, I'll send it in, wake up, got the one that's in there, wake up,
I gotta give my life together now, I love to go around, all I see are snakes, and there's that still hate, cheap,
I know it, everybody knows it, I see their face, and there's absolutely no good,
because they lie still hate, cheap, I know it, everybody knows it,
God, humbly, make me a servant, I ask for mercy, I don't deserve it, I can spot some slaves too,
I'll prefer it, it catches my eye, though, I need to change, I'm always chasing, and at my neck, people will kill for,
I don't have money, there's never enough of, I don't have money, there's nothing but misery,
I don't have money, there's nothing but emptiness, in the world only God can fill me up,
don't put his love, the temptation just strong, I need to pray, if you want to change the path you're going,
there's a saying, I need to wake up, I forgot what's important now, wake up, come to money, ain't never day,
there you go, all are doing the trick on me now, wake up, I got to do it for my family,
here you go, I forgot what's important now, I'm losing my sanity, here you go,
God for one, I can say it made me wake up, I got to give my eyes together now,
I just got a new whip, I need another one, I just got a new crit, I need a break of one, I just got a new child,
I need a better one, I just got tangy, already spent, do you want what I got to do,
the game, we got to do it, he's on the game, there's a bovine marching around the street,
he's on the same song, and this is a piece of venery, and some of the TV is unbelievable emptiness.
The game Dobarles only God can fill me up, pour this love,
the temptation just strong, I need to pray, if you want to change the path you're going, there's a saying,
wake up, I forgot what's important now, I'm woke up, crush money, ain't never day,
I got to do it for my family We go, I forgot what's important now
I got to go, I'm a little sad, we go, got to go, I'm gonna say it
There we go, I got to go, I got to go, I got to go
What's again we made at friends?
It's Friday.
Cinco de Mayo.
No less.
Coming to you from the affluent suburb.
I'm sorry, you'll put it in the UK on another beautiful, beautiful spring day
I got to almost call it a summer day.
Eminending from the furry cottage, it should be a short code
With Michael Gomez wake up, the perfect song for me this morning
I had one of those days where you know where you wake up
And it just seems like nothing's exactly right
I just was irritated, completely irritated about life and everything
I thought that was stupid, why should I be irritated about life?
The fact that I woke up is it's good enough right there
Yeah, okay, we're at the end of the week
And got some stuff to go over with you
As I was getting ready for the show today
And we're doing a little differently, I'm actually drinking a coke today instead of a scentsail
We never have soft drinks in the house
Or rarely ever have soft drinks but Patricia came up with lunch while I was prepping
God, let me tell you
I went through two almost three hours of just going through my email today
I hate it, I hate, I hate, I hate email
I know we have to live with it, but you know it's like
There's business stuff, there's opportunities
And there's all these different comments and songs and stuff
And I really, I tried to read it all but more importantly, I tried to listen to everything
And it just takes so much time out of my day
I enjoy doing it, I really do
But you know, what are we at now?
We're at one o'clock already
And I sat down to start my email
And prep the showcase, basically how I start prepping the show
I keep track of stuff during the day
And so I have a running list of stuff
And then the next morning I just, let me just check and see if anything came in overnight
And it was astronomical last night for some reason
And actually almost none of the promos and stuff that came in
I felt like playing it, either way too long or not entertaining
Or just didn't do it before we maybe
It's my mood, I don't know what it is
So very little promos today
So I know coffee because Patricia said she brought up my one
She did make a great lunch for me
An omelet with a little bit of crack pepper
In a sandwich
And she said okay because
Because you need it today, you can have a coke
And so I'm downstairs in the kitchen
And into the mailbox pops a brochure of flyer
Yeah, I fold it over flyer
This is something I could easily send to the tonight show
It's from the Clandon Park Garden Center
And coffee shop, which of course if you're going to go to the garden center
Why not go to the coffee shop
It would make a lot more sense if this was an Amsterdam actually
But on the back of it and this is maybe even something
For the Yanks versus the Brits
But just because I just picked it up
Just moments ago
Okay, so on the back they have a watering special
And they have this eight, you know what
How many points does this star have here
A nine-pointed red star right in the middle of the brochure
And it says limited stocks
A water butt pump
Yeah, water butt
B U T T water butt pump
High power pump connects to your normal hose pipe
And I like now there's something the Yanks and the Brits
Definitely disagree on when we talk about the use of the word but what the heck is a butt
In the UK then
You know and I could totally see Jayl and I'm looking at this going
Oh, high power pump connects to your normal hose pipe
A water butt pump
Okay
Thought you'd be interested in that
Wow, what a lot of response we got to the
To the show where we had the lovely lady Patricia on
And was she ringing me about second life
And you know what actually I do understand
I want a little headphone ear there
I have one earring in my left ear
And I've been wearing headphones so much
You know, actually not that much lately with flying
But with flying and just doing the source code
That the
It's starting to get inflamed
I can totally understand where conversations
Regarding what goes on in second life
Are very boring to people who are not on second life
And I mean we're totally I am totally excluding you from the conversation
So I'm not going to do that anymore
In fact, I've actually considered doing a separate second life podcast
But you know
Where am I going to find the time of the day to do that
But there is some validity to what's going on there
I was watching the on Hollywood conference via stream yesterday
And I must have heard in 10 minutes
I must have heard someone mention second life at least once a minute
So there is definitely something to it
And it's not you know
I think that I'll just for go the conversation about it
But there is something about guys like me who check stuff like that
Adam Russell Hansen from the Dark Matters podcast here
Or in second life Russell Hansen
Yes, I got my real name in second life as well
I had you talking to Patricia yesterday
And me and talk about deja vu
I was wondering if you'd been listening in a conversation between me and my wife
My computer time and her attitude to it have been the biggest discussion point of our marriage
Okay, now I haven't had that problem, okay Russell
You know that but there's whole concept of playing games
Yeah, that's been a hot topic as you might have heard two shows ago
What I see is possibilities and opportunities
She sees this wasting time away from the family
But at the same time she fails to see all of the IT things she accepts as part of her daily life
Without thinking about it
Which came from the people like you and I exploring the potential of what may be
Playing your bills without taking a trip to someone's place of business
Sharing emails and digital photos with her sister in the UK
A voice-over IP, cheap phone calls
Yeah, that's all fine right everybody loves that stuff
And who who was working on that for years right exactly
I'm back in the old days from finger me
I used to tell the television hey man people are fingering me
She said what what are you doing on that computer
Those are the old unix days when you could provide your dot plan information through a finger command
Asons of other things it started out as someone tinkering with an idea
Exactly now an arguable point but what I consider a big misconception
Second life is not a game. I've been playing computer games for 25 years
An online multiplayer games for about eight years
Oh man do you remember moves and mugs you remember that?
That was oh it was actually that was kind of the same thing wasn't it?
I don't know if anyone was at college university in the in the mid 90s
It was big man you it was all text based and people would sit on it for hours
And you know you basically use your imagination
Very much like reading a book an interactive screenplay actually
I can tell you second life is as much a game as windows or macOS is a game
You can play games in second life show
But it's much more than that
It's a platform for a new way of creating content and interacting with the online community
What I can do is only limited by two things people's imaginations in the state of the technology
Virtual worlds I see at the level of technology of MS-5 or maybe in the online world
Around the time when links tell that nifty p where the guy prior to HTML really
Taking over remember it well
We've been given a be a band's technology and doing our best with what's there in this such
It looks simplistic and clunky to those account grasp the potential
And it's not intuitive enough yet to appeal to the masses
But that's just a matter of time
If we ever get over the hurdles of bandwidth given two or three years
Virtual worlds are going to grow enormously as preferred medium to render act with the online world
Just listen to that online world
It's already a phrase being used to talk about the internet
But what is today we're talking about text and titty graphics
You know it's interesting. We don't even realize any more than in our common day speech
We go to a website and in fact I remember when people started saying that
And it was very interesting at the time
I went there. I went to what were we doing the planet rebook dot com yeah
I went to planet rebook
That was it almost by the definition of the description of virtual work in coming
Hey guys, if you're flying over here you're missing the airfield
Because that was really you know going to planet rebook going to bud what going somewhere
We go to a website. Isn't that interesting where you're not really going anywhere
It's already crept into our into our vocabulary
The paradigm is about to be expanded to something which more closely resembles what we actually see in our real life
Meaning it should be more user friendly and intuitive to the non-IT literate
Which is always limiting factor to how much of the community accepts technology
It has to be easy fifth use for someone who has nine clue about computers something just hit me when you were saying that
Remember was it Microsoft Bob was that it when Microsoft tried to create a like a virtual environment
Instead of the traditional desktop
Maybe we should be looking at it that way
That was it was a huge failure by the way
It was so clunky and so dumb
But there's I'm with your man. I'm with you. I'm right there with you on the you know that it's that it's no different from macOS or windows or any other type of environment
Were you manage information?
Finally regarding the matter of wasting time of on the computer
Obviously some people can take this to extremes
But I'm also that any work or extra curricular activity that currently exists
Personally
I don't drink. Don't go to the pub or parties with mates. That's why you're right. Why would your wife as pissed off dude?
She got to live it up a little bit.
Take competitive sports. I'm at home when I'm not awake. How can this be a bad thing?
I'm there when needed. My kids can come and see me whenever they like. My wife knows what I'm doing.
I'm spending
Oh really
Very little money compared to activities away from home
But still I spend too much time on the computer or so I'm told
Thank you very much. Sometimes I do spend too much time on the computer
Well, and my other hobbies, throwing boom rings, flying radio control helicopter's
Making interest here and of course my astronomy and podcasting
But that still seems better than spending too much time at the pub
And no matter how many times I've tried to get it to come join me in my preferred pastimes
She still breathes and attempts to include her
Okay, one last big comment. Please stop saying that every person in second life
Is having six?
Oh please.
That's one of no interest in that side of it.
And I'm not the only one that I know of.
Sure it's a big part of it and those who are interested
But as much as I'm interested in real life, second life holds no appeal to me in that area
Talk about all you like but don't throw all of us into the same mold
It's not helping us promote second life to others as a serious way of communicating
with the community and doing business when people come back and say, but I don't carry
Say it.
Okay.
That's it from me.
Yeah.
I think that more of those golden tickets.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
You've still got plenty, but I haven't seen one in any more
Downloads yet.
So get cracking and get them out there.
Anyway, bye for now.
Alright, buddy. Thank you very much.
Wise words from Down Under.
Gotta agree with you completely.
It's just not about playing.
This is a new wave communicating.
That's all I'm identifying and you're right, man.
You can call it playing at the computer, but I've been doing this all my life
Since the second year, my wife and I were married 18 years now.
I've been tinkering around and it's so funny.
You say that I said, look, isn't this amazing?
Look, I can type in FTP and then a file comes in and look.
Hold on. Hold on. Just wait. It's downloading.
Don't move. Hold on. It's coming.
Oh, there it is. Look. It's a little red ball.
And then we move to the web and every single step.
What was the member I see queue? I see queue.
That was the predecessor to all real instant message clients.
I think this is just another step.
Alright, moving on.
We've been talking this past week.
And I think, by the way, that we're going to get a best of Charlie.
We're going to have some other notes here.
Patricia was looking for something in my office and I always tell her,
please, don't do that because now the note that I had is of course gone.
I asked just lovely.
This is me off. Okay.
I've been talking about silent birth.
The all in relation to Katie Holmes and Tom Cruise and Scientology.
And Mark Dand said, Adam, I enjoyed the show.
One of the reasons because of the clean way of you look at things and that you listen
with a smile even to those who criticize the show.
Well, of course.
My comments on the silent birth stuff.
Hypnosis stuff.
What was said is true.
What is said while not less or not or less conscious gets recorded.
The important bit is one can become the adverse effect of these recordings.
Good, better and different.
Now, what was said about intentionally putting in good commands is a bad thing because
let's look at it.
What that amounts to and what hypnosis does is make one into an automation
to a greater or lesser degree.
I don't understand that sense.
Good, better and different.
The words or concepts go in.
Since, say, one is being programmed with one's permission or not.
One is being programmed.
A programmed effect on the unconscious mind in Scientology.
One does things to become more cause and less effect.
Mark, I think you've just hypnotized me with your completely in intelligible message.
Yeah, but I kind of understand where you're coming from.
And I was thinking, I would really like to talk more to people who understand about mind control or mind programming.
We've done a pretty good job with this Senseo project.
You know, wherever I go now, whenever there's a burp in the room on the TV.
Man, if I was in the movie theater, it happened, someone would probably say Senseo.
Certainly, if I knew I was in the room.
Is it actually possible to hypnotize someone through a podcast?
I mean, there's gotta be some hypnotist out there who is listening to the show.
And I mean, consider that most people listening to this with ear buds jam deep into their ear.
I really like to experiment with that.
And with your permission, of course, listeners to the Charlie.
Let's see if we can do some.
The Senseo thing is definitely a programming, but how far can we take it?
This is kind of a Yang's versus the Brits thing.
Actually, this was a comment on show number 377 from a UK listener and a fan.
Adam Curry versus the ordinary bloke.
And this is an audio bit just waiting to happen.
AC wakes up at 6 a.m. with a lovely Patricia.
Heads downstairs for a double Senseo in the curry cottage.
Ordinary bloke wakes up with a screaming child at 6 a.m.
And falls downstairs for a cup of instant coffee in a terrace in some northern UK town.
AC turns on his G5 Apple Mac on 20-meg broadband super duper speed.
As the satellite hovers above the lovely affluent town of Guilford in Surrey.
The ordinary bloke turns on his Dell PC piece of crap Microsoft thing.
He has the dial-up modem connects at 56 kbps as the rain falls down in the, in the, in the, what?
In the arf you learnt to podcast town in England.
I don't know what that is.
AC begins to podcast to the world from the curry cottage with talk of his car.
A Jaguar soon to be running on biodiesel and saving the world.
Whilst the lovely Patricia makes AC a breakfast of scrambled eggs and smoke salmon with pepper on top.
Ordinary bloke begins to grueling one hour commute to work to Manchester on,
unleaded in a 10 year old Audi A6 soon to run out of unleaded fuel and destroying the world.
Whilst the nagging wife chucks the pack lunch OB for got into the pin.
AC burps a sincere burp.
As NGB, CSB and Roger Smalls state that they have recently quit their day job and are meeting up
with AC in the curry condo and San Fran.
Ordinary blokes.
Well, he farts an instant coffee canco at the boss.
The secretary and the phone in sick bloke states that they, that they won the lottery the weekend.
And are meeting up with AC in the curry condo and San Francisco.
AC after podcasting the serious and iTunes and blogging and flickering some picks.
AC joins his second life and enters the badass pleasure rooms in the curry castle while smoking a spliff.
The ordinary bloke, after working all day without a break and receiving C.C.s of emails,
you will never read.
Ordinary bloke joins his second life in the cardboard box of the I can't afford a real home
never mind a virtual home in the land of 56 KBPS.
For AC after flying around all afternoon, the glorious sky of Surries UK and the D.S.C.
lands on a landing strip of Brazilian qualities.
For the ordinary, ordinary bloke, after messing all afternoon in the dull and cloudy atmosphere
in the office of greater Manchester UK, the ordinary bloke bumps into an old stripper of press-cut qualities.
That's a very UK joke there.
AC and OB take a day off and head to Amsterdam and bump into each other in a cafe.
AC offers OBSN sale, spliffy trippy smoke and OBS offers AC a logger.
Conclusion, AC and OB are both happy and both enjoy the experience.
AC gives OBSG mail address to keep in touch and OB replies but ends up in the junk mail filter of the AC world.
Man, I wish my wife my life was that.
I should really jot down everything that happens, but it's much more like,
I'm just, excuse me.
It's much more like I'm just seem to have never ending supply of email.
Oh boy, a way to fix that, please, definitely a way to fix that.
Let's see how we do it on time.
Man, I already blasted through 20 minutes of just talking about crap.
Everyone was talking online about that Stephen Colbert, a speech that he gave at the White House press core dinner.
And so I took some time to download. It was on a bit torrent, which still took forever.
Yeah, maybe saving bandwidth somewhere, but you've got this application open running all the time.
Your computer starts to slow down.
I don't think we're quite ready.
Just that was not a big bit torrent experience for me.
But I'm really so much, you know, praise for.
Now Stephen Colbert does a show for those of you who don't know in the States,
right after John Stewart's Daily Show and it's a very,
well, it's just like more or less like the Daily Show.
It's, you know, it's a fun look at politics and world news.
And I didn't get it.
I didn't think it was funny.
I thought, you know, all of us one liners were like kind of like chuckle one liners.
And really, it kind of appalled me to see, you know, here's the world's press sitting there,
making jokes about the low polls, about Dick Cheney.
But really, it's, it's appalling.
You know, I expect so much more from a press core and even Stephen Colbert, you know,
when will someone really seriously say something about what's happening in the world today?
You know, what a missed opportunity that was.
I certainly didn't think it was funny.
You know, and I'm a big fan of using comedy and humor to talk about serious issues,
but I found that a tremendously large, you know, missed opportunity.
It just didn't work for me at all.
If you haven't seen it,
don't just look at the Colbert thing, which is at the end.
But look at every single guy that stands up there and talks and,
oh, man, it's Hollywood.
It was, it's politics.
It's show business for ugly people.
It really is.
It's just, it kind of disgusted me.
Coming up on a serious stars 102 as we head into the weekend.
We have, oh, great.
We've got a Wichita brother for it on tonight.
That'll be on it to 9 to 9 to 9 30 East Coast time, CC Chapman,
closing out the entire evening.
And just in a few moments from out Pacific Coast,
Hellway with Mark Yoshimoto,
Namcoff in the Pacific Coast, Hellway players,
East Radio Dawn and Drew.
And with a bit of like Gilmore Daily,
I think he was at the On Hollywood conference,
so they'll probably have some interesting guests on there.
And we'll be back Monday right here on serious stars 102
for you checking us out on the satellite radio.
If you want to hear the rest of the show,
you'll have to go to dailysourceco.com to download it all
and check out more great podcasts at podshow.com.
And thank you all so much for sending all those great messages
from Portsmouth.
That's where Patricia and I went to see Joan Collins.
Wow.
It seems like I got a lot of listeners in Portsmouth.
And it really is an interesting looking town
and Patricia and I definitely plan on going back soon
to see it during the daytime.
They even had, what is it called?
You know, the self-proclaimed seven star hotel in Dubai,
the Boersh, Arap Hotel that looks like a big sailboat.
There's like a mini version of that in Portsmouth,
which is the weirdest thing.
There's very picturesque old world type of English
seaside town or harbor town, I would say.
And then there's this very modern structure with a blue sail at night,
which wasn't ugly by the way.
It fit in very nicely.
But what's the story with that?
And thank you all so much for checking out the source code
and for those of you who have been calling into our voice mail line.
Yeah, this is Scott TD in Saskatoon.
I love your phone idea.
There's one problem with it.
You're going to get people calling in drunk.
Now, I know you might not intended to,
but trust me, it's going to happen.
Because half the podcast I listened to,
have a phone number for that exact purpose,
so people can call in well drunk or other forms of intoxication
like you enjoy.
So just to warn you, hopefully you don't get mad people
for doing that because I probably will eventually at some point
because well, it's a lot of fun because you really can say
whatever you want and the stories that I have come up with
already on the unemployment line,
check them out at unemploymentshow.com and the strange brewed
at the strange food.com.
They're, they're drunk dies from all over the world,
are hilarious.
And I think that it could quite add to the show,
but also subtract from it because you might have
too much time going through these.
Yo, I saw Mr. Curry.
Like in stuff like that.
I got a lot of that this morning.
And I, yeah.
Some say, and we've had this conversation a lot of pod shows,
like well, you need to get a producer,
but I think that if I had a producer who would pre-screen
the emails and the voice emails and the audio feedback,
then I might as well just become a regular radio guy,
you know, walks in.
Oh, here I am, five minutes before the show,
which by the way is exactly the way it works.
And the producer's got a lot of stuff,
and he's been working for hours.
I think that's a big part of this.
You've got to be down to the trenches.
You've got to be doing it yourself,
because I am the show, not a producer.
I mean, I could certainly use someone
to do other things for me,
like pay the bills,
take care of my schedule,
clean up my office,
Roger Smalls, where are you?
Hello, Adam.
This is Lorenzo Longness.
You may remember me from my hit series,
Renegade, where I played,
along with my big girlfriend, Kathleen Kinmont.
I've been listening to the chat,
John, I think we have something in common,
a literary tradition.
I want to introduce you to the certified center
for a literary tradition.
Just some examples.
You have the curry castle, the curry cottage,
the curry condo,
now the poggio palace,
kind of surprise that your name isn't Adam,
something I guess Adam,
and it was taken in Adam Adams,
would be a little too close,
but maybe Carl Currie.
Carl doesn't really fit,
Kurt Currie,
and that's too close to Kurt Loader.
Anyway, Adam,
I think you need help.
I think you need to check out the certified center
for a literary tradition addiction.
Besides that, the way I get help is
I listen to the daddy cast.
It helps me cope with my problems
and help my children
little Larry Lombus,
and Lucy Lombus, who is named after Lucy Wallace.
Adam, please get help,
and please say hi to your wife,
Patricia Pai,
and your daughter, Christina Currie,
wait a minute.
Your sickness is more than I thought.
Adam, get help now,
and listen to the daddy cast.
That's a promo, man.
It's true.
I do suffer from what you call it,
a literacy?
What was that?
It was something weird, weird name.
Yeah, I like that, man.
I like it.
We've got the curry cats.
We've got the damn dog.
And yes, the Chacha.
Hi, Adam.
It's Karen from RumorGirl.com.
And I'm calling because I was really
getting annoyed with all the talk about second life.
Until yesterday, when we did-
This, by the way, is a very typical story.
Very, very typical story.
I've received many of these,
but because it's come from the RumorGirls
around the Pod Show podcast network,
I really had to play this for her.
I tried to do our podcast,
and I was over at Carolyn Frank's place.
And we just-
The Carla cast.
Frank, please, second life all the time.
And I'm like, what is the big deal about second life?
So I looked at it.
I saw the curry mansion,
and I saw that obnoxious pod cast pickle thing behind you guys,
or, yeah, I think it is behind.
Yeah, it was just so annoying.
And I was still like,
what the heck?
What is so great about this stupid second life?
And what's all the talk about it?
And even in our podcast, Carla,
and I talked about it,
and we said, we just want Adam to go back
to his normal Charlie.
That's all we want.
And so anyway,
today I'm listening to the Charlie number 380,
and I'm listening to people talking about it.
Now I feel addicted.
Why?
Because now I know what they're talking about.
I know about the mansion.
They're talking about a couple of people.
I'm thinking, I think I saw them yesterday.
And now I'm thinking about getting second life.
What are you getting me addicted to?
Now, first of all, with pod cast thing,
now it's a stupid second life.
Great.
I can't even deal with my first life.
Now I'm onto my second life.
Anyway, I just wanted to say that
I love being a part of pod shell,
and check us out at rumorgirls.com,
and I'll talk to you soon.
Thanks.
You'll be your baby.
Thank you so much.
Now, I'm not going to talk about it anymore.
I'm not going to talk about any of my experiences
in second life anymore.
I'm not going to do it.
See you in five years when we're all in there.
Hey, Adam.
This is you.
It's on here.
You're neighbor at Ferris.
Just going to say hi,
and standing in my office looking at the Delta Sierra.
You're parked in the hangar right outside my little workshop window,
and she's very clean and tidy.
Nobody's back to other aircraft until he'll be delighted.
She's lovely.
Did you get the notes?
I left on her the other day with a picture of the diesel power there,
craft us for and check you the other day.
Very cool.
Anyway, thanks a lot.
See you here at Ferris.
One of these days.
Oh, you forgot to say tailwinds.
In that nice,
these are people that only know me through the daily source code.
I love that.
That's so incredible.
I got a call from from Jason at the tower this morning.
Said, hey, Adam, how you doing?
Hey, look, I got your customs form because you have to,
if you come in from outside the UK,
you have to every single time you have to file a,
actually, is that a customs form?
It's an immigration form, I think it is.
Is it?
Is it immigration?
I think, well, immigration to customs.
So you have to file a form.
It's really easy.
You fill it out.
You have to do a flight plan anyway,
and then you fax it off.
And you fax a copy to the,
to the airfield we're going to land.
And it was so cool.
Jason said, hey, Adam, I don't miss Jason here.
That's right.
That was the jury is still out if,
if Roger Smalls doesn't work in the, in the control tower at,
at the pharaohs airfield.
He says, I got your immigration form,
but you might want to send it again
because it wasn't really legible.
But I heard yesterday on the podcast that you're coming,
you're going to see your mom and Roger dams.
So I, I assume that's what it is,
but you know,
we don't want to have another visit from,
from customs or immigration.
So why don't you just refax it?
I was like, wow, man, this is some reach we've got.
This is really cool.
So indeed,
I am going to see my mom again tomorrow.
Um,
I hope she's,
well, I'll give you a report on Monday.
Yeah.
She sounds great on the phone.
She has a good day.
She has her bad days.
She literally says sometimes.
She says, well, you know,
yesterday,
so that I got,
I had a real bad day.
So that I did dip.
I didn't give a,
so here's my mom talking, right?
I don't give a fuck or I didn't give a fuck yesterday.
I don't care.
I know you'd be disappointed in me,
but I don't care about anybody.
And, you know,
so two men.
And I keep telling her,
that's, that's when you got to call me,
mom.
What is that?
That's the recycle bin dudes.
They're late today.
I was bank holiday,
of course.
That's why.
So,
uh,
going tomorrow and Patricia is sending me off with,
some of her famous soup.
Uh,
because my mom has to eat more.
She's got to eat more.
Hey,
if any of you who are listening live in Los Angeles,
uh,
I don't know if you listen to KLA,
but I got a very interesting voice mail,
uh,
regarding that,
and I don't quite understand it.
Hi, Adam.
Uh,
so was that room of you on PLA radio?
I heard you,
but,
uh,
I wasn't sure if you were live or not,
and you didn't say anything about it.
So,
I was just calling you curious,
but you sounded wonderful,
and you got the good work.
Bye.
So now I'm not sure if you said KLA,
or P-
Shut up!
They're backing up into the cul-de-sac.
I don't know if she said KLA,
or if she said PLA,
but did anyone hear me on the radio in Los Angeles?
Uh,
it makes no sense to me.
here,
this is a sound seeing tour of the,
uh,
the cottage,
recycle pickup,
recycle it.
Don't waste it.
Call the recycling hotline.
Oh,
1483,
445,
084.
There's a bunch of guys with no t-shirts on outside my house.
Hmm.
Okay.
So, well, that's going on in the background,
because it's,
it's not all irritating.
I,
uh,
I kind of broke format a little bit,
the other day,
if you can call it that,
and uh,
and it's solicited some feedback
on the Iranian situation.
And,
and not because I want to get deep into politics
and talk about stuff,
I really want to understand it,
because it just,
it makes,
what I'm hearing,
what I'm reading makes so little sense to me.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Uh,
makes so little say,
this is what podcasting is all about.
We don't,
What sound proof studios?
We ain't got no,
just thanking sound proof studios?
And I just wanted to see if anyone had any views,
and well,
some appreciated the thoughts
some didn't,
and some actually had some very interesting insights.
sites. Hey Adam, it's Ryan from Rhode Island. Thanks for that really loud beep on the
answering service there. That's fun to my ear. Sorry about leaving a message on
a cell phone. I know you said try not to do that, but here I am doing that. Just
wanted to call in way in a little bit on the Iran topic that you brought up
here today's source code was at 358. I have to say the comment that you made about
Jacob, who seems to be right on the funny, feels the same thing right now. Every
time I see Bush leaned it over the podium. It seems like I could just picture
him as a school yard bully waiting to punch somebody in the nose. And I was
talking a few people that worked for me who are pretty much directly immigrated
from Iran. And they're really worried too. Their families are there and they've been
trying to make plans to move people around and see who can stay with who will
outside the country. Because they're just worried about number one
higher administration and number two, the Iranian administration. That's
sub-situation and I really don't want to see this thing on full the way. It looks
like it's gotten. Anyway, take care and thanks a lot, bye.
Hey Adam, what's going on? I'm the sort of fact winner of the StickWorld podcast. I'm
currently driving in my car here in Las Vegas, so 97 degrees. I have the
air conditioning on full blast and it's still hot. Anyway, so I just had to
call in about this. I'm still in the middle of listening to a number 380, so
number 380, where you asked about people right in or call in or send a feedback
about their opinions on what's going on with Iran and the UN and the US and all
that stuff. Now, this is just my opinion and I'm going to keep it really short
because I've already recorded this net this three times and it was like three
minutes long. Anyway, I don't think that you should have done that. I just
think we remember you a few shows that you were saying you didn't want to talk
about this stuff. So what made you change your mind? And I know I noticed when you
when you asked for the feedback that you're a little apprehensive too, but it's
kind of curious what's going on in your head. And you know, I don't know about other
people, but I kind of use the daily source code to get away from stuff like that.
You know, we get it in the newspaper, we get it on the radio, we get it in TV.
Everybody's talking about it, you know, and it's kind of nice to not have
something out there where you're not having to deal with it for 40
minutes at a time, 45 minutes at a time. You know, it's kind of like like podcast,
you can kind of pick and choose what you want listen to. You know, I
subscribe to over 25 podcasts that I listen to every day. And none of them are
political. And to be honest with you, actually none of them talk about politics
either, which is kind of nice. And so I just had to call in, I had to get back to
the show. I got a listen, because I got 24 other podcasts to get to you
before the day is over. There's one of the call in and give you my opinion on
that. So, and I guess because I may a student pilot, I can say this, tell
it. Yeah, right on man. Of course you can. You've got that right. You've
earned the right. You're in the machine. You're in sheet metal with rivets
my friend. Of course, you can say tailwinds. In that cool from Rhode Island to
Vegas, a through iPods and MP3s, it still blows me away. What's happening?
I'm standing here and it wouldn't console in a spare bedroom in England. I
love that. Now, I don't want to get political. I'm, you know, just a
couple of observations. First of all, I'm really, really, really tired of
people beating up on any political leader. I'm tired of it. Okay. I'm tired of
people beating up on Bush, on Blair, on any, any leader. You know, it's
more than just the leader, because the people still have those people,
certainly still have the power in their own hands to change the world.
And the interesting is happening here, although I don't know if it's good or
bad, but the British nationalist party is that that would be in peace
stands for their winning local elections, or they won a significant amount of
local elections in the UK, which means Tony Blair's labor party just might
be on the way out when the next elections occur, which is also quite a
mystery to me how elections are called here in the UK. So again, the reason
is not, it's, I don't want any, I'm not interested in really political
talk. I am interested in the world around us than what's happening. And
when I hear all this atomic shit over and over again, that's when all
my alarm bells go off from saying, you know, it just doesn't make sense.
You know, there you've got our buddy in Rhode Island who's got friends who have
family in Iran and they're concerned and they're trying to move their
family out. I mean, so it's clearly not the Iranians. It's not those
Iranians who want to, you know, nuke me or or nuke you. Is it really the
leaders? Is that really who's doing it? Or is this something else
to play here? Hey, Adam, this is Chris and the financial aid podcast with a
tin foil hat moment on Iran. Here's a very quick primer and oil using
second life as an example. Right now, there are two exchanges for oil,
9x in New York and the IPE in London. All major transactions on the world
market are in US dollars, which is a great benefit to the US economy.
It means that all countries wanting to buy petroleum products on the
world market must have US dollars in their federal reserves purchased from
the United States, just like you purchased linden's and second life from the
linden corporation. However, Iran is setting up an exchange of its own
supposedly we go online this month called the Iranian oil boss.
Its chosen currency will be the euro, not the dollar. If the Iranian oil
boss becomes wildly successful on the world market and there's a good
reason to believe that it may as countries such as China would welcome the
chance to use a currency not linked to the US. Then some economists believe that
up to 20% of the currency being used in international oil trade could be the
euro. That's 20% fewer dollars being bought in first life for oil.
The effect on the US economy would be devastating as we require massive
infusions on a daily basis of foreign countries purchasing
our currency and our debt. Having 20% fewer dollars being used in
international oil trade could tip the US economy into recession quite easily
and even forced the US government to potentially hyper inflate its currency to
avoid default. Well, any of this come to pass? It's hard to say, but it's
definitely food for thought and certainly more information out there that
you can use to make decisions when you're watching the media.
This is Chris from the Financial Aid podcast at financialadpodcast.com
tune in daily. It's for financial aid news and disturbing tinfoil hat moments.
Take care Adam. Do you can check in any time you want with disturbing tinfoil hat moments like
that. Thank you so much. Now things start to come into the picture for me. Now I'm
understanding it. Okay. It's about things apparently it looks like stuff is not about
atomic energy or weapons of mass destruction at all. This is all about economics.
I haven't read that anywhere and I read the, you know, that recycled piece of shit, the
financial times. I say recycled piece of shit because it's printed on, you know, like yellow
recycled paper. So I guess that's it then. Discredit those guys because they're trying to take
our business. That would make sense. And then there's this whole pipeline business. You know,
we really are in the middle ages still when it comes to the world stage.
It's all about turf. It's all about money. It's all about who's, who's the boss of who
is coming. Yes. Comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip
can't start a weekend without a note from CSB. Hello, Adam Kerry. How are you?
So I am just a listener of your show. I would like to suggest you something as a listener.
Namely, one of my favorite radio presenters has a number of correspondence who are regular
listeners appointed by him to report on subjects such as video games, London Underground,
urban, music, urban music etc. The opportunity to become a correspondent is a very, very
one and much valued by listeners of this radio presenter. I hereby suggest Adam Kerry that you
too will appoint some correspondence on various topics and let them plaque the topics
or podcasts and you would play their shot of your reports on regular basis. Once a month for
example. I volunteer for being a correspondent on European Union, but I reckon that several
people would volunteer as correspondence on various topics and areas of interest. Just ask your listeners.
So have a nice weekend mate and move your skinny ass out of this fucking gulfot to admire the rest
of beautiful UK too. Dood, I admire it plenty. I saw Portsmouth just the other night and tomorrow
I'll be flying over, dover and all kinds of other wonderful places. It's beautiful and as a pilot
you have such a different perspective on the land that you live on. So I enjoy it. You know,
comic strip that I think that's exactly not the way to go. Everybody, every listener of the show
as far as I'm concerned is a correspondent. Whatever's going on in your piece of the world,
you know, or in the piece of your life. Let me know about it. Our voice mail phone numbers are 201-625-635-7.
That's our number in Jersey. Still proud to be the Jersey boy. And of course, in the UK,
London, O2O-768-1375-3. I'm going to drop the Yanks versus the Brits for the Friday festivities
because I wanted to play one more song. We're already moving way past the 40-minute mark and this
one is about pod save music and you know that's close to my heart. Hi Adam, it's been
downing. I listen a song in Melbourne, Australia and on the Charlie 374 you played Mr. Lovely
by Beth Thunley. If you don't remember the song, he's a quick snippet.
Actually, like there are songs so much dumb to Beth's website where I listen to
so many other songs that she had on there and I decided to purchase her album. Beth has
installed me that I'm the first to train to purchase her album and it's an artist I would never have
heard of if it wasn't for the pod save music network and the daily source code. So thank you, Adam.
No, dude, thank you so much. Are you kidding me? I'm glad you remind me of that song.
I don't think so. You must be good, please, Beth. That's much better.
Straight off the pod save music network, Beth Thunley for your weekend festivity kickoff.
It's the song. In the morning I'm probably done here by luck. I can't say you'd be long gone.
Oh, Mr. Lovely.
There's no, there's no, there's no, there's no, there's no.
That ain't never aọ's.
He has a pricey. He has a pricey.
Looks like a hope.
Oh, she urge you knocked everybody into the world.
In one day, she reminds me of her song.
I don't know that time she'll find this show.
No, I know the more it lurks
No more I hate my head deeper
Oh, Mr. Lovely
I'll see you again
You want to grow my friend
Well, you're active in the middle and can't wait
You're just a slave in the morning
You're just walking in the rain, can't you?
There's no shame in the rain
Let's roll up and take you to the restaurant and be on a day
Bethorne Lee, Mr. Lovely
If you think and why does Adam suck so bad on the cowbell?
I just want you to know that I don't really have the proper proper equipment yet because I've been using a pencil
All right, and and the pencil just doesn't have the right, you know, girth or length or weight to really get into the rhythm, all right
So I want you to know that there are obstacles in my in my cowbell playing and I'm really trying to
Had a really nice email conversation with Beth or since I played her the first time and it's so nice to see
Someone fresh and new to potsafe music to go like wow, what is happening here? You know all of a sudden
I'm people buying my stuff and Australia sending me email and and it's lovely to see that happen
It really is said, Mr. Lovely, right?
Okay, I told you about the the potsafe music
Some are stuff that we're working on and now
I haven't really discussed this with the sales and marketing team, but just think
Parks think big parks think all around America think wouldn't it be great if you could go see
A potsafe music showcase
In a really professional environment wouldn't that be cool?
Okay, now there's only a couple of them so and and trust me. It's not the mouse house, okay?
You know Anna and this is Regis from unemploymentshow.com
AKA Regis the soda and second life
I've been out there about a week now checking it out due to your suggestion and most of that time has been me screwing on with my avatar
Trying to get a good outfit going and you know trying to fix the size of my nose by look good and I realize what we need
We need the second life Metro sexual moment. We need somebody that can help people with their hair style and tell me what color would be and
You know, I guess I get a pot show t-shirt that would take care of most of my outfit
But yeah, the second life Metro sexual moment is a good way for you to expand it
Also regarding second life. I don't get to outplayer. I play in a cover band and we do
Anything from the Beatles to Tom Jones to, you know, Rick Springfield or Stone Temple pilots
We do you know everything from pretty much to the rock genre and I was thinking that if we get the streaming thing worked on online
That I could be a good opening act if you had the videos playing at the castle sometime
You know because I can take a lot of requests if I could just you know show up with my acoustic guitar and
You know get the cloud gone before the the main act come on that would be really cool to do
Or if you're having a party just want to throw me on the roof and just you know party up there people and you know play some tunes
That would be fun too, so but I don't know about the streaming thing, you know my process are kind of wigs out as it is on second life
It's probably because I have too many tabs open and fire fox at the same time, so
So there you go second life. I got a sign off here
I can't see tailwinds I'm not a pilot. I can't say I can't do the wider flick
I don't even do that stuff anymore unfortunately
But I did think of one thing that I could sign off with and that would be to wish you many blow jobs
So so BJs Adam and I'm hoping this catches on because I really want to hear comic strip bloggers say
The low jobs and in charity or how about you know Roger small doing it?
May the blow jobs see with you Adam
There you go buddy, we'll be getting many and
Many blow jobs in the next week. Thank you later. Oh man at first I'm like no not another second life comment
But then you really pulled it out man. I appreciate that. Yeah, many BJs to you
And may you receive or shall you give this weekend either one is fine. Let's have more those this weekend, okay?
Get your ass out of second life and let's concentrate on blow jobs
Much better idea
portions of the show brought you by earth link the pod show challenge on the way soon brought you by earth link
You're gonna love it. You're gonna be able to participate and win valuable cash prizes and change advertising at the same time
I know it sounds really hokey, but you can love it. It's good for having a lot of fun just prepping for it
Also, of course, I'll keep you download with the with Heather and Janelle download.acu.com
And if you're looking for a great deal on domain name go to do that go daddy.com and
Upon check out use the special promotional code dsc3 dsc number three and you'll get your domain name for only six dollars and 95 cents
And that's it a little bit longer than intended
We'll be back to 40 minutes on Monday another full week coming up. Have yourselves a great weekend
BJs everybody
Show podcast stick it in your ear
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from pod show and limelight networks