This is MV from bedtime stories my kids love.
If you want stories that will keep your kids from going to bed,
check out Shadow Falls, and don't say I didn't warn you.
This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
Show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 453.
I need more intros, send me intros.
I'm a Mac, and I'm a PC.
So are you ready to get started?
Nope, I've got a lot to do.
Got to get this trial software deleted, update software, get some anti-virus.
Well, sounds like you've got a lot to do, so I'm just going to get started.
What? What are you going to do?
Go play some games that came out in 1998.
What did you say, bitch?
You heard me?
Now you're getting cut.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass,
then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
She was best studying abroad.
He was on tour.
Playing in another dime.
They partyed hard and they partyed wings.
A little north of the sand.
He dreamed about her in so many ways.
She dreamed about her in French.
Well, she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
That is the one.
He's his mother son, not like anyone.
He just needs time to heal.
They met in New York a few months later.
He was still living alone.
Hugging the ball and masturbating.
Never answered his phone.
That first date was a movie together.
Outside it Brian Pock.
Well, the spirit I'm saying, Louis,
just went on for a vlog.
Till they drank wine.
Until they saw his cars.
Well, she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
That is the one.
He's his mother son, not like anyone.
He just needs time to heal.
They finally hooked up for the first time.
The night before the Fourth of July.
He felt so awkward saying goodbye to the girl who just changed his life.
Now my friend, they are in separate ball.
She even gets that boy to go to the gym.
Now if you don't think that's love, you must be cynical.
Oh, maybe man, you're just dreaming in friends.
Yeah, because she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
That is the one.
He's his mother son, not like anyone.
He just needs time to heal.
Oh, she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
That is the one.
He's his mother son, not like anyone.
He just needs time to heal.
Yeah, he's the one.
He's his mother son, not like anyone.
He just needs time to heal.
Well, that's right.
Oh, it's been too long to play that one.
Can he butchers what to do with Michael from the pod save music network, my viola?
Add it again.
Hey, everybody.
How you doing?
It's the daily source code episode 453 coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey
known as Gilford.
It's the curry cottage.
Please send me more openings.
Let's see.
I've been really enjoying these intros you've been sending me to the show.
I've left.
I've got four, five, four.
I've got five, five, one.
And I've got six, six, six.
Please.
Somebody fill in the gaps for me, will ya?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's one of those days.
It's one of those days when kind of nothing's going on.
And when I'm thinking, what the heck am I going to do on the show today?
There she is.
My pillar.
Not below.
She's there to save my ass.
What do I do?
Adam, hey, it's Amy Mack.
This is day five and today we're doing lunches.
Lunches.
Can you believe we've been at this for five weeks?
Yeah.
This has got to be hot by now.
I can't wait to show you.
All right.
Let's get started.
What are we doing?
You're going to start with feet shoulder with a pair.
Let's take a big step forward with your right leg.
Okay.
Now pause and then bend the right knee and have your body moved straight down.
Oh, I know.
And like always, you don't want your front knee to come over your toes.
Okay.
Your left knee should be about two inches from the ground.
Oh.
Come back up and bring that right leg back to the center.
So you're in your beginning stand.
It wasn't quite two inches.
Good.
Now the left.
Left.
Okay.
Big step.
You're long legs.
So the step she covers from ground.
Yes.
Pause.
Now straight down.
You should really feel this in your back leg and your foot.
Okay.
Come back to center.
Great.
Now back to the other side.
You have seven more to do on each side.
Why ask seven on each side?
Don't forget to squeeze your stomach and breathe.
We don't want you to become like a head of, you know.
This exercise is already a lower body exercise.
It focuses on the butt, thigh as an abs.
Can you feel it?
Yes.
Good.
The pause allows you to align yourself so that you keep proper form when doing the lunge.
Keeping the front knee from coming over the toe is really important and protect in your knee.
And maximizing the benefits of the exercise.
To find out more health and fitness tips or to subscribe to my show, check out the fitness
attack podcast at fitness.podshow.com.
As you mentioned last week, Adam, we're going to make exercise a separate feed.
Yeah.
We'll be located at AsurSize.com.
So for now, it's a working progress.
But we're getting there.
So stay tuned.
All right.
I think that's it.
Fabulous job is always more a weekend and have a great birthday.
Until next time.
AsurSize.
Thank you.
Thank you Amy Mack.
Seven on your side.
I feel, I don't know, man.
I don't know if it's helping at all.
It reminds me of fencing.
We used to lunge all the time.
You know, I was, I was like a third national champion in the Netherlands when I was,
I don't know, 15 or something like that.
Fencing.
Yeah.
You know, sounds kind of faggy.
I've got to catch my breath and I've got to lay off the splits.
Hey, Adam, kneel here from the Podsafe Revolution.
Bring you your weekly football Friday Podsafe tune.
This week I'm recommending a track called Slow Burn by Sacramento's seventh standard.
Now, they're not up on the PMN yet.
But if you know me, these guys are coming soon.
Now, remember way back in May.
I was creating a Podsafe marathon playlist.
That marathon went well until the end when I literally crawled to the finish line.
I finished in three hours and 30 minutes, which isn't bad, but now I'm out to beat that time.
So I'll be running in the Prince Edward County marathon on October 1st here in Ontario, Canada.
And for that occasion, I'm once again building an open-source Podsafe marathon playlist.
Now, I've just released Episode 17 of the Podsafe Revolution, which is a 76 minute mix tape of what we have so far.
So anyone out there who is pounding the pavement with an iPod plugged into their brain,
training for an event, or for those of you who just want to check out what this whole revolution is about.
Check it out at the PodsafeRevolution.podshow.com.
Thanks to the power of Pods Show Plus.
You can just add comments to suggest songs for the playlist, or you can email them to podsafeRevolutionatgmail.com.
Now, for those of you about to run, I salute you.
And Adam, grab your cowbell.
This song needs it.
Until next week, I'm wishing you a kick-ass food by Friday.
Cheers, man.
Of course, I already played slow burn.
So I feel kind of stupid now for playing that.
But I did want to get him his word out about the Podsafe mix marathon mix tape.
Let's see, I got a pretty cool email yesterday from Kevin.
First person show.net.
He says, always looking, always looking for stuff for you, for audio, for the daily source code.
This is, and of course, I'll put a link in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
This is a guy taking on a telemarketer.
Now, I have to say, in the United Kingdom, I'm amazed at how many telemarketers call.
And by the way, it's like my bank, usually.
You know, it's Barclays Bank.
And they're always like, we want to review your account.
I said, if you call me one more time, I'm going to review the account.
Of course, I didn't record that.
But it's just always around 830 between 8 and 9 o'clock.
It's just calling, and calling, of course, in the States, that's supposed to have diminished
because of this, you know, never call database that was set up.
I wonder if it actually has diminished if telemarketing has slowed down at all in the US.
But this guy, and I think he's from the UK, he kind of turns the tables on a telemarketer.
And I really liked it, and I think I will use this tactic.
Check it out.
That is okay, sir.
One is a little bit more about what you're asking.
Well, I am calling you on a APT.
And today, we have a special offer of a free mobile phone just for you.
You're not going to have to do the work together.
Well, sir, in order to get it, you must give us details about yourself.
What else can you tell me about this offer?
I'm definitely really interested at a really, much a little bit more.
Well, sir, what we need to do is firstly get information from you.
So that we can tell you more.
You come and see exactly.
Well, sir, if you let us know.
Sorry about that.
Thank you, sir.
No problem, sir.
That's a really nice touch.
You're doing really, it was really ghastly like death cough.
That works.
I think if you give me the morning information, what I really feel about this offer.
I'm definitely really interested at a really, much a little bit more.
Well, sir, I am trying to be telling you some more.
Please, please, to be letting this in, sir.
Well, it's what I'm having with you, exactly.
But sir, I am telling you how to work.
You know, sir.
Sorry about that.
You sound like you are sick, sir.
Maybe you do not like this offer.
I'm definitely really interested at a really, much a little bit more.
I am not sure I can tell you anything more, sir.
People who are not letting me see me.
And you keep saying the same thing over and over again.
I'm not worth it.
No, I cannot.
Ah.
Haha.
No, I cannot.
I cannot tell you now.
Fantastic.
I'm going to do that next time.
Hey, I'm really interested in your offer.
Can you tell me a bit more?
And that way, we have to get some of your details.
No, you tell me first.
Tell me a bit more about the offer.
I like it a lot.
Sorry about the shitty quality, but I think you got the gist.
One, two, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven.
Again.
If you want to call in to the Charlie Voice Mail Feedback number.
It's one, two, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven.
Put a plus and fun of that.
If you're entering this into a speed dial into your memory on your mobile phone.
So you can use it worldwide.
In the UK, if you want to call our London number,
02076813753.
Hello, Adam.
Hey, it's Martin Gd.
I have so to get point to get in the message.
Yeah, I was listening again to the Charlie and you're done.
Remember with your daughter?
I can synthesize and empathize.
One of them.
I'm a definitely self.
I look at 16 year old daughter.
They grew up all so fast these days.
And you got a nice and bucky head.
Yes.
So I'm watching my daughter, like any dad water,
making sure that her boyfriend's out of the scumbags.
That I was.
When I was at age.
And at the same time, I'm going to remember that when I met my daughter's mother,
we're now divorced.
She was in 2017 and I was 29.
Are you with us?
So I can see it from both sides.
I'm so to speak.
Yes, I was out scumbag who was pinching somebody's daughter.
This is the same time.
I've never got the daughter off that age.
Who was scumbags?
I'm over there.
The Charlie did.
It's like you're divorced.
So that's my whole point.
It doesn't.
You have like a couple shots against you.
You were what?
Well, you 20.
What?
It's like 12 years older than she was?
And my advice is because you can throw your kids' lives.
You can be there to pick them up when they get hurt.
But don't try and control them too much because they're low-needed.
I'm sure you remember when you and I've said something.
You did the complete opposite.
Give that advice.
Don't make demands.
They're always going to be there and looking to their parents to pack them up and pick them up.
Okay.
Words are advice and don't laugh.
This has been two days.
I'll now do them.
Thank you very much.
We're not telling you or not to go see Liam.
How can we?
We have this 15 years age difference between the two of us.
Of course, it's a big difference between meeting each other when the younger one is in his 20s.
And the older one is in her 30s versus 16 and 21.
I just feel right.
We haven't forbidden her.
Obviously not.
And I got to tell you though.
I can tell.
She's hearing what we're saying.
We're just giving her advice, right?
We're not saying she can't go out with him.
We're not saying he can't come over here.
We're not forbidding her from doing anything.
If you put a belief, I'm keeping my fucking eye on it.
I think you better believe that.
Yeah, this topic of conversation brought up a lot of feedback.
Particularly regarding...
Hey.
Hello, son.
What is that?
What's...
Where's that coming from?
The hell was that?
Is it...
It's not my blackberry?
The fuck is that?
Where's this coming from?
Oh, hold on.
It's another phone.
Shit.
Who called?
Interesting.
Someone from the Netherlands.
This is a really old phone I never used.
He could tell.
It was actually my windows mobile.
That's interesting.
I don't have to see what that's all about.
Anyway.
PWF ended 10th of course.
He was trying to be humorous.
I thought it was pretty funny.
But he sends it a pretty twisted comment.
PW, my brother.
I love you, man.
But that was really, really creepy.
But the comment he sent in that Adam Curry about checking out your daughter's friend.
It was like a really sick porno movie.
Please don't do that again.
Oh, man.
Have you ever heard a message from the future?
Hello.
This is, this is Edward Lloyd.
Am I getting through?
Can you hear me?
Recording this.
In the future.
The countdown has begun.
The transformation starts September 1st.
Words from thefeature.com.
Comics trip.
This is left channel.
This is right channel.
Higher Adam Blackberry.
I mean, Curry sausage.
Curry roast.
Yum.
Here's your European Union correspondent from comics trip.
blog.com.
In stereo.
Adam, matey.
I am pissed off at government of UK.
Because they have fallen for tabloid propaganda.
And decided to block three movement of fellow EU.
European Union citizens from Bulgaria and Romania.
That joined EU on January 1st, 2007.
This is wrong.
Decision.
I am set.
God.
Please forgive the braids for they.
No, not what they do.
Yo.
Our European correspondent.
Comics trip blogger checking in.
I haven't even read the paper yet.
But I presume that the United Kingdom is said,
Yeah, we don't want the new European Union citizens in just yet.
Please.
Bulgaria and Romania.
Stay away.
Oh, man, they're going to catch some grief for that.
It's going to be interesting.
Why doesn't the UK just step out of the European Union?
You know, then I'm using the euro.
The pound, of course, it makes them extremely powerful as a world force.
They've got great markets here, financial markets.
Yeah, I mean, if you'd like sheep, if it like lambs meat and pork,
what else do you need?
We don't need anything from Europe.
Thank you very much, CSB, for keeping us on the tip of that.
Yesterday, I made a call out to the aviation podcasters.
I said, hey, what the hell are you guys doing?
There's no risk aid.
Nothing, you know, talking about the craft that's going on in the world.
You know, about, uh, I really want some insight information.
How you guys feel about terrorism?
Open up a little bit.
Jo deon from fly with me.
Which you can find at flywithmeet.podshow.com.
heard the call.
I don't think he quite understood what I was asking for.
Maybe our emails just crossed and he hasn't even heard my show yet.
But he did send me a clip from a recent episode about the mile high clubs.
He's talking to one of the flight attendants on one of his flights that he captain.
And he walked in actually on someone having sex on the 76.
We are on the other way doing it because we could hear the park.
I've got to get to do it.
Nobody would go in.
Psycho. Oh, screw that out.
Go in.
Psycho up in an up and up in the door.
What did you see when you walked in?
Two pair of asses.
And you know, a little, a little plumped and a sweat and going on.
Yeah, you got to listen to the show to hear the rest of it.
Flywithmeet.podshow.com.
From that show, actually learned how you can open the laboratories in an aircraft.
You know, it's really simple.
You think that they might have some kind of past key or something.
But if you look at the actual sign, and this goes for the 747, I think the 400 series.
This definitely works on Virgin Airlines because I've tried it.
So you have that little sign that when someone's inside and they slide the,
the bolt to the right, which locks the door and it says occupied.
That actual, the enclosing of the occupied sign can slide left or right.
So if you want to open the door, you just slide that over to the,
well, whichever the opposite direction is of the door frame,
towards the inside of the door, and it'll pop right open.
Just a little tip for all my Charlie friends.
And if you do that, you might want to consider recording that and sending me the audio.
Business week is doing their annual poll of the,
I think they call it the best of the web is that what they call it.
Let me just take a look.
I have the link here.
I'll put that in the show.
No, it's obviously a daily source code.com.
Let me check.
Why isn't this not opening?
I don't know why they do this in September or August of September.
But apparently, daily source code has been nominated for Best Podcast.
Let me see.
Yeah, a best of the web is what it's called.
Okay.
So I'll put a link in the show notes.
Vote for me if you feel it's right.
Or vote for Vicky.
Vicky.
Richase.
Richie.
What if you want to do?
It's really weird.
Ask a ninja is also on the nomination list.
And so you've got a podcast that isn't publicly available.
You've got a video podcast and you've got a daily source code in this.
I can't remember what the other nominees were.
You can also write in your own nominee.
But I thought that was pretty interesting is that they're really mixing it up.
It's almost, you know, it's like difficult.
You know, how do you really put that all into one category?
I don't know if that's actually possible.
Yesterday we talked about the gemma in Germany and the podcast music network.
And Thomas checks in with that.
Hi, Adam.
This is Thomas from the German podcast association.
By the way, I don't like any podcast.
I don't like associations in general.
I'm kind of against it.
I don't think they do anything except create lots and lots of paperwork and notes and
wikis and stuff like that and rarely ever get anything done.
But let's see what Thomas has to say.
We are in to the discussion about gma and rights to play podcasts since October 2004.
Let me help you and the other podcasts to understand what's going on.
First, if an artist has a contract with a gma,
there's no possibility to make any exception for him or for the gma.
Whenever his song is played in public via radio, podcast, or even in the live performance,
you have to pay for it.
Second, if you, even if you have.
The new gma license for podcasts, you need also a lowence from the gbl,
which is the association of record labels or from the record label directly.
It doesn't matter what PMN do, it's a matter of how gma and gvl react.
Maybe the artist themselves should be put some pressure on the gma,
as long as gma controls the right of publicity playing songs.
They are in advantage.
We think one of the major changes should be that artists and Germany are allowed
to restrict the contract with the gma.
That means they should be able to allow PMN or similar networks
to give the podcasts the rights to play the songs.
That would be the only possibility to be on a legal and on a right side.
Thanks, bye-bye.
Hi Thomas, or of course you could put it on the pod show on the podcast,
the library network servers are based in the US.
That may technically be the way to do it.
But I just say stop chasing it.
Don't run around, don't ask people if the artist aren't.
If there is an awareness part and I think we should all make artists aware
that these performing rights organizations outside of the US
have a monopoly on who was able to collect fees or who was able to license their music
and I think that we need to continue with that awareness campaign.
But that's about it.
And just don't play.
I'm sorry.
Just don't play him if they're registered in the gma database
and you can't play him.
Don't play him.
Don't go running after all these organizations and trying and fixing it.
It's just not going to work.
It just doesn't happen that way.
I got really tired of trying to do that here in the States.
It does not work.
Or, of course, you could move over here.
Yeah, come on over here.
You can stay with me for a little while.
Just a little while.
This weekend, I'm actually leaving tomorrow Friday.
I've got a big, big flying weekend.
So I hope the weather is going to be reasonable enough, I guess.
There's hopefully no more hail and thunderstorms predicted in Holland.
Throughout the month of September, we've got a lot of reverse engineering
and backing up to do for our paperwork.
We went to New York to get our marriages, certificate copies,
which has an upper steel affixed to it to make it official.
This weekend on Saturday, we're spreading my mom's ashes.
Beautiful place that my sisters found.
Now, this is illegal, so I'm not going to tell you where it is.
But it's actually, it's a place that is called butterfly park, if you can believe it.
And so we're going to do that on Saturday.
Since we're going to do that in the afternoon, I don't want to be rushed.
I'm going to stay in Amsterdam, stay overnight and fly back on Sunday.
Which is the third of September, a date I'll always remember.
But tomorrow, so Friday, Patricia is going along and we're going to do a quick trip up and back,
because she has to get some paperwork squared away.
So it's off to get the paperwork done, then I bring her back and then Saturday,
probably mid-morning, not too early, fly over to Amsterdam for the weekend.
So I'm not quite sure what's going to happen with the show tomorrow.
But we'll weasel it in somewhere, I'm sure.
And then Saturday, third of September, as I said, it's my birthday.
42.
Now, we don't do much with birthdays in the curry cottage.
I think after a certain number.
You know, I mean, yes, sweet 16 was fantastic.
Christina's 18th will be a big deal, her 21st, and then she's on her own, man.
And then we're just done with celebrating.
Franco from Rockcast Italia has caught on.
He congratulated me a couple days early.
And he sent in something which is from the hitchhikers guide to the galaxy, a piece of audio.
And I forgot all about this, but 42 is quite an impressive number actually.
Good evening. Oh, deep thought.
Do you have them?
I'm not so for you.
Yes.
I have.
Really is one.
There really is one.
To everything, to the great question of life, the universe, and everything.
Yes.
Now you ready to give it to us?
No.
Wow.
Though I don't think you're going to like it.
It doesn't matter where we must know it.
No.
Yes, now.
All right.
Oh well.
You're really not going to like the tellers.
All right.
The answer to everything.
Yes.
Live.
42.
Yeah.
We are going to get lynched.
Yes.
There you go.
42.
Do you know something special about the number 42?
Let me know.
Voice mail number 1, 2, 0, 1, 6, 2, 5, 6, 3, 5, 7.
And here is another one of our finalists for the earthling ad challenge.
Vying for $2,000 in economic reward and huge social reward knowing that the winner will be used as the actual advertising for earthling.
10 lessons I've learned while surfing the internet number 1.
Enter your email address on some websites as an open invitation to spam.
Number 2.
Before forwarding an email about the ghost of a dead boy appearing in the theatrical film.
Three men in a baby.
Check Snopes.com first.
Number 3.
Spyware.
Then forms you that you have spyware is not very helpful.
Number 4.
The FBI will never send you an email warning about your visiting 40 illegal websites.
They'll simply bust down your door.
Number 5.
Never ever Google the Toronto-based quartet.
The barricade ladies on a computer at work.
Number 6.
Bill Gates and Microsoft are not tracking this email.
And fording it to 15 other people will not get Walt Disney signed to send you free passes to Walt Disney World.
Number 7.
There is no such thing as a national do not email registry.
Number 8.
There is no ousted prints in Bangladesh willing to share $15 million with you.
Number 10.
You think as your service provider will solve most of these problems.
Unfortunately, the remaining few will take some common sense.
I like that one.
That was pretty good.
It was a good internet lore in there.
As you probably know, this program is...
And more people are paying attention if you want to make your podcast the easy way.
Design specifically for independent audio production in real time.
Dummy proof, which is why I use it.
It works on a PC.
Then you want to check out Cast Blaster.
Hey Adam, this is Steve of the student to be the ardent octopus cast.
I think we're going to call it.
It hasn't happened yet.
But I'll tell you why.
I just wanted to mention to you that Cali Lewis is unbelievable.
And you did a great little interview about Cast Blaster.
Me and some friends have been trying to put a podcast together.
Basically, our lives are hectic and busy.
We're pulled in 9,000 directions at once.
So I decided to go ahead and take the initiatives and put it all together and just have them contribute
the content because that might be one way to get it done.
And I wanted you to know that I know that you're a doer.
And you get things done.
And I don't know that I necessarily am.
But I really want to be.
And you inspire a person in that direction.
So look for our podcast soon because we are going to do it.
We're not going to stop until it's done.
We're going to call you back unless you know that the ardent octopus podcast is available for
subscription, download, whatever.
And enjoyment.
Holder.
Have a great day.
Alright man.
Thank you very much.
Looking forward to it.
Some of your promo when you're all new.
Long for today.
It's another one of those awesome artists who have jumped onto the pod safe music revolution.
You may know him if you're 42.
He's to play with Aaron Clapton.
John mail him his blues breakers.
This is with you on Charlie.
No body.
Never let me like you do.
Understand me like you do.
I'm shit my ass.
I'm happy that some tears will you.
You're loving.
Makes me feel complete.
With your loving.
No one can copy.
You got to need ways.
I'm constantly amazed with you.
I love you.
And I'm trying to treat you right.
Yes, honey.
I'll be your comfort in the night.
You make me sleep.
I'll do most of the thing for you.
I love you.
No body.
It's a way to erase.
Never take your place.
No body.
I want to share some fun with you.
I love you.