This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 362, the hip hop edition.
Hmm.
I like my Charlie's served up.
GoDaddy?
Don't come.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I guess it's Adam Curry.
But I got 700 messages for you from friends who tried to kill you.
Interstended aircraft, back to them.
All the rest that we can't so some kind of the scam that prevails in my head.
The form of spares.
And I'm the one she's so lucky that she's got $20 million that she has to protect.
She can't wait.
And we're in a cruciated time to answer.
And all she needs is my hang.
Number through the transfers shirt.
Oh yeah, that sounds total to the gym.
And hit my ATM cardication idiot.
I can't believe that people offer this shit.
It really sucks to last year.
This little correct made a hundred million bucks.
Look, I'm on the free vacation.
To the white hole in you.
It's my credit card number to verify.
Well, I was just quite fed it for you right now.
But right after hell, he decided this time we'll allow.
True interest rates are red and all time low.
I'm no financial genius for one thing.
I know I'm better off getting money from my zero mom.
Then from sketchy chick.
Ty just give me his VAM,
so you can see.
What the reason, I'm just sore.
Some my eyes grow in vices.
Or these people think that he's so much my nag.
The heroine is in larger, something to come
With a battery charger, here's a two-for-one offer
I don't know about you, but what the hell am I supposed to do with you?
Here's another chick who wants to meet me online
For a one-on-chat, just twelve ninety-nine
She included a butcher, as her name is Barney before that price
We could chat with her written a red army
Like a boy from home, I can get rich quit
I can buy stupid herbs like that, I'll never get sick
And if I get quick, I'll get a paper or something that'll show me how to buy men
So can't I doubt for nothing?
It's amazing that these folks are so concerned about my health considering when I had a flat
I don't want stop to help you, but I can think for myself
And I'm not falling for squad, whether they can get me 3k, 4 or not
Space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space,
space, space, space, spaces, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space, space
The following is a true story. Only the bandwidth has been changed to protect my quota.
That was good on earth, so why I'm going to keep it see if I can make it work?
I want to travel to the future and visit Captain Kirk, so until he gets some money that I know I can trust,
he can rot in 2000, whatever, like the rest of the bus.
Okay, let's see. I've got a message from my mother, my cousin, Dave and Spam.
Spam, my sister, Tracy, and Spam? Spam Spam, his spanПam looks cute, so it's litter and Spam?
Spam Spam Spam, Spam Spam Spam, Oh look, somebody bought an album.
Spam Spam Spam, Spam Spam Spam Spam Spam Spam Spam, Spam Spam Spam Spam Spam Spam Spam Spam Spam Spam Spam Spam Swamp Spam Spam.
-"Spend Теперь upfront, spent spent spent spends spent spend spends spends spent spent spent spoil
smell.
skateboardable smell!"
Spout time somewhat upgraded at Hunts, sudden death from the Podsafe music network,
and spam they are from New Jersey, New United States, you can find it in music.vodshow.com.
More hip hop on the way.
I'm of a different variety which, you'll just have to stay tuned for, it is Wednesday,
everybody.
It's a special day.
Today, we're going to be testing our golden ticket enterprise contest
challenge systemology architecture or something like that. So that means that
you might not even be hearing the show. Stuff might have already broken. Who knows this so many
different things that could go wrong with this home in a second. I'm still adjusting all
the knobs here, getting everything all straightened up. I'm going to try and keep it
relatively short today because all kinds of stuff going on here at the cottage. Remember
we're leaving on Friday for vacation going to Portugal and just getting there is
being turning out to be quite a trip by itself. You know, we were able to get
lodging. We were able to get some flights, but the flights don't actually originate
from Gatwick. So I'm trying to arrange a aircraft that will support the three of us
and our two large banks. I don't know if that's going to work. We might turn out
just driving to the nearest airport. So as I said, lots of stuff to plan and
and to get prepared for and that's all home. And it's just much to do. It's
going to be very hard for me to switch off. Let me tell you 10 days. It's going to be
beautiful though in the in the Algarve in Portugal. I haven't checked the weather
report, but hopefully it's a little better than here in the UK. Although it's not
cold. It's like 12 13 degrees. So it's nice. It's kind of grayish outside. No blue
skies. No no son. No win for that matter either. But we've got a full Charlie lined
up for you with some interesting things. And although I don't have a
metro sexual moment keyed up for you because I'm not going to be able to do it today,
I did not want to withhold this wonderful piece of feedback for you or from you. Hi,
this is Carrie Anne from the class on laptop.com. And this is airdry. Airdry has a problem.
I have a problem with Adam Curry. You seem to think about him a lot, airdry. I think about
him a lot. And Adam, it hasn't gotten any better this week when you started talking about
your never regions. You need to stop talking about those. It's driving me crazy like I can't
sleep. Yeah. It's interfering with the work. It's interfering with everything, really.
Thank you, Adam. Lip gloss. Lip gloss and laptop.com. There you go. It's a pretty good show.
I've been trying to get them signed to the Pod Show podcast network. I don't know if
we's connected yet or where we are in the process because Richard Bruer Hay takes care of all that.
That's the lime. The limey fellow you might speak to on the phone.
And yesterday, it started probably around 11 o'clock. I started getting messages and comments on
Curry.com and all kinds of trackbacks and pingbacks and flatbacks and Apple Jax.
About this show called Keith and the Girl. Keith and the Girl are a podcast that
definitely have had my eye on for a while. They've been podcasting for quite a while now. I think
they're close to, well, no, I know exactly. They have 247 or I guess today 2408 episodes.
Never really been able to enter into a dialogue with them. Although we just kind of started an email
conversation. I only have one email address forum and only got one reply and just in the past
a week or so, actually. Now, before we could continue that dialogue at all,
someone apparently sent them a Pod Show contract. Now, this can only be from a handful of people.
So, it's not that hard to trace back. But apparently someone who decided not to sign with Pod
sent a contract that was meant for them to Keith and the Girl. And Keith and the Girl
did something really amazing. They read entire portions of the contract, including all the
legalese on their show and commented on it. And although I was surprised that anyone would do this,
I was completely blown away by the entertainment value of this. It's, I wish all my contract
readings were like that where you could have just laughed at it and have fun and joke around.
And you can imagine that there's all kinds of calls now in the Pottersphere and the
Bloggersphere and Pod Show. What is your response to this? Well, you can imagine this was
this kind of, you can imagine that this was like, whoa, what's going on here?
For two at a sleeve, Michael Butler, the Rock and Roll Geek had his recording gear at Pod Show HQ
when the shit hit the fan. And now for another exciting episode of the Pod Show evil contracts.
Boy, I could use a beer, but it's almost midnight and I still have to get 10 more unsuspecting
podcasts that's the sign of way their souls before I can go home. Oh, no. Richard,
Adam and Ron once you in the chamber. In the chamber? And you better hurry up, I don't think
they're in a good mood. Who is it? It's me, boss. Enter. Stay right there. Listen, Bill,
get that Pod Show content on the top 10 list or you'll never release a Vista. What is it, Rosie?
I have Richard for you. Richard, Ron and I have been reviewing your work and we're wondering if you
are really dedicated to Pod Show. Why, boss? Well, your signings are beneath quota this month.
I'm doing everything I can. We sign hundreds of shows. It's not enough.
Adam's right. We need big shows. We need big stars. How about,
how about, what's his name and that chick? Why am I just signed them?
Boss, I think you mean Keith and the girl. We haven't signed them because they hate us. Have you heard
their latest show? They spend the entire time crashing us. How could they hate us? We are Pod Show.
Let me hear that show. Here, boss, put on these phones.
Bist weekend.
I don't know, man. I think they like us. They think we suck. They say we are evil and they say we're
the devil. I don't know. I think this shows funny. Maybe they don't understand us. Anyway,
I like the girl. Adam, maybe we can break them up. How about Adam and the girl?
Think you'll go for it? Yeah, like the sound of that. Adam and the girl.
Sounds good. I don't think that's a good idea. They hate us.
H mate. They just don't understand us. Have we ever spoken with them?
No, really. We've tried. Did they know any of us? No, really. They just slam the contract and slam
us all the time. So, with no real reason, no real communication. They just make their own opinions
and pull them out of their asses. Well, yes. And they build their audience by putting down Pod Show
and other podcasts. Yes. We promote them on our site. We promote them in our shows. Yep.
And for this, they stab us in the back. Yes, again. These are my kind of people. Are they
former entertainment industry executives? No, they're comedians. All same difference. What do you think,
Adam? Let me get this straight. They don't know us. They haven't worked with us. We promote them.
They trash us. Then they think other people are dumb enough to work with us if we own everything
and give them nothing. I guess so. Let's get them. If they're making a living by
trashing us, the least they can do is come and talk to us. Right, Adam. Rosie. Send a limo.
They're in New York. Okay. Send the jet. We don't own a jet. Okay. Call our legal department.
We don't have a legal department. No, legal department. Which asshole wrote this contract?
You did bust a little. Oh. Well, what's the problem? They think we sign people up for life.
Own everything and don't make anyone any money. And your point is, they think we're like a
record label. Well, in that case, they're idiots. I want them. Yeah. Let's get a Richard.
What should I do? Bring them to San Francisco. Let's talk to him directly. They'll never come.
In that case, maybe they are the devil. Maybe they want to keep podcasting for themselves.
Yeah, podcasting for themselves. Maybe they're jealous of Dean and Drew. Don't entrue us.
Dean, Don, whatever. Just get them. Bring us, Keith and the girl. Okay, boss. I'm on it.
Ryan, Mr. Johnson, line one. Tell them to hold. Get Keith and the chicken on the line.
Yeah. And Rosie? Yeah, boss. Rimshot, please.
Keith, Camda, your insightful review of our business and console support are truly innovative.
Adam myself and our entire family would like to invite you to come out to San Francisco. We'd
like to make you an offer. You can't refuse. Richard will be in touch. Great.
Hey, we're a bunch of actors, huh?
Thanks to Michael, Rosie, Richard, Ron, the Pacho players.
And Marc Yoshimara, an MCoff for the late night work, trying to get that all together the last minute.
All right. There you go. The offer does stand, though. And it's for our nickel, no problem.
You're still tuned to the Daily Source code. Greetings, Mr. Curry. To you and to all the
residents of the Delta Sierra Charlie Nation. I'm very pleased to inform you that you're site,
Curry.com, has been selected to be linked from the big giant button on March 29, 2006.
So you're probably asking, what does this mean? Well, it means that anyone who goes to big
giantbutton.com on March 29th and presses the biggest button on the internet will be sent immediately
to your site. Why your site? Every day we link the big giant button to something we like.
And Adam, we like you. I hope you and some of your listeners will check out big giantbutton.com.
Starting March 27th, we'll be linking to a new site every single day.
Visit the big giantbutton. Press it and see what happens. Take care, Adam, and keep up
the great work with your podcast and with Pacho. Yeah, so I'm just realizing I'm a total
torque. I should have played that one yesterday. Now I'm not getting the benefits of you going to
the big giantbutton. I was going to say tap that button for me, baby. Damn. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay,
here pop on the way and a couple other interesting promos for you. And something that I promised
you today, a brand new experiment. Hey, Adam, it's Ilya Koja of here. I want to if you're
Russian listeners. I know I'm not a chick, so you won't enjoy my accent that much, but anyway,
I just listened to Charlie 361. It took me three times to listen to that. He said,
I know I'm not a chick, so you make a lot of listen to me. And two things popped into my mind.
First of all, the golden ticket. Actually, it is possible to find it without listening to every
episode. Basically, it took a pair of the file sizes. Or if you're listening to some of
tech savvy, they can compare the Czech sounds. And unfortunately, and I'm defying Czech
some of a DSE with a golden ticket, we'll never be the same as DSE without it. Second is
more like a question about the pot to more besides you mentioned earlier. But the way I have nothing
to do with it, I'm just someone who likes to question things out here. I don't know how it works,
but what if instead of inserting the ad directly into the DSE file, they inserted to the playlist,
you see what I mean? Just like we now, or your iTunes party shuffle, they will not modify any
of the three, they just play an MP3 ad and then a podcast. Well, it will be legal. For example,
if users hit a play on an empty playlist, it will still play an ad because it's already there,
but fault in the application. Just some food for thoughts. Anyway, great shows and those video
and yeah, yeah, those video and yeah. And I really, I played the whole comment. First, I love
it when just listeners check in, you know, that's so cool. We got lots of podcasts with checking
a bit listeners. I really love hearing from listeners who aren't podcasting yet or necessarily.
Regarding the pod to mob, so they definitely got the, they got, they got my message at least.
I sent them an email to, they did not respond to that. So not only are they're not running ads
in front of my show, I've been removed from the entire directory and the show doesn't exist.
And I think the debate is, it's pretty good. There's an ongoing conversation. You can
catch some of that at curie.com and it's a tech and rotty probably is picked up on it by now.
And I think that those guys just made an honest mistake. That's what I truly believe.
Now, back to the golden ticket. So here is the concept. We have this technology we've developed
called D-Gap, dynamically generated asset placement. And what this enabled, actually you've probably
you've already witnessed it. If you're listening to the show, when I started recording,
all I do is I say, you know, Delta shared Charlie 362 and, you know, and that's enough.
But when you hear the show, you hear things like a 10-second tag, promoting our GoDaddy,
one message many voices campaign, which points to this show or whatever show you're listening to.
And it alerts you to the fact that there's something coming up in a code that you want to
take advantage of to get some great discounts. And the cool thing about it is we have podcasters
creating their own messaging for their own audiences. Okay, that's another conversation.
But with this technology, we can do a whole bunch of interesting things. So the concept for the golden
ticket, I mean, the golden ticket is very simple. For one of the downloads of this Charlie,
of this show only, not of the archives, only for this show. And one time only, if all goes
according to plan, I know Andrew Grummit is sitting there with a moist ass, hoping that all goes well
because you're not been working on this. He's in all the programming and all the scheduling and
all the stuff and got it all set up and we did a test yesterday and it worked. But this should be
one download of this particular daily source code podcast, which will contain a special audio
message with a way for the recipient of that to contact me with the special phrase, the phrase
that pays everybody. And if they do contact me with the correct phrase, they will win the key
span audio video dock for the iPod plus the audio video RF remote courtesy of keyspan and
our very own Sam Levin who scammed that for this test. Now, this is not a contest, this is a test,
it's beta, it's completely beta. So anything could happen, it could break 8 million people could win.
I've only got one key span dock if it all blows up and we'll just have to call it a wash, okay?
But I think it will actually work. Now, what's going to happen? I just have to pay attention to the
time here. Let me see. I've got to jot down this time, hold on a second. So,
19 minutes and 35 seconds into the show. If you heard nothing different than you, you didn't win.
One of you's heard a special message, which is inserted in that split second at 19 minutes and 35 seconds.
Those of you listening to us on a serious star's 102, sorry, this doesn't work for you,
but you could still go home, download this podcast from dailysourcecode.com.
Better get subscribed to it. There's all kinds of information about how you can subscribe to podcast
and get them automatically. So, you still, yeah, I've once got a chance.
And in fact, what could happen and this would be kind of funky is I could even download my own show
and I could win the prize, which of course would mean that we have to repurpose it. So anyway,
hopefully everything will go okay. And as our Russian comrade pointed out there, yes, there are many,
we've taken a lot of the spoofing and scamming things into account. But yeah, in general,
there's no real good way to hide the winning ticket. Of course, if it's just an open contest,
if you're a registered listener, well, that would be a whole different story and that would
probably work very, very well. And in the future, we can do this across multiple podcasts.
And I think we can have a lot of fun with it. So tomorrow, hopefully, we'll have a winner
and we'll know if our test was successful or not. Oh, hello Adam, it's Cali from Geek Briefman.
I want to touch your penis. All right, just kidding, it's magic. I just had to say something to get
you to play my goddamn prom, not prom or comment, because you never play my shit anymore Adams
Curry and people complain, oh, fuck, never mind. Listen, I heard you're having this golden ticket
contest, which I think is a phenomenal idea. So phenomenal, in fact, that I'm having a similar
contest on yeast radio. Unfortunately, however, for your audience, it's already finished.
But the good news is, Adams Curry, you won. I'm having a very similar contest. It's called the
Golden Shower contest. And you, one, Adams Curry, and I'm going to take a piss on you. I'm
going to pee on your face. Do you believe anything is possible? We do. Where are flink?
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers. We're Earthlink.
We believe your personal information should be just that, personal. And we believe your
internet should be a friend, not a foe. We're Earthlink. Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net
and discover what our internet experts can do for you, Earthlink. We revolve around you.
Hi, Adam. This is John from Seattle, Washington, USA. You recently expressed a wish for listeners,
not just podcasters to send you audio comments. So, here you go. I'm a relatively new listener,
and I've been hooked since the first show I listened to several weeks ago.
Until then, I had heard about podcasts, but like many people, really didn't pay much attention to them.
Then a week ago, or so, I got it in my head that an internet radio show would be a fun hobby
and began researching. Well, I quickly learned that my basic idea for a show was way out of my
reach due to licensing fees from me as a coasting fees, et cetera, you know, the story.
So, when a friend reminded me of podcasts, I started researching and of course, your name came up all
over the internet. I remembered your name from my formative years as a teenager watching MTV in the 80s.
Yeah, I know, scary, isn't it? And I just had to get an aggregator and check out your show.
I was hooked. I'm currently touring with the idea of doing a podcast of my own,
but having a difficult time figuring out the things that I'm passionate enough about,
to do a show on. So, for now, I am exploring the world of podcasts as a listener
and waiting for them used to strike. I figure I should keep this short in case you decide to
air this. I love the Charlie, and I look forward to many more. I have some more questions and comments
to send you about podcasting and other topics mentioned on the Charlie. But I'll save those for another
time. I hope you enjoyed this audio comment. You know, someone should really coin a name for these things,
like, podment or audio meant audio comment. It's just mental, blah. Anyway, I look forward to
sending you more. Talk for now. And bye everybody on the saddle. Bye.
Those of you still with us on the podcast. Thank you very much for hanging out. Just a couple more
things before we get out of here. Probably at the end of each episode, although no one was
really commented on it. You've heard this, uh, this jingle. So, who is the man behind the code?
Who is the illustrious cast blaster Mike? Well, it took a priest to figure it out.
Cast blaster Mike needed some time alone. He needed focus and concentration for his programming.
So he rented a cottage in the middle of the woods. When I, uh, has this called things to program,
I usually retire to the woods and so I can fully concentrate. Finally, people would leave him alone
so he could work on cast blaster. Hey, Mike. I heard you were camping out here in the neighborhood
of where I live. So I thought I would say hello. So we sat down and talked and talked about Adam Curry
and his own special way of podcasting. You know, when when Patricia walks in with a couple of
tea, he immediately, you know, switches on a second microphone. He says, just sit down and we'll talk a
little bit and improvise. He just goes to make a cup of coffee. Yeah, he just wants to see. I'm just
going to walk away. I'll be back. It comes back here, like, but do you, do you find that
of the way? No, no, no. It's funny. About the first idea for cast blaster. One part guess I will never
forget is that he was to the BBC in London and on his way back to the cottage. He made his show
in his car. In the car. Yeah. But he did that with, I think, a CD player, an MP3 recorder. I
think the I River and a separate mic and all kind of wires and it wasn't mess. And really difficult.
And very dangerous. Every day you scroll. Yeah. I thought, well, if he takes a laptop with him
and a little program, it should be a lot easier. So I wrote what later would be called cast blaster.
Within an hour I had to reply like, this is what we need. About the future of podcasting and the
pot show delivery network. I listened to recently to an interview with Adam and with Ron Bloom on
podcast for one while and they were talking about their overall vision. It was the very first time
that I really started to grasp this whole idea of it's not just about some kind of way to commercially
link podcasting to advertisers. Way bigger than that. It's creating some kind of platform
that helps podcasters create an audience and gather an audience. And I'll start it out as a
technical solution to a problem. And it has turned into a social thing. If you want to join us in
mic's cottage and hear more, listen to the latest episodes of the Daily Breakfast at daily Breakfast.com.
The illustrious father, Roderick. Yeah. So if you want to know the Genesis of cast blaster and how
products like that come to life, that was a complete internet enterprise really how that worked.
And it's a beautiful story. I realize the problem will contain a lot about me. But that's
really the Genesis of cast blaster. It's cool to hear what cast blaster class need pop flessy.
Cast blaster mic is all about. Okay, a couple things to wrap it up. First of all, sad news. Very,
very sad news. One of my favorite UK podcast, although not really a UK podcast. But that I listened to,
to learn about British culture was the I miss blighty podcast. It shut down, which really sucks.
The host of the show works for broadcast. I can't say too much about it. Nor does he on this final
episode. But the host of the show works for broadcast organization and they took issue with his podcast.
And so I guess they've affected, he's shutting down before they shut him down. I believe. And I just
wanted to say, I'm really going to miss you, dude, because all those little Angloisms that you would
talk about, they're very helpful for me to understand the culture here. And it's funny how that
works. You know, when someone is away from the country and they talk about the country, they really
hit on a lot of topics that are often overlooked just in conversation in the country itself. So sad
day for that. Regarding the Gmail issue that I've been having some good news there, I received a
I received a Gmail from Danny, he says Google has a solution coming up for the issue. That's basically
of my drive filling up completely or my space filling up on Gmail. The solutions for business
users currently, I'm in a beta test with Google, whereby I modified my domain name's MX records. That's
basically, I remember I told you it's so good to have a domain name. Get yours now at godaddy.com
because you can change your MX records to have any email service work with your own domain name.
Use code DSC one and get some kind of groovy discount. So he pointed those towards Google servers once
Google verified the ownership he's now able to use the Google UI to read his own domain mail.
Where of course you can have terabytes of space if you want to. Of course this only helps
folks with a domain, but doesn't include support for hosted accounts such as GoDaddy. There you go.
Fantastic. So I'm very happy about that because I think that is indeed
the solution. I'm not quite sure how they how they index it though. I guess they have to have access to your
no wait a minute. Well, I don't know. We'll find out. But because if you point your MX records somewhere else,
then the files are going to the email is going to go somewhere else. Anyway, so I suppose the way it
works is you get the Google user interface, which I like so much. It better have the search in there.
If it doesn't have the search in it, I mean, this search-based email really, really works for me.
You know, whenever I say, oh, I remember there's some email I was supposed to look at something,
you know, you can enter just a couple of keywords and usually you'll find it on the first hit.
Google Gmail fantastic for that. But I would like to be able to utilize my own disk space. So if that's possible,
that'll be fantastic. One more here from Ellie Renner. Comment or mention that maybe you could have Uncle
Jesse. Wait, did someone say Uncle Jesse? Yeah, I don't know if he died. He's coming off. He's kind of
sued on. He's a Justin stuff. He's a sad-lap repair man coming after you. Sad-lap repair man,
what's he gonna do? He'll fit your misconceptions and answer questions too.
Nothing in the universe and he can't do for you. Sad-lap repair man.
Sad-lap repair man. Yeah.
So a comment or mention that maybe you could have Uncle Jesse come up with a best of show
for days that you're on a way on vacation. Along lines of user-generated content.
In fact, Ellie says, why not let your listeners do it. Just give us a few guidelines,
length, for example. And then sit back and wait. As your talented audience cobbles together,
their favorite moments from the Delta Sierra Charlie, you would still have full editorial control.
But hey, sounds like a win-win to me. Well, what do I think? Ellie from, what do you
did? I'm sorry. It's WTFWJD.com. Nice. I think that's an excellent idea.
And we should calm the box. Best of Charlie's the box. So what would I need? Let me get the trusty
blackberry here. Let me look at the calendar. Oh, I missed a call already. Okay. Shit, there was a
charter plane call. Okay. Let me see. So I'm gone from the, so I need,
this April right three, one, two, three, so I need five. I'd only need seven shows
because although we return on the 10th, we're going to, it'll be actually the 11th before
back in the cottage. Yeah. So I would need seven shows. Can we do seven shows? That will be
completely awesome. Let's, you know, the best way to cut down the work for PDAB is if you can
actually make him 24 minutes and 30 seconds with the best of bits. I think that would be fantastic.
I can't give PDAB any more work to edit stuff together. But yeah, if you want to create a show
and please don't email it to me, put it up on a server so we can grab it and then we'll give you
full credit for putting the box together. That would be fantastic. I would love it. It'd be great
for the satellite folks, too. So please, yes, fantastic idea. And finally, yesterday I played a promo
for the Alpha Omega podcast, complete hip hop, received an email today from Otis. It says,
A to the D to the A M U to Man. Thanks for the shout out. A lot of you know, I will hit you back
this week and let you know what's going on. The clubs in Seattle in Portland as for the military
backgrounds. I was in Berlin in 89 when the wall came down and a lot of he was in West Germany in 1990.
We were in the same unit in Fort Lewis, Washington. And here's a hip hop song. We downloaded from
music.podshow.com. The song is called Blow Your Whistle is the Remix by Azemoff. So, that's a recommendation,
Like a jackhammer when I move to your dead toe
Flip it, flip it, rinse the crossbow, rinse it
Showing girl shirts with a wanna gun pistol
What a really wild style, my wild man's got a cool light
People got the round, you gon' rock with y'all again
Lookin' the playin' the ball, let me show you
Cause that's the stuff, that's my word
We're gonna show you how we get down when the dirty
You heard, you when it comes to the bitches
What I DJ bringin' the ain't y'all up the hall
Like DJ singin' the matter to stir, I'm sayin'
You gon' make you dead, it's just rock to the rhythm
Shake you outta your pants, you didn't say it now
Ain't no need for you to sit down, people get like
You know that this town, you do it all the time
That's part of the plan, it's about this, y'all all over the jam
When the beat came, y'all know it's the remix
We can get live, it's gon' leave, it's the mistake
When the end, you makes you get a let you know
When I'm a whistle, many whistle, home, oil, let's go
Go away, go away, go away, go away
Oh, damn it, I'm smashin' back with smashin' flash
Like a shit, I'm blastin' loads with fries
I'm faking flake, get a crackin' in face, playin' shake like a false
Get a hit, hide a scotch, spray, get it raw
While you get it on tape, I'ma take my ass, break it my life
I'm sorry, the auditory on this motion
Like as his ass, he need low shit
So it's forget, war will force for five minutes
Live to the far back, get a scotch, pop, pop
Now he's still flyin', he's like a B boy
But saw hands in the sky, hands throw the party, pop
Swallow like one of the highs, on your mighty sides
Every little world you turn before, where you live
It's real, it's real, it's real, it's real
And I need a hollow back for you
Now I'm in the go, go
Oh, yo whistle, and blow, yo whistle, just blow, yo whistle
Here we go, whistle, and blow, yo whistle
Just blow, yo whistle, just blow, yo whistle
Just blow, yo whistle, and blow, yo whistle
Just blow, yo whistle
As I'm all fucking the jammers, not an issue
These suckers and transplants, they all on a fish show
The don'tness rockin' every style on the menu
It's to get the team keepin' in line
And then if you've been, you'll never use WW
We rockin' spot with 100 mags of my legs
And show the shot right on 100 mags
Like get live in your spot, y'all come
People checkin' the rhyme, they love it all the time
All the time, all the time, I mean to get me to cook it
I was, yeah, I can flip a record
Who's my Billy Cyrus?
It's a race, he's out of my brain, furnace, I burn
But I want to recharge him, blow, hot, follow
So, and we're at the end of this, I'll probably sample this
To cook it rockin' that fat, the record's fine
And he may have got beats for miles
And then ain't your boy, it's therapy for flys down
The car imposes it for get away
You catch this mega-hike tonight
He's got co-hatty so we can skate on my joke
Cooler than I fan fooler with the man
When like we need to get the football ball go band with a more horse
Cause you know base that you have, for the people that I see
Many stars as grand
But like low on heel, they mess around with triads
My soul purpose and my rage is to get you empty
That's how you can jump
You get the ready to throw the rules
To the play, man, it wasn't my fault
This data, adrenaline rushes your late
And you scold that heights
Like you might go mix with red balls
It's the fist to keep the bugs
Waste slapping your bones
Square balls
I'm not an exclusive club that dunks to my
Be the music that's gonna let them know the guy
Make me forget your worries of the show
Anyone I know the lad
Still take it to the bed
There's y'all many people
It might move on the head
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Let's go, go, go
Yo whistle damn flow
Yo whistle just blow your whistle
Oh, you whistle damn blow
Yo whistle damn blow
Yo whistle just blow your whistle
Yo whistle down blow
When you eat some free steamed slice and dowter to the tissue
Any six of these warm?
traveled
Basics changes life and downs
They teach you
Yeah, just blow your whistle.
Thank you guys for giving me just an ounce of street cred.
We're going to find that on the pot-save music networks.
Cool to hear the hip hop on music.co.com.
I want to know how this would sound on the club, man.
Shoot.
Someone please play the club.
Let me know what people think.
I think it's highly sensible.
And that's it for the Charlie Ford today.
Again tomorrow, we'll find out if the Golden Ticket worked.
And I'll see you back here.
I'll be able to do a Friday show as well.
And then it's on vacation.
I'm so incredibly ready.
Thanks for your staying subscribed.
Adamacard.com for your feedback.
DailySourceCo.com for the latest episodes of the show.
And curry.com for your comments.
Take care, everybody.
Get this podcast.
And we're great ones.
Like it.
On the high performance podcast.
Delivery Network.
From Podgeau.
And limelight networks.
I love it.