For the first time ever, the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr. in one action-packed DVD collection,
own all 27 episodes, the cult hit, including all new interviews with Carlton Koo.
First thing that Brisco did that impressed us was, we're not only to come in and really read the dialogue well as an actor,
but he also did a standing flip in our office.
You've flipped too for Brisco County!
If you like the kind of TV you can't get on TV, get your copy of the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr.
Available now on DVD!
Hey, this is PD Love, and you're listening to the Daily Source Code 478 for Fubar Friday, the 13th.
Kind of scary.
This episode may contain some mature and well-reather strange material, something like this.
Pump that, that side, that bad boy up and down, you pump it, you pump it, you pump it, you pump it, and then all of a sudden it becomes frothy.
Pour a little bit in, then the coffee, and then the rest, and it's good.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding, it's a matter of curry.
You pump it, you pump it, and then all of a sudden it becomes frothy.
Pour a little bit in, then the coffee, and then the rest, then it's good.
Someone slipped a note right in my pocket, said what's going on with you.
Nothing out the ordinary, I say, except I'm feeling kind of new.
Someone picked my heart up off the floor, so why should I keep quiet anymore?
Because I've been tied to a treat for as long as I'm out.
When you said it free, now I'm ready to go, and I won't be alone anymore.
I finally got a place, got my food in the door, my food in your door, oh.
Someone said you crazy, your delusion, oh.
I can do all that, it's to the cool American likes, simple minded thoughts under your head.
But there's not a single country of the world that could say it any better.
I'm a beautiful girl, has that been tied to a treat for as long as I'm out.
When you said me free, now I'm ready to go, and I won't be alone anymore.
I finally got a place, got my food in the door, my food in your door, oh.
And it's so good to be back home, don't know why I never go.
I don't feel like I can do time.
So tell me what you've got under control.
It's so hard to have a feeling that I'm not let alone, no.
So please indulge me for a little longer, don't worry, we're almost to the end of the song.
Because I've been tied to a treat for as long as I'm out.
When you said me free, now I'm ready to go, I'm ready to go, I'm ready to go,
it's so long to be holding a fool, I know it's good enough if it wasn't for me.
And I won't be alone anymore, I'm finally got a place, got my food in the door,
my food in the door, oh.
We're got our food in the door, we're gonna ask you.
The Jeff Smith, the one and only official imaging consultant of the daily source code,
brand new song from Jeff, I got my foot in the door, and did he see I got my footing your
door at some point? Sound like a really bad German porn movie.
Hey everybody, how you doing coming to you from a cloudy northern California today?
It is the daily source code, my head is, as you can tell, completely clogged up,
but I'm feeling a little bit better, I'd actually last night, I had some work to do, so I couldn't
get into bed until, was about quarter to eleven, which is a little bit late for me, because
you don't like to get up at five thirty to get the show cranking for you, get it out before the
satellite window closes. And I'd actually reset my alarm to six thirty, I said to myself,
I'm not deserve an extra hour, it's fucking Friday, I need it. I welcome at five fifteen,
you know, no difference, it's like, every since I did that year-long morning show three
years ago, I just can't sleep longer, it just doesn't work anymore. It is Friday the 13th,
of course, traditionally, that's a day of bad luck. I've never had, can I knock on some wood here?
There we go, knock on some wood. I've never had any bad luck on Friday the 13th,
and I hope you have a very lucky Friday the 13th, and let's see, it's I'm looking forward to the
weekend, because I really, really, really got to regain some strength, traveling to New York,
Sunday, and then we have meetings Monday, and Tuesday, I am on a panel at, it's an agency in New York,
called OMD. Now, no, no, not related to orchestral maneuvers in the dark, but they're doing a
huge, I think you call it a symposium, really, so it's for advertisers, advertising agencies,
buying media buying companies, and I think I'm on a panel with one of the YouTube guys,
so that should be very interesting, and actually I should see if I could get that recorded,
if I can share that with you, and then Tuesday night, back to San Fran, because we got stuff to do
here, and well, in a week from now, then I'll be going home. I must say, it's always that
first weekend when you think, it's time for the weekend, what am I going to do with the girls
and wait a minute, they're not here, but of course Patricia's doing just great, her parents are
over in my absence, which is, that really works out well. I love her parents, you know that,
right, my in-laws are great, but they do get a little, um, they're a little busy.
If you got in laws, you know what I mean, but it's great so she can spend a lot of time with them,
focus all of her attention on them, oh, man, they're over it. They're like 81, 82 now,
so God bless them. Hope she enjoys it. What's that?
Hey, are you doing girl? Are. Hey baby.
It's going on. My tea here. I hope you won't mind. I let myself in.
No, it's okay, and, you know, that's okay. I mean, come on. I mean, bro. Hello D. S. C. People,
what's going on? I think, they're happy to see you, Amy. All right. Mom and I choose
everybody's dying to know yeah okay what do you think nice let's give it a little squeeze
here hey me that's fantastic I love it it's me too I'm excited I think it looks great
thank you you're actually starting to fill out the room for those jeans you know
could do that very good that could do better I think does it feel nice
you get lots of compliments well of course it could look better so that brings us to
today yeah what this early this early oh I know how you are about incho so you play
the intro okay all right ready let me go okay ladies and gentlemen it's
exercise this is the one and only Amy Mac saving out of the
break it back bring it back baby okay now we're ready okay today we're starting
to push up position all right hands up your shoulders all right yeah just like that
okay all right on your toes good okay now lift your right leg up and then bring
your right knee to your chest all the way up and then back out and down okay
all right good we're going to eight on each side eight ready yeah one eight good nice and
slow yeah seven seven six hold on don't let that head fall yeah four yeah three you
missed five two don't don't don't let you back drop one I'm going to hold the
all right good love side okay other side here we go eight ready yes okay eight seven I'm
breathing yeah sorry for God six yeah five people those toes yes four three oh it's
burning yeah yeah excellent let's make one all right that's it so early I thought I would go
easy on you all thank you baby I really need that so now that I'm here what's
for breakfast you want me to cook some more are you going to do something I can finish
the show if you want to get breakfast started why don't I do the show you do breakfast
all right fine I'll go make breakfast you finish the show okay all right I have to warn
you though I can't cook so this is gonna be pretty a beautiful girl like you can't cook
all right well at least give me a good plug after I leave now all right everybody have a
great weekend until next time ladies and gentlemen the one and only Amy Mack
assurizing my ass back to health let me see how there's a plug I got to give Amy here thanks
Amy if you're going to egg and bacon to the yeah exactly right there let me see there was a
plug I wanted to give for Amy here hold on a second oh well that's messed up the hell is this I'm
using that Google notebook thing oh this is crappy hold on a second why isn't that working
oh man I really got to me Amy Mack let me see what do we have do we have it here yeah okay
so fitness attack fitness dot pod show dot com that's Amy's a regular podcast and on the 24th
which is what uh 10 days from now 11 days from now ascercise dot pod show dot com launches
and starts over a day one and also coming in November fitness attack on espanol with the diva
matablu um diamarta excellent good show is coming here all right now man that really
Amy every single time you you visit me on a Thursday or Friday it really it really gets pretty
complicated to breathe after a while hey Adam David at Belita will be here in New York City that
could term in from central park just a couple of things I wanted to give you a shout uh oh
from over here in New York City uh I'm the guy that wrote Tom Cruise scares me and the religion song
and uh mom is just don't let your babies who can go and play that whenever you feel like it it's
got a life expectancy of a few weeks but a couple of things listen I just uploaded the religion song
to the pod safe network so if anybody wants that song it's available there um I'm amazed at the
warm reception that song is getting I thought for sure people gonna come after me for that one but
it's uh it's up there on pod safe and um mom is don't let your babies I made available for a
free download at thatcatarmand.com and uh and uh it's also on my podcast I love the company okay
up I just wanted to give you a shout cuz um I was doing what I do in central park you know for a
few thousand people and uh and uh you know kind of let people know about the daily source code
and uh man I'm making you a star it's central park a few of my closest friends want to say something
hey hello we love you so I'll see you when you get to New York man we'll hook up and uh listen
on this week I'm playing a lot of great great artists from the pod safe using that work on
I love the company at thatcatarmand.com so I hope I see everybody there okay please wait
David David David looking forward to meeting you hooking up dude it's gonna be real
tight in New York but we're least gonna have coffee or or a scotch one of the other that's for sure
uh I love the company David it polito just don't want to get this guy on the onto the podcast network
the pod job podcast network uh only two pieces of feedback that I'm gonna work on today uh that
came in uh since yesterday of course it's football Friday so we got some great tunes that I want to share
with you uh two main topics yesterday of course the Cory Lidal Crash and uh and the North Korean
Newcast set off hey Adam this is Matt and mom speaking Michigan hey on uh DSC 477 you had mentioned
something about North Korean explosion you know I just heard an article today on uh I think was this
we can science podcast and they had said uh kind of like the whole skeptical thing was a while back
I guess it was a massive explosion in North Korea something to do with a mine or they were building a mine
and it set off all the seismic you know meters saying that there was something going on people thought oh my gosh
this is a nuclear you know a test and quickly North Korea said no this was an explosion bubble of
well that kind of puts into the whole mindset that you know hey if this guy really is crazy like a fox
basically this guy's a big you know mad genius why not be doing the same thing so you know while the last
time they got everybody thinking so let's do it again and then just say yeah we did do it you know
this he's definitely out there um anyways just want to make a comment about that and then also
if I could do my shameless plug if you know listeners want to check out the first dedicated amateur
woodworking podcast out there uh we now have videos too it's Matt Basement Workshop.com and uh
definitely a scruncher so take care straight greens and sharp blades uh straight greens and sharp blades
nice I like it despite the fact that you're a scruncher well you know I've listened to your show
I've seen some of the video stuff you guys have done uh all you're missing all you're missing is a hot
babe on the show you know like uh like tool time then it would be fucking perfect I like your uh
your theory there um what was the strength on the Richter scale of that previous explosion which
they said was just a mine explosion was it also coincidentally around a four on the Richter scale
no one has really been able to come back to me yet with you know I mean what's the point of a
nuke you know um I guess you can make a small nuke right that only sets off a little explosion
towards really just their word against everyone else's hmm anyway interesting theory I like that
um let's see there was one other thing we talked about yes they which of course covered most of the
news but um I'm glad that most of you like to my take on uh on looking at the story
yeah at a long time yes you were sir immediately yes I'm sure you've heard about the
crash and then hadn't yesterday uh pitch for New York Yankees colloidal uh when there's some trouble
I guess wait a minute wait that's the wrong one I'm sorry uh I'm so sorry
this is what I meant to play for you hey Adam this is Tom Rockle from the Buckeye Drive's time
podcast and just wanted to say thanks for taking the time to kind of go through an explanation about
the playing crash in New York yesterday every other news outlet not the news junkies I listen
and read just about everything I could find on yesterday we're all kind of working some kind of
an angle about either blame you know who's fault was it and or a political angle about how could
this happen again and there should be no air you know nothing in the air around New York which would
mean no light flights no helicopters you know that kind of stuff and uh you're the only person
slash aviator to get in there and give an educated guess on some possibilities and not play the
high games and just really appreciate it dude I was totally my pleasure I do want to revise
my analysis a little bit though because now there's more information that I receive yes and I have
to say again it's all been from CNN the best information that I've gotten on on this incident
which I do know a lot about about flying has been from CNN so they had more information from the
NTSB the National Transportation Safety Board I've got to trust those guys you know they put out
all the the accident reports which I read pretty regularly you know in particular for the type of
aircraft I've been flying in or for interesting situations because you know you're supposed to learn
from this stuff so the first of all the aircraft was not going north the south it was going south
north for all intents and purposes for the analysis of the wind blowing the aircraft towards Manhattan
right right into the city that doesn't make much difference what is very interesting is that
the aircraft was at about 500 feet and they actually had the radar flight path so they they tracked
the you know they can go back and they can look at the radar data and they can see exactly
and barely I bet because once you get below that you know four 300 feet radar really can't track
it's but I'm gonna say that I have to believe that this was indeed fact that NTSB was putting out
it looked like he was up about maybe a little bit above 500 feet and then turned left
and then descended very rapidly another 200 feet so down to about 300 feet and then crashed into
the building basically heading south so almost a 180 and there were more eyewitness reports from
the ground which really are fucking useless because I mean you know people will hear something
and then they'll look up and then they'll think they saw all the events before the actual crash
I mean it's all it's it's very unreliable data but they had a couple people now who were saying
well it looked like the plane did two barrel two or three barrel rolls one eyewitness actually said
the plane didn't crash head on but it crashed with its underside against against the building
and then in addition to that there was an NTSB spokeswoman who said it appeared that the engine
was actually still running when it crashed into the building so here's now we do know that there
was an emergency call so the engine may have been running but it may have been severely underpowered
my analysis is still going to be kind of the same except one major difference oh and the flight
instructor no details about his how many hours or his type ratings other than that he's been
flying since he was a teenager that doesn't mean too much but he was only 26 I have to say all my
instructors have been older than I am and I really like the old guys I really like the guys with the
experience because you know they just don't take no crap from nobody particularly not if you're
a celebrity or well known or you know and I can imagine that there may have been some of that going on
with this instructor and with the with the with the student with Corey Lidal in this case or
he was piloting command but I probably he was still kind of under instruction while they were flying
but what a horrible mistake to to try and attempt a turn at 500 feet if you have an engine failure
and you're that close to buildings that that is just it is really the automatic
response you know turn turn away from the wind so you have the wind at your back so you can get
maximum glide and then start looking for a place to land but when you're flying up that east corridor
there is no place to land so the there is only one decision and that is into the water
straight ahead down into the water you go and and the this probably wouldn't have happened if they
so I'm just I'm just guessing here obviously but from you know I started with helicopters
so my helicopter experience really taught me you know when you're in a helicopter you don't even
try you you try not even to fly over a patch of woods because you know in the event of an
emergency you've got to do an auto rotation which means you're going to be down the ground pretty
quick and you got one shot there's no long glides in helicopters it's one way down and and you
can land it safely but you've got to have the room to land you've got to have some space so in helicopters
we often fly around those types of situations if I was flying up the east river in a helicopter I
know for damn sure there's only one place I'm going down and I've made that decision before I
enter the corridor before so that you know exactly for this so you don't make and make this type of
mistakes so I believe automatically engine failure or there was some type of performance issue
turned with the wind in their back and started descending of course and I believe that the
barrel roll was probably because they were really trying to make the turn to avoid the building
and probably just rolled it over maybe and it's also possible that the that they reach a
stall situation so the the rotation of the engine would have certainly facilitated that left flip
and they were out of control at that point so it's very very sad it's so what we call an aviation
having a bad fucking day hello there I'm Christina Curry host of episode four of BG Blast
be sure and check us out this week as we spin tracks from tricky and the wild bunch here about
Pallon is a webbi nominate internet TV show and much much more only two weeks left of the
hallows cream promotion so you better hurry up see you on the show oh baby I miss you hi Adam this is Tanya
back from Ireland I just wanted to tell you with me lucky charms oh that I'm actually a listener
I'm not a podcaster to block the listeners like Stacey here beside me hello Adam I think about
BT Potcho it's just that it just doesn't sound like it's localized the whole thing it sounds like
it's made for the BT UK market so to my ears it means BT Potcho isn't inclusive because it's not
localized content you know what I mean basically people want to hear a Scottish accent on
tartan podcast and they want to hear an Irish accent on the Dublin culture slot spot cast exactly
people want to hear low could you say the Dublin culture slots well how's that hit what was that
yeah an Irish accent on the Dublin culture slot spot cast it sounds like you say culture slots
pod I love it I love that I love this concept exactly people want to hear local voices talking
about local things that means getting unique British content and authentic Irish content that's right
yeah another thing Adam BT's marketing muscle it's not as dominant in Ireland as in the UK
now we're not getting the same message from BT in Ireland as BT puts out in England oh hold on a second
hold on a second oh let's just back at him for a second okay we have a partnership with BT
and part of that partnership is to be able to use their marketing muscle anything they've got
anything and that marketing muscle is not the messages you're seeing we're going to be providing
the messages pod show you know it's it's it's it's our game here so we're going to be using
BT's media muscle because yeah one of the which one BT's one of the biggest advertisers
in the UK at all telco companies are so um that's what we're going to be using it for
and localized of course we think we'd have an American accents doing Irish shows or or Londoner's
talking about Manchester no way hey those of you on series stars 102 we've got another three and
half hours of great podcast coming up on the pod show on serious have a great weekend I'll see you on Monday
let's continue with the girls from Ireland think we do do we know we don't the reason for this
is the two markets they're distinct like this is in terms of the currency the local infrastructure
and the telecom regulations as well what currency do you guys use there actually in in Ireland
that's really stupid I don't know that you know I've never been to Ireland which is why I don't know
what's the currency of Ireland is it the blues now here in Ireland we hear about BT
show this is based on what you say on your podcast now you make a personal and that's the best
toy you talk about things for people that are interested in podcasting all right now I might be
making this bigger than it needs to be but you know we are different I am never against making
it bigger than it needs to be Ireland we play harling better than we play football we drink longer
than anybody else in Europe that's true and you can actually legally land your airplane on our
grass pastures even if they're not designation as an error drill it's green everywhere over here
and that means that we can grow our own wood pellets yeah I mean you find our own biodiesel fields
how about that you got to get your ass over here for patties today you really do you're going to
hook me up you'll say chill oh you'll say that's so nice girls okay first of all thank you so much
for the invitation to land my airplane on your grass strip whenever fantastic how about weed in
Ireland if it's so great up there I bet you guys got some killer herb let me know about that will
I'll check this out you're gonna love this this is this is awesome it's football we got to play
it's so crazy right yeah okay go
I used to watch his show every Tuesday night he made a movie or two they were great but they were all right
I miss his mo kenies bo we're missed
And is the dream where I'm around you
And we are getting good
The memories we've all of a man
Will always be messed up
TV, they don't sell his cereal at the store
They don't show his cartoons are TV
In more, these days I have been with my turn
Make it come back Mr. TV
We're messed up
TV, they're thinking about you
And I'll tell you the truth
We will roll around you
All around you, when you're alive
The memories we've all of a man
Will always be messed up
TV, they don't sell his cereal at the store
Can't sell his cereal at the store
They don't sell his cereal at the store
The memories we've all of a man
Will always be messed up
TV
That's some high-fifth shit man
That's a mixed-master Mandy from Tennessee
I received a link and email to the
To the Potta music network
And it's been quite a while since I've actually listened to
Every single song that an artist had up on their page
This is really interesting
First of all, there can never be enough songs about Mr. TV
Let's be honest about that
But you've got to check out Mixmaster Mandy
This girl who, as a whole band
It's not just her
Bills herself as a female back in style and humor
And damn straight
And there's a whole different range of styles
And there is some very back-ish stuff
Some like Weasery stuff
Our vocals are really, really amazing
To go check that out
Of course, link to that in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
Yesterday, or at least last night
To Pacific Standard Time
You might have, you know, I've told you about this
Accurate target cast that we have, right?
Which is essentially, it's an entertainment-based show
But it is without a doubt
An infomercial to inform you about the new Accurate RDX SUV
If you were, if you went to Accurate.podshow.com
You might have been greeted by
Reginald fart bottom
You know, whenever we have some maintenance upgrades
We'd like to actually highlight it
So we were running some of our wacky videos again
And there was a new one, claymation
Reginald fart bottom
But of course, it wasn't our intention to actually
Make that show up on all pages
Such as, you know, podshow.com
Yeah, but we wanted to have something different
On our partner channels
Such as Accurate.podshow.com
And I kind of missed that one up
So if you were wondering what the heck is that all about
That's what it was about
Everything restored back to normal now
But in the future, we'll do some customized stuff
For a free-to-art partner channels
Accurate.podshow.com
But while we're at it, check this out
Yo, Adam
Yo, trucker Tom here
Hey, I wanted to tell you my
Splendid story
I knew you would
For a long time now, I've been
Kind of lazy and
Been buying all these diet
Cokes diet Pepsi
And I decided that
You know, drinking that all the time
Just because it's convenient
Probably isn't really a good idea
For a long-term hydration
You know, the problem I've had in the past
I just couldn't bring myself to
By bottled water
You know, the idea of paying for water
Just really has bothered me
And so finally, I decided
That you know, I'm going to have to just
Break down and start buying water
Instead of diet soda
You know, bottled water by itself
You know, it just doesn't taste as good
As the diet soda does
So I'm cheating a little bit
What I've been doing
Is using Splenda
You just unscrew the cap on the
On the bottled water
And put about three packets of Splenda
Down and there
And put the cap back on and shake it up
And you've got a nice little drink
That, you know, it's better
Obviously than the
Carbonated soda
But
Yet, you know, and I'm drinking water
I'm drinking plenty of water as I'm driving each day
Thought you might be interested in that
There's a, there's a use for
Splenda
Besides, you know, flavoring your
Since a.o. or your coffee
Or whatever it is, you're flavoring
Try flavoring your water
Hey, you can find me at trucker.com
Podcast.com
Or trucker.com
See you later, my friend
Take it easy
And watch those domain name
Oh, yeah
Frapper
Oh, Tom
I still do not want to know what you're talking about
Oh, sorry
Here comes the echo
We've got to put that in today
This is what a great, great, amazing product
The Splenda stuff is
It's so easy to
To advertise for too
I don't do shit
You guys love this stuff
It's clear
It's so clear
I gotta figure out if soccer girl is in on this
Splenda promotion
Because I have a feeling that she and Ryan could do some really interesting
Test with that
Nemo to self kind of do that
It's Friday
What if you not heard yet on this daily source code?
Huh?
I'd like to make a motion
To rock this mother out
Just to come and throw
You're on her
Please don't bang that gavel
You can try this cowbell out
Let's all give a night
To the hardest work in lawyers
Drives inside
And hands
But yeah
What do you say?
Yo, what's up, Adam?
It's Jersey Todd, the official musical
Just of the Cha Cha
So dude, can you guess my favorite class in law school?
No, civil procedure?
No, boring
Property law?
Black acre versus white acre
I mean, who the hell cares?
Criminal law?
Forget about it
Those people are screwed
No, no, my favorite class
Was contract law
And I just wanted to thank you
And the gang from Pod Show
For sending out my very own copy
Of the Pod Show contract
Dude, that think kicks ass
The phrasing, the word play
I mean, I read that for like two hours
And it's a thing of friggin' legal beauty
Loved every part of it right down to the left
Cautisol
And let me say one thing to the podisphere
After reviewing the contract
I signed it without one change
That's right, Jersey Todd has signed with Pod Show
So crap, crap
That means I have to come up with some more good stuff
Of the DSC, right?
All right, let's think about this
I know
The Jersey Todd shall work out
Okay, ready kids?
Here we go
Take both your hands and put them up to next to your head
All right
With the palms facing out
Palms facing out
Now bend your ring finger in your middle finger
So they touch your palms
Got those devil horns up
Good, good
Feel the burn
Now let's take your head back
And shake it like you were saying
Yes, over and over
Let's repeat
One, two, three, keep going
Because from the pod safe music network
This is Pilfuck Confession Box
We use album just dropped as available
Everywhere head banging music is sold
This is the song finger gun
On the daily source code
Go
anish
Now, let me take it by the ground
Now, let me fall
Go, baby, my deem, my deem
My deem, my deem, my deem
My deem, my deem, my deem, my deem
My deem, my deem, my deem, yeah
My deem, my deem, my deem
Oh, crap. That's a music right there, man. I tell you,
a pillow for confession box. Jersey Todd, thank you so much and welcome to the family, my friend.
What an endorsement that was. Thank you so much. Wow, my ears are like, oh shit.
I've lost all high end in my head now. Before I forget that, it's Friday.
Monday Tuesday Wednesday Thursday,
Friday, and it's final fun. Yeah, that's right, everybody. It's end of the week and
actually I'm going to be on the Gilmore gang today, I believe. So that'll probably, I guess we
record it today and then it comes out on Sunday or something like that in eight million broken up
pieces. So I'll check that out at Gilmoregang.potcho.com. Final thought for the week. Well,
there's really only been two things that have been on my mind near the latter part of the week.
And that's of course Corey Lidal and North Korea. You know, you really just have to look at these
incidents and I think yourself, you know, who's better or worse off? You know, the Corey Lidal have a great
life until it ended so abruptly. Yeah, I think he did. Who's doing what he loved? You know,
and is he in any, was he in any more or less danger before he crashed, you know, than we are North
Korea and shit heat up and all this talk of global thermal nuclear war, it really only brings me
back to my life philosophy and the final thought for this week is whatever you do in this life.
Please ride the wheels off this motherfucker.
All right, everybody. That's it. I got a good idea here. I got to get dressed. Yeah, that's right. I do this
in my bathroom. I'll talk to you from New York. Next time we speak, which will be on Monday,
have yourself a great weekend, data source code dot com for the show notes for information about
the songs that I've played today, everything else. And of course, you can always email the
Adam at podshow.com. Um, again, have a really, really good weekend. Take care, everybody. Bye. Bye.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network
from podshow and line-white networks. I love it.