Potcho is pleased to bring you the following killer content direct from the all new feature rich potcho.com
Get it play it dig it
Hello, yeah
Hi, yeah, I'd like to order a cake
Sure, did you want a European sell cake?
Yeah, why not okay. I'll try this
And we'll call it trimmed. Did you want to round it?
Pink
Pink yeah, what do you want red on it?
Okay, you're gonna write down Adam and Leo
Adam Adam and Leo
Leo
Yep
May love
May love keep you hand in hand
For the rest of your lives
dsc 503 and can I get your name?
Yeah, my name is Yazzi. I'm the host of the Yazzi's weekend dance floor podcast. Can you repeat the
All the all the thing altogether?
Adam and Leo may love keep you hand in hand for the rest of your life
dnc 503
That's excellent
Let's just now the turkey sitting on the table stuffing and the next generation of my mother-in-law's
twice baked potatoes. We only know stuffing. I'm headed to the couch for a nice big now
This is Delta Sierra Charlie 503 and Adam Carey is coming up
But first please stay tuned for public announcement
Don't use sugar in your coffee sugar destroys your teeth and makes you fat
Please use a splinter sweetener instead
I'm dining for this hotel tonight
She didn't see me clean down the stairs to have a free
She told me that I wanted to come in my bedroom
That's the sweetener
So I'll be tickled save the floor
I'm the sweetener
The sky
You
Leave
It
The
You
Leave
The
In
Right
Everything
To
The
New
Earth
By
The
Arch
A
Then I'll never let the sleep, then I
So I'll be tickled, say it in the door
Underneath is the breath of snow
Why?
Who would have been wouldn't have been
If Daddy had already seen
My feet get sick and I'm not left
I wouldn't have been wouldn't have been
If Daddy had already seen
My feet get sick and I'm not left
No!
It doesn't get more yanky due to the mat
Twist and sister
I saw mommy kissing Santa Claus
Hey!
We've had thanksgiving
It means it's time to focus on the holidays
Christmas
It's on the pod save music
Networking you can find a link to it for your own podcast
If you want to play that
DailySourceCode.com
Everybody how you doing it is Friday
DailySourceCode episode 503
Coming to you from once again
Just a beautiful Northern California
At the Curry condo in San Francisco
Yesterday the sun was out shining
Blue skies, not a cloud
Same thing today it's fantastic
And of course had to get up really early
And be at the stores at 5am
Is this something new?
I don't remember this from last year
I certainly don't remember from living in the States
But black Friday which is today
The day after Thanksgiving
Which is the last Thursday in November
I think so
That's the day when all the sales are on
Everyone goes shopping
And it's called black Friday because the stores
Essentially pull their balance sheets
Into the black by selling so much stuff
So there's great bargains
But everywhere I saw promoted people going to
Let's show up at the store at 5am
I hope your Thanksgiving was good
If you celebrate that in the US
Or indeed in Canada although you already celebrated it earlier than we did
So hope it was good
Hope you had a fun time with family
You're probably just rolling over about now
Because of course no one is working today
I knew that my day was going to be funky yesterday
It started off with a phone call
Hey Adam, it's me Jousel
I can't really get into it
But I just got here in San Francisco
It's about 7 o'clock on Thursday
And I have to figure out what I'm going to do
And when I do figure it out
I will give you a call
Goodnight
So that was Jousel who would
Already threatened that she was
Sorry that she was going to come up
And that's the last I heard of her yesterday
So I hope everything's okay with her
I was actually at the office at 2 o'clock yesterday
I was invited over to Rosy and Kimo's house
Rosy works at Potcho
Her husband Kimo is in free accident and grittle
And so it was like 12 people
It was really really nice
People who I guess maybe had nowhere else to go
And they put on a real feast
It was just fantastic
And Sue and Kevin Kevin
Both also work at Potcho
They were also going to go over to Rosy
So I said well you know what?
Instead of taking Bart
Which is what is the Bay Area Rapid Transit System
I said why don't we fire up Trinity
You know we're loading that we got bottles of wine
And some desserts and stuff
And we'll load it all up and we'll go across the bridge
Into Oakland
And we'll have a big adventure
Actually I think I said a big adventure
So we agreed to meet at the office at 2 o'clock
And I'm kind of like looking around
Because I'm thinking you know
Yeah I'm waiting for Sue and Kevin
But what if Giselle's angry boyfriend shows off
Hey, I don't know who this is
But stop fucking calling Giselle asshole
So I didn't
There's more people who are pissed to me by the way
I don't know who the fuck you are
But stop calling what you're asshole
And I had the Tom Tom Navigator
All programmed ready to go
So here's what happens
So the office is on second street
So we basically swing around
Go up past the condo again
Up onto the Bay Bridge
And we're maybe
Three minutes onto the bridge
And I can feel it
I'm like Guy's something's wrong
Because I'm losing power
Not that Trinity has
I should actually I should do
Shoot now
I don't even have the Trinity jingle here
Well
I said I'm losing power
And it was like it was
It was literally that I was losing power
So I put on the hazards
I'm in the left hand lane
Because I just kind of got onto the bridge
And she starts slowing down
And I'm pumping the gas
And I'm trying to figure it out
And I'm putting it into lower gear
I'm putting it into neutral
And so I kind of get it going again
And if you know the Bay Bridge
You can get off at Treasure Island
And so I kind of got the car going again
And we're driving along
And some of this consists of me restarting
While rolling along
It was really the weirdest thing
And I'm looking at the eyes
And I'm like out of fuel
Because I had at least a quarter tank left
So I think the fuel gauge was correct
Because that's really what it felt
Like fuel starvation to the engine
And you know so we're rolling
And then it's like look we can get off at Treasure Island
The exits on the left hand side of the bridge
And then we can roll all the way down to safety
And on all of a sudden she caught again
And like I'm making a decision
We're going for it
And we're off and okay we're it's a long bridge
And so we emerge from the bridge
This is the point where the GPS has to kick in again
Because we've been under this metal structure
And I don't know where to go
And for some reason of course
The GPS decides to reboot
So we miss the exit
And we have to get off the freeway
Circle around come back
And on an inclined up the freeway
It starts
Dying again
So I'm doing my series of restart
And everything and I kind of were kind of limping along
And it's really busy
And you know I'm not making no friends
So we finally pull over
And perfectly you know with a gas station right across the road
A call box right in front of us
And Rosie had actually
When I got Trinity head said you know he had just
Take this triple a card you know you never know
And I'd stuck it in my wallet
And I'm so happy I did
Because I call them
After actually
Getting two gallons of diesel fuel across across the road
From the gas station
Which was not the answer
I think the fuel pump went
And you can see pictures at curry.com
I posted some flicker pictures there
I think actually the show up on atom.podshow.com
As well automatically you'll see some pictures
Of Trinity being hoisted up
Our buddy Charles
It was there
I kid you not in under ten minutes
And he drove us right to Rosie's house
And so it was like happy Thanksgiving
Rosie here's here's my car
It's now in front of your house
Without to go figure it out
So
Rest in peace there Trinity
We'll patch her up of course
But I'm now a little bit worried
I have some significant trust issues
With Trinity at this time
And I'm really just not sure
How a relationship is going to unfold
I don't know this though
If you like maybe you ate a little bit too much yesterday
Do the exercise with us
Help from Adam
Thank you for coming
Thank you Amy
I'm sure you're still full from how they food yesterday
It's going to keep the move smaller today
Oh thank you very much
That's good
We'll head and switch your mic
Okay
I'm going to stay on this one if you don't
We're going to be working on the floor today
Let me put it on the floor then
Okay
Lay down on your right side
Use your right arm to prop your head up
Okay
Now take your left leg
Lift it
Bend the knee
And bring it over the right leg
And set your foot down in front of you
Oh
It can land anywhere between your right knee and hip
So much for sexy poses
Okay you'll twist it up and go
Yes I am now what do I do
Good
Now flex your toe and lift the leg towards the ceiling
Oh
And back down
Okay
Yes
Just like that
Seven more
You can put your left arm in front of you for support if you'd like
Five
Try to keep those hip stacks
So you're at leaning forward or backward
Two
Good
Okay
Untamed yourself and roll over
Then place the right leg over the left on the floor in front of you
Yes
Okay
Now lift the left leg
Eight times
Okay
Remember to breathe
Make sure you're squeezing your stomach
And butt
Which is exactly where you should feel this
And also in your legs
All right
Great job
I'll let you get back to your holiday veggie now
Don't forget
We're doing fitness attack in Spanish now
So check it out
Fitnessesp.pacho.com
Until next time
Thank you Amy
Fitness attack
You're an Espanol
Yeah Amy that really helped
Thank you
I'm feeling much better now
Much better
Actually hit the button by accident
I wanted to say something before this hit you
Plus
Four
Two
Seven
Six
One
Three
Four
Two
Seven
Five
Three
I was going to say
That there's an awesome video that Jill Mills and Robert Dolby produced
And they put it up
It's behind the scenes at podcastcon
UK 2006
You can find it at podcastcon
UK.podshow.com
It's actually quite long
It's about an hour and ten minutes
But I was blown away by what these two put together
If you want to know what's happening in the podcast scene
In the UK
Check this out
Very pleasantly surprised
And this hour flew by
And I'm typically not anyone who can
Excuse me
Sensei I was blind up
I'm not someone who can
You can really sit through anything
I can't sit through an album
I can't, I can't, an hour worth of anything
It's very hard for me
As part of the ADD
And but it just flew by
It was really, really excellent
And I'm thinking these two kids
These two wacky kids
They got to do some more stuff like this over in the UK
Of the luck going on
I was really, really pleased to see this
Because I think it did encapsulate
A lot of word podcastcon
UK was about this year
And it's definitely not a
A podshow-only program
Believe you me
But very, very interesting
And it's also a heavy
Slant towards the music scene
Which of course is always very interesting in the UK
What do we have more UK?
It's coming again
Podfest returns to the purple turtle in Camden, London
Presented by Gojang Podfest Association
We advise you as bonus.com
And we're just starting it
Another great knowledge of live entertainments
Featuring performances by Seren Co.
Superkicks
Union street runners
And Curve slider
That's Wednesday, 29 November
The Purple Turtle in Camden
Bringing you the best in live entertainment
It's Podfest
More details at www. Podfest.co.uk
And I've been assured that
The evening's festivities will be recorded
And we'll be put up on BT Podshow.com as well
Hey, a lot of feedback about two things
First of all about Twit, Leo Leport
And everyone has told me the name of the journalist
And I keep forgetting his name
Hold on, this is what Gmail is good for
I just search for Twit
Just search for Twit
And up pops, will Harris
There you go
Will Harris is his name
Okay
So a comment about that
Yeah, I've had email with Leo
And I'm going to be
Not, I guess they taped Sundays
They do a call in
So not this coming Sunday, but the Sunday after that
I'm really trying to figure out this
Patricia and I have a very challenging schedule
For the next couple of weeks
Of course she's doing that
Dancing with the stars
So it's going to be
And I got to come back to San Francisco
So we're just trying to fit everything in
But tomorrow I leave and I go home
Which is great because I think I'm really able to accomplish
An incredible amount in one week
And then go back and then come back like a week
Or eight days later
I actually feel pretty good about that
I mean, the flying part is kind of gnarly
But otherwise
And the other thing
Oh man, I had no idea that I would get so much response
About the Chris Moiles thing that I let you hear
From BBC Radio 1 on Wednesday
Some interesting comments coming in
I had a mission of uncorking uscots
I heard you talking on 5 or 2
About the fact that I anchor Chris Moiles
And the tip you've played
I suspect that Chris knows full well
What a podcast is
And he doesn't see his future there
So what's with this?
I think it lay my job
But after all ridicule on the whole thing
And gently turn this way
These liveers from following this sort of thing up
No more than that, expect from him
That's the best he can manage
You're probably better off in the morning
Listening to Terry Logan
If you want a bit more informed in television
Wims you in comment
I've got one ready at the end
But you already knew that anyway
I for now
Yeah, I listened to Sir Terry
And every morning we listen to Sir Terry
Logan on radio 2
I haven't listened to Chris Moiles enough
To really have been able to form an opinion on his program
But what I have heard is that he does tow the line
I think he's kind of
Hmm
He's doing a bit of a shock-jock thing
Yeah, is my general feeling
From the times that I've listened
The only thing I ever thought was really great
That I love was the date diversion line
I think that's an awesome, awesome idea
I don't know if it's a Chris Moiles original
But you know, just to be very, very clear
I don't give a shit about the guy
You know what he says or it doesn't say
I'm just hoping he picks up what we're talking about
And broadcasts it again to his audience of millions
Come on, let's be honest about it
Oh, what I'm interested in is going to write the last message
You can ignore that because this is the real message
And that's through for your might case
He's an absolute parcel
All sort of the highest order
What an arrogant runger
And it's got nothing to do with like
Not knowing who you are or what podcasts are
He talks to people like that all the time
And this is the kind of shit that
That teenagers in this country listen to
And expect that's the way to go on with people
That's the way to go on and treat people of it
Different religions are different
There
Different ethnicity
It's a
Second build this morning
You really have what an absolute idiot
They say they may say hello this idiot
To go on the radio and preach to the masses
These are the big listener following us
It's no doubt about it
He has a very big listener following
There are only seconds there to tell you
What a what a what a what an absolute one
He hasn't got the same style yet
Adults about anything
And I just urge anybody
To listen to this podcast
It's not really your source
There's infinitely better content out there
Infirmantly
And just turn on the radio
To listen to tell you open
Just because he's not fast enough
Doesn't mean he's not good
It's a good clean form
Bit of a loss
People who know how to
I don't even know what I want to say
Now he's got me so bloody runger between the people
What a fossa
They cheers me at anywhere
Bye
Decaf maybe next time my friend
Oh, gotten into some social political issues there
This is what what's the Chris Moiles is destroying teenagers in the UK
I'm glad you haven't investigated the podshow network too deeply yet
I think we you know, I'm very happy with the BBC program
It costs me 131 pounds a year
It's it is truly
User supported
So people who have a television or radio have to pay for it
You pay for a license and that pays for the for the content
I like what we're getting
I think it's fantastic
I think should do more of that high-brow stuff
Leave all the low-brow stuff to us
Come on mate, we should have Chris Moiles
Let's do it trade
Okay
Why not
We'll take Chris Moiles
And we'll give you
Mark Hunter
Tim's safe
We've got what I was looking for
Hi
We've got M
A BBC just to follow on from that
We've also got regional BBC stations
So you get BBC North
We see North West
We see Midlands
Expect
So the BBC provide regional services
Well
Ask for Chris Moiles
These are Aaron Wangar
There you go
As far as I'm concerned
I wouldn't listen
He's podcasting
It's the last thing in the radio
Or in the
In the
What a pretty spicy young man
I am
Get it
I am matey
You are a very feisty young man
I'm enjoying it very much
Yeah
I didn't do a really good job of explaining
Exactly how the BBC works
I realize that
It's it's complicated
But yeah
There are lots of regional stations as well
It is very networking
Like
But I guess the whole point is
It's user
Supported
I'm sure the government
Of course the government kicks in as well
But it's basically paid from taxes
Whether direct taxes or indirect taxes
I love it
I think it's really good
I think it's a good thing
I'm saying the cause
I'm just going to point to your
Chris Moiles comments
Chris Moiles
I ask you how to speak
You know in the day
It's not a big thing
The Internet is in 2004
I think I would say
That's what the Internet is
It's going to be more
It's the latest in the
Human
Characters
Chris Moiles is
How to speak
He would also like to be called
This radio
That radio
Stop
You should know
Whether it's anybody
It's a low understanding
That
That radio
So
It's a good performed
This is this
What was the strong language, now you've got the interest in?
Okay, he's abusive. See, I told you there was like a shock-jock thing that was going on there with him.
If you have to formally apologize to Elton John, you really did some fucking wrong.
I think you've had to use of course one of this, and you realize the way it impacts the perceived effect and the way you're moving on.
In the end, you tell me that you're an elephant in some brown names. You've said that you just have to mention that there's other products that the same is not available.
So, for example, I'm going to explain that I have to explain that I'm very safe and confused.
So, I can mention that that's five nine, but I will have to mention that there are a few three parts available.
That's what I'm talking about.
I love Microsoft.
That's fucked up.
That's really fucked up, man. Do you got to do that shit?
No matter what you say, you have to provide a complete opposing view, what a waste of time.
Really? What a waste of time you have to do that. That God for podcasting.
There you have it. Complete and detailed information.
Oh, on the Chris Moiles courtesy of your David source code friends, the audience.
Found this on pms. Thought it was good for a Friday.
Because I feel the same way sometimes about it has been heard lately.
Well, that you do. On the Saturday night, you know I had a withream of you.
And I was thinking that you so out of sight despite the fact that you're in my view.
And it's true. One could love you like I do.
So listen when I'm down in here, I think the love you've more than a lizard than me.
Was that you girl? Who was looking so good? When you bought it, I know it's going.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You've got everything but a fool. And I never want to do.
I think enough you've more than a lizard than me.
it's come out
Who's at you girl, and was looking so good, when you put it in a no-gance boy,
and that was her girl, and I mean that would you wear your smile when you count your hair and a tear,
but you've got everything I've done, and you all I ever want I do, I keep in love with you more than a little bit of it.
Now you'd be thinking, if from the UK, no way, they're from Illinois, they are the Jerry's, but of course as they call themselves British Influence Guitar Pop Band.
That's from Chicago, to be exact.
I love you more than Elizabeth Hurley on Daily Source Code episode 503.
Still gonna check out some more great podcasts, actually new stuff, not even on the podcast, music that we're coming up in just a couple minutes.
After some feedback which pertains to my business.
So Adam, it's my turn here from the Golemash podcast, which is hosted on Podgeau.
It doesn't say a few things about the new Podgeau Podgeau Plus and the MB to the latest version of it.
First of all, a couple of my listeners to my show are visually impaired and they use an access box system, screen reader,
to act as Podgeau is called Freedom Box.
Now the old Podgeau, you'll work very well with it.
Now the new Podgeau doesn't work very well with it at all.
In fact, one of my listeners totally lost my podcast completely because it finds a new Podgeau
to be completely unnavigable via Freedom Box access app.
You know, this is a very upsetting to me to hear this.
It's interesting, I had lunch with IL, Al Shavit, who now works at Podgeau as well.
It's guy who really understands building out big technology, crap.
And I said, you know, there's so much stuff that comes through daily source code that pertains to our business.
It said, they should be fucking listening to it.
And I know that the best way to get someone to listen to it is talk about them.
But yeah, you know, I remember when version 1.0 came out.
We had a lot of the accessibility issues.
And of course, we all vowed that we'd be very careful with our next version.
And guess what, sucks.
Yeah, this is I definitely want to fix that.
The problem is I'm pretty sure that in general web 2.0, if you can call it that,
it's not very vision impaired friendly with Ajax and cascading style sheets.
You know, and whenever you change something, particularly when you have software,
there's trying to figure out what is happening on the other end.
This box reader, whatever you call it, you know, things have to be adjusted and crap.
I hate it when that happens.
Okay, so we'll definitely put this in because we got to fix that.
I know there's a lot of visually impaired listeners of the daily source code and apologize that we've completely fucked that up.
It shouldn't be too hard though to fix whatever the main issues are.
But I think we're going to have to do is we're going to have to get a specialist in on the case.
So that we can kind of build it more into our foundations.
We've started some of that and I all I can do is apologize and promise that we all once again,
I've tried to do much better with that.
By the way, this video box is made by Sarah Carekin.
I can be found at freedombox.info and it was interested.
Also, the problems with the, who, what is it?
Since the revamp, I've had to be failures to do automatic uploads by a Casplaster, not plenty.
Hopefully, that should be fixed for you.
Actually, we went through that a couple of days ago.
We had an actual issue with Casplaster uploading.
But as far as I know, that's all taken care of.
It works for me.
So if it's working for me, then I presume it's working for you.
If it's not by the time you hear this, call me again or email me, let me know.
Or use the podcast or support link at the bottom of any page.
If it was the old version, it would upload perfectly.
This time we try and upload.
And it just fails errors.
The front and center was going on there.
Also, when I tried to do the manual upload, it was a complete pig.
To find the actual upload show.
There was an obvious add a show.
And of course, that's not the option they wanted.
And I found it sort of very deep, sort of with the entire domestic control.
But it wasn't, it's not exactly intuitive.
I don't know what your thoughts on there, Adam.
I didn't hear that you had it.
I mean, had it usability tested.
Was that with real users?
Or just the pseudo users that you people within Pot Show incorporated.
It's been tested on like outside people.
I said, come and start Adam.
This is my kind of from the show.
I mean, the UK.
I'll just take that.
The last night comment is British humor.
There Mike.
Okay.
Of course, we tested on real users.
We did not, by the way, tested on visually impaired users.
Now, we probably tested on the same users as that Pew Internet study.
Very interesting.
And if you've heard about this, Pew Internet, they basically concluded that since April,
when an average of 7% of the American public had heard a podcast or downloaded a podcast,
downloaded a podcast.
Yeah.
That is now risen in sort of six months time to 12%.
And this, I love statistics.
I love to argue about it.
Guess what is it amongst the study of 2000 people?
I think it's representative.
I'm no statistician, as you all know.
But I guess it would have to compare versus the numbers that they're looking at because they
are using percentages.
So that's a nice jump.
A couple of other interesting things.
The biggest demographic jump 50 to 65.
I thought that was pretty interesting.
Every category is up.
Every age demographic.
But over 50 seems to have jumped higher.
Which, of course, is completely consistent with everything we keep saying about advertising.
Advertisers always want to go for the young, young demographic.
But people with actual money are buying computers and iPods and are tuning into this stuff.
It's not just a young man's game anymore.
But the BBC interpreted the study a little differently.
They interpreted the study with the headline podcast numbers show, quote, few hooked.
So they start off with the 12% versus 7% earlier this year.
However, in the original study, there was a question actually took the effort here to get the original study.
Take a look at it at pwinternet.org.
And let me see if I can just find this one question.
So the way the question was worded.
I don't want to misrepresent this because it's really important with this stuff.
So the question was, please tell me if you ever use the internet to do any of the following things.
So this is the actual call out question.
Do you ever use the internet to download a podcast so you can listen to it or view it at a later time?
Okay, so that was the 12%.
So people are actually downloading podcasts to listen to it or view it at a later time,
which means video podcasts are also important.
And then the second part of this question,
did you happen to do this yesterday or not?
And only 1% in both cases in the study February to April 2006 and in the August to November study,
in both cases only 1% answered yes.
So clearly, lots of work to be done.
And that kind of confuses me, well, maybe it's on par with subscriptions.
Maybe this whole subscription thing isn't working all that well,
because I can only imagine if 12% I see what's 1% so about if I just did the math on this,
a little under, so like 9% of people who have downloaded a podcast are subscribed,
whether they're doing a manual subscription, i.e. I'm going to pick it up or whether it's being done for them by technology.
That's a little lower than we're seeing. I think we're seeing about a 30 to 35 rate on podshow.com, percent rate.
But just kind of interesting that that's what the BBC decided to headline with.
Well, thank you. You pointed out where we have to do some work.
And that's not a problem.
It really isn't very, very happy with these results. That's pretty incredible.
We've almost doubled the numbers in half a year, so congratulations to everybody.
Congratulations to you, listeners, because you're the ones benefiting from all this shit.
Let's see one more thing here.
Hi Adam, it's Neil Ford from the UK. Just calling just been listening to five or two,
and just want to add comment to your cast class, cast a blast a bit.
And to say, I think that you, whoever at Podshow is responsible for assisting the guys from overcast,
the Mac application, to get that working with the PVA.
I know it's not quite there yet. The version I have doesn't quite support it,
but I know it's in the works and obviously I suspect that somebody at Podshow is helping the guys
out to make sure it'll work because that functionality is just going to be absolutely fantastic.
Being a Mac user, cast a blast is not an option.
So having a piece of software that is going to work with PVA is fantastic.
And everybody involved in that process really means big thank you.
Just want to write that.
And to say as usual, just keep doing what you're doing. Enjoy the show.
And it was great to see you on the Thursday.
Yeah man.
Take care.
Thank you.
Yeah.
In fact, I know that this work has already been completed.
Now we have an API on Podshow Plus,
where you can use any type of software you can create that speaks a pretty simple language.
I think it's a, think it's straight XMLRPC.
There may be a few couple special bits in there.
But we, that's how cast blasts are actually talks to the system.
And that's how any, any uploader, I guess.
It's funny that you mentioned this and I can't quite find the comment.
Com extra blogger also sent me this fantastic comment about how we need an uploader.
This is an opportunity for someone to make some money by creating an uploader.
Or someone to, to get some notoriety with their programming skills by creating an uploader.
So we've actually made it a completely compatible with Uber Castor.
There were some very interesting issues on the Macintosh side that I think Apple actually had to fix.
I'll have to ask Andrew Grummit some of the history of this is a developer.podshow.com.
And one of my resolutions for the coming years that we pay more attention to the developer community.
Who have been extremely helpful and have gotten a lot of cool things into podshow plus.
But we really haven't done much to support it yet that, you know, you can really say, wow, look at what we did.
We've been doing our best kind of with with a little bit of extra time that we do have.
So there was something about the way the Mac handle XMLRPC calls that had to be changed.
I believe that was changed with Apple.
I have seen the actual, you know, like a hello and response from Uber Castor into podshow plus.
And I think those guys are just firming up their next release and it should be in there.
And I can't wait because that will finally give Mac users a fantastic way to upload your show and your show notes.
Everything is all done in one go right into your feed.
So that'll be exciting.
But again, you know, you can create any type of uploader.
The API is exposed open.
It's commonly known.
It works with the validator, all that stuff that you need.
And you're more than welcome to to create something.
And maybe you have some kind of fantastic business proposal for us regarding that.
Very open to listening to all of that.
You're doing everybody.
It's Marcus couch from the scene scene and podshow music rewind.
Happy food bar Friday, everybody.
Hope everyone in the US had a great Thanksgiving.
I know you're probably out doing a little bit of shopping right now.
So I'm going to give you a real rocker here on Fubar.
Adam, I know you're anxious to get back to the round corner towels.
So here's a song just for you.
This band is called Revery.
They're from Virginia Beach, Virginia.
They've been played on both rewind and the scene scene.
I know you're going to enjoy it.
This one's for you.
It's Pop Star Wedding.
Rock out of Pop Star Wedding.
And I'm sitting in the blues.
I don't need food.
And we're getting into the shoe.
I won't take no credit or a dollar from you.
Don't you feel me?
I got nothing to lose.
There's no way to move.
There's got to feel it.
I got stuck in the snow.
I'll see it all the time.
I don't think that I can take it all my life.
I don't need to see you.
I got to feel it.
I got to see it all my life.
Seems like I got to hold all the now.
So if you're trying to take me down, you can't forget it now.
I'll make a heart run, honey.
I'll wait for the day to score.
I'll make a heart run, honey, honey.
I'll make a heart run, honey.
I've got to see this.
And I go chill out and I'll roll up
Seems like I got over now
So if you're trying to take me
Now you can't forget it now
I hit it all the time
I wasn't brave enough to take it all
The rubbery pop star wedding, thank you very much Marcus Couch from the so-called
reaction on the punch you're about here.
That's what I'm talking about.
Hi, this is Ed Ovet, host of the Ed's Mix bag podcast, stopping by the daily source code to
wish Adam and all of his listeners a very happy holiday season and a very happy and healthy
new year for 2007.
That's so nice, Ed.
Thank you very much, man.
That's right.
We're wrapping up a year as we wrap up a week.
What day is it today?
It's Friday.
One day Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, full of Friday, Adam's final fun on the Wii.
Well, of course, as we bring yet another year to an end, it's been quite an interesting
one for me.
I've had some emotional ups and downs, particularly with the passing of my mom.
So as we do here in America, as when we hit Thanksgiving, you know, and we did this last night,
I was wondering if it would be different from any other Thanksgiving that I've had with my
family.
But people do kind of say, hey, you know, here's the shit I'm thankful for.
And it's nice.
And the only thing I can really think of that I'm thankful for is the health of my wife and
daughter.
Not 100%, all things considered, you know, they're healthy.
And maybe I'm just getting them to become a really old fucking fart.
But that seems to be the most important thing to me.
In fact, yesterday, the last night, I thought I got back from from the feast I'm sitting
on the couch and, you know, just digging around, looking at stuff and I thought, if I
didn't go out and buy a toy for myself, something I really really wanted, it didn't
matter what it costs.
What would it be?
And I just couldn't think of anything.
I just wasn't interested.
I'm completely content.
I'm completely happy, particularly because those two are healthy.
And that's my final lot of the week.
Yeah, speaking of which, I have to get the lighter to sign off the show.
Hey, everybody.
Thank you very much for listening.
I'll be back in the curry cottage starting Monday.
I'll be there for a week, and then I'll be back here at the condo in San Francisco.
If you did celebrate the holidays, I hope it was a great one.
If you're in the UK, pocket man, it's weekend and joy.
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery
network from Podgeau and line-white networks.
I love it.