This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy.
Delta Sierra Charley, four, five, six.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Podcasting is an out-of-curry.
You've got a brand new high school work,
some cool street, every day.
Sir, I had a podcast in the show.
This is a lot of pain.
Is that the thing when we have parties?
Yes, you know, it's your fault.
I've shot my hair, you smell damn sick.
Something that you don't shoot into the door.
You don't get it, I've had.
You listen to my show.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
It's kind of in between all kinds of stuff today.
Our offer was accepted on the house that we put an offering on.
That's really exciting.
That's the first offer we've had that's actually been accepted.
Now we're going through this period of trying to close it all up.
Right now the current owner, she's fine with getting to a close real quickly.
But she can't tell us when she wants to move.
And it seems that the cottage she was going to move in that was going to be empty.
That those people have to move out too.
So guess what we're in a chain?
Yes.
Fantastic.
My lifelong dream fulfilled.
The phone could go at any time.
There's all kinds of activity going on here at the cottage.
And it's warm.
It's really awesome weather.
It's like 26 degrees Celsius.
27 degrees sun shining.
I wouldn't quite call it an Indian summer yet because I think that has to last for two weeks.
I'm not going to complain.
That's for sure.
Let me just wrap up a couple of belated birthday greetings that came in.
Because it's almost like someone sent you a card that came late and you don't thank him for it.
And because of the whole nature of podcasting people are finding out it was my birthday.
Well, significantly after my birthday.
Oh, almost.
I can't pilot error already.
Oh, yeah.
Here we go.
Try this.
Oh, I didn't carry this.
It's fine from Germany.
And I just wish you a very, very good birthday.
And I just found out that we actually share the same birthday.
I was born 30 years ago to do this thing.
And I hope you have a great party.
And let's wish it's from Germany.
And laugh the show older.
And that's in tail moment.
Brought to you by Patricia's stew.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy, happy, happy birthday dear Mr. podcast president.
Wow.
So Adam did that.
Good to see you.
Happy birthday.
And thank you.
Thank you so much for playing the divas on your last DSC.
This is from the divas at the divacast.com.
We love you.
Thank you.
Celebrate well.
Divacast.com.
The divacast.com.
All right.
Well, this party has to end.
And we're not going to like it on the high performant.
Damn.
Get naked ladies.
Now I did divas.
Thank you very much.
Now I, you know, you guys think that maybe I don't hear these shows.
But when I'm over in England, I have such an advantage with the time.
I'm up a way before anyone else in the US.
And so, you know, and I have a lot more.
Well, of course, I spread my day out twice as long because San Francisco wakes up at 4 p.m.
Our time here.
So I'm sometimes can be on the phone until I, you know, 12 30 1 a.m.
But it gives me a real advantage to just listen to stuff without being disturbed
because everyone else in the company, most of them at least are asleep.
So I did listen to the divacast.
And I listened to your response to, to my comments on it.
I'm just going to say it again.
Right now, you are, you're on kind of on the edge between the view.
Right?
Which is a bunch of women who are sugarcoding things and not really being honest about their feelings.
Even if it's contrary to the other view members.
And you're on, you sometimes step over into something really, really wonderful.
But you know, there are definitely opposing viewpoints in your group of five divas.
So let's hear them.
And if you really, really, really are friends and you want to do this and you want to create something that's more than just
clutch, which a lot of it is in my humble opinion, then you've got to dare to go the extra mile.
You have to, you have to be willing to offend someone else to make a point or to get a conversation going.
And you don't have to purposely offend somebody, but by expressing your own view point,
honestly, honestly, and don't, and all this, you know, talking around subjects and using,
I don't know, please, please, there's so much potential there.
Be honest, if you really are friends, you can have a fight.
You can have real words and then walk away and be friends.
It really, if you are friends, it will work.
And otherwise, it's just kind of like the view.
But I do appreciate the happy birthday greetings.
Thank you very much.
Now, if you want to hear a great promo or creative promo, something that just really caught my attention,
I think you're like this one.
Well, quality podcasting with killer music and commentary straight from the middle of America,
then listen to my dad's show.
It's called Worlds of Wayne, and it's freaking great.
Worlds of Wayne.
Hey, hey, hey, did you just say the effort?
Oh, oh, no, I said great.
No, I mean, before that.
Oh, it's okay.
I said it with the tone.
Like this son of a...
Oh, okay.
As long as you use the tone.
But if I get a call from school, you are rounded.
Oh, podcasting tones are fun.
Hey, yeah, they are.
Watch this.
Kiss my...
Go!
Yourself.
Oh, that's a bad one.
That's a bad one.
But hey, this is a podcast.
We don't have to use tones.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I don't, but you still have to.
Oh, shh.
Hey, hey, you watch your tone.
Listen to Worlds of Wayne.
Get it on iTunes or check it out on Worlds of Wayne.com.
Worlds of Wayne.
I love that.
And people accuse me of me using my child for profit and entertainment purposes.
Great.
Watch your tone, young lady.
Yeah.
Fantastic.
Portions of this show brought to you by accurate.
Check out the new RDX SUV.
We've got a target cast, which is really.
It's an infomercial, except we think a lot more interesting.
And not so in your face, and it does go in depth.
And it's a lot of fun.
You can find that at accurate.podshow.com.
A couple of weeks ago, actually, let me play this thing for you.
First, you know, this is the kind of stuff I'm now getting out of my voice mail.
Now that now the voice mail is, I guess it's being published.
It's on the show, show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
And people are just using it to leave me messages.
Check this.
Hi, this message is for Adam Curry.
My name is Blake Landown.
I'm from Technology IQ, a Division of IQ PC.
We are a research conference company, and I'm putting.
I am not reading this from a script.
Together, a conference on content management.
And I wanted to invite you to sit on a panel about podcasting with some other individuals, including
Chris McDonald and Accenture, two people from IBM.
Michael Priestley and Jamie Roberts, and also Steve Dowling, Manager at Apple.
I think I know him.
Because podcasting, please give me a call at your earliest convenience, and you can reach
me at six.
Yeah, this is so unbelievable.
And so this goes on all the time.
Six, four, six, five, three.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
Stop with the phone numbers already.
Oh, it would have been nice if she had said folder or scruncher.
Yeah, so she's clearly never listened to the show.
I get this all the time.
There's just tons and tons of requests.
The ones from the Netherlands, I just completely ignore.
But you can imagine that Ron gets a lot of requests.
And we're busy.
We're on different sides of the world, literally.
Working in multiple times, time zones.
We're just going nuts, just doing our thing.
You know, and an interview is always, it's always an hour and a half.
You got to just sit down and think, prepare for five minutes.
And there's blah, blah, blah, preamble.
And then we talk.
And I think the way Ron and I are, we usually like to take our time.
And we don't want it to be rushed.
You know, we might as well not do it at all.
So several weeks ago, Joseph Jaffey, who does a podcast called Across the Sound,
he used to have a partner and now he does it himself.
And it's the new marketing podcast.
Now he had requested a joint Skype interview with Ron and I for a while.
And now I'm subscribed to a show.
So I listened to it.
And I said, I think we should do this because there's marketing people that listen to it.
I think it'd be pretty interesting.
So this took the typical few weeks of scheduling.
Again, still two different time zones.
I think Joseph had a was right in the middle.
And I think he's in Westport, Connecticut.
So we had three time zones to work with.
You know, it's a chunk out of our day.
So especially a Skype interview.
It's always going to be an hour and a half.
So, you know, we set it up.
And we do the interview.
I thought was great.
You know, Ron and I were just chatting away with Joseph.
It really wasn't an interview.
Although it was and was prefaced as such.
But it was it was a good chatting.
Personally, I even told Joseph, I said,
Dude, you know, you shouldn't edit this at all.
You should just leave it.
I mean, leave all the, all the, all the crap in there.
I love that.
Yeah.
And you guys listen to the Charlie.
You know, I love that.
It makes it fun.
All the best bits never made it on to MTV, right?
Um, so he said it was going to do it as episode number 50,
which he thought in what's, you know, it's the big episode 50.
That was fine.
That's great.
Love it.
And I listened to it.
He did something that I don't really like normally.
In this case, I don't like it either.
Um, it's he split the interview up into two parts.
Now, the Steve Gilmore started doing this with the Gilmore gang.
And I don't like it.
It doesn't work for me because, um, I want to hear the whole thing.
You know, I want to control when I can listen to the rest or not.
And it feels now like I'm being held hostage to stay tuned to something.
So, not digging that.
And I don't like it when it's done with interviews that way.
It just seems like, you know, why?
You know, you could use next week's zeitgeist is so many different ways.
You know, and things can change.
And maybe you get busy.
Whatever.
So, anyway, so we cut it in half.
Um, and he, um, I did hear, I don't know if he edited a lot.
Didn't sound like it in the, in the first half.
Maybe some bits.
Maybe his own stumbles that he took out.
That's, that's pretty typical.
That's what Rob does.
A forward podcast for one.
One is he takes out all the ohms and the stumbles that he does.
This is so, it's so contrary to what I like.
Um, so I just said I'm subscribed to the show.
So I heard the episode 15 and episode 51 comes in.
And there's something very surprising that Mr. Jeff is saying.
Please listen along.
Thank that the you know is actually our positive and quite constructive.
I guess it's a little bit of soundvertising as per Adam Curry.
Speaking of which, this is meant to be part two of the Part Show interview with Ron Bloom and Adam Curry.
Uh, I am not going to play part two of the interview on episode 51.
And I'm going to do that for two reasons.
One.
Well, all right.
Uh, so this had my interest.
Oh, he's not going to play part two for two reasons.
Now let's listen to the first reason, which I presume is the reason.
Because I've been so busy.
I've never been this busy in my entire life.
And that's not necessarily a good thing.
And I just have not had the opportunity to edit part two of that interview.
The second you really need to go and look at.
At his website.
And reluctantly I'll post a link to it on daily source code dot com in the show notes.
You know, sometimes where voices just don't match up with with the face.
Um, this is one of those cases.
Well, I guarantee you that you have a very different image of what Joseph Jaffee looks like.
Because actually he's a good looking guy as, you know, as guys go.
But he sounds like, you know, Roger Smalls territory.
Anyway, so that was reason or one crazy busy.
No time wanted to edit couldn't do it.
Never been this busy in my life.
And here's what he's going to play it off on part is I have got absolutely no love from Adam Curry.
I haven't even had a mention on the daily source code about the interview.
No traffic driving.
No love.
No referrals.
No track backs.
And so I think I'm just going to hold part two of the posture interview hostage.
All right.
So he didn't have time to edit the interview.
He didn't have time because he's never been busy in his life.
Yeah, he's going to hold part two hostage.
Because I've given him no love, no attention, no promotion, no traffic.
I'm sorry, Joseph.
I didn't know that this was like an audition or something for your show.
You know, we went through trouble to schedule this.
You know, out of the bottom of our hearts, I'm a listener.
But now it's like because I didn't promote your show.
And I didn't send you love.
Joseph, Joseph, I know you're listening.
Hey, dude, come here for a second.
Bend over.
I'm about to give you some love.
Bitch, can't believe you're doing this.
This is so stupid and wrong.
And, you know, it's like it's offensive.
I spent an hour and a half, you know, answering your questions, you know, for your podcast.
And then you chop it in half.
You know, I figure I'm waiting till I send over a lot of love, Mr. Chopin.
And until such time that I get a little bit of acknowledgement from Mr. Curry.
Oh, now it's Mr. Curry.
And you want acknowledgment from Bend over, bitch.
Affluent suburb of Geoford.
It's the affluent suburb of Surrey.
It's actually engulford.
In Surrey, London, the United Kingdom, Europe, the world.
And as soon as he gives me that love, I will give him love back in return.
All right.
I don't want your love, okay?
I'm not interested.
You're good looking guy, but I don't want your love.
Now, I hereby withdraw all permission to air my interview, part two.
You can't have it.
I do not give my consent for you to air that interview.
Fuck you.
You nuts?
Do not air that interview.
Part one's already out there.
That's okay.
You may not air part two until such time as that I feel you've given me enough love.
Then maybe, maybe I'll consider it.
Voice mail numbers plus one two zero one six two five six three five seven.
But the plus and front.
That's for if you're entering it into your cell phone plus one two zero one six two five six three five seven in London.
Oh two oh seven six eight one three seven five three.
I'm number three now on the business week best of the web.
Ask a ninja number one by far by far.
It's such a and number two is NPR.
So it's just not not one specific NPR podcast, but NPR.
And then comes daily source code.
You can write in your own favorites though.
So I fully expect Keith and the girl to be on their soon and Dawn and Drew.
Uh, I'll put a link in the show notes.
You can go find it podcast peer awards.
Finalist announced.
Man, we did well as pod show this time.
What's with this time?
Is it the first time?
I don't even know podcast peer awards.
Find us a bit of an ounce number.
Half everyone on the arts entertainment.
The strip at the strip dot pod show dot com in the cooking food wine and beer category.
Guy girl on the bottle wine dot pod show dot com podcast or Joe.
Favorite digital flots of pdub music accident hash accent hash dot pod show dot com geek brief as news documentary current events.
Keep brief dot pod show dot com.
This is great production a second nomination for pdub with digital flots.
Some digital flots in the pod show dot com regional of the Alaska pod show.
Spirituality, life spring storytelling.
There he is again, pdub as well as geek brief in storytelling.
Pdub.
Maybe it is.
So an august 31st.
The five top scoring qualifies he's category one on some categories.
Less than five post of winners in the month of September.
October one winners are now.
It's great.
Congratulations.
Great job you guys.
Great fucking job very proud.
Hey, I'm Drew Cohen from Phoenix Arizona.
Wanting to take exception to the discussion of sensing that's been going on lately.
I am a 15 year fancier moon lighting is a sometimes sensing coach.
When I'm not at my day job as a open source software programmer.
I think anyone who says that sensing is a faggy sport hasn't really been involved with it a whole lot.
It's an extra very intense very athletic sport.
Understand that the uniforms and such aren't the most attractive things.
Certainly not something I'm going to wear going out for an item at town.
But in reality they're really not all that different from the uniforms worn in football and baseball and other sports.
You know there's plenty of safety reasons and things like that.
Obviously for them.
But to describe it as faggy I think is unfair and not something that people better involved with it would even come up with.
Yeah.
I'm going to get so much trouble for this.
I loved fencing.
I just thought that the uniforms weren't the most masculine uniforms in the world.
Particularly if you've got a build like mine.
Hey, play some football as an American football.
Yeah, you look good no matter what kind of physique you have.
And with faggy I just mean not really manly.
I don't mean anything really sexual about it.
On the other hand, other callers have mentioned that they can kill you with one stroke.
And I think that's a little bit ridiculous as well.
The sport fencing is after all the sports rules aren't exactly what I would call useful for real dueling situations.
And I certainly wouldn't expect that the fencing that I've learned would be able to save my life if some weird situations were.
I disagree man.
I totally disagree.
In martial arts they'll tell you as well that if you have anything in your hand like a newspaper or an umbrella.
Or an umbrella or a newspaper is actually a really good example of rolled up newspaper.
You can actually thwart off a knife thread and maybe even a gun thread.
You know, that's that whole parade deal you do, you know.
And okay, you don't want to like swivel around and stick them with your fingers because they ain't going to do much.
But you can definitely defend yourself.
I disagree.
I think that there are many, many advantages to that type of thing.
Anyway, I just wanted to give you a brief brief.
I want to see you back on that.
If you want to check out my fencing club actually, we're at easyfencing.com.
You are ever in the scenic area.
Sure would love to give you a quick lesson.
Maybe I can say a little bit about saber.
Since you said you never got to check that out.
Maybe we could set up some kind of podcast smack down and get you in Marcus.
You should learn an improv to beat on each other with some metal sticks.
Anyway, that's all for now.
Thanks.
Oh and folder.
Uh-huh.
There's nothing I can cut off of the boy.
I don't want to do that.
No, no, no, that would be very wrong.
Yeah, I'm going to go to Phoenix.
Thank you very much for the invitation.
That's very nice of you.
Should I ever happen to be in Phoenix?
Yeah, maybe.
I don't think I'd actually go out of my way to do it.
Let me, oh, I just need to, if only I could get in some fencing today.
Hey, by the way, the new place.
It's so close to the airport.
Oh, man.
I can actually fly from flying in from big and hill towards the
Arkham VR.
If I deviate, I'm not going to tell you how much you're aware, but if I deviate
just slightly, I'll fly right over the house.
I'll call with that be.
Ah, still no phone call.
Still waiting to see if we actually capture the new cottage.
Which really isn't a cottage.
Alright, come up with a new name for it.
Uh, let me see.
What else do I have here?
Uh, who sent me this?
Sinclair sent me.
Ah, that's really cool.
From, uh, Hammaker Schleimer.
It's, uh, little drumsticks.
You plug into your iPod and then you can drum along.
And it, uh, as you drum on the table, it can create all kinds of drum sounds.
I like this.
It triggers it off.
Uh, that might be something to plug into the mixer.
Thank you.
It's only like 20.
Was it for 25 bucks?
I think we'll get that.
Very cool, man.
Thank you very much.
Hey, Adam.
It's Bill.
You know, I was just listening to, uh, Charlie 440.
I'm catching up.
And, uh, again, mentioned that he was an origami folder.
And it made me think about something now.
I'm not going to tell you whether I'm a folder scruncher.
That's just, just, I don't know, a little bit too personal.
But, uh, I won't say that I found myself, uh, trying in the, uh, other way.
And, uh, you know, it made me wonder.
I wonder how many, uh, of your listeners have now experimented with, uh, whatever the other option is.
Uh, other than what they normally do.
That might be interesting.
No.
So, have a good one.
Ah, shit, folder.
Yeah.
I knew it.
I don't know.
I've, I certainly have.
And by the way, people who, who wonder what this whole folder scruncher thing is about.
And why I continue to talk about it.
Well, obviously, people are calling in and saying scruncher of folder just does identify you as,
which part of the human race you belong to.
And, of course, it gives me a great excuse to play this.
Hey, Adam David from South Florida here.
Uh, it's quarter to 12 on Friday.
Uh, just listening to episode something or other, uh, four, five, two.
Anyway, trying to subscribe to Perversion for profit here.
And I can't find a, and a link anywhere here on your, uh, on your, uh, on your podcast site.
And I don't want to use pod share plus.
I think it's a great service, but I just don't have a useful word right now.
I want to continue to use iTunes.
Anyway, where's the link?
How do I subscribe to this thing?
Uh, thanks.
Thanks.
On glad you asked that.
Uh, and some of these things are changing.
We're updating the interface all the time.
And it's going to change quite radically.
I think we'll do a, uh, one very radical change.
Um, if you go to any episode of any show on, uh, pod share plus a pod share dot com.
Uh, so you, you have a show site.
It'll show you the most recent episode.
You can go there, go into the archives.
Every single of those pages has all the different options.
It has an, uh, an RSS link for raw RSS.
It has an iTunes link, which it will actually subscribe you to the show,
just by clicking on it in iTunes.
We also have a Windows media player.
So you can play the episodes in your Windows media player.
It doesn't download them, but it plays them on the fly.
Same for, uh, for the real player.
No, I'm sorry.
Yeah, real player and a Win app.
Nah.
Yeah, Win app.
That's it.
Um, now here's an interesting fact.
So you could just go to any of the episodes.
You can either copy the, uh, the XML in or just click on the iTunes link.
It'll subscribe.
What's interesting.
If you create a channel and this may change your mind about, you know,
you're using iTunes.
It's, we are definitely built to be used with iTunes and the iPod.
So if you create a channel, you have a channel in your collection.
And if you put shows in there,
if you actually click on the, uh,
uh, so if you click on the channel name itself,
it'll expand.
And in there, you'll see, choose your favorite downloader.
And if you select iTunes,
it'll download every new episode from each podcast.
As it comes out from all the shows in that channel.
So you may want to revisit experiment.
Let me know if it works for you.
Or if it doesn't, please, definitely.
Why?
From day go to beach.
It's the, hey, Adam, can I leave it down here?
And of course, day go to beach.
Uh, hey, I was listening to your commentary on, uh, New Orleans.
I can tell you how to help.
I was down there about two weeks ago.
There are portions that are in pretty bad shape.
There's portions that are pretty good shape.
And easy thing you can do to help is to go down there.
Believe it or not, the, uh, the French Quarter is in great shape.
Uh, they just need some business.
And commerce is the way that you help build up the community.
So if we have more tourists going down there,
uh, it creates jobs, creates income,
gives those people a chance put on their feet.
So, and, and hey, you'll have a good time.
How can you beat that?
Have a good time.
You see an interesting place.
You get to see the stuff firsthand.
And, uh, and you're just in good.
So, there you have it.
Holder.
I'd like to thank you, folder.
I'd like to have your view, uh, your views on that.
If, if that really is the best thing to do.
Um, although it's instinctively, it feels absolutely right.
I don't know if going to the French Quarter is going to help everybody.
But, uh, let's talk about it.
Let me know what you feel what you think of there.
Otherwise, we can help when you were,
we're right upon the, uh,
the first anniversary.
Man, there's a lot of anniversaries.
9, 11 coming up.
Yeah, it seems like TV is full of it.
So happy we're now talking about that today.
We're listening to Weird Nylon.
All weird.
All the time.
Weird Nylon is a podcast recorded via Skype.
We've Carlin New York and Paul in London.
Let's say we get the name.
Nylon.
En-Wife in New York.
L-O-N-Felundan.
And it's all about weird stuff.
Defiliping judge really consults business will do ours while making decision.
This is the annual world in Rebellion against humanity.
What's next with Pete Doherty?
Find out to answers to these questions and more on the next Weird Nylon.
www. WeirdNylon.com.
Give us some feedback at CarlinWeirdNylon.com.
If you've got any groovy stories, you know the kind of thing we like.
Just drop us an email.
Thanks very much for your time.
Thanks for playing this.
Cheers.
Bye-bye.
All right, Parkie.
Get this touch.
Don't say it on.
And I got to change that too.
Don't say it didn't do anything for you, Parkie.
Okay.
Alrighty.
We're coming down to the final final few days here for the EarthLink ad challenge.
You've been hearing the finalists all over the network.
The winner is going to run away with a couple grand.
And of course, their commercial will be used in the official EarthLink.
And I think we can go beyond that.
Honestly, it's just so much creativity.
I'd love to have a couple of these others running in rotation.
And I think that they all receive some form of prize.
So yeah.
Okay, did everything else?
Uh, that's about it.
I could, let me just play this one then.
This is a celebrity endorsement from someone that you don't know.
Of course you don't know me.
The New York Times once called me the most famous person in New York that nobody knows.
That's true.
Go ahead, search it.
But you notice several hundred thousand people I am known as that guitar man from Central Park.
And I'm here to tell you that EarthLink is just about the best thing you can get on the internet these days.
I mean, if you're anything like me and you hate junk mail, EarthLink's spam blocker alone is worth the high speed connection that starts at 1295 a month.
It comes with free anti-virus software, a firewall and spyware blocker.
Look, take the word of somebody that you don't know.
And you have no reason to trust.
Get EarthLink.
This is the song that I didn't have time to play yesterday.
I like it a lot though.
I can't, I think I've heard Christina talking about it.
So let's load it up and blast it out today.
Okay, I can get you with the 44.
I'm gonna keep with the net.
I can keep with the car doors.
Let me hit inside it 17 tasks.
I can keep with the block.
I'm gonna keep with the mech.
I can keep with the bottle of beer right over you too.
I can keep it in this land.
It's time to be one more time.
If you want to be the one too.
Bad energy.
Think you're so fine.
But there's so many ways I can kill you.
Come on.
Shut up, you shit.
It's in your life.
Cause I don't want to hear you.
But I can't, don't just run over.
And there's so many ways I can't.
No.
I can keep with the switch blade.
Or I can use them shiny net.
Just break out.
The Terminator.
I can't catch it.
Yeah.
I can keep with the rest numbers.
Just jamming your head.
Or I can wax you with the moose.
It's cheese.
So I'm covered in red.
It's time to leave one more time.
If you want to be the one too.
Bad energy.
Think you're so fine.
But there's so many ways I can kill you.
Shut up, you shit.
It's in your life.
Cause I don't want to hear you.
But I can't, don't just run over.
And there's so many ways I can kill you.
Yeah.
Well, I can keep with the toy in your hand.
Or I can keep with the sound.
Probably not the Hyundai.
But I can still keep it in nothing.
I can keep with the hit run.
Or I can easily country drive.
Run your down, escort it up.
Your ass stuck under my four wheel drive.
And it's time to be one more time.
If you want to be the one too.
Bad energy.
Think you're so fine.
But there's so many ways I can kill you.
Shut up, you shit.
It's in your life.
Cause I don't want to hear you.
Don't just run over.
There's so many ways I can kill you.
That's the break-up.
No.
Death and destruction.
Scorer know they hit on the wall.
When the jacks attacks us, wax with the next.
To print the backs of the black chain attacks.
So many ways I can kill you.
Some of your ways you can die.
Some of your ways I'm gonna get you.
So let's just rip it up one more time.
But I'm a sucker.
I'm a sucker.
I'm a sin of broken shit.
I'm a happens week.
But if you want to feel it that someone's wrong,
you can't fall.
Until I hear what that sounds like
just for a long time, if you want to feel it.
Be
And so family friendly indeed medsumo so many ways to kill you. That's gonna wrap it up for the dating source code for today
Of course, I'll be back tomorrow
DailySourceCode.com Adam at podshow.com
Take care everybody. Bye bye
I love it