This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code
to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 389er.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
The glove compartment is an accurate name.
Everybody knows it.
So I'm proposing a swift murdering train.
It comes behind its door.
There's nothing to keep my fingers down
and all I find are souvenirs from better times
before the gleam.
Over-tailed life's fading days to find
yourself a better life.
I was searching for some legal document.
Is the blame be down on the hood
when I stumble upon pictures I tried to forget
and that's how this idea was drilled into my head.
Because it's too important to stay the way it's been.
There's no way how our love did slowly fade
and now it's gone.
It's like it wasn't there at all.
I'm here I was just like a disappointment ever come.
I'm quiet.
Why no way got out of my head.
There's no way how our love did slowly fade
and now it's gone.
It's like it wasn't there at all.
I'm here I was just like a disappointment ever come.
When I'm lying all night when I'm lying all night.
and come in if you want that's cab for cutie title and registration please
from the pod safe music network actually turned on to that song by martina
butler Michael butler rock and roll geek show his daughter martina does a
show called emo girl talk and she's actually doing something for a demo and
she played this song and I was posted in the demo for like man I kind of
dig that so I hope you appreciate how I look today for once I'm actually
in complete attire I've got the button down shirt on no tie but I just took
off my jacket an actual black jacket you know not like a leather thing or
that diesel jacket that I have or no I'm I'm prepped and ready I'm back
actually from a great meeting in London with Ben Fervayan who is the CEO of
British telecom going to tell you all about it because I'm very excited about
about what at first of all how cool is that I left the house at what I
leave 11 15 11 15 gotten a cab took me to the station and you know right
through you know that's 25 30 minute train ride I was I was perfect timing I've
got it down now see instead of waiting 20 minutes I can get there right on
time get my ticket hop on with just moments to spare quick cab ride from a
waterloo station to Newgate Street where the BT Center is and you know
have a meeting then come back same thing actually I scored a oh man it was so
nice I saw that I had like eight minutes to spare getting off it getting out of
the cab getting ready to get on the train on the way home and I'm like okay
Burger King I can smell it I got myself a nice water meal hopped on the on the
train and ate it in first class and stank up the whole place all the way home
and literally just got back and figured I would share my experiences with you
guys because that's part of my fun at least for the daily source code but first
just briefly about last night as I've been starting to understand even better
how to utilize what I'm now calling the user interface of the future some
call it a virtual world some call it a game you know it is second life but I'm
really learning how to utilize this thing as a communications tool
yesterday in the pod show palace casino theater can you believe I actually got
that I had a couple people over and you can actually just sit down I can play a
video and so I played some stuff that work on it pod show some trailers and
some other things that you'll be seeing soon this is just like my little closed
beta to gauge reaction but it was so easy to do this and to have people
commenting while the video was rolling you know it really isn't interface I
found something else which is this multi-chair thing now you just have to
visualize this because remember this is just about connecting with people when
you're doing it in a very visual way and this multi-chair thing you sit down
in each person that sits down in the chair a new chair appears and I think
there's a max I saw the max yesterday at around 12 I think but it's really
good because everyone's sitting and it kind of controlled not moving about because
when you get too many avatars too many people as it were roaming around
then everything slows down and we had a real good conversation and there was you
know as I said there was like 12 people in the chairs people sitting around
and it was you know we actually got some chat going on we're talking about the BBC
was doing and I knew some of the people I didn't know others and then just as the
conversation was kind of you know at a certain point you have too many people for
a conversation which is also and also be a problem with anyone can just come into your
virtual space I saw that Emma was online so I sent her an instant message I say
Emma we got like the whole gang over here come on over I got I got your pole your
stripper pole and sure enough Emma came over it took her about five minutes because she
said she was with another customer I'm not quite sure what that means but I'm going to
leave it at that so I paid her $500 blind and dollars and and of course on various web
blogs you'll see pictures of that fine gathering yesterday at the castle oh my goodness
that was fun though but it was good and yeah even talk a little bit about British telecom
by my meetings today it really it's a it's a great interface it it works very well for me
in limited quality quantities because it does get a bit you know overbearing and
just a bit after a while so I don't have a fully prepped show I haven't even listened to the
voicemail message box this morning because it was just so much to do and get ready and
I actually had prepared the cast blaster demo or the cast blaster machine which I used for
cast blaster as my demo machine because I was going to show the the CEO cast blaster of course
but also pod show plus and the pod cast delivery network so you know lots of lots of
preparatory work getting it just right and I wanted to leave on time so it could be in the lobby
at one for the 130 meeting to be able to configure their BT open zone because of course with a
company like British telecom if you use their internal systems you know Gmail is blocked Yahoo is
blocked no Yahoo isn't blocked actually but Gmail is blocked so you can't retrieve password
easily and all this stuff so I just wanted to get on the BT open zone which of course they also
have in the building completely separate network and just be able to do the demo from there to show
what we were getting into together before all that though there are some things I have to admit
that take precedence over the CEO of British telecom.
all right he's up to tricks now now he's up to high jinx and I like it so I'm curious
here is comic strip program from comic strip block.com I just wanted to tell you that I called
London speech radio station LBC that you can also hear in Guildford last Sunday to ask about
something the presenter whose name is Ian Lee who is also a grand son of the actor who played
in Star Wars and by the way I mentioned you Adam and here is what was he's reaction.
it's another carry reference this is I don't carry. Do you know here?
yeah who is he?
excuse please don't let the road any. I don't carry lives at the road yeah.
I don't carry yes do you mean madam carry?
no I ain't Adam carry. Hasan.
no Adam. Madam Kira.
close but not close enough. Okay so Adam carry is a guy who is in Guildford.
he lives in Guildford yes. He invented podcasting.
he invented podcasting.
yes wow.
so it now you know who invented podcasting.
Madam carry.
no Adam carry.
Adam carry.
okay yeah anyway thanks.
okay thank you.
bye bye.
that was a call from Germany.
Adam carry.
so you can hear Adam that apparently some radio presenters still don't know who the
fuck are you?
maybe some post-save music artists could write a song who the fuck is carry.
something like who the fuck is Alice.
ciao.
you know comics are blogger you are my hero dude.
I think you should call every single radio program in the UK and record this stuff.
and every single time you get you get the host to mention my name on the air.
I'll pay you five hundred linden dollars okay every single time.
be happy to do it. I'm happy to have you terrorize these guys. Fantastic.
okay onto business then.
so it's no secret that we've been thinking about setting up pod show UK and part of the reason is
besides the fact that I like being here and because my girls are here too you know I kind of
get the tag along with the family and we like it here and there's a thriving podcast community
which happens to speak more or less the same language as we do in the United States.
despite all our differences and more on a future yanks versus the brit segment for that.
but we met with a whole bunch of the podcast community.
some of the thought leaders at our draft and darts not too long ago.
not everybody could make it unfortunately but at least we got a good
good vibe for what is going on and a lot of passion a lot of excitement.
and in order to open up something in any or any other office for that matter believe it or not
you know the the eight almost nine million dollars and of course there's the the money
runner I put in. so let's say the ten million dollars that that has been put into pod show
is just not enough to open up another office with five to eight people in in London.
or anywhere in in the United Kingdom for that matter just look at the exchange rate for one
but also it was never really in our plan to do this until you know we had significant revenues
and now a lot of things are coming together a little bit faster than we thought some of them
simultaneously when it rains at pores kind of stuff. and so we were really looking for as we
do in the US as well for two types of partners one is an advertising agency who has clients
of course and during our week here we met with several of them several who have US companies
have a British annexes and vice versa. as well as distribution now for us distribution is
well it's a whole bunch of things but it's anywhere that we can feature podcasts and hopefully ours
as well not just ours but yeah we'd like to put ours up there and an example that is iTunes
pod finder I actually haven't seen the new pod finder thought I was supposed to come out yesterday
it should be up so that's distribution now on pod finder we promote rarely promote a pod show
podcast it's really to promote podcasting in general but you can you can see what you know what the
the obvious types of partners are for us. excuse me since I haven't had a freaking drop all day
so with British telecom it's a very interesting company they do not have a mobile arm even though
they are the default telephony carrier here in the UK and beyond the UK but most prompt
predominantly here in the UK they're very interested in in y-max no secret they're coming out with
they an IPTV service offering and the company is although often seen is a little dusty and
old and stodgy you know they definitely have an attitude about where they want to go and it was
only a couple weeks ago no I was more than that actually it was about two months ago when I was
last days I was in San Francisco the last time that we were asked to come and meet with
a number of key executives of British telecom what happened to be in Silicon Valley so we did that
and I don't think they were quite expecting what we had to say but when we basically had
laid it all out they said wow you know we should see if we can work together because this is very
timely we're coming out with new products etc and so we've been talking meeting some negotiation
not you know we we don't like to negotiate really really long and drawn out because if if the
intent of a contract is not the same from both sides no amount of paper is going to make anything
right so you know you try to avoid those situations usually it's a bad sign if there's a lot of
back and forth on a contract at least that's my experience so we so the out that we're down to the
wire here and the final piece was for me to meet with the CEO Ben Forvian who was a Dutch guy
and to seal the deal I guess so we had exactly 20 minutes scheduled this is very typical for a CEO
by the way 20 minutes and since I'm the default pod show guy I was off to go and do it
Ben Forvian interesting although I was pretty sure I'd never met him before I know of him and
have seen him on television shows he's a Dutch executive he ran parts of a KPN the Dutch
to a telephone company he was CEO of loosen technologies he also worked at I believe endimole
Holland media group he's one of these guys who's definitely been around and has been there
there's someone calling me what's that no sorry that's KJ he wants to talk about the meeting
we'll have to call him right back so when I came in you know and I was kind of prepared to
you know how to you only have 20 minutes I just want to make a really good impression that's why
I was all gossiping up and Patricia helped me of course maybe look pretty and makes me also confident
and I know that he had just received a the equivalent of a night hood from from the Dutch queen
so I'm already to congratulate him on on this prestigious award and I figured I'm not going
to speak Dutch right off the battle at him choose the language so yeah nice to meet you Adam Croix
oh nice to meet you we've actually met before well I guess I'd make a big impression on you then
huh like oh shit this is not good but he's a really very awake
aware kind of guy you know and so he immediately is pushing on you know so I got the cue
I'm into my rap about what pod show is what we've been talking with his team about and all the
guys were there you know we worked a lot with Steven and Gavin and so you know they were in the room
I couldn't just tell they're like oh man this is it's got to go right and I and what was
fascinating is so I took him through pod show plus and he's like oh yeah I really like this yeah
this is good so I'm still in couch potato mode kind of said well you know you couldn't configure this
so you can listen or watch things at your office or say well so I can have this set up so that I
can get stuff at home when I come home from a busy day at work and it'll say here's what I've
collected for you after a busy day of work I said well we'll have to put the words in the busy day
at work part but yes exactly what it does and we you know went ahead and create he said oh I'm
interested in cooking so I love it when when people try and break a demo like that so I you know
once straight to the director he pulled out a vegan the vegan cooking podcast actually
put that in build Ben's test channel and he's like okay so but what if I want to make something I
say well I'm glad you asked so I whip up class blaster he's like hmm hmm so I give a quick run
through when I say but you know instead of explaining all this let's just record a podcast
so I hit record and actually I think and this was just through the microphone on the
Chiba so it sounded like shit but I had to overmodulate because you think the microphone's bad
on the Chiba the speaker is even worse it's like it's almost like an iPod speaker only that someone
someone you when you don't jam into your ear he let's listen to I think we have that test podcast we
created on poppin it up now it's actually on the podcast delivery network so here we go
is it playing a crap shoot I have to I'm sorry all right I'll continue to talk well my
engineer actually does some reconfiguration here so and you know and he and so I show this
cast blaster piece and we record it and I show him how easily gets shot right up to the
right up to the to the pdn and he's like okay I like this this is really good so I can do
this how about video I say well you know obviously you know we add the video component to cast blaster
and you do the same thing and you still have to provide your cameras like no no this is great
he said this is one of the biggest things we learned at end-a-mole and end-a-mole of course
is famous for the big brother program he said is the results that we achieved by hiring regular
people and not actors to be in the television shows that that was brilliance and I'm like dude you
are a visionary that's for sure he'll I think I've got it wired up so okay so whatever we say now is
okay yep and then we can have we can add uh so we can add a drum to that if you want yeah okay
but that's the voice and now how do I do a video see there he goes yeah the video is guys we're so
smart he's straight straight to the video amazing okay so that's all we did basically you can
hear him jabbering away and he was like boom boom boom question after question and then he says
I like it this is great what what what what what what's the deal what are we doing and then the guy
said well basically you know we we have the deal we just you know without saying and it's like okay
we just want your blessing and he's like and and I immediately jumped in and said yeah this is
actually just the courtesy call you know just say hi and uh and he said this is fantastic this can
be bigger than dream works I want to talk about it tomorrow to the shareholders and I was like oh
anyway I think we're in business and of course until it's signed in blood
which means we have a partner and I think it's a damn good one they are really they've you know
without going into all the details of our agreement of course hope you don't mind
there's going to be a lot of push for marketing for podcasting it will not be exclusive to BT
customers only it'll be for everybody of course there'll be tons of BT branding
which is obvious for obvious reasons and and we're really going to push this to the forefront
and I think in in combination with the BBC who are educating people almost daily now on on what
podcasting is I think we will really kick some ass now will also be creating show specifically
for the for the UK market you know so what we have budgets and you know please don't go
filling up the Gmail because I know everyone is excited and I know that there's lots of stuff
that we all want to do just let me you know give us a few weeks to get everything squared away
but I'm so happy I'm even more happy now that we had a chance to meet so many cool people at the
draft and darts meet up at the bricklayers arms because well we said we would do our best and I
think we're there so extremely excited about it let me see I was going to you know what I was going
to try and hit the exact satellite window for this show let's screw it let's just play another song
some I played before but it just felt right for the mood it's a bit of a style council
lanky fallen hard for the girl
I'll kill them for them yeah you were over it now I hear the ground just say you're waiting for
something to come around but you'll never see it coming
no you'll never see it come in inside your head and it's hard
you're my friend when you fall in your heart when you fall in your soul
you're my friend when you fall in your heart when you fall in your heart when you fall in your heart
when you fall in your heart when you fall in your heart when you fall in your heart
lanky fallen hard for the girl from the pod save music network all these songs that you
here on the daily source code become available for purchase excuse me the day that they are played
on the show so go off on the support these artists buy a DRM free free and clear MP3 you can
read download it you don't lose it and you support the artist 100% of the money goes to the artist
except for a small transaction fee which does not go to pod show and we're really happy to be a
part of the pod save music network and of course the pod save music movement one other thing
about British telecom I love their assistance and secretaries there so fun to flirt with them so
easy telling us that whole american vibe and if Patricia were here she'd say I'm full of shit
and definitely full of myself and I'm telling you it's fun and I like them I like them all
add them a credit dot com free feedback daily source code dot com for the latest show the podcast
feed and the archives and of course credit dot com for any conversation that might be ongoing there
which doesn't necessarily have to be the same conversation in the podcast tomorrow we'll be back
with yet another charlie see you then everybody bye bye
get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery
network from pod show and limelight networks I love it