This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want to hear content with badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code, get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 3-6-4
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I got it.
You may think they're benevolent or maybe even kind.
You may think they're the kind of guys who help you every time.
But show once you're now to enter in the fold.
Just sign up on the dotted line and let them have your soul.
The come track is simple.
It's all in black and white.
Except for all that other stuff.
But you don't have to mind.
You needn't have to argue.
If you really feel abused,
you've signed away your life.
And now there's nothing you can do.
It's the evil pod show that sunk you up and then they'll go.
Out the door and search it more.
Stupid suckers just like you.
You may say,
Holy hay,
I've screwed myself and deep today.
But now it's done.
You cannot run.
It's all too late.
You better sign it.
I won't sign it.
You can't make me sign it.
No, I won't sign it.
I know I won't, I know, I know I know, I know, I know, I know, I know
Hey everybody, thank god it's Friday this is the Daily Source Code, the last
one before my luxurious 10 day vacation, how you doing everybody, Jeff Smith, you are my hero
man, I love that, that was so fantastic, and the funny thing was, after Jeff sent that to me,
we talked about this for about a day or two, actually yeah for about two days, and he
sent this to me, and the funny thing was he said in his email, he said, hey dude, you don't
actually own the rights of this forever, do you?
Oh man, what a genius, genius talent, okay, well I'm going to try and make it a relatively
short show because we got to go, we got to get out of here, it is what's the time here,
it's 1130, and I told you I was doing all these different preparations to get out of here,
we're going to the old Garvin Portugal, what I didn't tell you is the journey that we
actually have to take to get there because not only was it almost impossible to find any hotel
rooms anywhere where the sunshine and Portugal I think today is about the expecting 24 to
25 degrees centigrade which is just right on the money for me, we couldn't get any flights
either, and you know the Delta Sierra, although a fine machine, it has limited bathroom
facilities for a trip that long because I don't know what is that, that's like 2,000 miles
or something to get from here to Portugal, so the only flights we could get is from Rotterdam
and that's tomorrow morning at like 7 a.m. so we had to decide, okay, how do we get from
here to Rotterdam, and of course I'm like oh yeah, oh yeah, we can fly the Delta Sierra
right down to Rotterdam and then well that wasn't till I started doing the weight and
balance, this is very critical if you're a pilot, when you're flying you have to, you
first of all know that you're not overweight because at a certain point the plane just
won't lift off the ground, and of course the balance is also important because if you're
too heavily frontloaded or backloaded you may not be able to, you might not just literally
have enough stick to take off or land either, so I started to do some calculations based
upon the suitcases, the girls are packed, we're driving, there's no way we're lifting off,
it's like forget about it, I didn't want to start limiting them on what they could
take and all that stuff so I said forget about it. What we're going to do something exciting
though, actually haven't done this yet, we're going to take the super V8 to Folkstone, that's
where the Euro Tunnel is, now the Euro Tunnel is this huge massive project that's been going
on for more than a decade and it's a tunnel between the United Kingdom and France, so you
go from Folkstone to Calais and you literally drive your car onto a train, it's a 30 minute,
35 minute train ride underneath the channel and then from Calais we'll drive up to Rotterdam,
so in total I think we'll probably be driving four or five hours, but we'll see some of the English
countryside we haven't seen yet, we'll actually, you know, it's the first real big trip that the
the Shagua, the Shagua will be going on, so hopefully it hangs together and we'll also see
some of the French countryside and it should be pretty nice and then we'll stay overnight in Rotterdam
and be at the airport right in early off the Portugal, and of course I'm sure that we'll land
so early that the hotel rooms won't be available and we'll be able to unpack and do any of that stuff,
but who cares? I'm glad we're going, I'm ready to unplug and unwind.
See, my brain is so fragile, I'm not only physically tired, I'm mentally tired.
In the meantime though, we've received a whole bunch of box, best of Charlie's,
Bravo Oscar Charlie's, we could use a couple more and P-Dub was going to be slinging those onto the
under the satellite in my absence, I think there's actually seven days that we'll have to have a
different show, or we'll have a best of show, and somehow I got to figure out how we get those
posted onto the Charlie feed as well, which is going to be interesting because the actual,
it's a whole long story, but God, I can't wait to migrate over to the, over to the pod show,
P-D-N where I can actually stack that stuff up and have it all automatic, so somehow I'm going
to have to figure out how to get those shows uploaded and we'll figure something else. I got to talk
to so many people, but maybe on my two-hour drive to Folkstone, I'll be able to get a hold of some
folks and set some of that stuff up, but thank you very much everyone who's been sending those in.
I don't have the list here, but I'll make sure to get you off some cool pod shows swag,
and we need about just need a couple more, so if you want to send one in, please feel free to
and we'll be happy to use that. Okay, I'm going to, as I said, I'm going to try and make a
short show today, but we have some interesting stuff that came in via audio comments.
Hey Adam, how you doing? This is Dave from the yoga pages podcast. You can find my podcast at the yogapages.com.
It's for yoga lovers around the world. We do yoga news, interviews, and product reviews.
The reason I'm contacting you is regarding the DGAP technology. I'm working on a second podcast now
that would kind of a for-profit model that would depend on using the DGAP technology, and I've,
you know, heard you with the GoDaddy thing and putting it into some of the podcast. What I don't
know is, is that available for everyone? Or is that just a pod show kind of an exclusive thing?
So if it is out there for all of us to use, can you point me in the right direction? I'd appreciate that
and keep up the good work with the Charlie time for me to check into today's episode
and see if I'm the Golden Ticket winner. Bye-bye. So yeah, that is kind of a, it is a pod show
technology that we've been, that what we've been thinking about it working on it for probably over a year now.
Andrew Grummit did most of the technology K1, of course, did some stuff on that.
Well, the whole pod show team has been involved in it because it's never just one person that does this,
but Andrew has really been working on a lot of the logistics of it and the core got some
particularly on the Golden Ticket stuff, which really, people are very excited about this whole
idea and we're going to take, we can take this in so many directions. So drop me a line. Let me know
what your idea is and we'll be happy to see if we can help out. And if you have an idea that we can
test out, I'd love to do that too because the Golden Ticket is just one small step into the future of
what we can do with this stuff. So yesterday, we inserted yet another Golden Ticket chances were
one in 25,000. Those were your odds of receiving the ticket. It actually, the ticket was
issued quite early in the day. I think it was probably in the first couple thousand downloads. Again,
this is all random. So although your chances, your odds remain one in 25,000, that's the way it's set
up. It could have fallen at any time and so it was issued and Andrew and I were like,
okay, it's an issue because we still haven't heard from the first Golden Ticket winner,
which kind of makes, it also reset my brain a little bit about this stuff. And if you think about,
excuse me, I'm saying, if you think about how the five, Willy Wonka Golden Tickets worked,
it took several weeks, I guess. We're not in movie time, but in the story before all of them were
actually discovered. And you had all those kids eating all those thousands of chocolate bars, right?
So yesterday, I received this. Oh, my gosh. Oh, man, I want to, I can't believe it. So I'm
listening to your show and, you know, I'm kind of still bummed out from yesterday because I doubt
I don't want anything. And all of a sudden, you know, the sound goes away like mid-set and
saying, what, what's going on? What's down? System broke or what? And there you are. You're saying
congratulations, you won. And I'm thinking, what? Huh? I'm still dreaming. No, I'm still dreaming. You
know, I should, I should have slept like 14 hours straight because I haven't slept in a while.
And I'm thinking, I must be like, you know, how you get a dream within a dream?
So, I'm thinking I'm still dreaming. Anyway, dude. So what, you're going to call me? That's
going to be a trip. Okay. Cool. Hey, you know, I should probably promote my show.
Get some listeners to that. It's a different world podcast and get it on iTunes. Or you can go to
music.potcho.com, do a search for it's different world. Don't put in the
comments. You won't find it. And check my show out. Oh, man. All right. Woo. Wait a minute.
I don't have an iPod. Oh, I won. Woo.
All right, this is okay. Can it's out. I'm curry. Oh. How are you doing? Good. Is this what you're going to do?
Dude, give me the phrase that pays. Oh. Oh, man. I'm actually talking to Adam Curry.
Dude, congratulations on being our first golden ticket winner. Thank you. Thank you.
Yeah, it was the other guy's first things all in, I think. No, you're the first one to dial in. Of course,
there's one more golden ticket out there floating around somewhere. And as I promise, if that person
picks up the ticket, then they'll win too. But I was so excited when I got your message. They,
you know, like, we were all jumping up and down and everyone in the office was excited because it
worked. Dude, it's not working. Yeah, that's not working. It's almost scary. You could almost take it to
another step and actually target people. I think maybe possibly. I don't know. Yeah, that would be
so evil. We don't want to do that. This was all for the fun. I was actually pretty happy that,
you know, you hadn't figured some way to hack it out or whatever to figure it out. You just,
now, if I, if you, are you in the Bay areas that where you are? Yeah, yeah, I'm in San Mateo.
Yeah, because we could see from the logs, we could see that it was from the Bay area and your
Mac user and you have iTunes for your podcast, right? That's right. Now, that's a evil that we know
that shit. You know, that's what, but yeah. So dude, I think I didn't want this like Bay of Girls
crying. I was hoping I can get through the call without something happening. That's okay. How many girls do you
have? I have a little girl she is wishing 19 months now and a little boy he's for your goal.
Oh, bless you. They sound really excited about the whole golden ticket concept, too, don't they?
Yeah, I couldn't really say, but yeah, I'm glad it worked. So Ken, from your message I understood
you don't have an iPod? No, I don't. So that remote won't do you much good then, I guess.
No, that's not like that's it. Don't worry about it, man. That's a shit that never makes it
onto the radio. This is real. This is real life. You know, people have kids and they, they don't
cooperate. It's great. Now listen, Ken, we're so excited about this and I know you don't have an iPod.
So instead of the the the remote, which we will give away in a future goal and take it,
I'm going to send you an iPod, okay? Of course, man, this is historic as far as I'm concerned.
We've done something really cool. I want you to be happy about it. Not sitting around with a
phone. Oh, man. I didn't listen to your show on the computer and if I don't do that,
I actually downloaded onto a memory card sticking in my phone and I listened to it while I
got my way to work or something. Oh, fabulous. Oh, I don't have to do that anymore. Oh, wow.
Well, listen, Ken, I'll let you get back to the family. I've got to see, I have your address, I think.
If not, do I have your address, did you email that to me?
Please tell me when we're done. Email me. I love this. Email me, your address and I'll get
an iPod out to you in some pod show slide. Okay, you know, just like five minutes ago,
they're running around laughing, having a great time and working broadcasting, working radio,
working podcasting. It's all the same time. That's perfect, man. I love it. Listen, we're just
really excited that it worked and really appreciate you helping out in the test. Oh, man.
And I'm glad it's going. Now you have your podcast. You want to talk about that for a second.
Give it a plug? Yeah. Yeah. My podcast is called, it's a different world.
If I talk about gadgets, I talk about news that will be now. It's quiet. What's that?
Talking sound. I know I talk about, you know, the new gadgets out. I basically introduce
you know, the stuff to people. So, you know, people might not be tuned into, you know,
what's new and what's going on and they probably don't care. But, you know, they listen,
my show, just get a, get a heads off on what's going on. And what's up? See you,
we're all. You can go to my website, but it's probably better that you go to
music.potshow.com. And type in. Now give me your website, man. Give me your website.
What's it? It's a different world.com. It's a different world.com. You know what? I was listening to that
thing. I was listening to your, to the, to the, to the message you sent in a Patricia walked in.
Well, I was, I was, I'll cueing that. You said, yeah, he has a really good voice.
Oh, man. Yeah. What the mic. I hear you. Where do you think these go on is from?
Man, from the microphone, from the PR 40.
Oh, I'm nothing without the mic. But yeah. All right. Can, well, listen, when I'm in San Francisco,
maybe I don't know West Coast, we can hook up sometime. And in the meantime, I'll make sure you get
a nice little package, including an iPod and some t-shirts and stuff. And once again, thank you
very much for participating and staying subscribed to the show. I sure will. And I'll tell everybody.
All right, buddy. All right. Thank you. Thank you. Okay. Have yourself, have yourself a great,
great evening or great day and, uh, we'll, uh, we'll get stuff off to you and we'll hook up for a
cup of coffee one day. Oh, that's a good cool. That's cool. All right. Hi, everybody. This is Andy from the
polar bear podcast. Now, I've noticed that people have some really strange ideas about my home
come through Sweden. So I thought a straighter things out a bit and killed some of those myths
you might have heard. But that's not all I do on the polar bear podcast. I also deliver some
strange and design news from over here and give you an idea how odd people sometimes behave
in this country. And then of course, I have a little music review section. Sometimes I do interviews
without coming artists who I think to serve a little more extra airtime. Anyway, if you're curious
about the exotic life in Sweden, you should definitely check out the polar bear podcast. Subscribe
through iTunes or on the website at polar bearpodcast.com. Now let's get back to the show again.
So this is Andy, signing off. I had another straight writer over at Rutgers Ramlin's podcast.
The podcast that features entertainment, politics, and pop culture all in one half hour show.
Now some of our recent topics have been the war on terror, the war on Christmas, and the war on
Hillary Clinton, which my opinion has been a very good war. And so I also liked to balance that
off with some entertainment news and pop culture items. I've talked about one of the 80s TV shows
called WizKids and also one of my favorite television shows that I was personally involved in
Babylon 5. And I've recently begun using a piece of software that you know gas blaster and get
hang of it and really like it. So once again, please check me out at RutgersRamlin's.com. That's
our UTT-ERS Ramlin's.com.
Hi, I'm Ninja, the host of the Hot Fossils in Rubble Matter Show. I give you 15 give or take minutes of
fun-filled observations, commentary, reviews, performance pieces, and sometimes interviews.
Sometimes serious, sometimes not, sometimes hot. I invite you to try it out. That's the Hot Fossils
and Rubble Matter Show at HotFRM.lognatrix.com. I'm also listed on www.qpater.org. Give it a try.
I'd love to spend some time with you.
Got me, yeah, I've been. Love to spend some time with you, too. Hold on a second. Damn.
Sometimes these audio comments are just so soft and volume. It's impossible to get them all right.
Okay, there you go. So I was pretty happy with the results of our golden ticket and we're going
to start thinking about more ways to utilize this and we'll probably do some more testing. If you
got any ideas, let me know. It's always fun to try new stuff out. And I was also pretty happy with
the Skype call. That kind of worked, too. Here our dog is really happy. We're leaving. He's barking
all day. Our little dog is a little Yorkshire last night. We were looking for him. We couldn't find him.
He was actually in the suitcase. In the suitcase. I'm coming with you guys, right? We've never been
away from him for 10 days. We can't take him with us because if you leave the country, then it's
another six months and all kinds of blood tests and crap before you can bring a dog back in.
So poor little survivor. I was going to actually try to get another Skype call going because I
finally got a real conversation going with Brad Zutout from Pod to Mob. It started off on, you know,
we finally just connected on him. I don't know. I think that he didn't receive some of my emails.
I mean, that's completely possible. Whatever happened there. That's, you know, how that should
go with the communications these days with busy people. But we did have a pretty good dialogue on
on the email and I said, you know, dude, we got to come on the show. Let's talk about this stuff.
And Brad, of course, agreed now. He's in out on the west coast and he has some personal
shit going on. Some of his is ill. So, you know, he couldn't, he couldn't get to a phone or a
Skype or anything when I want to do it to yesterday. And of course, because of the nine hour
time difference is just not going to work out. We really wanted to get this going now. But it just
unfortunately just didn't work out. But I have to say that after, after some, some back and forth
on the email, I don't think these guys are evil. I think that actually, I think that they're very
very enthusiastic. Have some pretty good ideas. I'd actually like to try and, I mean, this is,
this is how I started out with him. The first email I sent was, okay, you know, maybe we can work
together, maybe something we can do. And then after I didn't hear back, I started to get pretty
huffy. And he's, I got to say, he seems like a pretty cool guy. And he says that they actually
started the whole project because they were fans of the Charlie and a couple other shows and
they just wanted to be able to hear it on their cell phones. And I said, okay, look, then
put me back in the directory, make me available again, the daily source code, but don't insert
any ads. You could certainly say, you know, this, you're hearing this podcast, thanks to
Pod to Mob technology or whatever, I'm all fine with that. And then when I get back, we'll continue
the conversation. I think, you know, he may still be thinking a little bit differently from,
from the way we're thinking, but at least we can have a real grown-up conversation about it.
So I'm very, very happy. And I'm sorry I'm going away. I just, I, I really can't get into this
in the next 10 days. So I'm going to hang back and think that, you know, we'll actually,
we'll actually be able to work some cool stuff out and get everyone on the same page here.
Those of you checking us out on Syria stars 102, you'll be hearing best of Charlie's, I guess,
for for the next week and a half. And of course, PCH is up next. You guys have a great weekend,
and then I'll see it in about two weeks. And those of you still listen to the podcast.
Let me just continue with that Pod to Mob. So anyway, maybe this maybe Brad just isn't a great
communicator on the boards and stuff like that, but on email he's saying he seemed okay. So
I'm going to neutralize my, my feelings. And when I get back, hopefully we'll have a longer
conversation. And in the meantime, I just have to say from everything that I've received and
the communication I've had, they don't see me, well, they seem very enthusiastic. And I think that we,
we actually might be able to get something really good out of this. Because at the end of the day,
I have received emails from people who, who actually said, you know, dude, we, we really
use that stuff. We can't receive podcasts here in the office because the, the network is,
doesn't allow, you know, MP3s and huge downloads and stuff like that. So it's been kind of a
a way to get to the shows anyway. So we don't want a lot of people out. We just want to make sure that we
have an agreement over, you know, who, who can do what to, to what stuff. So looking forward to.
Yeah. And curious, Metro's sexual moment. Just wanted to say that we will, of course,
be giving away the key span AV dock for the iPod and the AV RF remote. I'm going to send that
off to to can as well, along with his iPod. And if the first golden ticket is actually discovered,
well, we still have that key span AV dock for the iPod and the AV RF remote. For you,
if you discover that golden ticket, be the, the ticket was issued to someone using a juice receiver
by the way. So if you're using juice, you might want to check it and see, see if there's a little
present for you. It's the Metro sexual moment. This is where we, this is where we throw down
the guys, you know, we talk about guy stuff that we're kind of embarrassed to talk about face to face
around the water cooler and you know what's really cool? The chicks are checking it. Hi Adam,
this is a great team with a comment or the Metro sexual moment. You talked about getting rid of
body here lately, but I feel you've left out in areas that's kind of important. Don't stop
it's another region while you're grooming. Take a trip on us, can't on and visit the underarms too.
That hair traps oil, dirt, sweat, and germs, leading not just something pretty gross to look at.
But to some pretty serious challenges, the modern theater technology as well. Women generally have
a fairly sensitive sense of smell. So there's something nice for us. Maybe we'll do something nice
for you. That's the first time I've heard a woman say take a trip up town. I agree.
And you know what I usually use for that? I usually steal my wife's lady shave and just kind of
just kind of sip away there because you're right. It is a sweat trap. And indeed, modern
theater technology has a hard time with that. By the way, I'm using acts these days because
you know, it gives you all the chicks, right? Yo, Adam. Trucker Tom here. Voiding dry skin seems to be
a major Metro sexual moment, topic of choice. I'm a big believer in the power of proper nutrition.
I've void dry skin by taking something called essential fatty acid nutritional supplements.
And this made a huge difference. If one has dry crack skin or even occasional tang nails,
one has an essential fatty acid deficiency. Chronic dry crack skin problems can be cured in about
two weeks with the daily dose of essential fatty acid nutritional supplements. And keep this in mind
if your skin is cracking on the outside, something is likely cracking on the inside as well.
Here's a testimony to our podcasting in the internet. A truck driver that I'd never met
before came and knocked on my trucks door shortly after I parked in a small Ohio truck stop a few
days ago. He not only knew my name, but he knew a lot about me because he had listened to most of
my podcasts and seen my pictures and video podcasts on the internet. Is a video version of
Casplaster possible? The answer is yes. There's an existing piece of video editing software
that's been around a few years called serious magic visual communicator. And that's at seriousmagic.com.
It enables real-time video recording to wind us PC in the style of the newscast with the timeline
and the integrated teleprompter. It's possible to integrate audio, video, and still image files
into the timeline as you record video in real time from a camera. You can find me at truckartom.pocho.com
and truckartphoto.com. I can't say tailwind since I'm a truck driver and not a pilot. However,
I can say biowinds or tailpipe. That would work too. Trucker Tom, thank you very much, dude.
By the way, on the Casplaster video, a Casplaster mic really is working on that. He's got ideas. He's
off, he's been programming all week in his little cottage. If you listen to the daily breakfast,
we're father Roderick interviewed him. And thank you very much for chatting. You know what's
frequently out as you talked about, if your skin's cracking on the outside, just imagine what's cracking
on the inside. Oh, man. Yes, this and many more handy tips. On the daily source codes,
heterosexual moment. Hi Adam, this is American Matt from the wannabe podcast of for God and
Country. And I've been following the conversation about contracts. Now, I am not an attorney,
nor do I play one on TV, but I am a law student and I have had contracts. And I think part of the
problem here is that people are fearful of what they don't understand. And what people don't get
is that a contract is just a starting point. When an organization like yours sends someone
a contract, of course, it's going to be a wrote form contract to save you guys a lot of trouble.
And you kind of know the base point where you want to start. But people don't get that this is just
an offer. And then from there, the conversation opens up. They read it. They say what they like.
They say what they don't like. They say what's missing. And a conversation happens and a relationship
is established and ultimately through a negotiation process, they have the freedom to change
the contract around. See, if you guys can come up to something that works for everyone,
or not. And I'm a think that part of the problem is people seem to think that because you're the
pod father, you're the god father. And what you say goes and that contract is it, it's wrote,
it's written in blood and they've got to sign their solo way. Which, well, I don't know about the whole
signing away of the soul. I've heard a few things. But it would just thought I'd like to clarify
for some of your listeners that contracts are never written in stone. Even God knew that because
Moses broke that one. Have a great day. Bye. All right. Just one one misconception. I want to
clear up about that. Oh, man. All this writing on the internet. A contract does not. I repeat
does not state we own your stuff. Okay. And just doesn't say that. Whatever interpretation you
hear from anyone, it's not what it says. All right. I got to get off. I got to get out. I got to get off.
Yeah. I got to get off too. But I also have to get out of here. And I want to leave you with a song
that I've played before that I really, I really like this band. I love this song just to death.
It's a relatively new on the pod safe music network. And what's interesting about this is
I was setting up Patricia's computer downstairs so she could listen to my shows when I'm
in San Francisco because it turns out she doesn't listen because it's not it's intimidating
to her. So I like that because a lot of the stuff that we're developing that we're going to be
releasing just about a couple days after I get back from from holidays is going to solve all that.
It's going to take away the intimidation factor. Make it much easier for you to listen to podcasts.
Remember, we're about listeners primarily. Yes, lots of good tools and stuff for podcasts.
But we've really focused a hell of a lot of attention on making the listening and discovery
experience much, much better and the interaction with the podcast. So that's pod show applause and you'll
see that around the same time frame. We're trying to get it just in time for tax day, April 15th.
And Christina was looking over our shoulder and up in the dashboard popped up the show and it's
and started playing and Christina was looking at the show notes. She said, thank oh Jones. I know them.
Said really. She said, yeah, yeah, I've known for them. I know about them for like five six
months. I love them. And then she immediately went back to her own computer and emailed me two
tracks that she's that she had. So now I know I'm on to something. And you hear a lot about, you know,
the the big success of my space is Arctic monkeys. It's like is the same thing at the Guardian Media
Conference. That's all that seems like the only thing that can talk about is someone broke out and
and now is successful for thanks to my space. Well, I think we're going to see a lot more of success
like that. And I think that these guys, these guys could be one of the next big smash hits coming
out of the pot safe music scene. Dango Jones. First day. Oh, you might want to crank it up because it's
ready. First date. Electricity. When you walk in, you see my circuit tree. Back it up. We
out of two. When people swear that out, you always play cool. I think I know you. I'm going
to make you look super junk and don't get your quick fix. In my car, you've got a sweet tooth and
I'm your titlic boy. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, oh, no, no, no... no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, we just absolutely
The catwalk, I like to play it to squid
You won't be wanna show, spray paint your
Touching your
And cruise yourself, it don't be wrong
So take a chance, give me a shot
You think I'm bluffing, I think I'm not
Get on your hideeal, give me a heart attack
I got a question for your sweet ass
Oh no, no, no, no ooooh no no
And now say hey
Do your kiss of a first name
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, okay, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Oh, danko Jones, if you're a WrestleMania fan this weekend according to CC Chapman from
accident hash, one of danko's songs is going to play over the opening credits of WrestleMania.
So congratulations to the guys and I hope you have that kind of first date tonight, a good
one.
I'm going out on the town.
I'm really going to try and stay away from the podcast.
I have a feeling that somewhere made a week, we might do some kind of video thing just
to show you that we're having a good time and to check in.
It's very, very, very hard for me to unwaan, but I plan on spending a lot of fun time
with the girls.
Swimming, sun, surf, maybe I'll even try some golf, that seems to be what everyone does
in Portugal.
So, of course, I'd like to check in every single day with Gmail to delete stuff, so
that stuff doesn't start bouncing.
Hey, everybody, where's my, where's my lighter?
Now here it is.
Hey, thank you very much for, for checking us out, stay subscribed because eventually
stuff will just show up automatically.
That's the beauty of all of this podcasting.
So, it's daily source code.com to check out all the new shows.
Keep your eye on podshow.com, stuff is going to start changing right before you very
guys.
And when I get back, well, man, we'll be ready to go public beta with podshow plus than
the podshow podcast delivery network.
I'll miss you guys.
Bye.
Another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery
network from podshow and limelight networks.
I love it.