Think Advertising sucks.
Think you can do better?
Pod Show and EarthLink are willing to put our money where your mouth is.
Listen to this podcast or go to adchelens.podshow.com to see how you can win big
in the EarthLink make advertising better challenge.
And now, brothers, are reading from the book of Charlie.
Chapter 400.
And RSS was upon the face of the net.
And it was good.
Then did Dave create the enclosure tag?
And it was very good.
And Adam looked upon the enclosures and commanded that they should move in an automatic
fashion onto the iPod which the prophet Steve of Cupertino had cast upon a land like white
grains of sand.
And the enclosures to look at him and say,
yeah, right.
And so Adam did write the script that would compel the enclosures onto his pod of eye.
And it was good.
But Adam knew it could be better.
And so he cast his source code out onto the net and set onto developers
hardy upon my code that would me all be able to benefit from a better file
catcher and put onto eye powder.
And the developers did party on the code.
And the code was pretty good.
And the developers said upon to Adam,
send us content so we might test the code.
And so Adam sent them content on the first day in the second day and so forth.
And on the sixth and the seventh day he rested.
And yet still he called his content the daily source code.
And loaded the pod catchers go forth upon the net and use them to obtain the content
and listen to it upon their computers.
And their CD players and their iPods and their eye rivers and so on.
And thus the daily source code became the place where users and developers
party together.
And there was no need for transmitters.
And the people rose up and declared,
we don't need no sticking transmitters.
Then did the users send their own content to Adam.
And some of it was good.
And the piloted state upon to the world with 16 million dollars of our planes
strapped to my ass and the next generation of radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
And so the daily source code grew.
And then Adam did drink of the secrets and sails.
And then did he belch upon the mic and invoke the names and sails.
And thus the people get the names and sails in their heads every time.
One of their numbers burped up on the land.
And it came to pass that Adam did call his old friend Ron
and get a field gang together and create pod show.
And the daily source code continued to grow.
And in growing its name the shrink.
And it became known as the DSC.
And in the language of the tribe of the pilots.
It was called the Delta and Sierra and Charlie.
And the people who had the iPod known as the shuffle did cry out and sound
to Adam.
Who is us?
Or we do not know which episode we are listening to.
Since we lacked the display upon which to read a file name.
And thus did Adam count the number of the Delta Sierra Charlie at the beginning of the show.
And it was good.
And then did Patricia and Christina visit upon the Charlie.
And it was even better.
And Ron and Adam gathered the content and the hosts and their shows from all the corners of the net.
And put them upon the pod show network.
I put silly ads upon them.
And it was good.
But the ads were bad.
And so the users created their own ads.
And then it was good.
And the people who were busy and liked the abbreviations called upon Adam.
And it referring to his show they called it the Charlie or the Jia Jia or the Carlos.
And then the counting of the Charlie reached 20 score minus 1.
And seeing that the Charlie would reach the milestone of 20 score or 390 and 9 and 1 more.
Did I create this program to celebrate the anniversary of the Daily Source code?
And thus did I scan the way to be the one to say Delta Sierra Charlie or zero zero.
And it was good.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need lost thinking turns, man.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm testing this battle curry.
Oh, where you're gonna go?
Now that's so town's gone.
How you're gonna do?
What has been so one done?
What you're gonna hit right at that tip?
The Larry essence of cool.
In streets I didn't fly.
I still ain't your eye.
For you I know that it's true.
It's my eye for the know.
What you're gonna say?
When they talk it down.
That I'd be covered today.
It wasn't nothing, nothing but a plane change.
You don't say so town's the way it's on.
That it be.
And someday we'll build it all again.
When we've had enough of this empty day.
The fact you murdered this holy man
will start a fresh crazy event.
When you're gonna see that so town's dead.
And all those beautiful people you used to know.
Well they ain't so fair.
When you're right at high.
You're new for the skies.
Just being like once you're grown.
With one bringing your heart something that came.
You thought that you'd better change in the world.
You'll say so town's the way it is.
But it makes you new.
Some day we'll build it all again.
When we've had enough of this empty day.
The fact you murdered this holy man will start a fresh crazy event.
Well they ain't so fair.
When you're gonna see that so town's dead.
Now that's so town's gone.
Just being like once you're grown.
I'm talking about so town's dead.
Because so town's gone.
But there's those crazy clothes to guess the way.
Flows in your head.
And your peace sides everywhere.
They don't back in so town's dead.
Nobody's telling what happened.
All those dreams are peaceful.
And understand it and hide it.
And rub it.
Now I want to be in the game.
Have I ever heard of it?
Don't let see this old town.
Showtime which is born.
You're not the one.
Just being like once you're grown.
That's for mellow start of your Charlie.
After all the show is 400.
How are you doing everybody?
It is Delta Sierra Charlie.
Daily source code episode number 400 coming to you from the Curry Cottage in the
affluent suburb of Seri known as Gilford.
And kicking it off was a long song.
That was long.
I finished my sense sale before the song was even over.
I'm sure I'm bordering this.
Anabule is what I'm going to say.
From the podcast music network reading from his bio.
Ola.
It's considered to be the UK's finest sold singer songwriters and performs over 100
shows a year in the UK island in Europe.
He's emerged as an artist of distinction.
Honing is writing in production skills at the same time evolving into a passionate
and committed performer.
I don't know man.
Sounded like Michael McDonald to me, but I liked it.
And thank you very much Howard Greenstein for the opening there of number 400.
That was also long.
Those two combined really helped us and say oh intake.
And I just wanted to mention that Howard's nephew Sawyer is in hospital recovering from a spinal injury.
It has been able to move from the hips down for two and a half weeks and I quite sure what happened.
He's 12 years old and it would be cool if you sent him a little message.
You can do that at getwellsoyer.com show notes will contain the link as always.
So I'm about on time today recording the show.
And of course you could be listening to this on serious stars 102 or hopefully you're listening to it as a podcast.
400 episodes.
If you lay them all out back to back and you play this show every single day, seven days a week,
13 months I think is how long it would take for you to listen to every single one of them.
And Patricia's like wow that's cool congratulations.
What is 400?
I wasn't going to do anything with people start sending me all this 400 show stuff, which I really appreciate of course.
But yeah, it was like we did it at 100 and 200, which was nomed X and 250.
You can do it at 250, you can do it 400, you can do it five.
Who cares?
Just the fact that you guys are listening and subscribe, that's all that I care about.
Hey, as I'm leaf and portion fifth, just wanted to congratulate you on your 400 show.
Long time childlessness since 1997.
I thought I sent you this feedback on Friday.
So by the time I guess to choose day you should have catch up on all your GML and voice mouths.
All right, cheers.
Oh, was that the UK version of the lighter click?
That's your drug of choice.
Thank you very much, buddy.
Adam, good morning.
It's you clocked, levy.
Oh, he's tired.
Like, what am I like?
Five minutes into TSC 399 and I just heard the Kabel song.
And I've heard you mentioned me.
And the email that I sent, thank you so much.
And man, that pronunciation was unbelievable of my first name.
I'm guessing that is a combination of you knowing Dutch and having that sound,
and probably hearing my previous audio comes.
I don't think you'd actually ever mentioned me on the show before,
but that sent you a couple of comments before.
So you've obviously heard them.
Appreciate that very much.
Keep up the fantastic work.
I am super even more inspired now to really get that the podcast going.
Keep it up and the best to Christina and Patricia and all of us.
Pretty mom as well.
Thanks man.
Bye.
Alright, you've thought.
Yep.
And you met her back.
Start.
You've read.
You've thought.
And yeah, I grew up growing up in the Netherlands.
You get that sound, which is not a very pretty sound.
But it is very distinct.
And in fact, in the second world war,
it was often used to see if you were really one of the good guys.
A Dutch person would ask you to say groaning.
Growning was really the one, which is a place in the north of the Netherlands.
Kind of like the way the Yanks would say,
who won the World Series?
You know, to see if you were truly an American,
the Dutch youth sound check.
And you can tell.
You can tell if a German person does it because they do it a little bit differently.
And I would say probably Dutch and Yiddish are very close to each other.
But that's a very distinct sound.
So thank you very much for the voicemail.
If you want to send a message in,
we've got a number New Jersey 2016256357.
Because you can take the boy out of Jersey,
but you can't take Jersey out of the boy.
And if you're in London, or if you're in Europe and want to use the London number,
although I think that even with Skype out,
you're going to find the Jersey numbers cheaper.
It's 02076813753.
Put me in your phone.
Okay, just put the number in.
Here it is.
1216256357.
Okay.
Add to address books.
See?
That wasn't too hard.
No was it.
So I've maintained my presence on Windows,
although I've done a little more studying
as to what exactly the differences are between Mac.
And it's not just the OS, the operating system.
It's also the hardware itself.
And of course Apple has a great connection between the hardware and the operating system.
And many pieces of software because they really control a lot of those pieces of what
becomes a PC, a personal computer.
And of course with the Windows, there are different,
they're even different processors, of course.
You can use different versions.
Got Intel and AMD.
It says it.
Ah.
This is a moment brought to you by the Gilmore gang.
So what exactly are those differences?
Well, let me tell you what.
First of all, before I even get into differences,
here's one thing I hate about Windows.
I hate it when you install a piece of software.
And it decides that it's going to become your default piece of software for particular file type.
And this happens most mainly with MP3s.
Anything that you install or auto install,
thank you very much.
Another thing I don't like about these PC manufacturers.
It auto installs.
You know, then all the icons change.
And yeah, you can set it back to,
oh, I like stuff opening in quick time.
I don't want things opening in iTunes.
And I certainly don't want stuff opening in the hell.
Is this piece of crap?
Hold on.
Let me see.
What is it called?
I thought it was open.
Hold on.
Let me see.
It is.
I see a piece of crap.
I hate that.
Music, melody, maintainer or something like that.
And it makes all the MP3 icons in a little stupid icon.
That I really dislike.
Really dislike it.
Ask me.
Please ask me if you can be the default.
Don't just do it.
So here's some really simple differences that I noticed.
First of all, the layout of the desktop.
And although it's very obvious.
And I'm sure you've seen this before.
And you, I don't know if we even talk about it anymore.
With a Mac, your hard drive or what on the windows would be.
My computer is located in the upper right hand corner of the screen.
On windows, it's on the upper left hand corner of the screen.
And your stuff starts building up left.
Whereas on the Mac, it starts building up on the right.
So the most obvious change is to just shift that stuff over to the right.
And that's what I'm trained to do.
I'm trained to go to my computer in the upper right hand corner.
So yeah, even though I was building, you know, new neural neural networks in my brain
by remembering to go left.
Screw that man.
I put it all up on the right.
The task bar is the other main difference.
And I found this wonderful utility called.
But the heck is it called?
Object doc.
Oh, yes.
A very commercial name.
However, what it does is it simulates the OS XOS 10 doc at the bottom of your screen.
And it removes the task bar.
And you get all of the same functionality that you're used to with the doc on the Mac.
And that's also something that, you know, I really missed.
It's trained to go down there to launch my applications.
I don't want to go to a start menu.
I don't want to go to the desktop.
The desktop is my workplace.
I don't want filling up with icons to start stuff.
Another thing I'm not too keen about, which happens automatically all too often.
In fact, even cast blaster does that.
By the way, using the new version of cast blaster with audio plus,
very interesting concept.
Then the, I guess the downside to Mac versus PC is really the way stuff feels and looks or looks and feels.
And let me elaborate just a little bit.
The feeling is, I'm talking about the mouse, you know, how the trackpad works and how it scrolls across the screen.
It just feels a little more.
I don't know.
A little more cheap.
I can't explain exactly what that means, but just feels kind of cheap.
However, it's really fast.
The same goes for the display.
I have a beautiful LG monitor.
And, you know, the colors are great and the brightness is there.
But it's, it's still the Mac just has a better display technology.
Of course, things do go just a little bit slower on the Mac.
They render a little bit slower on the screen.
Just displaying stuff.
I can tell.
It just takes less time on windows.
Same for scrolling and moving stuff up and down.
And I can only presume the reason for that is that Apple sacrificed a little bit of speed for all the beautiful pieces.
Which, of course, in the long run when we have computers that are so powerful that the user experience will always be a continuous snap.
You know, then it'll be nice to have a beautiful, beautiful view, beautiful feel.
Just have everything feel luxurious, but still have the same speed that Windows has today.
I think we're probably still a long way off from that.
Because I've played with a couple of the Mac books, which, of course, Intel based.
And, you know, now you're really competing with the same type of processor.
And it is just slower.
And so, if anything, I'm liking the speed of it.
I'm getting used to the kind of cheap feel.
I can't, I hate to say that way.
I can't quite explain it, but it just, yeah, it feels cheap.
And otherwise, I don't miss too much, honestly.
So, I think what I'm going to do is continue on Windows.
And I will take the power book back to the Mac store in San Francisco when I'm there.
Which should be Tuesday.
And by the way, thank you, IJ, who left a comment at curry.com about the, uh, was about object doc.
Because that is indeed one of the, one of the things that I just really, really missed.
Quick little Trinity update, of course, you should know as a listener to the daily source code.
The Trinity is my Mercedes station wagon diesel 300 turbo diesel, I should say.
Um, which is eggnog colored.
And, which actually has its own theme song.
It's only one thing we might as well sing along.
So, I'll send this link, let me see, uh, who sent it to me here.
Martin Wright.
And it's about challenge X, a three year competition sponsored by General Motors,
the US Department of Energy and other industry leaders.
17 teams will re-engineer a GM equinox, which is a crossover sport utility vehicle,
to minimize energy consumption emissions and greenhouse gases while maintaining or exceeding the vehicles utility performance.
Well, engineering students at the University of California Davis have unveiled their entry.
It's powered by electric motors and a small internal combustion engine that can run on gasoline or ethanol.
So, they're looking it up to, uh, what they're saying here.
Up to 40 miles running on battery power and then another 40 miles on the internal combustion engine.
And that's all cool, you know, so it's a, it's a very environmentally friendly vehicle,
but they've named it Trinity.
Oh, I'm sorry, but I do have a slight problem with this.
Well, I feel that we have some kind of branded trademark on Trinity and certainly have prior art to show forward.
I, you know, it's, I don't care if they, well, if they call it Trinity, they have to at least say that there is an original,
the OG of the TD, Trinity.
No, I'm saying, oh, how come that didn't work?
Crap.
I'm supposed to fire automatically.
Yeah, right.
Though G Trinity, right, yeah.
Still episode number 400.
Adam, it's Derek Kay Miller from the Penn Machine podcast.
I haven't left you an audio comment in a while, but I wanted to be there early in the morning for you,
because it's late at night here in Vancouver, and it's early in England,
and I wanted to say congratulations on the daily source code,
the Delta CR Charlie, the Charlie, the Carlos,
Wat Throciento's number 400.
How about that?
I've got a little story for you, actually.
The first podcast I ever heard was DSC number 200 that you did live at Nomdex last year,
and I wasn't listening on my iPod, and I wasn't listening on my computer.
I was there in the audience, and I was looking up there on the stage and going,
what the hell is this?
But I came around within a few days.
I was taking the songs that I was recording, and I was posting them on my own podcast,
and then I put them on the pod safe music network.
And over the past year, I've had hundreds and hundreds of podcasts use that music,
and I've had thousands of people here of them.
And you know what?
Not long after that, I started getting the editor's association I belonged to,
into podcasting, and then earlier this year, my wife started her own podcast over at lip gloss and laptops,
and just recently, I came on board as the new co-host of Inside Home Recording.
I can't believe it.
Suddenly, I'm Mr. Podcast Guy.
I'm like the podcast expert.
People have had me come talk about podcasting, and last year I didn't even know what was going on.
So, thanks, because I don't know if it would have happened if I hadn't been sitting there at Nomdex,
with you doing DSC number 200.
So, here's to 400, and here's to many hundreds more.
Although, of course, it might be the Patricia and the Guy show now.
Anyway, great job, and I hope we'll see you at Nomdex this year.
My wife's coming to it's like a Miller podcast frenzy there.
Talk to you later.
To Patricia came in.
She sticks her head around the door and just stands there.
And of course, there's nothing. You can't hear anything.
And did this.
Yeah, and I said, yeah, it's great.
And then you just stood there.
I'm like, what are you going to come in?
So, yeah, can I just sit here and drink my cup of tea?
I'm like, no, I don't want an audience behind me.
I just made myself a nice cup of tea.
I see a man standing in his underwear here.
I'm not in my underwear.
I enjoy my cup of tea and enjoy my husbands's body.
I'm a half half.
What are we calling?
We call it a weekend baker's outfit.
What?
You called it something, you're...
I mean, someone had a question about that.
Hold on a second.
Where was it?
Dave Crossfire.
I couldn't make out the clothing articles in the podcast
and can't find the text in the show notes.
You said you wear boxers and what?
It sounded like wife beaters.
Yeah.
Yeah, wife beaters.
Is that a wife beaters?
Yeah, so if you've ever watched cops...
It's always a man who wears that.
Every single guy who's beating up his wife wears one of these t-shirts.
You know, just with the straps.
Yeah.
That's a wife beater.
That's what dawn from dawn.
Yeah, they move easier in it.
Yeah, you'll beat your wife more easily.
She'd take note of that.
Yeah, right.
So...
So I said, if you want to come in, then you have to say,
you can't just sit here and drink your tea and do nothing.
I'll charge money for that.
Like some people I know who won't do anything unless they make money for you.
Yeah, right.
Uh-huh.
Exactly.
So this is show number...
You know what?
Through all this, I miss the satellite window.
Grape.
Oh, you did?
Yeah.
And now?
Well, I'll make it 49 minutes.
You slipped out of that.
Yeah, I flipped out.
Okay.
This is my 400's show and everyone sent it.
I know.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Mr. Adam Curry.
Yeah.
So you're going to continue to come on the shisha?
Now, and then, you know, there are people who want to hear you on your own too.
No, they're all right.
It sounds like sounds like everybody just wants you.
I read it.
Like Lady Patricia and the guy show.
Why?
Right.
Like I've nothing else to do.
Oh, excuse me.
Mommy.
I know you.
I need to be sure there's...
That's right.
Give me someone coffee.
I was right.
Take care of you guys.
You know.
Okay.
And I'm going to London tonight.
Yes, you are.
It's not a great thing overnight.
Meetings all day tomorrow.
Isn't it cool that we're setting up an office here?
Oh, it's so cool because I was thinking
when you are going to the office here in there and now and then.
Yeah.
And then, yeah.
Have a re-went.
Yes, I'll go with you.
Oh, really?
Not through the office, but I'll go and have an eye.
Come and clean.
Come and clean my desk.
I don't have to go by myself in the train.
Okay.
Oh, that's cool.
And I'll get that's a boring part.
But then we also want to go if I leave it like,
leave it like 7.30 in the morning or 8 o'clock really?
Sure.
Uh-huh.
Well, if it's very cold, I don't know, but I'm up anyway for it.
No, I'm up anyway for Christina, so.
I'm glad you're here because I got a note from Ulrich, Ulrich Pulsin.
Yeah, Ulrich?
Ulrich.
And he sent me a link to a BBC series.
Is it Ulrich?
It probably is, let me say.
No, it's Ulrich.
With a cake.
Okay.
Ulrich.
Ulrich Pulsin.
Uh-huh.
And it said, did you read about, you must have read this in the paper, the Chris Moiles, who's
the number one morning radio show host here.
He had used the word gay.
It was something about, um, see if I, uh, he had said about a ringtone.
Uh, he said, I don't want this one, it's gay.
And so there are a whole bunch of complaints.
And of course, this relates exactly to that whole, you know, common, that back and
forth thing, that back and forth thing that I had with Madge or Richard actually, back
and forth thing.
I believe these sort of remarks.
It's so yeah.
Well, anyway, so the B, then you can analyze everything, just if you say, back and forth
is, uh, that's gay.
So, hey, would you please not record the studio?
Sorry.
It's already hanging together with Gaffer tape and bailing wire.
Um, so anyway, so the complaints went to the, uh, what they called, the Board of Governors,
who, I guess, like the people who make all the decisions at the BBC because they take
a recomplaint seriously, I presume.
And they said, it was not homophobic because the word gay now means rubbish in modern playground
speak and need not be offensive to homosexuals, according to the BBC Board of Governors.
And what if they say so then then it's, it's, it's that way, baby.
It's a truth.
So here, so, and then the BBC publishes the history of the word gay.
That's kind of it.
Happy.
Belief to be derived from the old French guy, GAI, the Latin guy is, or a Germanic source,
originally meant carefree, happy, or bright, and showy, gay, basically.
From the late 17th century, it acquired sexual connotation of uninhibited by moral constraints.
That sounds like me.
Then Gertrude Stein's, Ms. Fur and Ms. Scheme from 1922, cited as first published reference
to ambiguous sexuality, that Noel Coward pens tribute to dandies of the gay 90s, wearing
green carnations in 1929's musical, bitter sweet.
Then it was used to describe foppish dress code unattached men or bachelors, until adopted, adopted
by homosexuals themselves in the 1960s.
I didn't know that.
Originally used as an adjective, as in He is gay, the word is adopted as a singular noun.
I am the only gay in the village, it actually says it right there, that's funny.
Then you only gay in the village, you know.
So it went from an adjective, you know, an adjective, as a word that describes it, what
do you call that in Dutch and by fucho-gnau-mort?
Yeah.
How old are you?
Is that right?
Yeah.
To self-standach, noun-bort, a singular noun.
And then children, students, use gay as shorthand for rubbish, don't use bewordleck, bewordleck
have you in bewordleck?
I don't know.
That's all conjugation.
I can now come bewordleck, macho-gnau-mort, the benek fucho-gnau-mort, what do you
do?
OK.
You're speaking in tongues.
Children and students now use gay as shorthand for rubbish during the 1990s.
And now, at the end of this, it's a BBC by the way.
Bloggers substitute gay for boring or dull, reversing the original meaning.
Yeah.
How, I mean, that's how language changes.
Yep.
Isn't that in a language language?
Oh, it changes so much, because you can say something and people will look at you
like that stupid, because you mean something else.
It goes really, really fast, listening to your daughter, you can hear that.
Oh, my God.
Well, the changes faster than I can print pages for her art homework.
That's for sure.
No, no.
They're talking about the mallet.
Yeah, the mallet is back, and they like that.
And it's cool.
It's cool.
Can you believe that?
Yeah.
And we used to have that painting that, yeah, the made me look like Barry Manillow
with a mallet.
We can hang it up again, because now it's good.
Exactly.
I hate that painting.
I love it because you gave it to me.
Oh, it's a sweet.
It was, it makes me look like Barry Manillow with a mallet.
Well, it was a little Chinese guy, New York.
Let's face it.
I am Barry Manillow with a mallet.
I saw him painting and he did it really quickly, really fast.
I mean, and I said, can you, I had to sort of cover from a magazine, but the two of us,
yeah, when we left for America.
It was a picture from Hovert de Roast.
Yes, no, no, no, no.
Yes, it was.
It was exactly.
It was not from the paparazzi or anything.
So I, and he copied that, but in his own way, you look like Barry Manillow
with a mallet.
So somebody who came to a house said, what are you doing with Barry Manillow?
It's crazy.
Stroking his mallet.
It was so funny.
But the mallet is bad.
The mallet is bad.
The mallet is long enough.
I need a mallet song.
Jeff, make me a mallet song.
We need that.
So funny.
Oh, and the kids, and I know now why she was so grumpy the last couple of weeks.
So Christina?
Yeah, yeah.
I noticed a couple of pieces of paper in her waist basket and I could see here
in there.
You read her, of course, fondness that she threw out.
No, no, no, no, she always writes little.
What do you mean, no, no?
And then she throws it away.
Did you read them?
Sometimes it just lays there.
So I thought, what is this?
And then you could see that she was actually, I am very grumpy the last couple of days
because she was very disappointed in that Jack.
You know, okay, that her parents, that his parents are taking him to Spain.
Yeah, but the way he reacted and suddenly said, well, it's over then because he doesn't
make any sense.
And, you know, it's not going anywhere so goodbye.
She was going through a self-help therapy.
I think so.
But I read some very wise words, very, but she was a bit disappointed and grumpy
from it.
So very understandable.
But you read her shit.
No, I didn't.
He did.
She said, just said, I read something.
But somebody has to clean it up.
But she is wise.
But then you understand it.
And then you see that there's a lot going on.
Yeah.
I have to, I have to do.
I mean, I felt bad for her when I heard about it, but you know, I don't think
it was a lot of time.
You know, and well, no one really told me the story about how he did it, I didn't get
that information.
That's why I'm glad I read it here and there, yeah, sometimes she writes it down
and throws it away or leaves it on her desk, you know.
But she doesn't, she doesn't, because sometimes she did you read that and I said, well,
yeah, you know, it was just there and she doesn't.
I'll tell you honestly, if she, if I had seen thrown out stuff in her way space, I probably
wouldn't have read it.
I just don't do that for anybody.
That's not specifically her.
I just don't do that.
No, I normally don't.
I mean, I could read all of her email and everything, I guess.
No, but I saw her writing a lot and I thought something's going on there.
She wanted.
I thought she was prepping for her show.
That too.
Yeah, that too.
Maybe she'll have some, but it's already over.
It's, it's healing, you know, these, it makes the, the, the, the, the, the, the morning,
I was grumpy because of her throwing, and actually the 11 pictures printed out and, of course,
the Mac is the only machine that was configured to the printer and that was broken.
And so I'm trying to print stuff and it's going really slow and download a driver, which
was going to take 20 minutes.
And she does everything, uh, less minutes and, you know, do you remember the last minute,
man?
Uh, no, refresh my memory.
That's you.
Sinbad.
You know, we had a song less minute, man.
Yes.
That's a good one.
Wait.
Ah, ah, ah.
Here we come.
Last minute.
Yeah.
And then there he is.
Who can do it later than anyone can?
Yeah.
So bad news for you, baby.
Oh, yeah.
Yep.
You know what starts this weekend?
Oh, football.
World cup soccer.
What would we have to see that one?
What one?
The one from England.
Is it England, Germany?
Yeah, but baby, hold on second.
I'd have to see that.
There's going to be games every single day.
Well, I'm saying bad bad news for you is because none of your TV shows will be on.
It'll all be football.
You don't care?
No.
Yeah.
You can watch.
Really?
You're not going to go like.
No, no.
I have a lot of magazines to read and playboy.
Maybe I can do some research on my computer.
Not?
Yeah.
Absolutely.
We know it.
When you're on your computer, all you have to do to keep up and be able to talk with
the neighbors is listening to this podcast.
Hi, Adam.
This is Phil.
We're from the Soccer Show podcast available at SoccerShow.com.
And we're going to give a quick preview of the upcoming World Cup.
The World Cup is being staged in Germany.
Kicks off on June the 9th and culminates in the final on July 9th.
The hot favorites are going to be Brazil, followed by England, Germany, Argentina, and Italy.
We also have our eye in Holland and France who are just outside that leading pack.
You can get odds of 66 to one against the USA winning, which reflects the difficulty of
their draw as much as the quality of their team.
So Tony, what are you going to be checking out this weekend?
I think Friday you've got to watch the opening game of the tournament.
Germany against Costa Rica, 12 new Eastern, on ESPN2, you've got to watch that first game.
It's a real potential banana skin for the host Germany.
They've got a lot of pressure on them and the crowd could turn against them if it doesn't
go their way.
Okay, Saturday I'm going to be checking out of course, England versus Paraguay, come
on England.
That kicks off 9 a.m. Eastern on ABC.
You've got to keep your eye on England, center forward, Peter Kraut.
He's six foot seven tall, conservatively 60% of which is neck.
If he scores, you'll see him do this crazy body popping robot dance celebration, which you do
not want to miss.
Well, I think if I've recovered from Peter Kraut's robot celebration, then I'm going to be
watching Serbia Montenegro against Holland, 90 A.M. Eastern on ESPN2 on Sunday, Holland might
up for the tournament or a really classy side with some outstanding attacking options.
Serbia Montenegro, SNM as they may be destined to be known or a decent side, but they're
going to have to be depain to make it out of group that also features South American legends
Argentina.
And that brings us to Monday and the USA versus the Czech Republic, that starts at noon
Eastern on ESPN2.
London, Donovan, and Democracy, easily offer their best chances of hitting the net.
An interesting matchup is going to be the towering Czech Straker Jan Kohler versus the
Man Mountain, a Gucci onaway in the heart of the American defense.
The soccer show is going to be produced in daily shows throughout the tournament.
We're going to discuss all the games that have been played, preview the upcoming games
and cover all the news and gossip as the tournament progresses.
We're going to be playing Listen of Oismail as well, so please feel free to contribute.
Check it out and add us to your subscription list wherever at soccershowt.com.
So you know, I don't give it a rat's ass about soccer, right?
I'm stupid because I said England Germany, but no, of course not.
You're not stupid.
You just don't know anything about sports.
Now, the Germany is the host.
Yes.
I thought England was also playing against it.
Well, they could.
It could one.
No, I don't think they're in the same pool.
I sure hope so.
I don't think they're in the same pool.
They're in the same pool.
That's what I heard.
So I'm not a big sports fan at all.
I don't give a rat's ass, but I love this.
These guys are going to send me two minute updates so that if you just want to keep up with
what's going on and what I like is anyone in Europe knows where they can see the game.
But this is they tell you when you can see it on in the states, which is kind of cool.
And they're going to give me updates.
You know, I don't need more than two minutes of it.
And just need to know which game I have to watch.
Because you're right, if England plays Germany, yeah, of course I'm watching.
And I'd like to watch how about Holland Brazil.
I think they have to play each other.
I think Brazil is going to kick their ass.
Do you think so?
Yeah.
But America is, is a long, is people.
America is a long shot favorite of mine.
I think America might actually do something this year.
We'll be kind of cool.
We'll be cool.
And there's more where that came.
Hi, this is Dave Lyfton of the soccer blockers.
And the best way to follow the action in Germany this summer is by joining us at the
World Cup Roundtable.
Every night America's top soccer bloggers will discuss the matches of the day.
We'll be the upcoming games in a whole lot more.
Come check us out at WorldCupRoundtable.logspot.com.
All right, there's even a pod safe song about it.
Really?
Yeah, and you should learn the words.
If you're rooting for England, it's called Come On England.
Thank you, you remember that.
In 66, when all of a way I wish I'd been alive to see that game, ever so big such
sense has come all the way.
We have the players, we knew what they could do, but they couldn't help us when World Cup
Roundtable, yeah, you're all England, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
No, you're not aware
Yeah, come on in one, yeah, yeah
Let's start our tune
Please bring back your mind with you
Yeah, come on in one, yeah, yeah
Let's start our tune
Please bring back your mind
I'm waiting here
You gotta walk up to a horse
And three lines on our chest
Cause we all know we are the best
We're gonna get this song played
I'm waiting here someday
Come on in one, yeah, you can play
Come on in one, yeah, yeah
Let's start our tune
Maybe she can't go on in one, yeah
Come on in one, yeah, yeah
Let's start our tune
Please bring back your mind
Okay, nice song
Sounds a bit a little bit like his head is stuck
In half of the ball or something
In half of what?
In the ball
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm tired, I'm tired
I love the lyrics
We'll drink a lot of beer
Yeah, yeah
Go on in England
This is the most important thing
From the bot pods I'm using that word
Listen to their bio, this is great
Started in April of 2004 testosterone
Who's with that call?
Was formed by the two guitarist Ian and Dave
When they wrote their first song Amy
Realizing that they needed more members
Hahaha
Dave and Ian asked their friend Jack to join
And completely line up with Nick on bass
Unfortunately Jack left the band in order to pursue his own career
That's in the bio, I love you guys
That is so funny
That's marketing
That's wonderful
That's good
The influences Blink 182
Nerf Herder
Bowling for soup
And Green Day
How old are we, babe?
I'm fucking older we now
Yeah, right
I just got some nerdy stuff to do
So you're welcome to hang around
But
No, I'm actually waiting for you
So I can do your hair
And then I can get the hell out
Yeah, I have to do some stuff
Alright, let me finish up
I've got a couple of nerdy stuff to talk about
My computer and stuff
Okay
Will anybody enjoy that?
Well
Yeah
That sounds good
Oh good
But the good thing about is if they don't
They can just fast forward
That's right
To the song at the end
Or they can fast forward through that
And that's the way to get rid of it
Out of your system
It's out of my system
Right
Out of my system
Have you been injured
Listening to average podcast
Have you been the victim of pod faders?
Have you been fraudulently induced to listen to a podcast
That has some standard pod safe music
And a really lame host
That I urge you to subscribe to the Jersey Todd Show
At www.JurzyTonShow.com
When another pod cast is responsible for your podcast
And injuries
We will work to provide you with the best pod cast
Experience available
Jersey Todd is a real New Jersey lawyer
But has no desire to waste your time talking about the law
On the Jersey Todd Show
You'll hear a unique mix of pod safe music
With the best rants on the net
Just listen to one of our satisfied listeners
I used to subscribe to them pod cast
With that their iPod
After five minutes my ears hurt
Oh
Then I got smaller earbuds
Now my ears don't hurt so bad
And oh yeah
I listened to that Jersey Todd Show
That's some fine listening
Well listen to our celebrity endorser Matthew Ebel
Hey this is Matthew Ebel
And I've been listening to
Jersey Todd Show
From Jersey
And it's okay
So if you're in an accident or injure yourself at work
And you're injured really badly
And there's one bone everywhere
You should call an ambulance
Chances are the ambulance driver
Is listening to the Jersey Todd Show
www.JurzyTonShow.com
Oh man
A lawyer with a sense of humor
I love it
The ad challenge is still on
It'll be on for quite a while
It's going to be fun
Pretty soon I'm going to start playing some of the stuff that's coming in
So basically you come up with the way to sell earthlink
Help us sell it
And you'll make some money if you win
You know for those guys from Jersey
They set up the promotion
Ad challenge.podshow.com
It's a really long show
In fact for those of you listening to this on serious stars
It's time for me to cut out
Let's see
I think we'll have Pacific Coast Hellway next
And then you regular Tuesday line up
We'll follow
And of course I'll be back tomorrow
For you
Well, it's going to be just another show
And for us here doing the podcast
It'll be 401
Man
All right serious listeners
Take care of seeing tomorrow
PCH next
Bye
Two split shows
What it is
It wasn't planning on having Patricia coming
But she always makes me laugh
Big time
Okay
I promised some geeky stuff
And it's about my
About my Macintosh
Because you know this thing had a really strange
Fryout
I've had screens go and
Distrives go and
All kinds of other stuff
And by the way this 1.67
Geagerhertz power book G4
I've heard other similar issues
Besides the audio issue
Which was one big problem
Which we got fixed
And the fan became really noisy
And I heard that happened with other people's
Power books as well
And I didn't just hear it from here
Say actually heard their fans start to crank
And then you tap the speaker
I mean it's just it's all hardware stuff
It's just poor manufacturing
I guess we're designed that
It's still being tested
So people are sending in their comments
And feedback
Hey Adam this is VT
From the gaming's edge podcast
Wanting to make a quick audio
Comment about your recent Mac was
Specifically the fact that you
noticed that the second life client
Actually runs faster on many PCs
Then it does on many Macs
This of course is a direct result of the fact
That when Lyndon research first
Created second life
It was developed initially for windows
Yeah probably for whether direct ex
System calls or something like that
Yeah the Mac will get
This is really where the problem started
With the Mac I have to say
When it started running second life
It could really really hot and the fan
Will be blowing full speed
And then that would make my palm sweaty
And all kinds of sweaty gunk would feed
Feed into the keyboards
And as I said keys would just pop
And off because I was tapping
I'm so hard
Of course you second life
Basically the Mac version
Is just a port of the windows
Codebase
Now they did go in and do some enhancement
Specifically for the Mac port
One of which being adding
Some OpenGL specific calls
To increase graphics performance
On Macs that have higher end graphics cards
And also added some auto-vec instructions
That being the special effects
On the G4 and G5 CPUs
That are in many Macs
To increase the background performance
But those little tweaks and refinements
In the grand scheme of things
Don't really quite overcome the fact
That the version that you play
Second life when you're playing on a Mac
Wasn't really cut it specifically for the Mac
Another key thing to consider
When comparing the games performance
On the different operating systems
Is the fact that unlike Windows XP
OS 10 actually uses protected memory
Which essentially trades off
A small fraction of your overall system
Performance in favor of a much greater level of system
Is this turning you on as much as it's turning me on?
Probability
So when you factor in the fact that the game was a port
And that it's running on a system that is consciously
Sacrificing speed for stability
Yes, there you have your performance
That's it
That's the hardware configuration
In both cases is at least comparable
CPU graphics card memory
You get the idea
So aesthetics and user interface aside
There are actually some very significant differences
In Windows 10 and Windows XP
Protected memory just being one of the most important ones
Having said that
I do feel your pain
Regarding all your hardware failures
But suffice to say
I think your laptops tend to get a little more travel
And abuse than the average persons do
I could go on
But this is getting kind of long
So I'll leave you with this thought
Okay
What happens when gaming nerds cut a record?
Granny got game
Hot safe music network
I did
Check it
Okay, thank you
Nerdtalk
Oh
Yep
So I was right
I was writing my assumptions about sacrificing some of that
Nice smooth stuff and stability stuff
Which should be actually Windows stuff is stable
It's not another stuff is crashing on me
Sometimes a little hard to switch between applications
That are graphic intensive though it takes a long time
Which sucks because you know that way
It's very hard to do a quick hide on second life
When your real life girlfriend comes in
Hey, I'm a start from the just start from podcast
That just start from that order
I was listening to DSC 399
And you were talking about your fried power book
And how the keyboard and mouse wasn't working
But did you cut up on the external keyboard?
If you did that you could probably boot off the install desk
And that should give you the driver's career too
If not, you could just get one of those new MacBooks
But that wouldn't solve the burning enough stuff
When you've all three problems
I was surprised they hear you complaining about the Apple hardware
I switched it over two years ago
And I have an old power map G4
I use it for everything including my podcast
And a lot of video editing
And I've never had a hardware problem
So I hope it helps
I look forward to show 400
You can find my podcast that just sounds not worth
Bye
All right Josh, thanks buddy
Yeah, yeah
I just refused to accept that I've gotten all Monday morning models
You know, it's just
But I've been through this with you
I've been a
I've been a Mac beta tester
Up until the Mac actually became just as useful as Windows
And now I'm noticing some of these hardware things that are just pissing me off
You know, it's really making me angry
And I must say there's a lot of software out there
Running on Windows
There's a lot of software from Mac too, but
I don't know
It's still kind of up in the air
All right, the wind it up
Pods have music artists
Where people on behalf of Pods have music artists
Ask me all the time
How do we get a song played on your show
I said, I don't know
You send me an email or something
Get my attention and then
I'll listen to it if I like it
I put it on
It's that simple
And of course everything being played on the
Daily Source Code from the Pods have music network
If the artist is into it
It goes live for purchase after being played
As a part of our Pods show plus
Rollout
A rolling rollout
And one way to get my attention is to call into the voice mail lines
Hey Adam, what's up?
This is Gary Alexander calling you from Los Vegas
I'm originally from South Carolina
I'm a singer songwriter
And I am a Pods show
Pods say from music artists
And I really like for you to check out my music
I have about four songs uploaded right now
And I think you may dig the song listen
Which is basically a songwriters' plea
And the song was upon the time of America
I think that you may dig some of that stuff
And I think that you'll get it
I've been performing since I was 14 years old
I'm now 30 years old
And it took kick in and I had a record deal
We won a brother's interview in details
And I'm more excited about Pods show
Than I have been about any of the other shit
That I've been involved with
I know it sounds like I'm just kissing ass
But you know I don't get fast no fans
I dig what you're doing
And I hope that you dig what I'm doing
Check it out
Gary Alexander Pods say Pods show music artists
And I think that you may dig some of that stuff
She's a small tail girl, with big time dreams
And I'm just a Romeo, with some fainted blue jeans
Yes girls like this, and made me want a role on my dreams
Once upon a time, a miracle
Oh yeah, once upon a time, a miracle
She can eat us, when they go 20 years
I don't know, I hear that song, and I roll down the window
I think back to those days, oh I remember
You're supposed to have a miracle
Oh yeah, once upon a time, a miracle
She can't eat us, when they go 20 years
She's got a bit of a spring scene vibe too
Gary Alexander from Nevada
Originally from a small town of America, Joanna South Carolina
Once upon a time in America, and just got an email from the satellite repairman, Peter, although I was late and he was late
And it's too late to tell the serious satellite listeners about this
But special guest today on this interesting day to day zero six zero six zero six
We'll be none other than Satan, check it out at pacificcoasthellway.com
I'll be back, oh no, maybe not tomorrow because I'm going to the city
So you may have to miss a show, but then certainly we'll have one on Thursday to catch up and Friday
And get into the world cup and do all kinds of fun stuff, I guess
Adam curry dot com and daily source code dot com for the podcast feed
And of course, if you want to jump into the conversation with the regulars, hop on over to curry dot com
See tomorrow everybody, bye bye
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from pod show and lime light networks
I love it