This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 3-8-8 Hello America I love a podcasting in America when it came
to podcasting about the microphone and downloaded audacity.
My show would be called Tatooine TV, the funniest Star Wars audio birdies on the internet
period at jrdonline.com.
I have recorded 30 podcasts but I still only have a few hundred downloads a month.
I want to really podcast world like Dawn and Drew, what can I do?
Sorry you wish my help.
Have you been listening to me?
Yes.
But you know you don't sound anything like you did on MTV.
It's just in sale.
Do you listen to the Charlie every day?
Charlie who?
The Daily Source Code, the DSC.
The podcast that is a life and breath of podcasting everywhere.
The Charlie.
No, I don't have time to listen to another podcast.
I spend my days writing funny Star Wars parody bits for my podcast.
You wish me to help you become a phenomenon.
But if you don't listen to the DSC every day, then I cannot do.
Listen.
A bias in sale and move to England.
Well, 2 and a 3-8 bed.
Okay.
Have you ever interviewed Jeff Ron?
I feel the need.
The need.
First day.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic.
Isn't that scary?
I've done without me.
Maybe one day we'll see things I'll say.
Feeling sorry.
I ever felt this way.
No one else to play.
Yeah.
Time all my sight and I have all the dreams.
I know what I'm saying for me.
I'm feeling fine.
For this I feel dreams.
And all I'm saying for me.
I never saw it coming.
I expect it.
I'm sure it is somehow.
Feeling sorry.
I never said I can.
Sorry.
With all I can for now.
Time all my sight and I have all the dreams.
I know what I'm saying for me.
I'm feeling fine.
For this I feel dreams.
And all I'm saying for me.
I'm feeling fine.
Time all my sight and I have all the dreams.
I know what I'm saying for me.
I'm feeling fine.
With this I feel dreams.
And all I'm saying for me.
Wow.
I can be almost considered a golden holy.
I'm going to show Lady Patricia.
I was ready 35 minutes ago.
And that was after we had already agreed.
She was going to take her walk on the downs.
And then she'd come back and then we'd start the show.
And so I was ready in about her 15 minute walk.
And I'm ready and I'm waiting.
And I'm waiting.
And I'm like, what's going on?
Now the in-laws are here.
So things are a little bit different.
Stuff is a guess done out of order.
And too early or too late.
So Patricia was still doing her makeup.
It's a podcast.
It really doesn't matter.
Hello.
Here she comes.
So we had to wait for that.
And she just went down to make us a bit of tea.
And I'm delaying the intro.
Hi.
Hello.
Yeah.
Yes.
Luckily.
Hey, baby.
Thank you.
Okay.
In the cottage studio.
Just wait while my lovely co-host gets situated.
Look at your chair ready.
I've got your ear buds ready.
Ready to fall into your cleavage.
You're invited.
That's right.
Hey, baby.
Oh, hello.
I'm so happy.
Okay.
We're going around.
Yeah, exactly.
I'm so happy.
You joined me on the show today.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Because I've.
You're a bit exhausted.
I'm just a little bit.
Yeah.
It's been like nonstop.
How much can a person handle more than this?
I'm sure I can handle even more.
But I just like.
Yeah.
Could I have to go to the dentist at three o'clock today?
Oh, you love that.
No.
I hate it.
But now, but this is for a full.
Please.
Yeah.
I like that.
I don't like it while they're doing it.
Fresh from the dentist feeling.
Yeah.
And then you can run your tongue along my teeth.
Your teeth are nice.
On thing?
We miss a part.
Patricia's having.
What is it?
Well, I have.
Two thousand hour maintenance program that you're.
People who know, who know me a little bit and people who seem.
Everybody knows you, baby.
See my picture.
I've gorgeous teeth.
Yes, they are.
We start like.
Yeah.
That costs a fortune.
Uh-huh.
Because I'm one of these people.
We spread it out over three husbands like my god.
I invest so much money in my mouth.
Sound strange.
You put your money where your mouth is, baby.
Exactly.
So I'm one of these people that are.
Extremely unlucky with my teeth.
Yeah.
You know, nobody ever.
Notices.
I knew I said something.
Have you been smoking my splits?
I don't know.
I've been talking with Dutch a lot.
And so you don't see it.
But if you knew.
How much work is this?
It's a struggle.
So this is another six months program you're on.
Yeah.
Now I get new implants in there.
Now these are.
Because they get bleak.
And then they're on.
Now these are.
Because they get bleak.
And then they pull them out.
Not the teeth, the front teeth, the front teeth out.
They're beautiful.
It's on the side.
But it's all the mullers and everything.
And you know, these days they just make sure that you get new ones.
Yeah.
But it's quite a procedure.
Quite a procedure.
God.
It takes a long time.
Yeah.
You have to be very patient.
And it's painful.
But I go for it.
Yeah.
I do it.
It's very important.
Because it's so important to chew and to eat your food and enjoy your food.
Which is very good for your stomach.
Which is very good for your body.
Which is very good for your whole health condition.
Exactly.
Absolutely.
And as we know, you are.
Do you wear a life itself?
Yeah.
But what?
You have to invest in your life.
Yeah.
You know.
Cost a lot of money.
I can't understand that some people, if you cannot afford it.
What do you do?
Well, you know, if you look a lot of the British teeth around you.
Yeah.
People aren't doing much.
Well, there's plenty of oral professionals here in the UK.
I'm reliably informed.
I said I'm reliably informed.
Okay.
Oh, but you know, remember, I make the trip to China.
Yes.
And what I noticed is that all Chinese people,
most of the Chinese people have very bad teeth.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Because they probably have no dental care there at all.
No dental care at all.
Right.
Yeah.
Very strange.
It goes, you know, they have sort of their own.
All messed up.
messed up in your mouth.
It's, it's amazing.
Okay.
Patricia's going to be with us for the entire show.
A couple of problems I got to do though.
And especially this one.
Because this is from the satellite repair.
Wow.
Faithful digital flats and listeners may remember back to episode number 22,
where my dad proved that all adolescent boys are brain dead.
He told the story of how he and a group of his young friends burned down
a wooded hillside while playing with matches.
A girl would never do anything like that.
Well, I beg to differ.
Hi.
I'm PW Fountain.
And that was the voice of my daughter, Billy.
We think that girls can be just as brain dead as boys.
Keep an ear peeled for digital flats number 36 in which she will plead her case.
I've played that for you before.
Have I did digital flats?
PW Show?
Hey, tell stories.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Not as much as daughter.
Billy.
I haven't heard that.
I don't think she, well, yes, she's, I don't know if she's been.
Don't you know, ready?
Well, no, she's, I have no idea what this is about.
We have to listen to the show, I guess.
That's quite the promo.
It's a teaser.
Oh, Christina will be so jealous.
Well, that she's not doing her show.
Yeah.
It's like, well, how much do I have to do?
I'm not going to force her to...
She wants it.
But, you know, she's very busy with school and she...
And boys.
And boys and socialize.
So incredibly busy with the boys.
Yeah.
Wow.
You know what I just saw?
I saw a long time ago, but I've seen it again.
And I didn't know they had Oprah over here in the...
Yeah.
I didn't know that.
So I found her again.
And...
They were...
Goodness.
I'm so happy.
Yeah.
And they were talking about something that is very close to my heart,
because it's sometimes...
I hated too, actually.
And that is that lots of...
There was a man who said that all the webcams,
especially the webcams that kids have, teenagers,
should be destroyed.
Really?
Because it is...
What's that?
Why the problem?
So we're showing on.
And the only...
They only have webcams to show themselves.
To have porn to have sex.
That's what he said.
And that's what they were talking about.
And there was a boy in the studio who actually started a thing in his bedroom,
just for fun, show himself.
You know, hi, waving, getting on dress loop.
And he's now a web 2.0 millionaires.
This is my body.
Do you see that?
And then he got reactions.
Yeah.
No kidding.
And...
Oh, we want to see this one.
For money.
People would send him money.
Yeah.
So, you know, while he was doing that,
and then suddenly I thought that this is...
This is wrong.
So he told his dad.
And...
Okay.
That's really wrong.
Because he was in trouble.
Somebody wanted to kill him.
Somebody wants to come to his house.
So he thought this is not good.
This is not going anywhere.
So he told his dad.
And the dad just...
He was talking to Oprah about it.
And he said that pediatricians, they were lawyers.
Oh, yeah, of course.
He worked with children.
Sure.
Actually, most of the people were people who were...
Who worked with children, who were doing this,
who were having it out really.
And so now he's protected by the government,
because...
But listen, they have to move.
But listen, my dear.
But so he said, all the webcams, for kids,
it's wrong.
They have to, you know, destroy them.
I'm there.
We'll destroy all the webcams after we get rid of all the guns.
Okay?
Which one do you think is more dangerous?
The gun laying around the house or the webcam?
Nobody was there in Oprah's show tonight.
No, no.
Of course not.
An Oprah or Oprah.
Or...
Orka.
Orka wouldn't say that.
But, you know, isn't that just a little screwy
when you think about it in the United States,
where webcams have to be banned before semi-automatic handguns?
But this is for the kids protection.
What do you think guns are?
What do you think has guns in their hands?
They're kids disappearing.
We had this whole discussion with your mom just the other day.
It's like...
She said, where is this world going to?
All these horrible things I read about in the newspaper.
I said, we're going in the same direction we came from.
She grew up literally.
Always an answer.
But she was literally what?
She was eight years old, ten years old during the Second World War.
The Nazis were bombing Rotterdam?
No, she was...
Eighteen.
Really?
She was a Christian.
You're right. She's 80 already.
So she was a young woman.
Witness this.
Now, which one?
I mean, come on.
I mean, yeah, there's shit that happens.
I think it's just, you know, we're hearing about it consistently.
And it's all bundled in a nice little package,
calls the newspaper, which is delivered, you know,
this nice package of crap is delivered to your doorstep every single morning.
Here's something to depress you about.
Yeah.
But it's not like...
Well, bad people.
The world has been around.
Exactly.
The evil time.
I think all the good things we're doing with webcams.
And all those stories, when I said, all those stories.
Remember, Jack the River.
Allton, Jack the River.
Mm-hmm.
In the London fog.
Exactly.
All those little alleys where people got murdered.
Well, but these car jackings, like, well,
you think you even said it, that they used to stop your stage coach.
Chop your fucking head off and take your gold.
And take your horses.
Yeah.
And screw your horses.
Take your gold chop your head off.
Mm-hmm.
No way, man.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
Tell, but it's not really.
You know, women mothers, women mothers.
And sometimes you lay away from it.
And yes, every time I come in and hurt cameras on it,
what are you doing?
Yeah.
What are you looking at?
But she's on MSN chat and then they have the webcam with her bodies.
I've looked at it.
I said, Mom, I know.
I know who they are.
I recognize and write away if something's stupid.
Oh, I think OK.
I think it's a very limited phase that most kids go through.
Most of them come out of it on the other hand.
It's like, oh, look at all this stuff we can do with our camera.
Yeah.
We know what we can do with the camera.
Give a camera to your chin.
You're a San Francisco.
Excuse me.
Well, we're in San Francisco.
We're looking at each other.
Oh, on the eye chat.
On the eye chat.
Yeah.
That's hot, baby.
But you're so like, are you sure no one can see this?
Yeah.
I don't know.
It doesn't make it just a little bit more exciting, baby.
Anyway, it's so naughty.
You're so naughty.
Mm-hmm.
See?
Adam, don't do that.
Don't do that.
Somebody!
Get a bigger lens.
I can't see it's all.
Now I didn't say this.
No.
It doesn't.
Are you going to say, you know, you're going to be playing around?
Oh.
Up.
Pfft.
People are really dirty.
I didn't go out.
People are really clean.
onia more.
Yeah.
He was fine.
Give up.
Get him.
C'mon.
You put his hand out.
He's actually rink of inside.
he's sitting and doing something big.
OHA!
OK.
This guy is going to be human.
So he's like, that's my kid is crying as bloody eyes out because I have a neglected and for two days
or I've been in second life the virtual world known as second life. He couldn't take the boy with him.
Well, no little vip chair. Vip chair.
Vip chair.
Yeah, we love those voicemail comments, 201-625-635-7 in New Jersey again in London,
O2-076-81375-3 and there have been a couple of since you and I spoke there's been lots of
pro and con, you know, second life is good, second life is bad, you know, virtual world's good, virtual world's
bad, I don't care, I do care. You want to hear some some more responses? Okay.
Okay.
Hi, now you're doing this is Chuck from Jersey.
Joyce is a local column in South Jersey but I grow up and someone calls for the north.
How do you write? It's good to hear that somebody's proud of being from Jersey. I catch someone
just like I work in Pennsylvania. But anyway, just wanted to come there real quick about our negative
feedback you're getting about dreaming and your second life talk. Everyone listen to your show
simply because they want to hear what you're doing and things like that and pod show and
everything like that. I personally don't have a training myself but I enjoy listening to the
trendies and for what I'm hearing from all the feedback everybody's loving it. All the sudden you
start talking about second life and because people are involved in second life they're all upset
about everybody's got a light interrupt it's part of what you are. You're in the second life right
now and inspired me to sign up. I haven't had a chance to get in it myself yet but I signed up for
the delicious thing. Anyway, people need a light and I'll have fun how talk to you soon
later on the show. See, that's a Jersey boy sticking together, right? I'm in my third life already.
Oh yeah, one does that start at 50? You're third life starts? Yeah, that's 50. You're still enjoying it?
Oh absolutely. Yeah. Okay. Always take my teeth back. Me too. I could be driving a Ferrari.
Hey Adams is reigning with from second life. Do you realize it is three o'clock in the
fricken morning and I still haven't been to bed yet. I've been up chatting with everybody in
second life hanging out at the Castle Cove just enjoying the dialogue and having a good time.
It has completely sucked me in. Anyway, Adam, you and I share a similar situation. My husband
completely doesn't understand second life. Things that's just the game and waste of time just
does not get it at all. Does that? Well, let's be honest. It is a waste of time. Well, it doesn't
not. It means if you have to, how do you say that? If you can't spend any time with somebody
or, you know, your family and you're so busy and so involved in it, yet then. No, it's problem.
That's a problem. That's what I mean. So actually met a guy yesterday through second life.
I told you about this last night, we're actually going to be business with him. And I met him
right in on the roof of the castle. It doesn't get vlogging, which is something else I like to do.
So anyway, also wanted to tell you that I absolutely love the person coming on the show.
I think she's awesome. I love the dialogue between the two of you and she just add something really
special to the show. Yeah, who does? So keep up the good work and I'll see you in second life.
I've been a DSC listener and a cober and I love the Charlie. Good night. Good night.
Okay, say hi to you husband. I know a good. I do not. I do not sit up until three o'clock in the
morning. No, because I don't take that. I just slap you. No, you don't. No, but I just keep on saying,
huh, are you coming to bed now? Yeah, and I keep saying, yes, in a minute, I'll be right there.
Yeah. And then I try things. But often that I'm actually doing things in, you know,
on San Francisco time. Yeah. That's what I'm usually doing. Yeah. But it has to be with our sex life a little bit.
Bullshit. That's total bullshit. You were in second life while I was waiting. Yeah, but I don't feel.
I don't feel very sexy at all lately. Because of second life? No. No, I know.
I just, my head isn't different. No, I know. I know. I know.
Yeah. And just joking. Just. That's what you say. Well, apparently could you tell me what day that was,
so I can reconstruct and see how did I miss the signals? You just don't recognize it now. Then
and if you don't respond, then I go back in my bedroom when they're okay. It's okay, Han. It's okay.
That's why our marriage is so perfect. What? What? Doesn't matter. No, I'm just, there's so much going on.
If you have a brainy husband, that's, yeah. And what does that mean?
You don't brainy. Are you not satisfied? Do I not satisfied with you?
Yes, you do. Okay. Do I not satisfied with you often enough? No.
Are you kidding me? Oh, man. Really? Yeah. But it's, but we have a teenager running around the house all
hours. Your mom and dad are running around. Yeah. Yeah. Here. Just for two days. I mean,
they're here two days now. Yeah. And already are you tired of it? No. No, I don't mean it like that.
No, they're going to help me while and help us while we're going to. I know that. I know,
but usually after about a week of them being in the house. Can you imagine you have two
80 or 80 old 80 year olds? Yeah, it won't. Can't speak anymore. 80 year olds in the house.
I mean, that's not easy. Because they repeat a lot for those of you.
Yeah, mom, you just told me that for those of you listening on Syria stars 102 coming up
today. We've got Pacific Coast Hellway, which is next followed by East Radio Don and Drew
Gilmore Daily. And then I think it's episode 36 now, the pod show music rewind. The rest of
this show you can find a daily source code dot com. But my parents are fantastic.
Oh, the fantastic. It's so sweet. But they just don't so nice and so young for their age. Yes.
Very good. And I'm very, very lucky to have them. I'm still kind of stuck on this whole. I don't
satisfy you enough. Oh, stop. We're going on a trip together. You realize that, right?
Yeah, just you and me. That's what I was thinking about. I'm saving myself for you.
Okay. Yeah. Hi, dear. How did the visit at the doctor go? Did the doctor say?
Just as I thought, the Marcus just has a slight speech to lay and that he's a boy. And then it's
no big deal. What? He has autism? Oh, no. Hi. This is Michael Bull from autismpodcast.org.
My wife and I had a very similar conversation to that one. And we were looking for help as
soon as we found out about our son. That's why I started an autism podcast.
In autism podcast, we interviewed specialists about some of the latest therapies, parents about
their experiences, as well as teachers who teach kids on this spectrum. If you're looking for some
information delivered in an audio format for autism, which now afflix about one and 166 kids born
today, head to www.autismpodcast.org or in iTunes, just search for Autismpodcast. Thank you.
Changing the world, huh? Wow. Isn't that cool? That's cool. Yeah, there's a lot of really
interesting, we're putting together a whole channel of family and health and stuff. There's a lot
of really good stuff out there. This is good. I got to do my Tourette podcast. Yeah. It should be a
video podcast. Isn't it wonderful to talk about your problems like that? I have no problem.
Problem talking about my problems. No, I mean, about things that you, you know,
like, did you live with? Like, not satisfying my wife. Often enough. Yeah, that's just wonderful
baby. And Tourette? I think, but it's so charming. I love you Tourette. Thank you. Really? Yeah,
it's very interesting. If I could combine that with my sexual activity, then maybe I'll satisfy
you long time. I love you long time, girl. Yeah. But you know, it changes in your body.
So it's great. Sometimes it's there. Down there. That, that I control. I have, I have
total, deep control. I'm getting better. Yeah, I'm really in trouble. There's a new pod,
even the pod finder. Right? That's the thing we do for iTunes. Yeah. We highlight all new
podcasts. There's a new one out. I think today. And there was this one pod cast in it, which is
so well done. I just wanted to play, uh, I think it's just, I don't know if it's a whole episode
of just a piece of it. It's called the weekly radio address podcast. You know, the president
does a weekly radio address. Yeah. In fact, it was a Kennedy, it made Roosevelt started those,
the fire side chats. And so the president still does them. No one, I don't think anyone cares about
them. Uh, but this is a parody. I definitely care about this version. Now a message from the president
of the United States, George W. Bush. Good morning. This week began a bold new era in promotion of
alternative energies to reduce our nation's dependence on foreign oil. As my scientific advisors
have explored the new types of automobiles for the next century. They have devised the people powered
car. Giant holes will be cut in the floor beneath these cars so that the driver can propel the vehicle
forward with a running barefoot start. This automobile will be lighter. The frame constructed of
simple twigs and animal heads. Instead of rubber tires, more foot-efficient stone wheels are going to
be used. And finally replacing the horn will be a squawking prehistoric bird,
conserving power by using nature's voices. Just pull his tail and use the cries of primi
will be the worn other drivers of oncoming dangers. These new cars will hold up to two families
allowing you and your friends to go to the driving movies or to the Bronto Burger Hut. He style,
but science is still confounded on how to keep the car upright when large cuts of meat are served.
But we are a nation of innovators and we must work together to solve these problems and move into a
bold new age of the future. Thank you for listening and God bless you. Yeah, well it almost sounds good,
isn't it? I thought it was really good. I like that a lot. I got so many comments about
the earbuds falling in your cleavage. I'd call them guys. You haven't, I know you haven't heard it
because let's face it, you don't care about the show. I've never listened to the show unless you're on it.
I don't listen to what I'm on. Even when you're not on it. Yeah, it's something I can hear when I'm
walk through the house. So we have it was a Cheechen Chong, one guy named his wife's breast,
Cheechen Chong and then some other guy actually called up and said, well, you know,
one of his wife's breasts is smaller so they call that one tiny. It's like this is so wrong.
And that's all like that. I just want to talk about Patricia's breasts. Yeah, I mean you've been gone for two
days. Look what happens. Yeah, I refer to you as dude. Yeah, yeah, what's up with that?
Because we're buttons. Also, what's up with that? Yeah, what's up with that? Do I call you dude all the time?
Hey, dude, dude listen to this. Do you mind? No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I call you babe. Baby, honey,
hun. That's from the whole area. Dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude. Check out this
mix dude. I'm one of the dudes. Is it him? Is it him? Oh, it's not. Is it him? No, it's not him.
Yeah, I'll continue. Okay, today about Patricia fly around to eat broose dick. I guess well,
I'll be saying tailwinds to her now. Thank you. Tailwinds. My broose dick, yeah. Tailwinds. Exactly.
Yeah, tailwinds. Tailwinds, not wings, wings. Tailwinds. Tailwinds. Okay. So you excited about the trip?
Yeah, I am. Yeah. You know, we have to, we have to do shows when we're on the road. You realize
that don't you? No, really? Yeah, so I mean, here's my life, right? So we're speaking in New York.
We have to go get our marriage papers. We have to do shows. And I have to satisfy you long time.
So I'm going to be a really, really busy guy. I don't know what I'm going to do.
I'm going to be a younger than I am. You sure? Today, I feel old. I talked to my mom for like 45 minutes.
Draining. Yeah. Yeah, and the horrible thing is the blisters in her mouth.
From whatever they're talking about. More things. If somebody is in that situation as your
mom is, you want to talk to them, but sometimes you're scared to talk to them because you're afraid
that you might say something different or wrong or, you know, it's so hard because you want to
help. You want to talk to them. But anything you say is not good enough. It's not, you know,
helping it all. No, but I think my mom and I, we, we've, we've definitely moved beyond that stage.
It's really easy for us to talk about it. You're very good at it. Yeah, she loves to talk to you.
Yeah, because you, you throw a bit of humor in it. And you know, now what else do you do?
Yeah, what else? I mean, what is the best thing? You don't know. And I think keeping the humor
and, and yeah, and that's what I say. Just try to, we have to try to stay positive. That's
so much better for the, for her body. Yeah. So, well, hopefully they'll get the, uh, the pain,
uh, and the control, and licks or whatever they're, so now they're, they're uping the morphine and,
you know, the uping the pretness on and whatever, uping a lot is what I'm hearing. Yeah. But
she didn't sound just stoned. No, no, no, God. Whatever she had, they gave her last time.
She used to totally whacked. Totally. And I couldn't help but laugh. But yeah, because she'd say,
she'd be talking to me about something. She said, no, where is that ham? Yeah, it's with this.
There's no way. Wait a minute, mom, I got to catch up to your hold on and not stoned enough to fall.
Yeah, conversation. Yeah, uh, okay. Um, let me see, whatever. Oh, yeah, this is, uh,
uh, just a couple of promos. I got to do hunt. Then we'll wind up with some pod safe music. Okay. Okay. All right.
Remember this song? You heard his music on Adam Curry's daily source code.
Wonder what pod safe pianist Rob Costlos been up to six? Yes. Yeah.
A flashters well for very videos and documentaries.
Tune in on Monday. May the 22nd from my interview with pod safe music artist Rob Costo and
find out what he's been up to at trucker-tong.podshow.com.
You haven't met Trucker Tom, have you? You've you've met me? You've seen a picture of him, right?
Yeah. Yeah, I sent all kinds of minerals and stuff for you. He's always coming back with all kinds of
Right, yeah, with the health tips.
Now you sent them to me.
That's right. You would love Trucker Tom.
He's about your height.
You guys would look great together.
What was that?
Well, I'd love it once someone my height comes along.
I don't know. I'm sorry.
I don't take it the wrong way.
Sounds a bit, uh, I don't know.
Humiliated.
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
Didn't mean, oh, I didn't mean that at all.
But he's a bit yours.
It's like, I'm a little person, or no.
Okay, they came out the wrong way.
Exactly.
But first of all, you'd like him.
Okay, you'd like Trucker Tom.
Yeah.
You know, it's interesting.
He's about your height.
Oh, what do you mean?
Someone from Austria's speaking.
I've been a listener of the Delta Sierra Charlie for over a year now.
And I do, of course, have my own podcast, the ETW podcast,
echo tango Oscar Oscar, just search for that in iTunes.
Unfortunately, it's German, but I think your German speaking listeners
will have a great time listening to this podcast.
Now, what I'd like to say is, um, please add and get out of my head.
You know that sound?
Every time I hear that sound, I immediately think of the daily source code.
And lately, it's been getting worse when somebody next to me a little cigarette,
you know, with that sound.
I said, actually, another partial podcast.
It's basically, you're just like you doing your outro of the show.
And so I'd like to be pro, uh, deprogram.
Could you do something about it, please?
I mean, it's, this stuff is messing around with my head.
And I can't bury any more. I'm sorry.
So this is allowing us to run from the ETW podcast, echo tango Oscar Oscar signing off.
And, uh, keep up the good work and please get out of my head.
For 20 Adam.
Do you have 420?
We gates then, my friends.
That's exactly what I wanted you to do.
I wanted you to say a few words to all of our German listeners.
Yeah.
I, I, I, I, I, I, uh, Adam.
Yeah. Adam, yeah.
That part I'm just a, yeah.
We just, uh,
geschate, uh, uh,
yeah, I can see in the microphone.
Chances.
It's, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a moment.
While my, my, uh, what's in here?
Brains.
Brains in the doits.
My brain.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
What's cowbell in German?
My, my, my.
Cubella.
It's, um, uh, occupied right now.
The set?
Yeah, beset with English.
Yes.
Yeah.
And it's, it's, it's, it's in there.
It's, it's, it's somewhere, it's somewhere, it's somewhere.
I don't know.
It's just before language.
Yeah.
It's in there.
But I'm talking about, and I understand everything.
Yeah, I understand, uh, uh, yeah.
Yeah.
I understand, as we, uh, our, uh,
Commitment and guidance fits.
No, uh, excuse me.
That's constant.
It's acting.
That's the only German I really know is from the porn movies.
Don't say that.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Well, dear, what's on the agenda for today?
You going out with, uh, with the folks?
Now first, I have to go and take my walk on the, on the down.
Right.
Love that.
And it's nice for them, too.
They're going to go with you.
Yeah.
They're going to do the walk.
So I do the walking with them.
Yeah.
And, uh, after that, we're going to discuss, uh, dinner.
Yes.
Very important.
Yeah, that's, uh, oh, it's very important for your parents.
And I, um, uh, let's look at, let's not forget to, um,
to call Christina's, uh, school.
Yes, let, let us, let us not forget.
Yeah.
Did you, did you cancel the car?
No, but I will.
Okay.
I don't know.
And hopefully she can go back to school tomorrow.
Yes.
She has a kidney infection.
It's kind of bites.
Yeah.
I've got a, I've got a real stable of winners here.
There's some time that's happening.
Yeah.
I'm going to do.
You're going to, uh,
a lot of, uh, bladder infections when you were.
Yeah.
No, that was, when I was much younger.
Between, like, told me that 17 and 22 had lots of bladder infections.
Yeah.
It was horrible.
Um, I was going to ask you something.
Um, they, they say that it starts a little bit.
When teenage, you start to, uh, to touch each other.
Yes.
To become sexually active.
I say that like that.
Yeah.
Um, you're talking to a, a father of a teenage child.
I know.
Tough to even fathom all that crap.
Oh, no.
Um, I was going to say something else about your parents.
Hmm.
Yeah.
You, you, you, you, you looked at me and said,
you're so nice to them.
You want to say?
No, well, no.
It was, uh, I'm good to my parents.
I don't remember.
I'm very thankful for you.
I really don't remember.
They were good parents.
Well, there's still good parents.
Yeah.
Uh, that's why.
Now, I mean, when I was young,
I mean, I do remember them as very old,
fashion nice, you know, but they, they shape you and do it.
When, um, it came from school with her apron on.
With a cookies and you dad with this hat.
Did, did, did, did, did, did.
Hello, little white picket fence.
Very, little blue.
Yeah.
All right.
Um, okay.
I don't remember what I was going to say.
Oh, it was something about your parents.
I'm a parent.
Yeah.
Just in general.
Ah, no, that's matter.
Okay.
I don't have it all together today.
I got a lot of chips to do.
Yeah.
I'm just, you know.
You have a bit, uh, empty.
Maybe, maybe that's it.
Why?
This will help.
You remember this song, don't you?
Laura Clap.
Hey, hey sister on the source code.
I have a scene.
Just sent a bad decision.
Hold on.
Quick to anticipate.
Which part of what she needs.
While she puts her fake eyelashes on.
Every morning, say, in reaction.
Have the room set at its fashion.
Hey, hey sister, you can't let your head down.
You ain't done nothing bad and nothing else.
You feel so clear, babe.
You're just the pilot.
I don't remember what I was going to say.
This crazy life will live and it's all a part of what I was going to say.
She's under self attack.
Can't do this, can't do that.
Or she might lose her pressures.
Friends, watch your figure, watch your weight.
Clean out that empty blade.
Throw your know that in the way to live.
Look at you.
Time for so soon to let your eyes shine.
Listen, girl, pay close attention.
Hey, hey sister, you can't let your head down.
You ain't done nothing bad and nothing else.
You feel so clear, babe.
You're just the pilot.
I don't remember what I was going to say.
This crazy life will live and it's all a part of what I was going to say.
Hey, hey sister, you can't let your head down.
You ain't done nothing bad and nothing else.
You feel so clear, babe.
You're just the pilot.
I don't remember what I was going to say.
This crazy life will live and it's all a part of what I was going to say.
Two.
You feel cool, girl.
Well, that's all I love it.
I love that if you notice that little piece of Hammond.
The, the, the, the, the B3 in there, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was on the right, the right moment.
This is whole gang of pod save artists in in Tennessee and Laura claps from Tennessee as well.
It's good, isn't it?
Fantastic.
Yeah, I love it.
I love it.
Before we go, yeah.
Now you've been, you've had your station in your kitchen for how long now, like maybe six months,
four months, five months, your computer, your eye Mac,
Okay, so you've been emailing and you've been using Skype a lot, Skype out, which is pretty cool.
Yeah.
Now, what is the thing you hate the most about what happens?
I mean, what, what are the things that you've experienced?
But they won my password over and over and over.
Right, right, that's for your email.
Yep, for your email, yeah.
I don't, I don't like that.
Yeah.
And well, sometimes is your, your mail is not coming.
Mm-hmm.
That's stuck.
Yeah, or spam, have you gotten spam, spam, spam, spam, spam?
You hate the spam?
Oh, oh yeah.
So here's what I was considering.
Mm-hmm.
Now we can't get the actual.
Yeah, gra.
I'm going to feed gra constantly.
Don't throw those out.
Save them.
So I can set that's why you long time.
Yeah.
And then, and those, uh, penis, uh, extenders, and I don't know what.
What is that?
Yeah, I do.
I get them.
Do you get them, too?
Well, I don't.
I don't even have a penis.
Because I'm using Earthlink.
And Earthlink, as you know, has the, uh, has some, some awesome spam filters.
Mm-hmm.
That cuts out all of that stuff.
So I was considering switching your mailbox.
Could also that, you know, can't get the mail or password.
That's all crap, you know.
That's just some ISP shit that just isn't working, right?
Mm-hmm.
So you want me to change that to Earthlink?
Yeah.
Yeah, make it better for you.
Yeah, sure.
All right, so we'll do that.
Those guys have got it all together.
Check them out at Earthlink.net.
Thank you for just great idea.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, baby.
Um, so it's going to be a funny week.
I'm not quite sure about tomorrow's show.
Because tomorrow I'm, uh, doing the demo and, uh,
having the meeting with the, uh, the CEO of British telecom,
we're told you Ben provide.
Yeah.
He's a Dutch guy.
Uh, I, uh, I think he's, I think he's, uh,
something with the BBC.
You had also, that's Thursday.
That's Thursday.
It's, uh, by the, it's BBC Scotland, I think.
They don't really?
Yeah, yeah, well, you know, we had, like, we have BBC London.
Yeah.
Uh, you've got the South Counties, which is, uh,
come out of Guildford University.
That's actually where I'm going to use the studio there.
So there's people in Scotland that you have Scotland matters.
Yeah.
And then Friday, something else is Friday.
Can't remember.
We have to be on Friday.
Friday if you have to pack.
Oh, no, I, I, I thought I was, uh, this time I had the,
oh, no, you're the automatic suitcase.
The automatic, the automatic, the packing and unpacking suitcase.
Of course.
Yeah.
Okay, baby.
So, uh, I'll let you go.
Okay.
All right, thank you.
Well, you were.
Thank you for pulling me through the show once again.
Just, it takes a whole cup of tea.
One cup, I know.
It's one, it's one cup of tea, or since I, I want you to prefer.
And, uh, I'll be back tomorrow.
The show will probably be up later than normal, as I said,
because, uh, what is that?
That's my dad.
What is he doing?
He's hanging the numbers because we don't have a number on that.
Oh, my God.
And he said, do you have anything to do for me?
Please give me something to do.
We haven't, and 80 year old with power tools in the house.
He always wants to do something for us.
I said, okay, hang the numbers on the door,
because the mailman is so confused.
Yeah, all right.
All right, all right, all right.
Funny. Well, it's the end of the show.
It's the end of the show.
Perfect timing.
Okay, everybody quickly.
Right, I'll, uh, see you tomorrow.
All right, here on the daily source code.
Bye, Hunter.
Thank you.
I love you.
Bye.
Another pod show pod guest.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this pod guest and we're great ones like it on the high performance
pod cast of Liberty Network from Podjo and limelight networks.
I love it.