Delta Sierra Charlie 3-2-5
The first time I've ever seen a Delta Sierra Charlie heading forward the highway, looking forward to the entryway, and what if it comes up on safe?
It's not a big Friday, it's not a big Friday, it's not a big Friday, it's not a big Friday, yeah.
One is, as I say, while it is a methane high, the drink too much coffee and a foreign gas tank.
When you're lovin' McDonald's right doing sound filler, to a 16 gallons of flammable waste throughout my ass.
In the destruction of the music industry in my ears, I like to think I'm a greasing up the future.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just in this old curry.
Oh yeah, hello everybody, it is Friday, this is not a repeat of last week's show.
You're not playing the same dance on the film.
How do you not want to start the weekend off with some cowbells?
Why don't I sing one, four, three, yeah?
Try to rock while penting, yeah!
I hit my paws in the patio, my arms got so pissed off!
Making plans aboard in the camp, we go!
Came to have me facing enemies on the knees of challenges!
You can't hear me, you can't hear me
You can't hear me, you go grow up
You don't want to down, want to down, want to down, want to down
See my arms, you feel the wind falls free
I play when I feel it all
I get into the body, feel your fear
I want to let's party, feel all the time
See, see, see, see
This boss calls over and over
Take the staff out of each other
Don't get used to it
You don't want to be needed
And not away, don't kind of take the money
You want to take them all
Oh, I wanna those things
I'll go home
Oh, yeah
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
On and on!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, reamo爷爷爷Ea gyzo!
Stingray 143 from the podcast music network music.podshow.com, it's Friday everybody, how
you're doing, how you feeling. I'm feeling pretty good. We were up real early this morning. Lots
of girls to move around the planet today. Patricia, off to see her sister for the weekend. As
you know, the SESNA 182 RG is completely dismantled engines out, interior out, everything's
getting refurbished, rejuvenated. And oh, yes, the youth will come back to the 182 RG. So my boy's
Nick and Roy picked her up in the mooney, which is a very different type of aircraft. And I
preface this to Patricia. I said, you know, you kind of got to walk over the wing to get in.
She's like, oh, well, I'll have to wear the proper shoes. It was amazing, though, where I gave
this beautiful leopard skin suitcase set for Christmas. And she took what I thought was a rather
large suitcase, because, you know, just remembering the moonium, like, man, I don't know. You wanted
to put that thing. There might be your fellow passenger. How do you hear all that? Is that his or
hum or what am I hearing here? I've got, I don't know. I got to look at this shit here. Anyway,
so she was off, off in a way. She's already landed sent me a text message. Everything's okay.
Okay, Christina's at school. And of course, I'm taking her and Owen to the garage in London.
Turns out it's North London, which is like an hour and a half drive. It would be very interesting to see
because they're going to the panic at the disco gig tonight. And big surprise. Now, I hadn't
mentioned this on the show, but Casplaster, Mike and I got into a fabulous row. I mean, we got
like into a flame war that flamed out on email. It was pretty interesting. You know, basically,
fuck you, fuck you. No fuck you. And then that was the end of it for a day or two. And Mike
came with a wonderful piece offering today. I don't know if it was intended that way, but I certainly
take it that way. He sent me a special pod father edition of Casplaster, which is just fantastic.
If anything, I've been bitching about not having enough players because I've so many different
pieces of audio feedback and stuff that I want to line up that, you know, I'd wind up using
external quick time players and stuff. And so now you fired up, but actually says Casplaster, the pod
felt the pod father edition. Instead of the 10 jingle cart machines that are mapped to the
function keys, I have 12. And of course, you have 12 function keys, so it fits perfectly. And now
I can actually have space left over for, oh, you know, stuff like, you know, that or a fantastic.
And I have 24 players for tracks. Thank you, Mike. This is exactly what I needed. I'm so happy.
And now, um, I guarantee you it's going to be an extra super long show because we've got all kinds
of feedback from all of my favorite people. Like I said, G&B was some feedback on TSC number 324.
So about this whole split thing, um, the car's native was definitely right. Um, artists have
traditionally made pennies on the dollar with music. And in fact, we still do, um, love spirals
and sign up with just about every one of those digital music stores out. They're all the majors,
iTunes, rap, city music, net, MSN, music, Napster, Sony, Connect, Yadayada, Yadayada. And the amount
that we make ranges from two cents to 86 cents. Um, there's, there's no standards. So, um, you know,
but we're happy to get whatever we do because, you know, if you normally make a dollar something
per CD, making two cents to 86 cents per song is actually pretty awesome. So I think, um, people should
chill out and not be split and hairs on how much money they're going to be making from the PMM downloads
because it's all good. Isn't it? It's all good. By the way, I'd like to thank all the podcasters out there
for their support of love spirals on the positive music network. And for reading our tracks,
so I think, thanks so much. Appreciate it. NGB, I love it when you send voice feedback to me. I love
it so much. Yeah. Um, so lots of feedback on that slouch, checked in. Um, yeah, he kind of said the
same thing. I think, uh, and again, we're not focusing on this too much, but I'm pretty sure that,
um, sales through PMM and depending on how, uh, you know, if a podcasters involved in the middle of
they want to take, uh, a fee. Oh, my left foot is itching on or if they want to, you know, of course,
you don't have to. You'll be able to give the fee right back to the artist. Anyway, between 50 and 65
cents, probably sounds about right. You know, universally across the board, I think, just the transaction
fee on the 99 cents song is about nine cents, so maybe 10 cents, nine or 10 cents. That's kind of
something you can't get away from a regardless. So, um, apologies that we're, that we're still not
in the public beta testing of this. Uh, we've got, uh, Dan and, uh, we got to Dan a man and Jersey Joe
working on the code, tightening it all up. Um, and thanks, of course, uh, to everyone who was sent in
comments about, uh, you know, certain, um, things that can be approved on the Pods of Music Network,
some security enhancements, all this stuff is, is extremely appreciated. And, of course,
is being passed right onto a Chris Rockwell and Dan and, uh, and Joe and all the boys and girls
who are working very hard. As I said, um, 24 tracks to play things didn't fill them all up,
but I came pretty damn close. Hello, Adam. My name is Ed hidden with the ed hidden dot com photocast
and the I co host the late source podcast available at studio lighting.net. And those are
two podcasts for photographers out there who want to, you know, they're more about lighting or
find out things that I do with photography and hopefully you can learn from my mistakes or my experiences.
But today, I have a question about enhanced podcast for you. Now, the photocast is enhanced podcast,
but I'm a PC user. So I had to con one of my mac friends into actually assembling all of the pieces
for me. But I purchased QuickTime Pro and examined the file properties from an enhanced podcast created
with the chapter tool and kind of my AAC file that I made in QuickTime Pro and I tried to match
up the properties as much as I could and seemed like it was outputting the exact same format as
the chapter tool was. I played the same in QuickTime as as an enhanced podcast does. However, when I
exported out to QuickTime or iTunes, it just kind of behaves like a normal audio file. No images,
no links, no anything. So I'm, I'm stumped. I've tried QuickTime or tried Apple. I've tried their
forms. Nothing's happening. And there's no announcement or anything whether anything's going to
ever come about with a chapter tool version for the PC and I'm very frustrated and I'm kind of at
my last draw. So I'm asking the pod father. Challenging your listeners out there because I know
you got some bright brains out there in the audience. So let's see what we can do. I look forward to hearing
your response and thank you for everything you do for the podcast community. Take care. Bye bye.
So this is very interesting. I believe Cas Blaster Mike actually had some kind of windows thing
that was doing that. I think he was, he was looking way deep into those files to see what was possible.
And from what I understand, it is very possible to do that with a windows application. It's an
open format as far as I know. But this is kind of interesting. It is kind of the way Apple does things.
I don't even think that the tool that's out there now that's being used widely. I think I got
it from versiontracker.com. I don't even think that was an Apple product or seeded by Apple.
They do seem to kind of have that mantra. So seems like there's a perfect application for
developer who wants to make some money, shareware version or version that has a trial period and then
you're typical 1995. Whatever it is for that software had by that stuff all the time. Particularly
the 1995 stuff. I have so many applications that I've used that have come from independent software
vendors as they call them. Or usually a guy with a big fucking sense. Sorry. A big fricking senseo.
And lots of hours at night to work on cool stuff that people really want. We did make by the way.
And I'll just say we the community of power book owners who are definitely disappointed by the
lack of response on Apple's part regarding this loop sound looping issue. We made the consumerist.com.
And I got some angry emails too. People saying, hey, Apple responded, it's shut up already.
Well, the thing is they didn't really. They didn't say, we'll go back to you. If we find anything
now, the only line that was listed on the tech document that also says the way to solve this
is to only use one audio application at a time. The only extra line they say and there is,
you know, watch this page if information becomes available. It didn't say like, we're working
on an hard behind the scenes guys. Why don't make y'all happy? Never mind. Casplastic is doing just fine
for me right now. Thank you very much. Hi, Adam and everyone out there in DSC Nation. This is
Sean from the QCast. You can tune into the QCast for the best in news, sports, podcasting,
other technology and entertainment, all from the perspective of 13-year-olds. I guess you can say
we're truly flying into the future. Oh, and how can I forget? We will always give a daily perspective
on school and the like and improve the best in pod safe music. Check out the show at QCast.org
and be sure to subscribe. Hope to see you there soon. Thanks.
Do you believe anything is possible? We do. We're our flank.
We believe in an internet that's safe from virus hidden scammers. We're Earthlink.
We believe your personal information should be just that personal and we believe your
internet should be a friend, not a foe. We're Earthlink. Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net
and discover what our internet experts can do for you, Earthlink. We revolve around you.
I'll take a big fat ass any day.
Hi, I'm Mary and I'm Parallel from the Mary and Parallel show. Adam, we are pleased to
announce and very excited that we have joined the pod show family. We are safe to be part of an
amazingly talented group of diverse podcasts. We also want to bring a little girl part of the
network along with the fantastic females like the bitties, the mummies, and of course,
and just because we're joining the most powerful podcast network in the business,
we'll still remain the same girls we've always been. We'll click lobster, we'll take road trips,
we'll argue, we'll discuss guys, we'll visit the market, we'll argue, we'll go to the post office,
we'll play around on our Mac, and we'll also argue, and we wouldn't have it any other way.
If you've never heard of the show, check out our video podcast. We're up to 30 episodes and are
going to be bigger and battered in 2006. Hey, and maybe we'll get you a sense of what
I find. Now that we're all in the network. That's my front door, Carla.
And then I'll listen to the nurse get her a black fine. No. And again, Adam, we're super
excited to join the pod show and don't forget we love you Adam. Bye.
I love you two girls. And welcome to the pod show family. Great to have more of
they also do a video podcast of the show, which is at first glance, you might think
unbelievably boring with one static shot, but you kind of get sucked into it and then throw
them out of it. Like, can't help it. And the girls don't forget, by the way, we have more women
on the pod show podcast network. I had the run, John L, who are sponsored by iKview,
download.acview.com. Yes, you mentioned magic course, and then there's all of the queue potters,
some of the women, some undefined, but all all great shows were happy to have them aboard.
Dawn from Dawn Drew. You know, let's go on and on. I think it's actually I love it. You know,
I think that there's many more women in pod casting than we're seeing women in broadcasting.
At least that's my my personal experience. Great to have you guys aboard.
Hey, it's Friday. So that means we've got tons of stuff to do. And wow, what would a Friday be without
a bit of Trinity? Unless be honest. You can humbers sing along, if you wish.
Just three short ones today. Of course, I don't have Trinity here with me. She's sitting comfy
and snug in the garage at the Curry condo. So, um, but there is some stuff happening over here
as a Mark Waymouth email me at him on the local BBC news in the Midlands. There was a clipping
which ties in with the attached article and hyperlink about the first garage in the UK to offer
100% biodiesel. Sounds like you should get up there for the English angle on things,
which is bound to be a little more basic than anything in California. And it's a link from
positive news.org.uk article number 45. I'll make sure a link shows up in the show notes. Thanks, Mark.
Yeah, I think this thing is really taken off. In fact, I was watching a best of top gear
yesterday. And they raised a mini, a new mini versus a scoda diesel and the scoda beat the
pants off the mini. Even though the audience thought that the mini would win. And of course,
the scoda was a diesel. And the reason why scoda is making diesels because they say it is the
future of automobile engines. And I think I have to concur. I believe we'll, you know, just before
we get into the Mad Max situation, we'll all kind of be, you know, pooping in our tanks, using
that biodiesel. It'll work. And it smells so wonderful. John Prosser says, Adam,
interesting piece on biodiesel. We'll show him on the BBC Monday, the 16th of January.
Why are you in San Francisco? Starts about 10 minutes in. It's inside out chip fat is the
title of the feature. It's from the BBC show inside out. I don't know if that's still available
on the BBC website because they do take stuff down after like a week or so. But make
you very much John. It's good to see the stuff is happening in the UK. And David Patrick
says, uh, biodiesel must be going big time. We're starting to get the first backlash about
his production. Oh, second. I think I have to go look at the link here. Well prepared, Curry. Here
we go. It's a BBC link. Biofuel raises global dilemmas. The massive depots and west six
grains sprawling processing plant and henstredger filling to the brim, not only with locally
grown wheat, but also with hope for a more environmentally friendly future. Uh, but people are
pitching and moaning about having those things nearby. But you're right. I think backlash
and we're going to see a lot of backlash coming. This is just impossible to think that
from a political perspective. People aren't all over the map on this stuff. You know, trying to
protect their their own interests, which is something that can be expected. And we'll just keep
on truck and boys and girls as we keep our eye on that fabulous biodiesel industry with Trinity.
Yeah, thank you. I don't for being in her take. Trinity. Oh, Trinity. Yeah. Right on.
Some feedback from Frank Yonan who has, you know, it's a ball's in my court, Frank. I apologize.
Frank really did all the design for the tattoo that I want to get. And Patricia and I just haven't
really found the time to sit down and go over the last couple of bits and send that back to them
for one final revision. We've got everything down. Everything's pretty much done. So I apologize
of just been a bit late. He did weigh in this for this show with a couple other topics. First splits
on PMN. I'd like to have something and let's me push artists for free and push our other artists
for a little share. But in the end, it's all about the numbers for me. How much is generated by
what link? Not money, but successful transfers. Number that I can use for other projects, other
parts of my site, etc. Not quite sure. Okay, so you want to how many people you've sent
over to an artist's website, perhaps? I think we can do that in a problem there. And yes, it will be
entirely possible for a podcast or a listener who helps in selling a track through a link on
their show site or a show notes or a link on a listener website or weblog any kind of HTML page,
essentially. You'll be able to give that entirely to the artist if you wish. Or maybe we can set up
a third category of charities. Just as an example, I don't care. That's fine. Whatever you
guys want to do. About learning Gaelic, I can understand a bit of Gaelic, but had a hard time
speaking of writing it, uh-huh. Learned it by translating clanid and anyotunes. Interesting.
To arrive from having to paint letters in art school where I did book of Kells Illuminations.
Wow. Why were you translating Enia and clanid lyrics? Interested.
And uh, what is this? In case you're too enlist, nah, I don't know what they want to go into that
right now. Uh, let me see. We have, uh, we have another audio crew. I have another audio feedback
here. Let me see how long is it? It's about a minute 17 and won't make that before the
satellite window closes. Okay. Let me tell you then, uh, let me see if there's anything else that
we had to talk about. Shoot. Here. I'll grab this one. Hey Adam, I was listening to your show,
uh, 323 and I heard someone sent you an email about, um, your show and there's Enmicro.
I actually have a Zenmicro and I do use media player. And of course, I listened to your show
and I listened to it on my MP3 player. And everything is working fine and, um, I have never had
any trouble with the transfers even with the new shows. So I'm thinking, maybe it's his firmware.
I know creative just uh, release new firmware. So that might be a problem. Anyways, thanks. Bye.
Yeah, good point. Although, you know, it's, in fact, I was given a Zenmicro, uh, portable MP3 player,
the Zen, something. I forget what it is. By the way, these are the people who invented the Zen
cast. And the first thing when the box was given to me was said, oh, you have to go and update the
firmware. I'm like, that is not a good thing. They should really make sure that, you know,
they get all their software stuff rolling and you shouldn't have to, you know, they should package
it with something so that happens automatic. Hey, folks, listening to Syria stars 103 Pacifico's
Hellways up next, then Madge, then Dawn and Drew and tonight, it's the roadhouse with Tony right
here on the pod show. Oh, shoot. There we go. Sorry. I forgot to open up the fader. Actually,
I got a feedback on that about that sound. Very interesting. This is from the application
countdown clock. Real simple, beautiful, love it. My young says, just FYI, FYI, the sound from that
countdown clock program you use is indeed registered to Sony. SOE specifically, that Sony online
entertainment. It's the you've just completed a quest sound from their ever quest game.
Keep using it if you wish, but if Sony finds out, I'm sure that give you plenty of copyright
hassles. Whoa. Okay. Don't want to do that. And is that absolutely 100% sure? We know that Sony
didn't rip it off from somewhere. Maybe the countdown clock guys can check in with that. They should
probably be aware of that. You know what? Since you were so nice to send me a free copy,
if that indeed is something you got from somewhere out there and you want that change because
you probably get in trouble. Eventually, if they find out about you distributing this stuff,
let me know. I'll make a new sound for you. Be happy to hook you up with that.
Hello Adam, come and buy it. What's in the fall of Portuguese? I heard just speaking a little
Portuguese one of your shows, so this is to test your years. My feedback is about the upcoming podcast
deliver network. I really looking forward to that. And you hinted about the partnership,
partnership with LimeLide. From that, I assumed that all the hosts here in the
cybersecurity will be done by them. That makes sense. But my question is, have you considered ways
to migrate existing RSS feeds into the new network? I currently have my podcast hosted at
Potomatic.com and would hate to lose my scars with faithful listeners. I'm a podcast or here in
some follow and if any of your listeners are from Brazil or can understand Portuguese,
and I want to listen some of the best tunes of the Potomatic music network. They're
welcome to listen to my show at rickpot.potomatic.com. That's our ICKPOD. The show's important to
use since my idea is to promote the bands around here in Brazil, and the podcast scene here is really
growing. Without that, maybe I can quit my day job. In the meantime, more cowbell.
Yeah, excellent. Good question. Yeah, of course we consider that. Absolutely. We call the
feature the feed vacuum. And when you sign up as a podcaster to the with pod show to the podcast
delivery network, at least you're given an option to sucking your pre-existing feed. And the
files actually, it'll suck everything over for you. And you can don't have to wait for it and
start sucking and you just keep on a truck and you'll see little status bar up there in the top.
It's pretty cool. Now, let's talk about this for one second, though, because there is something
very important to mention. If you want to, of course it will depend on what RSS fee, this is
really for podcasters, y'all. What RSS fee do you want to be using? Now, if you use a service like
feed burner, if you use a service like, well, libson or what was the one I've got the one you're
using? Okay, whatever one. You know, changing that, it basically needs a technological insert,
which we call a redirect. And not all company, I believe libson offers it, you know, so if you
wanted to leave, then, and by the way, they should charge money for it if they don't, they should.
If you want to leave, then they can just redirect all requests for your existing feed to the location
of your new feed. I'm going to have the exact same issue when I migrate over to the, to the
PDN as well, because I've been using a radio user land RSS feed for, well, forever, basically.
So, I'm going to have to ask them, the folks at radio user land, if they'll put a redirect on
their server for me, I'm hoping they, they offered it once, I'm hoping that they still will,
that'd be very cool. But the real solution to this, and of course, I've messed it up myself.
The real solution is to register a domain name and use that domain name and take a little bit of
time to understand how it works and what you can do with it, because it really makes moving servers
extremely efficient and easy and you don't have to rely on anyone else. Maybe
a system's administrator for your domain name, but if you go to a place like GoDaddy, they make
it pretty simple. And in fact, when you sign up to the PDN, you can, you can map an existing domain
name to it if you want to buy one. Then we actually have GoDaddy will be integrated directly,
so you can, oops. Oh, podpim is going to get angry. So you can map a domain name immediately to
to your show site and your RSS feed. And if you want to move and you want to go away,
then all you have to do is just point it to a different server. The domain name and the RSS feed
know that stuff and those links will all remain intact. That's really critical stuff. And I encourage
you to take it. Is there, could someone please send me, there's got to be some kind of how to
a really simple, well written document about domain names and just for, you know, for a podcast,
you just want to get going, but does want to, you know, be looking out towards the future,
so they can understand what, you know, what you go through. I mean, in fact, I'll even look and see
if GoDaddy has any of that stuff on their site, you would expect to have some, some information
about it. And of course, there's all kinds of services that you can add to it and you can have email
at it. So, you know, looking forward to it, I kind of get to Brazil, man. Ron and Marta, I
went to Brazil for a new year, so I said it had a really good time. Patricia wants to go to.
Yes, so much to do, so little time.
Metro, sexual, metro, sexual, sexual, sexual, sexual, sexual, sexual, it's Adam Curry's Metro,
sexual moment. Oh yeah. Adam Curry's Metro, sexual moment. I got to say, I catch myself
humming the tune quite a lot these days, which is a little bit disconcerting, but hey, thanks very
much everyone who sent in audio feedback for the Metro's sexual moment. Let's get right to it.
Hey, Adam, it's Derek Miller from podcast.pandmachine.com. Leave a message for you again.
I've got a cold, so I've got a really good radio and answer voice right now. Anyway,
you wanted some audio feedback for the Metro's sexual moment. You've got it. I have three things
to talk about. One is electric shabers. I'm an electric shaber user, but we've got our
controversies too. I use both the rotary shabers, the three head things like the fillet shave
and the brawn foil shaber. Right now I'm using the brawn, but I think I prefer the rotary
shaber more. It seems to shave a bit better on my face, and it doesn't seem to drop so many
little fragments of hair all over the place. Second is facial cleanser. I really like the stuff
with the little microbeats, and I've got some sort of generic brand right now that's got like an
orange scent. Really nice. Good stuff. You should use it as well as moisturizer. Finally,
this you'll like to know about. Here in Vancouver in Canada, there's a place called the
absolute spa. They've got a few locations, but the hotel Vancouver downtown, they've got a men's
only spa, and it's got PlayStation while you're getting your pedicure done. Now how good is that?
No, I also haven't been there yet, but I think I'll go. Anyway, that's my Metro Central Audio
Feedback for now. I'm at podcast.pinmachine.com. I've got an out of love. I've got a podcast with
free songs. I'm on the podcast using network. Right now, I've got this great radio and that's
a voice I wish I had to keep it without having the cold. Talk to you later. I do. You know what?
If you're in San Francisco, I'd give you my parking spot while I'm away. Thank you very much.
Yeah, you know, I worked at an electronic store when I was 15 on Saturdays, and I worked at the
same, well right next to the counter I was at, and I was selling like everything from cassette tapes to
resistors, capacitors, transistors, even some chips. Right next to me was the, you know, the department
that does electric gear, like mixers and vacuum cleaners and shavers, but sometimes they come over to my
counter, and this is the nasties thing, because their shavers wouldn't be working anymore,
and then they'd come up and they'd have one of those foil shavers, and they'd pull it out of
their pocket, and they'd be like, oh look, my shavers, we're going to be more, and they'd plop
open the top right there, and all the hair would come out and just cover my entire counter.
It was the most disgusting thing. So I really got tuned into it, when someone started pulling
that electric razor, their pocket would be like, stop right there, whatever you're doing,
you have to be the next counter, please, sir. Yeah, electric doesn't work very well for me.
I've gotten pretty accustomed to the G3 power raise, and I must say it's, it's feeling pretty good.
I have bought my first replacement blade and cannot tell any difference between the original
it came with yet, certainly not visual, but I've only done one pass, so I'll keep my eye on it.
The other one lasted for what? A good three weeks, so stay tuned for more on that.
Hi Adam, this is Doc from all critters.potshow.com, and I just wanted to let you know that
I'm one of those kind of guys there, very lucky, because I got a wife that loves that three
day growth look, and that's how I've had it. Never go on a shave it up, because I think she'll
kill me if I do. So anyway, I like that, a trim up the edges, just a regular bit razor, and you know,
turn around dry shave. Usually you don't put anything on, jumping this quick shower, and hurry
up and get nice and land it up, close those pores up, and it usually works out quite nicely for me,
so. That's what I use, nothing too fancy, nothing too special. Tried the wall, I liked it,
but I got a new one, and it's called the peanut, and the peanut is absolutely cool. Everybody's
got to go take a look, because this is absolutely the neatest little electric razor you can get.
It's got the little attachment that makes it so that you can go ahead and shave down really
super close, and keep that three day look. I mean, it's just great. I love it. Robin loves it.
I love it. But can we say, you got to make them all happy. Doing a great job with the daily source
code? Hope to talk to you soon. All right, dude, make sure you send me a link. Maybe you did. I didn't
catch them. Send me a link next time. The peanut is that what you said? So many devices that we have to
check out on this show. If in case you didn't know, the Metro sexual moment is where we all kind of
hang out and talk about, you know, men's beauty in moisturizing and shaving, like that.
Nick Zypler says, heard on the DSC323 that you wanted to work with deal with Gillette to get a
free mock three power to all of your listeners. Did you ever think about trying to work with
deal to get those of us who have already purchased one free blades? Just an idea. Thanks for the
great show. Well, that may actually be tougher than you think, because that is the bread and butter,
you know, they want to give away a shaver with one razor and one battery to get people completely hooked.
You're already hooked. But I of course I'll try. You know, I'll try. Shoot.
Hey, Adam, it's KFC. From the potchick show, and I have a Metro sexual moment for you.
My husband, Mr. Flows, sometimes, had not had a pedicure. Oh, wait, no, I think you had one
pedicure a couple of years ago. But anyway, so I'm getting this pedicure across from my age
office. And they've got this really amazing chair. A lot of pedicure places, ladies, you know,
have the vibration chairs. Well, this one was just home and God. It was better than any other one
that I'd set it for. So I'm like, okay, that's it Saturday. Next week, I'm going to bring my husband
here. I'm going to get pedicures together. It's sitting these like total massage chairs. You know,
just for a treat for each other, because we don't do shit like that much. And hey, my show is all
about positive. I've been this was very good for that. So he got a pedicure and he faced a
defeat in the little bubbly tub and they rub. Just so you know, guys or even girls, if you haven't
had one, it's amazing. Usually they're under $20 to last. And most times, you can just like walk into
a nail place and get them. But guys, more and more men are doing this. I was talking about that
and they were saying, oh, for sure, that lots more men are coming in. So Dan gets this pedicure
and they rub his legs and use all this mint and exfoliate and do your nails, all this stuff.
And then at the very end, like, come. I said, hey, why don't you get them? Get them wax. He's like,
no way, man, that sounds painful. I'm like, no. Paraphine wax, man. Paraphine wax, your feet, guys.
Oh, he was just like, oh, my God. What they do is they grease up your feet and then they stick
them in this like hot wax. But it's not hot. Like, oh, he hot. It's hot, like, ooh, that's
kind of hot. And so you dip your feet in there and then they pull them out and they dip them again
and they pull them out into mint again and they pull them out and then they wrap them in plastic bags
and you sit and they, and they kind of like, they're like little sauna bags around your toes.
Yeah. And then after, I don't know, like, five or ten minutes, they, um, I was listening to
the Don and Drew show while we were doing it. It was perfect. Anyway, so they, um, massage the bags
on the wax and everything on your feet and they're just so soft and silky and, um, um, I found it
very hot and Mr. Prossi liked it too. So there you go. For your mental section moment and
your mental section moment. Yeah. I was ready to tune there. I can't see. Thank you. Appreciate it.
Man, it's just just tiring all that metro sexual moments stuff. And I can just hear Chris Rockwell
yelling and saying that I'm turning them men into pussies. No way, dude. You got to try this stuff.
Yeah, I like drinking beer and farting and watching football. Of course I like that. But
paraphernal wax on your feet, my friend. No, no, no, that is something you really must try.
Yeah, um, I'm part of a close class trying to make a difference at a local hospital.
I'm living in the northeast of Ireland. And in the last four years, we've had three A&E
departments closed in and one hospital almost completely closed due to lack of equipment and
staff shortages. We're working on a method of enhancing some of the older equipment, like
Harry Potter, Harry Potter machines, through modified airport express. So doctors, nurses,
nurse stations can mar her their patients, even while they're in their offices and other
parts of the hospital. So let's say I'm a patient. This allows my doctor to check only,
then go to the A&E patients during the x-ray and still have my vitals on a screen with them all the time.
We're working on software for palm, windows mobile and tablet PC. And because I've really
found the java, we're going to be running a confibrillator type widget in the corner of the tablet.
So the doctor can always see my vitals. It's kind of like a system widget showing CPU usage and
RAM usage in the corner of the screen, but it'll show hardware and that kind of thing.
Essentially, I don't know, I'm sending this to you as we need some help. We don't have any equipment
to test this on. We've really grateful if anyone could help us. We're looking for a tablet PC,
a few palm-based devices and a couple of windows mobile devices.
And even at other, they can help contact me at tom.landi, l, a, n, d, y at gmail.com.
Thanks very much for your time. So I've actually exchanged some email with Tom over the past
couple of days about this. And it's a pretty cool project. They really are trying to do this
on the spot, on location, getting the stuff implemented. And trying to make a difference in
health care, dudes, I'm all for it. And I have my craplet here, which is it's just that mind you.
It's a craplet, but it works pretty good, except for the the sound card is shit.
And the battery is, you know, the battery doesn't hold the charge much longer than 10 minutes.
Be happy to send it to you for the good cause. If you promise to keep me up to speed on, you know,
send me an audio feedback from time to time. Just let me know how things are going. Let me know
how the apps are going. And anyone else, you should send me a link to a website. Oh,
I guess you sent you, you mentioned to email. If anyone has any mobile devices, I mean,
you know, this is what happens. And you start casting shit away. And it's just laying here in the corner.
So be happy to send it to you. Absolutely. On its way, send me an address. And you know,
you'll have to figure out the battery thing cause you'll be very disappointed with the mobility of the
craplet as it is cause you really have to stay tethered to the wall. So yeah, let me just
reinstall XP and wipe everything off and clean all my shit out. No, I'll send it to you. Absolutely.
Thomas Vincent, sent it to email. Love bill. Then we played bill sound scientists. It was very
happy about the free download of the new album. I was even more pleased when I looked at their
schedule. So they will be in my town Friday night, expect an audio review of the show and perhaps
live sound seeing of the concert next week. Looking forward to it, Thomas. Those guys are good. Well,
that guy is good, I should say. Really like Bill a lot. Hey, we're getting through it.
Couple more audio comments will be done and we can get started with the weekend.
Hey, Adam. This is Matt Dutillo from the Matt's today in history podcast at Matt's today in
history.com. I just listened to DSC322 and you were talking about celebrity and the Corey from sports
talks.com. Got the ball rolling with that. And I had mentioned this in my blog just a few days ago
where I think what's going to happen with celebrity and podcasting is that most podcasters,
guys like myself are probably always going to work our day jobs and we'll have listenerships
in the hundreds or low thousands. And we will be well known to those people that tiny little
niche that we serve. And I think this is going to happen not only with podcasting, but with other
forms of media as well in music, you know, maybe indie movies. I think that the group of people that
are, you know, quote unquote Hollywood famous is going to become smaller and smaller as our
entertainment options become more diversified. I'd be interested to get your thoughts on this.
Anyway, great show. Thank you for what you've done for podcasting and have a great one.
Yeah, Matt. Thank you. Good weekend to you as well. Yeah. I think you're right. I don't think we'll see
another Howard Stern appear in any form of media. We'll probably see let's just take audio podcasting
as an example. We'll see thousands of Howard Sterns with, you know, somewhere the hundreds,
some of the thousands, some maybe with 10,000 listeners. And that'll be a really
interesting group of people both by individual show, by individuals and an aggregate.
And I think, and we've talked about this a lot, the relationship between the podcaster,
the producer of the podcast, and the audience is something very special, not to be devalued down
to an advertising CPM, you know, cost per thousand impressions. I think that's, you know,
the whole idea of selling stuff solely, certainly solely based on CPM. I think it's really
selling a lot of this short because look at what's happening. Look at what's what's going on
with commercial messages. Look at this podcast. Look at what's happening with the eye dog. It's such
a beautiful example. Yesterday I played that song. My music, myself, and my eye dog. Something like that.
I love that a lot. So I think that you're absolutely right. That is what's going to happen.
And it'll be fun to watch and fun to be a part of and fun to jump around and fun to listen to
the different shows and different shows even in the same genre. It's going to be cool. Really will be.
And Nicole says hi out. I'm there about three or four podcasts in the Irish language. Those
of us who speak the language call it Irish. Scott's gaelic is gaelic. The pod father of Irish
language podcasting is named Khan Charlie Oscar November November. He's been podcasting for quite a
few months. I'm Neil. That's india mic echo alpha lima lima dot blugsbark dot com.
So I guess I should check that out. I should have played a piece of that. I was stupid in my.
Okay. I'll get that set up for the next time Patricia makes a disparaging remark about gaelic language.
Hi. This is Peter from the ultimate mix podcast. I'm inviting you to join me as I journey through
the pod safe music network. Each week I will be spinning the best music new or old from the piano.
That will be inviting you to listen up to interact with your suggestions of great music that I can share
with other subscribers. So for an ultimate mix of music where Rhett's fun co-punk jazz a rock
be sure to join me as I cover all aspects of the music revolution that is pod safe music. So if you fancy
having your ears fine tune to the best music around, then head on over to ultimate mix dot
block spot dot com or find me in the i change music store. The ultimate mix podcast great music
of my style from now on.
Well hello Adam what's shaking this is Brad from Boston Masterchusets finally home of the
world champion Boston Red Sox. I'm coming to today January 26th 2006 raw unscripted unreherst
unproduced without a lead in or any music. In fact I don't know what the hell I'm doing
but I'm having a blast. I'm new to podcasting and this is my very first experience recording.
So I'm really flying by the seat of my pants. I figured out how to record a vocal track
using garage band on my power book G4. So I hope it is of the format and quality
at best acceptable to you and your listeners. I've been listening to Delta Sierra Charlie
for about six months now and really enjoy your show. I especially dig the podcast format.
I'm a fan of the talk radio and an even bigger fan of the Tibo revolution and for me
podcasting has really had a sweet spot. I get a kick out of all your aviation references
during your show because I'm a professional pilot. I fly for a company called netchets www.netchets.com
is a private fractional jet ownership company and I fly the sessness citation 10 business jet
a real speedster and a lot of fun to fly. I was wondering if you had had any experience
soaring or flying gliders. I started flying gliders a few years ago as a hobby and highly recommended.
As a flight instructor I find it an exceptional way to develop stick and rudder skills
and it is a phenomenal way to share flying with friends and family. Let me know if you have any
questions about flying gliders. I'd be happy to talk to you about it. Before I sign off,
I had a few questions for you though. First, do you have any tips, references or resources
for new podcasts and listeners alike looking to get more involved? I'd really appreciate it.
And second, during Delta Sierra Charlie 317 you promote a band called the Butterfly
Catchers. I really dig their sound and have tried to find their music on various websites whether
be their own or through the pod show network where I could buy their music free and clear
but I've had no success. I would really like to get a hold of their album and listen to it further
and short of waiting for the podcast network and pod safe music which you guys are working on to
kick into full gear. Do you have any recommendations where I could go to get a hold of some
their music? Thanks for introducing me to podcast and I'm looking forward to all that the
pod show network has to offer. See it. All right, dude. Well, let's go in reverse chronological order
then shall we? You definitely can find the Butterfly Catchers at the pod safe music network that's
music.podshow.com. Any good place is to start if you want to get into pod casting. I would
suggest going to podcastally.com and if you're a listener, I suggest of course going to podshow.com.
Of course I'm going to suggest that. Don't get all huffie now.
And about the net jets thing, dude, that is very cool. I've actually been considering for quite a while now
purchasing 25 hours for net jets Europe because, you know, sometimes it's just, you know,
you want to make sure you can get out of an airfield, IFR and all that stuff and maybe want to go
a little bit further than just the Netherlands. And so I thought maybe 25 hours would be
would be reasonable to just try it out. So yeah, I love the concept. In fact, I started a
fractional helicopter company based on the net jets concept. Of course my mistake was trying to set
that up in the Netherlands where they don't want you to do anything in the air. So that was quite
an interesting journey. And congratulations on your first recording. Good deal. Okay, two more things
in the amount of here. The first one is very interesting. Speaking of the Netherlands,
there's a chain of very cheap clothing stores, which is called Z-Mum.
And I guess here, and I think that I've more than just closed, but in the states, we would say
K-Mart. And in the UK, maybe Woolworth, I don't know, something like that. But you know,
really cheap-ass shit, bad lighting. And they have now decided that they are no longer
going to play music in their stores because they find the Dutch Buma Stemera, which is Ask Abbey
Am I equivalent, more or less? Their fees to be too outrageous had cost them 50 to 60,000 euros a
year across all their stores. And this actually seems to be a trend of stores and other public
places who basically are paying. And they use the radio, which I think is pretty amazing because
the radio, of course, already pays once for the song. And then because they're technically
re-broadcasting the radio by having speakers on in a public place, they have to pay once again.
That's crazy. Now, I'm hearing noise about other, actually, restaurants and bars
who want to go completely pod safe. This is a fantastic fucking development.
Although I say good luck. Let's see if the authorities let you get away with it. I believe that
they will say, you know, there's just to assure that there's no risk of you playing or playing songs
and music that are licensed through us, you're going to have to pay something anyway. I would not be
surprised if that is enforced. And it's compulsory. And instead of, you know, well, it may not
turn out that way. But if it does, you know, then I definitely think this is something we should
dive into because the concept of pod safe bars, pod safe restaurants. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. I'm seeing
this go very, very far. And finally, I am Marpezia from MarpeziaNow.com. I've attached my new
single double-fisted. I hope you like it. I heard a rumor that you can't find good rap music. Well,
if you don't like my song. Oh, well, play it anyway. Ha, ha, ha. Please take a listen to my show, too.
I play all kinds of great independent rap artists. Ha, ha, ha. You will probably never get this.
Talk to you later, Marpezia aka six foota. Well, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Not safe for young years.
And I don't like to roll with you, man. He's eye cake's one Carlos and up chicks. Only
behind me, she's make a moth cliques. We get prom pics, adoptings. We know nice and free drinks.
Where VIP would you think? When I in the club, everybody should be in love. Everybody want to hug.
And I get down into a resort. I get a little pussy. They ain't a week's bumping.
And the wait just don't hear me. So when I hear it, I though I'd do up. I know what Martin is
going to hook my ass up. And it begins with ha, ha. Marpezia's double face did.
Rolled, rolled, rolled equals, and double face did. The whole table is
getting twisted. I just get it true. But some say it was not just a word.
Rolled, rolled, and rolled equals, and double face did. The whole table is
And I keep penny on ice. I like it corrode it in my right.
Felicity is supply and drinks. All night the dark liquor makes me want to fly.
Cause I'm doing a try to take advantage of this time sexy savage.
Just as I see that my hands ain't free, but I'll still do damage best believe.
So we're to the wise, a grab about the thousand when you're talking to me.
We're looking into my eyes cause I'm six, two, eight shit. She could do our Marpezia
hook thought to new. So if you want to keep me nice, order me a drink and make it twice.
Rolled, rolled, rolled equals, and double face did. The whole table is getting twisted.
I just get it true. But some say it was not just a word.
Rolled, rolled equals, and double face did. The whole table is getting twisted. I just get it true.
But some say it was not just a word.
And you need a drink to your left. And one for your right.
We gon' get fucked up. If it takes all night, come on.
Rolled, rolled equals, and double face did. The whole table is getting twisted. I just get it true.
You gotta have to trust to know what it's about. Marpezia's in a house or beast to make you bounce.
Six foot two, it looks long. It's hell. What I do, what I do, what do we wear.
Oh, you gotta watch these two rumors like it like me. I don't care who she might be.
Because without Ben, I don't get scintail, I won't break and down.
Oh, you'll be male. So fuck it. Let's dance, everybody. Raise your hands, fit.
Shake that ass, like Marpezia fits. I'm that little real queen born in the bag.
Yeah, that I mean now with TVCA, Central Valley, California. Yeah, it's where you fight me today.
I'm that bitch, Reppin' Motown. This is for the notes.
How to hold it down. And if you see me with a frown, I'm on empty, by a round.
Tell the bartender what to do. Order me to roll that in a head and see through.
Rolled, rolled equals, and double face did. The whole table is getting twisted. I just get it true.
Yeah, educational, for sure. Double-fisted.
Marpezia. Why do I play this? Well, first of all, I liked it.
Second of all, wouldn't it be cool if we could melt the hip hop culture and podcast culture together?
I mean, that's just an art form that is just oozing through any distribution channel possible.
Yeah, you know what you hear on the radio, that's the stuff that makes it through, but it's the stuff that's
pounding on cars, on city streets. It's CDs that are being burnt and handed out on in school yards.
You know, this is the stuff that is just beautiful for potsafe music and podcasting. If we,
you know, if we look at the music side of things, oh, a girl can dream, can't she?
Hey, everybody, have yourself a fantastic weekend. I'll be back on Monday.
Some time next week, I have to go to the Netherlands for this court case. And of course, we'll
be taking the, uh, the Dishiba, uh, slap top with me and with cast blaster with the potfather edition.
And so you won't have to miss anything, essentially. I hope not, at least. And, uh,
well, if you have any feedback, itemaccurry.com, or, uh, you can always drop a promo at promos.podshow.com.
And, of course, this show was found the daily source code.com. We can find the feed to subscribe to
and just listen to new episodes as they come online. As Roger Small says, the best thing to do
is set that page as your home page. Have a good one, everybody. I'll see you on Monday, bye-bye.