Find this podcast and others like it at the number one new media network,
paucho.com.
Better faster, stronger, stronger.
And now with new minty fresh scent.
You're listening to Donut, Sesame, until 5-0 minor.
With 15 pounds of pasta, sliding down the drain.
Stainers?
And a sense sales strap to his ass.
Huh?
We don't need no stinkings.
He likes to think he's cooking in the kitchen.
Puff the casting.
It's Adam Curry.
You're listening to Donut's Gerrit Charlie.
The Daily source code.
With the one and only part on Adam Curry.
Brace yourself for the show that's got it all.
Potsay from music, the Lady Patricia, and of course, your host, Adam Curry.
Come to you from the Curry Condo and San Francisco, California.
Delta, Gerrit Charlie, 5-0, 9-0.
Oh, yeah.
Well, the tip of Jesus dropping in again.
I'm all alone out walking tonight.
I used to have a spring in my step, but now something is missing.
And I know it's not right.
Last year I was good and oh, Charlie,
Satanic was too to his word.
I was the top of the list of all those things.
I was the top of the list of all those who were blessed.
But this year I don't know.
I give back those toys and gadgets and it connects.
That he left under the tree.
Don't need the sweater and the jacket and the egg.
No, I've had it and it's no good for me.
If it's here, I've been thinking that I don't need a thing.
You get hiding a box, it's true.
There's all I want for Christmas is some hugging,
and it's kissing from you.
I give up my eye and watch a flow of blackberry.
I don't need to make any calls.
No, don't need my sling box.
Maybe you could call me crazy.
I don't watch it at all.
The magic bullet, the toast or the thing that makes the roast beat like so on TV.
All my brand new fender tell a caston.
It don't mean nothing to me.
No, I give back those toys and gadgets and it connects.
That he left under the tree.
Don't need the sweater and the jacket and the egg.
No, I've had it and it's no good for me.
Or this year I've been thinking that I don't need a thing.
You get hiding a box, it's true.
But all I want for Christmas is some hugging,
and it's the kiss in front of you.
Yeah, you know what's it to?
So come on baby, don't leave me blue and I'll be here.
Let's start something new.
Yeah, I give back those toys and gadgets and it connects.
That he left under the tree.
Don't need the sweater and the jacket and the egg.
No, I've had it and it's no good for me.
This year I've been thinking that I don't need a thing.
You get hiding a box, it's true.
There's all I want for Christmas is some hugging,
and it's the kiss in front of you.
And it's the love and some sweet.
I don't have a wanted on my Christmas,
but it was you.
Yeah, it's the encounter.
Just now when the Christmas is here, baby.
Some Christmas, hugging and kissing from you.
Everybody how you doing coming to you from the Curry condo
in a very sunny Northern California and San Francisco to be exact.
It is the Daily Source Code episode 5-0-9.
And just do you hear that?
I got a little home here.
I got a hummer.
Let me check, check one, two.
Okay.
Yeah, got in yesterday.
And after an uneventful flight, you know,
Virgin VS 19, C12K, if you're looking to blow me up, that's the one.
A little disappointing that normally they change the movies.
At the beginning of the month and I hadn't changed them yet.
I don't understand.
And boy, the state of movies can be so bad.
I think I've seen just about every single one of the 25 movies
that Virgin has available.
And it's...
They're also predictable.
Anyway, it was beautiful yesterday.
Got in one straight to the office.
We have a board of directors meeting this morning.
Got this afternoon, actually.
One o'clock.
And after that, it's like the first holiday party.
We've got like three holiday parties.
Well, I'm here.
So Patricia actually...
I love her to love her to bits, man.
She put together all the different outfits.
That's the cleaner Perkins thing.
You wear this one to Ray Lane's birthday.
This one to the Pod Show holiday party.
We are kind of in that festive spirit, aren't we?
And so are the Podcasters, by the way.
Lots of promos.
Hey, everyone.
This is Ed Roberts from a looking up a window music podcast.
Well, it's that time of the year.
Time to get ready for the Christmas season.
Time to get into some great Podsafe Christmas songs.
2005 saw some incredible Podsafe Christmas music.
And with the growth of Pod casting over the last year,
2006 promises to be even better.
And that's why I've started up a brand new podcast,
specifically for the Christmas season.
It's called Podsafe Christmas.
Every day, from now until Christmas,
I'll play two or three great Podsafe Christmas songs
that you can take with you as you get ready for the Christmas season.
It's your daily fix of Christmas music,
direct from the world of Podsafe music.
Visit PodsafeChristmas.com.
You can subscribe to the feed directly from there
or you can listen directly from the website.
Your soundtrack for the holidays.
PodsafeChristmas.com.
It's so weird, you know, traveling between two different continents.
It's hard to get into the Christmas vibe, you know.
It definitely celebrated differently in the UK.
And by the way, in the UK, the weather is kind of Christmasy.
It's shit.
It's completely, I left it was raining once again.
And then, you know, you get on a sheet metal tube
and you fly for 10 hours and then you're kind of out of it.
It says difficult.
Just kind of through some stuff here,
Ubercaster, which is, let's just call it the Cast Blaster for Mac,
although it isn't.
It's something completely different.
But a lot of people are using this program, Ubercaster.
And the question that came in a while ago, I think,
was when is this going to work with Podschio with the Pod Cast delivery network?
Just like Cast Blaster does.
If you haven't seen Cast Blaster, Cast Blaster.com,
you can create a podcast on it and fill in your information,
your details, your username and password
for the Podschio Pod Cast delivery network.
And it'll shoot up your show notes and get your feed in order
and take all that stuff and take care of all that stuff,
populate your homepage, etc.
And the question was, when is that going to work with Ubercaster?
And I saw that a new release came out of Ubercaster.
It's still a beta version.
And so I'm looking for the, you know,
for the compatibility, because I know that we worked pretty hard
and to grummit work with the guys at Ubercaster.
There was something really weird in Mac,
in the Mac OS that didn't do XML RPC properly.
I know a little bit of tinfoil hide moment.
So I know that that got resolved.
And so I'm looking through the revision history notes.
And it's out, it was actually in there in the previous release.
Only it says,
oh, check this out.
This function, this functionality,
not available in the free beta version.
I wonder why?
So I guess only if you pay for Ubercaster,
do you get that capability baked in?
Nah, it's a shame.
But anyway, that's, you know,
it's open for anyone.
Anyone can go to developer.podshow.com.
Still waiting for someone to make a,
some kind of connection from audacity,
which, of course, makes so much sense.
An open source project with an open API.
Could it be any easier than that, guys?
Even though we're in San Fran,
UK listen up, pay attention now.
Yeah, got an awesome piece of feedback about the,
I was waiting for this to happen.
And in fact, it took a little bit longer than I anticipated it to take,
because we have had other things lined up.
Well, I'll play this for you and you'll know what I'm talking about.
There Adam, it's probably beef and punky radio here.
I've just got a brief message for you.
And this has come in from one of our listeners.
This came through our beauty podshow page,
which is rather nice.
It says, the podshow stinger does suck,
but you know, sounds like some American
selling me a kitchen in the 50s.
I have to agree with them.
The podshow stinger in my opinion is absolutely rubbish.
I've had this idea for one that I think might be a bit better.
I will talk over the bits that are already done.
You'll see what I mean.
Podshow.
Beaty Podshow.
Sing along, too.
That's creative.
Podshow.
Beaty Podshow.
Wow.
All the way from good old blighty.
Just make it better Adam.
Just it was a favor, will you?
Yeah.
They sent in another one.
Let me see if I can find that one.
That was pretty funny, too.
Yeah, I agree.
They sucked total ass.
I'm American.
I'm not English.
So I'm waiting for you guys to send something in.
Make some stinger as you call them.
Make them make me some stinger,
so we can put those in front of our UK podcast.
Yes, it's me.
Paulie beat from punky radio here.
Hi, Adam.
I just like to say that we've had a few comments from regular listeners
to punky radio since we've gone on to Beaty Podshow.
It's a fabulous pleasure to be here, of course.
But I don't have to say your stinger is rubbish.
What an earth is going on.
Why have you got to say, oh, no.
Used to be in milk, but no.
It's an incredible blaty.
This is a good opportunity anymore.
I can't believe you're not using an English accent on there.
I'd like you to discuss.
I'd like you to change.
I've had enough.
And as if here's proof,
my co-host Tony never says beat to a ghost and Tony.
What do you think of it?
It's pants.
There you go.
There's your stinger.
Okay.
Another beaty, beaty Podshow podcast.
That's pants.
Make some.
Will you send them to me?
Adam at poncho.com.
Hey.
Stop fucking sizzling at Paul.
It took me a second or two to understand that one.
Because, of course, the original was.
Hey.
I don't know who this is, but stop fucking calling sizzling at Paul.
And stuff is getting out of control.
Here's the edit room.
Stop fucking sizzling at Paul.
I haven't heard from sizzling a while.
I don't know who this is, but stop being calling just out.
You guys are out of control.
One, two, one.
Six, two, five.
Six, three, five.
Seven.
One, two, one.
Six, two, five.
Six, three, five.
Seven.
Hello.
Adam.
This is Paul.
I'm getting calling from the UK.
You know, you said, of course.
I know it sounds.
Put me this.
Come in line number into your phone.
And then you'll just phone it whenever something comes up.
That you want to comment on.
And that is exactly what I've done.
Put it in tonight.
And then something came up.
Interess in the accessibility of pod show and B.T. pod show.
And all that good stuff.
And so far, yet, it has been very much in access to blockchain.
I'm talking as a blind person in the screen reader.
But very excited to hear what you were saying.
And show five, five.
About being able to make actually a lot of it.
I love it.
My sister, the story was because of the software that you're using.
Having accessibility.
Controls within it.
So looking forward to very much.
Looking forward to paying loads of good music and all that the pod show has to offer.
And it's a very skydiving.
So thanks very much.
And this is Paul Hopkins.
Sign in us.
And you can listen to my podcast.
www.vipodcasting.lipsing.com.
All right.
Take care.
Oh, God.
A blind folder.
Mind you.
Yep.
When I walked into the office yesterday afternoon, Andrew Grummit was one of the first
people I saw.
And he said, Oh, dude.
We're about to push a whole bunch of fixes.
Accessibility stuff.
We've got to figure it out.
So we've been working really hard.
Apparently, it aged Q on this flash stuff.
We got a great tip from a listener.
I told us that there were all kinds of accessibility options in flash.
So I think we're getting pretty close there.
To people do take this very seriously.
Believe me.
As a whole bunch of stuff that that we've been fixed.
I think with every push we do now is like 50 new fixes are going up.
It's really.
It's pretty outrageous.
It's cool.
Saw some interesting numbers.
That was reading through just some news articles and stuff on the plane.
The first one was this pew internet study.
Where the number of people who have heard a podcast in the past year has double
from the year before.
That's the great news.
Interestingly enough, mainstream media has picked up on another piece of the report.
That states that and this, of course, is still something we have to work on.
That states that only 1% of people.
I guess what they're trying to say is only 1% of people have subscribed and download a podcast every day.
I think it's a little unclear in in the survey itself.
But mainstream publications have taken that to say.
I've seen headlines like podcasting 15 minutes are up.
Yeah, dream on motherfuckers.
And another statistic that I thought was interesting.
Zoom apparently took a 9% of the portable player marketplace.
Since it's launch.
And that, of course, is being touted as a tremendous failure.
And I don't want to get into the pros and cons of the zoom.
You know, the iPod has currently now has 63% of the total market in zoom has 9%.
Let's just say 10%.
I'll take 10% of any kind of market like that.
I don't think that's bad at all.
In fact, I was amazed.
I guess we'll find out the real numbers after the holiday season.
But I think this is whenever you have a market where there's a clear leader,
you can always take away, I mean, it's almost literally the same as podcasting.
What is the global advertiser broadcast advertising market?
What is the US broadcast advertising market?
That's tens of billions of dollars.
I'm pretty sure.
So, okay.
So if we're taking, was it 12% now or listening to podcasts?
I think we're starting to tap into something really big.
It'll be quite a while before we put a dent in mainstream advertising and broadcasting.
But come on.
We've only been around for two years.
It's podcasting and already 12%.
The zoom only weeks and 9%.
I don't think that's bad at all.
I had him.
This is the long term, long term listener of the DSC.
Adam, I'm just going to pick you mind.
Me and the good lady were off to Amsterdam on Friday to celebrate my birthday.
And apart from the usual spots, the red light district,
one that is that you could recommend a nice place to eat or maybe somewhere to see.
We're staying in a family of big boards called the BoCell,
not quite sure that's all about the serenity.
And also as well, I'm a fly from the Newcastle upon time across to Amsterdam.
I'm just wondering what the connections are like from the airport into the main city centre.
Maybe you could tell me a little bit if you're able to.
Love the show and keep smiling or by the way, the wife's culture and I'm a folder.
I don't know if you want to go to Amsterdam together then.
That could cause problems.
If she scrunches and you folds, you just might want to leave her there, dude.
The BoCell, literally is a hotel that's a boat.
I have never been on it.
Was this a holiday package that you chose by any chance?
I don't think you could.
You shouldn't give a shit about that because it's clean and it works.
And it's reasonably located for the city centre, but you are literally on a boat.
But you should be having a lot of fun in the city.
So obviously, the red light district isn't even what it used to be anymore.
They've closed down large sections of it because of excessive drug trafficking.
None of the girls are Dutch anymore.
And that was kind of the fun of it.
You could walk in the red light district and you could wave high to the girls.
And they would speak your language if you were Dutch that is.
And it was how much more fun back in the old days.
You definitely want to go to the light supply.
And part of what you have to have to do as a tourist.
You have to go to the Bulldog.
I'm sure you've heard of that.
Ask them for the menu and have a sample from the menu.
Although if you were to walk in the lights a strat,
which is the street right off the lights a plane.
And you walk up, say, I think is it's two bridges.
Yeah, if you walk up two bridges and hang a right onto a crab.
I forget the name of the street.
Just ask someone for global chillage.
Global chillage.
That's the coffee shop you want to go to.
And I just tell them that Adam sent you.
Hi Adam.
How are you doing?
This is Aaron from SLV podcast.
I just took a question.
I was only just come across your show in the past couple of weeks.
In fact, I've been listening to it for about DSC full 50 onwards.
And I was just kind of wondering.
Is there any way to listen to all your old shows?
Some of the very very similar to what Rob Goldbeard's top of the podcast has been doing
his basically just really re-releasing his old shows on the, on the almost old feed?
I was just, I was only wondering purely because it will be great.
I think it all shows me.
I'm chiseled again and on the phone and what I was just saying.
Check out my podcast.
SLV podcast.
I'll tell you what you say.
Chiseled again Adam.
Ta-da.
Yeah.
Well, obviously, if you go to dataacourceco.com, you can go back in time on the calendar in the archives
and you can select any day you want and see what I was talking about then.
Up the, was the first two weeks of January will be moving.
We'll be moving all of our, all of our stuff into the new cottage.
And I think that I'm really just going to not work at all because I'm going to have to really
help a true show and pay a lot of attention to this move because it's been going.
It's been way too easy.
We've got to run into some crap somewhere.
So what I'll do there is I'll probably ask people to put together best of Charlie's again.
And maybe we do it a little more organized fashion.
So we don't have, you know, like five people trying to do a show for one day.
But that's probably, I like that a little bit more.
We do the best of Charlie's and we mash up bits from from previous shows.
And when we were in Patricia and Christina and I were in Portugal, we had some great
best of Charlie's that people would together.
It was just absolutely fantastic.
So I think that that's really what I was planning on doing.
But otherwise, you know, be my guest.
And go through the archives.
It's only 500 and eight besides this one that you haven't heard, perhaps.
Let's see what else did we have.
Report from the sun that have very, very trustworthy publication in the UK.
I might add apparently in any given 24 hour period.
20 million Brits come to orgasm.
That didn't sound right.
20 million Brits have an orgasm within any 24 hour period.
You guys are a bunch of horning by the fuckers.
You know, there's a lot of folks out there that claims to be Christian, but they ain't.
But we don't have to debate about what we should think.
If you were a chef, you wouldn't listen to what Jesus has to say.
He wouldn't be in the mess here at night.
In a world of sin, a man came to save humanity.
Now, after 2000 years, Jesus has some things to say.
The Jesus interview.
Get your feedback for Jesus.
Coming soon to audioattitude.com.
Oh, glory.
I can't wait.
The man is coming to talk to us.
Speaking of the man.
Hey, Adam, it's CC Chapman.
How's it going, man?
Great to see you in London at podcast on UK.
It was cool that we got the cross paths there.
Pink shirt and all.
Right, man?
It's all good.
Listen, I want to tell you about something that's pretty cool.
I know you don't play in second life very often anymore, but I wanted to do something
different this holidays.
I wanted it because I know last year, Potsay for Peace.
Both of us were really big into getting that going and getting it up and getting it live.
And I know you're still a huge supporter of the song as I am.
So I thought, wouldn't it be cool if we could bring Potsay for Peace to second life?
So what I've done is I worked with Brittany Mason to get a little holiday cheer that
I could spread a present that I could give to people.
And what actually happens is when the person gets the present when they open it up, it gives
them a snowman.
And what happens because I wanted it, you know, non-denominational.
So it could work for every holiday out there.
It puts a you put down a snowman.
And when you click on it, it starts playing the chorus from Potsay for Peace.
But it also opens up a website.
Takes you to Potsay for Peace.org directly.
And also gives you no card explaining what the charity is, how it worked.
And encouraging people where they can go to buy the song for 99 cents and where it
how it benefits.
So if you see one of these little snowman floating around second life, click on it.
And support Potsay for Peace.
It's a great song.
Slow.
I'm still amazed at what he did with it.
And all the artists took part in it.
I think it just is a testament to the power of podcasting and new marketing across the board.
And I think it's great.
I knew you'd be, I knew you would dig it even though you're not in second life a lot.
Because we've now brought, you know, we've crossed another threshold into yet another medium
for this to get played and hopefully open it up to new people.
And it gives you a perfect opportunity to play it, right?
Because that's what we're all about.
So I'm going to get out of here.
I just wanted to let you know.
Peace and be wild men and hopefully see you soon.
All right.
So you see.
You're a folder or scruncher.
I don't think I ever ask you that.
I folks listening to this on serious satellite radio stars one
to the stars channel.
Go to Podsive.
PodsafeRepease.org.
So you can listen to that fantastic song.
Which, of course, was a collaboration that we put together last year of,
was it 30 different Podsive Music artists?
First winter snow outside my window.
Feels like at that time again to be.
The mistletoe.
A Christmas show.
And the lighting of that famous Christmas tree.
People are shopping for their loved ones.
I'm making plans for a Christmas tree.
But it all goes by.
And the wind goes by.
And then we have to wait another year.
What if every day?
Christmas?
What are one and the more?
This one tree.
It will never feel blue.
We make all our dreams come true.
If Christmas were every day.
It was time to bring out the good people.
I just look around now and you will see it.
Everybody's nice and full of light.
And they get to those who are in need.
What if every day?
Christmas?
What are one and the more?
This would be.
It will never feel blue.
We make all our dreams come true.
If Christmas were every day.
It was time to bring out the good people.
We make all our dreams come true.
It will never feel blue.
What if every day?
We make all our dreams come true.
If Christmas was every day.
What if every day?
Christmas?
What are one and the more?
This would be.
It will never feel blue.
We make all our dreams come true.
If Christmas was every day.
It was time to bring out the good people.
We make all our dreams come true.
It will never feel blue.
We're in the sky, every day
We fly, every day
We fly, every year
Chris Morillips
Googling his Star
Chris
Chris Morillips
So chants
Oh man, we're gonna be cool if in like, you know, I don't know, 50 years, we're all dead and
people still play that song. Wouldn't that be fucking cool? They could certainly happen.
Pods say for peace, what if every day we're Christmas, uh, put together by, well, masterminded
by by slow. Uh, we had the 30 or 40 different Pods say music artists across the globe all sending
in their individual pieces, all put together like a big huge jigsaw puzzle, and that's the
result, which of course you can find on the Podsave Music Network and all the songs that we play
on the daily source code available in the show notes, a daily source code.com. Okay, uh, so the first holiday
party tonight, uh, this is the Cliner Perkins holiday party, uh, Cliner Perkins, uh, one of the
investors in Pods show, uh, they have a lot of investments in very interesting companies, uh, so who knows
who will bump? They got a lot of people that hang around and, uh, like Robin Williams, Oprah,
Bono, uh, I hope some of these people are there. Don't tell me it's all going to be
guys and dockers. That one would suck. I will report tomorrow, my friends. Take everybody,
have yourself a great day. Bye-bye.
I'll love it.