This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy.
Delta Sierra Charlie.
Four, two, eight.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this show.
Fantastic. It's Adam Curry.
Heavenly Liberty Jones.
Works in the shop that she owns.
Lessons to music like swing.
When there's no customer's in.
Just because she don't like to drive.
Takes the sea I stood fine.
And these are thoughts outside.
To the river at night.
This is the awesome thing.
Why don't you come for me and take me your way.
If you like this.
This is the awesome thing.
I wish you would buy.
We keep the money back to my place.
This is the awesome thing.
Why don't you come for me and take me your way.
If you like this.
She's gotta clean the ride.
And there's a name word in play.
If you lose a lonely desire.
Give it to yourself.
Why don't you come for me and take me your way.
If you like this.
Give it to yourself.
Why don't you come for me and take me your way.
If you like this.
This is the awesome thing.
Why don't you come for me and take me your way.
If you like this.
I wish you would buy.
Or give some joy.
And you come for me and take me your way.
If you like this.
How do I know?
We keep the money back to my place.
I love this song. I know I played earlier in the week, but I heard it again yesterday on the U.C. radio show.
Damn! The shakes, Liberty Jones from the Podsake Museum that we're kicking off the Wednesday, Charlie, coming to you from a overcast, cloudy and foggy northern California right by the Bay San Francisco, from the Curry condo, good morning everybody, how you doing?
Or good afternoon, or good evening, or if you know Australia, how's tomorrow doing? Let me know, hey everybody, it is humday, hold on a second.
As I said that, we just got a little bit of sun shining through, so I have to put down the shade here. As you know, this is the Baker's Rack Studio.
And it's right next to the window, so when there's a little bit of sun shine, then it just reflects right on the screen and I can't see my show notes.
Hey, lots of stuff going on. Lots of stuff to talk about. First thing is an update on the Curry Cottage Quest, which the Lady Patricia has been on.
You know, it's interesting. I leave and all of a sudden, she's found the house that we need to buy.
Or I should say Cottage. It would be the official Cottage since we've only been renting the Cottage that we're in now for the past year and three quarter years, almost two years now.
And so we'd identified the place, absolutely phenomenally beautiful. Of course, I've only seen pictures, but even Christina liked it.
The price was definitely what we were willing to pay for what we were going to get. And this could be a place for us to settle down for quite a while, I think.
And so Patricia, you know, she called me up. We've been going back and forth over the past couple days.
And I said, hey, baby, no problem. Go ahead. I'll make sure that you can use the checkbook and go buy it. That's kind of what it was.
And what happened is really something for a little segment we call Yanks versus the British.
Now we're from our sponsor. It's the Yanks versus the British.
We'll drive each other crazy, but everybody knows that it's apparent to see.
Let's just like you and me, it's the Yanks and the British.
The Yanks versus the British.
Mind the gap. So when you go to buy, we've bought many houses in our lifetime together, bought and sold some houses.
Some very successfully, one not so successfully, but I think we're pretty good at it.
In primarily in the states and in the Netherlands and in Belgium.
And so now we're ready to do it in the UK. And so as I just said, you know, I said, hey, baby, take the checkbook and go buy it.
Let's, let's get a house when I come back. I'll see what you've purchased. Well, little did we know this is not how it works in the United Kingdom. Oh, no.
So they have a price listed and Patricia went back for the second viewing.
I talked with my husband. I love it. Who do I make the check out to? Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, this is not how it works.
We're going to have it on view for two weeks, at least.
And then, and we, of course, we already have some offers in Patricia said, well, you know, just tell me what will it take to take it off the market.
I don't know. We want to give everybody a fair chance.
Bullshit. What's up with that? Here's how it works.
Apparently, they take these so-called offers and then whoever's closest to what they want, I guess the, you know, we just said, hey, you're asking that much.
Okay, we'll pay for that. That's fine. We'll take it off the market for that or tell me what it'll cost.
No, apparently, we go into this sealed envelope bidding process.
And to make matters even worse, even if you're in the middle of negotiations, the vendor, as it's not the guy who's still in the house,
but the vendor can then decide to sell it to someone else. It's very, very confusing.
So now Tuesday, I guess the close bids are going to be solicited.
And then I, I guess we have to write down a new number and then hand it in.
It's just really a very weird situation.
I've never witnessed this before in any country at all. It's like, you know, you want to buy the house?
Yeah, I'll buy the house for this price. Okay, you know, usually try to knock it down a little bit, right?
Or you say, well, you know, I'll take your gardening equipment and I'll take, you know, some of this stuff, whatever is not included in the sale and so I'll put that in the separate agreement.
And then you're good to go. This is confusing. I'm not sure what to do. If anyone has any recommendations on how to continue and, you know, how much more should we bid than the asking price?
This is so weird. So weird. And who knows?
Maybe all these so-called offers are bullshit.
Anyway, yanks versus the brids. We're learning as we go along.
Yes, that I talked about interviewing a comic strip blogger and he sent me an email and he said, absolutely, I'm not shy.
You can ask me anything I want. Anything that I would want, I can ask him.
But no online interviews. Only in person.
And I have to give him at least one month's advance notice.
And it has to be on a Saturday, but he did say that he would then come to England. So he doesn't live in the UK. I thought he might be living in the UK. I wasn't too sure.
But he's not apparently because he has to fly over.
Maybe I'll just fly to wherever he is.
But I think I should do this.
You know, some folks have even emailed me saying, hey, man, you know, I kind of like the mistake of comic strip blogger. We keep learning more about him every single day.
For instance, yesterday, who knew he spoke Italian and it sounded pretty good to me.
So clearly a character on the Charlie we need to learn more about. So once I figured out my calendar, I guess I'll just do it.
I'll just set it up and we'll interview comic strip blogger and find out what this guy is all about.
SQPN presents the secrets of the Caribbean.
How much do you know about TV channels?
Who is Davey Jones and where does he come from?
Who is Davey Jones?
What is the history of a mysterious flying Dutchman?
Simon, rock, rock, rock, rock.
Well, looks the evil and terrifying track.
You don't come to men, yikes.
Why does the black spot mean eternal damnation?
Oh, David Jones is your soul.
When do imprisoned souls recover their freedom?
We are cursed men.
Join me on my quest for answers
as I explore the depths of the Caribbean waters in search of the hidden treasure of tales and myths behind the adventures of the pirates of the Caribbean.
So to www.sqpn.com and subscribe.
Oh yeah.
It's the good father, Roderick.
Hi. What's up you?
Hi.
I say pirate's my game.
Excellent.
How long we know father Roderick now?
Well over a year, I think.
Man, the his production has just improved by leaps and bounds as fantastic.
And this sounds like a great show.
So I'm going to definitely get that and put it into one of my channels on Pod Show Plus.
Hey, great news.
You know, this year will be the second annual podcast Expo, which is held up in Ontario, California.
And a number of Pod Show podcasts have been nominated for awards this year.
And I just wanted to give you the list.
Actually, I'm not just a podcast.
In fact, best podcast directory podcast alley has been nominated.
Best comedy podcast, the rumor girls.
Best cultural slash arts podcast that goes to most people are DJs.
Best mature podcast, soccer girl.
Also nominated in the same category, Dawn and Drew.
And best pod save music podcast, accident hash.
CC Chapman up in the Metro West studios and Boston congratulations.
That makes me feel really good.
I'm not on any nominations this year.
Which I'm okay with.
I don't know.
I don't fit into any category.
What did I get last year?
I get the best.
I got best produced, which is so funny because first of all,
I figured I would have gotten the lifetime achievement award.
But best produced, I really don't produce much.
You know, I just grab all this shit in the morning while I'm actually taking a shit.
Folder as you know.
And then I line it all up and I just go.
You know, it's it's all live to cast blaster.
Nothing done in post editing.
Or I certainly don't do much leg work on the production.
But it was very nice anyway.
If funny thing about the podcast expo actually it's the portable media expo.
Not quite sure if I'm going to go this year.
When is it September and September and August?
I'm not hearing as much buzz as I did the first time around.
But I got an email.
I'm not going to say from who.
But there was apparently a relatively large swell.
A request for a panel of erotic podcasters.
And they were denied such a panel.
And that's okay because whoever runs the conference and decide whatever they want to do.
But what came back was, you know, erotic has no place at our conference.
Dude, this is there's so much erotic going on in podcasting.
We're finally free.
We can finally talk about all the things we want to talk about.
And now we can't have a panel.
So still not sure if I'm, I don't need an erotic a panel personally.
Not at the expo, but I think I might drop in.
I just want to say hi to some people because it's been a year.
And there's been a lot of stuff going on.
So we're still working on the calendar.
And I don't know.
I still got to see if I can buy this house or not.
Hey Adam, it's Scott Parent from American cliche.
Just wanted to send you a quick message to say thank you to you in the gang over at podshow.
I signed up with with you guys about, I don't know, a couple of months ago mid-May.
And since then since I joined the podshow family, had a couple of great advertising deals.
Now this, the new opportunity, I'll be on serious and a serious rotation starting early August.
And it's been amazing.
The podshow delivery network has been awesome, you know, the speed and the reliability is just, it's there.
And now with the release of podshow plus I think you guys are just really onto something and tapping into something
that that's really needed out there in the community.
So you put together great staff, Richard, Matt, Joe.
Those are the people I deal with on a regular basis, but you've got a great team over there.
And I just want to say again, thanks.
It's really worked out well for my show.
For anyone out there that's thinking about taking the leap and joining podshow plus.
And, you know, putting their show up there and creating a page and, you know, just do it.
It's worked out really well for me.
And I just wanted to acknowledge that and say thanks.
So thanks again, Adam, and I'll talk to you soon.
Take care, man.
All right, buddy.
And you ain't seen nothing yet because, man, now we're finally we're whipping into into medium mode now.
Now that at least we've gotten architecture launched and we've got stuff kind of stabilized and working.
Oh, we were down yesterday for like a good 45 minutes.
That was interesting.
Some really esoteric thing happened.
But it was great because, you know, back in the day Ron and I would usually just go,
Oh, fuck, would freak out.
We'd be running around trying to figure it out with people.
And yesterday when it happened, we went to launch.
And we came back.
It was, it was a beautiful, beautiful experience.
But now we're in, really, in full-on medium mode, as I said.
And now we're, you know, getting podcasts into different rotations in the spinnets into, you know,
the frequency of changing of the flash on the homepage, you know, what's recommended in new channels.
All this stuff, the program guide, it's exciting.
There is a lot of stuff going on.
And it's just continuing throughout the week until I leave on Saturday.
So as I said, you ain't seen nothing yet.
We're just getting started because even though we're hearing a lot of podcasts are saying that
very happy with what they're seeing, this was built for audience.
This is built for listeners and for viewers.
And wait until you see the dashboard.
I mean, yeah, we've got the bubble, bubble players.
What, which is ugly.
And it shows what we're thinking about.
It doesn't quite do everything we, we wanted for our unleashed, but it's rolling, you know.
So also the positive music network integration.
That's just so much to this comment.
I'd love to hear from you, voice mail numbers, plus 201, 625, 6357.
That's the number you want to use for Skype or alternatively.
We have a number in England in London.
And that would be plus four four two zero seven six eight one three seven five three.
If you're dialing from the states and you're not on a on a cell phone.
Say the cell phone, you do the plus and then the one for the country code.
Otherwise it would be O one one four four two zero seven six eight one three seven five three.
And people are calling in responding to yesterday show.
Hey Adam, it's Brian from Chicago.
And we're going to win away in the states.
I'd like to tell you about a spam blocking system.
I would send you the link.
But obviously your email is an organ.
Go to devoracv-o-r-a-t.com slash blog.
And on the left hand side there is a link that says I get no spam.
Click that.
Use it service.
You will get no spam.
It's great.
And they'll be able to do everything that you're doing.
If you have their run box crap that you just doesn't seem to be working.
I don't know.
The folder.
See you later.
Okay.
Thank you, folder.
Good to know.
Oops.
Sorry about that.
Whoa.
One two check two.
Whatever.
Yeah.
And I think I figured it out.
I think I figured the run box stuff out.
And I think I've got it working now.
But it is true.
John Devorac says that he does not get any spam.
And I was just looking at the stuff coming into run box.
It's unbelievable.
And a part of the, I figured out a big part of the problem.
Since I'm also the postmaster at curie.com, everything that's sent to anything at curie.com
was also coming to me and was being forwarded through the system.
So it's just going through all these loops.
And literally, if you so, you know, forget about what spam comes to Adam at curie.com
Just the stuff that, that these spammers will, it's a very educational.
They will just spew at a domain name.
And they try every combination of name.
And, and of course, that was coming through to me.
But then you look at it.
It's five spans per second.
And each of them is at least like, you know, six K in size.
But you know, have you seen that other spam where you get like 10 images
of about 25 K and it looks like a scanned piece of paper or something
or like a scanned shopping list.
You know, these things are, oh, that's about 150 K.
So that's why stuff starts to fill up and, and gets just stupid.
But I will take a look at what John C. Dvorak is talking about with his,
I get no spam because it's so, I think it's almost impossible to spoof everything.
The crap is broken. Email is broken.
And this is something we're going to do with, with our dashboard and in podshow
plus imagine imagine if you could create just a special place where you could feed
your friends with cool media.
So I'm not talking about, you know, jotting off a message.
Use instant message for that.
Now, this is instant mashing where you'll open up the dashboard or somewhere
in podshow plus if you, if we're in each other's entourage, you know,
if you dig me and I dig you then I can feed you and you'll see a picture of me
and if I've dropped a movie or an episode or an entire show onto that,
it's going to be there for you.
Hold on.
I got the phone ringing. Can't deal with that right now.
So, you know, that's the whole idea there is that if you don't want to receive
stuff from me anymore, then you can just say go away.
You know, that's what we don't have with you.
We don't have a way to authenticate.
So say, yeah, you can send me stuff and it's cool.
I want to receive, we can send it back and forth.
And an easy way to break it off.
And when it comes to sharing media, I think we've got that problem linked.
Hey, Adam. This is Doug and Kathleen from Art of Go Go.
I was listening to DSC 424 and was blown away to hear that.
So, brother number one, the hardest working man in show business,
the godfather of soul, Mr. James Brown,
enjoying the pod safe music network.
You can't miss when James Brown arrives to funk up the party.
Hi, Adam. Congratulations to you and the pod show team
on your one-year anniversary of the pod safe music network.
It's also Art of Go Go's, one-year anniversary.
And to celebrate, we asked podcasting brother number one,
Jeff Smith, the right to new song for Art of Go Go.
For the latest art news, reviews and interviews,
listen to the Art of Go Go podcast.
You can find us at article.com slash blog
or visit iTunes and search for Art of Go Go.
So here it is, the premier of the new Art of Go Go theme song by Jeff Smith.
Thanks, Jeff. Here it is.
Don't know much about heart, but I know what I like.
It's more than pretty pictures.
Yeah, that's right.
It can be fine. Art of four men's too.
But where can I turn it?
If I don't know what to do.
You don't have this podcast to think.
But I'm not this one, but go go go.
Go go go go go.
Oh man.
Jeff Smith's got a whole cottage industry run and doesn't it?
Go, love it.
Go, go.
I just ordered five more things from Jeff.
Check them out at JeffSmith.com, Jeff's spelled G-E-O-F-F.
And you guys are so right.
When the Godfather of Soul, when James Brown shows up
on the pod save music network, you know something right
is happening.
And James Brown was nice enough to make a special little thing
for me to share with you Charlie listeners.
I'm so proud of this.
Hot save music and music then and you can play on your podcast.
Hot save music is kind of music.
You can play on your podcast.
Let a legal momma jump out there.
But it means it's the right to there for you to play it on a podcast.
Deep round on a hot save music,
out, never, out, get round.
Hot save music, out, never, out.
Deep round on a hot save.
You didn't, never, out, out.
Deep round, out, once they music, out.
Deep round, lay on the hot save music, out.
Yeah.
I should play the first 10 seconds for a couple people in the office yesterday and I said,
Wow, man.
That's all cool.
James Brown did that.
Yeah.
I love it.
I must say though.
I had dinner last night with a good friend of mine Greg Lollie who's an independent record promoter here in San Francisco.
He does a lot of hip hop R&B stations here on the West Coast and literally will promote records on behalf of the record company.
He lives kind of at the asshole of the industry if you will.
And we came up with a plan that is so cool and involves, uh, was it about nine or ten top artists and podcasts,
podcasters using podsaic music and the podsaic music network and I just can't tell you about everything right now,
but I think we're going to see more big name artists seeing the value of working with podcasters to promote their stuff.
And I think we're going to see that pretty soon.
Hey, um, if you listen to us on serious stars one or two PCHs next, we'll be back tomorrow with Thursday's addition from the condo.
And for those of you still here.
Well, of course.
I mean, I can't just to make you feel good about thinking you're going to hear some James Brown without bringing up the godfather of a soul.
Yeah.
I can't walk on over to the podsaic music network.
Good bucket.
James Brown.
Yeah.
Good bucket.
Fuck.
Yeah.
All right.
I can go now.
Yeah.
Music!
There's an all the way!
Step on!
Up!
You're down!
That's the same again!
Hey hey hey hey!
Up!
Good time!
Good to be!
Hey y'all!
Got a brand new thing!
It's the same again!
But it's the bathroom!
You can't hold it!
But the body can move it!
Come on!
Hey hey!
Up!
In London!
In Berlin!
You got no bullets too!
And Paris!
Look!
Hey Paris!
Go!
And then Paris!
Come on!
It's the same again!
Hey y'all!
Got my guns!
Bunk!
Huh!
Oh yeah!
Look at me!
You got me!
Somebody!
Breathe!
Take that!
Good to be you!
Buh!
Oh man!
It's a good song too!
It's not like you put some crap up on the network!
Put a real James Brown original up there!
I love it!
Got bucket!
James Brown!
You'll find a link to...
This pot set music network page in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
By the way, I guess Adam and Curry dot com works again, but I would suggest to keep using
Adamette podshow.com.
And of course I was talking about going visiting my friend last night Greg Lawley.
Which means I took Trinity out and I hadn't actually seen Trinity since the last
time it's here when the transmission dropped.
Wow!
First of all, they had parked it back in the garage underneath the condo.
I'm like a P4, you know, away at the bottom.
And I couldn't believe it.
They had washed it.
And I have chrome rims.
I didn't even know I had chrome rims.
And it shifts.
Oh man, you can barely feel the shifting.
It really has Bentley Rolls Royce like floating quality now the car.
And they fixed some exhaust thing was busted.
So it doesn't sound as noise as it did.
Actually, it's like a luxurious car again.
It still has the nice loft of McDonald's floating around you.
But hey, it's good for the environment.
Yes, it is.
Hey, Adam Steve Web here with a life spring family podcast.
Man, this war sucks.
And it is a matter of fact, it sucks so bad that I decided that I was going to break
format with a life spring show and talk about it.
I don't normally talk about politics as you probably know.
But with some things that I've heard set on some podcasts recently and with the news coverage
I'm seeing.
And then the final factor that made me decide to do this show on the the war was an email
that I got from a listener of mine.
Well, listen to the show and you'll hear the email that he sent me.
And you'll hear my response to it.
You'll hear my response to the war, the situation there.
And of course, I take it from a biblical perspective and also the human perspective.
I sat down with my brother-in-law, Steve O'Brien, who is the associate pastor at the church
I attend.
He's also a chaplain with the United States Air Force reserves.
And so he has that perspective as well.
And we spent about a half an hour talking about the war.
And I'd really encourage you to take a listen to life spring number 98 and see how it fits in
on your perspective of the war.
Yeah, war sucks.
No doubt about it.
And now on a happier note, I really want to say how much I'm enjoying pod show plus.
When I first started, I had one show, life spring podcast.
But now there's a family of podcasts.
And so you can check it out at podshow.
Go to lifespring.podshow.com.
From there, you can get links to all the other life spring shows.
Oh, and by the way, I'm a scruncher and I stand while I record.
I stand to my friend, but scrunch and sorry, you can't take me down that road.
Yeah, it's funny. I got an email yesterday.
I've been talking about when I went to Iraq in 2004 and did a live radio broadcast.
I've actually received some interest.
I'm not going to say from where, which aren't forces, but I have received some interest
about possibly going over and doing something similar.
Well, let's see, about three war zones, the United States can choose from these days.
But I think that would be quite interesting.
Because besides the human aspect of this show that we did from Iraq,
and actually broadcasting live and really connecting troops with their families back home,
I learned a tremendous amount about the country about what was going on.
And so it would be fantastic opportunity.
And I mentioned this to Ron yesterday, and he gave me one of those looks like,
the kind of look he gives me when I tell him that I'm doing something new with flying.
And he said, dude, if you go, I'm going.
So, keep you up to speed on that.
And thank you very much, Steve, for all the nice words you had about Pod Show Plus.
Although, it's not without problems, it is not.
Hi, Adam, just been listening to one of the shows,
and I thought it would give you a quick piece of feedback on signing up for Pod Show.
The one minor annoyance I found was that when I was putting it on my details,
and it said, I agreed to the terms and conditions.
I kept on the terms and conditions,
thinking it would open in another window.
It opens in the same window.
And then when you go back, it's white based all the details you've put in.
It's not a big problem, but sort of you give a feedback.
So, it's made.
No, it's stupid.
Yeah, it's a totally dumb thing.
That makes sense.
Of course, it should pop up in a separate window, so you can read it.
Dude, so sorry.
Well, the whole crew listens to the daily source code.
It really is a great way to feed back stuff
that we want changed.
When you hear someone saying that,
oh man, it's going to fix it right away.
It doesn't sound like it's a huge problem to fix,
so thank you very much, appreciate it.
But we totally need to fix that.
If it's still not fixed.
And now, we have the Troy Needs and iPod contest running.
And I thought I was pretty clear,
but people still don't quite seem to have it down.
I'm going to give away a video iPod to the best domain name.
And this all started with Troy Needs and iPod,
and then we had a dot com.
And then we had the next domain name, which was,
by the way, Troy Needs and iPod dot com,
I still find extremely original.
And of course, is a contender and in the running.
Then what do we get?
I need an iPod more than Troy dot com.
And I said, please put it into one place.
I want you to put it into a comment at daily source code dot com.
And it was like, yeah, I got one at daily source code dot com
and five at curry dot com and still lots of them coming
in through email.
I realized that part of that is because people are behind a few episodes behind
and they're just now catching up.
So, resubmit it, please go to daily source code dot com
and put it into a comment there.
So, I can really track it and have it all in one place.
Hi, Adam.
This is Tom from the Fox View podcast.
And just leaving you a message here about a new domain name
that I got for your Troy Needs and iPod contest.
So, I had three criteria for picking the name.
One was it had to be something related to the Charlie.
Two, it had to be a name that suits the outcome of the contest.
And three, it had to be a name that is easy to remember
and rolls off at the top of your tongue.
Now, the name I came up with, and you can insert a catbuster
gum roll here, is www dot.
I want an iPod by listening to the Charlie dot com.
Now, if I am outside chance, I don't win the contest.
I figure I can often do the buzz of aim to the winner.
Next change for maybe an iPod.
I don't have any film in it last year, so I can't still offer the main name.
But I can't refer you to my podcast at www dot.com.
Thanks for that, Adam, and talk to you later.
There's always room.
Always room to promote your own podcast, isn't there?
Call me off guard there, dude.
Of course, castblaster does have the drum roll.
I was just late.
So two things happened this morning as I was going through my email.
CC Chapman sent me a screenshot of, I guess it's at the Rockstar Supernova.
You know, that's the Tommy Lee reality show.
I think it was actually on last night, I caught the tail end of it before I went to bed.
And it was a screenshot of the website, and it shows what Tommy's favorite songs are.
And you guys, I don't know if it's a direct sale or what the store was.
But on the list, he had, I think two or three black lab songs.
I'm like, yeah, I know those guys, you know, I'm known them for quite a while.
They're on the Podsive Music Network.
So that was the first thing that happened.
Then as I'm going through the voicemails, again, the number is 20165-6357.
This is what shows up.
Hey, Adam, it's Paul Durham from Black Lab.
I'm trying to get a bit of a west coast touring thing going playing some acoustic shows.
I'm in San Francisco, July 28th at the cafe.
I do Nord, and an honor of Fuba Friday, and National Sisters Admin Day.
I will be playing live at Podsio headquarters.
Just to get you warmed up for that night's acoustic set.
I hope you're on the rest of your pod people can make it.
Meanwhile, it's something like rockin' the daily source code.
We hear a black lab.
I've got this single call without you, and I need a bit of the curry cowbell.
Here's hoping you could help me out with that.
All right, man.
How are you?
Thank you so much.
This is great.
Fuba Friday is for the 700 people who used to work at Think New Ideas, the company that
Ron and I built in the 90s.
I know some of them still listen to the show.
We had something called a Think Drink, which is on Friday at 5 o'clock.
That was it.
We shot everything down.
We hung up on clients, and we got together.
We had some food and drink, and just chatted, and played some music, and hung out.
We had people within the company present things, or it's just a cultural thing.
We've done, in fact, I've done it in other companies, and Ron did it in other companies
that I wasn't involved in.
Now we have the Fuba Friday.
Of course, Fuba are stands for fucked up beyond all recognition.
We have a very large engineering staff.
The rest of everyone who works at HQ loves what they do.
We have to unwind on Fridays.
We have the Fuba Friday.
We get some drinks, and we get some food, and see last Friday, Ron and I presented all the stuff
that we've been showing to distribution partners, and also advertising agencies in the US,
as well as in the UK.
It involves all aspects of the company.
Everyone gets a shot at presenting what they do to the rest of the company.
It's always done with humor and fun, and it's always alcohol-induced.
I have to admit.
So now it appears, and we've had some bands play before.
Black Lab is going to play on Friday, and I hear an invitation there to play calm down.
Unfortunately, I didn't bring the curry cowbell.
And Friday, as we rock it out for the weekend, I'll play the new Black Lab.
This is without you, on the Charlie.
Keep up.
It's just we took.
Keep the record down the books, but tell me what it was that I'm wrong.
I think about California.
I think about getting out of here.
I think I'll change my name.
I know I'll never be the same.
I know you're sick of me now.
I know you're sick of my eyes.
I never learn to keep it to myself.
I think about California.
I think about burning down this town.
I think I'll change my name.
Maybe you should do the same.
If I were you, if I were you
No matter where I go
What I do I always feel with you
If I were you, if I were you
Tell me what I do
What I say, I'll cut out
And I'm this way without you
Is that you?
I'm just this one's
Tell me forget that I was drunk
That night when I said
Said that I would jump
I'm out to my death
You should ever be
You promised that you'd always be with me
Are you black eyes to live
Cause I just can't live without you
Without you
No matter where I go
What I do I always feel
But I'm with you without you
Without you
I'm with you
I'm just this one's
Tell me what I do
What I do
I'm just this one's
Tell me what I do
What I do
I'm with you
I said Friday we'll bring you the new black lab that was without you winding up the Wednesday
edition of the Daily Source Code, DailySourceCode.com is where you can find the latest
show, the archives, and a place for you to put comments. And of course, Adam at podshow.com
if you want to send something through email.
Alright everybody, thank you very much for listening. Thanks for getting the show. Thanks for
subscribing. Whatever you do have yourselves a great day and I'll be back tomorrow.
Once podcast a livery network from podshow and line-white networks, I love it.