This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
The show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy.
K2.
To see our Charlie.
Delta Sierra Charlie.
462.
Sometimes an atoms on a loan.
He needs his love right there on the microphone.
So here she is, yes, the Lady Patricia.
The say to have some better than one.
And with his angel from above.
There's nothing that they both can't do.
A make you wild as dreams come true.
So grab your ear buds and jam them up.
And let the fabulous show begin.
It's Adam and Patricia.
Yes, Adam and Patricia.
Adam and Lady Patricia.
There's one pet.
I love to pet.
And every evening we get set eyes broken.
Every chance I get is my ghost pussy.
Never scampers, never hurts.
But I love the true sisters.
And it's so cheap because it's hers.
It's my girl's pussy.
Sometimes it goes out at night to return.
The break of dawn.
No matter what the weather's like.
It's always nice and warm.
Always neat and always clean.
Never bossing, never mean.
Works just like a clean machine.
That's my girl's pussy.
All right.
Let's see.
Come to daddy now.
Yeah.
That's it.
What do you say to me?
Me?
What I like to hear.
Listen.
I got something to say to you too.
Me?
It goes like this.
You like it?
Yeah.
I thought you would.
Listen.
One more thing to tell you.
No.
Sometimes it goes out at night to return.
The break of dawn.
No matter what the weather's like.
It's always nice and warm.
Never skimpers, never puzzled.
But I like the thrills it's does.
And it's so cheap because it's hers.
It's my girl's pussy.
Mm-hmm.
What is it with your guys?
No.
This was.
Hi, everybody.
That was Ian Whitcom.
Of story.
Hey.
In UK.
This is a classic bit.
This is my girl's pussy.
Yeah.
Sent to me by Marcus County of the Seenzine.
It is a wonderful song.
Yeah.
It's a nice warm wonderful song.
Yes, it is.
Let me see.
I'm looking at it.
This is at his website.
What is it?
It says America's, huh?
America's foremost teen pan alley man.
You could layly virtue also.
Grammy award winning recording artists.
I'm sorry.
Ian Whitcom.
I'm American from Surrey.
I was probably an American record company.
I'm American record company.
I mean, he's American, right?
Oh, I want, oh, okay.
Okay.
You got it?
Yeah.
He's been making songs for a long time.
I think I guess they re releasing this re releasing his songs.
Okay.
What is a very funny song?
Yeah, it's cool.
Hey, everybody.
It's.
Friday.
You know, football Friday, right?
Maybe.
No.
I want you to just.
Why?
I want you to talk more.
It's taking my mouth right now.
Very good.
No, what you did.
Yeah.
Well, that's how people at home can hear you.
Okay.
I was going to say it's a 462 is the episode.
We're at the Curry Cottage.
Football F U B A R.
Football Boy.
No, that's F O O B R.
F U B A R.
Yeah.
Is an engineering term.
Okay.
Fucked up beyond all recognition.
Oh, that's sort of a Friday.
And that's kind of what this Friday is from the Friday.
All right.
So tired.
But you are tired.
Yeah.
I can see that.
I know.
How can Bloom still be walking around?
I don't know.
How can he actually, I mean, he's 50.
He's a bit younger than I am.
4?
Not 5.
How does he do it?
How does he do it, man?
I don't know.
Although they told me last night we had.
So we've been in London almost all of this week.
Of course.
We announced our partnership with the BTBTpot Show.com.
And so that was what was that Wednesday?
Yeah.
No.
Tuesday.
No Wednesday.
It was Wednesday.
Okay.
Remember.
And so I came home because I had to record stuff and do all that.
And everyone went out to dinner.
I told me that Ron looks pretty wrecked.
I told him he could be good there.
He is also young in life.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
I'm glad I know.
I'm glad I don't have that problem.
That situation is better to have an older woman.
You're now.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
He seems to be doing fine.
I don't know about that.
Yeah.
But underneath you don't know that.
He must be very tired.
Oh, yeah.
Of course he's tired.
But in good spirit.
Of course.
This has been the fantastic week.
We've had a great.
You know, we saw we opened up BTpodshow.com and people can submit their songs or or pictures or whatever they have.
Video audio podcast doesn't matter.
There's like.
There was 500.
Exciting.
The first day.
And it's something some really amazing shit.
I think you'll really, really like it when I show it to you.
Adam, it's a little strategy in Cleveland.com.
Listening to daily source code number 447 and hearing poor pictures.
Nothing with your ear buds.
And I challenge you.
Today's September 12th 2006 to go online and replace.
Patricia's headphones that you snagged from her.
Yeah.
Thank you.
It's not even.
Absolutely right.
Because they're one size.
Can I just ask you something?
One size fits old.
Not me.
What the ear buds?
Yeah.
The official iPod ear buds.
I know.
It doesn't fit my ear.
No.
Your hole is too small.
Your holes are too small.
Uh-huh.
Had to get you back for the mouth.
Yeah.
But if I give you a pair of headphones like this.
If I go back and give you yours back.
We actually wear them with your hair.
Are you going to do like an abyss?
I care.
I don't know.
And the hair wasn't that good.
That was the the wrongest thing in recording history and music video history.
And it looks very insecure.
I think.
You know what I think?
What should we do?
Do you want to give anything you want to talk about?
I have my got all kinds of stuff.
Well, no.
I was just reading the papers.
Yeah.
One more thing to worry about.
Well, we're messing away.
Like, oh, you're just figuring this one out.
This is Al Gore's movie.
Of course.
We know that with the global warming and Al Gore is doing great job.
The great job.
Reminding us.
Somebody has to do it.
But um, and if you read it, you think it's scary, actually.
You know.
So what have you done to protect our planet?
What do you want me to do?
Well, what does Al want you to do?
Did you read his book?
No.
Did you see his movie?
His movie opens today in the UK.
But I'm a good girl.
I always do everything right.
You said.
You said one more thing to worry about.
I didn't spray that hair spray anymore.
No.
No, they fixed that a long time ago.
Yeah.
So that's that's done.
I heard that that's okay.
And what else can I do?
Tell me.
I think since the reason you're seeing Al Gore and all the papers today is because
the movie opens is an inconvenient truth.
Do you want to go see it?
Yeah.
That would help.
Didn't you see it in?
Remember it was at 7 a.m.
Yeah.
Oh, you had your eyes closed.
It was 7 a.m. in Monterey, California.
Yeah.
But I heard it was actually very interesting.
Well, it's a big hit.
The movie.
Lots of people are going to see it.
Yeah.
I also have the book.
Did you read the book that we brought back with?
No.
Did you see me reading the book?
Just wanted to put you on.
I was making your shakes.
Yeah.
You're here to get you in shakes.
Excuse me.
We had this conversation last night.
Yeah.
I'm taking care of you.
You know?
Excuse.
Oh, man.
Like you said, that's the only thing you do.
Well, there's no more time in the day to read a book.
You're never on the computer.
You're never surfing around.
Yeah.
And it's a bit a little bit.
It's quite a job to keep you in upright position.
You know, in upright.
And what is that?
Please fold you.
Put your trade to tell you tables in the upright and stored position.
That's what it is.
Please put your husband in the upright and stored position.
Yeah.
Good morning.
Time to do it.
Make more doughnuts.
Exactly.
Yeah.
It's fun.
We have a good team here in the UK.
Yeah.
You haven't met any of this.
Anybody.
Wednesday.
I'm going into town.
I met the podcastings.
You didn't eat some of those.
You didn't eat some of them.
No, you didn't eat some of them.
Some of them.
You're using.
So you didn't eat.
But using.
What the.
I mean.
Some of them.
We're working with us.
Yes.
Right.
God.
And be careful.
They people already think I'm an evil ass.
That sounds a bit rock and roll, probably.
Yeah.
So I think you met Neil.
I think pretty sure you met Neil Dixon.
You probably don't remember.
But if you saw him, you would remember.
Yeah.
And so I'm meeting with Neil.
Wednesday for lunch.
You want to come?
Yeah.
Neil.
Waterloo.
Wednesday.
Yeah.
I have a meeting with some people.
Wonderful.
You want to come in?
Yeah.
You can you can have lunch with us or you can.
I'm a famous podcast.
Yes.
How many times do I have to be here?
You are.
So famous and so well paid.
Well paid.
You're so.
I haven't seen anything.
You can see that big name.
I've got the best.
I've got you.
I've got you, babe.
Okay.
Maybe this will help.
Maybe this will help me get going.
Yeah.
I told you about Amy Max's answer size.
Okay.
So I kind of missed a show this week because of everything that was going on.
So normally I do answer size on day that you're not here.
Yeah.
Because you want your ass.
Because you don't listen anyway.
Yeah.
I don't have to embarrass myself.
So why don't I do the exercise with you here today?
Okay.
And you know what this is all about.
This of course is many, many weeks ago I said my ass is disintegrating.
I need help.
My wife is complaining.
Titing up the bomb.
And Amy Mac of the fitness attack podcast, which by the way is like highlighted on iTunes
and gets just an amazing audience.
You should listen to this.
She's really good.
She also trains the whole pod show office.
She does.
Yeah.
Twice a week.
Tuesdays and Thursdays I think.
They have a workout.
All right.
Otherwise we'd have a complete assless opening.
You know, very exact.
Because your guy is sitting and sitting and sitting.
Hi.
And another part of the bar.
We're from Pod Show.
We have no ass.
Yeah.
You may have to help me out of here.
Amy.
I got you.
Hi.
He's ready to save Adam's ass.
Yeah.
I'm Amy Mac.
Thank you.
Adam's ass.
Okay.
Are you feeling good Adam?
No.
I'm tired.
You ready to go?
Yeah.
All right.
Grab the wireless because we're on the photo today.
You'll have to narrate on it.
You're going to go down on all fours and go to the table position.
This is where your hands are under your shoulders and knees are under your hips.
Great.
Knees on your hips.
Your right leg with your knee bent and 90 degrees.
And the soul of your foot toward the ceiling.
Oh yeah.
Now you're going to raise your leg toward the ceiling as far as you can keeping your knee
at 90 degrees and without bending your back.
These are donkey kicks and we're going to do eight and then switch legs.
Ready, go.
Here you go.
And seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
Great.
Bring that leg down and take the other one up.
Eight, seven, six, five.
Four, three.
Yeah, you're doing a great.
Still with me?
Yes.
Good.
Switch back to the right side.
Eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
And now the left, last time.
Ready, go.
Have you eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, and one?
Yes.
Come down.
You're done.
This is in range by lower body exercise.
If you want to get fancy, you can set a dumbbell behind your knee and squeeze your cap.
A dumbbell?
A dumbbell, yeah.
This has a little more resistance and a little more intensity to this exercise.
To find my show, go to fitness.padshow.com.
As always, it's been a pleasure, Adam.
Until next time.
Thank you, Amy.
I enjoyed that.
See you on hands with me.
Well, thanks for not talking during the entire thing.
It's like, you're supposed to be describing what I'm doing.
Okay.
You're seeing it with your mouth open, though.
It's amazing.
I'm like, would you please say something?
I'm checking out your ass.
It's funny.
Every single day.
How was it?
It was good.
It's not that bad, huh?
What?
Your ass is not that bad.
Well, the Hacom yours complaining about.
Yeah.
Well, if you feel it, you know, you squeeze the bun, the bun, the bun.
You can feel that it's a bit empty.
Yes.
The shape is still there.
But it's a bit floppy.
You are so harsh.
Uh-huh.
For some reason, every single time I do one of Amy's exercises, it hurts everywhere
except my actual ass.
I mean, isn't the part that hurts?
That's the part that's going to build up muscle.
Yeah.
How can my ass doesn't hurt then?
Well, how does it work?
I don't understand it.
Because I saw that your knees were not underneath your knees.
What do you mean?
I didn't perfect.
No, no.
No.
Please go back.
Talk.
That's even easier.
Yeah.
I'll know what that's better.
I'll go a little bit more back.
Back with your knees.
That's it.
Now it's good.
Now you have to do it.
I can do that.
Say it one.
To know you can do it faster.
Yeah.
But it's no big deal.
No big deal.
Yeah.
Right?
Come on.
Don't keep kicking away.
Well, I was taking a walk with you on the downs.
And we were going up.
And I was listening at you breathing.
Yeah.
And it's not bad.
It's actually not bad.
Well, no, of course not.
No.
You're.
I'm about to kill over.
I said.
Put a mattress.
It's not bad.
I have to say.
You know.
And I remember when we lived in America, you always did a lot of swimming.
Because you were.
Yeah, we don't know.
Such a sports guy.
I know you can.
And I did not swim a lot.
It's not true.
In the pool.
It wasn't a lot.
Yeah, but you are good.
You're good.
And we did.
And everywhere we went on vacation, we're hanging on things.
And going behind boats.
And you know.
Because you're actually a sport of guy.
Yeah.
But you know, I think a lot of that stopped after the motorcycle accident.
I got like really unsporty for a long long long.
For a year.
It took me a year to get my.
My gosh.
Didn't.
I know.
It did not scare me.
It made me very aware.
Yeah.
But you go on everything.
So if you say, John, we're going to jump.
We're going to hang on.
I'm going to do it.
You do it.
You're right on any.
I used to.
I don't think I do that anymore.
Now you think a little bit.
I just remember it was a pain in the ass to not be able to sleep properly for a year.
Not be able to take a crap pop properly for a year.
Yeah.
Because that's literally.
What's in it horrible?
You're back.
There's something about your back and taking a crap.
That's very real.
Oh.
I'm not going to do it.
They say it's related to it.
Yes.
I'm not going to show how it works.
People with back problems probably have also.
intestines who are not working very well.
Yeah.
I have intestinal issues today too.
Last night we had.
So we're staying at the standards in hotel.
Which is one of these already.
I had a room with an egg in it, huh?
It was a fucking egg.
An egg.
This size.
How was it?
Two feet long.
Two foot long egg.
It's one of those hip.
Ian Schrager hotel.
Did you sit in it?
No.
You could drink.
You could trip over it.
But what did.
What was the function?
Just to look like an egg.
Yeah.
Exactly.
God.
What an investment.
So they had.
Yeah.
Fantastic.
So we had dinner and they had the.
Was it wagyu?
Wagyu beef?
Mm-hmm.
And I said, you know, what's wagyu?
I think it was wagyu.
Does it sound right wagyu?
Let me look it up.
And apparently wagyu is.
The cows get massage.
And good food.
And, you know, people are talking to it.
Oh, here we go.
Wagyu.
Crap.
Oh, do we even have sound of that?
For several Japanese wagyu need also known as Kobe beef.
Kobe style beef.
Yeah.
But the waiter said it was from Australia.
Australia.
From Australia.
But yeah, what do they get?
Well, maybe it's a Japanese idea.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, very typical.
It looks good.
Looks like a nice looking cow there.
Is it a cow?
I really don't know.
That's the question.
Imperial cattle from Japan.
Japanese.
Well, whatever.
What I said.
Yes.
Okay.
But I said this morning.
If your body is tired, then you shouldn't eat things that your body has to work for.
I know.
Because then you can just want it some more.
I know what you mean.
Because that's what my mom used to say.
All you need to take.
Because you have been sick.
Yeah.
It's sick for a long time.
It's my state.
I think your mom's right about that.
Actually, I don't think to liver liver.
I had to.
I have to.
Yeah.
That's not good for your cholesterol.
Isn't that horrible?
That's the way we live these days.
I do.
You know, and I was reading in the paper this morning that they were going to bend.
They're a very skinny skinny, very skinny models.
Thank God for that.
The worst example ever.
Which ones give me which are the which models.
Well, because they don't even have names.
These are the kids that get selected.
And they have no.
Yeah.
Well, that's probably the way they're built.
But it's such a bad example, because I notice Christina talking about her body almost every day.
Yeah.
She thinks she's fat.
You know, not because she loves to eat, but you know, you can hear that it's troubles
her because she sees different pictures in the magazines of very skinny, skinny
models.
I'm most of those.
I think that's the way you should be.
Most of those magazine pictures, of course, are indeed of 13-year-olds and have been
photoshopped.
Well, photoshopped.
Lots of photoshopping.
You know, they select a lot of fun.
So what you're saying is that this really is affecting teenage girls, this story.
Oh, yeah.
Why were they banned from the fashion show?
And who is the authority?
Who is the fashion police?
The magazine, people, they said it's over now, we're not going to do it anymore.
They're not going to put magazines.
They have complaints.
Yeah.
That will be a good start.
That's a good start.
They put fat bitches in there.
Because Christine looks beautiful.
She is gorgeous.
It's nothing wrong with her.
So what are they going to put in there now?
What is a little bit more normal?
For example, Kate Moss looks normal.
That's a normal girl.
She's not too tall.
She's not too skinny.
Yeah, that was right.
She is nice.
She's very normal.
Snort some cocaine with peaked dough.
That's not what I'm saying.
Very normal.
The picture.
A little bit of heroin.
Yeah.
What people do.
I mean, yeah.
Okay.
Well, I'm just telling you, that's another fine role model, which is perfect.
It's not a role model.
I mean, her body is a normal.
I'm just giving an example of somebody that looks a bit normal.
Okay.
So the fashion.
But I'm just going to hold on to this story.
Okay.
So, hold on.
I'm trying to understand because I think I just really want to know who is saying what?
Is it the fashion?
And really, I'd like to know.
Yeah.
The fashion magazines.
So the fashion magazines are saying we're not going to show those pictures anymore.
This is about wrong.
Let me finish.
God, you never let me finish.
I just want to get my fucking question out.
Man, you haven't answered before, have you asked the fucking question?
Yeah.
The question is.
Because right now fashion shows are going on.
And I believe that the fashion either the, um, the kutriese.
Yeah.
So the people who are also.
You don't know.
Just say, I don't know.
Who is they?
Who's they?
Probably.
Where's the newspaper?
downstairs.
Which newspaper was it?
The son.
The independent.
Oh, the independent.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
That picture.
Not only with papers with pictures.
Okay.
Excuse me.
All right.
So let's find out though.
If who exactly who it is.
If it's the fashion.
Fashion.
Yes.
The authority who was calling the shot.
Who used models in the magazines.
Models in the fashion shows.
And if they start banning those very, very, very,
super skinny.
Because that's where it has to start.
Then it's much banning them from the catwalks.
From the catwalks.
Or from the advertisements.
The advertisement.
From from start somewhere.
But do it.
Okay.
Well, then this has to start with the magazines.
So I'll be very happy next week.
When I pick up a Vogue.
Sorry.
Next month when I pick up Vogue, which is the fashion Bible.
Yeah.
Yes.
And I see no more skinny, skinny under nurse children in the magazine.
You're telling me that's going to happen.
Yes.
They're going to try that.
They're going to try to start somewhere.
The fashion.
The fashion authority.
Police.
I will bet you.
I will bet you a million pounds.
It's not going to happen.
They're just, it's just lip service.
It's just not going to happen.
I don't believe that.
The strange thing is that if you look at the the designer stuff.
You know, you think, wow, it looks so cool.
And the jacket and then put something over it.
And you do.
And you put it over jeans.
Now when you try it, it is a normal person.
You look like an idiot.
You know what I mean?
Yes.
You have to wear dress over jeans.
And then maybe put socks over the.
Over the over the jeans.
This is the fashion of the moment.
Yeah.
This is the fashion.
You have to dress up your legs.
Dress up your legs.
No.
What are you talking about?
I saw Victoria Beckin with their legs.
Yeah, that's now because it's beautiful weather.
She has a shorts on now.
But the winter is dress up your legs.
What if you have a big bigger heavier legs?
That's not going to be a nice side.
All right.
I know you folks listening to serious stars 102 are riveted by this advice.
That's a lot more really good stuff coming up today on your Friday at 102.
No, I think going.
You know, so design is just coming up with things.
But they're thinking about very skinny, skinny, unusual looking people.
All right.
Let's talk about something else now.
Okay.
So that's.
I'm happy with that.
It's a mother because I know that all her friends and also Christina.
Isn't my butt big?
I mean, I mean, yes, we don't have a little bit of a tummy.
Yes, you should.
Last night, we talked about death.
Yeah.
That was, that was the, I think really the first time.
You would not tune me.
I feel like shit.
Yeah.
That was maybe the.
Oh, there's the, there's the post guys.
But did you call them?
Or did they bring that guy?
Yeah.
Of course.
Oh, man.
Is he going to interrupt the show?
Well, sure.
I should get it.
And you can just go on.
Well, I don't know.
Let's see if he rings our door.
Sure.
Looks like it.
Just as I was about to talk about death, he shows up on your doorstep.
The business post guy.
Postman rings the post.
Why?
Let me just see.
Is he coming?
Yeah.
Hold on a second.
Let me get a song.
Should we play a song?
And then we can go figure that out.
We talk about death.
I want to talk about death.
I think we should talk about death.
Yeah.
I'll play a really happy death song.
Okay.
Hold on a second.
I played this yesterday.
And I really, really liked it.
Yeah.
I really liked it.
And actually, as I played it yesterday, I thought,
I should play that on Friday for Patricia.
I love you every single day.
I love you from the moment that away.
I love you more than you'll ever know.
I love you wherever you go.
I love you here and you smile.
You're teeth in your eyes.
You're so much more beautiful than me.
We should be together.
We would be so happy.
I picked you up and down the streets.
You are walking next to me.
Hand in hand.
We walk along.
We'll be so happy.
People will say it's wrong.
I love you every single day.
I love you from the moment that away.
I love you more than you'll ever know.
I love you wherever you go.
You took an order against me.
The magistrate said that I was naughty.
Within a thousand feet of you, I cannot go.
I watch you from the edge of the exclusion zone.
Yesterday you were wearing pink.
You went into the park for a drink.
It had scotch and coat with the man named Brett.
Brett is dead.
Brett was a threat to me.
I love you every single day.
I love you from the moment that away.
I love you more than you'll ever know.
I love you wherever you go.
There isn't anything that I would rather do.
Then spend the rest of my life with you.
But they want to send me to jail.
Because I sent you my love in the mail.
I want to keep you in a box of beautiful box with velvet lining and a hole in the lens.
So I can slip your food.
We'll be together.
It will be so good.
I love you every single day.
I love you every single way.
We'll be together just you and me.
And the woods in the cabin in a box for eternity.
I love you every single day.
I love you from the moment that away.
I love you more than you'll ever know.
I love you wherever you go.
I love you every single day.
I love you from the moment that away.
I love you more than you'll ever know.
I love you wherever you go.
There from Australia.
No, what's that?
Told you.
It's a great song.
The Gorses.
A single day.
You know, nice.
They're wacky.
It's kind of like a stalker song.
Yes, it is.
But it's creepy.
But someone could love you like that.
I put you in the basement.
You know, like that.
And we'll never let you out.
In a wooden box with velvet.
Mmm.
So last night Patricia says,
Oh, God.
I'm afraid of dying.
That's pretty much what you said.
Yeah.
And we really hadn't talked about this since my mom died.
No.
And,
Well, we talked for a while.
How do you feel this morning?
Much better.
I didn't have the chance to express my feeling.
Actually, because it was your mom.
Mm-hmm.
And you are not really talking about it.
Although you had, you suffered enough.
All those weeks, of course.
And I thought,
Whew.
Well, it was a progression of two years.
I saw it.
Hale a little bit.
Yeah.
Well, here, I think here's the basic conversation that we had.
So for both of us, this was the first person who close to us who died.
Yeah, that's close.
Yeah, definitely.
And I was there.
You know, that even if you've ever seen someone breathe their last breath.
Yeah.
It's quite an experience.
We didn't have a lot of friends or people close to us dying,
which is wonderful, actually.
Yeah.
A lot of people we know very seriously through show business.
But it's still not quite the same.
No, not quite the same.
Not quite the same.
So a couple of years ago, a friend of ours died.
Which one?
Yeah.
Oh, Baya.
Baya.
Before that, ale.
But ale.
He drank himself.
He drank himself to death.
So, you know, we, and he was a crazy person that really enjoyed his life.
And we all knew that somehow he wasn't going to last breath.
He was going to end like that.
I was not unexpected.
So, but when our mutual, mutual friend, Baya died of cancer so fast, you wouldn't even, you know,
believe it.
That was very traumatic.
You know, I walked around for hours in Amsterdam and cried my eyes out.
I couldn't just, I didn't know what to do with the feelings.
I've never felt it like this.
And now that you're mom, and I've seen her, actually, two or three weeks before she died.
That's, get the hell out of me.
And I was, I was in shock when I saw her.
Yeah, I know.
And, you know, coming from showbees, and you know how to suppress your feelings and not show it.
So, we all did.
We had a nice and lovely afternoon, but it was, had an enormous impact on me.
Didn't talk about it, actually.
And your mom and I, and I were actually not, like, mother-in-law and mother, you know,
and, you know, and daughter-in-law, we actually became friends and we talked, you know,
for a long time on the phone about all sorts of things.
Because your mom was very intelligent and wonderful to talk to.
And, and I miss that.
And, um, now I start to think about it every day.
I think, oh, she's not there.
And, oh, it was so scary.
And we were so fast.
And you start to think about death.
And then I go with, with my dog to the doctor.
The last one that we have left, little, little swabber, is a Yorkie.
He's always been fine.
He's, he's, uh, healthy dog, never been sick in his life.
And what said the, the vet says he's going to die.
He has, uh, a, a kidney failure.
You know, okay.
That's death again.
And so, you know, you, there are some weeks and days that you just, you know.
So here's what I concluded last night after.
And now the less couple of nights,
I wake up in the middle of the night and get scared, scared of everything.
And everything is dying.
And I don't want to die.
And, and I have the heart disease.
And, you know, and all those stupid, you know, like, stupid things.
And you wake up and you think, oh, you know, it's not that bad, actually.
And then it's gone.
But it ruins your night.
No.
And you are scared.
It's dark.
You all, you feel lonely or snoring.
Everything's snoring.
Everyone's asleep.
You don't want to wake anybody.
But you feel horrible.
You want to have a warm, you want to just feel somebody.
And, you know, and so very typical Patricia of course has had this for three
three nights or maybe even longer and doesn't wake me up.
So last night, finally, the story came out.
And here's, because, you know, we were, it was a good conversation.
I think, um, short, but I'm not sure.
I'm not sure.
How long?
You kept saying, shut up and go to sleep.
Eventually, I'll just say, okay.
Yeah.
Okay.
Um, we are not, um, we are not religious people.
Yeah.
We are definitely spiritual people.
Very spiritual.
We have faith in things.
But, you know, there are hundreds of millions of people.
If not billions of people around the world who have a belief.
And as we talked about it last night, it kind of dawned on me that a lot of religion,
a lot of belief, is about dying.
And it's a way to overcome these exact fears.
You know, people who are strong believers, whether they're Christians, or Muslims, or Jews,
or Buddhists, or what else is there?
Harry Krishna.
Whatever it is.
It's, it's usually about the afterlife.
And people who believe that strongly.
That strength have no fear.
Do not have fear.
And for me, my mom dying.
And of course, it's emotional for me.
And I've been able to, well, you know,
I've been so busy that it's been much easier for me to suppress emotional feelings.
But I wasn't San Francisco for three weeks.
And I had a good, you know, good time by myself to process and things.
So the emotions, but process.
But my mom dying made me no longer afraid of death.
I'm not quite sure if I wanted to be fast or slow.
I really don't.
Really?
Well, you know, my mom did have a chance to say goodbye to everybody.
And make a men's and talk to a lot of people and do.
And really have some conversations that she,
excuse me, that she needed to have, that she wanted to have.
When I called Uncle Donna, I'm like the first thing Uncle Don said is,
you know, in the Bible, he said, it states that you're blessed
if you don't die suddenly, so you can say goodbye to people.
So that could be true.
There's something to the piece of it that we said for that.
So I'm not sure about it, but I'm not afraid.
Because you, it makes no sense to be it.
I feel better when you said goodbye.
What do you mean?
Well, do you think you, the feeling about somebody dying and you have the time to say goodbye?
Do you think it's better for the whole process?
I think that I witnessed the entire process was easier.
It was more of a gradual slide.
I think that was a lot easier than all of a sudden.
Being jerked from your life, I think that's somebody gets killed outside.
You know, run, run over by.
But that's, but I didn't die.
So I don't know, which, you know, that may be better for me, but was it better for my mom?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Yeah.
But I'm not afraid of it.
You can't be, I just don't think you can be afraid of something you can't stop anyway.
There's one thing I know for sure.
We're all going to die.
Yeah.
You know what?
I'm thinking all the time because when I was there that afternoon,
there was the last time I saw her.
Yeah.
She said to me, she was sitting there in a chair with a little head on her, on her head.
And she said, my God, you look so good.
And you know, sometimes you don't know what to say when people say that because she looked so horrible.
So horrible.
You know, it couldn't get worse.
And I didn't know what to say.
And I said, oh, yeah.
Well, I really, well, I got up so early.
And I thought, what the hell was that all about?
Why did I say that?
I'm still thinking, why did I say that?
But I didn't know what to say.
Yeah.
Because usually I would say, well, you look very good yourself.
You know, nice dress or decent of that.
Maybe it was beautiful.
But you're kind of avoiding the topic.
The topic surrounds the idea of being afraid of death.
And you and your mom too, by the way.
Definitely afraid of death this morning.
And we said to each other, let's not do that anymore.
Your mom is freaking hers.
I mean, she's 81.
So I understand.
Well, don't forget that.
And your dad's 81.
And he's had a quadruple bypass for 20 years.
I understand all that.
Yeah.
And they're burying their friends.
But so, so, but I guess, I guess we're at the point now where, you know, you can make a choice.
There's a couple choices.
One, we can be afraid of death.
Two, we cannot be afraid of death.
Or see, we can become very religious.
That's also an option.
You know, I've never been afraid of death.
I've never thought about it.
I was too much.
I was so busy enjoying life.
You know, enjoying every day, waking, you know, how I am.
Every day I wake up, I think Jesus, you know, I'm happy to be alive.
Oh, I said, Jesus.
But I did mean that.
Oh, God.
You are really so happy I'm alive.
And another beautiful day to gift.
Yeah.
You know, I think like that.
Right.
So then, why spend one second of that beauty?
Let me finish the question.
Oh, I thought it was a question.
It was a question.
Let me finish the question.
Okay.
Even though you and I don't need more than two words,
we do have listeners who want it.
That's true.
Okay.
So if you're so happy, if you're so happy,
when you wake up and it's a gift,
why spend one second of that day worrying about death?
Why don't do it?
Yeah.
You've got to agree with me.
That's just worthless.
It doesn't, it doesn't contribute anything.
There's nothing you can do.
But the fear of death.
I think is death.
Yeah.
Really?
And you and your mom, with all respect,
yeah, it's just something I've noticed in 20 years.
And you know, it's like,
Oh, God, I was gonna happen.
Oh, does something happen?
Oh, did you fall down?
You died.
Oh, we're gonna die.
Oh, don't do this.
Oh, very happy.
Happy people.
Yeah, yes, you're happy,
but there is an inner, un-ease that you have.
That I'd really, I'd like to help you get rid of that.
There's a urge to take care of other people.
But that's one thing.
That's one thing.
But everything.
But it's very focused around death.
No.
I don't think so.
As the ultimate.
It has this moment.
And this was my moment.
This is your moment.
And it was this week that I thought about it.
Maybe some things triggered.
I don't know.
Also, as my mom showed up in your,
maybe that's it.
Maybe that's it.
Maybe that woke me up.
I don't know.
Hmm.
Because someone hasn't completely passed on until she's visited Patricia in her life.
Yes, absolutely.
Absolutely.
And you're telling me, I don't believe.
Well, that was not what I said last night.
I said, you know, I have my own story.
I have a belief as to what happens when you die.
Yeah.
And maybe I can't even really verbalize it.
But I do have some kind of ideas about it.
Which give me something to believe in.
Yeah.
You have different experiences.
You believe much more in the spirits and the spiritual world.
So you've got to build your story and then believe in it and stick to it.
What difference is it making?
Mine as well.
You know, be happy because you believe something's going to happen a certain way.
And maybe if you believe something's going to happen a certain way.
It actually will happen that way.
Yeah.
Sometimes you feel guilty because you've got such a great life.
Everything goes so well.
That's not good.
I was reading in the newspaper George Clooney.
Yeah.
Told the United Nations that they have to help out in Darfur.
I saw that.
Because if the UN pulls out there was it 7,000 relief workers, then two and a half million people will die.
Yeah.
And that was a story about an inch wide below the fold on the inside towards the
crease of page three.
Yeah.
But it was on the news also on BBC news.
But as an entertainment story.
Or do they really?
No.
I've seen it a couple of times because he called it as horrible as the Holocaust cost.
Oh.
You remember for Darfur that guy.
He did like, I don't know.
It was like 1500 pounds or something like that for a helicopter flight that I put
up.
Yeah.
So it was an auction.
You came from a Holocaust to do that.
Oh, because it was for the Holocaust.
Yeah.
That's what I said.
From Darfur.
It was a country.
He gave money to Darfur.
Oh, that's why.
It's about Darfur.
Why are you mentioning in a helicopter?
Anything to talk about helicopters.
Oh, no.
No.
Now, just hit me.
I just remembered because it's been like a year and a half since I've been trying to
hook this up with this Pascal who was going to surprise his dad.
He did all this money because I had helicopter hours and said go ahead and you know.
That's what I did it.
Yeah.
But no, but no.
But no, no, no.
No, no, no.
I saw him and on TV is on George Clooney.
George.
And I thought it was good that he did that.
Yeah.
Somebody has to tell me.
I hope.
I mean, what do we need to do?
This is what this is the point that I.
It always breaks down from me.
What can I do?
What can I do at this point?
I mean, I've helped raise money for Duffer.
But what can I really do?
Well, they have to give these people attention and why is the you end pulling out?
Why is the you end pulling out of Duffer?
Exactly.
See, we got it.
Why do you think I know that?
No, no, no, no.
You watched the BBC report.
Didn't you?
Or you just looking at George Clooney's ass.
That too.
Exactly.
This is the problem with with celebrity endorsements ladies and gentlemen.
You get people looking at their ass.
Maybe I should just stop ascertaining.
And then in the meanwhile, you think, hey, you know,
who's doing a thing about?
Apparently September 30th is some kind of deadline.
So we'd have to do something pretty quickly.
Exactly.
But it's clearly messed up.
Horrible.
Okay.
That was a pretty much big fucking bummer.
Yeah.
Bummer conversation.
But it feels good.
You have to get rid of your feelings now.
Because I sometimes tend to keep him and not,
and not, you know, express yourself.
Yeah, for not worrying other people with it.
Yeah, but it doesn't work.
It doesn't work.
Boring other people with it.
So are you still afraid?
Of course I'm afraid.
And I am afraid.
Yeah.
And that's also since, you know,
I was diagnosed with an heart disease.
Before that,
I never thought about it.
Never.
I thought I lived forever.
You know, now it's just, you know,
hanging above my head and just keeps hanging.
You got to get rid of that thing.
And sometimes I don't think about it, you know,
and most of the time I don't think about it,
say that.
Uh-huh.
But, you know, there are moments.
And because, and the thing is with heart disease,
if you worry and you stress,
your heart hurts.
So it's sort of a cycle.
It's a vicious circle.
Yes, it is.
So let's work on that.
Yep.
Let's think happy.
I'm sure lots of people have ideas and suggestions
and feedback on this.
There's no doubt people will be calling.
A column will give you the voicemail number.
Plus one.
The plus is necessary.
If you're entering this into your mobile phone.
Uh-huh.
So plus one, 201, 65, 65, 65,
seven, or in London,
207, 681, 3753.
That will be plus four, four,
Uh, we'd love hearing it.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm saying, you know,
and then podcast, podcast.
Yeah.
podcast.
Well, podcast.
It's actually very good to express your feelings.
Yeah.
And it doesn't cost anything, actually.
To do this, you know,
just grab your mic and get rid of it.
Very good.
Are you going to do your own show now?
No.
Is that a note?
That's a note.
You'd be great.
You'd be great at your show.
There's a new Frank Truth.
I would be in my own language, I think.
Oh, really?
You do a podcast in Dutch for that huge Dutch audience.
If I, if I, if I,
Why you are so good in English?
No.
You listen.
Still translating my head now and then.
Oh, man, your head must be overloaded.
Wearing about death, translating languages.
If it gets complicated, I have to,
because I hear it in Dutch, and I don't have to quickly translate it.
The more you do it, the more you speak to language,
is no exactly what I mean.
I know, I speak to languages,
but the more you do it, the more naturally it will come to you.
Yeah, I know.
Or the more it will come to you naturally.
See, no, I was having problems with the Dutch in English.
Okay.
Anyway, flying to Amsterdam Sunday.
Yep.
Getting all of our visas and all that crap done Monday.
I hope that you're, um, identity, uh...
No.
Come in the mail today.
No, did you see it in the mail this morning?
I didn't see the mail.
No.
Oh, okay, maybe it's there.
Okay.
It's so much paperwork.
No, no, no, that was, that's a FedEx.
So much paperwork.
So much that has to be done.
I know.
But.
My goodness.
Okay.
Do we leave it at that?
Yeah.
Think about it over the weekend.
Oh, you know, you can, you're not always, uh, fun and laughing.
Oh, no.
Yeah, this is, I think this is fun.
Discuss our thoughts.
Let's talk about it some more in a couple of weeks.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
I think we'll go lie down now.
Yeah.
I can see that.
I think I'm going to crow into the fetal position.
Yeah.
Fall over.
All right, baby.
Everybody have a great weekend.
DailySourceCode.com.
Adam at podshow.com.
And, uh...
Thank you, hon.
You're welcome, darling.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it.
On the high performance podcast delivery network from podshow
and limelight networks.
I love it.