Think Advertising sucks.
Think you can do better?
Pod Show and EarthLink are willing to put our money where your mouth is.
Listen to this podcast or go to adchelens.podshow.com to see how you can win big
in the EarthLink make advertising better challenge.
Delta Sierra Charley, 4-1-4
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
I have a large of a listener.
Back in the dark.
Some colleagues do the show.
I need you to show.
I've got a metal picture.
We're on the show.
I'm on the show.
I need you to show.
We need the show.
I'm on the show.
I only do autograph after the show.
I need to be the crush.
Find the drug that will get us high.
I see it all from a different point of view.
I'll never sell you out.
Is that what this is all about?
My mouth is dry.
And I thought you would roll my side up.
Way to stand.
Right in the wall.
We don't get in the walls alone.
After all.
It's all alone.
Today is the day we run away.
Today is the day I'm getting off on you.
Today is the day I can't but push.
Find the drug that will get me higher.
Leave it all behind for something new.
Did I sell you out?
Is that what this is all about?
You will.
It's dry.
But I don't think you wasting your time on me.
If you ride it on the wall.
We don't get in the walls alone.
After all.
It's all alone.
We don't get in the walls alone.
After all.
We ride in the walls alone.
We don't get in the walls alone.
After all.
For a new York City straight to your ear buds.
Thanks to the proudly music network.
My best friend.
It's only love.
And it already weighs.
Everybody how you are coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey.
It's An kills for it.
That's right.
Direct from Kurii Kotters your daily source code.
Now, I'm going to assume that most people who listen to the show actually are no longer in school.
Do you remember the days?
The day and today is one of those days.
If you look outside, it's it's beautiful weather.
The birds are chirping in the background.
If I just shut up for a second, you'll hear them.
Come on, you crap heads.
See, when you ask them to, they never do it.
The birds are chirping.
The sun is shining.
And remember when you were in high school, or maybe even in grade school.
And those wonderful words the teacher would say is, kids, today we're going to do some different.
We're going to take class outside.
You remember that and like, and you'd really be into it and you'd all go sit on the grass in the sunshine
or maybe in the shade and he'd bring along some of the drink and he'd have your books.
And actually it was, you'd really be able to concentrate really well and there was always a good vibe.
Well, I want to do something different today as well.
This morning, I was sitting in the big green thing going through the pod segment music network,
listening to all the new tracks that have been submitted.
By the way, this is something I used to do when I was on the radio.
Once a week, the record promoters would come by and say, hey, here's this new song,
here's this song, check out this album, check out this record.
And we'd spend a couple hours on a Friday, usually, going through all the new releases of the week.
But these days with the pod segment music network, you can do that.
In fact, you not only can you, but I do that every single day.
I sit here and I listen to all the new tracks and all the diverse music and I'm always smiling.
Whether I like the songs or not, just I can't believe the energy that people are putting into this.
So I figured today would just play a lot of music and stuff like that.
Adam, yeah.
Aaron.
Hey, just wanted to call and find out why I lately, everybody that's been leaving a U of message on the voicemail,
sounds like they went to the Captain Kirk School of Broadcasting.
Exactly.
And I enjoyed Sierra, number two is what's up with that, man.
I mean, like, what a bunch of non-polishers, who doesn't have time to sit around to
almond-collar, voicemail.
Yeah.
Love a show.
Crashing.
Burn it.
Exactly.
Not a lot of voicemails in today's show.
If you want to leave one, though, you can give us a call in New Jersey.
The numbers 201, 625, 635, 7.
In London, our number is O2O, 768, 1375, 3.
You won't hear any fancy greeting just to, hey, leave your message and I look forward to
hearing from you.
So, in the vein of playing music today, some more stuff in the pod save music network.
Delphany and blue, and California.
Yeah, I love you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah,
Right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right
right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, ooh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, ohh, oh, oh, oh, oh, ohh oh
That music needs you
Let me hold you
Delphinium blue, California, of course you can find links to every single song on today's
show in the show notes, a daily source code dot com.
It's so cool reading the bios of these artists that they put up themselves on the
pot safe music network.
He's from the District of Columbia.
I'm just going to read this verbatim.
Delphinium blue has been described as a mixture of Pet Shop Boys, Prince, Moby, and
Pet Shmode.
It's pop rock wrapped up in electronic production created by one guy, Arlon Godwin, an openly
gay songwriter and producer who was performed before more than 250,000 people in the last
year alone.
Yeah, all of the songs that you hear today on the Daily Source Code will be made available
for purchase if the artist wants that because that's all part of the big, unlabeled concept.
This is so liberating, man.
I used to do music shows all the time, but it was kind of whatever came out of the computer.
Of course, when I was doing shows 25 years ago, that's kind of like old school, you know,
feeling good.
So I'm going through through my email and through notes and I stumbled across a news report,
which it really shocked me that I hadn't that I didn't know this had happened a couple
of weeks ago.
The report that I read was from June 6, so I think it's from the first week of June.
I did not know that Billy Preston passed away.
If you don't know, and the whole fact that I, and I was in the US, I think it was in
the States, right?
I mean, this is Billy Preston deserves more than, you know, just a little mention in
rollings on rollingstone.com.
He deserves more than maybe a quick 15 second to pass away this week in entertainment tonight.
This guy deserves some major props.
He was truly the fifth beetle.
And the sixth rolling stone, if you think about it.
Here's this, this is from my thing, this is from rollingstone.com.
Let me just read this to you.
Billy Preston, the exuberant keyboardist who landed dream gigs with the beetles and the
rolling stones and enjoyed his own series of hit singles, including out of space and nothing
from nothing died Tuesday at age 59, which is way too fucking young.
Rolling stone didn't write that.
That was editorial by me.
Preston's long-time manager, Joyce Moore said Preston had been in a coma since November
and a care facility and was taken to a hospital in Scottsdale, Arizona, Saturday after
his condition deteriorated.
She says he had a very, very beautiful last few hours and a very beautiful passing.
Preston who had battled to chronic kidney failure had undergone a kidney transplant in 2002,
but the kidney failed and he had been on dialysis treatments ever since.
Okay, so 75% of this report is about him dying and not about the tremendous amount
of work this guy created for us.
And of course, none of the songs that he created are pod safe.
But in this case, I think I have to make an exception to my own rule and I really don't
care if I go to jail for this because Billy Preston deserves to be remembered in rock
and roll in pop history as someone who was really important and instrumental.
And also, and this is a widely known fact in rock and roll, not very known in entertainment
show business reporting, but apparently he also had a huge penis, it's just one of those
things you pick up, you know, being in the business for years and years.
And at one point, I believe he was married, I don't know if he was married to Syrida or
Syrida was married to Stevie Wonder, I can't really remember how that all fit together.
But he had a couple of hits with Syrida, one I could not find on the Napster, which is
it will come in time, which was one of my favorites.
And from when I was growing up, but he had a huge smash all over Europe with the song
that I'm going to play for you now, again, it's not pod safe, but damn Billy Preston,
I'm going to miss you.
With you on Born Again, Billy Preston and Syrida, illegal play on the Charney.
Come bring me your softness, come for me through all this madness, warm and
don't you know with you, I'm born again.
Come give me the most weakness, now that you there is no weakness, the life safe
within your arms I'm with you.
I was half, not whole, instead, with none, which of you is born, and need of one.
Come show me your kindness, in your arms I know I'll find this, warm and
don't you know with you, I'm born again.
Come bring me your softness, come for me through all this madness, warm and
don't you know with you, I'm born again, I was half, not whole, instead, with none,
which of you is born, need of one.
Come show me your kindness, in your arms I know I'll find this, warm and
don't you know with you, I'm born again.
Come bring me your softness, come for me through all this madness, warm and don't
you know with you, I'm born again.
know with you, I'm born again on the daily source code, and that really does piss me off
when people who've contributed so much get so overlooked because of populist demand for
entertainment content.
I really truly feel that's my duty to bring stuff like that to you, and I think it's
well worth the risk in this case.
Another one of those fabulous musicians and artists who contributed so much, certainly in my
lifetime with the music which of course is the soundtrack to your life was Dan Hartman,
and he died, oh man, I think Dan passed away 12, 13 years ago, and not a fucking
peep man, almost nothing, and this guy made, he was a personal friend, but he had so many
hits, just unbelievable, and I remember, and this was pre-podcasting, I was still at
MTV, I could barely get him to play a video, you know, I can dream about you as the more
like a VH1 video, if it's dude, it's Dan Frick and Hartman, and I just never really understood.
So again, I feel that's my duty to highlight some of that stuff when it comes along,
which I hope isn't too often because we like having all these great artists around, you
know what I mean?
Ah, okay, let me see how we doing now, I think I can play one more song here that the
serious satellite listeners will be able to enjoy, of course, those of you tuning in on
serious stars 102, you're in the middle of our pod show podcast block, taking up your
10, the clock in the eastern time zone, we have Pacific Coast Hellway coming up, he's
radio, Don Drew, Steve Gilmore's Daily Show, let's see, Thursday today, so I think it's
also digital flawed some, and of course, Michael Butler will wind it up with some pod
safe tunes and some good kickass rock and roll between 930 and 10 o'clock.
From British Columbia, Johnny Ferreira, he's an award-winning saxophonist, international
touring and recording artists that writes and performs his old brand of R&B, swing, jazz,
and rock and roll, backed by his 8 piece band with horn section, rock and guitar, boogie
piano and his screaming sax, it's something different, I think you're like the 90
down, I don't care about you cleaning up, I'm making your eyes as quiet enough, I won't
even watch a Stanley Cup when you're well and I'm not it gown, just out of here and
let's snuggle up, I light up the candles and feel your cup, I got me standing at a
tension now and you're wearing that night again, I've been waiting so long for this
side to barely control myself, the little lovin's a what I missed, I can't think enough
then there's such a night night, night night, night, night, night, night, night again, I've
taught all the way around, you know what I'm saying, when you're wearing that night
it gown, I'm buttering creams, what your skin feels like, there's a rubbing your shoulders
left to right, I always want to stay the rest of the night when you're wearing that night
it gown, don't even get some air, the neighbors might see but I don't care, I know if I was
there, but I would stay when you're wearing that night it gown, well I've been waiting so long
for this side to barely control myself, the little lovin's a what I missed, I can't think enough
then there's such a night night, night, night, night, night again, I've taught all the way around
I've taught all the way around, you know what I'm saying, when you're wearing that night it gown, yeah baby
my night night night, night night, night, night, night again, I've taught all the way around,
you know what I'm saying, when you're wearing that night it gown, I'm buttering creams, what your skin feels like you're
night it down night night night night it down
It's tight tight tight, I'll never wait around
You won't say it and I won't say it
When you're wearing that naughty gown
I know about you
But you just don't hear enough of that on the radio
You know what I'm saying?
You cannot get that anywhere else
Podcasts are bringing it to you
You can find that all in the Pods have music network
Every single genre that you can think of is there
It's really busy this week for me
Every single evening we're going on until
Or at least I'm going on until around 11.30 midnight
Talking to Pod Show HQ in San Francisco
As we near the unleashing of Pod Show
The Pod Show Plus, the Pod Cast delivery network
And portions at least of the upgraded Pods
Pod Save Music Network
It's all going to come together at the same time
Just before we start opening up our offices in the UK
It's getting nuts
And I know I haven't given you an official date
But trust me when I say that we'll be liberating your media
Yeah, here's something I want you to help me out with
So of course I've been keeping you up to speed on my mom's progress
And one thing that is maybe the Charlie listeners can help with
Because I've had four doctors look at it, mouth hygienists
All kinds of specialists
Because of my mom's diminished immunity
She's developed these blisters in her mouth
Which makes it incredibly painful to eat
Or even in many cases to drink
Crap
If you're on serious, go to dailysourcecode.com
And listen to the rest of the show
So you can hear exactly what I need from you
Because maybe you guys can help
PCH is next if you're listening to stars 102
And those of you who of course are really hit to
And listen to the Pod Cast, you can just keep listening
So these are like source
And I don't want to cross you out
But it makes it incredibly difficult for her to eat
Which of course is the one thing she needs to do
The most right now is eat
And we've tried everything, everything off the shelf
So you don't have, you know
There's all kinds of stuff that will numb it out
And give you temporary relief
But it's really looking for a longer term solution
There may not be one
But if you know of anyone who's in the same situation
My mom is in
And has had something similar
And if you know of a solution
I'd be very happy to hear from you
Adamaccurry.com
Today kicks off Nomdex
In Seattle, Washington
This is a Chris Perillo's show
Chris and Ponzi
I have to say it's really Ponzi show
I'm sorry Chris
But Ponzi really is the engine behind this
You're the front man dude
You know, you're like a facade
Just like me for Pod Show
But it's okay because we all need a strong woman behind us
Making a shit really happen
Now unfortunately I couldn't be at Nomdex
I had fully planned on being there
Because I really do enjoy the show
And I think it is
It's a great place to meet people
It's a great place to hear interesting speakers
And it's just a well organized conference
And it's always a lot of fun
And Chris and Ponzi are full of so much energy
It's just a joy just to watch them
As they go about making this a huge party
So I want to congratulate them
First off with the Nomdex 6.0
And Derek Kay Miller
Created a song about it
Which is pretty funny
And I'd love to share it with
Nomdex
It's typical to explain
It's big bang
Nomdex
It's a set of the sun
For the good and boys
Nomdex
All the high tick toys
But cast an aggregate
Video black and crazy tagging
Harry's pissing Ponzi running
Madly at the course
Don't cheat for death
All the free swag
To be had
Because I've become a monster
Nomdex
Every conference
Sucked and I turned it around
I attended my first nomdex to the age of six
Every then I know about life
Love for the human condition
I learned a nomdex
If mankind
Will be saved
The answers will be found
Among the pocket presenters
Any bad memories
Are my people working in the fight
Oh, easy
Nomdex is like that
I'm into the picture
I say, so I'm here
All our good friends
I don't know Nomdex
It's a point here
It's a witch factor
Up into the fucker
If you're tired
I'd light up
When they give you something
I'd give you something
I'd like to give you a nomdex
I'd like a nomdex
The audience might echo you
Upon the stage
And your choice
Of a web feed format
My cause of rage
You know I think
We really ought to try
To the globe
That bandwidth
All that bandwidth
Sky high
The world's shortest
Teddy Gettles so low
For fantasy, yes
And life world
Ask common to count
Mags, boats, paddling
Seas, mobile phones
They look at me
Don't know what makes it so good
We brought an algorithm
To explain it
Every good
I won't
But we can't
Nondex
Seas, boats, paddling
Is it one or three points?
Cloud everyone
Nondex
It's piggybound
It keeps us out of control
I'd like people
Come in with that
Give someone to say
Hey, could I come and pitch my product
We basically kick them in the shin
I hope there's a life feed like last year so I can listen in because I truly look forward to hear any of that and that was it
John Edwards is keynote speaker, so that should be a good show
You know, I forget every single time I do one of these segments. I get a whole slew of yanks versus the Britscom
Everybody knows that it's a yarn to see. Let's just like you and me. It's the yanks and the Brits
The yanks versus the Brits
Mind the gap Charles quietly sent me something really funny. He'd picked up which totally encompasses and encapsulates
What the real differences are between the yanks and the Brits from the Brits side this time
Here we go. Being British is about driving in a German car to an Irish pub for a Belgian beer
Then traveling home grabbing an Indian curry or a Turkish cabab on the way to sit on a sweetest furniture and watch American shows on a Japanese television
And the most British thing of all well of course suspicion of anything foreign
Here's the central part dude. He's also on the pot safe music network Tom Cruise scares me
How about you? He shouldn't be that scary
He's only five foot two
But ten people some mission impossible three because he's always talking back
Scientology makes an ordinary guy like me say Tom Cruise scares me
Oprah scares me just like a little pub
I think on her worst day she could beat me up
Now she started out like a nice young girl but you better watch out because once your plans unfold
She's gonna take over the world and Oprah scares me
Another guy who scares me is that David Blaine
Things he's extraordinary
I think he's quite insane
35 hours just standing on top of a pole
Then he tried to hold his breath in a goldfish pole
To die prime time is his goal and he scares me
Dick Cheney scares me
With those be the eyes
They get intense and glary
Every time he lies which is often
He's got a machine where his heart should be
Just pumping out an evil philosophy
Issues people in the face and gets away
Scott free and he scares me
Wolfe puts her scares me
I just think it's nuts
To have a name that's scary
Wolfe puts her on such a little pots
Now the folks at CNN think the man's revered
But he's kind of like an elf with a scruffy fear
And his monotone voices just a little too
Winner and it scares me everybody
Talk to the scares me
How about you?
He shouldn't be that scary
How tall is he?
He's only five but two
But ten people saw a mission in possible three
Because he's always dreaming about a Scientology
Makes an ordinary guy like me
Save Tom Cruise scares me
Ordinary people like you and me
David, he polito is his name
He can find him in Central Park in New York City
Hundreds of thousands of people have seen him there
He performs during these months really
He's funny
And he's got his stuff up on the pod save music
Now work all the links to that of course in the show today
And for the ongoing conversation go to curry.com
And all that's going to change pretty soon
As we move over to pod show plus
New tools for listeners, ways for you to enjoy pod
Cast better for you to share pod cast with others
To talk about them, to promote them, to contribute to them
It's like magic box
All right
Dude, I think that's it
That's right
I was going to say that this has been nice
Hope you enjoyed it
Hope you liked the songs
Of course, the beauty of pod casting
As you can skip through a song you don't like
And this is just fun
In fact, this is the kind, well not these songs in particular
But I do like kind of DJing stuff
I really missed doing that
And once we get pod show plus pushed out
And we're rolling with that
I certainly plan on doing some DJing at the pod show
Palace in second life
We've got, I call it DD
What's her name? Drew
D-R-U
She's, uh, she's been doing the DJing
She's from the UK
And she's so, the way she does it is so cute
It's really an enjoyable experience
Just too bad
That, you know, all the limitations of second life
You can basically only have 28 people listening to it
At the same time
Thanks to Cast Blaster Mike for sending me the new new new new new beta version
As we get ready to integrate everything
Not only does it now post directly up to the podcast delivery network
It's got a little HTML editor in there
Which, uh, well, you'll see
I've used it on the show today
And, uh, bam, it's just getting so much easier
Even for me
I'll see you tomorrow everybody
Take care and of course tomorrow
Friday festivities
Get your pod safe music picks in
Another pod show podcast
Stick it in your ear
Get this pod cast
And we're great ones like it
On the high performance pod cast
Delivery network from Podjo
And line-white networks
I love it