This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 422.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
On casting, kids, Adam Curry.
Oh, morning, Vietnam.
Hello, cameras. Remember, Monday is malaria day.
That's my time to take that big orange pill and get ready for the whole team in Tuesday.
We will happy to meet you as Lisa.
I just become
I burst in from heart
It's the most begin
I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here,
I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I'm here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am
For my sight, for every life that shines
Shadow of the world
I am here, I am here
I am there where you're sleeping
I am lying, I am lying
I am there for every life that shines
I am there where you're sleeping
I am here, I am here
I am there for every life that shines
I think he's done again
I am here for every life that shines
an airport called South End, which is a mid-sized field.
They take heavy metal there as well.
And I knew the captain Dan wouldn't be able to fly
safety pilot with me on Sunday.
And I couldn't get Jason, who's been flying with me before
because he had to work in the tower.
So I said, you know what, why don't we alter our flight plan
on the way back?
That's from Antwerp to Farrowks.
We'll stop off at South End.
Then we'll have seen the airport and I'll feel a little more
confident.
And so we did that and everything went fine.
And I, oh, man, fucking impeccable landing.
A greaser as Captain Dan called it just nice and smooth,
barely felt me touched down.
And I hadn't told Patricia that I'd actually never
flown solo in this aircraft ever before.
Well, you know, because the missions have always been to Antwerp,
which, as I said, is that a lot you have to do
as a reasonable amount of work that has to go on,
particularly communicating with air traffic control,
that at least six different people you have to talk to
and watch out for other idiots who are flying around on the weekend.
Of course, who don't talk to anybody and just seem to fly around
it will.
So it was a beautiful day, Sunday.
It was about 10 miles per hour of wind coming just from the north,
north east.
So actually perfect for South End because they have a 0, 6,
2, 4 runway so you can literally fly right in.
And off we went, first time together,
we've never been in the plane together alone either.
So of course, we did a little semi-mile,
mile high club thing at 2,400 feet.
So it didn't really count.
And it was really just a kiss because damn there's a lot of work
to do in that continent.
So I flew Patricia out, you know, great, dropped her off at South End.
Everything was perfect.
Now on the way back, as I said, I'd never soloed in this aircraft
before, of course, I flown solo because you have to in order
to get your license, but I never actually landed it with just myself.
And I didn't really think about it because, you know,
I guess typically I've always had minimum of two people and
oftentimes four and it behaves differently, you know,
because of the way, it's very obvious.
And it doesn't matter, Patricia's not heavy,
but you could just put 20 pounds in the right hand front seat
and it will make a difference.
But I just wasn't thinking of it.
So I'm coming in for a few, because I dropped her off,
I was going to fly back to some grocery shopping
and then go pick her up at the end of the day.
And I come in for the landing and everything's perfect.
And all of a sudden, it just like, because it was so light,
I configured it a little bit differently.
And I start to bounce and start to pour up around
and so I call it go around and I fly around, try to do it again.
Another oscillating bounce, like, oh, wait a minute.
Of course, I'm much lighter.
So the third time, of course, being a charm,
and I dropped it onto the tarmac.
And as you know, as we say in aviation,
if you walk away from the landing, it was a fantastic landing.
But what was really nice is that Jason, as I said,
he couldn't come flying with me.
He was in the tower.
And so he's, of course, watching this, you know,
watching me, like a fucking flipper, a Cirque de Soleil moves.
They're trying to get the plane on the landing strip.
And I'm like, oh, Jason, I'm going around on this one.
He says, oh, it's all right, man.
And it happens to all of us.
He was really nice.
It was so nice to have that kind of reassuring,
don't worry about it, dude.
We're not laughing at you here.
And of course, he was laughing at me,
but at least he wasn't humiliating me publicly.
And I had kind of neglected to mention
the Patricia that I'd never soloed in the aircraft,
but she had a great time.
It was so nice.
You know, so I picked her up and we flew back
and that whole bit from South End to about big and hill.
It is, you know, there's relatively no traffic.
You can see London right off in the distance
because you're flying over the Thames
at the last bit of the Thames there.
It's completely smooth air.
It was just wonderful.
And we had a great time and landed without bouncing.
You know, one of Adam's typical plump were downlandings,
but it was without bouncing.
I just, I did call to the tower and said, Jason,
I might wheel still on and said, yeah, we either still there.
But Patricia said she definitely wanted to do more.
And I'm very happy because how cool is it
when you can take your bride and hop into your plane
and fly somewhere else completely different.
So when I get back from San Francisco, leaving tomorrow,
for it's actually so it's a week,
but when you take travel and everything,
it's probably nine or 10 days.
Because we've got a board meeting coming up on Wednesday,
which I'm very excited about.
And we're now we're really kicking to gear.
Now that Podshow Plus is stable and we're fixing all the bugs,
we have some interface, some redistisions to make.
And of course, we're going to start getting down
with, you know, building up the network
and bringing people in.
And we're going to be organizing registered listener drives
and all kinds of amazing stuff that anybody
can participate in, whether you're a podcast,
but probably more importantly, if you're a listener,
you can participate in helping the growth of the network
by helping out your favorite podcast.
And actually, yeah, making some coin while you're at it.
My sister put up another podcast.
She's willow.podshow.com and her podcast is Italy.podshow.com.
And she does a podcast called from the,
from the Hills of Florence, Italy.
And her first one, she had a messed up microphone,
but now she's got her, her mic set up,
her husband did a little jingle for.
And I'm just, I'm loving it.
You know, for all for the years that I've been podcasting
and tinkering around with stuff.
And she's very technical.
She does, she's a PHP programmer.
And you don't hear a lot of programmers actually create podcast.
Now that I think of it, you know,
for her to jump on means that, you know,
I think we did something right with, with podshow plus.
It makes sense.
Of course, there's all kinds of shit that we have to take care of.
Hey, we'll be discussing a little bit of that in this episode
of the Daily Source Code for two, two.
And some other shit, literally.
Adam, this is Ed Stofel here of the Flying Reports podcast
at flyingreports.com.
I want to thank you so much for all your work with the podshow team
for getting the site up and running.
It's a great concept.
And now that it's a public beta,
you'll know that find lots of technical issues.
I've made a podshow wish list and posted it online
in my section of podshow.
Most of them are technical.
I haven't figured out how to use the so-called vacuum feature
to upload my podcast files to podshow,
but the problem has been referred to one of the sites developers
to figure out the problem, and I'm sure he will.
I do wish there was a way to merge all these different IDs and pages.
Let's say I now have a music sign in.
My page at podshow, a podcast page name.
It does get a little confusing.
And when I picked my podshow name, I thought I was picking a name
for where the show would live.
But now I have to pick a different page for my show.
So that gets all little confusing.
The team, though, has obviously spent a lot of time
developing features that people will want.
And I do appreciate that.
And I'm confident that they will be able to solve the technical issues.
And I'm hoping they incorporate some of the ideas that users are submitting.
So thanks again, Adam, and tailwinds, dude.
Yeah, tailwinds back at you.
And did I have some yesterday?
Let me tell you, saw 170 knots ground speed digging it.
So all you're list, thank you very much.
Good stuff in there.
And of course, yes, we take everything,
and try to communicate as much as possible
in as many different places as possible.
I'm seeing Joe Carpenter show up on the Curry.com comments.
And Mark and Steve, the emo social network boys,
so almost anywhere that you're getting this information out,
we are definitely doing things with it.
I agree that it was a bit confusing.
It seems that even though the language was pretty clear,
I think it was clear, because we did go over this several times.
Still a lot of people really thought we were coming out
with some kind of thing for podcasters.
And I can't stress enough that we built this for audience.
And for people who want to enjoy podcasters.
And of course, we tried to put as much
of the good thinking into the podcast creation side,
not just for people who've been podcasting for a while,
but also for people who just are new to this,
come in as a listener, and then decide
they want to make a podcast, and really try to cater to that.
So we figured everyone would sign up with their desired user name.
And I guess we made some thinking errors in there.
And there were quite a significant number.
And I say no, at least 20 podcasters who registered what they wanted
for their show name.
And of course, if you have, let's say if I registered,
instead of as Adam, I registered his daily source code.
And then I went and created a show
and wanted that to be daily source code.podshow.com.
It wouldn't work because daily source code was already taken.
And that's my main identity.
So the really are, you have your own identity on podshow plus.
So when you sign up, sign up as yourself,
and then you can create shows.
As many shows as you want, as many episodes as large as you want,
you can, the files can be whatever you want, literally,
which of course is the beauty of the podcast, the living network.
But you can't, you know, what you need to be aware of
is that if you sign up with your show name,
the name is then going to be taken.
So that would be the first, and we've got to figure out,
if this is going to be an ongoing problem,
or if this is just a temporary migration issue
is people who already have podcasts
want to get them onto the podshow network
into podshow plus.
So we have migrated a number of people by hand,
because it was still pretty manageable.
I think there's a tool being put into place
for people as that goes onward that you could possibly swap
out your show name for your identity name,
or something like that.
So we are working on it.
Obviously, it's not top of the list,
but it's in the top range,
because we do want to help everyone out,
and that's why I said we're doing a lot of these manually, as well.
Now, regarding the feed vacuum,
this is a good question, and I know you're tuning in saying,
where does the talk about poop?
Yeah, don't worry, it's coming.
I just can't get through a couple of these.
I see my kind of question about the feed vacuum,
and then I think I can answer that specifically.
Hey Adam, it's Mike from the Let's Speak Italian podcast.
I just have a quick question for you
about the feed vacuum in podshow plus.
I wonder if you might take a minute
and just explain how the vacuum is supposed to work,
because I've been trying for a couple of days now,
and I can't figure it out.
When I go in and I enter in,
what my new podshow domain name is supposed to be,
it tells me that that name is already taken,
and it won't suck over my RSS feed,
and all my files into podshow plus.
I know that the podshow domain name that I selected
is mine, because I pre-registered
and got a confirmation back,
that that's my new podshow domain name.
So is the podshow domain name,
is that my domain name as a podcaster,
or as a listener, or both, I'm just confused.
I can't understand why it won't let me enter in,
the new Let's Speak Italian podshow domain name
that I've reserved.
I did send your boys an email a couple days ago.
I haven't heard back,
so I was just getting a little impatient.
I'm definitely interested in moving over to podshow,
moving all my stuff over there,
but I just can't seem to figure out that feed vacuum.
Maybe you could address it in the DSE.
Thanks, man.
How do you get it?
Yeah, pronto.
Okay.
Exactly, exactly the problem I just highlighted.
In addition, we've seen some people who use the feed vacuum.
The feed vacuum is really a migration tool.
So if you want to make use of the podcast delivery network,
which is free and you can read the agreement,
every single time in fact you go to your show,
you'll see a link to the agreement.
So you can be reminded of what it means
and what we can do for you.
You can start a new show by sucking over
your existing podcast feed and the shows.
Now what does happen is people may have a feed
with, let's say, 20 shows listed in it
or sometimes much more than that.
Those actually have to be transferred
from your current host over to our servers.
And that can just take a while.
I mean, you know how long it takes
to download one show.
Even though we have high speed connections,
it kind of depends on the size of the file
and the connection that the host that you are currently using has.
So it can take a little while for all the files to be sucked over.
And of course, the whole thing wasn't working in the beginning
and we apologize for not sucking,
literally not sucking because we sucked
because we didn't suck.
Anyway, that's taking care of.
And I think that people who signed up with a show name
now understand that there is a way to convert that
and we're making it tool available.
Yeah, and I'm Mrs. Chris and Philadelphia.
I have a comment on my own channel.
My console page is eGoAPEX.podshow.com.
I think, let's set up a page there.
I sent up a collection.
And I set up a channel full of all the podcasts I want.
Put them in the iTunes.
And they aren't showing up, you know,
as I'd expect them to.
I'm still subscribed through all the normal feeds.
And so I see the dawn and do show up in, you know,
it's own feed and not in the podcast channel.
I'm going to have to take a look at it all.
Well, basically, what I want to do in the future
is have this one feed for my channel sent to quick news,
which is a program that once runs on my palm,
which is Wi-Fi.
And amazingly, in my single studio has Wi-Fi now.
So basically, when a new podcast arrives, quick news will check
down at it, boom, there it is.
I can listen to on my palm.
That's an ideal world.
Hopefully, you can get there eventually.
OK, let me just interrupt here for one second.
OK, that's exactly the way we designed it.
And we've had some issues with the channels.
I think, particularly what is happening is you're putting a show
into a channel.
And then for some unknown reason, some shows disappear from the channel.
And that is a bug.
And we're trying to fix that.
Believe me, I'm all over it because I've been using pod show
plus and the whole channel metaphor for months now,
while I was in beta.
I've not used iTunes for months, literally,
other than sync up to my iPod.
This is exactly what we wanted to make.
So you actually couldn't make your portable.
When I was at your, I forget the name of the aggregator you
were talking about as a pod catcher.
So you could use that or you could use juice,
or you could use your mobile phone.
And the new Nokia has a podcast download
the function built right into it that was the N91
since sale, payment you bastards.
So the idea was, and you'll see,
and actually, I should lead by example,
and I'll do this later on today.
Most people have like music shows, talk shows, comedy shows,
those are kind of like their channels.
But the intent, and I should do this myself
and actually perfect for the upcoming trip,
is you could have a channel for your iPod,
a channel for your trio or trio,
a channel for at work, a channel for at home.
And all of these channels have different ways
to download them.
And so if you're in your channel view,
and you click on a show or you expand the channel,
you'll see that the four download options,
which includes iTunes, just click on the iTunes button
and it's automatically going to subscribe
that channel into your iTunes.
So everything that comes into that channel,
and I think we've limited it currently
to three episodes per show,
will then flow automatically into the channel,
the way you named it right onto your iPod,
if you hook it up.
And of course, you could do the same for any other device
that understands RSS, which is kind of the beauty of it.
And so Tiva will be able to do that,
and your skybox in the UK, and maybe some other offerings
that include stuff you hook up to your television.
So that is indeed exactly the way we designed it.
So go into the download function.
You can see that you can get even the RSS XML,
if you want from the channel,
or as I said, you couldn't select iTunes
and just select it in boom it automatically,
open up iTunes and subscribe your entire channel in there.
So if you want to add another show to whatever it is
for whatever reason, so let's say I have my walking the dog channel,
yeah right, I could add another show to that,
and when a new episode is available,
it'll automatically show up.
And of course, because I've subscribed to that in iTunes,
I'll be able to listen to it while I'm walking the dog,
which is, let's just do it,
but example, because I just don't walk the dog.
See what else you got here about here.
I'm already going to skip the whole RSS process
and be able to download it straight through.
So that's, yeah, but the one thing is,
pod shows, website doesn't look very nice
on my palm web browser, it's called the laser,
and there's not much else out there for palm otherwise.
So maybe some, what is it, PHP, magic, that'll make.
Magic, that'll make.
Yeah, okay, I got it.
Yeah, well, so that's, I think we should make some of the channel,
functionality available for mobile,
so you can shuffle stuff around, but until these browsers
get much better, and the speed gets much better,
and they certainly don't understand how to interpret the Ajax
we use on the page.
Really, you control everything from the web browser,
and when you're mobile, you should just be able to get the shows
you want, because you're subscribed to them
in your mobile channel.
Hey, if you're listening to us on Stars 102 on Serious
Satellite Radio, go to podshow.com, check it out.
I think it'll be amazed that what else can be done
with these things called podcast,
besides just putting them back to back on Serious 102,
which we do every day, and PCH is next.
Okay, I've one more thing about podshow plus,
but first of promo for a new show,
a guy who, unfortunately, we've only been able to work
with him on Serious Satellite Radio,
because the Frank Truth podcast,
which has been around for a long time,
I love to bits, Brian knows does this show,
and of course, it's not pod safe,
but now he's got his podshow plus account up and running.
I don't know if he's using cast blaster or not,
but he's got a new show, and it is, well,
it's definitely different from the Frank Truth,
and honestly, I got it.
Hey, forget the nose, spin zone,
welcome to the nose zone, great music,
no bull, nose zone.podshow.com.
Hey, Adam, I'm Fuggler J,
what's all from the big ugly podcast,
the and I am a folder, and for fuck's sake,
we're not gonna get into the details.
How do you get people to talk about this stuff?
I promise you, we're gonna talk about some other shit.
That's coming up, stay tuned, you put mysters.
Anyways, I just wanted to say that looking forward
to checking out podshow plus and hopefully migrating
my show over to podshow servers here in the near future,
just a couple of questions concerning that.
First of all, I'm wondering how the free hosting
is going to be affecting podshow handing out contracts
what the new plan is on that front.
Hey, good question, I like it.
Well, we're gonna have all kinds of promotions
and things that people on the podshow plus
can participate in.
If you create a show, if you've migrated your show
over to the podcast, the literary network,
we're gonna be reaching out to you.
You better believe it, we're going to have,
as I said, registered listener drives,
so you'll actually be compensated
for each registered listener you bring into your show.
And I do kind of like that, by the way,
you can see who's listening to the show.
Of course, it doesn't represent the entire audience,
certainly not for existing shows,
but for people who are listening to the show via podshow plus,
it's right there, you can see their faces
and click on them and talk to them
and they can interact back.
And also, we're always looking around the network
for what's going on.
So that's literally how we're going to bring people
into the family.
The podcasters who on the podcast,
literary network now participate in a number of different
promotions and ways to make money
and to promote products and ideas and services,
and including our own network and shows on the network.
There's a whole bunch of incentive programs
that we have running and now we have the site running.
Now we're going to roll out all the stuff.
We've been having in our heads for years now.
We can really blow this out and make this huge.
So that's how that's going to work.
This is kind of just, we don't see a huge amount of money
in add-insertions.
It's low-hanging fruit, literally,
and the volume of podcasts being consumed
does really does not constitute the scale necessary
for an add-sense type model where you're inserting Google
add-sense into webpages based upon the context
of the webpages.
The volume is just not there and the click-throughs
are very different concept when it comes to how someone
interacts with entertainment they take on the go.
So there's a whole bunch of things there
that just really aren't that interesting.
What works for us is to market the relationship
that a producer of a podcast has with their audience.
That is very powerful.
Advertises are understanding how much value is in there
because advertisers are smart.
And they're seeing all the opportunity.
And so we're not just reinventing broadcasting, if you will,
but what is advertising?
How does that work?
How do you get your message across?
No crap, I should probably do the earthling here thing right now.
Since I'm on it, let me do that.
Here's another one of the finalists for our contest
to the challengerather at challenge.podshow.com.
Did I even load this thing up?
The hell am I doing?
I'll play it from here, hold on a second.
Let me fire this up.
Big, you made it possible for my ex-wife to find me.
She has my core, she has my dog, she has my kids,
she has my freaking frog and me.
You made it possible for my ex-wife to find me.
Reliable, high speed and introduction, or stable than your marriage.
So just one of the many ways people have been able to participate in changing advertising
and making some money on the side, if not full time, as well.
And we have a number of those examples.
So we're really trying to build an industry here.
And I think we're getting somewhere.
Really do.
Okay, let's continue with your comment.
And also, it's probably a couple of weeks in the future before anybody
have a chance to check this out.
But apparently there's a new program called Cross Over Market.
It's similar to one for Linux Elijah Run Windows applications on Mac OS 10
running Windows.
And I'm wondering if any of your listeners are planning on using
that so they can on cast blaster on their Macintosh machine.
Anyways, thanks a lot for the show.
Oh, and also, and thank you for playing sunny comes on Fridays.
Charlie, I played them a couple of weeks ago, and he's really good stuff.
Yeah, it's good stuff.
My great.
Yeah, I know a number of people who are running cast blaster and some kind of Windows
emulation on a MacBook Pro.
You know, all this stuff is going to melt together.
It'll, everything will all run everywhere.
I'm so glad we didn't put the investment into a Mac version, particularly seeing how
this is all working.
We should probably help the emulator guys out of anything, or the window and window or
wine people or whatever, you know, parallel, boot, and all that stuff.
Whatever it is, right now I'm just really still happy on my Sony Vio laptop.
For it, you know, now that I've gotten used to all the key commands, I've got
a little control H to hide stuff.
Excuse me.
That wasn't worthy of us in sale.
Painty cox occurs.
Patricia and I were talking about a language bug on the home page on Friday.
Miss miss spelling of it.
Let me just see this comes from Peter Jarros.
Hey there, this song could help you remember the difference between it's and it's
with an apostrophe credits are available in the ID three tags.
Oh, let me just mouse over there.
What is the credits?
Hey, credits don't say anything.
That's interesting.
His show was Jesus on the radio.
Jesus on the radio.com.
And of course, once you hear the song, then you immediately know how to remember.
Oh, if you wanted to be possessive, it's just IT.
Yeah, it's part of it, it's supposed to be a contraction and it's IT.
Possibly, it's got to go ahead, it's got to go ahead.
Got it, won't forget it ever again.
Hey, I have a story writer.
Just had a question about the player in Pod Show Plus.
I'm on a Windows machine.
Uh, first thing I couldn't get it to work or actually it was working on one computer
not the other and I turned out that I had to update my flash player on the one computer
and all seemed well.
But now I'm running into another issue where again, just one of the computers,
if you hide the pop-up window that the player is on, it actually stops playing.
So basically, you can't do anything when you're actually listening to the podcast, which is kind of annoying.
But again, it's only on one computer and they're both running Windows XP home.
And I believe they both have the same flash version.
So I was wondering if this is something that you've encountered or if anybody else is encountered
and what the fix is for that.
Thanks a lot and we'll talk to you later.
So this is something I've seen too and I consider this to be a serious bug.
I don't know what's going on with this and it happens intermittently on my machine.
I have, as far as I know, I haven't changed or upgraded my flash.
You know, Windows from time to time will just reboot your computer and say,
thanks for updating, which I thought I had turned off, but it maybe was a critical update.
But I even see it sometimes and this has been going on pre-pot show plus launch with the
pod save music network where if you actually cover one window with a flash player running with another window,
it'll cut out and if you just move the window over so that piece of flash is exposed,
then it starts playing again.
Even if you scroll it down or up off the view of the actual page outside of the pain view that you're
looking at, it'll also stop and this doesn't happen all the time but I do see it and I have to
agree it's 100 million thousand percent annoying and I don't know if it's something that we did
or if it's something with flash does or maybe it's something the way Firefox handles
plugins, if you know, please let me know because I'd love to stop that too, that's, and again,
it's intermittent, it doesn't happen all the time so it's completely annoying.
What were those, or those voice mail numbers again? I can't remember what was that.
The number you're looking for is 206, 65, 65, 65, 65, 7, but I'd rub that in a little bit.
Hey, you're asking for comments on DSC420 about the new patch of site and look at it,
play it around with it. I got in and I have my profile and one problem I'm having is some of the
pictures I have downloaded that we're downloaded as day pegs don't seem to be showing up. Don't know
what that's problem on my end or your end anything you can suggest there. The other thing was,
as I was trying to put my feed from my service into yours using your feed vacuum,
family instructions are a little confusing. I'm a complete rookie at this podcast thing so
coding and stuff like that. I have no idea and I very well may have any missing something really
really simple but I don't know maybe if there could be, I don't know, like a tutorial or a frequently
ask questions or something for those, you know, computer, some literate people like myself and
rookie podcasters, anyways, but have a good one and eight people. Yeah, you know, writing
help and frequently ask questions and stuff like that is hard stuff, man. That's not trivial.
So we clearly didn't do a good job for you. I think you may be missing there's a if you
there's a little arrow you can click and it'll expand help almost for every single podcaster option,
but it should be pretty self explanatory. If you're still having problems, we actually have
links at the bottom of every single page. One is listener support. So if you have a problem,
you can open up and it goes straight through to our, was it live person, mantis, whatever,
back end. So it always gets registered to take it as issued. I believe you should receive an email
after you've entered that that, you know, it's been acknowledged and a ticket has been created.
So you can track it and use that in future reference. And of course, there's also a podcaster
support link. And I think they have a lot of standard answers and they're starting to create the
FAQs, which you really can only create once you've had some FAQs. You know, yeah, we had a lot of
beta tester FAQs, but you guys are really doing that FAQs. So voice mail numbers 2016256357
and New Jersey put a plus one in front of it. If you're at your cell phone right now and you want to
enter in our UK number, it's plus four, four, two, zero, seven, six, eight, one, three, seven, five,
three. And now ladies and gentlemen, it is unbelievable. The amount of comments I have received
regarding scruncher versus folder of toilet tissue. I am, I'm amazed and yet at the same time
to smade about about the audience. What is it? Why do we want to talk about this? It's because
something that is never talked about that is always kept private. And I never stopped to think about
the difference between folders and scrunchers being a folder myself and user of other types of
accessories. And now it's just gotten to the point where I have so many different pieces of feedback
and so much audio. I'm just going to play the most recent ones for you back to back. So you could
shuttle ahead five minutes if poop grosses you out. But it's quite amazing the things that people
have to say about this. And it also concludes the discussion. Okay? Hello Adam, the manly geek here,
just calling him response to your data call about scrunchers versus folders. Well of course,
I'm a folder since I'm also a great fan of origami. And yes, you guessed it. What I import and
on the pod, sometimes I take my toilet paper and I create origami shapes from it. The favorite
things that I like to use to wipe my ass is origami cranes, frogs, and paper mache heads of Hillary
Clinton and Larry King. I love to have them kiss my ass. Anyhow, just thought I'd let you know,
probably more information than you wanted to talk about. Adam, this is Robert and Toronto from the
Whiteroom for Radio podcast. There's folder and scruncher thing on the little confused. For sure
in my house, and there's always two or three women because I'm, you know, one of these lucky guys,
although I always sleep with one the other two or the younger generation. But they're women
nonetheless. Now they always scrunch for the front. And I can see that. But I think they probably
fold for the back. I'm a folder for the back. I don't say you can scrunch into the back properly.
There's a real interesting piece on the back part and Howard Stern's private parts.
So you talk about the appropriate and proper way to wipe yourself. But I sound like he was
a fold. But I think women generally, you've got to define this now. Are they scrunching and
folding or scrunching only or folding only? Anyway, Robert Toronto, Ruth Radio, podcast, let's see
on this episode. Hey, Dan. Hey, dude. Adam, this is Dan from Wichita, Kansas. The birthplace
of the Delta Cia. We just wanted to let you know that in Kansas, we're not scrunchers or folders.
We still use corn cobs. Thanks. Hi, Adam Curry. This is Eric West with the Beats efforts
to skill at www.sf.com. Just find a way in on the rescue room situation. I would have to say
paper comes off the top, scrunched and always put the lid down. Thanks. Talk to you later.
Have a great week. Hey, Adam, do these just a few more calls from the Netherlands.
I just have a small remark on the scruncher folder issue. Like beside the fact that I'm a scruncher
myself, I always like to finish it off with at least something went. That's because I've been
tripping a lot in India. And one time I heard a guy, an Indian guy telling someone who was
sitting a tourist sitting beside him in the train and was complaining about not toilet paper
being there. He said, well, sir, we always do it. They wipe the Indian. You know, they wipe their
their asses with water and just their bare hands. And the tourist found it in disgusting idea.
We're on the Indian guy set. Well, sir, what would you do if you would have some
sheet in your face? Would you only wipe it with just a piece of paper? Thanks. Keep it up.
Hi, I'm Ms. Curry. It should be from San Jose, California. You can find my podcast at
theshubishow.com. Sorry for that shameless plug. Anyways, so I previously called in about
being a scruncher. And that was like scruncher pride. But I was in the bathroom yesterday. And I'm
like, you know what? Let's try out this folding thing. Let's just try something new. And it sure
takes a hundred thousand times longer than scrunching. But my God, it feels so much better than
scrunching. And a lot less toilet paper used, too. So 12 scrunchers out there in the world. Try
folding. It's great. Yo, Adam, Trucker Tom here. Scruncher versus folder. I'd say I'm definitely
a scruncher. I don't know if you've ever had to use too many truck stop restroom facilities.
Kind of pisses me off. A lot of them are using these giant rolls of really cheap toilet paper.
And you go to pull on it. And a lot of times it just break a term cup at off. And so you got to
carefully roll that stuff out and kind of get a big wide of it. And, you know, because otherwise,
if you don't have a big wide of it, something's going to slip through. Probably we don't want to go
there. I do love another question regarding people using public restroom facilities. How many of
you people out there? And how many of you some states require the, you know, you have the
little thing that you line the seat with. They've got it up on the wall. You just just got the
little dispenser and you just pull a thing down and you put that down on the toilet seat.
But a lot of states, the majority of states don't require those. And so how many people
line the toilet seat with toilet paper? How common is that? I personally think it's pretty common.
I do that myself because I don't want to just sit on public toilet. And, of course, that's, you
know, since I'm out here on the road all the time, that's really my only choice. So how many people
are lining the public toilet seats with the toilet paper? You can catch me at
truckartom.podshow.com and now also truckartompodcast.com. Catch you later.
Hello Adam and Patricia. This is Jared Nadeog from St. Louis, Missouri. I do not have a podcast,
but I simply love listening to the Charlie. Your podcast, as well as several others,
helped me make it through my 12-hour shift at work. I was just listening to DSC 421 and I wanted to say
that I am a folder. I wanted to leave a comment about the toilet seat, whether or not the toilet
seat should be up or down. I grew up where the toilet seat as well as the lid is always kept down
when not used. I just can't stand walking into a bathroom and seeing the lid up.
So anyway, keep up the good work on such a great show. Take care.
Hi Adam and hello Patricia. My name is Dana aka Wanker Girl and I'm sending out a big
hello from Newfoundland Canada. This is my first time sending you a comment. So please be kind to
me. Anyway, in show 421, Patricia said that talking about poo was a guy thing and I just wanted
to say that I completely disagree. My absolute favorite topic of conversation is poop.
I'd last tell my check. Yeah, I'm a girl. Any conversation about poo is fantastic because it
always gets people laughing. There is nothing funnier than exchanging stories about really stinky
poo's or massive sized poo's. Weirdly colored poo's or my favorite accidentally pooping in your
pants. So there you have it. Girls like poop too. Anyway, I'll shut up now, but first I got to insert my
shameless plug. I have a listen to me at my podcast Blurm at Blurmcast.com. Oh and by the way Adam,
I'm a scruncher. Scruncher. There you go. The topic of poop is now officially closed,
the scruncher or folder conversation. Do you because I just like to move on to something else?
Please, and what's so funny, you can see how it goes in waves. It takes about three or four days.
I can really even a week sometimes after I do a show before the comments really come rolling in.
I still got to get used to that because a lot of it is immediate because people are listening
immediately and then a lot of people catch up later on weekends or just or behind or listen
on different schedule, which is fine, of course. But then all the comments come much later.
It becomes an administrative nightmare. I'm telling you. But thank you very much.
It was such wonderful insight. It really is. It's so good to know my audience. I love you.
Every single one of you poopers.
Yo, let's up Adam. This jersey tied the official musical just of the Cha Cha.
And every once in a while I went a big case and I sent the client off the Jake the jeweler in the
city or go tell him to hang out at Tiffany's. And I was thinking, hey, as a podcaster, what can
I do to add a little blink to my podcast the jersey taught show? Well that's easy. Jeff Smith,
check this out.
What do you say?
You might even live in this case, jersey side. Yeah, yeah. It was jersey side.
Oh, jersey side. Show up now. It's jersey side.
Oh, yeah. I know it's just a touch.
So it's pretty obvious what my pick of the week is going to be. It's Jeff Smith.
And I know you've heard a lot of Jeff Smith on the Pontiff music network, but I don't know if
you've heard this song. This song just came up about a week or so ago. And it's amazing. It's
called Save Me. And it's typical Jeff Smith. It sticks in your head and makes you feel good. So
from the Pontiff music network, this is Save Me. Oh, and check out the fun little ending. You're going to love it.
Yeah. I know it's not right. I can't keep this up every night. I know. I'm wrong.
I admit it. It's so go and knock my ego down. Save me from myself. I could be somebody else.
Maybe just like you now too. If I could just calm down and be more sweet. Do I talk too much
of down myself? Oh, yeah. Enough about you. Just let me steal the spotlight now. Oh, no.
Save me from myself. I shouldn't be somebody else. Maybe just like you now too.
If I could just calm down and be myself. It's that all right. I'm only begging you to help me out.
Yeah.
I don't spend the best I can to be a more considerate selfless man oh yeah
I've heard it before, but I'm trying harder than ever before
Draw me, save me from myself I could be somebody else maybe just like you
If I could just come down and beat, save me from myself
I should be somebody else just like you, if I could just come down to me
Somebody else's name, somebody else's name, I need somebody else's name
I use somebody else's name, I need somebody else's name, I need somebody else's name
Oh man, just myth kicks ass
G-E-O-F-A. Thegefsmith.com
Jersey Tots. You want it up for me, man?
I can lawyer when you want him, you can never get him, you know?
Start the Jersey Tots.
We're just as late as we are.
Chef Smith on the POD save music network.
I love that song. I hope you get the play on the daily source code.
Hey, how have a good week everybody. This has been Jersey Tots and I'll catch you on the flip side.
Thank you very much, Jersey Tots. I did that yesterday. Well, flying because I was going over big and hill so often.
I've crossed it four times in one day.
And and there was a very nice female voice
on the at the control tower and so on my third trip going to pick Patricia up I said I'll catch on the flip side
I came back with like
Wilco November 277 dealt this y'all
Delta Sierra
My okay, okay, not quite getting the yank humor yet
Everybody thanks for listening to this long show full of pod show plus another ship
Literally and tomorrow I'll be traveling
Off to San Francisco so there will be no show Wednesday morning. I'll be back with you
If you're looking for more shows go over to atom.podshow.com
Check out my shows ID eggs shows I like
Those men be some things you like to listen to so until then take care everybody. Yeah, I got a new lighter and
See on the flip side another pod show podcast stick it in your ear
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance pod cast a
Leverie network from podshow and line-light networks. I love it