Delta Sierra Charlie 346
$16 million worth of airplane strapped my ass
Then the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into the future
You've seen the video!
Somebody told me you're a San Francisco
They said you're working in a box and you become
Somebody told me that you're not on top of the world
You probably walkin down the street with your earbuds
Jam so deep in your ear, yeah you're going down
You probably found this little MP3 for free
We've been playing this, but not on the radio made this
Just so I could let it go, there's anyone around here
Still have a radio, and he won't hear at all
Anyone here at all
You should go and see him out in a cool bird scene
It's way cooler out there, yeah I think so
But maybe you just like it in your cozy little world
You can play this, but not on the radio made this
Just so I could let it go, there's anyone around here
Still have a radio, and he won't hear at all
Anyone here at all
Maybe I'm just good to what you say
Maybe I'm from my hell, maybe I just like it if you
Turn it off now, turn it off now
Don't forget about us, I'm real in West Virginia
We can make it on our own, and we'll do it just fine
I can't afford here at good, but it's outside
We can play this, but not on the radio made this
But not on the radio, hey now, switch off your radio
But on the radio, we can play this, but not on the radio made this
Just so I could let it go, there's anyone around here
Still have a radio, anyone here at all
Anyone here at all
Jeff Smith, changing the music business before your very eyes
Not on the radio, perfect Friday song, you saw the
Stupid mixer, you saw the video, yesterday on the very first
Victor Mike Charlie, the video music cast, which I did
Had a lot of fun doing that, it's been a while since I've
Messed around with video editing programs, last time was during our
Reality show, so I'm used to looking at different things, mainly high
Quality, and of course when we're looking at smaller screens
That's a little less critical, learn an incredible amount
First of all, man, just to put together a seven minute video
Two hours, everything all combined, that's a lot of work
It's more work than a podcast
I used I'm movie, of course I love the Mac for video editing
It does very well, audio editing as well
Still using cast blaster as my playout system for recording the show
Lots of feedback, first of all, it seems like it struck a chord with just about everybody
I think that Jeff and his family did such an incredible job on that video
And the song, it's just, it's a hit, you know, here's a guy who doesn't have a record
He has a record coming out, you know, which will be a collection of just, he has tons of songs in the
Podsave music network, he's the guy behind the Metro sexual moment
Which we'll hear later today, Trinity, Roger Smalls, and even sent me a little surprise
Which I'll share with you in just a bit
This is great, you know, I was listening to that whole music conference that I pointed out on
Curry.com yesterday and I'm going to just have to do a whole separate show about it
I want to have a couple of artists, so I maybe just do our own little round table and have a conversation about this stuff
Because I heard so many things that I agreed with and so many things
I strongly disagree with and there were some things that were just completely overlooked
The number one interesting point I thought of that entire discussion is the podcast hotel
Which I'm sorry, I couldn't be at it. It sounds like it was going to be great
I think they're coming to San Francisco soon, so I hope to make that one
You know, everyone kind of glossed over the PROs, you know, the performing rights organizations like ASCAP BMI
And that's really where the the problem for podcasters start and there was so little conversation about that
There was a lot of intertwined conversation about
Royalties about mechanical rights about distribution about sales and somewhere interwoven with that is also the performing rights
Organizations who want to charge money, so it was just it was a good conversation, but man, I wish I'd been there
My bad, I just couldn't make it. Okay, so back to the video for a second
Besides all these great comments from everybody
There were some some negative comments and which was to be expected. I'm a glad I got them
And it was really surrounding the choice of format. I basically just, you know, took eye movie and you know, there's an expert export option and there was iPod
So I just selected iPod of course
Who is it Chris Taylor was one of the many people to point out that you know, this is H264
Codec and it's only slightly more useless than windows media video
And he makes several suggestions
Let's see the suggestions he says that will work on as many devices as possible is either divix
I have to beg to differ on the divix because that won't play out of the box on a quick time player
Exivid MP1 MP2
Or if you want direct iPod support MP4, so not the M4 V I guess. Okay, so on the next
Victor Mike Charlie L. I'll make sure I do a better job of choosing the format
I totally agree with that by the way and there's lots to discuss about
About digital rights management, but really about formats and and lock-in
Gosh, I never thought we'd have to have this conversation, but it is definitely coming
We have to be very very careful and support MP3 to the max as much as we can and continue to support it
And be very well we'll get to that later on. This got there so much. This is going to be a long show
Probably already seen in your in your podcast catcher or iTunes whatever you're using or maybe just in a quick time player or real real player
I mean this this thing will play and everything right you probably seem to long show, but it's jam pack of excellent feedback
Two pieces about the flicker trial
Again for people who are following this March 9th which is next what Wednesday Thursday
Is when we get the judgment and we find out how we did again two pieces to this case one is
The theft of my pictures from flicker which we're listed as non commercial use only in the creative comments on the flicker site
They said that they they said that the line you know this picture is public meant to them that they could use it and publish it for profit
And the other one is endangerment of my child
So two pieces of feedback on that now
And then can you tell us your one time listening to the first time listening to your feedback
I've been listening with a lot of interest to the upcoming trial or loss of their
You've filed with this tabloid that's misused or ripped off your flicker images
And it occurred to me when you're talking the other day about how they had used the word public as their excuse for it
But you didn't mention anything regarding the virus terms service
So we're not there had a look at their site and or super purchased by Yahoo this is no Yahoo services service
There's actually some notes up there if you have a look regarding copywriting or contacting the copyright agent if any misuse of materials is occurring on their site
Or I think from their site as well
So perhaps a nice kind of season the sister from them or something at least backing up that word public
Can't be interpreted in that way from you know a big mega corporation
Anyway, hope that helps. Good luck with their lawsuit love your show
You can check out my blog at www.gamebasekey.com
Dude don't record those in the while you're washing doing your laundry. Okay. It doesn't help the sound quality
Okay, so I'm pretty sure that will win the you know, but that will will be ruled in our favor about the the theft of the pictures the question of courses
You know, so what are the damages and we went through this on previous Charlie's we talked about what those damages could be
What we actually submitted is what we have to find out how much money they made first to determine how much of that extra profit that they made off of our pictures we want to take
And we want to be on 110,000 euros as an advance on those damages
But of course, you have to quantify and that well we went through that whole discussion of what is a picture worth according to the magazine a picture published on the internet is worth nothing
So if let's say the judge rules against me against us
In that particular instance, well, then of course, I'm going to take it as far as I can go because that is very important for the internet in general and for the millions of flicker users
And we know the guys at Yahoo, so I'm sure that won't be a problem to to get into the right places there and have them make a statement about it
So we'll just have to see
It never ceases to amaze me what kind of people listen to this show. I love it. I really do all kinds of ages, all kinds of vocations
And when you get into legal matters, you know it, even I have lawyers listening
Hello, do you have a lawyer here?
Hey Adam, this is Todd from the Jersey Todd show.
As you know, I've been a fan of the trolley for a long time and I've been extremely interested in listening to you talk about your court case
As a practicing trial lawyer, I actually think it's kind of fun to hear what your perception of what happened at your recent hearing
You see, there are a lot of times when I listen to other podcasts and I feel like I'm completely on the outside
I'm not a radio or entertainment guy, my show doesn't have crazy production
I know nothing about computers to be as real
And you know, I really don't know anybody in the entertainment industry to name drop
However, when you start talking about trial law, well now you're in my dog pound
Uh-huh, first let me say I know nothing about the Dutch legal system or its legal community
I did spend a fun night at the Bulldog and Amsterdam before law school
But more on point, I'm pretty amazed on how fast your claim had gotten to a hearing
In the US something like this would have really taken years before there's any kind of substantive decision
So if everyone had already agreed to the facts, I actually think that it's pretty cool that it moved along like it did
Well, let me just address that for a second first of all, dude
Next time you go to the Bulldog call me, I'll make sure you get something from the special menu
Um, second
Uh, so the main differences with the Dutch court and please really think about this
We have no jury system, there's no jury to address
Only professional judges and when they run out of judges because the courts are busy which happens all the time
Then they revert to back up judges who are lawyers who work at commercial law firms
So I think that's a difficult system to comprehend coming from
Coming from the US and of course the UK has a similar system to the US
Um, we requested a special procedure called the Court Hadding which means a short procedure
Brilliant and you can do that in certain instances and the reason we saw this procedure and the reason it was granted to us was because
There was endangerment to our child the magazine doesn't just stay on the rack
You know, just it isn't available only for that week, you know, it winds up in something
In Holland, they have something very interesting. It's called the lace mappa
And essentially for a reduced fee you can buy a bundle you can rent a bundle of magazines
Which are second hand and so a week after all magazines are published they get they get bought up by these
Uh, by these distributors who distribute these collections of magazines
And so you'll pay maybe, you know, let's just say 10 bucks a month or whatever and every week
You'll get your package of magazines and then at the end of the month or the end of the week
You put them back in their folder and the guy picks it up gives you the new one
And that one gets passed on to the next family who's going to read that for a price of maybe six euros
And it goes on so down the line until the magazine is pretty much been spent after eight to ten weeks
And then it winds up in the
In the barber shop in the hair salon
Which was funny because the judge actually said that she believed that these magazines didn't show up in her hair salon
And my lawyer is one of my lawyers bald
So I said well, you know, I think we should stop about here because we're way unbalanced on this side of the table
Anyway
So
Because there was endangerment of the child
And we requested a recall of these magazines to get them out of these collections
They gave us, you know, this court time in a short time frame
Which still was more than, you know, almost three weeks from when we started to file all this stuff now
Just going back to the previous comment, of course we sent a cease and desist and demand letter before we took him to court
But that's when those guys came back and said, oh well, yeah, maybe we did take your pictures
Well, here's 1500 bucks, you know, you should just take that and be happy and shut up
Okay, let's move on
In the US, I guess we call a motion for summary judgment where there are no material facts and dispute
And it's just a question of law
In that situation a judge can decide the matter on a motion from either party
And that motion would be dispositive of the whole case
However, I think that there are some things that are universal to trial law
Regardless of if it happens in Dutch court or in the US court
And there are some universal things to having a client and being a lawyer
So Adam, as a former law clerk to a superior court judge, a former deputy attorney general
And a current ambulance, Chaser carrying all of the 300 active litigation files
Would you care to join me on a tour behind the scenes?
Take me there, buddy
First, the judge could care less whether or not you had your green contacts in, your blue contacts in
Or whether or not your hair was nice
The judge has seen a lot worse and a lot better than you
Oh, I totally disagree, first of all, I revert back to the fact that these are professional judges
So you always want to be at your best
I think by the way, the fact that the defendant, the editor in chief Mark von The Linde
Who said he couldn't come because he fell down in less skiing and hurt his knee
And of course, the same night he was on television, via phone
It was not in person but via phone
Even saying that, oh, my knee is much better
And the curries are horrible parents and all kinds of nasty things
That does not bode well
I know I've been through these procedures before where
The defendant did not show up and the judge's a little, he said, well, he doesn't seem to think it's important
It does matter, it really, really, really does matter in the Dutch court certainly with celebrity
It matters because people are influenced, you know, this judge knows who I am
She knows who my wife is, she has preconceived notions
And I have to, you know, she may think, I'm an ambulance chair
So dude, then I'm just trying, you know, I had to say things like, hey, in the 20 years we've been married
And we've been together and in the public eye we've never sued a gossip magazine for anything
That she does not know
So I disagree and I think that it does make a difference and being respectful and
Both to the court, to the judge and to the process I think is really important
And with that comes dress code
There's a reason why lawyers have to wear this, you know, in Holland, the lawyers have, they don't have to wear the wigs like they do in the UK
But they wear a black dress with a, you know, white little thingy mobabi
So there's dress code, you know, so with that comes blue contact lenses
In fact, I always remind clients about their non-verbal communication with the court
The judge saw everything that went on from the moment you and your adversary walked in the door
So unless your name is Anna Nicole Smith, it really didn't matter how you look
Well, dude, the judge was female, okay, so I think Anna Nicole Smith would not have been advantages
But she was female, somewhere between my age and Patricia's age
And I think it does make a matter, it matters difference, make it whatever
Dude, I think the judge asked you a fair question when she asked what exactly is the remedy here
Remember, criminal courts are set up to punish, where civil courts are set up to make an injured party whole
As I've said on my podcast and and basically to anybody that will listen
The R I double A has been pulling a fast one on everyone
Yeah, the damages that they are seeking in cases where they're seeking like 150 large
It's ridiculous because they've already set the market price of 99 cents per song
This is exactly what I told the judge and and this it came at exactly the right moment
Where she was taking a fence while taking a fence, she was questioning my use of words like theft and and you know
A huge disservice to intellectual property at large
You know I said hey man, it's the same words that the R I A a uses and what is their song worth 99 cents
So what's my picture worth?
Okay, let's see what else you have to say about that so in those cases if somebody were to swipe a song or even a hundred songs
The basis for damages should only be 99 cents
Now I'm not saying if that somebody was a distributor of of you know unlicensed music and they're you know putting up their own network and distributing it to a lot of people
Yeah, I think those people should be punished and I think that punitive damages would be appropriate
But to the average person who swipes a song the value of a song is 99 cents
But that's that's a discussion for another day
Okay, I mean other one of these things these five minute comments another day
Sure, what amount of money will make you feel better about what happened in the situation?
All the court ultimately has jurisdiction over
Is maybe the judge can have them write a retraction maybe an apology and the judge will ultimately award you money
But as far as the judge ordering someone to be fired or amagging to be put at it
Hold on a second. I never asked that the court to fire him when these guys offered me 1500 euros
I said you know what he is my counter offer my counter offer is I didn't say fire him I said
You know dismiss him from his function as chief editor and that'll send a strong message to the other chief editors
That they just have to watch their peas and cubes. I didn't say fire him. That was my counter offer. They should have taken it because now I'm going to crush them like a little bug
Or even for them to provide you free cases of sensial for the rest of your life and ain't gonna happen
So you may have put so much pressure on the magazine internally that they may have to choose to fire someone that was involved with this situation
But certainly what this is accomplished is that they're gonna get a lump of coal in their stocking the next time their Christmas bonus comes around
Yeah, that is actually true. I know that for a fact and that is one of the main motivators is I know that the publisher outducks owned by a reformed family in the Netherlands who clearly support non-family values have no morals
I know that they sent when they hired this guy they said and whatever you do no lawsuits
So that's why this guy is all freaked out is because I'm attacking him personally
I'm putting their magazine in the shady light that it belongs currently they can change
So they probably will get a lump of coal, but again, and I extend this offer
And I know they listen because they have transcripts of this show transcripts of the show calling me a drug user
Okay, so they said some things that were true
Transcripts of the show they listen to it again
We can drop the whole thing if you say that you were wrong and you are removing this guy from his position as editor and chief
That's it then we're all done then and and I will start out to drop everything. It's that simple it is that simple and believe me
Just like you guys, I have enough money to continue the fight
Particularly because it's personal as well
Third, here's the one that's going to blow you away
Generally, I think the judge knew exactly what direction she was going to go in before you or any of the lawyers walked into the court
I spent an entire year researching and writing decisions for a brilliant judge here in New Jersey
And most of the time he would push me to find research to back up what he was thinking
And we would just go out and on the bench to confirm everything
Sometimes I knew exactly the way he would rule and write it up the right way before he even told me to
Look my boss is a former newer cop that became a judge
If I goofed it up he'd have me doing pushups in the hallway
But my point is at him that the judge knew exactly what way she wanted to go and really was just looking for justification
When I go up to the belt of vision or I have to do with a panel of judges
I generally can tell whether or not I'm screwed
So this really brings me to my last point. Wait before you get there. Okay
I agree with you
I think this judge did have a preconceived notion as to what the suit about and how it was going to work and how it was going to fit together
And I think that I was prepared for that and then I almost automatically gravitated towards explaining what this was really about
And why I was here and why I was taking my time away from my family, from my job, from my colleagues, from my art, from my fun
From my country
And I think that that was you know, that's when I got to the tipping point and hopefully I was able to convince her that this was about something else
Then she came in with so I do agree with you there
But I'm very happy that she appeared open-minded and really opened up to what I was trying to communicate
And there comes a point in every lawyer's career where they've reached that old crap moment
Over the years I've represented many, many clients that have chosen to use my voice in my time in a way that makes me absolutely no sense to me
And absolutely has no basis in reality
I still got a couple of files like that
I mean, I've had files so bad that they bark when I walk into court
And I think the position that the lawyers are in for the magazine are really in that old crap moment
Yeah, no, I agree with you there on the old crap moment
This guy was totally befuddled and flustered, didn't know how the internet worked
The magazine doesn't know how the internet works
And if you're listening to this podcast on serious stars 103, I invite you to come back to Monday for more source code or go to dailysourceco.com to download the rest of this great conversation
Okay, they're gone, let's continue
There are attorneys certainly sound like they are and I kind of feel bad for them
They've been putting that position like a train seal and now we're just trying to bark like a lawyer
I mean, I'm not into making predictions or anything, but it sounds like the hearing itself went well
I guess it really depends on what remedies are available to the judge if she were to find your way, which it sounds like she's going to
Now, it certainly sounds like she has all the ammunition she needs and it'll be fun to see what she does
Now, I can't send you a bill for this point two of billable time
However, considering how cheap my rates are, let's just say we can settle up in one special DSC way
A promo
Hold on a second, my brother
Your promo as I see here is going to last 26 seconds
I'm sorry, you clearly have my rates confused with your rates
Uh-uh, Jersey Todd
Um, you owe me another three comments at least
That's right, come on, you Charlie heads
When you're done listening to the chat chat, come on over to the Jersey Todd Show at www.jutotshow.com
And check out my show where I play some of the best unheard podsafe music and go off on some pretty good rants myself
I don't add them since I'm not a pilot, I can't say tailwinds, but I have never get into boat once or twice around Jersey
So all I can say is keep you right on the right returning
And well, now back to your regularly scheduled Charlie
Thanks buddy, the chat chat, okay, so I'll I'll take off one audio comment
You'll only only two more fantastic really appreciate the feedback dude
It's good to it's funny how that works isn't it how you send in this audio comment
And I can actually have the conversation with you, I don't know
Somehow it just works
Yesterday I had quite a rant about the EFF
Talking about John Perry Barlow and Cory Doctro
And I guess the Charlie's reaching far and wide now
Because on previous things like the podsafe music network terms he didn't hear
But now people are passing stuff on to him and that's cool
So the reach is spreading out like an ugly ass oil stain
And Cory fired me back in email
And I asked him if he would put it into an audio comment which he did and I really appreciate it
Let's listen to his feedback which is very interesting
On the inside workings of the electronic frontier foundation
Hi Adam, it's Cory Doctro
Someone just forwarded me a piece from one of your recent podcasts
And you were talking about what EFF doesn't do
I don't work for EFF anymore, I haven't since the New Year
But I thought I would clarify a little what it is EFF doesn't do
Just from an inside perspective
I understand I'm not really speaking for EFF here
I don't work for them anymore
But I do think I have a pretty good sense of some of the process that goes into choosing cases
EFF's got a bunch of different briefs
It's got a lobbying side, it's got an activist in campaigning side
And it's got a legal side
The legal side gets a lot of requests for legal help
But it only takes on a small number of those
It's because EFF's legal strategy is impact litigation
That means taking on court cases that set or break precedence in the US legal system
So that means EFF doesn't defend individuals
whose cases aren't going to set a binding precedent by and large
I think they're probably been exceptions
But EFF isn't a legal defense clinic
It has a list of cooperating attorneys
These are attorneys who sue or defend people on a low-cost or pro-bono basis
And the legal intake staff at EFF circulates cases that EFF can't take to those people
Sometimes EFF helps out with those people as well
Giving them expert advice and amicus briefs and so on
EFF is an impact litigation organization
Which means that it chooses the cases that turn its members donations
Into the largest impact on the laws that will govern the internet as possible
There really aren't enough donations in the world to defend every individual who gets bone by the system
But if you pick the right case, you can win precedence that affect millions of individuals
For example, when EFF won the Bernstein case and legalized crypto
It was nice to have defended Dan Bernstein
He was a mathematician who was getting a shot from the feds
But the important outcome wasn't that Dan got to publish
It was everyone's right to use crypto that came as a result of this
That's enabled every commerce transactions taking place on the web since
Not to mention all the Chinese dissidents and others who benefited from access to privacy technology
Okay, hold on one second. I just got a jump in here
So, understood
And I know a little bit more about the EFF
So here's what appears to me
First of all, the curry versus MTV networks lawsuit is pointed to
In the legal community as jurisprudence
It was the first
That I'm aware of the first large-scale domain name dispute
And I think even reference by EFF as a case that provides jurisprudence
So I think and this is really my feeling about the EFF
It's not about anyone personally but just the EFF and it's an organization
And often any type of organization that defends you or helps you
There's always going to be people who fall on the edges
I feel that I do fall on the edge
So the review process of what can be jurisprudence
I don't see how a lawsuit between MTV networks and an individual
Over domain name
Which involves a brand and a trademark and you know possible
Random act complications or references
Maybe I'm not a lawyer
You know I can't see how that is not a
A case that would be interesting to the EFF
What I think instead happened was they said oh it's the MTV guy
It's MTV and it's some dispute something else
And I didn't look into it and wouldn't listen to the story
Now granted when I met John Perry Barlow and discussed this
You're both pretty stunned so maybe I didn't communicate very well
I certainly didn't send off any letter to anyone
I just thought he would be able to communicate
He seemed to understand at the time but of course we were understanding lots of stuff at the time
So I think there is kind of a double standard
It seems like EFF always wants to come up for the little guy
As long as he's a scientist, a mathematician, a student
Someone who has no apparent financial means to bring a suit themselves
And I think that's an overestimation of what celebrities might be able to afford
Or people who, yeah the celebrities in general
When you see someone who's certainly in the 90's still
If you had to take celebrities and we know that celebrities can be total losers from some reality show
Maybe I am just a total loser for some reality show
I think there is a double standard there and that people are judged
Not by what the importance of their case
But often just by appearances
It's a very human thing but I think the review process of which cases are taken on
Should be looked at. Let's just continue because Corey has some more
And by the way this is I love this
And Corey wanted everyone to know up front that he has some kind of weird thing with his microphone
He's aware of it and we couldn't get it fixed
It doesn't bother me so let's listen to some more of Corey Doctoro
I don't really know the specifics of either the MTV case
Or the current case you've got involving your flicker photo
And I'm not a lawyer so I can't really comment on the moment
In any depth.
Hold on. I don't think that you're looking Corey
I think you should know this
Isn't this the kind of stuff you write about?
Isn't that what you do on boy and boy?
Yeah we get all the funny stories
Isn't this an important one as well?
Yeah a magazine taking pictures off of flicker
Even though they have the creative comments license which you advocate so much
This is important you should know about this stuff
You know this I think is exactly the stuff that you should be involved
And whether you have anything to do with the EFF or not
Or some insight into the calculus that goes into EFF choosing the case
And the right thing to do there isn't to look at whether or not EFF is on your side
But whether winning for your side creates lasting overarching changes in the league
Okay so there you go. I think that winning and beating out
Violators of the creative commons license
Who are probably going to get away with just a slap on the wrist
I think could be something that would have jurisprudence
No system which is EFF's brief
Some considerations to figure out whether that's the case
Well if cases are fact intensive and likely to require a jury
EFF isn't likely to take them because juries don't make binding precedent
Well that's great because we have no juries in this case
We can check that box. There we go
Decision that a jury hands down
Doesn't necessarily get honored by the next jury or the next court
If a case hinges on areas of law that are settled
Where it's been proven out that the law's constitutional as bad as it is
It's unlikely EFF's going to take it
Because in that case the only way you can change that law is to actually get a new law passed
And EFF will likely be working with other organizations on the hill
That work to introduce new laws and overturn old ones using non litigation strategies
Okay, so in this case then obviously EFF couldn't help me because it's only for the United States
And not for any other countries. Okay got it
And finally if a case is likely to be settled out of court
Chances are EFF won't be interested in taking it because of course
If you settled not a court you don't make a precedent
Okay, and of course I have said that I would set a lot of court
But I would lovingly take that back if I had you know all the help in the world of big intelligence smart
You know organizations like EFF so I you know doesn't this is not about money
It really isn't it's about where are the boundaries for the little guy when it comes to intellectual property theft
And where are the boundaries of endangerment of a child which is not really EFF's mantra I understand that
None of this is hidden or obscure by EFF
But it is a pretty subtle point and I think a lot of people who aren't experts in this kind of activism miss it
I certainly wasn't really clear on it until I started working for the organization
None of this is because EFF doesn't want justice for individuals
EFF is an impact litigation organization and it tries to turn small donations into big wins
And that means hard by hard done by individual sometimes don't get help by the organization
But EFF's cooperating attorneys list is very large and often does find counsel for those who need it
EFF does have a commitment to justice for as many people as it can manage
But as I say the only way that it can choose how to prioritize is on which bang will be the biggest one for its litigation bucks are more importantly
The litigation bucks that people like you and me have donated to them
So I hope that clarifies things I'll just mention in closing that is Barlow is still involved with the organization has been
Since the founding as far as I know he was a founder and he's still on the board of work and a board of directors
I think he's been on a continuous lay. I'm maybe he's taken a year off here or there
Does he still have that awesome bud? He's been around for 16 years
And I'm pretty proud and pleased to call him a friend
So I hope that was helpful. Thanks a lot. Have a great day.
No, Cory, thank you very much. I really appreciate it and
Dude, official friend of the Charlie come on back anytime you want, send it an audio comment about anything
And shoot, I'll even ask Jeff Smith to make up a little jingle for you
Oh man, this is going to be a long one, but there's so much good stuff still to come
I hope you don't you know that take your finger off of that fast forward button don't do that
Podcast 4 on one this week featuring Michael Butler the rock and roll geek show a lot of ass kissing my way
But a pretty good show. Make sure you catch it.
Hey Adam, this is Mark from zero gravity radio in Kansas City, Missouri
And I proclaim this weekend to be a pod save music weekend
Matthew evil and Laura clap
We'll be performing at club in the talk on the third and the fourth of March
That's Friday and Saturday at eight o'clock
And the address to Barbara Natasha is 1911 Main Street in Kansas City, Missouri
Phone number down there if you need directions is 816-472-533
And I hope to get everybody from Kansas City to come down in support
Matthew and Laura and pod save music down at Barbara Natasha
Fill the place up and it'll be a blast and Adam
You wish you were here with us
Oh man, let me tell you if I was in San Francisco this weekend
I would have gotten on a plane to come to see this show
Just to hang out with that group of people that sounds so awesome
Laura clap might the new love of my life are you kidding me?
And then lighter flicking
Oh man, it's not that being here at the cottage is bad by the way
Patricia and I have some nasty stuff planned for this weekend
Speaking of nasty
Adam, it's Angie, long time to see
So love spirals are starting to book some shows and support of our new CD
And I was thinking how cool it would be to have a pod safe music network
Presents Love Spiral Show with say a few other payment-related bands in our style
We'd love to play in San Fran, man
And it'd be fun to do intimate performance at pod your headquarters as well
So let's chat about the possibilities
I got some intimate performance ideas at the headquarters, baby
You know what, this is a good idea, I'll get the pod pump on it
And Michael Butler
And I don't know if we can do it this month
I don't know when you're planning your dates
But let's see if we can work some out
I mean if we can find a venue and by the way, Rosie
At pod show HQ she's so tied into the San Francisco scene
She'll be able to help with ideas
And yeah, be great if we could do it, be great
And I'm sure that if we need to come up with a little budget to help support it
I'm sure we can work something out
I was gonna say something and I saved this
Patrick Bouse says, hi Adam, first of all great show
I'm listening to it now for a year, 11 every minute of it
As a San Seo customer, yeah, this is a Blumenal Adverts work
I'm registered to the San Seo newsletter
And today I got one which is pretty interesting
Pickwick comes out now with a tea pad for the San Seo machine
Because you like the San Seo
And you like to drink tea, I thought this was worth a mention
PickwickT.com, the tea pads
Sounds kind of nasty, doesn't sounds like a sanitary nap
Can talk about marketing
Okay, thanks buddy, really appreciate it
Let me just put that up there
So we know that I talked about that there in the show notes
I wonder though, you know, if you have the coffee comes out
I mean, wouldn't the tea water, the actual tea mixture
Come out of the same spigot as the coffee
And won't you taste that?
I mean, there's nothing worse in the world when you're in a hotel
And you order tea and they bring it up in a pot
At one point contained coffee because you can just taste it
It is horrible, I mean, I've had this at the best hotels in the world
And man, I've caused a shit about that
Usually not to hotels in former empires of the British empire
And former colonies of the British empire
A couple more pieces of Gmail feedback
Stewart Davenport Adam, just like the comment on the pot's
If music network re-download function, great idea
Keeping my download history, giving me the ability to get that file again
Without repaying is brilliant and truly a community safe feature
Whereas ample has done a half-hearted attempt
They certainly record what you've purchased
But not giving the function to re-download those tracks
Feed of charge, free of charge is appalling
I have sadly lost all my music on my Mac
And they expect me to repay 100 pounds plus in music to get my music back
Now I understand if I buy a book from a store and lose the pages in it
I can take it back to the store and ask for replacement pages
But hell man, that is data
I've paid for it surely, I should be able to download again
This is a joke
Viva la revolution Adam says Stewart Davenport, Manchester UK
Dude, thank you very much
Yeah, no, and this is very concerning
And I'm learning more people are sending me articles
About how this vives
I mean, you know what, we have to be really careful
Of these systems that have some form of sanctioned built in
Like the iPod
You know, we just have to be very aware of what's going on
Steve Jobs said, it is recent fun products announcement
That he feels that all your music belongs on your iPod
And you take your iPod from place to place
It's on your head, you stick it in your boom box
You put it in your home, high-fi
But your music belongs there, which means
You can only get it through the combination of iPod
And iTunes and there's DRM on it
Which only plays on the iTunes
So you kind of get locked in
At a certain point
You know, what happens if a law is passed
It says all musical content that has played on devices
It has to be
You know, it has to contain DRM
It could happen
We're living in really strange times right now
What if Apple says, we really don't see any value in the MP3 format
Do you really think people will defect on mouse
That's in great numbers
To other portable devices
I don't think so
Not yet
If we start to kick some ass
And get more and more people
Hooked on podcasts
And boy
In hindsight, the name really isn't all that great is it
It is confusing
That does kind of suck
I mean, of course, the iPod is also 78% of the mobile music market
Lots of things to think about here
But be very, very careful
Gabe Kangus
Adam Man, it was rough
This past show with your wife
I was on the train
I was so frustrated
I was about to get up and scream
Let Adam tell his story
She would not let you talk and it drove me up the wall
She would say
The sky is red
And you would correct her by saying no baby
The sky is blue
And she come back with yes
That's what I'm saying
Okay, it's off my chest
Gabe Ganges
I'll do it
Welcome to the nightmare that is my life
You know?
This is the way it's been for 20 years
And I wouldn't want it any other way
I really wouldn't
We're a pair, man
We are a pair
Okay
Those of you who have been reading along
With the message boards
With the comments on curry.com
There's been quite a lot of controversy lately
Concerning a commenter
Comic strip blogger
And now Comic strip blogger
Is pretty abusive in his writing
And he seems pretty emotional
And he does really kind of say it
As he feels it and calls it like he wants to call them
He's been really offended by me
Calling him stalker
And of course, you know, I consider
Roger Smalls to be stalker as well
But
I kind of turned it around on myself
And I thought, you know, how do I feel
When people call me the big-haired fag
Well, that actually I love
That's probably about example
How do I feel when
Yeah, MTV guy
Or not even a derogatory term
You know, I'd rather just be known by my name
So let me just say this
I apologize for calling you a stalker
Comic strip blogger
Roger, I don't apologize for calling
He was stalker
And I think that people really do like
To hear a contrary point of view
That it does work in comments
It really, really does
But you got to work a little bit on your social skills
I think and with this, Comic strip blogger
I would like to invite you to become a contributor
To the daily source code
By sending me your occasional comment
Don't make them too long
I have to be able to understand them
And you can't get pissed off if I don't use it
Because, you know, I don't believe me
Believe me
I do not play everything the Roger sends it
Okay
And
And I'm not the only one who clearly is thinking this way
Comic strip blogger
Because here's what the Jeff Smith did for you
Comic strip
What is the sound of 200 episodes of the financial aid podcast?
Is the sound of nine months of education financial aid
Student loans, scholarships, personal finance
And how to find a job
The sound of 11 financial aid experts and PhDs
Interviewed for their expertise
It's the sound of $497 million in scholarships, grants, and free money for college
Is the sound of over 500 pieces of positive music played on the air
And now it's the sound of a free iPodnet
It turns music stored gift cards, or Matthew will's new album, beer, and coffee
We're giving away prizes to see you now on our 200th episode
But you can only win by subscribing
Subscribe to the financial aid podcast today
www.financialaidpodcast.com
Hello Adam and listeners to the Charlie
This is Doug K from the Conversations Network and IT Conversations
And today I'm exploding with exuberance to announce the next in-person podcast academy
We've put it together with Boston University
For Friday and Saturday, April 28th and 29th 2006
We've got four half-day sessions dealing with topics that include podcasting basics
The business of podcasting and podcasting in public radio, education, the corporate world
And advanced topics such as video casting, music licensing, and interview recording techniques
We've also got a great lineup of instructors this time including Dan Brickland, Paul Figiani, Tony Khan, Michael Gohagan
Jake Shapiro, John Furrier, Steve Garfield, CC Chapman
And myself, you can get to the complete schedule and the details at podcastacademy.org
And if you register before March 15th, you'll also receive $50 off the registration fee
That means you'll get two full days of all the podcasting you can take for only $250
Those dates again are Friday and Saturday, April 28th and 29th at Boston University
And that's podcastacademy.org for more info
Thanks Adam and of course, Tailwinds
Hello Adam, this is Tokyo Dan from What's Happening and Tokyo Podcast
I'd like to thank you for playing my promos on the Charlie
But to get to the point after two things I want to ask you about
First is about the Podsafe Music Network
I noticed that it's easy for someone in Japan to buy tunes
But how about the other way around?
Will it be easy for artists in Japan to sell their tunes?
After digging around in the clicking by website
I noticed that it's mostly for North American and European countries
There's nothing about Japan
And I'm a bit concerned about this because I've convinced a few independent Japanese artists
To put their songs on the Podsafe Music Network
Well, they're happy with the international exposure they're getting
But when they are finally able to sell their songs on the Podsafe Music Network
Will they be able to get paid?
And since they're in Japan and have Japanese bank accounts and credit cards
Will they be able to receive the money that people pay for their songs
Without suffering the fees imposed on international bank transfers
I was wondering if you could shed a little light on how this is all going to work
The second thing I want to ask is, do you have any plans about expanding to Japan?
Well, I love what you and Pods you are doing
And I'd sure love to be a part of it
Perhaps something like an evangelist?
Heck, I'm already doing it
I'd be happy to go around to the local gindies artists
That's what I call the Japanese independent artists
And put the word out about the Podsafe Music Network
In the live music clubs and private recording studios over here
If you ever need someone over here, I'd appreciate it if you kept me in mind
Well, keep up the revolution, man
It's really great
Alright, my brother
To answer your first question, very good one
Now, you will not be receiving money from clicking by
God, now I don't even know that for sure
I don't believe so
No, I think you will be receiving checks
That at least the administration will be done by Pod Show
This is one of the big things that we're working on before we actually do this
Because there are other questions like, you know, when do we cut a check
For every 99 cents or is it for every 10 bucks?
You know, those kinds of questions
Unfortunately, international banking does blow massive chunks
Massive
I mean, I've transferred millions of dollars and it just it's been gone for days
Of course, I've also had it going 20 seconds
The way it should go, but you know, this all kinds of bullshit
I mean, major ass bullshit going on an international banking
So we're going to do as best as possible
But look, you know, we're not bankers
And we're not in the banking business
You know, as a part of the whole unlabeled concept
If there's a company
That can help us with
Making payments better outside of the United States
Because I agree, man, I get Amazon checks
I should put my fricking senseo back on the homepage
You know, so it gets a couple hundred bucks
And to cash them, there's an exorbitant fee
Exorbitant fee to cash that
You know, of course, means it should be an international bank that should honor this
But, you know, this is how these fuckers make money
What can I tell you?
Second one, Japan
Not actively doing anything in Japan
I'll tell you the markets that we're actively looking at
And by the way, that's not to say that if you have a great business plan
We don't want to work with you and form a partnership
Of course we do
Currently, we are actively working in the UK
In the German markets
So I'm not just saying Germany, but that includes Austria
That includes Switzerland, that includes a piece of Italy
But the German language market
There's a lot going on there
Very excited about podcasting in Germany
And we actually have a team on the ground in China
Yes, you heard me, China
And we've had this team on the ground for a couple months now
And we're making great progress
It's very interesting
Tremendous opportunity to open up
Verbal and visual communication
Which is very difficult to block and to fire wall
And to filter out
You know, to start to really encourage a China breaking out
And joining in the freaking party
And of course we're building the audience here
In the west
We're going for our 100 million listeners
In the east, we're looking at 100 million tiny screens
And believe me, it's really going to happen
I'm very excited about that market
And what's going on
In fact, I'm planning a road trip
Won't that make for a sound seeing tour
Hey everybody, it's Friday
I need some freaking cowbell, you know?
Yes, some bass will do too
Dynamite lady
On the chart
There's a way to die
Can I blow me to your side
I hold your name so clear loud
I'm the huge show of a mine
That's right
Dynamite lady
Lil Taylor
She'll get the whole party
Dynamite lady
Oh god
You
I got the tip
What did you do
We had a side
What
It's my ever
It's my world
Everybody
It's the world
The moment I was never fighting for
And now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying, I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I
I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm try to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm thinking I'm trying to catch this, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I'm trying to catch it, and now I
Uh, you know what, I'm feeling so good.
But here.
Ben, see you, Kappa.
She's a baby, thank you.
Yes, you're right.
You know what, you're on perfect, the timing is impeccable.
Because you're the dry mouth.
They have a very dry mouth.
Yeah.
You're getting front of the mic, baby.
So we can hear what you're saying.
Yeah.
So you have a very dry mouth, but that I was just about, I was just about to tell everyone
this is a double split show because I'm going over time and how it was just I was in a good
groove.
Oh, okay.
I'm going.
I'll leave you alone.
So I need, and of course, I didn't have was a cup of tea.
Yes, I drank my show, my show drink.
All righty.
Thank you, baby.
Love you, too.
Ah.
That's it.
So that's right.
It's funny this morning, just on the split, it's just thing.
Kristy, I was trying to Christina to school and a police car was coming up behind
behind us and a couple other cars.
With the sirens on, I said, oh man, they're coming to get me.
That's the split police and she kind of got freaked out.
I said, no, you kidding me, right?
No, no, tell me it's not true.
No, of course it's not true.
I said, man, you could be like on cops and I said, and I thought about it and I said,
you know what?
I don't think I've ever seen anyone on cops on the show who's been arrested because
they were stoned from marijuana at least.
I've seen that either addicted to alcohol, to crack, to cocaine, poverty is usually a
big reason, just despair, but someone who's on, who's that smoked marijuana, no, you
don't see them.
I don't think.
I could be wrong.
Let me know.
Matt's from Bristol says, Adam, I went into hospital last week for a small operation.
Nothing too serious.
Thank goodness.
And we afterwards, I had to stay in overnight and got very bored with no TV, et cetera.
So my darling girlfriend, left me here, iPod to listen to my iPod.
I had loaded it up with podcasts to listen to, including the Charlie.
So once she had gone home and the doctors were leaving me alone, I plugged myself in and
listened to one podcast after another.
After a few hours, I realized that I hadn't really thought about the pain and been having
and was really relaxed.
It was great.
I could drift off into my own little world while listening to various podcasts just
rambling on.
So when short podcasting is a great pain killer, and that makes me feel very good, Matt,
from Bristol.
That's awesome.
And you know, that's what it is, man, it's the hit of the mind.
And you know, people can tune pain out.
That's what you did without even knowing it.
That's really, really happy to hear that.
That's fantastic.
Boy, I hope you don't mind, maybe you should stop the show now and then listen to the rest
over the weekend or something, because we've got so much more to do.
I've got two more or three more comments.
I've got another podcast I've song I want to play for you and of course.
Okay, for the Metro section moment, this is the place where us guys come out hang out
together.
You can be a real man.
If you want, you're more than welcome, because we are real men.
We talk about the stuff that, okay, so we just don't feel comfortable talking about it.
Usually, right?
Not around the office, not around the locker room.
So kind of this asynchronous mode of communication, let's everyone kind of get stuff off
of their chest and share ideas and thoughts.
And it's not just us guys, the women are checking in with great regularity.
And I think we should listen up because they're telling us things that, I mean, at the end
of the day, I'll be honest, it's about getting laid, okay.
So here's Charlotte Hinton says, hey, Adam, all the way from the home of Lord of the Rings,
I listen to your cast on a regular basis and just thought it's share something with you.
The body shop to a fabulous product, it's the sesame shaving cream.
Now, I'll tell you what, this stuff is the best and it leaves your face or at least my partner's
face.
Silky soft.
You have a partner and I'll be like a boyfriend or a husband, partner, sound so official,
like you have more than one.
Maybe it's just a wishful thing.
There's also a face protector that you put on after this, which adds the redness that
you make it, which adds the redness that you make it afterwards.
Oh, but once you've used this cream, there's no going back.
No rash smells delicious as well.
Actually, combine with a mock three and there's no going back, great for your legs as well
if your female or otherwise inclined.
Oh, the way, that's all I wanted to say, Charlotte, thank you very much, dear.
Rob Stokes next up on the Gmail and by the way, I love it when you guys do these an audio
comments because, you know, it's like an audio type medium, it says Cory Greenberg, who's
in the old college buddy of mine that presenter on NBC's today show has a blog devoted
to old fashioned gentleman's shaving, escaping void.com.
Says Cory, so I did a segment on NBC's today show about the lost art of wet shaving,
how old school razors, badger hair shaving brushes, and high end English shaving creams,
not only deliver the greatest shave that you can possibly imagine, but bring back the
pleasant, gentlemanly ritual that has been missing since the blood bath of 1971 when
EDM in led a coupe to become a coup to become the ruler of Uganda and you let introduce
the first twin-blade razor.
Nunes of people all over the world watch the segment and I guess lots of guys were unhappy
where their shave's too because the viewer reaction was unlike anything I've experienced
in the years I've been appearing on the today show.
As ridiculous as it sounds, the ensuing rush on razors, brushes, creams, created a worldwide
short as of shaving goods.
Vendors reported doing a year's worth of business just a few days, overnight, funky vintage
razors, caked with hobo whiskers and soap scumb that used to go for a few bucks on eBay suddenly
began climbing to well over $100.
How cool is that?
You know, of course, I'd say that, you know, maybe the metro sexual moment had something to
do with, I don't think NBC's today show could take all the credit, but now look, you know what,
I think it's just excitement about trying something different, that seems to be what's working
for everybody and that's why we're having these conversations.
Let me see if this audio comment is loud enough, I may have to stop the music on that.
Hi Adam, this is Robin from all critters.podshow.com, I was listening to the daily source code
today and I noticed you were looking for metro sexual moment comments on which underwear
women like on men.
Well, I'll give you my vote.
I like the ones that are called boxer briefs.
They're kind of like a hybrid between the boxer underwear, but they're not as like bulky and
baggy and they're like a brief because they're hugging and fitting, but they're not as short
around the leg, they go longer down the thigh to give me that wonderful, clean look and lie
and that goes well anyway, it's really sexy.
So that's the one I find sexiest is the boxer brief.
If you don't know what they are, go look for them, they might be fairly new because I don't remember
them being around a long time ago, but who knows, maybe it's just the guys over there, I don't know.
All I can say is that I like the boxer briefs, they're long, lean and they're good looking.
Hope you get a lot of other audio comments and feedback, few metro sexual moment, keep up
the great work on the daily source code, we're totally addicted, thanks, bye.
Thank you. I always love to hear from the ladies. They know what's going on.
This seems to be a general trend, guys.
It seems to be these boxer brief things and that's what I've worn for a hundred years.
I love them, you know, I like to have something going down my leg a little bit, of course,
I've got very long legs. I just don't like when I sit down and shit rides up on me, you know,
and I'm not talking about my ass because, well, I might enjoy that part, but you know,
in my legs there, and scrunchy, no, no, no. I would rather go commando than have to wear
briefs or anything as scrunches up. Okay, let me see, I had one, I'm going to skip this one.
Okay, let's do this last audio comment. It may be too soft, so I may have to turn down the music and
see, yeah. This is Maureen. Michelle Suster from Whisper Pearls.
Well, Adam, I love your voice for one thing. Okay, really hope. You were the following.
Not boxer's and not exactly briefs. I know, the Metro sexual man wears these sort of in-between
like Rostrichy, half-boxer, I have brief things and just very sexy and soft, and
you know, they come in exciting colors, not just the white, not just the black, and not just the
black, and if a man gets an erection, they sort of move with him, not lob out of a boxer's
short, and not get sort of tight and squishy on the briefs. So that's my option. Those are like best,
and I'd be really curious to know what you wear. This is Whisper Pearls.com. Listen, baby,
I wear exactly what you like and you people, you better turn the volume down because I'm going to
apply the ending. Yeah. Oh, man. Okay, Metro sexual moment. Okay, just one more topic that I
want to get into. Hey, Adam, I wanted to send you my comments about the white listing issue.
This fucking white listing issue is piss me off. Hold on a second, let me just say what that is.
This is about sending emails. If you send emails from a company for registration purposes,
you will, if you get any great number of these, and as you'll hear in a second, even if you just
have a whole bunch of people on a CC line for a company email, you can get blacklisted.
And that means that you're trapped as spam and you aren't put through to the large providers.
Namely, the big ones would be hotmail and MSN both Microsoft properties. There's actually a company
that you have to deal with specifically to be removed or put onto the white list for those companies.
And now we know that America online is coming with their email tax. And so that's what this
white listing is about. As my day job, I teach at a local college and some of my classes are online.
And when the class starts, I email all my students to tell them about the class, how to get started,
et cetera. To start of this semester, when emailing my students from my college domain,
which is an EDU, I received six underlippable messages from a very large webmail provider.
After a little research, I discovered that I had been automatically blacklisted because I was
sending bulk messages to this webmail provider. It didn't matter that they were emails that were
expected by the webmail provider customers, i.e. my students. So I contacted this webmail provider
and it was suggested to me by them that I send individual emails to my students. They webmail
provider stated it was their policy to block all incoming bulk messages to protect their customers.
I have over 150 students each semester to make emailing students easier. I use the email program.
It's integrated into our online learning system. So all I have to do is compose the message
select the class and email it to the students. I'm not going to sort through over 100 email addresses.
Eat semester just to find the addresses for this particular webmail provider to send those
students separate messages. The good news is, I complained and complained and it looks like they
have whitelisted me. Now, I never received the confirmation email about it, but my messages
are not blocking more. And when I'm not teaching, yes, I do produce a podcast, mostly news,
and you can check it out at mostly news.net. Good flying at them. Talk to you later.
All right. Thank you very much. And I'm very happy you sent that audio comment in because
a lot of this sounds like really geeky talk. And I know that a lot of listeners to the Charlie
say, you know, I kind of tune out of skip past all the tech talk. But this affects you. Here it is.
It's affecting a college professor, you know, and he has a dot edu address. And by the way,
I'm happy that you're getting trapped in this as well because the minute they say, well,
we'll let dot edu go through, you know, then it's going to get really fucking messed up. It is.
And then, you know, that justifies a charging dot com addresses. And, you know, what's a business?
What's an individual? This is horrible. This is not the way email was intended to be. And it's
going to be the next big frontier. You know, the fees are outrageous to, you know, to be insured
that you're continuously on a white list. You know, maybe we need some kind of, uh, open source
white list is what I was thinking. You know, something that that that consumers could pressure
their ISPs into joining that should be some way that, uh, that we can verify email. And low and
behold, Sean Murphy says, you've been talking about having to pay to get your email through to the new
podshow signups. You should check out open SPF dot org. That's open SPF's share a pop of Fox
slot. Make sure your podshow domains have SPF records in the DNS. I know Gmail checks. I'm not sure
about any of the others. SPF and a nutshell is a way to designate which servers are authorized
to send mail for your domain. Um, so that's a good one. And we'll definitely, uh, look into that.
And, uh, that may be something that we want to have implemented. But I mean, this really has to be kind
of on a, oh, shit. I don't know. There's some smart people, you know, you know, a day wine is going
to come up with this idea. And then, you know, we'll all use it and then we'll all get blamed for not
giving him credit. But someone, someone has got to come up with a fantastic idea to make this work.
So that, you know, you can receive registration emails and the corporations don't have to pay,
you know, you may want to be a corporation tomorrow. You know, you may want to start a company.
And you'll, you'll see what you're going to run into with this shit. You know, this is, this is
squashing entrepreneurialism. Um, Philip Masin, Masin, I think, from, uh, where's he from? Where's he from?
Sydney. Hi, Adam email is probably the most used crappiest implemented application on the net to date.
When SMTP, that's the simple mail transfer protocol was first created. I'm sure it's for a
father's never imagined that it would be abused to the point it is now. I have an easy solution for it.
When you register your DNS name through internet, why can't internet and cooperation with someone
like very side issue a issue you a digital certificate for your server? If you receive an email
from a server without a valid digital certificate, it gets rejected. With a valid digital certificate,
you can ensure that the mail becomes the server. It says it came from. I don't believe you need
individual digital certificates for individual mailboxes, but certainly a $2 per year certificate
for a server would be the ideal solution. Okay. So here's the difference. I believe that these
companies who perform white listing and are working together with ISPs and they're doing it
under the guise of spam. This is not about spam only. Detecting spam. I think this SPF
record all that stuff that makes sense. I think that is a good anti spam message or anti spam measure
so that we know, hey, this is the server it's coming from. So if it is spam, we know exactly who
to go to because it's an authenticated email message. So that would be an easy way to at least
remove one big step in the process. So I like that and I think we should definitely go that way
and to have a very sign or to have that a part of the DNS system, I think is a very good idea.
However, what is happening, this I'm telling you this, this is the same as this is like a DRM
thing. You know, there's these big mail companies. Microsoft has a singular company
a deal with you. You can't tell me that there's not kind of some setup there. What is the
name of that place? I have to find out the name of that company. So if you want to be whitelisted
on either hot mail or MSN, there's only one company you can deal with. I mean, this is a fair trade
practice this thing as far as I'm concerned. It's really pissing me off the more I look at it.
Again, you know, Pod Show can afford to pay these fees and you know, we're in negotiations right
now to try and get the 80,000 down to some other, you know, number that we feel a little bit more
but it shouldn't have to be this way. This is not, this is a hijacking of emails, total
fucking hijacking and anybody who wants to start a company, you know, you can create a website,
you can get all kinds of, you know, you can open up an e-commerce store, you can do transactions
via PayPal, but the minute you want to communicate through the most common denominator of the
internet, namely email, they are fucking hijackers sitting there just waiting to grab your money
and it disgusts me. Hey, what happened to the wiki show notes? No one's updating it anymore.
It's, we're behind this seems to be like, no, you know, no, I think what's going on is it's
very, it's very hard to have the comments separate from the show notes. Somehow, I got to think
about that. I mean, it's very easy to hit the comments. That's where all the passion comes out,
but there's no more passion in the show notes. It's unfortunate. There's always a link to the
what I can now call the user show notes on each, on the show site, on daily source code and
query.com, but it's just not used. Okay, two more things about advertising. Oh, by the way,
before I get into that, it just seems like a real obvious thing to me, you know, there's two ways
to do it. We can fight, you know, the unjust, or we can try and route around it like we've done
with a music business, with a pod safe music movement, which goes hand in hand with pod casting.
So, you know, we could always, I could talk to the Earthling guys about this. This seems like a
perfect place for Earthling to step in and set a precedent, whether for an emailed registration
system, or, you know, at least coming up with a way to make a whitelist thing very easy between
users and who, you know, customers of Earthling and users who want to communicate with them.
They could be transcending, and I bet you that, you know, in large numbers,
consumers can show what they really, you know, they can move with their feet, right?
So I think that we'll probably have to do that one way or the other.
Yes, so there was a meeting in New York, by the way, with Earthling, because we're moving closer to
upgrading advertising. Stay tuned. Now to the comments. Oh, I'm Adam. I just finished listening
to Daily Source Code episode number three, four, one, and I had a thought about all this Earthling
advertising you've been working on. I think the problem is that traditional,
by the way, that comment about Earthling was not meant as an advertisement. I meant it as a real
comment. This is kind of coincidental. Lots are just too long with a podcast. You tend to hear
the same spot over and over. So a much shorter spot will do. There are also are not so many issues with
static changing the dial, catching in the middle. That sort of thing. If you hear the
advertisement, you tend to hear the whole thing you tend to hear clearly. So instead of a 30
second spot or a 22nd spot, why not look for something in the 5th to 10 second range? For example,
I've trimmed one Earthling ad down to about 7 and 300ths of a second, and I think it communicates
the message pretty good effectively, but it's a lot less annoying and it takes less time,
which leaves more room for either more content or more ads in the same amount of space.
Where are you, Link? Make this smart choice. Visit earthling.net and discover what our
internet experts can do for you. Right. So I agree with you when I disagree with you. First of all,
you're not going to hear me play the Earthling commercial on this Charlie because
what's the point is to talk about what that company is about and what they're doing
and to involve them in the conversation. I'm not getting paid for Earthling by seconds that I
play anything. I think that's even the three quarters of a second or whatever you cut it down
to even that's boring. These are the things that we've got to work on. Every single, was it
Paul, was it Paul Pinfield from podcast user magazine? He wrote this whole article and there's been
some back and forth in the weblogs about it about business models and he lists three models
and what no, what everyone seems to be overlooking is that advertising is currently geared
and there's a trillion dollar industry or 800 billion dollar industry. My phone is ringing. Hold on,
who's that? Oh shit, it's KJ, hold on. Let me just, ah, let me see if I can still get him. KJ.
I'm taping the show, you're on right now. Hey, yeah, I'm taping the show, you're on.
All right, no, it's like phone is frozen like the West Virginia York. So since we're on the Charlie,
how's it going in New York, man? I was just talking about Earthlink and I just mentioned
you had a meeting with him yesterday how to go. Hello? Sorry, I think you're a connection
might be a bad one. So I was just, I was just saying that you had a meeting with Earthlink
yesterday in New York. Oh, it sucks, hold on. I said that you had a meeting with Earthlink yesterday
in New York. We did it. We had an excellent meeting with the folks at Earthlink and I think things
are progressing nicely. It's a, you know, I think it's a effort that is going to be a very,
very interesting one. It's just going to be a process of planning everything out and making sure
it's executed well. They're very excited about it. We're very excited about it and I think we'll have
some interesting things to talk about fairly shortly. Dude, I got to step back for all the
enthusiasm that's just spouting out of my phone. All right, listen Chris, let me finish
a show and I'll call you later, okay? Well, thanks. All right, buddy, take care. Bye.
There you go. Straight from the horse's mouth. Oh my gosh. Chris is great. He sounds a little dry
and I kind of hijacked in there. There you go. I tell no lies. It's actually happening. It's
actually true. So with all this media changing we're doing, I know of, I'm repeating myself.
I just have to say it. Advertising will change as well. Right now, it's a, it's a clash, you know?
It's like, it hurts. Everyone understands it. Everyone gets it, including some switched on advertisers.
We're having the conversations right now. We're being very careful. We're planning because we're
putting something on the map here. We're going to change advertising. We're going to change the
value. How it's measured? It's going to be, it's, that's what that's the kind of enthusiasm that
to, that I'm talking about. One more then. Hi Adam. This is Michael Kickingbear,
what the indigenous people's music podcast. And I just checked out an interview on CNBC with
someone from EarthLink. I guess they've put a bit in to be the primary provider of a citywide
Wi-Fi network. I was wondering if you had heard any insight about that. Apparently they're also
looking at Chicago as, as a second city to be involved with this. I would think any broad rollout
of Wi-Fi and broadband internet is going to be great for podcasting. As more people can be
connected and pull down content. So I didn't know in your discussions with EarthLink recently
if they alluded to, to how that was going. But I was just kind of interested in sort of thought
about the DSC and everything that you've talked about recently. I guess the upcoming involvement
with end users, EarthLink's ad campaign process. So anyway, it's just curious about that.
Thanks again for listening. Thanks for the DSC. And again, this is Michael Kickingbear,
indigenous people's music podcast at www.native-music-podcast.com. Thanks. Dude, bye bye.
Dude, that is such an awesome name. Michael Kickingbear.
It's like to introduce you. Here's the taxi Eric Michael Kickingbear. You know,
check the leaning muel. Everybody's here. And I passed on your request at the Native American
as a genre to the podcast. Music now work absolutely. Well, you know, this is, I think we're
going to get to this. What you're hearing now is a conversation which is relevant to the listeners
and contributors, I might add, 70% of the show is made up by you, whether you're making music,
whether you're making jingles, whether you're sending an audio comments or emails. It's made up by you.
I'm just kind of mashing it up and assembling it and we're calling it a podcast. But, you know,
we're a community here. We're doing something. We're talking about Wi-Fi. We're talking about
email, blockages and guess what? Wouldn't it be awesome if we could bring Earthling into the
conversation? It'd be good for them. It'd be good for us. It'd be good for all of us as collective users.
Okay. Oh, man. I don't think I've done a podcast this long and ages. In ages, I tell you.
Okay. We're almost done. I just want to get it all out. You know, there's so much, so much.
Just get off my chest so I can have a clean empty weekend. Please indulge me. I just wanted to say
I'm really digging in the new G-talk features or G-Chat in Gmail. If you can figure out my Gmail
name, then you can add me. If you keep sending me messages, I'll block you. But, you know how it works.
I don't know. I'm willing to try it out because that's not a different application. You know,
and when I'm on email, then I'm also kind of in instantaneous chat mode that kind of makes sense to me
to have email and I am integrated that way. Also thanks to all the writers who have been sending
in emails. Yeah. We need writers in podcasting. Did you hear that rant? I just went through. It was
so, I mean, you can hear the emotion, but I don't have the right words at the right moment. Like
Mark Yoshimaru and M-Coff can do awesome rants on the Pacific Coast hell of ways. Really,
really good. And, you know, I think I could, I just have to time, you know, just don't have the time.
But if you write it, I could say it. And we work together. It would be, you know, we could make
it a combination of our words and we could communicate even better what we're trying to say.
Hey Adam, it's Seth from Radio Goon. I just wanted to point out that on the Podsafe
Music Network, a lot of record companies are putting their artists songs on the network,
but they're putting their own production company in the artist field. I find this as a podcast
or extremely irritating when I'm searching for artists and I find, you know, X records or something.
And then in the song name, they put the artist and the song. I don't know if there's
some way to enforce it, but it's pretty frustrating, just in general. Just thought I'd draw your
attention to that. Love the Daily Service Code. Thanks. Thanks, dude. You know, I think that we have
this has come up previously. There's a couple things going on. First of all, at its core,
it's probably a design fault on R&D. You know, thinking Podsafe, we just never thought that
record labels would join in. And there's tons of record labels. Even some big ones. Even some
big ones who are uploading music to the Podsafe music network. I haven't made a big deal about this
because I actually have mixed feelings about it because, you know, is it really happening,
you know, on the up and up or are they just kind of, you know, are they sliding underneath the
law and just, you know, are they doing all these things? And but on the public side, you know,
suing soccer moms. Once you try and sue a soccer girl, you boys, I'd like to see that. She could sue
you so hard and I'd back her up. She's on the network, you know. But I too have noticed that.
And Michael Butler has been instrumental at getting all these independent record labels in.
And since we don't really have a facility for it in the, uh, I guess in the database,
and also because the owners of, um, of the material that's uploaded are the record companies in,
I'd say 99% of all cases. You know, you join a record company, um, the record company pays you
and you basically give up the masters. And so, you know, upon uploading to the Podsafe music,
that work, you have to be the rightful owner and in many cases, the record companies are the owners.
So there's also kind of an ownership thing on, on, on their side. Um, so indeed, this next song,
which is from East West Records, which I think is a, that's a big one. That's a pretty big, uh,
it's, it's an indie label that is sub-label of something big. Um, this is song called Los Angeles by
patent pending, which I'm going to play for you. Um, and indeed, it's, uh, it shows up as East West
Records. You know what, I'm going to, I'm going to dive into it. Uh, it's something that will definitely
have to be put on a little bit longer term, uh, but I do agree. It's a pain, uh, but of course at the end
of the day, it's the music, the counts, right? And boy, does this kick ass? Perfect Friday song.
Getting better, gather, ladder, know that there is no time and have no one ever said forever.
Me do at the time, I'm lost. Please get me out of, got to be kidding me. There's
coming, we'll let you throw away this chance of a lifetime, you'll be so fine. Say nothing
because nothing nice to say. There's no, there's no way, people lose this meaning.
Lord, it's all in our screamer screamin' screamin' out loud. I said the said to miss a seeding out her soul.
She said, I'm tellin' like your father. She said the way, they tellin' we'll be sure we don't find.
Getting better, gather, ladder, know that there is no time and have no one ever said forever. Me do at the time,
I'm lost. Please get me out of, got to be kidding me. There's coming, we'll let you throw away this chance of a lifetime,
you'll be so fine. Say nothing because nothing nice to say. There's no way, there's
people lose this meaning. Lord, it's all in our screamer screamin' screamin' out loud.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. She said, boxed, Angela, this has never been so good.
She's died, we'll shine in it and fall on her. She said, the way, they tellin' we'll be sure we don't find.
Getting better, gather, ladder, know that there is no time and have no one ever said forever. Me do at, got to be kidding me.
Darling from coming, I know that you're falling deep down in your body's vibrations,
my fallen apart, get me out of here, get me out of here, get me out of here, get me out of here,
yeah, yeah, I know that you're falling deep down in your body, get me out of here,
I just can't stand.
I'm having fun.
Los Angeles.
Get me out of here.
Oh.
Major error camps are going on here at the college.
I heard my nerves going.
I'd shoot crashing and flying pacitudes.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Okay, that's it.
I'm ending it.
We've got to stop somewhere, hour and a half.
I hope you guys don't mind.
I just had so much pent up energy.
I'm feeling really creative, that whole music video thing.
Yesterday, just got me in a good vibe.
I love all the energy.
The wave is on an upswing.
I can feel.
I can feel it.
All right, everybody.
Have a great weekend.
DailySourceCode.com.
Check out podshow.com.
If you want to see other interesting podcasts, if you'd like to listen to them,
and of course, my email is adamaccurry.com.
I have a great one, everybody.
Oh, Friday.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.