Delta Shara Charley, 3-3-1
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass
Than the next generation radio content in my ears
We don't need no sticky drinks
I like to think I'm flying you to the future
Fantastic, it's a battle curry
Baby there's something that I like to say
I hope that my words don't get in the way
But there's something that you want to know
I can't I explain all this love that I feel
How do I prove that this heart is for real?
Now I don't just close, I don't want to let go
I can no longer hide, there's some dying inside
And I'm feeling like I'm gonna fall
This is a dream that I don't want to wake
This is a feeling I don't want to share
And I can't make it to my own
I don't want the night turning into the rain
Because I'm afraid this will fade away
That's it
That's it, that's it
And I'm lost
Sometimes I feel as though I don't deserve
The love that you give but I'm so reassured
Whenever you kiss me there in the dark
There is fire that's burning within
When I feel the passion the room starts to spin
If you leave, I am left with a smile
You are all I'll drink alone if I can't have your love
I would rather have nothing else
This is a dream that I don't want to wake
This is a feeling I don't want to share
And I can't make it to my own
I don't want the night turning into the rain
Because I'm afraid this will fade away
That's it, that's it, that's it
And I'm lost
Sometimes I feel as though I don't deserve
Stay around
I would give anything to hold you here
My own
But what I've found
Someone in a battle will be beautiful
This is a dream that I don't want to wake
This is a feeling I don't want to share
And I can't make it to my own
I don't want the night turning into the rain
Because I'm afraid this will fade away
That's it, that's it, that's it
And I can't make it to my own
I don't want the night turning into the rain
Because I'm afraid this will fade away
That's it, that's it, that's it
And I can't make it to my own
I don't want the night turning into the rain
listening, well, I always enjoy listening to digital
flotsom because it's so nicely produced and there's so much
attention, it's paid to sound and editing.
And it this being the first year anniversary.
There was a lot of podcasts who checked in with
congratulatory messages.
It was really a nice warm fuzzy feeling overall,
but it really inspired me to work on the sound again.
And I learned some very important things about my
wonderful laptop, which of course is running cast
Blaster Software.
You can download a free trial at castblaster.com.
I have a creative labs sound card that I stuck in there.
And apparently, and for those of you who are not in the
note like myself or new to the PC platform,
and Windows can be quite mysterious, I have to say.
Apparently, there's all kinds of drivers and software
that is installed with the install CD and there's all
kinds of settings.
Who knew that the card was set to output optimized for
headphones?
I don't know what kind of headphones that we're talking about,
but when I switched it to stereo 2, speaker 2.1 or
whatever the option was,
oh boy, big, big change.
And I think you probably will notice that just listening
to Kevin Reeves, how good that sounded.
So really, I didn't figure it out until I did an A.B.
comparison with the internal sound card and said,
wait a minute, this thing can't suck that bad.
And on top of that, I got into it and started to
switch with Ling and tweaking the knobs on the TLA 5052
stereo valve processor.
So I hope you like the sound today.
And you've all been graded, giving me feedback and letting me know
what you think of it.
And so I think we finally struck on some kind of paid
heard here.
Also, thanks to everybody, I'm learning a lot about PCs
and Windows.
Who knew?
Thank you very much for sending back all of your reports.
Castblaster mic had already predicted that me reading along
with the time, so right now, this is what I did yesterday
if you weren't listening.
I said right now, I'm recording it seven minutes and 26 seconds,
27 seconds, 28 seconds.
And everyone, of course, immediately looked at their iPod
or MP3 player, or Jesus, we had people on Windows,
media player, and that was off on every single one of them.
I'll just run down a quick list because I must have received
50 of these reports.
Dave Smith, Windows Media Player 10,
show us about one second out from your to my timings.
Andrew Grummit from Podshow, four seconds off.
Sean Bartolls, let me see, you said 36.35.
At that point, on iTunes, it was 36.31.
So that's six seconds off.
On the iPod, Squid says, was it four seconds off?
Wind amp, four seconds off.
What's this next one here?
You were dead on a 2430 on my iPod.
I double-checked this, and it was the same every time.
OK, so I was 2430, I was dead on the money,
but then when I said 36.35, it showed 31.
It just goes on and on and on.
Of course, the amazing Kevin says, he Adam,
I was about three seconds behind when you announced
what your timer was.
I'm using iTunes 6.02 because, of course, I'm
lazy asked, listening to your show consistently,
enjoying the hell out of blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I'd like to plug something, but I have nothing to plug yet.
There will be a podcast from you someday, damn it.
But if you want, plug Coca-Cola for me.
Great product does wonders for cooking
and your battery posts on your car.
Have a good one.
Thanks, Kevin.
So here's what's going on with all this.
Timers in general suck.
And you'd think that they be on the money.
It's just amazing to me, these discrepancies
of three to four seconds.
It's pretty outrageous, actually.
And it's not my fault or your fault or anyone's fault per say.
It's just that most timers, the software that do timers,
are just kind of easy about their timing.
And particularly when it comes to MP3,
it's not doing the sort of checking that this timer
that's built into cast blasters now doing.
It's actually taking the sample rate
and dividing it by the number of samples
and making sure the moon is in Aquarius
and praising Murphy and standing on one foot and all that stuff.
But actually it's very scientific.
And if you were to measure out the exact length,
based on real time, real world time,
it's now exactly right.
It's really that timer is all these devices that are off.
The interesting that iTunes seems to come
the closest when it comes to that.
So anyways, just, it really doesn't matter
because podcasting is no longer about time
and frequency and dimension and all that stuff.
So, but it's all solved.
Thank you.
And really all we're doing this for is just to make sure
that PW and I had exactly the same timing.
Although this could come in handy
if you're doing a so-called double-ender,
this is something Don and Drew pioneered.
The double-ender is where you basically have a conversation
on Skype and you each record your own portion.
And then later you mix the two together.
Now, if you were to do it on two separate PCs
with two separate timers, you'd probably wind up
with a discrepancy of three to four seconds
depending on how long the show is.
Now, I presume if you do it with cast blaster,
then you will have exactly the same time reference
for both those files.
Good, now we've got that past us.
Something you might have noticed in the news, Paul Nayeric,
actually said, I remember on David Sorsko
a few months back talking how you wish people could share
their hotspots, got a lot of those emails
because this new site called phone,
FOXTRAOT-OscarNobemberFone.com is, well, it is essentially
what I was hoping for a while back.
And of course, this was already being done in open sources.
The idea of creating some kind of firmware
that you could easily load into your Wi-Fi hotspot
that would enable people to share your bandwidth
based upon a couple of rule sets.
And I think that I shall look at the article here.
I don't know if it has those.
There was like pirate, wizard, llama, something like that.
Let me see if I can find the different levels of openness.
Like it's not have to go back to foam.com to figure it out.
But anyway, it's Google and Skype
who are putting this together.
And this is, I think this is just phenomenally interesting.
Because once you get software,
you get people to actually be able to load software easily
onto these routers, which will enable you to say,
hey, I want no one to share my bandwidth.
I want anyone to share my bandwidth or I want anyone
to be able to share between these and these hours, et cetera.
Once you've got that done, then we can start thinking
about if we have enough of these hotspots
about really layering a whole new network on top of everything
else, which presumably could be something
like a mesh network of Wi-Fi hotspots.
I don't know.
There's all kinds of great stuff.
And I've learned that when it's totally technically
possible to do this, excuse me, that was nasty.
Download.acview.com.
Yeah, that's my new Vulcan Mind trick.
So I'm trying, I'm going to try and deprogram everybody
from the Senseo link to the burp.
So I'll just mention different sponsors each time I do that.
And I'll do a different one each time,
so that we can deprogram you.
If something sticks, let me know, though,
because I'll have to work on you personally.
Anyway, I've learned that when something is technically
possible, but isn't being done because well,
factors like bandwidth or scale or attention, et cetera.
Just wait five years.
And it'll probably be here.
Something very similar to what we're talking about,
or what we've been talking about in the past,
well, on the past couple of months here,
on the Daily Source Code.
And just when you thought you wouldn't hear from them again,
yeah.
What you've got here is another message round that you're strong.
That you're strong, that you're strong, that you're strong.
Hi, I'm Roger Hea.
You know, we've got Valentine's Day coming out soon.
And I haven't actually got a girlfriend yet.
I was wondering if she'd have to help me out.
So I think this year's the three next week.
Can you make it go out and make some 50 girls, Frank?
I think with your good looks and my assistance
and my 8 million pounds worth of cardiac reasons.
I'm sure we could find some girls to talk to.
I think with many love, we'll begin exactly three p.
for the end of the night if you're interested.
Right now, I just remember you don't actually think,
so maybe if you'd give me a minute in your parties of car,
that would be certainly a lot cheaper than the taxi.
And you've got my address.
So I'll look forward to you back in 30.
I think it's not very romantic, shea, but not a whole shea
into the back of the car.
So I'll swap the parties to live there.
Actually, other stations still got your helicopter
because they're really well in crest girls,
but you will have trouble talking and it out.
Roger, what the hell are you talking about?
If I knew to directly post Roger now
wants to go out on a date
with me to go pick up chicks?
And we're supposed to do that with Bacardi Boresers.
Ooooo.
Roger, I'd love to.
Unfortunately, I've got to travel so I can't
make it for the next couple of weeks, but the idea's good.
Maybe, you know, we could just meet
for lunch or something and kind of ease into a personal relationship
before we can go out cruising for chicks.
And I don't have the helicopter anymore.
It's a, it basically wrong machine for my mission.
If the only place is I'm flying or, you know, to rotter dam
or maybe some other place in the UK and really fixed wing
as much better for that.
So maybe we'll just drive.
But let's, let's meet for lunch first.
Let's take it one step at a time.
And I hear by the way that your jingle is now one of the hottest
exchange ringtones in the UK.
Yeah.
And you can't eat.
You can't eat.
Totally got to get that on my phone as a ringtone.
Simon Powell says Adam, some of your listeners have been mentioning
on the Charlie lately.
I'd like that on the Charlie.
They often get asked how much can I listen to a podcast without an
iPod or how can I listen to a podcast without an iPod?
I have had that a lot too.
And so I've set up a site about this.
This is actually a pretty damn good idea.
Still basically, I want to develop a good resource
where you can direct a friend.
Basically, it's, well, a second.
Let me make sure I get the, isn't this the address?
Oh, shoot.
I think it's no iPod.
This is so stupid.
How could I have not saved the link?
Hold on a second.
Let me just see what's his name, Simon.
Gmail to the rescue, right?
Let me see.
Simon.
I thought I was no iPod required.com,
but let me just check.
I don't want to mess it up.
Here we go.
Incoming.
Yeah, no iPod required.com.
So yeah, if someone has that question,
just go to the site, no iPod required.com.
I think it's a great initiative, dude.
That's totally the type of stuff that we need to be doing.
And check this out, man.
This came in on the BBC in Peru.
Podcasts are being used to bring agricultural information
to villagers and farmers.
I'll just read a bit from this from the BBC
in Peru's remote and de-in-mountains.
Villages like Shanta Alta only have electricity
for two hours a day, despite this a new pilot project
is using podcasting to get important agricultural information
to farmers.
The farmers do not yet have the means
to listen on portable MP3 players.
And of course, they'll be surfing on immediately
to noopipodrequired.com.
UK charity, practical action, has married
old and new technology to podcast twice months,
twice monthly updates to eight information centers
in the Kajamaqa region.
This is really cool.
Who are these guys, practical action?
They're doing something good there.
This is very, very cool.
So I'll make sure there's a link to that on the show notes
for today.
And of course, it'll show up in the time-code-based show notes
at the wiki it's show notes, dotting foe.
Also something new that I noticed in my Gmail account today
is next to, you have your inbox, star,
your sent mail, your drafts, and your spam,
and your trash folders.
There's now a new one that popped up called chats.
And there's nothing in there.
And it looks exactly like you'd expect,
or a link.
Exactly like you'd expect a mail folder to look like.
Only what they're going to do, it doesn't work yet.
I guess if you have Google Talk,
which is their chat client, your history will show up there
just like email.
And they say pretty soon, chat in Gmail is coming.
So that's pretty interesting.
Integrating the integrating chats with email in Gmail.
I do have, obviously, you automatically
have a Google chat account when you sign up for Gmail
or any other Google service I believe, but still.
That could be interesting to use.
I pretty much use Skype all the time for instant messaging.
It seems to be what we're using around the office,
the most as well.
And now let us talk briefly about the cartoons.
This, of course, is topic of the day.
Everywhere except newspapers, interestingly enough,
the newspapers are very shy here in the UK
about really delving into this very deeply.
But from what I understand is that a top Iranian newspaper
has now written out a contest for, let's see,
what's the name of the newspaper, the Hamshari.
They're looking for, oh, this is really bad.
They're looking for cartoons and characteratures
that they can publish in response.
Now let me say a couple of things about this.
First of all, I love it.
I love the idea of using creativity and words and pictures
and art to express ourselves as human being
across any boundaries that we have to cross.
I love it.
Let me tell you, the stuff people write can be,
I think, as hurtful as sticking a knife in you.
In fact, I've seen many people have the exact same reaction.
And we're really good at it online, aren't we, guys?
We're really good at yelling and flaming and hurting each other
and it gets the emotions going.
It really gets you riled up.
And I think we do that quite a lot.
Maybe not just on forums, maybe it's with office workers,
on email, it could be through SMS.
And there's all kinds of ways that we lose our aggressive
energy that way.
And clearly, there's a lot of people
where they don't have these outlets.
I say, let's get them some terminals.
Let's get them some video cameras.
They can do video podcasts.
Let's set them up.
Let's get them help.
Let's start the dialogue.
Let's start yelling and screaming at each other.
Let's do it online.
A perfect place for it.
I'm very, very excited about, of course,
I'm doing it with mainstream media first.
But it can't be that far off for it.
And I think we should help them.
So I'm going to move the blank very away.
I think we should help move them into the debate online.
They're already sending out threatening emails.
So they've gotten that far.
So maybe we have to create an email to weblogs system
just so that they can participate and maybe a weblog
to email system news readers.
Come on, there's got to be some way that we can do this.
I mean, we shouldn't be afraid to give them the technology.
So we can go to a new battlefield, a new place.
I'd love it.
Now, that said, I think it's really unfortunate
that what this seems to boil down to is Muslims versus Jews.
It's like, how many hundreds of years
do we have to deal with this shit?
That's so disappointing.
And it's, you know, it's fundamentally
to not believe it's about the religious part of the conversation.
It's really about cultures.
And it's something that dates back to dates back a long time.
And it just continues.
And it seems a fucking pointless.
But I'd love to have more conversations about it.
At least if we can do that.
And by the way, I think what's happening in Western Europe
is just a repeat of history.
When the Roman Empire existed, which, of course,
was all of Europe with Rome being the capital.
There was actually in Constantinople, which, of course,
that we know as Istanbul, was really the eastern capital
of the Roman Empire.
And by the way, the Christians,
were very much where they had a very similar attitude
or they projected a very similar attitude to what we see today
from what we call radical extremists.
Now, they didn't have ways to blow themselves up in public,
but they showed a complete lack of fear
when they were thrown to the lions.
And it really puzzled the Romans.
And this is, of course, only from the history,
I've learned it, you know, correct me if I'm wrong.
But it really was a protest.
And there was no religion in Rome.
It's like, everyone, we got a whole bunch of gods.
Well, hey, you know, your god looks like our god.
That's cool.
You can come live with us.
And slowly, that started to decline.
I believe what really happened is the, quote, barbarians,
and Christians who were outside of the empire
and wanting to come in, they eventually were led in.
And they were led in unneeded.
And what happened is it was just, the infrastructure
could not support all the, quote, barbarians
that were brought in.
And that's probably a little bit of what we're seeing right now
with immigration in Europe.
Now, that said, we're going to continue on the podcast,
talking about this for a couple minutes.
Folks on serious satellites, they tuned for Pacific Coast
Hellway.
It's next.
God, I love doing that exactly on time.
Ha, of course, there are other opinions.
Aaron Warmus said, I believe that the cartoons were just
the last straw, stuff bothers me all the time.
I can ignore it because I can say that it's just a cartoon.
However, if it were my perception that I was being persecuted
for religious reasons, then I probably wouldn't stand
for this form of what could be seen as adding insult
to injury.
Simply, we are not just publishing cartoons.
We're invading countries, torturing killing innocent people,
stealing oil and publishing the offensive cartoons,
just my two euro cents.
Okay, duly noted.
But, you know, there's a lot, this is this stuff.
If once again, it boils down to these two religions,
battling it out, then this has been going on way before
quote stealing of oil and publishing of cartoons.
It just seems like it's the same damn thing.
And it's disappointing.
But I really do hope we could bring really, really do hope
we can bring more voices into this.
Let's help them out.
So maybe they won't have to be shooting AKs
and throwing eggs and torturing stuff
to get attention and lose some of that aggressive energy.
I see, I see, I know myself.
It feels great sometimes to flame someone.
And of course, when you get flamed,
it comes back at in different ways, but it is that energy.
It's the same thing.
And you'll be able to hurt people just as much.
Just as much.
And you can love people just as much.
I just wanted to revisit the censorship
of the Rolling Stones Super Bowl halftime performance.
The ridiculousness of them cutting out
just two short phrases from these songs
that have been, that the stones have been playing
for over 30 years, that played on the radio
around the world.
This is really mainstream media's version of jumping the shark
to have to censor that out for whatever reason,
whatever fear they had of a repeat of the Janet Jackson
wardrobe malfunction saga.
And last night I was watching the news.
It was BBC News 24.
And what they do a lot here in the evening
is they review the Morning's Papers.
And this was just, it's a laughing stock.
It is the laughing stock that this is going on.
And it just shows what a disconnect this is taking place.
And I'll just say with mainstream media,
I mean, I don't know where it's coming from.
And what parts of governmental backing these types
of or influence government influence these types
of censorship moments have just, it's so stupid.
From the country with the largest pornographic industry
on earth, and with the best porn movies I might had,
how can it have come this far?
I'm so happy we have other ways to get creativity art
and words, oh, yes, words out there, really.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
Where are flink?
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses
and scammers.
Where are flink?
We believe your personal information should be just that,
personal.
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe.
We are everything.
Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net
and discover what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthlink, we revolve around you.
I got an email yesterday from KJ, got some great news.
I told you that this is an ongoing dialogue
and is we're reinventing media and reinventing,
probably not just reinventing, but evolutionizing,
radio, television, print, through whatever we can do on the internet.
Advertising is going to come along with that.
And I got an email yesterday, the Earthlink folks
have definitely gotten the message and we've come up with an idea
that I think will blow you away.
And obviously, I can't tell you right now,
but it should be happening within the next two weeks.
I think we start, yeah, I think we start March 1 or something
like that.
And I really think you'll like it and you'll be really happy.
And I will just show that we actually had a dialogue
between listeners and between an advertiser
and I'm really, really excited about it.
So just wanted to mention that, too.
I had him.
I've heard you talk about netting on your show before.
I've heard about the netting Olympics,
the alternative to the winter Olympics.
There are currently two and a half hours netters signed up
to this, it's all done on the internet.
With podcasts and bloggers.
I'm going to find out more about this on yonhawit.com.
Right on yonhawit.com, was that it?
Yon, yarn, yarn, harlot?
Of course, there's an Olympic because I'll Olympics for knitting.
I knew that.
I actually, I think I talked about knitting in this piece
that I was interviewed for German television.
It's state-run television, ZDF, which is
so I just do it you fancy and pretty good piece.
I must say, although I think my hair,
Patricia looked at it, she goes like, yeah, yeah,
it's really good because she understands German perfectly well.
And she said, what's with the Donald Trump hair?
I'm like, oh man, I'm so crushed.
You know, I'm out there in San Francisco all by myself.
And I think I've made no secret of it whatsoever
that I just can't do my own hair or the way Patricia can.
I miss it terribly.
My questions have been answered about speed limits in the UK.
OK, so clearly doing 90 miles an hour was not a good idea.
P.W. Fetton actually said that was dangerous.
And of course it is.
But I got, let me see, Paul from the flashing 12th podcast.
He sent me this lovely page, which has all the different speed
limits, because we have dual carriageway here.
We have a single carriageway, and we have the motorway.
Subsequently, it's 60, 70 and 70.
So the top speed limit is 70 miles an hour, which isn't too bad,
actually.
And I got, who was it now that said that basically, they'll give you,
who else, Richard Smith, he goes to the same thing here.
OK, if you're caught above 90, you may be looking at massive
speeding fines and possibly charge with dangerous driving.
If you're seen around the 80 mile per hour mark
and are seen to be slowing down by the police,
you probably will get away with it.
Yeah, so from what I understand, the kind of general rule of thumb
is it's 10% plus three miles per hour.
So if you're doing, if you're supposed to be doing 70,
it would be 77, plus three would be 80,
and then you're kind of OK.
But in general, we shall also just keep the speed limits, I guess.
And we clear up the thing about the two chefs mark yesterday.
Chef Mark from New York says, Adam sounds great.
Actually, I spell my name with a K at the end
from Mark and Chef Mark is with a C.
But I've been in contact with them about the name,
although I think there's a slight difference in weight class.
We may go ahead and do the whole wrestling match thing.
That would be great.
We need to throw down in the Truffle's chalk.
At Truffle's shavings topped chocolate
between the two chefs, Chef Marks, to see who really is the true
Chef Mark.
And I got to tell you, Mark, with the K,
you may be in trouble when it comes to the all drawn battle royale.
It could be tough for you.
OK, let me see, what are we doing now?
Well, 32 minutes.
Good.
I got a couple more things to do with you.
This is, of course, the place where us guys get together
and talk about things like, well, about me not being able to do my hair on a pure frustration.
Actually, if I, one of these days, I should go through the whole rigour roll that
I have to do, just have my hair kind of look like anything that is not the Mona Lisa.
It involves a lot of product, OK?
And by the way, nothing we talk about here in the Metro sexual moment is a paid advertisement.
This is just an open conversation.
Still waiting for a sponsor to come in to sponsor it, but it certainly wouldn't be
gelat.
I've got to wait too much money.
I don't think that needs a sponsor anyway at this point.
Besides, we could take it anymore, because the only thing would accept
would be freeraisers for registered listeners of the Daily Source code.
Let's get to some comments in the Metro sexual corner of the podcast.
Hello there, Anna.
What are you doing?
It's here's Wichita Rutherford.
Now, let me tell you something.
That the day after listening to your Metro sexual moment, I actually had one myself.
And it made me a little uncomfortable because the fellow I was with, it made me uncomfortable
about the situation.
I know, but this is it, Miles Nails.
Oh, look at you.
So this is where you go at your blade.
That's right.
Come out of the bone in here.
There you go.
What do you do?
That starts with your blue blaster a little hard.
Wichita, I have to tell you I'm not comfortable here.
Oh, we'll actually crack.
Nobody cares if you're getting a manicure.
And who do you know it's going to be here?
I'm serious, it's making very uncomfortable.
It's not cool, it's not cool.
See, this is what I'm talking about.
Girl, I don't care what you're talking about.
This is, I don't want anyone to think on the top of person that would come in here and do this.
You need to get in touch with your feminine side, my little friend.
Yeah, but yes, but yes.
You sat down, let me do your fingernails.
You ain't that big a human.
Well, if anybody sees me, they're going to think I'm, thank your watch.
Well, they're going to think I'm.
Metrosexual?
Well, there's nothing wrong with it.
Hey, I'm straight.
I'm a guy and you're a guy.
Me and you use buddies.
And in the middle is Metrosexual.
And that puts both of our sexual orientations,
hone an even playing ground.
That's why I can do it all your little parties and bars
and not feel weird.
Hang in around people like Gladys.
Who's real name is Phil?
So you're saying it's like common ground for all of us.
Bingo!
Now, sit down.
Because after this, we're going to go shopping for hats.
Ooh!
You'll thank you.
Wait till you see us all steps and number I've been looking at.
Nice huh?
Come fake clothes, eh?
Who let's get adventures after this?
Hey, leave me!
Can we get pennies after our manny?
Metrosexual?
It's an encourage Metrosexual moment.
An encourage Metrosexual moment.
Yeah.
Hi Adam.
This is Chris from the MathCred podcast.
Thanks to your show.
I have switched to a non-alcoholic aftershave.
And I now use a moisturizer with SPF-15.
I'm planning to look this good forever.
I have a tip and a question for the Metrosexual moment.
First the tip.
I don't recall ever hearing you mention the cuticle tool.
You can get one for a couple bucks at the drugstore,
and it keeps your nails looking sharp.
To be honest, I can barely tell the difference,
but I guarantee the ladies will notice and they love it.
Now for my question.
No matter what cream or razor I use,
the lowest part that I shave, you know,
the part that's more neck than face,
gets red and irritated and razor burned when I shave.
This is true, even on the first run with a new razor.
Please help me out.
Then head over to my podcast.
I discuss the mathematics behind every day situations.
Check it out.
The MathCred podcast and MathCred.com.
Thanks Adam.
Yeah, good question dude.
I actually have exactly the same problem.
No matter what I do,
usually it's all razor burned down in the lower regions.
This morning, actually, on my way out,
I nick myself with the mock free turbo razor.
It was like a neat little V shape.
I have no idea why that happened.
That has not happened ever since I've used it,
but yeah, if anyone has any thoughts about razor burn
and how to circumvent that,
it would be welcome here in our little Metro sexual moments.
Hi Adam.
This is Derek and I live in Alberta, Canada,
and 14 years old,
and I have a Metro sexual moment for you.
I use two products that I got for Christmas
in a skincare package type thing,
and they're both made by say knives,
and because I'm in my teens,
I do have some problems with acne.
I really don't have it that bad,
but I do get stuff for months and a while.
So, I use two products.
I want to use in the shower,
and I want to use after.
One is an apricot,
deep cleaning cream cleanser,
and it is supposed to not dry out of your skin.
It doesn't have any oil in it.
I really like that.
It's good for my acne,
and then during the winter's in Canada,
it gets quite dry.
So, my skin tends to dry out.
So, I use a product called 24-hour moisture,
and it's advanced moisturizing lotion,
and it seems to work really well for me,
and it makes my skin nice and soft.
So, I have those two products,
and I really love those.
I hope that helps with the image of sexual moment.
You can visit my website at your voice.cjb.net.
And I've got some cool stuff there, so thanks.
Bye.
Yo dude, thank you very much.
And make no mistake.
Particularly to the younger listeners,
you want to be moisturizing from the minute
you hear my voice talking about it,
because when you get old, like me, old and decrepit,
you're going to be really, really, really, really happy.
Because your skin will just be nice and supple,
and you won't have those wrinkles,
and it may not matter to you right now,
but boy, I'm telling you, it will one day.
I'm going to make you a sexual moment.
Yeah.
I learned a lot about mixing multiple sound sources
and cast blaster on that one.
I completely forgotten that completely forgotten
the fur that I've heard had done his own music.
So, oops, sorry about that.
It's still learning, but it's coming together now.
And I think the sound, I think,
basically got it there.
I've got it in a good place.
Of course, I may be listening to this now
and cringing because it's clipping and distorting
all over the place.
Who knows?
Okay, to wrap it up today,
a little update on what's going on,
Pod Show HQ.
Talk to Chris Rockwell.
Looks like Thursday will be able to start
the first beta test of purchasing.
To quote him, he's so close.
He can barely taste it.
I think it's what his exact words were.
And the whole thing is we wanted to have,
the one account, the one store,
of course, to want to have it to be persistent,
log on into the, you know,
the Pod Save Music Network and into the purchasing
and there's all these security issues
which he kind of had,
I got a little bit too excited last time I said
we were going to start betaing it.
But it looks like it's coming together
and the affiliate stuff,
which is all the unlabeled pieces.
Those will be rolling out very shortly as well.
So we're getting somewhere.
The same time I've actually been able
to invite a couple of outsiders
into the Pod Cast delivery network
and the Pod Show Plus.
Oh yeah, what's that?
Pod Show Plus.
Oh, secret.
Of course, I was really stupid about inviting people
because the confirmation email
when you sign up,
doesn't go directly to you.
So it has to go through one,
at this point it's going through,
I think Sue or Kevin,
and then they forward it on.
That was like an extra measure we put in there.
I can't for the life of me remember why.
But it's just great to see this stuff coming together,
particularly from afar,
you know, I've logged in now to the bug database
and I can put stuff in there
and you see status of it is actually
it's coming together and it's getting very,
very, very close.
And you should be hearing some,
some podcasters pretty soon
who actually will be up and running on the system
and hopefully with as much ease
as we've all, as we've all dreamt about.
For me.
Hold on a second.
What's that?
It's probably P-Dub
complaining about the show.
I see what it is.
Okay.
Let me play, let me see what I do.
That's 40 minutes.
You don't play that last thing tomorrow.
I'm going to play one more song for you.
As I was perusing around the pod,
say he's a network.
I thought to myself, man,
it's been a while since we've had a little bit of love on the show.
Let's bring it now, brother.
Love and there she goes.
I'm so good to you.
What ever happened?
Don't leave me so soon.
So I'm so good to you.
What ever happened?
Don't leave me so soon.
It's alright when it's okay.
Yeah.
It's just.
I can't win.
So, very minutes.
First and second kamera.
Then, you say you can't.
Take pictures.
My name is Fernando Carret and I'm the lead Bro.
I'm most beat off it here so I gotta decide instead.
Whoo!
Leave me, man.
ampness.
Guns are gay, yeah
When she goes, no one knows
A lot of men she's better
Can I sing now that she'll be back again?
This goes, this goes
When she goes, I get it
It's a stage
She died to tell the story
Oh, she died to tell the story is the story is the story
It's just a kid in my head, and I'm gonna love your dad
We're out of birth, right?
No, I don't wanna be a loom, I don't wanna be a loom, I don't wanna be your brother, I'm gonna tell you
Just that guy, we'll go outside
I know where we're gonna be
Yeah, I know, yeah, I'm in to
I can't breathe to everything
It's a treasure, I wanna be the guy
The girl's walking through the mirror
Oh, I'm so bad
Oh, he's crazy to read
Like I thought I'd get it getting
Just spread all your time
For those not up for this
But no real lies
Oh, this goes, this goes, this
Busico's a doubly
Ghost crazy on a know
Oh, let's see it's though
And as I see it though
Don't know, stupid back up next
There's a ghost, this ghost
With possiamo's a kill
And I get the light live
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Nooooo, wooivivivivivivivivivivivivivivivivivivivivivivivviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviviv
There she goes from the album of the year, find it at the Podsat Music Network.
If you're a podcaster and you want to play Podsat Music Register at music.podshow.com.
And there was something in that song that created yet another community test here for source
code listeners. When Brother Love said, I'm left, I'm right, and now I'm center stage.
In my headphones, it was reversed. So I don't know if I have something messed up here,
or I'm sure the Brother Love didn't mess it up. Let me know and check your ear buds.
Make sure you have, let me see, is this left and right? Hold on, let me see. It doesn't actually
say, hmm. I'm pretty sure that he's headphone that I have him on the right way, but I don't know.
I'll have to listen to my own ear buds. Hey everybody, that's it for today. I'll be back tomorrow.
We're going to do the hump day edition of the show. I think we got some Trinity coming up
and more good music. Good times. Good fun. There we go. Thanks, everybody.