Delta Sierra Charlie 3-1-6
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped my ass
In the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into this jar
I'm guessing it's Adam Curry
Come on you once again from Sunday Northern California
Hey everybody, it is your daily source code my name is
Adam Curry
At least it's probably Monday where you are
It's Sunday still here in
The Curry Condo
In San Francisco
We're bringing you some pot safe tunes
We're gonna out of town in a small cafe
She had the motion of the ocean out her
It was this way she had
Everybody looking back and everybody took him back
And anything she wanted all the guys all day
I was fine for so few things
I know
Too funny because she knows she got it
She got it and she got it
The moves I'm trying to get into
Don't make a man we're worried
Still like everything is okay
She got it
Pauice
And I think I wanna give you this bag
And every moment's I'll be on a bus
And say, it's my Pauice
And I think I wanna give you this bag
Pauice
And every moment's I'll be on a bus
She holds you down but when you need a push
She'll keep it on and she reflects
That she forces her look
She got everything and you got everything
You dream about everything's in a small
She's still your heart like it for now
She got it
Exactly what you want when
She holds you in a message just to see you get it
She got it
But then now I'll say if she was there for a GV
And a life of both this press and one was totally gone
Pauice
And I think I wanna give you this bag
And every moment's I'll be on a bus
And say, it's my Pauice
And I think I wanna give you this bag
Pauice
And every moment's I'll be on a bus
She'll keep this bag
Or 정말 you give us this
Fizz and Airbnb
See her guess
Wanna see just how deep work is
Guess what's in a magical secretplis she is
I'll pay with my corporate
I just want to travel inside and see her
economic deep soul
fresh from the West Coast
She got everything
It work is But ready to web she don't live
Don't care how people slow to be
Oh she's so friendly Hello Jack
Sam drills into masterfight
Keepin' a breath when like heatin' it has been hot
Take a great chick, she's the medicine
She got tricks and she got some treats
She's like the ground on the meat
You knock it off your feet, she digs
Everything about it for my head
I don't know if I'm a goose or never,
Knees and sells a music way, she speaks now
She speaks now, she speaks now
Consisting with an energy sense
She's like the middle games when it's time to play
She's like a farmer, it's not for watching
Just a whiff or a whiff or a memo
Make it me, skip me, skip me
Owls!
Do you think I'll do it like you
There's nothing I can help you
Owls!
Do you think I'll do it like I said
I'm about to make music that work
Black delicious
And it's...
Owls!
You got to run my epitaph right, there's actually
Certainly can't think so much
I'll have to get some official words
J-Mac from Hood High
Owls!
The craft!
Nice ending, a little surprise there
Hey everybody, how you doing?
I hope you are ready for another week
of hitting the daily grind
Hope you had a great weekend
I was all by myself
Of course it's a Martin Luther King day
So you may actually
Be chilling back, relaxing and not doing anything
An amazing amount of companies are not really honoring this holiday
Or not really I guess by making compulsory to come to work
Same as not honoring
I thought it was a national holiday
It was like a obligatory, it could be wrong
I had a great weekend
Which really started off Friday night
At the Pod Show HQ
We had some visitors
A couple podcasters show up
And this was actually all
All pre-arranged
Chef Mark, who has the Chef Mark podcast
Came by and cooked paella
For the entire office
He made so much and came in with the whole paella
Pan and his own gas set up
And just it was a wonderful smell in the office
But he made so much that we had to invite
The four neighboring offices just
And they even took stuff home in
Topwear and all kinds of other containers
To have so much of it
It was just fantastic
It was so good, I'm not a big paella
You're a fan actually
But it was really good, it was chicken
And of course the yellow rice
Which was not soggy
You know, it wasn't that milky, crappy stuff
It was just it was nice
And lobster tails and mussels
And oh man, it was so nice
Also met
Emily and Elizabeth from sex with Emily
The podcast sex with Emily
I'm not quite sure what the connection was
How they came along with Chef Mark
But basically Chef Mark and whole bunch of women walked in
It was very cool
And it was really nice
It was nice meeting the neighbors as well
And hanging out and Jady from Mad Pod was there
He was hanging out as well
Of course lots of folks were in town
For Mac world
Speaking of Macs
I've been bitching about this sound problem
Which you may hear in this podcast
All of a sudden you know
You may just hear this skipping or digital audio
Hang
And I have here a web page
It is
Here we go
Powerbook G4 double layer SD
Audio stutters or skips
Check this out
When you're running two or more audio applications
In your Powerbook G4 15 inch double layer SD
Your Powerbook G4 17 inch double layer SD
Whatever the hell that is
The audio may intermittently stutter echo or skip backwards
This can happen even if one audio application isn't playing
Or you have the sound muted in the application
Such as when playing a game
This can involve any application that uses audio
So just quick time items
IDVD and many third
Party applications like games and audio applications
To avoid this
No way
First of all
Here's recognition of the problem
I'm very happy to see this
Oh yeah, sound day night
You know what I'm doing
So that's pretty cool
Because the first thing you got to do
Is true
Something's wrong, something's up
About that
Now
It goes on one last paragraph
To avoid this
Run only one audio application at a time
If it looks like you have
One audio application running
But the sound is still skipping or
Stuttering check for hidden
Login items or startup items
Okay, obviously
That's not a fix
That's a workaround and a sad one at that
I have
Maybe see I currently have
Megaseg open
I have audio hijack pro running
I'm going to quit iTunes
And maybe that'll make a difference
It does say I must add
This document will be updated
More information becomes available
Okay, so looking forward to that
Got that one bookmark
And of course the link to that page
We'll show up in today's show notes
So Melta was pretty cool
We have this Russian scientist from Canada
It's pretty interesting
He had called called or called emailed
Ray Lane
One of our investors
And he had such a wrap on him
That Ray who was totally a guy
Who sniffs out bullshit
And just doesn't
Have much leniency for anything other than
Good stuff
Pass this on to us and say, I don't know
You guys should check him out
Maybe something there
I got a feeling that there's something going on with this guy
Wow
It was fun
He came down for a couple days
And we talked about
How man just the aspects of scalability
To what social networking
Is can be
It was just really really nice
To have someone extremely smart
Hang it out at the office
Oh shit
I'm burning down my power book
That will definitely
Cause audio skipping if I torch it
To anyone who said that was cool
Just shout out to him because I know he's listening
And I know he's listening because Matt he was able to recite a lot of stuff
Going on with the source code
But it was kind of cool you told me a story about
He's all about usability and interfaces
And told me the story about how in
I guess it was World War 2
There were so many
Gear up landings
And upon interviewing all the pilots
It turned out that
Especially in the dark
The concept of a handle to pull down the gear
Or a handle to push down the flaps
It was just too much confusion in the cockpit
And that's how they actually came up with a design
If you look at any
Certainly single-engine aircraft
You'll see that the flaps lever
Kind of resembles a flap
It's a flat button that you push down to
To make the flaps go down
And the
The lever to
Extend to retract the landing gear
Is actually a rubber round wheel
Resembling your wheels
And I was kind of cool
And more I thought about it
There's something to that usability stuff
Hey lots of audio comments for today's show
Hi Adam
This is Scott Allsmith from the road
No second why is that
Why is that showing up only in one channel
What sucks?
Hold on, you must be able to do something about that
I have the
Can I punch that mono somehow
To
Shoot
Okay, well
If I only do one channel you're going to hate it
That sucks here and stuff and only one one year
I
Don't think I can monoize this with what I'm doing
Let me check
I do anything with
Audio hijack pro
No, I don't think so
I don't think so
Let's see maybe I can make
Megaseg output mono
That'll be cool
Playback
I'll put
Shoot
Ah screw it
Okay
Listen on one channel then
Less travel the podcast
That would be the podcast that you've never listened to
Until now at least
Anyway, I hear that you have a little problem with
Jetlight
Don't worry, my friend, it happens to all of us
And the road less traveled podcast
Just got to stop
I got to figure out how to make that
That's got to be stereo
It's got to be two channels
I just can't I can't handle it. I'm so sorry
It was actually very cool because it's about
An anti jet lag diet
But there's just no way
No way and hell we can listen to that
For like two and a half minutes
Hi Adam, this is Jordan Taylor from Rhythm Angels
Rock and Blast cast over in Vancouver
Washington
I just got finished listening to Delta Sierra
Charlie 315 and while listening to it
I encountered a pretty serious problem
Man, I was just in kitchen
Mind my own business
While I was making a little bit of dinner
Had the MP3 player on
Taken in what you were saying
And then came the Trinity segment
All of a sudden
I'm dancing like a fool through on flower rounds
Oh man, this is not
He's really funny
She was walking her little dog and saw me bust and move
Needless to say
I'm now addicted to the Trinity jingle
All right, I can't get that thing out of my head
So thanks Adam
Thank you for getting that little ditty stuck in my head
for the next week
And now I gotta go explain to my neighbor
That I was not on drugs
Like she'll really believe that
I love the show
I can not go day without checking for another download of it
I'm going to go not for you
And my boyfriend who pointed me towards your show
To introduce me a podcasting
I would not be doing my own podcast
So you can check that out if you have a little time too
Wrathamangel.lipsen.com
I'll get you there
Talk at you later
Tailwinds my friend
Tailwinds back at you
I don't know everything froze up for a second there
I'm just going to ignore it
Just like it didn't happen
So you like that
You're into the Trinity tune
Okay
Kick off your shoes girl
That's right
Now if you're wearing a sweater or something
Take that off
That's right
I just want to whatever t-shirt you have on right
Okay
That's good
You can participate in this at home as well
So you're on your sock
May bare feet is even better
I think
Yeah
Okay
You ready?
It's even better if you have bare feet
Tight feeling pants and a tank top
Okay
Maybe you should go
Maybe you should put it on pause
And go and dress like that
And then come back
Yeah
Okay
You back
All right
Here we go
Woo
It is time once again to talk about
That piece of biodiesel
Her name is Trinity
Trinity
The quintessential luxury
Oh
Trinity
From the biodiesel
Industry
Yeah
Well
I kind of tell you
Today I had quite a trip with Trinity
That would be today being Sunday
I planned out a whole trip
And isn't it just amazing how you can actually survive
With a cell phone
Actually let's just say a blackberry
Because I don't know if you could survive with only a cell phone
But the blackberry
Which has a Gmail local on it
So I can find literally any address anything I want
And even get street maps if I want
And a GPS
So off I went with armed with
All I needed
My blackberry
My Tom Tom
Portable GPS
And I pre-programmed a nice little route
Which you can do with this Tom Tom go
First stop
Was
Ikea
In Emoryville
My goodness
This place is amazing
And you know what you just can't walk through Ikea
Without putting shit in your car
The absolutely don't need
They've got such a wonderful format of path
You know it
Before you know it
I was just coming for a table
Which by the way
I wasn't able to find
Nor was able to find that the Shandelier I was looking for
Like great reading land
But I can do
I got
Cooking utensils
Which I'm sure I'll never use
Oh very important I got six glass
Ashtrays
So I don't have to carry the
Outto its box around with me
Dropping ashtrays everywhere
But she performed wonderfully
It was great
I had the roof slid open
Across the Bay Bridge
It was just fantastic
I got a
Finally got a fuel for her power
For the pickup
Which of course is
Not all that much
But as you're driving along
Once you get up to speed
You can really smell
Kind of the lovely
Fumes
Wafting around you
Particularly with the roof open
It was really enjoyable
Beautiful day for it too
And after that I went for a quick stop
That I wanted to go to Berkeley
The bio fuel oasis
Unfortunately as I rolled up
In front of the egg
Look I got that
Oh there we go
I guess I had too many audio applications open
Uh, apple
Okay
Rolled up to what
I don't have to be called
Garage really
And kind of like the
Garagey industrial district
A cute sign
That said
They were open every day
Monday to Thursday
From 4 to 8 p.m
Friday's by special appointment
Open Saturday until 5 p.m.
And they're not open on Sundays
So I'll just have to go back
But I didn't have my recording gear there
But there was just no one to talk to
So that will obviously remain on the agenda
To visit the bio fuel
The Berkeley bio fuel oasis
On a Trinity trip
Let me just see this one
One of the common I got here from
Matt Snoggrass
Adam while listening to
DSC 312
One
You should have taken a digital picture
Of Trinity
Not parked over the line
And the other car that was parked over the line
Fight the power
He says
Yeah
Actually I did go to my guy Mario
And I said hey who hands out the
Citation's here
He says we do
Said dude that was so not you
Who did that right
And he kind of smirk
He said he knew who it was
He said don't worry about it
Which means it's being fixed
Two
When you leave Trinity alone for a while
You really should disconnect the battery cable
Leaving it connected
Drain the battery bit
After long stays at the
At the cottage
That could take its toll
Matt Snoggrass from Rosal Park
New Jersey
Thank you very much Matt
Yeah
But kind of
The way she just started up on one go
When I came back that makes you feel so good
Not having to dive underneath the hood
Let's
Let me see what this is a really long feed back that I got here
There's a lot of people that are
Responded to the
Babe code
Concept of starting a biodesol
Refinery in the Bay Area
And
I think that the
I have this feeling that the trip to the
Biofuel
Oasis in Berkeley will
Really help us get a much better insight
As to what kind of businesses
It can be in what it will take
And can you're opening hours
Only be from 4 to 8
Every single day
Stay tuned
Because that will be coming up soon
In another Trinity
She could talk
You didn't think
I don't for booping in her tank
We're Trinity
I am Trinity
Yeah
Hey, I got invited to the London Air Show
Cool is that
From the PR agency
Taking place in Earl's court
From 21st to 23rd of April
I guess that is so it's not in the airport
Then then
How do they do that?
Are they going to have any flying demonstrations?
Sure, I hope so
Well anyway
I'm just seeing this as Earl's court
That doesn't make sense
There's no place to fly any Earl's court
Is there?
Well, no wonder he hasn't responded
To my request if I could fly in
There's nothing cooler than flying in
To an air show
That is so awesome
Judy Engelsberg sent me an email
Which is representative of quite a lot of listeners
To the show
This is my 34th time that my subscription
To your show has stopped through iTunes
I've been listening for over a year
And I switched over iTunes from iPod or Lemon
Because I like iTunes features
But I have had to re-subscribe to your show
And I don't know why
I know it's easy to do
I just drag the RSS tag in iTunes window
Which I learned from you
Just wanted to let you know
Because you mentioned it once on the show
Are you doing it on purpose
To raise your iTunes podcast ratings?
That's pretty funny, Judy
First of all, no, I'm not doing anything to break it
But there is a feature in iTunes
Which initially I thought was going to be a really good idea
But has turned out to be extremely broken
The feature in iTunes
Is that it stops downloading podcasts
It doesn't unsubscribe
But it stops downloading podcasts
If you have not listened to five episodes in a row
And I'm seeing that
I'm subscribed to this evolutionary vlog
Whatever it is
And it's a community
The video podcast site
Excuse me
Sense out
I'm actually drinking to T right now
Oh, I was looking for a Sense out machine for the condo
Couldn't find one
I'll have to make another Trinity road trip for that
Anyway
So there's probably more than
Sometimes 10 videos a day come down the pipeline on that
And so it stops after five
And actually it will give a little
Exclamation mark next to the podcast
And then you can say, hey
Oh, it'll actually ask you
You have not listened to this podcast
No, I'll do you want to continue downloading or not
But I think it stops downloading
And it won't download the episode
You've missed you have to do that manually
Now, initially I thought that was a pretty good idea
Because
Well, you don't want people who were subscribed to stuff
Just to stay subscribed forever
But now that we're seeing
Different usage of these RSS feeds
I think that that should be
Probably be by default
That should be off
And it should be a preference setting
And that is probably what you're seeing
Judy
Maybe you listen to it from the web or something like that
Or a different location
Or you know
It probably just happened
And I do five shows a week
So if you don't feel like listening for a week
Then that's a shame
Because you won't get any new episodes
The next time you want to check in
And the question about
If I'm doing that on purpose
To raise my iTunes podcast ratings
Pretty funny because, you know, people
Lots of people ask me
You know, how is that top 10 or top 100
Organized and iTunes and from what I understand
It is
Compiled by
A number of new subscriptions
Over
I believe a 24 hour period of time
Which keeps the list obviously very fresh
But of course it does indeed keep it open
And pretty prone to
To trickery like that
This was kind of funny
This is a promo
Let me see
How written in
Kind of like what is it like
A talent like New Jersey, Thug, Italian, style
Something like that
Yeah, have a listen to promo is pretty funny
Hello, Adam Curry
Curry is like the f**king Indian cuisine
Right over here
I wonder when people listen to Adam f**king pancakes
If they get the f**king runs
What's with the f**king bleeps right now?
I don't f**king know what to say
Back to what I f**king pissed me off over
His body ran the holy f**king shit
It's out of me
What the f**king?
Adam, we're a little off of a game right now
Cause there's some kind of f**king bleep going on
What?
Little f**king's out over there
That's our engineer stuff about you
Recording all of f**king shows
Engineering f**king
That's every time I say
That's Louis
Every f**king time we're gonna say
What are those f**king words?
He's pushing that little f**king red button
Yeah, I'm gonna do a little test
Adam Curry likes to get his f**king f**king f**king
I can't see f**king
I think I'm gonna say
I'm gonna fix this f**king problem
I'm gonna f**king know
Hey, Louis
So what you said if you're on your own
I'll tell you your room out the way
Adam and they might come over and show some respect
You're my holy and man
Anthony the stupidest of a bitch himself
If it requires a toilet connection
Confine this requires a tolly dot com
It's QU AZ
ATOY
Got cal
So come on over in there
I heard you help a brick day
Yeah
Go f**k yourself
Listen to her
That was totally the only I changed music store
Bitch
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do
Where are a flank?
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers
We believe your personal information
Should be just that, personal
And we believe your internet should be a friend
Not a fo
Where are you flank?
Make this smart choice
Visit earthlink.net
And discover what our internet experts can do for you
Earthlink
We revolve around you
Hey Adam, my name is Ken
I've been listening for something like nine or ten months
You really got me inspired
And I hooked up with a guy that was wanting to do a radio show
But radio is like 400 bucks an hour or something like that
So I was like hey why don't we do a podcast
He agreed we tried it out
And we've been doing it ever since
It's a parrottox.com
P-A-W-R-O-T-A-L-K-S.com
Anyway
Ever since I've been listening to you
I've been thinking about this hundred million listener
March thing that you've been talking about
And I've been wondering how we're going to get this to come about
Well I think I've made it discovery
And here's what happened
I told my brother and law about our show that we were starting
And he listened to it and he liked it
And he wanted to tell other people about it
So I said we'll hold it a second
Dude let me make some instructions
And you can email that to people
And then maybe they'll understand what we're doing
So he did and almost all of those people
At least tried out the show and I think about half of them
Stuck around and they're still listening
Which is totally awesome
So here's what I did
I went ahead and kind of I type set a document
I'm calling it
It's a PDF file on our website called podcasting 101
Basically it'll teach any person who's never even heard a podcasting
What podcasting is how to listen
And how to manage your files and whatnot
I had total newbies proof this file
I had them dissected
I had them try it after it was over
I said you know hey you feel like you can do this
And they said oh yeah we can do it
So I'm pretty confident it's going to work
Basically if you go to a pair of talks.com
Go to the podcasting page
I have a print resolution PDF
As well as a screen resolution PDF
And I put them up on libson
So there's no bandwidth issues
If you want to link directly to them or whatever
But I just basically want to offer them up to the podcasting community
Take them email into people, email them to your
Have your listeners email them to their friends
And whatever and get them to subscribe to your podcast
You know I used paratox.com as the example
So you know hey if a few people listen to my show too
That would hurt my feelings
But basically if we're ever going to get anywhere near 100 million listeners
We're going to have to make those listeners
Not just find them
Hey Adam thanks for inspiring me
Thanks for providing a great show
I honestly really look forward to it
Every time you do it
And hope to your back from me
Thanks so much
Bye
You're very cool
By the way
Of course the ultimate
The ultimate goal for the 100 million listeners
March is to give a whole bunch of
Let's just call them tools to the listeners
So they can really become involved in the show
You know we're seeing stuff like
Wiki show notes
We're seeing stuff like forums, work very well
We need plenty other tools
And also let's
I know let's have the listeners have an identity
All the stuff that's coming with the pod show podcast network
That is on the way
Yeah hopefully
Hopefully this week
I think some of the
At least some of the podcasts will start using
Some of the tools of the podcast delivery network
So that'll be coming
I don't feel like talking about that tonight
Let me see
What did I want to talk about?
There were some pretty wacky stuff
Yeah a couple of people sent me this
About
And this is actually from
Where does this come from?
This is coming from the BBC again
Let me just see if there's a
I'll actually came through boiling boiling
There you go
Apparently in the UK there's
We talked about licenses that music stores have to play
Well apparently club DJs
Also if they are actually spitting stuff from their laptop
Or if they've burned stuff or downloaded stuff
They have to pay an additional 200 pound license fee
It's crazy
I can't believe it
Oh man
Well make so much sense
You know when there's only so many
Records you can sell and so many radio stations
They can play it
Which is of course a defined universe
Then you got to go you got to grow somehow
I guess that's one way
Martin Gordon said that Adam came across this site today
Skyvector.com
Which is like the Google maps of aviation charts
Don't know much about aviation
But thought I might pass it on to you
To share it with your fellow flying geeks
Tailwinds
Indeed Martin thank you back at you
Yeah it's very cool
It's basically you consume in
You can drag the map and these are really high-res scans
A lot of love and work it work when into that
Unfortunately there's only a few segments of the US that are currently available
But it's the typical of an open source project
That would be so fantastic
To have a worldwide coverage
Of
Basically all aviation maps
Although I do think there's some
Probably minor copyright violation involved
Hey check this out
Got some really cool news for you
There's a new breed of terror
No only as the ancestors
Hi this is Scott Sigler
Author of the podcast novels earth core and ancestor
Over 11,000 people tune in each week to hear ancestor
A free horror suspense audio book with a gory high-tech edge
And now I am thrilled to announce that I have joined the pod show family
To get the final two episodes of ancestor
You're going to need to go to Scott Sigler
Dot pod show dot com and get the new feed URL
And pod show will be the exclusive host of my new podcast novel
Infection
Do out the first week of March
I'm excited to join pod show
It's a cutting edge company that's going to rewrite the rule book of entertainment
The traditional publishing community can kiss my fat ass
And while you listen to ancestor, keep the ears open for the key phrase
That sure is fuck ain't no cow
That'll be decath pods for Scott next time at the office when we serve him some sense say
Dude, very cool to have you on board
That's very exciting. Scott's always in and out of the office in his motorcycle gear
I don't even know what he rides and I missed a couple other people drop him by the office last week
Because well trucker Tom came by and I really wanted to talk
I don't know what that fuck was doing
Maybe I was doing stuff with a German TV crew
Which, by the way, yes, I was wrong
It is spaitas. Durch of fans in. Not zoot Deutsch is fans in
So I apologize about that
But trucker Tom did post pictures of him standing next to
Trinity in the parking lot, which is very, very cool, but I'm sorry, I missed them.
Because I think he probably pulled up with his rig, I mean, so I missed all the vehicular
excitement at the offices past week.
Now, better luck next week.
Hey, what's up, Adam?
This is Jay Mack.
Just checking in, you know, I have a comment regarding a serious satellite, not that I'm not
knocking it or knocking a pod show or anything like that, but man, I don't know what it is.
But if you listen to, you know, any of the pod show podcasts, series 103, they all sound
like they're at AM, man.
I mean, it's the sound quality in comparison to the actual podcast.
And I understand that it's an outlet to, you know, for more exposure, but man, at the same
time, I mean, the sound quality is just man, I don't know.
So I'm just, I'm wondering, you know, what is the reason?
Why is the sound quality on your show through the, through the show, so high quality,
but at the same time, when it's streamed through a digital satellite service, it comes
through sound like it's through AM.
I mean, it's pretty bad.
So I mean, it doesn't do your show or Pacific Coast Highway, or, you know, any of those
very much adjust this as far as the sound of them.
So that's it.
I would like to hear what you had to say about it.
Don't forget, www.hoodard.com.
We got an interview with Jiza on the latest, this Jiza Wu Tain clan on our latest episode.
So check that out.
And that's it, man.
Talk to you soon and love the show.
See.
So they'll subscribe, man.
And actually, I'm stupid.
You probably heard the satellite window beeps of the window closing.
So that actually didn't air on serious.
And of course, that's where they could use this explanation.
So I definitely will have to play this again in the future.
Okay.
So just like any other digital transmission, there are bandwidth issues in play.
And interestingly enough, this also goes for satellite bandwidth because the satellites
both serious and XM are licensed through the FCC.
And they have allocated an amount of spectrum.
A double shot of sensor.
So they've allocated a certain amount of spectrum, frequency spectrum,
to each of the two satellite providers in the US.
And that represents, and I'm not, you know, I don't know all the calculations,
but that represents an actual number of bits and bytes they can pump through that
piece of spectrum.
You know, that's why you only have X amount of channels on your on the television band.
Same goes for the FM band.
This is how much has been allocated is chopped up in this case into two pieces.
And that's it.
So now in order to cram all those wonderful channels in there, they have to make some choices.
Because you can imagine that high quality digital data takes a more bandwidth
than low quality, just like it does, where a file is bigger if it's high quality than a file
for an MP3, for instance, that is recorded a lower quality.
So the trick they do is, first of all, all talk stations are mono.
So you know, because that's literally half the signal right there.
And then because talk is predominantly so talky.
They, they bring down the quality to almost an AM sounding frequency.
And of course, once you pump music through there, and let's be honest, MP3's is not
great source material.
We actually transcode every single show into MP2, and then there's another special,
as actually a special codec, I'm sorry, we transcode them to way files first.
And then from way we transcode them to the special MP2 format, which is what the satellite will eat.
And we actually, we look at this in the beginning, and it really doesn't matter.
It's just unfortunate that all we have is a mono talk channel.
And most of what is playing on that channel is mono, or is like, you know, cousin Bruce is on
there as well, so I guess he's kind of intended to sound like AM.
Oh, there you have it.
Okay, well, two things, first in admission.
I have been watching the National figure skating championships, and I have to admit I've been enjoying it.
Of course, this is the corner where us guys get together and talk about all those things
that we probably wouldn't talk about in public, not even at the water cooler, certainly not the
lockers, so I admit it, I like and I hate the new scoring system though, it sucks.
You know, I just want the 5, 7, 5, 8, 5, 9, 9, 9, but all this different stuff, I'm very disappointed by them.
But yes, and Scott Hamilton is a dog. He irritates me.
Have you been watching? Let us know. Let me see now.
And audio feedback from a member of the female gender.
Hi, this is Jenny B, and I have a request for your next metro session moment.
I know you do a lot of bits of that shaving, but I was hoping you could do one on how
guys can get that sexy stubble look, because I think I speak for a lot of girls when I say that is hot.
So I love you, show, and hopefully I'll see you down in the next one.
Alright, thank you. Well, first of all, I'm still using my original marketing quality
blade on the M3 power razor. And I got to say the trick for me in making this thing really work is
short strokes. So not long strokes, but short strokes.
And the way to get stubble is just not the shave for one day. It's the way I always do it.
You know, it's all about the timing. That's really it. It's the timing of when you're going to shave
and what you're going to be doing and how you want to be. I want to look and how you want to be
represented. Sometimes I shave at night so that I have that stubble during the day,
but that's only when some really important is going down.
And Patricia does not like me with stubble, let me tell you. She hates it.
I mean, she won't let me even kiss her. So that's interesting.
So how many women out there do like the stubble? Let me know, stubble or no stubble.
And in what circumstances is stubble better than others? That's an example.
That's it for our Metro sexual moment for this week.
Okay, what's going to keep going? I haven't been a pretty good time here.
Mark Smith, I heard you're crazy. Urban do-st ideas in Delta Sierra Charlie 312 about the
possibilities for linking up audio video pictures and time codes to create as you put it some
matrix shit. And I thought I should point you to the in the direction of this IT conversations
podcast called particularly pen-up. Man, it's a big word for the for the podcast or participatory
pen-opticon. I think that's it. participatory pen-opticon by gemis, kais, oh man, this is not my
day. Gemi, kaisio, it's a mouthful in hook hitting. But it's so what you were talking about and you're
like this. It predicts the ends of secrets. Cool. And now that I'm reading this, I'm realizing that I
have not listened to it. I apologize. Shoot. Okay, I'm definitely going to listen to that.
Participatory pen-opticon. I think that's what it is. So this was the idea that you have all this
stuff stored by time code. And you would have some kind of Tom Cruise like interface. You know,
one of his futuristic movies where you can grab stuff and just say, okay, show me all the pictures
that took place at this very moment on September 11, 2001 as an example. So that probably,
oh, that's why I came up with it right from those from those new 9-11 videos that have come out.
Let's see. Well, shoot. Okay. Well, that's basically all I had. One is, no, I don't think so.
Okay, that's it. Still trying to get the the strategy gas together. This would have been a perfect
weekend. But Ron realized that it was one year since his father passed and in Jewish tradition,
the family gets back together. And I think they uncover the headstone and eat eggs.
And obviously, there's a lot more behind all that. And I'd love to be educated about it. So that's
there's a perfect audio comment if you think it was sending one in. And let's wind it up with something
nice from the podcast music network. Shall we? This is our go out, Pinden. Oh, yeah. It's kind of like a
hip hop of the local hunting marlin off the coast of Miami.
Bring bonnie and like I get the sodas, baby. For don't we have to get it lifted in back.
Fillin like a million bucks, large man fat, Grace Lack's greased up, nice light,
black veterans hooked into my sauce, like meckers. Bargaining in sauce that they match and be
both. I must have colored suspenders, see the images so far. I'm a nice guy with a little money
to spend. And I'm an advertising girlfriend sent to just me. Is that what you come through? Look at
your people like what you can do. Come full, rip into my check it like one. So is the
weapon no women like when you've come full. Missed control without toe, that's so new. Don't give me
your attitude. Your toddler could get it to. I stay back and smack and hoes and job in a few
good. I be this low. You should assume I'm a 90 pound board. I've been pimples in my room with my computer
from last every hour of the night. Spucking in a net beat. I'll sound a whining of fire. Can
you in a net wave or sound a whining of fire. Be sweet. Wait, I was only pretty baby. Let the track
pop. Fillin with them in a video like a back rock. I'm feeling a little so big and we're
talking about the match. We're all proud. We're all proud. We're all proud. We're all proud. We're all proud.
We're all proud. We're all proud. We're all proud. We're all proud. We're all proud. We're all proud. We're all proud.
If I had a million dollars, I might do this. By six mid-90s, gas-efficient lifts, the rest I didn't
invest in sweater vests and socks. And a bunch of bumper stickers for the neighborhood. Why
tate of ease? You can jog my chrome down west, but the heck of it. Don't whip it to see if you
didn't want to test it. Get ripped in a moped race, because I'm in it for the money in the
thrill of the chase. Relaxing on yachts that were bought by rich, drinking soda, pop,
goblin, thick strips of shit, klinger, like it. So we can read this every your time.
Treating women like they women, because the feeling is wrong, opening doors, using terms like
management, managing you, when we complimenting them whenever we can. I like your hands,
and the dimples on your knuckles hop, and high-five, I smile with sheets, y'all the way.
So the women in the back can see. You said it's only the wanderer, I think you want to know
that not a girl hot, if a lover rock, I'll be back and I'll knock your guns.
Wait, I was only playing baby, nothing track. If you don't admit them did it,
I mean you like a backdrop. I'm feeling no snow, make me rip up the match,
sweat, or a gal pimping, or a gal pimping, or a gal pimping. All smiles in and a lift,
it get dodge ran, back in the women like you are, teacher, making that you're making me crazy.
You ask me to make you think you're making me crazy. You're making me crazy.
So the women in the back can see. You said it's only the wanderer, I think you want to know
the money. You're hot, if a lover rock, I'll be back and knock your guns.
You've got a job and hell, come and let me dispel me. You've been a dang well in the
wash them and leave me when I say that. I meet a great MC, shake his hand and tell him to say glad.
Oh bad, why did we call the mix of today? I only take you when MC with me to take no comparisons.
You might find me American G.I. and you might keep me with a fly, why?
Can I try more? Can you in a blind, white, the bottle of the first league over? Can you keep
cool and cool sides with Marilyn all day? This evening, I'm attending a Kennedy Swarray,
like a nerd, a rabbit, you were burned, it's slated rug. Give me your shitting and let me see your jitter rug.
You are burned, it's slated rug. You please get hit me and let me see your jitter rug.
You're with me to take no comparisons, you can keep me with that. You can keep with this, you can keep with that.
You could keep with this, you could keep with that. You might think you're skimmed or we don't give up!
You could keep with that, you could keep with this, you can keep with that. You can keep with that!
I'll pick you up in six, let's go, that is it
You're trying to catch a glimpse of this day, that is it
I'll knock you up in so fresh, that's it
I'll pick you up in six, let's go, that is it
One really has to wonder what Argal Pimpin is, you know
Such a nice mellow vibe for the late Sunday here at the condo
Totally fits with my new IKEA candles
Nice lighting, but able to create with my corner lamp
Oh shit, I was so into that and it ended
Argal Pimpin, you can find on the Podsake Music Network
Work it is by the Argal Pimpin music.podshow.com
And let me see, something was gonna happen Monday
Monday we were doing a couple of internal demos
What was happening?
I believe I'm going to get my purchasing demo
On the Podsake Music Network, that would be very cool
I actually did want to just tack on one little piece to the Metro sexual moment
I'm not going to go back and play the jingle
But what I did Saturday is I cleaned up the entire condo
I was like Freddie Mercury in that clean video
I'm telling you, it was great
I was sweeping and I was vacuuming and I was mopping the floors
On my hands and knees cleaning the toilet bolt man
Guys make a lot of mess on the toilet bolt
And I'm careful
I rewire the television so I can use that
I don't need that transmitter anymore
So I can use my wireless whenever I want
Not just when you have to have no internet
One of the TV is on
I did the laundry, I washed all the sheets, I washed all my clothes
That I nicely put in my hamper
I am truly, truly a Metro sexual man
Thanks for listening, stay subscribed, will you?
Pod Show
Nothing says loving like Pod Show from the oven