This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want to hear content with badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code, get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie, three, seven, one.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I heard you got your hands back.
I'm hearing about your flight back from Rotterdam and your lack of power.
Take off, I thought I'd come out and save this track just for you.
Learn to crawl.
This feature on the Spider-Man soundtrack.
We'll definitely take you back to the headband's ball.
Rock on it.
Love, you can feel fine.
You can dance with a little twist.
Tell your brilliant right hand.
Play me forget the lyrics.
Can you feel yourself in my better night?
Would you leave me at the sorrow?
To walk right up to me.
Who's talking to me?
I'm already asking.
Tell me.
I'm already playing.
Play me, please.
Can you teach me how to fly?
See, I'm scared to die.
Only just becomes to learn to crawl.
Can you teach me how to fly?
Can you keep me in my way?
I'll be there all the crowd in my should fall.
I'll always feel.
I can feel it like the spider-sale.
I can memory in my mouth.
I feel like I'm falling in love.
The bottom's falling down.
Can you see what's up there?
But I'm falling down in the middle.
I can walk right up to you.
Can you teach me how to fly?
See, I'm scared to die.
Only just becomes to learn to crawl.
Can you teach me how to fly?
Can you keep me in my way?
Can you be around the crowd in my should fall?
Close to you.
No no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no
buddy how you doing welcome to the curry cottage thanks so much you know I was going to
tell you more Black Lab about Black Lab but I forgot and I went to the pod save music
network this morning and woo something going wrong there let me see if we're
back online by now that looked like we were having I think that we're either
being attacked or it could be that or maybe just a whole bunch of traffic
not actually it seems to be working okay now home let me just see if I can get
to the Black Lab page for a second yeah pod save music network was offline
about an hour ago hmm okay no it seems to be working now that's
groovy special thanks for that track guys are from Montana and they actually
were on I don't know if there's still on Geffen Records or not but you can
find it at Black Labworld.com or at the pod save music network of course a link
in the show notes today to to their site well it's not very nice today
it was raining this morning so I'm real happy that yesterday was the day
that we went flying and thanks for all the comments now this is not the
first time we've done a flying sound seeing tour on an airplane or during
training exercises and I'd say about 80% of the listeners really dug it a
small percentage thought it was boring you know but hey it was something
different now I have to say though I was severely disappointed by garage band
here's how I did it for those you were wondering I got my eye river this is my
standard sound seeing tour setup by the way if you're listening to serious
stars one or two you didn't hear it yesterday because it took so long to
headed in garage band that we had to run a best of Charlie because I just couldn't
get up in time for the satellite window to for the opening of the satellite
window even let alone the closing so I have the eye river I've got a a
wonderful Electro UHF wireless microphone set so I had the recorder the
I River directly linked up to the receiver of this wireless microphone kit
that wasn't the back of the plane in the in the boot excuse me though I wish
you could say senseo but we're all out I'm drinking tea and I had the the
microphone actually stick right into the into the left side of my of my
headphones I've got a a Clark headset so it you know you get a little bit of
the outside noise but you got a lot of the radio chatter and the intercom and
then so I got home and actually I just let it record from the moment I left
the cottage to the moment I got back so I had over four hours recorded and whoa
this is where it starts to suck first garage band has to import these files
now these files were about 250 about 300 megabytes in size I actually had the
chop up them up because garage band would after 15 minutes of importing just one
of the files because I split it up into two garage band would say oh AIFF what kind
of file is this and you have an abort button you know and no other choice okay
abort boom gone so I had to chop it up in the little pieces imported all and
please don't make the mistake of doing an apple apple key asking you a quick
save in garage band because that doesn't yeah sure it saves your file but it
actually doesn't mix down which takes another 10 minutes if it's a long file
or even longer so I'm very disappointed by the process I really do like the quick
ease of editing and the graphic overview that you have but cool just it's it's
no good so next time we'll do it in deck or audacity or maybe even
pro tools it was just horrible experience I wasn't done until about six
PM my time with with all of the editing and go anyway so then we then of
course I still had to do my mix down right which took another 17 minutes for a
49 minute show just crazy crap no good no good but it was fun I had a lot of
fun flying with Jason and I'm sure we'll be doing some more some more flying
with him he he knows the area really well which is what I liked and you know as
he was pointing out stuff and maybe next week Patricia now go have lunch on the
island of white it's only a quick 25 minute flight from here so more cool
aviation stuff I think I'd seen this before but Ruben sent me the link again
to arrowseek.com which is a eroseek.com arrowseek you can track I think it's
a combination of Google Maps I think they're using that API and some other
stuff and you can actually track commercial flights I think you can also
track general aviation flights if a flight plan has been filed so if you're
if you if you love what you were here in yesterday then you might want to check
that out because it's definitely for the aviation geeks amongst us and we're on
time recording the show today but I spent oh I'd say a good two and a half
hours and second life once again it's this crack it's crack for my brain I
can't stop I'm I'm really getting into this stuff and when I retire again
I think that if it's still what it is today I'm going to retire into second
life and I'm just gonna live there during the the work day or I'll just live
there you know I'll have my my first life but then I'll really just be living
in second life I bought a parcel of land a nice nice hilltop it's
some beautiful fur tree was it spruce trees it overlooks an ocean and I bought a
castle yeah I've been out on a splurge and of course you actually buy this
stuff you know it does cost money and I don't know if if second life takes a
transaction fee for each time you buy something from someone else but I think
I spent in total probably about 30 bucks on the land and on the castle but
boy it's beautiful and it has some lock features so you can't get in unless I
let you in so now I can start building and it has multiple levels it's got a
sun deck it's got you know cool towers parked my hovercraft up on the top of
the roof I'm so excited about this stuff and what I'm noticing is that it
really is just an it's an uh well first of all it's a platform because you can do
anything you want and oh shoot I got an I am from so I can't remember who sent me that
but there was actually you can listen to music there was a podcast that I was
able to listen to I don't know if that's coming in streaming or exactly how
that works doesn't matter it works you can sit next to someone who's
listening to something you can listen in with them and it just puts in a whole new
dimension it really removes the necessity almost for the desktop you know
having I am in a pod catch and all that stuff next to each other I just got to
say I'm very excited about about this it's it's cool cool stuff so look for me
Adam Newman and E U M A N N on second life and if you're lucky I'll invite you to
my castle hey Adam it's Steve runner from the podcast for
depudations the podcast for runners at steverner.com and I am talking to you for
mile 14.51 here in a closely Massachusetts and I am running the 100th
Boston marathon I am proudly wearing my pod show t-shirt and I'm getting a lot
of looks and spectators who are cheering for pod show that you're on the course
you'll hear people shouting words of encouragement and since they don't know
your name they'll look to your t-shirt to see how to identify you so I'm here
you a lot of go pod shows
also a few other runners who are battling these 26.2 miles have been asking me
what pod show is and it's really cool to be able to promote pod casting especially
my fellow New England podcasters who are some of the most talented content
providers out there myself excluding and of course as I run this I'm recording my
own podcast fitpidations and it'll be a pretty intense sound scene tour that
I'll publish for the weekend of the 22nd of April hey thanks again Adam for
everything you and pod show do for pod casting I really appreciate services
like the pod safe music network and podcast alley and while mine is just a
goofy little podcast but running it's risk takers like yourself who really
legitimize the media this week I'll not only have podcast listeners listen to
me describe when I'm seeing hearing and feeling as I run this the 110th
Boston marathon I'll have friends running along with me so the wins at my
back and I'm definitely appreciating the tail wins thanks again Adam pod casting
from the Boston marathon I'm Steve runner and I've got to run well don't
on yourself there Steve you're doing some amazing things yourself my
friend wow and Steve was actually bummed that he that he he didn't top his
personal best time of four hours and 23 minutes or whatever no kidding dude
you're talking while you're running it was so cool that he had the go pod
I just want to say one more time that we had offered to sponsor Steve during his
marathon run and he said no I'll wear the t-shirt you don't need to sponsor me
and so we have donated that money to the MS walk that the biddies and CC
Chapman are participating and maybe they'll do some sound seeing and pod casting
is well in fact I'm knowing them yeah they probably will I was cool man
that was really really awesome that was just and I can't wait to hear the whole
show and yes you're more than welcome to say tail wins in this case absolutely
man I think it's a first I don't know how many I mean well he's been doing
his his Steve runner dot com podcast for a while but a marathon will pod
casting that has got to be a first hi Adam hey it's Bill Ray from billraydrums.com
and I just wanted to call in comment on your recent Delta Sierra
little sound tour it was great I started the pod cast on a left San Diego for
ocean side which is about a 40 minute drive and as we're coming up along the
engine trouble that you were having my car was running dangerously low on
gas so it was kind of a good thing that I actually heard your engine
trouble and it was sort of a solemn reminder that maybe I should stop and get
some gasoline so that's what I did I pulled into a gas station filled up and then
after that all your problems started going away with with the Delta Sierra and
as just as I had pulled into my driveway that was when the pod cast ended and
it couldn't have been any better timing it just fit into my whole evening it
was great the whole drive home was a blast even though it was just a bunch of
airplane plain noise it was really really good so anyway keep up the good work
you do a great job for pod casting and furthering this new media and check out
my band hey wwwdwd.tubbyfunk.com or you can check it out on my space my
space.com forward slash tubbyfunk but also check out billraydrums.com
thanks so much man talk to you soon and happy trails bye nobody I'm just trying to
see here are you on the pod safe music network at all now that I can reach it
again I tried it earlier because of course sending in a comment like that
normally I would play it hmm no tubbyfunk on the pod safe music network
what's up with that you got it on my space but not on hold on maybe if I just do
tubby oh it seems to be slow still the system well when everyone wakes up
in San Francisco I'm sure someone will take a look at it let me see it's waiting
waiting for ever here we go tubby no tubbyfunk hmm okay dude get it up on the
pod safe music network it's it's where all the cool kids are yeah briefly about
what happened the engine trouble I of course I also what may not have been
completely apparent to you is that basically one spark plug was blown completely
shot to shot the hell didn't work at all and that's what we identified so
thank god for those checks that you do before you actually take off and I think
that this is the same thing that happened in rotted ab when we had to abort the
landing was probably the same spark plug so of course when I got home yes that I
called the wind commander said dude you know I've got a brand new engine complete
overhaul and and this is what's going on it said no this is really typical
by the way he did tell me beforehand that he was leaving the original spark plugs in
for the first 50 hours then you take them out then you put new plugs in and then what
happens is these new plugs start sprouting all kinds of pieces of metal and stuff into
your cylinder so you're going to take those out after 40 hours and then you put new ones in
again and then you're completely good to go so this is very typical behavior for an
overhauled engine apparently not very pleasurable I have to admit but it's not a it's not a
big deal although what is a big deal is these plugs cost about 20 bucks per plug you know so
400 bucks later then you're finally all set and everything's rocking it was yeah that was kind
of scary I think it was the other day I was talking about we were talking about boot camp
which is the application that apples now made available so you can run windows on your
Intel Mac and I and I was sure that there was another application which actually
let you run both macOS and windows at the same time but not in virtual mode but in native mode
I think at least that's what is now I don't have an Intel Mac so I can't test it out
Joel McLaughlin was kind enough to send me the link it's parallels.com
P-A-R-A-L-L-E-L-S parallels and if you check it out I don't know if they have a demo they have a demo version
yeah they have a download this will actually let you run windows and macOS on the same Intel
based Mac so you might want to check that out let me see if they have a demo it's pretty cheap though it's
50 it's 4999 and you can oh you can actually run Linux you can run macOS X and you can run
Windows and apparently all at the same time so if anyone wants to check that out let me know what your
experiences are because that would actually sway me to buy a new Intel what are they calling
Macbook Macbook Pro whatever the on the flying tip Paul Smith says Adam on that sound
scene to where you did yesterday I swear the air traffic controller sounded just like Roger Smalls
that must have been the fair oaks were I went back and listen you listen to yesterday's show again
I have to admit it did sound a little bit like Roger
I was coming on coming to visit you in London on the 29 but I hear that you change it now
there's some day and I can't get any more time up work is only change you can change everyone's
arrangements because I'll let's make you a scrapped book and some clothes that I want you to sign
desperately if you want you can come around to mine with rounds for cups of hours
I've got some fondant fancies and some jammy rings if you want to try some of those and it's not
nice and now Roger Roger I'm so disappointed that you can't make it and by the way I've heard
that there are now Roger Smalls T-shirts in circulation and that several of the UK podcasters
who will be coming to hang out with us at the draft and darts hang out will be wearing these
T-shirts and of course the question is is one of them actually Roger Smalls I doubt it but I do
like the idea so apparently Roger won't be showing up it's a bummer man would have loved to
have had you there and here's where it's taking place if you're in the UK you don't have to be a
podcaster now you can be a you could be someone who wants the podcast you could be someone who just
wants to hang out meet podcasters meet your favorite one there's a wiki or I think that's at
Britcaster.com there's a wiki and there's about 20 22 people signed up now who are coming so it's
this coming Sunday it's going to be in London it's at the brick layers arms and that's in
Fitz Rovia London you sure that's not in Belarus Fitz Rovia if that's Fitz Rovia
Belarus for the UK podcasters draft and darts so I think we have a room upstairs or in the back
and yes there are actually darts there and of course some draft to be here although we'll have to
learn how to drink it without the head and looking forward to meeting everybody there and Roger should
you be able to make it you know that you are more than welcome I just had a note here what's this about oh
this was Chris from tips from the top floor.com who was also on second life and he says I'm going to
just scan through this real quickly he says that he's actually even thinking about a way to
create podcasting a podcasting place within second life if you haven't by the way if you're thinking
what what the hell is all the second life stuff about go to second life.com download the it's the
application it's basically it's an adult game if you will kind of a cross between the Sims and
doom and your favorite porn game he was thinking of creating the podcast cafe or we could have the
pod recorder or these SL cast yeah this is good stuff keep it coming guys I'm I'm very interested in
what we can do on second life I think there's a lot of cool stuff that we can do and wow what a smart system
let's kick it up again hey I'm Jordan Serves and I'm inviting you to check out on song anglia
a new pod novel it's about rock and roll street racing and a what's the finder's weight what
the hell does that mean finding yourself bullshit we're gonna stick it to the man in this book
actually uh main character does find himself just a really long way from home all right let me tell you
well what the story is about so there's this kid Kevin Kevin Mitchell after stepfather dies
Kevin steals a really expensive guitar from his family's music store he helps on a plane to England
to start his life again which is pretty much just going nowhere he's gonna start a new he jacks
car soups it up and then takes his time starting his rock and roll career in a woke unsure of his location
he sends altitude and a slate buzzing noise he's sad of quickly but then relaxed his dreams
for slowly becoming true but he still fell apprehensive anyone would he thought with the main guitar
a bottle of bourbon in twenty three dollars he looked out of the small square window and wish
like hell he was back home he sat back and the captain announced final approach
so hit on overdone unsung anglia dot potomatic dot com and subscribe to the feed here unsung anglia
today I'm joining serves reminding you to keep on keep it on tune in the unsung anglia
at unsung anglia dot potomatic dot com today and thanks to Derek came out of the music later
yo buddy I'd love it I love it when you're reading yes kids reading is not a concept
and doing it through podcasting hey serious satellite folks uh the windows closing will see tomorrow
for the Friday festivities and those of you still hanging out here on the Charlie
pay attention or don't listen whatever you choose it's up to you do you believe anything is possible
we do where are flink we believe in an internet that's safe from virus hidden scammers
we're earthling we believe your personal information should be just that personal
and we believe your internet should be a friend not a fo where are flink make this smart choice
visit earthling.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you earthling we revolve around
you I'm pretty sure that may first we start with the new um the new earthling campaign and that's
going to be made by you yeah save the world wind valuable cash and prizes stay subscribe to the
source code for more information no DJ no lyrics no talking no blah blah blah just music music music
that's not
times we really need to explain what our show is about apparently dominion we do it's called kinky
sex radio how much more can we say sex radio is a discussion between an amateur and a professional
from the world of kink and bdsn hi this is professor tom and misjust dominion from kinky sex
radio join us each week for a frank honest and sometimes graphic discussion of sexuality outside
of the vanilla world we'll take your questions and suggestions on the how to's the what ifs the
wise and the whereforces so join us on kinky sex radio dot com uh guys subscribe
hi Adam my name's dorn um i am one half of a podcast based in kalimbasohio uh we are solely
and absolutely dedicated to the music or independent music based out of kalimbasohio uh that is what
our show is all about and that is all that we do um currently we have a battle the band's going on
this battle the bands is only musicians from kalimbas so the only people who are accepted are
kalimbasohio bands um we would like however to have the rest of the world help us decide and
fact i'm even begging please Adam use your great internet power to help us spread this great
music that we have from kalimbasohio oh you know that's totally something for second life i've
got to have great internet power that you can that you can buy from yes you can buy the great internet
power help us decide who is the greatest band willing to submit their music to constant kalimbas
uh but the greatest band in kalimbasohio secondly i was thinking or i was listening to your uh
show about uh well you were talking about the enhanced version of the i guess pod safe music network
and i was thinking it would be great somehow if say we could combine or not we if there was a
plugin or some type of a api or some type of a web app for people like me who have websites
and who have people submitting music to them on a regular basis it would be great if that music
was at the same time submitted to the pod safe music network that way they wouldn't have to
submit it on one side and then see oh hey the pod safe music network was suggested here
i'm gonna have to go submit my music somewhere else it just be nice to be able to have it done
all in one place you know that's a question and it's something that will bring up on the dev
cast which is for developers and if you haven't uh checked it out and subscribed yet yet to one
today actually i think will give you the chance to get into pod show plus and the uh and the pod
uh pod cast literally network and of course a part of that is now the integration of the pod safe
music network i don't you know first of all it would be a great thing for developers to work on
but i don't know because you know there's a lot of stuff that you've gotten you have to
well it's not it's not a hard process but you have to maybe you want to read through what it means
and so we could totally do it and we'll put it on the dev cast devcast.podshow.com
we'll throw it up in the air and see what people think um i presume that you have a submission form
of some sorts but maybe it'll just be easier just to link back and forth i don't i just think about it
but it's an interesting idea and it would be a great tie-in to slink all of these wonderful things
not only is there the band websites there's the website of my podcast and other music podcast
like it but then there would be of course links back to the pod safe music network
well those are my thoughts about that uh i don't know you've probably heard them all before but
you know hey throwing it out there and uh please if you have an opportunity stop by constant
Columbus.com give us some feedback let us well listen to the music more importantly and uh thank you
no thank you good thinking i like it a lot because tying all that stuff together is what it's going
to be all about i think and as you'll see what we're doing with the pod safe music network
we're really expanding the capabilities for artists and how any of they can really
use their their pages now to communicate well not yet but it's coming soon it's just hasn't surfaced yet
you can use their pages to communicate different ways you know to have feedback forums comments
you know all this stuff so we're definitely working on it and with the developers who are bringing in
i think that maybe we'll come up with some cool APIs and things that will be able to tie all that stuff
together so um yes they stay subscribed for sure hey great news we've got a brand new podcast on the
pod show podcast network i'm this is Chris from 64mm.com skateboarding video log want to thank you
and everybody else time at pod show for bringing me on board if you like to watch rad skateboarding videos
with big wheels loose trucks and fat coping then just dial us up in your favorite news aggregator
rss reader or through iTunes or just log on the www.64mm.com slash vlog skate films time
yeah well i'll have you know that i was skating when i was 12 years old so that's what 29 years
ago uh 28 years ago uh no 29 years ago oh man and i actually walked around with a little
tube of graphite my pocket you know whenever my trucks got kind of jammed up or cruddy because of course
it couldn't you know we couldn't really afford the good stuff and i was living in the Netherlands so we
had kind of shitty boards but i still have um scars on my left elbow on my left knee i had a
huge crash up once while we were on vacation in in Texas going down to hill and i tried to take
up the same space as a an 18 wheeler i didn't hit the 18 wheeler but i wiped out so bad i remember
my parents trying to keep me awake they were afraid i was slipping into a coma so yeah
no totally love your your videos man it's awesome stuff i haven't been on a board in a long time
but i wouldn't mind trying it again maybe we'll get one in the office in San Francisco we've got the
perfect floor for it i'm feeling that someone has got to have a board and someone must have
a skateboarded pod show HQ and we'll be going out um about four weeks or now i think first in
New York for two days uh Ron and I are speaking at some conference in New York and then we had
off to Pebble Beach yeah boy does life suck huh i've got second life but first life ain't that
bad either and then we're going to be in San Francisco for uh for the remainder of the week and
Patricia's gonna be in the condo so it's gonna be uh it's not just gonna be cool it's gonna be
yeah sexy because the condo is sexy and i haven't been able to share it with my partner yet
does your podcast sound like this make it sound like this take the audiobooks content crash course
in just one weekend learn the tips tricks and time tested techniques of audio professionals
the audio looks content crash course how did KQED studios in San Francisco for more information
go to audiolux.org that's audioleuxie.org and some very interesting news popped on my radar
it's taken a while and i i think they're ahead of Microsoft now but if you use Gmail and you use the
spell check feature which i use often because it does you know almost any language you can write in
it now actually recognizes the word podcast yes good job Google now give me more gigabyte
yeah hello Adam this is Tokyo Dan of what's happening in Tokyo
i listen to your DSC 369 today and during the metro sexual moment you talked about japanese
men and you also mentioned me so i thought i'd respond some japanese men have long been
metro sexuals long before the word came into use and some of them just can't pass a mirror
a window without checking themselves out although i'm used to it now i used to marvel at how
a lot of the young guys over here would be in the train facing the window and prepping shamelessly
you know the japanese are famous for detail well it applies here too they would spend an
awful lot of time on one little strand of hair making sure it stood up or laid just right something
also been noticing lately is that a lot of young japanese are losing that nice cool all of
complexion to a rosy ruddy cheek then slightly greasy skin complexion like so many Caucasians have
acne is becoming more prevalent and i blame it on the american fast food chains that have been here for
the last 30 years and the greasy food they've been serving and this has nothing to do with men
but you should see the young women over here lately they do their makeup on the public trains i mean
curling their eyelashes plucking eyebrows everything the older people really get upset about this
and i wonder what these young women would do if i brushed my teeth and shaved well on the train
i guess if i did i'd probably start a trend anyway i'm going to email you a link about the
cultural feminization of japanese men and i'll check you on dsc 370 so take it easy at him
yo Tokyo Dan thank you very much how cool is this podcasting you know we we hear about
japanese men becoming complete metro sexuals i put out the call on the on the Charlie and one day
later i get an answer and learn something that had absolutely no idea what's going on Tokyo Dan
thank you very much if if you have anything for the metro sexual moment just drop me a line
adamant curie dot com and curie's metro sexual moment yeah uh Jeff Smith i just i was going through
the Gmail as i was talking about that podcasting that had actually recognized that now in spell
checker and he said he had some new stuff up on his uh on his uh depository where he keeps all of his
stuff and at first of all i can see that he's he's going to work for other podcasters man this
is fantastic he's got uh what does he it looks like oops whoop that wasn't good didn't mean to do that
looks like he's let me see he's doing for all around the world podcast the real raising giants
did something for geek brief pod Asia and he's done these oh hold on a second sorry let's try this one
sensio uh wait there's more sensio uh hello there this is David Goodchild i create a
maintain the podcast known as kosher cast dedicated to the Buddhism of Nitrin die shown in
in which we study aspects of our practice including the mandala the gohons on to which we chant
and hopefully uh at some point in the very near future uh the recording of the entire collected writings
of Nitrin die shown in upon which we base our practice so people who interested in Buddhism
as featured recently in this particular podcast who'd like to know a little bit more or members
around the world who are looking for Buddhism transmitted in this fashion please come to go show
cast gosho c-a-s-t dot lipsin dot com slash r-s-s you can email me also a Buddha magnet
and gmail dot com thank you very much no thank you and i also want to thank Steve web of life
spring podcast and his entire audience for all their thoughts and prayers for my oops all their thoughts
and prayers for my mom i'm going to go visit her again Saturday so that should be fun my sister's
is going to be there with her son julia so we have a good time and of course so i'm going to fly
with captain dan and he's going to make me do all kinds of instrument rating based maneuvers as
i start to learn how to fly the plane completely in the blind it was so nice you know to have people
within our our small community really thinking about each other and it's really really appreciated
and i and i want to do is i'm going to send my mom the link i got her a fantastic
to sheba laptop uh why with wifi because her her office is up on the third floor and it's uh
it's a little bit of a chore for her to get up there and you know and also she needs you know more
than just the tv in the radio you know she needs the the her window to the world so i should be
able to listen to to your podcast and i'm sure it's going to make a big difference in our life so
it's really appreciated that you did that Steve and also again to your entire audience one more thing
from the Jeff Smith treasure trove
go daddy go daddy dot com has new domain names transfers and renewals as well as one ninety nine
by a long and saying in backording your domain name
it's a quick block who's taking a new website builder completely male at
can't start a web page for digging a masking total DNS control
hosting plans started three ninety five and you get twenty four seven maintenance and protection
and private domain registration to go that and get your business you follow more than two hundred
surchanges go daddy go daddy go daddy go daddy go daddy go daddy go daddy go daddy
go daddy go daddy come on daily source code listener enter code DSC one when you check out save
an additional 10% on any order go get your piece of internet and go daddy dot com
oh yes the fabulous Jeff Smith find him at Jeff Smith the Jeff Smith dot com g-e-o-f-f for the
and that's going to do it for today's daily source code tomorrow it'll be Friday we're going to have
a uh... you know the Friday celebration thank god it's Friday please send me in some awesome
party tunes in the pot of music network uh... that is assuming that uh... you can get to it
it seems to be okay now uh... so please send some stuff in i really want to jam it out tomorrow
it's been it's been a really interesting week also today later today we'll have another dev
cast which will put up online uh... this one will include golden tickets for people to come
into the to the to the beta of pod show plus in the pod cast delivery network it's intended
for developers that's uh... the audience that we'd like to bring in first because their
audience who can actually change stuff and make it better and if you know html and php that's
probably going to be enough if you keep up with the current web you know web stuff then you'll
be able to participate and help out and of course use everything and break everything yeah
mm-hmm love it
uh... so that'll be up later today that dev cast because Andrew grummit whose own mom
has had some uh... some health issues she's doing okay he's visiting her in Chicago today
so he's getting on our plane early this morning now since Andrew is still is doing all the
de-gap stuff he sent the instructions and it's not hard because we have a great interface
you know to uh... ticket to to put you know for the golden ticket campaigns
but uh... i i'm not comfortable doing that to be honest with you so
probably look for it sometime uh... early afternoon San Francisco time uh... by then
Andrew will be in uh... Chicago and we'll be able to insert everything get it all up and running
so we'll probably let in uh... and so i'm somewhere between five and fifteen developers on
today's golden ticket and you will know if you want it'll be very apparent
okay everybody uh... i'll see you tomorrow we're gonna do it we're gonna do it with uh...
the friday edition feedback out of the curry dot com you know is go to daily source code dot
com to get the latest lowdown and if you want to continue to battle it out over the
european union with com extra blogger well yes it's curie dot com
see tomorrow everybody bye bye
another pod show podcast stick it in your ear
get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery
network from pod show and limelight networks