Delta Sierra Charlie 355
This is the St. Patrick on podcasting.io saying hello to all my cross Atlantic family.
And now I'm looking forward to hearing Adam Colis.
And he's day broadcast on the daily source code.com.
Slauncher on the Hawkejack.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
The next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding.
Hi, Adam.
I'm Benastina Feliporic.
This is Connor Winichon from on Timmel.
The daily Irish language podcast,
wishing you a happy St. Patrick's Day.
And we're gonna go back to podcasting.
Adam from our fellow pilot.
You know Adam, drawing green WXGC.net.
Happy St. Patrick's Day from Dublin Ireland.
We're not always spent in our spare time writing.
Hi, Adam.
Happy St. Patrick's Day is Dermanyor from the Bit of Bondamy.
Happy St. Patrick's Day from Steve.
And Jesse?
Patrick's List.
Happy St. Patrick's Day from Francis Anger.
I take knowledge.
Happy St. Patrick's Day from Debtion.
Happy St. Patrick's Day from Leemwork.com.
Don't drink too much on Sunday.
Happy St. Patrick's Day.
And happy St. Patrick's Day.
Happy St. Patrick's Day from Tom Rathley of Polydys.com.
Happy St. Patrick's Day.
Hi, Adam.
This is Stacy Serenclare.
Podcasting, Dermanyor.
We're the older guys.
I was a little bit kind of my head.
I wished that I were dead.
But I don't think you'll ever let me be.
I used to be with this gold.
And if I air airs the gold,
I'll try and go him and leave him in the street.
And then he says to me,
I air you, you know he was bloody.
And he called that thing a higher.
But each time I share,
I know that I am learning.
He hides his hand while my friends are chanting.
Everybody know.
La Tira de la Tira de la Tira de la Tira de la Tira.
La Tira de la Tira de la Tira de la Tira.
La Tira de la Tira de la Tira de la Tira de la Tira de la Tira.
Happy Saint Patrick's Day.
Everybody know.
Good morning.
Let me back to that old man.
Where it leads,
I'll never know.
Take me back to that place.
I've been where I've said.
I've never been.
I can't swim.
So I'll fly as his belly.
That old man.
I know that I'm drunk and you're born.
Everybody's gonna get drunk and I'll eat.
We're gonna have to get by.
Everybody know.
When you take me,
Sing me a tune.
If I'm out of a friend,
This shot's for you.
Feel it burn.
This it goes down.
But watch your hours.
It comes another round.
Drink.
Go on and tell your dancing.
It's better to run away.
I know that you're drunk and you're born.
Everybody's gonna get drunk and I'll eat.
Everybody know.
All right, let me back to that open road, where it leads,
I'll never know, take me back to that place I've been,
Where it starts at all.
So, and...
God bless the podsafe music network.
There's something for every occasion, isn't there?
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
Happy St. Patrick's Day coming to you from Curricondo in Raining,
Northern California, from the Curricondo in San Francisco.
It's shit!
Oh, man, yesterday was just...
No walking home, that's for sure.
And, of course, I was bumming I didn't have Trinity with me
after a long day at the office.
Wow, what a day.
Oh, we'll be talking about that a bit about the Board of Directors meeting at the pod show HQ.
And, actually, the whole day was just one continuous doing stuff,
really, really busy.
It was around, I think, around at 8 o'clock,
that Ron and I discovered we were the only two people left in the office
and we were doing, like, an MP3 playoff, you know, where he play a song on his speakers and his office
and I'd play one a little bit louder in mind and back and forth.
So, after we got tired of that childish stuff, we decided to go home.
And I just collapsed.
I literally...
Came in.
There was something actually on TV yesterday, it was pretty interesting.
On TV, yes, they had...
Was it the business...
The Daily Business News Show or something like that on KQED
here, out here in San Francisco.
And I was watching that.
It was about earmarking.
Basically, the way that Congress can sneak in all kinds of pork barrel budgets into bills that are being passed.
It was a fascinating stuff.
Basically, we're getting ripped off.
That was nothing new there.
And I just collapsed.
You know, I had a pizza from the microwave.
And I was in bed a sound asleep at nine.
Only to be woken around 430 this morning.
And I was pretty much done anyway with sleeping,
but I woke up because I could hear music and like,
wow, what was the music coming from?
And I realized it was my serious satellite receiver,
which I always have tuned to channel 75,
which is...
What's the name of that channel?
It's like the...
It's the old people, so a channel.
Let me turn it off for a second.
Let me see if I can get it turned on from where I am.
Yeah, it's like the elephant's Gerald channel is what it is.
And so, what happened apparently is the power went out.
And it must have been out for quite a while because
the portage, which runs Casplaster, which is always on,
was identifying that the battery had run down almost all the way to the end.
You know, how PCs work differently from Max, right?
If you're Mac starts to run out of power and he plugging the cord
or you turn the power back on, then all of a sudden,
all the warnings go away.
On Windows, of course, they don't go away.
So I can only presume that it went down to low power,
so I must have been out for a couple of hours when it turned back on.
And that, of course, is what triggered the satellite radio
because it was on mute.
But then when the power came back on, it was no longer on mute.
So stuff to remember there.
Apologies about...
First of all, let me give some props here for the opening of the show.
You heard Mark Gunn with the leprechaun song.
From the pod save music network, music.podshow.com.
Some fantastic greetings there from some Irish podcast.
Some Irish podcasters.
Much appreciated that show to my Gmail this morning.
And the song was The Bloody Irish Boys with Drunk Tonight.
I'm not a guy who understands drinking a lot.
I think you know that.
I think we all know what my poison is.
Anyway, apologies for yesterday's show.
Got plenty of comments.
Like this one.
Hi Adam. This is Franco from Rock as the Italian.
I've just listened to the Charlie Free Five Four.
And well, you started as usual with your wonderful tube compressed voice.
We are all used to.
Like this.
Though I thought I'd share another beautiful San Francisco sunrise with you.
Not sure if we're going to have one today.
Wow.
That valve compressed sound.
That's very, very, very good.
Then you came through this FAQ stuff and then came out like this.
It works for me.
But if you have other thoughts about nose hair, please let me know.
And particularly, I want to know it.
Or even worse, like this.
Sticking your nose and you turn it and it kind of rips the hairs out.
No.
Oh, Adam.
I just hope I'm full.
I didn't hear to this.
I don't know why.
That would be very, very bad for your reputation.
Okay.
There's just one thing you can do to make me forgive you.
That is, give me your magic numbers for the TLA 552.
And that would be okay.
That's all for now.
This is Franco Faroma, Roccas Titania.
Bye bye to everybody.
Franco.
Thank you, my friend.
Very much.
Yeah.
I messed that up.
You know what happened is.
First of all, I'm not on the tube compressor.
That's at home.
So I appreciate the fact that you liked the sound that I started off with.
And then I messed it up because there were some really soft audio feedback comments.
And I was trying to crank them up on the mixer and unbeknownst to really me because
Hey, it's six o'clock in the morning when I do this stuff.
I totally overmodulated Casplaster and what Casplaster does is really starts to try and handle
the too much sound that it starts to compress it and then you get the nastiness there.
The magic numbers for the TL, was it a 50, 52, 50, my TLS, TLA, 52, 50.
I guess you want to know what my settings are.
I don't know if I could take a picture, I guess, of where the knobs are.
But I mean, it doesn't really give you everything you need to know.
I don't think, but I'll gladly do that when I get back home.
Some new about Casplaster, by the way, the new beta version, beta 61 is what we're at now.
61, my goodness.
Some really cool new features.
One of them is that after you've played something in Casplaster, it grays out.
So you know, it kind of makes it less confusing.
You can see where you are and it just gives you, yeah, it just really makes a lot easier.
But I just wanted to mention that if you haven't upgraded to beta 61, you might want to consider that because it's cool.
Very, very cool.
So yesterday morning, after I got to show up and out, I was at the office around 815, 830.
Board of Directors started to trickle in around 9 o'clock and we never had a board meeting at Pod Show HQ.
And it was pretty funny because normally these board meetings are held at Kleiner Perkins on the infamous Sand Hill Road.
We're all the big venture capital firms are located out here in California.
And they have a board room that is bigger than the entire condo, actually.
I'm not kidding.
It's just humongous and a table that goes with it.
It's a major penis extender board room.
So those guys are pretty spoiled.
And I guess we had eight, eight or nine people who come in for these meetings.
That was pretty funny.
Our board room, our conference room, is very thin and very long.
So you can fit about, I don't know, about 15 people in there.
But basically our conference room is smaller than most of the interiors of the jets of our board of directors.
So we had some fun with that.
And it started to stink up a little bit after an hour or so.
But it was a great meeting.
I didn't say anything.
I didn't mention the frog.
You know, yesterday we did the special board of directors secret word of the day, which was frog.
And at some point the conversation turned towards, I think it was length of podcast.
And then someone said, well, you know, I'm still three days behind on the daily source code.
And there's a lot of talk because it's exciting.
You know, people like to talk about the content probably more than about the business.
And I kind of said, oh, well, yeah.
Well, that's, and then all of a sudden, there he was.
Ladies and gentlemen, our true board of directors up a month.
Jerry Newman went ribbit.
Very cool, Jerry.
I think, I think, I think, I think she might have done a ribbit as well.
But that was way on the other end.
So two out of six.
Two out of six ain't bad.
But it was great.
We had gosh.
And actually this time, we put him to work.
We have all kinds of stuff.
We want our board members to do for us.
So it was one of the best board meetings we've had.
Showed them the pod show plus and the pdn.
And some of the shows that are coming up and some of the video stuff.
And it was, it was good.
And it's nice to, you know, this is not a report card.
We don't have to report to our board.
This is a report for us.
And that's why I enjoy the board board meetings.
You know, okay, here's where we are.
Here's how we're tracking against our plan.
Obviously, some of that has to do with finances.
But a lot is with, you know, just goals that we've set for ourselves.
And we're doing very well based on our plan.
We're very happy.
And then it's just like, you know, smart people in the room to bounce ideas off of.
And I got to say, it's, uh, I loved it.
It was a lot of fun.
Wow, yesterday we had a Metro sexual moment.
And, you know.
So the discussion, uh, was about nose hair.
That's a new conversation that we started up.
Normally, if I got responses, you know, if I get responses to a Metro moment or
an eternity, then I kind of delay until the next segment.
But I could not wait to share this piece of news about the new conversation that we started up.
Normally, if I got responses, you know, if I get responses to a Metro moment or an eternity, then I kind of delay until the next segment.
But I could not wait to share this piece of audio feedback when you're regarding the removal of nose hair for the Metro man.
Hey Adam, this is the friggin' satellite repairman.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, stop the music, stop the music.
I have nothing to do with satellites.
Not only that, but here's another news flash.
There is no satellite window.
I have a regular window with a screen in it that keeps mosquitoes out.
I do not wear a space suit.
And unfortunately, I am not waitless.
But that's not what I'm here for.
I'm here to speak about the Metro sexual moment on nose hair.
Cutting is definitely better than plucking.
But plucking does have a special place in Metro sexuality.
I will explain.
Every guy has had this experience of being with his gal.
When she's talking about some emotional upheaval that she's going through.
We've all been there.
We've all had that glazed look.
We've all had that secret feeling.
If I could only give a crap about this.
Well, here's how us Metro sexual pull it off.
When she isn't looking.
Reach up to that nose.
Grab a few nose hairs and he yank them out.
I guarantee that your eyes will begin to tear.
Add a few fake sniffles.
And suddenly you are sensitive.
It works every time.
Hey, man.
I sure hope Ross isn't listening to what you're saying here.
Let me just try that.
Oh, second.
Wait.
Good day, Adam.
It's Michael Smith from Indie Film Nation.
I'm excited about joining the pod show podcast delivery network.
Indie Film Nation is a weekly show about independent films and the process of making Indie films.
The show features the latest industry news and updates from the film festival circuits from around the globe.
And every show features an indebted interview with an Indie film maker or industry professional from the US that UK or Australia.
Hey, and I even get a chance to spin a couple of tracks off the pod safe music network on every show.
www.indiefilmnation.com.
Thanks, Adam.
Oh, no, no, thank you and welcome to the network.
Fantastic.
I love it, man.
So many people who are just excited about joining it.
So on the release schedule, the unleash of pod show plus and the pod show pdn.
Today, we're going to have our meeting about what exactly we're going to release with because we have of course
if we have a ton of features and things that we want to come out with right away and then there's a whole bunch of things we want to
show up some more.
We're stuck today, actually, is the, you know, the shoremail integration and we're talking about this that we can't open up anything.
Even commerce on the pod safe music network until we are able to send the registration emails back and forth.
God, I hate being ripped off like that.
So that may push it back a couple days because we really, you know, if the emails aren't working right, we can't do anything.
That is not entirely dependent, well, we have dependencies based upon the service and being white list and not definitely want to check it before before we go live.
But everything else seems pretty good.
Today we, we meet about the the unleash schedule, so I'll keep you up to speed on that.
And yesterday it was funny because, you know, there was all kinds of meetings that were being scheduled for today for Friday and I'm like, oh, no, I can't because I have, you know,
Cali's coming in.
Cali Lewis, our fearless leader from the geek intelligence agency and she's coming to San Francisco and she's going to interview me and I don't have time.
I want to spend time with Cali and I was a real dick about it, you know, but of course, who was the real dick.
Yeah, I fucked up.
Hey Adam, baby, it's Cali.
We're not going to have until Monday and I don't want you to go.
They think and I'm standing you up, but Adam, I have to admit, I'm a little stressed.
Oh, what exactly does a girl wear to meet the pod father?
Oh, what's the etiquette?
I checked Emily post.
It's not there.
Do I bow and kiss your ring?
Is it a European kiss kiss on the cheek cheek thing?
It's so intimidating.
And then what happens if your hair isn't working?
I'm worried you'll back out at the last minute and that's not good.
I fly out there and you don't show up.
I mean, I do briefs from time to time without my hair looking the way I want it, so you can't let that be an excuse.
Oh, and now you say you have questions for me.
Oh, what kind of questions do you have?
Oh, my God, am I even prepared for this?
Of course I am.
I can't wait.
I'll see you on Monday.
Oh, Kelly, baby.
Oh, yeah.
Nothing special.
But I have questions for you.
Oh, yeah.
You just have to wait.
I'm excited about meeting Kelly.
You got a couple of new fans by the way, who are on our board of directors.
Oh, yeah.
I'm looking forward to it.
Okay, so I have some extra time today to do things that I was trying to push off, which
I've probably got rescheduled for Monday, but Kelly, I will be there.
I promise you, some things happening this weekend.
Tomorrow morning, we're doing, I don't know if it's the actual first episode or if it's a run through or if it's a pilot or a demo.
But we have a game show, which we're working on called bone and tomorrow.
I guess we're doing the first, it must be just the first run through.
I'll let you know how that goes, but I'm really excited.
I heard something as a bit of the production.
It's going to be pretty fun with real prizes, valuable prizes.
Timothy Pilgrim sent me an email regarding that guy from Dark Matters podcast yesterday who sent you the voice message.
Well, that was actually was that two days ago, I think.
Yeah, you thought he said black skies as he signed off instead of the tailwinds bit that you aviators use.
I think he said dark skies, which alludes to the worldwide movement to limit light pollution that ruins the night sky.
The professional and amateur astronomers have a hard time looking through their telescopes.
Think about all that wasted light that is spilled up into the urban night sky and bounces off moisture in the air.
Hell, just driving to the countryside turn around and look back into the city.
You'll see what I mean by the glow on the horizon.
Okay, so that's Tim from the twisted wrist podcast, Dark skies.
Okay, well, Pilots don't like hearing that.
We don't like to hear Dark skies, and we don't participate in that.
That's for sure.
Let's see what we have.
Talked about the need for another developer at Pod Show, Brian Longest.
SB Super VP Executive Director, Muckity Muck of Operations.
So many emails that Adam I heard on the Charlie said you need to get this from me.
Here's some more verbiage on the person we're looking for.
So if you're looking for a gig and you are in the San Francisco area.
The qualifications are email authentication standards.
SPF Domain keys, sender ID and DKIM.
Delta Kilo, India Mike, whatever the hell that is.
Previous experience with guaranteed email delivery companies, MTA email application servers,
email delivery, delivery monitoring, and accredited sender programs.
Okay, if you fit that bill, we'd love to hear from you just send an email to
Adam at podshow.com.
Better yet, send it to Brian at podshow.com.
And we'll get to you ASAP.
It's cool, man.
We're looking for more people to get this stuff done.
And I guess that is pretty important for the unleash otherwise Brian wouldn't have mentioned it.
Matt Moran, aka M spoke.
Adam, you mentioned on DSC 353 that you'd be meeting the guys from British telecom.
It would be good if you could ask them how they square the idea of podcasts, online gaming, voice over IP,
music downloads with their very low bandwidth usage caps.
I acquired them on this late last year, and the truth is the customer has no way of realizing
the bandwidth they're using until they get a bill from British telecom.
BT or the old nationalized telecom supplier in the UK.
Because of this, they are the prominent ISP.
Basically, they own all the lines no matter which ISP you get your connection from.
You mentioned that these guys are important.
Yes, they are, but they seem to constantly be 18 months behind everything exciting that's going on with the net.
Well, Matt, it's funny you say that because I actually did talk to them about that.
Just so we're walking out the door.
Because at the end of the meeting, I said, hey, you know, I should tell you my British telecom broadband story.
And they were like, oh no, oh don't tell me.
I said, oh yeah, it was horrible. You guys sucked ass.
And I wound up going with easing it.
Because they gave me a dedicated line.
And more importantly, they gave me unmetered bandwidth.
And I could see, you know, a whole bunch of glances going back and forth.
And here's what they didn't tell me, but what I learned, if that makes any sense.
Apparently, they're not doing anything about people going over their limit.
And they realize that to be competitive, they'll have to do something with unmetered bandwidth.
Of course, this was all installed, you know, these caps because of peer-to-peer.
Oh, shoot. You know what, satellite folks, checking out the stars cast on serious channel 102.
PCH is next with Mark Yoshimoto Nemkov.
And I'll be back here Monday, starting at six Eastern three Pacific time with the pod show on serious.
Thank you all very much.
Peter, go ahead, close your window.
Okay, they're gone.
Yeah, so back to the British telecom folks.
Yeah, I think they realize it.
And I think they understand that they have to change that.
But this was really an issue of peer-to-peer file sharing.
And it's about the upstream.
You know, I think they're confused, but they really do understand that that's not going to fly.
And I said, look, you guys do like, what is it?
You can do 40 gigs a month total downstream and upstream traffic.
I said, I eat that in two days.
And I think that you'll see some changes there.
These were the, this was the CEO of British telecom broadband, the retail group.
So it is completely about about the stuff that is delivered to the home.
And we're going to see how far we get with them.
They certainly seem like guys and gals who were very switched on and very excited about doing something cool,
not just with broadband in general, but really with pod casting specifically.
So I'll keep you up to speed as we move on through.
Comic strip.
You can't finish up a week without a word from CSB.
Hi, Adam Kerry.
Imagine that there would be a mobile cast blaster, a program that would record podcasts in mobile phones and
PDAs.
And it would also upload podcasts to the server.
All this recording and uploading would be done inside of mobile phones and PDAs.
Well, at www.voysatom.com, you can already find a mobile podcasting program that is doing these things.
However, only for Windows Mobile devices.
Unfortunately, it can upload to one special server only and
user cannot change the server where to upload.
Now that you and your Jewish pal Ron Bloom have a company for but
Whoa.
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
Comic strip blogger.
The hell is that?
Oh man, you are over the line.
Now that's stupid.
Does it matter if my partner is Jewish, Christian, Hindu, Buddhist, Muslim?
That shouldn't matter.
Why do you mention that?
Now you start to show your true colors comics strip bloggers.
That does not vote very well for you.
I thought that maybe you could do similar programs like that.
Like that from www.voysatom.com.
But especially and exclusively for podcasts that are very networked.
So the servers of podcasts that are very network would be had coded.
I promise that absolutely for free.
I promise that I would help testing this program for free for you.
It would also be fun.
Yo.
Yes, I am not much wine Steve.
You know, comic strip blogger.
What the hell is that?
First of all, I don't care about podcasting from mobile phones.
I don't need those special servers.
You've said before, plenty of mobile devices can record.
There's plenty of applications that let you FTP file somewhere.
Or email it.
That's even though I kind of just like receiving it that way.
But yeah, it's like, there's all kinds that we don't need no specialized servers.
And she, I really, really appreciate your offer.
As long as I go by the server for you to test it for me.
Absolutely for free.
No CSB.
I think you need to think a little bit about what you're doing here over the weekend.
And think about the things that you're saying.
This is a little bit off color, even for you.
I'm not digging that.
Why ended up for today for the Friday, Charlie.
An email from Kevin Reeves, our buddy,
we've played many times here from the Pod Safe Music Network.
He has a contest which you can check out at Kevin Reeves.net.
And the contest is he's giving away his autographed Fender Squire Guitar.
Here's how it works, the person who pre-orders the most CDs of his new CD
to give away to family friends, co-workers, lovers, etc.
Will win Kevin's Guitar plus a mention in the liner notes of the album and on his website.
And he goes on to say, I love it when artists are marketing and thinking about marketing.
This would be a great for a company who wanted to get their website product to service out to a global audience.
All the information is on the front page of my website at Kevinreves.net.
Well, dude.
No problem, of course.
Happy to mention that.
And also want you to hear the new Kevin Reeves tune.
It's wasted.
Night of the night.
We sit here alone.
Here in my house.
We don't feel like home.
I have lost our control of emotion.
It is such a tumultuous ocean.
We have the day.
I've been life's pretty gay.
I go on my way.
It's just not the same.
I think I can feel and say the norm.
But there's always a calm in the eyes of the stars.
And to wasted night, y'all know where.
Now I'm cheering for all the reason.
It's the feeling I'm the same.
It's just a piece of waste.
Now you've gone away.
So night, I was right.
Just to get it all out.
Night of the night, y'all know where.
Well, I can't wait to see you face to face.
And I'm hoping to shove you in and embrace.
So wasted night, y'all know where.
And to wasted night, y'all know where.
Now I'm cheering for all the reason.
It's the feeling I'm the same.
It's just a piece of waste.
Now you've gone away.
Night of the night, I said here alone.
And you know it ain't right, being out on my own.
Out of Someday I'll see you but until then..
How I think about you over and over.
And no or no.
So wasted night, y'all know where.
And I'm so wasted now and now I'm away
Now I'm here alone and this nothing's left to say
And it's so wasted now and now I'm here alone
And now I'm here alone and now I'm here alone
And now I'm here alone and now I'm away
Now I'm away
So I'm known that I feel so wasted baby
And now I'm here alone and now I'm here alone
And now I'm here alone
Well, although it's not the intent of the lyrics, kind of fits with St. Patrick's Day.
Kevin Reeves, wasted. There you go. Ladies and gentlemen, podcasting, saving the world.
No, no, wait a minute. Podcasting. Save the world and win valuable prizes.
Hey, that'll do it for the source code for this week. Monday, uh, I'm still in San Francisco here
for the entire week. Lots of stuff to do. Lots of stuff to talk about. Send me your comments,
Adamaccurry.com. Uh, let me know what podcasts and music tunes you want to hear if you
discover something really cool. And, uh, check out daily source code.com. You'll be seeing things
change. I've told you, you know, I've said this many times. Um, we're in the middle of, you know, getting
ready for the unleash of our final, you know, final pod show plus product to product and the podcast
delivery network. And that's all on the way. Uh, so, uh, you know, feeds my change in, uh, an MP3
naming conventions will change. And who knows, we're going to happen. And, uh, hopefully emails will
start flowing over the weekend. But I'll let you know on Monday. So check that out at daily source code.com.
Take care, everybody. Have yourselves a fantastic weekend.
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast of
Libri Network from Podgeau and Lime White Networks. I love it.