This is MV from bedtime stories my kids love.
If you want stories that will keep your kids from going to bed,
check out Shadow Falls, and don't say I didn't warn you.
This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
Show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Get it?
Wow!
Dreaming in.
Player prop.
Delta.
Seerator.
With $1,500, views, many bads, draft them I have.
And music I can't find anywhere else.
Dreaming in about years, I must look at the name for the savings source code number four.
Well now, chocolate cake makes my poor stomach ache.
And all those pills are too much for me to take.
Don't like cocaine because it makes me all up tight.
We call for every for makes me feel alright.
First of all, method making you hide.
But I've never liked going five days without spending.
As it makes you say stupid things like,
We call for angry for makes you feel alright.
We call to take you high.
We call to take you low.
The beans are making fly.
All the bug will make you slow.
Shootin' speed balls will make you sell your stereo.
But you never heard of going in high.
For a cup of Joe.
You know the crank will lend you right in the crank.
Smoke that nasty crack and you want to rob a bank.
For get the nicotine again.
Bend the dream.
Try to call for angry for full, a real mellow scene.
You know the crank will lend you right in the crank.
You know the crank will lend me right in the crank.
my hero giving you the recipe for success. Coffee and Reaper. Not pod save yet, but Lincoln
the show notes to his to this song on iTunes. Go ahead and buy it. I love it. I hope it'll
be pod save very soon. Everybody how you doing. Welcome to the Daily Source Code coming to you
from the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Gilford in the United Kingdom. A beautiful day
and we're inside doing our stuff. Lots of stuff today. In fact, recording a show with Christina.
A new show, B.G. Blasts. So looking forward to that. And it's kind of running down stuff that
you guys have been sending me. All kinds of different comments. I think we're kind of over the moon
stuff now. Over the moon landings and still some ideas about how to make certain chemicals come
up with highly high explosives. I really love this educated audience. You guys are you sending
all this cool stuff that it's just so fun to try out at home or was September coming?
You might even want to try this at the podcast expo. Hey, their daily source code listener. This is
KFC the pod check. How many times have you thought to yourself? Hmm. I'd like to see my favorite
pod casting personality thrown out of a plane at more than 14,000 feet above the earth,
plummeting down to their depth. And then just kidding, we'll give them a parachute.
Let the games begin sending your names now of who you'd like to see tossed out. KFC at podcheck.com.
Make them smile. Oh, yes, we will. I love that idea pod check. Yeah, if you've never seen what pod
check does, go over to podcheck.com. She's got some awesome videos that she's been working on of
basically hot girls jumping out of airplanes. It's something about it that totally totally gets me.
I'm loving it. So yeah, that's a pretty good idea. Who would we? What podcaster would we want
throw out of an airplane? 14,000 feet? Hello. Hello. Hi, babe. I have more food. Yeah,
well, I just started the show. I know what I saw. Do you need me more food? Thank you.
Nice crispy. I don't want to throw up being thrown out of a plane. What? I don't want to be
go. Go talk in front of the microphone so we can hear your ass. What's wrong with the microphone?
How come it's not working? I don't know. I heard you and I said, you said, oh, so cool. Yeah,
girls jumping out of a plane. Hot chicks jumping out of a plane. Hot chicks jumping out of a plane.
Okay, well, that's the thing I don't want to do. No, you're not invited. No. No. I want to stay in.
So no worries, babe. No, okay. So damn. You don't even want to fly with me. Right, this I do.
Just not over the water. Well, yes, I will, but you know, step by step because
don't trust me. Well, years and years ago, I didn't even want to go in a little plane like you have
right now. That's a little plane. Well, I mean, you know, planes like that. I said, I swear to
everybody, I'm never going to go in a plane like that. And I'm doing that now, so I'm going to be a
very brave. Yeah, I forced him. I'm going to get out of here. No, no, no, it's great. But, you know,
step by step, it's quite a long journey. So we'll get you out of the plane soon with it, with a pair of
hands. And then after that, you're probably pushed me out of the plane. Oh, please.
All right, by hand, you coming on tomorrow? I enjoy your sandwiches. Thank you. You're going to come on tomorrow?
Yeah. Okay. All right, baby. Love you. Love you, too. Yeah, good.
Hey, this is Scott with the Alaska Pod Show Adam. How are you? I was just catching up on my
DSEs. And I was listening to Triple Four. I fully expect by the end of the year, the price of
a barrel of oil crude oil to go up to $100. Mark my words right now. I said it August 18th, 2006,
by the end of the year, a barrel of oil will probably be about $100. You know, there was a huge
disaster in Alaska. Did you know that? I think they, um, there's 200, 200,000 barrels a day
they were coming out of Alaska. Who's doing that, was it? I can't remember which company was this
only a couple, of course. So they had to shut down because they were leaking shit into the sound
again. And of course, Alaska can't handle that. If Alaska has another exon disaster, Alaska will be,
basically dead. Okay, I was pretty excited to hear you talk about this. The oil spill situation
actually took place in Prudobay, which sits just across from the heavily debated Arctic National
Wildlife Refuge or Anwar. It was BP British petroleum who had not maintained their oil pipes that
feed into the trans Alaska pipeline since 1992. As a result, this past March, the largest leak
in the Norse low production history took place as much as 267,000 gallons of oil
poured out of the pipeline for five days straight before being discovered. The moral of the story here
out of my think is if we want to take control of the price of oil, we need to take a firm position
with oil companies like BP. And we do that through voting, who we place in office in our
states to help advocate for oil exploration, but to be done safely. So none of this happens because
we are paying for this at the pump. And I was quite honestly shocked to hear that BP was involved
in this and that they admitted their fault. They market themselves here in Alaska on a daily basis
on television as a forward thinking company and as green as can be. A hundred bucks, a barrel
sure. This spill we had is going to make it very hard to do further drilling and exploration in the
Norse slope. And you know, I could go on here Adam. I don't want to take up too much of your time.
If you're interested, show 100 is a good place to start Alaska.podshow.com to hear more. Take
care yourselves and yeah. Folder. Of course. Bye bye. I'm so sorry I'm being very disgusting here.
I have my mouth full. I almost made it. Wait, let's do a jingle. I finish up my sandwich, okay?
Right, um, Harper's Bazaar. A lot of people sent me this has in their September issue an excerpt
from diary of a lost girl, the memoirs of Colah Booth, a former writer for the days of our lives.
Who claims? That's the soap opera, right? Who claims that she was once. Oh, so I'm going to be
in Laden's sex slave in this. Booth says that bin Laden was obsessed with Whitney Houston.
And desperately somehow wanted to arrange to meet her. In his briefcase, she said, I would come
across photographs of star magazine as well as copies of Playboy. I would soon come to the point
where I was sick of hearing Whitney Houston's name, Booth writes, hang the bin Laden would go on
about how beautiful she is, what a nice smile she has, how truly Islamic she is, but it's just
brainwashed by American culture and by her husband Bobby Brown. Oh, man. Why didn't Osama bin Laden take
Bobby Brown out? And then let me, let me would have been getting somewhere, you know what I mean?
Yeah, Adam. I have a question which may qualify for a tin foil hat moment. Well, hold on a second.
Let's do it properly.
And now it's time for the tin foil hat moment. All right. Better be good then.
I want those listeners of podcast who doesn't actually listen to them on a portable MP3 player.
I listen to podcasts on my PC. My problem is that I haven't yet found a player, which is a
resume feature. I listen to podcasts and music during my workday, and whether I'm listening with
iTunes or Windows media player, if I'm in the middle of a podcast when I need to leave my
computer at the end of the day, I have to write down what time code I'm up to, so I can continue
from the same point the next day. This obviously isn't a problem for three-minute music track,
but with podcasts of 40 minutes to an hour, I have to do this regularly.
So I'm asking you and your listeners, do you know of a player which you can resume where you left
off last time in the 11 MP3 file? I realise it's not the end of the world to have to write it down,
but it's literally the only thing that isn't perfect in my podcast listening experience.
Any pointers would be appreciated. As a listener, I would like to mention one of my favorite
podcasts, one up yours, which discuss his games on all platforms. I'm not a heavy game player myself,
but these guys obviously have a lot of fun arguing with each other, and it's entertaining every week.
Thanks for the Charlie. Finally. Scruncher.
I write Christine. Thank you so much. Well, I think it's pretty valid tinfoil had moment question.
Now, I believe that the actual MP3 format doesn't really lend itself that well to bookmarking.
Of course, there's the enhanced audio format from Apple, which I believe actually the podshow player
can handle. If you are listening to, you can actually listen to an AAC.
I'm pretty sure I'll have to check this after the show. I'm pretty sure you can listen to an AAC.
The pictures will show up and you click on the picture and I'll take you to the link of whatever's
linked to it. Any quick time-based format, I believe, like a quick time movie, so video will
you can enhance that with the URLs, with the bookmarks. I think we can handle all that, but the actual
closing of a window that has a player in it, and window being a web browser, and then reopening
that, and remembering where you were, I think that is a pretty big technical challenge, actually.
It would have to have some kind of cashed information on your machine.
Maybe, first of all, I presume anything is possible, but I haven't seen anyone actually do it.
So if you know a player that can handle that, or the system, and quite honestly, I would think
that we should be able to do that inside podshow plus, because podshow plus is pretty much based
around two forms of listening or viewing, doing that right there at your computer or subscribing
to a show or to channels of shows or collections of shows, whatever you want it to be,
so that those can go automatically to your hard drive or to your iPod, through iTunes,
whatever you need it to do. Let me know if you have any solution for that for bookmarking
with a player inside a web page.
Let's conclude this tinfoil hide moment.
Let's see three pieces of email from the inbox.
Oh, okay, this is a, this is from Brian No, from the, oh, have you ever heard the No Zone yet?
Brian Show? You'll like it. It really kicks ass. He sent me this link to a page on MSNBC.com.
I'll just read the highlights and anonymous senior British official knowledgeable about the
quote, Hair Joe bombers told NBC that there was no threat to airplanes last week.
The terrorists have been under surveillance for over a year, and the UK government didn't plan
on arresting these guys until it surveyed them a while longer, but moved when they,
when they did because of U.S. pressure in contrast to previous reports, the official
suggests that the attack was not imminent saying the suspects had not yet purchased any
airline tickets. In fact, some did not even have passports. I'm sure this is going to be circling around
the internet for a couple more weeks. Just kind of puts an interesting, interesting twist on anything
on, on to everything about how the UK and the U.S. are working together. Timothy Freywin
in response to how do you actually make liquid explosives that you can carry that could really
blow up an airplane? He says, dude, haven't you seen diehard three? All they need is what
it looks like a carton of Rebeena and a bottle of Avion and Presto, you got one hell of a bomb.
You know, the red liquid and the clear liquid that are completely safe until mixed together.
U.P. K.A. motherfucker? That's what Tim says. And this was kind of funny.
There's a, I love it when you, you know, this is something that you get in the radio industry
all the time. You get emails and all kinds of communication from PR agents who are looking to
promote, usually it's authors of books. And so the subject line at the email says,
a radio interview opportunity, experts to reveal the hidden dangers of my space.
So Kate Richie sends this to me. And so it's basically it's a pitch to get this person on a radio
show. So in this case, I guess you're sending it to podcasts, which I think is pretty smart.
67 million my space users are more at risk than they know. The new myspace.com the new myspace.com
social networking phenomenon has become the focus of recent headlines with an average of 250,000
new members daily. It is the latest internet fad already. I don't like the way she's communicating.
But what she's saying is that there can be at least 30 different kinds of spyware programs
that are on my space that obviously, you know, spyware can really mess up your computer.
And she's almost insinuating in this entire email that, you know, myspace might even know
something about it. And of course, there's this expert you can talk to about. I'm sure he's either
one of the, what is he prepping? What is his deal? Let me see what the guy's name is. The guy's name is
sorry. I'm so lame. I didn't have all this, uh, prep's. Schron. What's the guy? That's his last name.
Schron is a lively entertaining guest for our familiar typical computer geek. He's engaging.
Oh, going and we'll light up the switchboard as he educates and advises your listeners to
engage in safe PC actions. Maybe bullshit, but it'll be perfect for another tinfoil hat moment.
Let me know if, uh, if there is indeed some form of huge risk with the way myspace operates with spyware.
Accured.podshow.com want to mention that. We have a big push for this target cast. It's kind of a
new concept. I would basically call it a new version of an infomercial where we were totally telling
you about a product. It's about selling you a product. The main difference is we don't have to do it in,
you know, 22 minutes or 30 minutes to rush it in after hours time. We actually can do multiple episodes,
look at all aspects of the creation of the car. And you're more than welcome to interact. There's a
lot of stuff you can do on the, it's a podshow plus plus page. So you can do all the, the normal things
of reviews and comments. Accured.podshow.com. Go check that out. Yes, that I did a clue number two
of the, the promo that's a riddle. This English girl calling in, giving me riddles. So I can figure out
what, you know, what the name of the podcast is. I don't know, I'm just playing along so far.
It's been kind of fun. And she gave me a clue yesterday, which I wrote down. I think I wrote it down.
Yeah, um, the first letter. Uh, what was it? You know, the clue was what used to be called
fly boys and is now a popular movie. I couldn't come up with it yesterday. But of course, lots of
people figured it out really quickly. A-b-r-r. A-b-r-r. A-b-r-r. A-b-r-r. John Glasscock figured it out
said it was aviator, um, most of me I've heard, Daniel Smelter, aviator. And then Troy, was it Troy?
Yeah, Troy Rutter from Troy needs an op iPod says, hey, uh, a crap. That's not the one I wanted
is it? Someone actually, I thought Troy had figured out what, what it was going to be.
Shoot. All right. I don't know. This is, it's kind of getting boring. And especially because they
didn't send me a third clue today, hurry up. Well, yeah, I have no time for this.
Carl Dearshow. Adam, several times now you've given the voice mail line number,
omitting the one before the 201. So you're saying plus 201. What I really wonder about is whether
this important cabin Egypt whose country code is 202, who's wondering why he's getting all these
calls about scrunchers versus folders. Have you ever tried calling the number to see who's at the
other end? Okay. So Carl, who's a scruncher by the way, says that sometimes instead of saying plus
one 201 625 6357, that sometimes as a plus 201, which would be the incorrect number and you'd
be calling someone in Egypt. So why don't we see? That's a good idea. Actually, hold on. I got, uh,
I got Skype a clue up here. Um, can I? Yeah, so we can do plus 201 625 6357. Let's see if anyone picks
that up. This'll be cool. No, yeah, I'm using Skype. We'll just say I'm a scruncher folder.
Okay. There's your answer, dude. Doesn't work. But luckily, I do have a fix for this problem.
Hey Adam, it's Jack Pitts here over at the pitcast.com. Let me start by introducing myself. I'm a
father, a husband, and just all downright lover of podcasting in general. Recently a friend of mine
and I were having a discussion about podcasting and how he thinks all us podcasts are idiots.
More so us podcasts that play music. He also went on about rambling how he thinks that once our cities
are lit up with Wi-Fi that it'll make podcasting obsolete. Now, what does your take on this? Do you
think that podcasting will go away? Do to the capability that will allow listeners to be able to
just tune into streaming audio such as internet radio stations in their cars, on planes, on trains,
or will podcasting just take a different route. Anyhow, inquiring minds want to know and also
Adam, thank you for the pod show plus. It's just an awesome site and I'm really digging it and also
folder. Dara. Thanks, dude. Okay. So that's a very good question. We've talked about this before.
What you need is not just blanket Wi-Fi, which of course is going to happen. There's going to be
connectivity everywhere you go, except on airplanes made by Boeing because they stopped that service
for whatever reason. Because they say it wasn't working out. Well, I never got to try it.
What will need is new devices. And I think a lot of that is coming out of the cell phone industry,
but there's a real, you know, there's a real conundrum there, which I'll get to in a second. But first of
all, podcasting was based on really the advent of having a player that you could take with you
that you at some points would connect up to your computer. And of course, that happened way before
the iPod really had some critical mass. And in order to create the illusion of or the ease of
radio, I should say with some extra benefits, it was necessary to be able to get these shows onto
your device without you actually even knowing about it, which, of course, is what iPod are
lemon did and still does or juice does, what iTunes does. And yeah, so whenever you connect up
your iPod, just the charge it even, it's going to transfer all of that stuff. Now, of course,
you could be listening to this story on a serious stars 102 and thinking, yeah, okay, so what is the
future hold force? Where's it going to go? Where's all this technology leading us? It's podcasting
stupid. Is it dead? Will it continue to find out? You'll have to download the rest of this podcast
at dailysourcecode.com. It's a two for Tuesday. Stay tuned for more on serious. Again, here on the
podcast, we'll continue with that because of course, I know what's going to happen. It's it's very easy.
So let's just step back again two and a two years ago. We needed a way to create this
this ease of use. So people weren't just thinking about iPods as something from music, but
I waited a minute. Here's something else. And all I did is I installed some software and clicked
on a few things. And now, whenever there's a new program from this particular producer, it just
shows up onto my iPod. Done for two reasons. One, because bandwidth is still reasonably
problematic. Certainly two years ago, it was tougher than it was now to be able to just
get something on the fly. But you were still tethered to your computer. And I think that's really
where the revolution is is taking this entertainment with you. We've had mobile devices for a
long time. But what's the entertainment stuff? You actually have on these mobile devices? What's
pretty poor? It's piss poor, really. And the reason is because, in my humble opinion, the telco operators
have absolutely no incentive to start pushing large volumes of bandwidth around their network.
That, you know, they're happy they can handle the text messaging, the multimedia messaging,
and voice calls. They're just happy that they can handle all that. These things do get
pretty tax when, you know, at peak hours. So there's no incentive for them to start shoving all kinds
of data around their, you know, their precious networks. So, you know, the stuff that they,
first of all, they want to tightly control it. So, they know that means compression and
formats, et cetera. So, the gatekeepers of their own networks, which, of course, is fine.
And what do they do? You know, typical big company hooks up with big companies and Hollywood.
And so their repurposing stuff is ring tones, of course, which is extremely successful,
particularly the real ring tones. And they are offering some content now. But it's,
there's really, I don't think there's any money in it for the content producer. And, you know,
just doesn't seem like there's an economic model there that is sparking and coming alive.
Otherwise, I'm sure we would be able to see, you know, like MTV on our cell phone 24 hours a day.
It just doesn't feel like that's going to happen. Now, for independent producers,
I believe most mobile network operators want you to pay to get onto their networks. So,
they just really haven't quite figured that out. And there is something that, to be said,
for, you know, what, what that is their networks is not a part of the public internet.
So, of course, now we're seeing companies like Nokia come out with Wi-Fi built in.
Now, Wi-Fi is still pretty messed up, unfortunately. You know, the, just the whole authenticator,
so many, you know, the authentication methods and, excuse me, since I said, I'm willing to
buy a project throwing your favorite podcast right out of an airplane in 14,000 feet.
Check it out at project.com.
I'm sorry, distracted myself. So, some of these, you know, the cell phones with Wi-Fi.
I don't know. We've got to come down. It's got to come down to design. It's got to come down to
efficiency of these networks. You know, was it, why max may be a future possibility?
Whatever's going to happen, it's going to be all access all the time. And it's going to be fast.
So, you'll literally be able to navigate a menu whether it's an application on your phone or
through a web page or whatever it is, click on something and it'll just start playing because it'll
come in that fast. You know, you can do that already today with most home connections with the
PC and a web browser. You know, you click on something and pretty much the minute the first
couple seconds of data have come in that your player will start to play it, whether it's audio
or video. So, I think that's what we're going to go. And of course, everyone will be able to utilize
this technology. You know, it's, and you'll see that mainstream media will use it as well.
And they're going to get really, really smart. Look at what some of the big television networks
are doing already. They're creating their own little my spaces and YouTube's. So, it's going to
be, it look, there's not going to be a lack of content offered. That's for sure. But what's going to
be new and fresh and different? What are we going to like? And will we have any form of control
over putting that onto our cell phones? I believe so. But it's not going to be through the
mobile network operators. It's going to be through the device makers. Who, of course,
are constantly fighting with the operators. If a, if Nokia does something that the cell phone
operators don't like, they just won't order the Nokia phones. You know, that's a pretty heavy
incentive to play nice with each other. It's actually, it's kind of, it's kind of cartelish.
You know, it's kind of Microsoft-ish when you think about it. Again, that's not really my problem.
We just want to make cool stuff. Enable creative people to get stuff out there and distributed
as wide as possible. Hello Adam. This is Chris and Philadelphia of Egladex.com. Two things
for you on your riddle segment that you had. I believe the answer, the first letter would be A,
which is an article that is spoken often. I'm sure you got a bunch of calls about that. And
separately, I asked this back into why, but it's around July 4, and you know, have stuff kind of
get lost. Kind of got lost back then. But about this web 2.0, moving all the stuff into, you know,
the internet, all the kitchen of the flicker, all your stuff on the online work processors. The
question for you is, how often do these things fail? I'm not too worried about big brother looking
in my files, but I am worried about actually a data center going down and loops there goes
on my pictures or loops there goes on my art or music or something. Since you are a businessman,
assistant, and maybe know about these things, failing or not. Just trying to need a little more
confidence in how often these data centers fail. So hoping to get back to me, good show,
and one more thing, reformed folder. Thanks to you, Adam. Bye bye. Good to have you on board,
my buddy. Well, you know, this is kind of like saying, will airplanes crash? Of course,
they will. Will big data ware housing systems crash? Of course, they will. Now, I think it's really
becoming kind of you. Oh, there's that word. You big with us. It just really doesn't matter anymore.
You know, where the stuff is on your hard drive, where the stuff is out there somewhere on a
server on the net. It almost doesn't make any difference. Yeah, you know, big files, some files,
it isn't really appropriate to access them. If you have to access them a lot, you may want to just
be a tad bit faster on your on your local hard drive. But that's really the way you got to view
with these things are big hard drives with with the web-based front ends. Now, I store my pictures
on Flickr. Why? Because I know they have a backup policy. I know that, well, you know,
I know about their own by Yahoo, so I think they're going to be around for a while. Obviously,
the smart thing here to do is to have a backup, a local backup. But, you know, your question is
right. One thing I know is with my stuff stored on Flickr, my stuff stored, like Gmail, I use
exclusively for all my email, all of my audio and video output to create the final mixes and
creations, at least are stored on the PDN Pod Show Plus. Any one of those, of course, could have
some catastrophic event. But in most cases, well, we even had this a couple of weekends ago. Remember
when I something went wrong and there was like a basic delete Pod Show button and it erased
400 gigs of content. Well, of course, we had a backup. It took us, well, it took a crazy
ass a long time to get everything backed up. Back onto the hard drives, a restored, I should say.
But, you know, we have a backup because that's a professional facility. Now, do you create
backups at home? On your from your PC, you may, most people don't. I'm notoriously bad at it.
But I'll tell you, I've had zero data data loss from data centers and services on the internet
in the past couple years, in the past three years. But in the past three years, I have had three
computers, Mac power books I might add, have the drive crash totally and I've lost some actual data.
So that's kind of what you got to look at. But as I said, you know, this ties into this whole
everything connected everywhere. I'm pretty sure that we're going to be doing quite a lot of
storing our stuff in other places. The real clue is not about the backup policies. I'm pretty
sure that that's going to be okay. But how can you integrate it all? How can you take something
that you have posted on Pod Show and how can you add that somewhere else? Not just within Pod Show,
but how can you add that to the Pod Save Music Network and vice versa and how can you
move that over to my space? There's a lot of people working on these things.
I think it's a Mark Canter doing the people aggregator, which is a very confusing name to me.
But I think he's always talking about how we should be able to connect flicker to my space and
et cetera. And I'm keeping an eye on that because I love it. I love it when you can integrate
with other applications, other technologies. Even this said this video program that I've been using
to create a perversion for profit, my video podcast. I have another one almost ready to go by
the way. It's just a little more complicated than doing an audio podcast. There's a lot of
transcoating and conversions. And of course, the hair and makeup. But even that program, which is
a visual communicator studio. It has 15 different ways to output. So I'm already talking to them saying
hey, why don't you just make it so you can output right to the podcast delivery network. It's what
we call an open API. You can hook right into it and have your customers post it right up. There's
your storage, your bandwidth, your show notes, everything all goes. And it's done. It's published.
I love it when stuff like that is possible. So you all reminded me diligently that I was going
that I wanted to play Carmen Tyler. And of course Carmen picked up on it too. And I've been asking
for naked pictures. She sent me a picture, which is of her as Miss Louisiana. And this is with her
blue dress off the shoulder and a crown. That's great. This was what she said. It was like,
I want you to send me an email here. Was it like 10 years ago or something like that?
I don't remember. Carmen without a doubt is beautiful. She has a beautiful voice. She's uploaded
some new tracks, songs that were written by David Patillo. He wrote 10,000 Angel's cried,
which Lee Ann Ryan's recorded a couple of years back. But there's another song that she's had
up there for quite a while on the podcast, music network. Obviously, linked to it in today's show
notes at dailysourcecode.com. And it's a song that you never ever hear on the radio. You don't
only hear it in church typically or at a funeral, which is maybe why not a lot of people like
the song. But this is a song that's known the world over and people absolutely love it for
for different reasons. And maybe just, you know, it's not really like a real Charlie song,
but I'll just play it. And I want to accompany that with a poem.
Yesterday from my sister Willow and Adely, she sent me, she sent me this email and she said,
I was looking for mom's manuscript, Dead Grow's the Ivy. I didn't know that she had a manuscript
called Dead Grow's the Ivy, which by the way, Willow says she couldn't find. But she found this poem
amongst her files. And she also enclosed the original word document, which was created September
9th, 2004. So this is before my mom found out about her cancerous tumor.
So I want to share this with you because you guys have been along for the ride for the past couple
years. And I want to play the song by Carmen Tyler. Here we go. It's called Miss Me but let me go.
When I come to the end of the road and the son has set for me, I want no rights in the gloom-filled
room. Why cry for a soul set free? Miss Me a little but not too long and not with your head
bowed low. Remember the love that we once shared, Miss Me, but let me go. For this is a journey
we almost take and each must go alone. It's all a part of the master plan, a step on the road
to home. So when you are lonely and feeling sad, go to the friends we knew and bury your sorrows
and do in good deeds. Miss Me, but let me go.
Amazing grace, how sweet the sound and that saved our ranch like me.
I want was lost, oh by now I found that was blind, oh by now I'll see
you.
The remaining dangers, tolls and snails. I have already
caught his grace that's all my heart to feel and grace will lead me home.
I believe in death, and now, 10,000 years, but I shine in us, the same
way we've known. Let's dance, to sing, to sing God's praise, then when we first
we go, then when we first we go on, on the roof of the city,
rag!
One in the last time you actually sat in listen to that song.
Pretty damn nice. Thank you very much feeding rays amazing voice. Amazing beauty.
beauty. I still use it since I'm naked pictures.
Hey, that's it for today tomorrow, Patricia on the show.
Adam at podshow.com, dailysourceco.com, take care of everybody, see you tomorrow.