Delta Sierra Charlie 321.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
The next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic! It's Adam Curry!
Hey everybody! It's the start of a new week coming to you once again
from the Curry Cottage. We're back home!
It's Monday!
I love you!
Kiss me now!
I like stuff.
I see you on the street looking over at me.
I can't smell that desire. So I'm in over my feet.
I try and shake it down, but it's easy to shake.
How I feel every time.
I think I'm losing my mind this time.
It happens to me.
I'm falling deep for food.
But I'm still, but still, if I know my name
We are holding every people in this ordinary world
I am holding every boy extra holding every girl
This is gonna be nice to remember the day
When you came home and you took me away
Didn't you let you know that I still do this way
Every day, every time I still lose in my mind this time
That hasn't to me, but I was falling into the edge of you
But still, if I know my name we are holding every people in this ordinary world
I am holding every boy extra holding every girl
This is gonna be nice to remember the day
When you came home and you took me away
Didn't you let you know that I still do this way
Every day, every time I still lose in my mind this time
That hasn't to me, but still, if I know my name we are holding every people in this ordinary world
This is gonna be nice to remember the day
When you came home and you took me away
Didn't you let you know that I still do this way
Every day, every time I still lose in my mind this time
That hasn't to me, but still, if I know my name we are holding every people in this ordinary world
I am holding every boy extra holding every girl
This is gonna be nice to remember the day
When you came home and you took me away
Jack in the pulpit
Extraordinary girl from the pod save music network
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
Yeah, okay, I've reintegrated everything into the podcast complex beer
Here back at home, still rocking on cast blaster
And happy to have the Dishiba Portage, now a fixed piece of the equipment
I can just use my power book for all the other stuff I use it for
Because we can't have more than one audio application open at a time
More on that later in today's show
Lots to talk about some sad news to start off with
Which happened for a Friday after I'd already put the show up
I got a call from Patricia
I think I mentioned this a couple times that our dog was not doing too well
She was old Jesse
We had saved as with most of our, I think all of our animals
We rescued her from the dog pound in Jersey actually
And she moved with us from Jersey to the Netherlands
From the Netherlands to Belgium, from Belgium here
With, of course, all the issues of getting her in the country
And she had really just gotten old and was deteriorating
So we knew the end was coming
But she just couldn't hang on much longer
Patricia had to put her to sleep on Friday
It was a major bummer
One, of course, just because it's like a child
It's a big dog
We've never had to put one of our animals down
It was really big we've always had cats and smaller dogs
All of our pets are our children
But this wouldn't even more so I guess
And it was really sad that Patricia had
Of course, I was asleep
Hold a different time zone and everything
So she had to take care of that
By herself
Which really suck because of course I wanted to be here to support her
And I couldn't be and of course I couldn't say goodbye to my dog
So that was sad
But it was very courageous of Patricia to make the decision
And to do it, not wait any longer
And I think that actually
Jesse already appeared in one of Patricia's dreams
And that's, it's funny that way
Because I knew it would happen
Usually within three to five days after someone
Or something is passed on
They appeared Patricia's dreams
That's when she finally gets the rest and feels okay
Everything's okay
And the dog is now in a good place
But it was, especially after being away for two weeks
And it was almost home on my way home
And so that just, that really sucked
Anyway
So it's a lot quieter on the house
There was no Jesse to come
I mean, oh man, it's quite a great dog
This was the dog that
When we lived in Belgium and I had the helipad out back
Whenever I came, whenever she heard a helicopter
She was like fucking radar from Mash
She comes, here comes daddy, here comes the helicopter
And then as I would be landing down on the pad
She would run right up on the pad
And stand in between the skids and bark at the cockpit
And be like, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Welcome, how are you doing?
And then she'd wait until we were down
She'd never get under the skids
The first couple times she did that
Everyone was a bit freaked out
But we got really used to it
She just run up and start barking at the
This is a huge helicopter
And then once we were down and opened the door
Then she'd jump up and she said hi
She had a great life, she really did
So I feel good about that part
Okay, so what should we start with today?
I've done a little line-up of stuff
Let me see, let's talk about the pod safe music network for a little bit
Because a lot of people
You know, now that we're getting, actually I was going to
Hopefully we were going to start testing on Friday
And it's going to happen sometime this week
We wanted to have a few things
Just change for the flow of everything
To make it a little bit better
Remember, this is all beta test
And I'll talk about this some more
As we get through some of these comments
You have to understand that we're not like
This is not like we're opening an iTunes music store
Anything, okay?
This is just us guys trying to make something happen
Trying to make something work
And just like the pod safe music itself
We'll release early and we'll release off
And we'll make stuff better
And we want to hear your comments and your feedback
And we're really just working very hard on it
Let's get to some of the comments about the pod safe music network
Okay, Adam, this is town camp from St. Louis, Missouri
I just wanted to release some audio feedback
You know, I'm extremely excited about being able to purchase MP3s
And the free and clear
I got my first MP3 player in 1999
So I've waited a long time for this opportunity
I just had a couple comments on one of the briefs for you
First, I really like the locker idea
Where music that I purchased will be available for me to download again
If my hard drive were to crash or something like that
Also, you mentioned some stuff about social networking
I think it's a great idea. We really need to bring this in there
Rating songs
Seeing how many people purchase songs
Sharing playlists
Sending people recommendations
Maybe even purchasing songs for somebody else
So I could pay for it
And it would show up for my girlfriend's account when she goes to law again
Another thing
It'd be great if we get songs that are included in a loss list
Audio format
Like flack
Then if MP3 ever goes away
We'll be able to convert our songs into whatever the good code I get
Finally, and I'm sure you thought about this before
But I just wanted to say it anyway
The artist in me would really like it if
Artists could pick the prices for their songs
Give pot show a fee off the top or a percentage
Kind of like eBay does
And then they could set it however they want
I think that would be great for
Artists being able to set marketing strategies
And doing supply and demand for themselves
Anyway, I'm super excited for going out and purchasing MP3s
From Pod Show
Until the download their up so
Till then take care bye bye
Yo, okay, so a lot of things set in there
The first thing I'd like to address is
You know the songs that are in and because we're not a store
And don't charge a fee or make you go through aggregators like a CD baby or whatever
To get your stuff up there
It is going to be up to the artists themselves
As to what quality they put up and make for sale
As we go along, I'm sure that they'll be requests
To change stuff
Actually, I've seen some people who wanted to change their
They're MP3 files or put up a higher quality
And weren't able to, that's a comment
That obviously has been passed on to the dev team
The development team
And then this whole thing about pricing
This is very interesting, you know
Everyone's focused on pricing pricing
And I'm focused on how do we
Get people interested how do we get podcasters
And listeners more involved
And how do we get actually before we can even talk
About pricing how about we make this work
So people buy some stuff
Timothy Pilgrim says you set up the newest form
Of media for audio, you set up the pod save using that
Working, you still abide by the antiquated
99 cent model of business
Come on, you've got the opportunity to do something right here
You're on the ball, obviously
So why latch on this archaic system that our economies
seem to be hung up on why 99 cents?
Why not make it an even buck?
Okay
Let me just go through the comments
And then I'll actually address the pricing issue
Specifically
Um
Let me see, do we have another one here
Hi, Adam Steve from Feed of Clay here
Just a quick note to say one of the best benefits
For artists selling their their tunes through the
Pod save music network is the fact that unlike CD Baby
Or items music store and artists can upload single songs
For sale and not have a whole album finish
Yeah, I like that as well
You kind of played she said on
Show number 197 which is from an album in progress
And it's great because now we can start selling
Singles and get the music out there faster
The new album is going slow because I have two young girls
And I take a lot of free time
Dude, you know priorities first right
Prayers for your mom. Thank you mom's doing better
By the way, you know she's still in the hospital
And there's no date when they're going to let her out
But she is doing better she's uh she's gaining some strength
And Steve continues by saying
I can't say tailwinds because I'm not a pilot
But thank you very much
Yeah, you know I
I saw Robin from Inside Works who's also a pilot
For a major major
Airline and he agreed
You know if you're going to say tailwinds
You can only do it if you're an airman or an airwoman for that matter
Uh one other thing
Uh that was a good comment from Peter Yarros
Adam's so glad to hear that purchasing on PMN is coming along
Well, I worry about one thing though
ID3 tags when I get music off the PMN
I've noticed the tagging is incredibly inconsistent
I'm willing to put up with that as a podcast
Are getting a free track to spin
But as a paying customer I think I'd be quite frustrated
I hope that there will be some sort of ID3 quality control for paid tracks
Uh well
There you go
I think that that is definitely going to be
Up to the artists themselves to make sure that that is
You know that that's taking care of
Otherwise
You know the cost of we already have
You know obviously silver cost and bandwidth cost etc
Which is over-seable
And we have
Chris Bershier's full time on the podcast
Music Network
Michael Butler part time part of his time is spent on it
You know those are real cost and then
You know the only way I can see that happening
Is if we then become kind of a buffer zone
Where we ensure the integrity
And the quality and all that
And I just think that
That's going to take a too much towards a
A stringent store format
You know and it'll also really slow down
House you know this is the whole problem
With the iTunes music store is getting stuff up there
It takes a minimum of six weeks
Unless you go with you know people in between
And all this quality control
I think we have to learn how to do this ourselves
I really do
By the way Peter continues
I'm not a real pilot myself my father was one for many years
He commuted to work by airplane before he threw his back out
I flown a plane before one sort of
When my earliest memories of
Is of sitting in his co-pilot seat
Reaching my little feet out as far as I could
To hold onto the yoke
I was wearing blue socks
And I remember being jealous that my dad had more controls on his side
Good time
So if I may add him tailwinds
All right. We'll let you go. We'll let you slide on that one man
So about this pricing
Um
I don't like the variable pricing idea
I you know I can't really put my finger on it
But I think that when iTunes music store and the
U.S. opens up to variable pricing
Which is going to happen it's already happened
And in other music
iTunes music stores and other regions
That what'll happen is when something gets popular
And the price goes up
That's exactly you know and the music industry
Is said this you know hey popular songs
Should be charged more
Um what I'd like to do
Is
You know as we get into this beta
As we just you know start and work it out
I think what we should do is we should start
Just at 99 cents why 99 cents and keep it fixed at 99 cents why
Well
Yes
What?
You're dropping by
Your microphone is attached to the karaoke
So you have to go get your microphone
If you get your mic then you can drop by
We get you know the the AKG mic
No that's cool that's fun
Come on
Which is dropping by everybody
Cool
Okay
So back to the 99 cents
Um
My feeling is and
And we can change this at any moment
That's a good thing you know nothing's going to be set in stone
But I think let's just start with
Um with 99 cents fixed pricing
99 cents of course because it is become more or less an industry standard
Why go cheaper because cheap and first of all for the customer
Who's buying songs?
I don't think there's a huge difference between you
Do you really go out and search for the 89 cents song or the 70 cents song
And you'd be more apt to buy that
I think that doesn't make that much difference
You know when you're talking the difference of 10 or 15 cents to the
To the to the customer I don't think it matters
From a marketing perspective
It feels very much to me like if we do that
If you go cheaper then you just cheap in yourself
You know just hey
Therefore it may not be as good this is what a lot of people think as well
And why should independent music be worth less
And why should it be worth more you know
It's let's just keep it on par and we can always go back and
Turn to variable pricing if that's what we feel the market needs to bear now another thing
That just amazes me
Is the amount of
Questions I've received about
Splits what's the split gonna be what's the artist gonna get well?
I've been trying to find out
The AKG yeah, yeah, that's the one yeah, where's the
Yeah, that's because you're giving
Hold on a second
Hold on
Come on
We'll speed into a girl
Mess around here in the show now
Position that
Okay, are you there?
Oops sorry I have to turn on you. I don't hear you yet
Oh, well, you can do you hear me?
Yeah, you can turn that up. Okay, and how come
No, but do you hear me you don't hear me of course you hear me you have to hear me
No, oh wait a minute hold on hold on let me let me just change something. Oh, man
I didn't think you were coming by in today's show
No, I said are you coming sometime this week is what I said hold on hold on hold on
Do you have it now? Yeah, now you hear me? Okay, but now how come we don't hear you hold on
I've got that in
Yeah, yeah, here you baby. Hold on. Oh, I see what it is
How about? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, there we go. Okay, uh, hello lovely portrays
Hello, how are you dear? Uh, and a little bit better. I was a little bit on the
The weather yeah, yeah, but that's because you know you're puked
You have children you can't even second time in 20 years
Yeah, that I that I know that you have puked and you have puked and that's like dribbled really
It's dribbled
Sort of gagging yeah, okay, so yeah, that's when you have kids and they have things home
Yeah, Christina's home from school today
And it was exactly the time that our beloved dog I just told everybody what about
Yeah, so I was already upset my stomach was already upset
I told everybody how how brave you were to do to take care of all that stuff
It's just I have nightmares from it. Yeah, nightmares because you know I always send you or leave you with the dogs at the end
I know and I walk away. Yeah, I have to do all that yeah, but this is I'm Dr. Dad deciding to
Let a dog die, you know, deciding like this is the time you have to die now
It's horrible. That's why I can't understand where people kill other people
Or you know, yeah, but if you're but animals, but if you're if you were terminally ill and you're in pain and and you just want to go
That's something else, yeah, but you know just do you do want me to take care of you then don't you?
Yeah, okay
No, what were shooting healthy people and and of course now
No, I cannot imagine I was thinking about that because I had to do that and and what and of course in England
You know, they they
What is your talk of it?
Hunting they do a lot of hunting. Yeah, and I don't understand that either the hunting. No, I cannot
Just now I know guys who go hunting and we'll shoot at ducks in the sky
But can't shoot at a duck if it's just sitting somewhere looking at another
They've been staring to you. Yeah, but if I'm flying over those shoot him. Yeah, yeah, so it makes it make it make me think a lot about these things
Yeah, yeah, and because I felt that way and I noticed also because I was alone this weekend and you know as a mom
You think about a lot of things you're more worried because you can't share it of course
But you husband because he's not there and you have a teenage you're going in and out and I don't know do things
You feel very lonely. I know I felt a little bit. It's scary. It's so scary because
You hear a lot of things on the radio like children disappearing and
Yeah, and
Or you know they get killed or girls that are just disappearing or they find them killed
I and I felt by myself is the world getting worse? Is it me? No, the world's not getting worse
You're just hearing more of it. That's all or that's what I'm saying
We just know too much. That's all. No, you don't know too much. It's just we more signals coming in
Are the people getting worse? I'm not mean
We're finding out how bad people really are it's like this whole
What's Jack Abramoff in
You know the the lobbyist
Yeah, he's been giving money to to all these senators and congressmen. It's you know
We just we learn of we're not getting worse now
Meiner people have always fucked each other up
Is that so yeah, yeah, sure. I mean, there's just it's still so disappointing
Yeah, yeah, I don't yeah
Absolutely
And I'm you know, I'm old enough
Yeah, you know, I should be
No, I think I have to get used to this by now, but but
No, you know, I'm not you can't get used to
I can't get used to
Now see so these were my little I missed you very very much
Yeah, I missed you too. I'm happy you're home. Yep. Gonna be home for a couple weeks and then I'm gonna go to New York for a week
I know
And are you gonna come to San Francisco?
Everybody wants to see you. Yeah, you got to come hang out dude. Yeah, yeah, yeah, otherwise I'm gonna get some boyfriends
You know, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, and
And the weather's a little bit better than two days of rain while I was there two weeks too
But it's always it's refreshing actually. Yeah, now it was it was refreshing
Okay anything especially you want to talk about you just drop in just to say yeah
These were my the thoughts so
Now I'm well, we might as well just they're gone. We might as well just say right now that you know
So I guess we're filing the suit with these uh with the the magazines. Oh, yeah, yeah, that too. Yeah, so
I guess I can say from the court from experience
Yeah, that that's getting getting a little bit more meaner than it was in my days
You know, I say 20 years ago or you know, and you know, and then yeah, but though but
Yeah, but the line has been pushed. Yeah, yeah absolutely. Yeah, the line absolutely. They say that here over here too
the
Celebrities yeah, yeah, it's a bit meaner
Being a celebrity big brother is on here's been on for two weeks and it's going for another week
I guess and Dennis Rodman is in in the big brother house. Yeah, he's cool
Makes me look pretty cool. Yeah, he's very laid back. Yeah, he is a little bit impolite
Uh-huh
That's a pity because I always defend the Americans because say, you know, they are really nice
Yeah, they are really sensitive and
That's just the way they are and and and they've been brought up like this
And they're different and we are in Europe speak for yourself
That's how we are yeah, I'm saying you guys you we are you Europeans you're you're yeah
You're okay, I'm married to an American, so but I'm kind of European. I'm not so I always defend you guys
always because I've been there. I've lived there the wonderful people
Always helpful and always always humorous. Yeah, when they're said that really said more said than we are
And when they're happy them
Very happier than we are. It's different. It's more emotional. Yeah, and I could see that the difference in the in a big brother house the
Americans Tracy
The one from they watch and then it's rotten excuse me
When I burp what do you think of when I burp what do you think of? I don't even hear it
It's supposed to say San Seo. Oh, he's that's out. Oh, God. Thanks for listening
You don't know this now
So yeah, that's when I was there
That was I was I was telling about that that that he was very miss on the street, but he is impolite and and and it doesn't say please
And thank you. Yeah, I'm ashamed about that because it's true, but he's very very smart and he knows
Very well, it's going on and he is very nice and he is like trying to help everybody out
Yeah, he just does not say please and I just a big you know
Oh
What a what a body on that guy, though
I'm calling crap
Yeah, he was wearing a leotard yesterday. Did you see that? Yeah, he had something the basket was big my
Goodness hold on one second. I just have to let everyone know who's listening to this on serious
sidelight stars 103 that our sidelight window is closing Pacific Coast. Hellway coming up next followed by
Magic and Dawn and Drew and if you want to hear the rest of this conversation you have to download the podcast
That's the end of that. That means the sidelight window is closed. Okay. You like that?
Close
Alrighty
So that's it for now
Okay, there was
Let me see I was just going to do yeah, now I was just going to go a whole bunch of podcast and stuff so you may not care
Do you know what I'm saying? Yeah, kind of well like the BBC
You know the BBC released their numbers. Well, you want to hear for one second just listen BBC about podcasting
All right, it's really but it's really interesting just listen to the first minute of this and I'll tell you what's
About seven podcasting has it seems suddenly taken off
The chat first of all podcasting a suddenly taken off suddenly
I thought it was for a long but listen this is really interesting. This is from the BBC from radio for you
And familiar with it means letting listeners download a radio program or other audio material
Entrepreneurs or personal audio player such as an MP3 or an iPod
Because that this morning show that the today 10 past eight interview was downloaded over 400,000 times last month
Secondly among BBC programs to radio ones Chris Moiles show
But podcasting could change the face of radio you don't need a license to do it
So it's open to other media groups to challenge the established broadcasters
Okay, so now this is where it gets interesting
Because what is about to say he's about to mention all these podcasts that are really successful
But none of them are from the BBC. I'm really corresponding to our Douglas reports
First it was Ricky Javez on the Guardian Unlimited website
Welcome to the seventh
Ricky Javez show on
podcast
I'm Ricky Javez with me Steven Merch. Hello there and it was the conservative leader David Cameron courtesy of the daily telegraph site
Thanks for listening. I hope I speak to you again on another podcast before long two days later
It was Tony Blair podcast by the son which said it was a significant a breakthrough as the first Prime Minister's radio broadcast by Ramsay McDonald in 1924
This is George Pasco Watson the son's political editor with the Prime Minister Tony Blair in the heart of Downing Street
With the son's first ever podcast and then last Friday
It was John Snow in Channel 4's first podcast a documentary about cannabis in the young
So basically it's the newspapers. It's the commercial television station very important
They're jumping on to it and like I got Tony Blair the doing and you know and it turns out that Ricky Javez
Actually went to the Guardian newspaper. They didn't ask him he went to them and said you know, would you enable this for me?
So he's probably not getting paid for it or number it much
So I thought that was really interesting
That's very interesting, but even more interesting. They released numbers. Are they getting it? Are they do they?
Well, it's typical BBC. It's government stuff. Of course they get it, but they're so fucking slow
It's like all the newspapers are already doing podcast. Well, that's why he said suddenly
Exactly like a boy doing suddenly. So such a this out for
They're December download numbers which is how a lot of this is being done now. So the best of moils
446,000 times
Today the today interview for in the 13,000 times the documentary archive. These are ones you talked about now
There's just 211 times and then it really starts to go down
Like go digital is 59,000 times and
Let's see the letter to gait like learners
2,796
We do more than that. We do much more than that
This show daily source code does more than their number one show in a month
So I just thought that was
Really fucking cool
No, no someone wants gay like that's nothing wrong. I'm just saying that if you look at the
You know what we're seeing now is the guys who've been doing radio for a hundred years
All right, you know suddenly getting into podcasts
The podcast is suddenly great, but they're not doing better than us. So look we're just on we're in a freaking cottage here
And we're doing more down
Significantly more downloads than than the BBC's top show. That was kind of the point
Interesting. Yeah, that's very interesting. I only have more of this crap. Do you want to you don't want to listen to all this?
Love a why not? Okay, good. Well because that's all right. So now
Oh, this is good. You'll like this. You know
Clear channel in America. Yeah, they own thousands of radio stations
I mean really thousands of radio stations
Which is is in most people would say
Radio sucks in America because of companies like Clear channel that have bought all these stations
They put one disjockey who then you know is you hear them on three or four different stations at the same time
So it's become very impersonal. Oh, yeah, and then so this is the big powerhouse, right?
This is a billion dollar company
Listened about because and they
Business week with the Heather Green. She does a podcast. She's interviewed me as well
She talked to the guy who's responsible for all the podcasting over at Clear channel at this huge
Conglomerate who's getting into podcasting listen to their download numbers
It's taking an entire show and making that available later and it proves to be a hit right out of the gate
We realize that our listeners were absolutely wanting to get our
content on their own terms and podcasting made that available so we slowly expanded and we now have
80 stations podcasting which is just a fraction of our total number of stations
But we added a couple of stations every week and we've already seen advertisers ranging from the local Mercedes dealer and
Phoenix Arizona to a an Apple shop in
You know, Ohio wanting to be a part of this as well. Yeah, I wanted to ask you about that
You know how you're what kind of business model you're you're using here
But I also wanted to back up and and talk a little bit about so
I mean, what have you learned about this podcast kind of podcast? I mean from this kind of podcast
What kind of what have you learned download so we um in the on demand content at at large
This was something new for radio stations to go on air and take go to our website
And you can get this content 24-7 was a brand new experience and it resonated right out of the gate
We saw our strip performances our sneak peek cd debuts all reaching audiences of upwards of of a hundred
Thousand and some of them several hundreds of thousand in in a very short period of time
So the demand for this was absolutely there like within a month or two months
Yeah, right right out of the gate with podcast in particular
We started with handful of stations we're now at 80 over the course of the last six six and a half months
We've already seen more than six and a half million podcasts
Okay
In the last six six and a half months. Yeah, we've already this is a publicly listed company by the way
So I don't I don't think the companies like that typically don't give out numbers about how successful they are
So just to put it into perspective he says six six and a half months. He's seen six million
Downloads the million
The daily source code and Dawn and Drew two shows do better than that. Yeah, just two shows
So these are the big it's the big clear channel incredible and listen it's not it's not podcast
It's like streaming stuff you know
We start to try and quantify where that no he thinks it's a big number actually and where comes from check
Okay, you mean download it or it's a combination. Remember what I mentioned was out of the gate
We kind of did podcasting one or one if you don't really know what podcasting is you can just dream it
You can download an MP3 or you can sign up for Tora says feet in the beginning what we found was more people were
Either downloading it or streaming it, but since then the the number of
Sign-ups fractual feeds has has eclips the other formats. Okay, so what's important about that
Is what he's basically saying is that more people are
Subscribing to their podcast and that now the more people listen to podcasts through subscribing because
All these clear channel programs and stations are always on the home page of iTunes
Yeah, well we're seeing is
Actually the ratio there's less people subscribed and more people just clicking around and listening and downloading and doing from websites
etc. So all all their new signups are clearly coming from iTunes
Right, and we're still kicking their ass
Yeah, with a two show
They will now
The numbers
He's so excited
Exactly these guys think that their shit don't stink and when I listen to how
That's what I mean did do they have the ears open? Do you know probably not probably not but I was just so amazing like my god
You know don't undo and daily source code do better than the BBC
Way better than the BBC and better than clear channel so you know it's our audience
They're in their little you know the only little world so imagine if you count up the 20,000 podcasts that are out there
How incredible the audience sizes. Yeah, just humongous amazing
I've told you about
Roger
Roger smallest oh
Yeah, you do he yeah. He's the guy that that drives around gulford
Oh, yeah, you told me yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Some people call him a stalker
But I think he's just a sweet kind of yeah, be careful. Yeah, you want to hear his latest podcast
the email in him complaining. Now I think he should all do I do and which is fairly
file safe and means you can quit I choose completely and that's all we need to do
set curie.com at your home page. Now that way every time you use the internet you
be able to see if happens recorded in the initial or not. And the bonus of course
you get see us in space at the top of his website wrap the day. I've noticed
that if you look very closely he keeps winking at you at the no have a
snow animation or not. I'm myself staring at that rate is actually at work it's
quite mesmerising I think in a certain night looks a sort of see that I
could just be me. So much like it's paralyzed and trying to communicate through
blinking it's probably just saying something I sense they are in law
code just with his eyes and eyes and mouth. You see the good thing about
is that he's a full community case now that whenever enough to school
is learning there up the best other must probably competing in some kind of
national right thing. But you've already got to my head and I'm sure I'm not
the only fan of that and I've been emailing him almost daily now for well
of the ten months just with thoughts, dreams or their comments and it's just nice
to play them now and not just ignore them. I'm then actually my first email
back from that then which is really really exciting I've got to hear actually
I can't say I've been using kind of things out of them.
Yes it is from aden at carry.com and this is to Roger and the school
Smalls on mail.co.uk and it's me. The secret is R.E. Please tell me where you
let Arden and you simply replied what now question
up which I think it's the time and so well we would say this
he still wants to know more information about what it is
because he's always got time for his fans. So I've been emailing him pretty much
ever since with this information, he shares Files family and him and I think he's
even said a special rule in his team helps them anything for me in a special area
Anyway I'm very flattered that a nice man called Jasper is written a thing
song about me for the daily source code. The last time someone wrote a song about me
I was a college at the time and it wasn't a particularly nice song
Unfortunately there aren't many words that rhyme with smalls. I seem to remember
that the lyrics were focusing mainly on my testicles. I'll leave that for which he is
because I have to get to bed. So have a good weekend.
So stop. On his testicles.
Yeah because at school they made up songs about Roger Smalls and I'm sure it was like
has small balls.
Sounds scary.
I'm not too worried about him.
If you're not.
I got a lot to do.
You want to hang out? Welcome to stay here.
No, I have to sit down now.
You're rubbing your tongue.
Yeah.
You don't feel good.
No, I'm still a bit lightheaded.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
It's a combination of being said and we have a new sponsor on the network.
Accu view from the contact lenses.
Oh.
Yep. They're going to get the information. They're sponsoring.
We have those.
Yep. We're sponsoring a podcast.
Which is Heather and Janelle.
So they're spot. They're underwriting an entire show by these two girls.
And you can find that at download.accu view.com download.
Alpha Charlie uniform Victor Uniform Echo.com.
And I'm going to get some free shit from them.
I want to get some lenses.
But you know what the biggest audience is?
The biggest audience for contact lenses is young girls.
That's why they're sponsoring this show with Heather and Janelle.
Because they have bad eyes or to do that.
Just want to have other comments.
Well, no, but think about it.
You're 15 years old.
Yeah, you don't want to wear glasses.
Thank you. So then, you know, what what more important.
You know, once you decide to go with a brand,
I think you're probably going to stay with that brand.
Oh, actually Christina was mentioning that because she has bad eyes.
Yeah, she wants lenses.
She said, I have to go. I want lenses.
Mom, because there's so many times that I don't see it.
Yeah.
But she doesn't want to put her glasses on.
Well, if she did her show, I bet you they would sponsor her.
You know, I think they they sponsor some other shows.
I think maybe Martina show.
Yeah.
But this is exactly the member when we did tampax.com.
Yeah, yeah.
Same thing.
Yeah.
Young women make a very important brand decision very early on.
You have a basically a couple of devices you can choose.
Yeah.
Yeah, too.
So why don't you go sit down, baby?
Yeah.
I have to sit down.
All right. Thank you for having me, Mr. Gary.
Thank you, Mrs. Carl.
It's good to be back, baby.
Is tonight tonight?
I'm floating away now.
Tonight is not the night.
No, you're floating.
Yes, you're floating, dude.
You're useless to me.
It's no good.
I love you, baby.
See you in a bit.
Bye.
Okay.
Oh.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
Where are flink?
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers.
We believe your personal information should be just that.
Personal.
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe.
Where are flink?
Make this smart choice.
Visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
Hi, this is Tony Starkler, Denison from the Roadhouse podcast.
The finest blues you've never heard.
You know, for the past 11 months, I've had the great privilege of bringing you music.
You'll never hear on commercial radio.
It really is the finest blues you've never heard because the suits and corporate radio
programmers just don't see where blues fits into their playlists.
But here's the deal.
The blues are back bigger than ever.
And we don't need radio at all.
Who stole my radio?
Today we're about to break down the walls of our little shack by the crossroads
and make room for thousands of new listeners.
Today, the Roadhouse podcast is joined pod show
and the podcast delivering network to blow away any memories of mind-numbing corporate radio.
The Roadhouse and pod show.
Man, I'm thrilled to be here and I think you will be too.
It's an hour of the finest blues you've never heard.
The Roadhouse.
Look for it at podshow.com.
Yeah, was a congratulations and welcome.
Roadshow.
The Roadhouse pod show.
The Roadhouse podcast.
You know, it was actually was Ron Bloom who really last onto that show early on.
He loves that podcast.
And so I'm sure he'll be happy to see that you've joined the network.
Very cool, dude.
Welcome.
Something a lot of people seem to be asking with all these announcements of podcasters
joining the network is actually it's not even a question.
It's more like a supposition that I'm reading more and more.
You know, where there's a comparison.
I don't know how anyone can make any kind of comparison
between basically added insertion networks and what we're doing.
But that's okay.
But the supposition is the right word, I think.
What people are just supposing is automatically fact is when you sign with podshow
that sign your life away and your copyrights and they tell you what to do on your show.
I just want you to know that that is not true.
And as we open up the network to everybody and anyone who wants to come in and join
and wants to help build the network.
Because it really only works if we work together, obviously.
You'll see that your show is your show.
What you say is what you say and your copyrights are yours.
So I just want to put that to rest.
Okay, so Friday, I'd already, you know, so we put the show up,
but already gotten the bad news about Jesse.
And then it was off to Google for our meeting there.
And here's something really interesting happened where we just got on the freeway
and we're on our way to Mountain View wherever it is.
And I get a phone call on my cell phone.
So pick it up and hey, it's, I forgot his name so and so.
From Apple.
Yeah, and it's not, it wouldn't be weird for me to get a call from Apple.
So I wasn't quite sure what the call was about.
I said, I'm calling about your power book.
I'm like, oh my God.
You know, all this bitching and moaning about about that audio stutter,
it's paying off.
So I'm like, yeah, it says, well, how is it?
I said, well, not too good.
You know, the story, he said, no, why don't you tell me?
So I go, I launched into this whole story about, you know, about what was wrong
and the issues and what Apple recommended temporarily.
He agreed and he said, no, that doesn't sound right.
Only having one audio application open.
That's not a fix.
I said, no, of course it's not a fix.
And then it slowly dawned on me that this guy is from sales support.
But he wasn't there to help me.
He was there to try and sell me apple care.
Because he went through this whole thing and then he says, right.
Hey, I see, yeah, that's really too bad.
You know, we should have that looked at.
I see you don't have apple care.
Are you still interested in purchasing that?
I said, well, no, I'm not.
You know, I don't give a shit about apple care.
You know, the shit's defective.
You know, I shouldn't have to pay extra money to have someone, you know,
at the genius bar card, apple pro or whatever.
It'll care pro, whatever it's called.
I have absolutely no desire to spend more money on you.
And he was like, okay.
I said, so what are you going to do about the problem I had?
So well, you know, I can just make a mention of it here in some in a comment field.
And I really don't know who looks at it from here on out.
I'm like, dude, this is so wrong.
So there you go.
It's how it works, I guess.
You know, I've got so much to go through.
I'm just going to keep going.
If you don't mind, it's Monday.
We haven't, we haven't caught up in a while.
And this, of course, is our own little private podcast moment.
No satellite listeners lurking on us.
And I do have some more, you know, basic podcasting stuff to discuss.
I've got an email from the, the pod chef, gastrocast.
There's a whole long thing about iTunes and how is feed broke.
And essentially, he wound up losing listeners anyway.
He says, because of iTunes, libson, and some bad technological lock.
I am now down 600 listeners.
I'm on the verge of some cool sponsorship.
And I need my subscribers back.
Would you please mention that the pod chefs, gastrocast, is available in iTunes of people search for gastrocast.
Okay, done.
I hope that works out for you, dude.
I've lost so many thousands of subscribers through iTunes shit, too.
It's unbelievable.
It really is, you know, just, you know, all of a sudden is like,
a group 20,000 drop off, and then, you know, in the course of like a week,
you can see these people literally re-subscribing.
Some of that may have to do with the, you know, the five download limit rule.
Something I really believe Apple should change, because, you know,
I'm constantly having to re-subscribe to any feed that has more than, you know,
that, or that has a high frequency of output because they come through.
And if you don't listen or watch in many case with video cast, watch, you know, five,
within five postings or five updates, then it stops downloading, you know,
it's a pain in the ass.
I think it's a good thing to have as a, as a preference,
but it should be something you could switch off.
This is definitely hurting the experience.
Speaking of video podcast, I think we got a sponsor for yeast radio,
particularly for Madge Weinstein's video cast,
and we're going to try and spread this sponsorship out over,
and it includes an actual video commercial, the amazing.
I've no idea what Madge is going to do with it,
but she's also going to spread it out amongst some of the queue potters,
and basically the whole, the whole Madge community.
So it'll be fantastic to see how that works and what they're going to do with it.
And I hear these commercials, I'm not going to give away who it is just yet,
but here the commercials were submitted for Super Bowl,
but were rejected because they were too, too racy.
So right on, that's perfect for us, I'd say.
Hey, ladies and gentlemen, first time I think I've noticed the second time
I've done this on the cast blaster, but it is.
And I have some good news about the metro sexual moment.
This, you're not going to believe it.
This portion of the program will actually be sponsored.
It looks like this is sponsored.
It's really interested in underwriting the metro sexual moment.
So I'm down with that, and actually, I'm potting down the wrong thing.
Actually, the sponsor of the metro sexual moment is from a product that I use.
It's not a shaving, implement or anything like that.
It's nothing we've discussed in the metro sexual moment in our little corner here.
We're guys get together and just bring out some of our feminine side.
Corey Crook says, hey, Adam, I've been listening to your podcast for a while now.
Enjoy your metro sexual moment and all the things you were doing with potting music.
Never blah blah.
On the real me to the subject, I know you've had some ladies right in and talk about how they love the rugged
stubble look.
I always sport to look when I can, but it can only last for a few days, right?
Not true.
I was listening to the show when someone had written and recommended a wall.
Let's W-A-H-L-Beard-Trimmer with a short setting so you can keep the stubble look at all times.
Last Friday, I made my way to the store to see what I could find.
And in my amazement wall actually has a shaver that comes with a rugged stubble guide.
I immediately purchased it, works great.
I would recommend that to anyone that wants to keep the look all the time.
Well, I'd like to look personally, but as I think I've explained Patricia is definitely not turned on to the idea of stubble.
Hi Adam, right here with PathMinderCast.com.
Hey, I've been enjoying the Metro moment on your show and I've actually found it helpful.
I do have one question though about the facial moisturizer.
I looked at my girlfriend's bathroom cabinet and they've discovered several moisturizer.
I am anxious to try one, but I am afraid that if I start using moisturizers, it oils and then will increase my acne.
I am in my mid-20s and I still struggle with acne.
So should I stay away from these oils and creams and go with something so based?
If anyone has advice on what to do about acne, that would be great.
Thanks.
Dude, man, I'm so sorry that Patricia is not here anymore because she probably could have answered that better than I could, but I'll tell you one thing.
Soap is not particularly good for your face regardless.
So, you know, I think that you can probably pick up a moisturizer that will be specifically be for people with acne.
Those of the acne fate.
But we do have a lot of experience here in the cottage and I will get some information for you.
As you know, we have a 15 year old young lady here.
Let's just say, sometimes the mornings are not pleasant when something new has appeared that was undesired.
See, a David Shepel says, thought you'd enjoy this site, shavingstuff.com.
Yeah, I checked it out. Definitely interesting.
And Mark Bars.
What, huh?
Come here for a second. I need to do it anyway.
Yeah, it's a box for three.
For nothing.
And he just very upset.
No, that's realistic. Put the headphones on.
I got a guy who needs some help.
We're in the metro sexual moment here.
Okay.
Okay. Let's I'll play it again.
Listen to this.
Hey, I've been enjoying the metro moment on your show and have actually found it helpful.
I do have one question though about the facial moisturizers.
I looked at my girlfriend's bathroom cabinet and have discovered several moisturizers.
I am anxious to try one, but I am afraid that if I start using moisturizers, the oils and them will increase my acne.
I am in my mid-20s and I still struggle with acne.
So should I stay away from these oils and creams and go with something so-based?
If anyone has advice on what to do about acne, that would be great.
Thanks.
So this is about shaving.
Yeah, we've talked about you have to moisturize after shaving.
It's the hormone here on the metro sexual moment.
So you're the expert on skin care.
So what should you do?
He's worried that using moisturizer will be bad for his acne.
Well, he has a girlfriend.
If she has moisturizes, doesn't she know anything about facial...
Sometimes it's very difficult for men to talk about that with their girlfriends.
That's why we have the metro sexual moment.
If he has acne, really acne, or I don't know how old he is.
Could you just answer the question?
No, because there's different.
No, it doesn't.
If he has acne because it will never go away.
He doesn't.
And he has it for a long time.
Or is he just in his...
He's 20.
So he's still growing.
Yeah.
Well, he can go to his doctor and ask for a special moisturizer.
Special creams, special things for acne.
Very good.
But he doesn't have acne, but she has a little bit of teenage pimples and things.
Uh-huh.
There's very good stuff.
But you have to ask your doctor.
Dermatologist.
Dermatologist or your doctor.
Okay.
And there's always something for you skin.
But do something about it.
If you really are upset about it, do something about it.
You don't need to walk around with it.
All right.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Now, can you keep that dog quiet?
No.
I'm sorry.
I don't mind.
It's okay.
You didn't hear me complaining.
He's upset.
And he's a bit nervous.
It's okay, baby.
All right.
Thank you.
We all thank you.
Here at the Metro Sexual Moment.
And then finally, Mark Barr.
So I was once in the floor to Mallon Orlando.
And a lady at one of those little booths in the middle called me.
Usually, I say, no, thank you.
But this lady was really pretty.
So I decided to listen to her marketing story.
She asked me for my hand.
But just to use a nail buffer on it, make one of my nails really nice and shiny in seconds.
I got one of their nail kits.
And I used the buffer and cuticle oil every other week.
I work as a systems admin.
Sometimes have to help users out.
I did receive a couple of compliments from female workers when I was working on their keyboards.
Then my hands and nails are so nice.
So besides the shaving and moisturizer, maybe it's time to include the other body parts
in the Metro Sexual Moment.
The nail kits are sold on the internet.
Not sure if they are all the same.
With my experience with magift and swiss up beauty sensation are good.
This last one also has nice body lotions, but they smell a bit feminine.
So I don't use them on work days.
Man, I wish I could quit my day job in podcasts every day while smelling.
Yeah, of course.
Well, listen.
I too have manicures done.
And I haven't done it in a while, but I do take care of my nails.
And I found that it's actually kind of fun to go with Patricia.
There's a place where, you know, it's like a Korean nail shop.
And we both get our nails done.
And yes, you know what?
It is appreciated.
There's nothing more disgusting than having a cis admin with really cruddy, nasty ass fingernails,
touching your keyboard.
And you're right.
Women totally groove on a nice groom nails.
And I'm curious, Metro Sexual Moment.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's it for our Metro Sexual Moment.
What else do we have on the menu for today?
Using two computers.
I'm using, uh, I said the Mac to keep track of everything.
Okay.
A couple of audio comments that I wanted to get through.
Uh, let me see.
Let's try this one.
I add them.
Nope.
Just a brief correction on a statement you made while reading my email on DSC319.
Just to refresh your memory and that of your listeners.
I wrote about my having correspondent with Jody Shelton's manager, Audrey Brandt.
In one of my emails to her, I suggested that they register Jody at the PMN.
She did and that part of the reading was cool.
Then after that, you stated.
Uh, looks like he's, uh, thinking about doing a podcast himself.
Very cool.
Okay.
Ed from Ed's Mixbag.
Thank you so much.
Guess it was the way I signed my email with the podcast name at the end after my name.
But just one of the clear things up.
Ed's Mixbag has been a labor of love since October 6, 2005.
And to date, I've done 16 shows and plenty of promos for the podcast as well as for fellow
podcasters.
Sweepers and bumpers come to mind for Dan Johnson of journey inside my mind and also a joint
effort between myself and Kevin of the first person show.
The mic tech show also comes to mind for whom I've done a short promo or two.
My robot friend Sydney and Mary have also helped out and are expected to sound off on
rhythm angels rocking blast cast very soon.
I know Adam that you deal with so many listeners and podcasters that it's next to impossible
to be accurate all the time.
Hence this little audio comment.
And if I might, just one more thing from the shameless PR department.
Hey, Adam, this is Sydney.
Thanks for giving it this time.
If you would be so kind as to have to record listeners to eat and eat.litson.com
wherever you empty stands for it's next bag.
That's stuff you WW dot eat and eat.litson.com.
Thanks again, Adam.
Yeah, no problem.
Patricia just walked in during that little promo and handed me a bottle of a brand called
Dermalagica.
A skincare system resorts and developed by the International Dermal Institute.
There you go.
She said they have a whole line of stuff and that might be what you want to use for acting.
Oh my gosh.
Aren't we just on the tip of all the stuff today?
Hello.
He had him David Martin with Planet podcast down here in Los Angeles.
Long time listter.
And I think this is the first time I've responded to your show.
I think it was because your Friday source code kind of hit a nerve.
In the show you talked about a tabloid that exposed your family.
And I had a bit of a flashback.
Before I got into making internet applications and podcasting,
I was an independent recording artist.
And I had a tabloid publication.
Do a similar thing to my family.
And it was a horrifying experience.
Back then, all we could do is pick up our lives and change our personal information,
which I know you've had to go through.
Just want to let you know that we support you down here in L.A.
And I will personally take up donations to help fight these low-life bottom feeders.
What I'm more really impressed about Adam is how you spoke about these jerks on your show.
You didn't give them what they want.
And that was to have their name mentioned on your show.
I hope that everyone from podcasts,
to radio, TV, newspaper, all media takes a lesson from you.
Way to take the high road.
After all, one of my mentors once said,
let's let them be the skunk at the backyard party.
Keep the faith that, Adam.
We're all with you, man.
Thanks.
And it's really just true.
You know, I'm suing this magazine for a number of reasons,
but the one that I think is is most relevant is for using my pictures from flicker,
publishing them in a magazine with a reasonable circulation.
And these pictures are protected on the creative comments copyright,
specifically the share-like non-commercial attribution.
Non-commercial means is non-commercial.
Now here's what's interesting.
I have a lot of lawyers who have emailed me about this
and are watching this because I guess there hasn't really been a real case
that went to court, certainly not internationally.
You know, of an example like this.
And usually you hear about the other way around,
because oh boy, if I took a picture from a magazine and put it on my weblog,
boy, how long would it take for me to get my ass sued off?
Well, that would go pretty quick as you can imagine.
So the other way around should work equally as well.
But what's interesting is even though lots of lawyers are contacting me,
no one from creative comments.
And there's a, there's a Dutch chapter of creative comments.
And they're very busy working with Buma Stemran, all these other right organizations.
But I really hope that they do pay attention to this particular suit,
because this is going to prove that, you know, how it all works.
You know, it's going to, we have an capability here to put something into the,
into the public eye and ear that is very new and novel and people will be interested about.
And, you know, grab your chance guys in Holland with your, because I'm suing in the Netherlands,
not in the UK, some people thought it was suing in the UK.
I just hope it's not like, you know, I was in the early days when MTV.com,
I'd registered that.
That's a whole long story.
But of course, you know, when MTV, when I quit and when MTV decided,
well, let's sue this guy for that name.
I contacted EFF, the Electronic Frontier Foundation, specifically John Perry Barlow.
And they wouldn't help me. They would not fucking help me.
And I think I thought, well, here's, this is a huge domain, the first domain dispute.
What a fantastic opportunity to bring forward, you know, the value of it, et cetera, just,
all these things that we, whether I was right or wrong is irrelevant.
They would not get involved.
Now, it was so disappointed by that that I, I've never really looked at much the EFF is doing.
You know, it's like, all right, when it comes down to it, when it comes down to an individual case,
then you're kind of on your own.
So I'm hoping this is not going to be the case with creative commons.
And, uh, definitely hoping that word will get around and that, you know,
will, you know, people will keep their eye on it, because I think this is really important stuff.
Now, man, are we just making this a freaking massive long show or what?
Yeah, mine as well.
A couple more things before I go.
Darren Wall says, okay, totally freaked out here.
Listening to Delta Sierra Charlie 308.
Yeah, I've got some catching up to do.
Just after you read about the RIA going after the Girl Scouts, you said,
I Barbara, come on in.
You know, you can say something, you know.
This was just as my wife, Barbara entered the room.
She stared wide eyed at me.
I think she thought I wasn't Skype to get you getting my own private live,
DSC happy new year to the Curry crew from Darren and Barbara.
Thanks, guys.
Well, you know, that is freaking actually.
But it's cool.
Kind of cool that way.
Lots of people have asked me about Mark Hunter's Tartan podcast.
And, you know, has he left Podshow?
What's going on?
Yes.
We had brought him into the network as a part of the music podcast.
There's also also make up the podcast, the Podshow Music Review,
the weekly review of what the music podcasts are playing.
And he basically, you know, said that he didn't want the commitment anymore.
And he wanted to be let out of his agreement, which we did.
And I wish him all the best, obviously.
And totally get it.
Totally understand it.
And so I think his frequency of shows will be somewhat less than it has been today.
But I remain subscribed.
And I'll be listening.
And Steve Harris says, Adam, notice your cast blaster set up.
Doesn't include all the usual ID3 tags.
You wouldn't notice this if he used iTunes to subscribe because it
fills them in when you download.
But I'm a net news wire guy.
Well, I found out what that was.
I indeed, the under-describe in cast blaster.
There's a thing for show.
Now, I've been testing the new version, which works with the Podshow podcast delivery network.
And when you, basically, you log into the network with cast blaster.
And you can have a number of shows.
And it's a drop down menu and you just select it.
And then it knows automatically where to post the show notes and where to upload the file to.
Unfortunately, with all this testing and moving around, that got deselected.
So now I've re-selected it.
It's got the daily source code there in the show name, which should show up in the album field of the ID3 tag.
So thanks.
A couple other people let me know about that as well.
So I totally appreciate it.
Check this audio feedback now.
This is from the Podance.
Look.
Return one of my calls, please.
I heard episode 2019.
You drunk, man.
I mentioned our name.
It was in the United States.
It's a delivery network, partner.
Bro, I'm screwed.
I got so many members of the media called me over the weekend.
I mean, you read the press release for that thing yet.
Dude, I got to get, you got to put the no-dam announcements
rule back in effect.
Chris is on the road.
I mean, we can't handle this right now.
Give me a week to get the news out.
I mean, Jesus, killing me.
Seriously.
If it comes to it, I will...
You know, if you keep talking about this, I'm going to get desperate.
I'm going to go get Chris Rockwell and a bunch of Mexican food.
We're going to break into Trinity and do our own damn biodiesel experiment.
Huh?
How does that sound?
It's getting a little crazy on the Sunday night.
You're pit, this pissed.
And you better return a brother's phone call in a hurry.
All right?
That's Aaron Bursell.
The Pod Pimp marketing communications at Pod Show.
I mentioned that we've partnered with Limelight for the Pod Show podcast delivery network.
Okay.
I promise I won't talk about Limelight until at least next week.
All right.
Final thing for today in the hook a brother up category.
How do you pick my care?
This is a quick step aside from the exercise we'll actually show.
I just want to let you know about my band's tour.
The freak accident we're going on the road with...
Vancouver's removal.
Seven ugly guys and too many vans tour.
Here's our tour dates.
Thursday January 26th will be in Seattle at the sunset tavern on Ballard Avenue.
For right-day we'll be in Tacoma, Washington at Hell's Kitchen.
Saturday, January 28th will be in Richland, Washington at Ray's Golden Lion.
On Sunday we'll be in Portland at Syballas.
On Hawthorn.
Monday, January 30th will be in Salem, Oregon at SIP.
And we'll be playing with the Cherry City Deadmeats.
That's an all-age show, by the way.
Tuesday, let's see.
Eugene, we're playing at either the Samurai Duck or the Black Forest.
It's not sure which, with a band called Some What Envious.
And then we'll be back home in San Francisco where we'll be playing on Wednesday the first
at the elbow room with the fleshes.
This is the all these shows are with removal as well.
Then Thursday February 2nd will be in Berkeley at the Starry Plow.
That one's with Kyoto Nation.
Then we'll be Friday we'll be over in Sacramento at all the iron sights.
And Saturday February 4th will be the last show in Poin Arena.
And that's at the VFW Hall with Lockjaw.
So, if you're out there, come check out our shows.
It's going to be fun.
I'm also going to be doing extra super actual show updates.
The freak accident is going to be on its own feed.
Still not sure how we're going to do all this, but we're going to do it.
Until then, I say to you.
But I don't speak Chinese.
So I'll just never understand why you don't have any more.
And why your boyfriend wants to kill me.
Can I watch this film?
And for in the morning, when I have to kill work.
So I can't hear me on the plane.
So I can have a push to see.
Or not depending.
I'm always playing at the multiplex.
And what is playing at the movies?
I need a Chinese phrase book.
A bit of freak accident there and some tour date announcements from Big Mike extra super action show.
I played those because I realized that back in the day, even on MTV, we used to do tour dates.
We had the concert guide.
And he used to be a big thing.
Of course, now with the web, it's much easier for people to just look at that information up online.
You hear from it in a multitude of ways.
But I was kind of cool.
The big Mike went back old school.
So I wanted to make sure he got some good distribution on the tour dates.
And I think I might be able to catch one of the shows.
Actually, I caught kind of one of the shows at the Pod Show offices.
When was Ron's birthday freak accident performed.
On what we used to call the stage, what is now known as conference room too.
We put the wall in finally, so we can't have him perform there next time.
Anyway, if you made it through this entire show, and I think this is some sort of a record.
68 minutes.
I really appreciate it.
I hope you enjoyed it.
Of course, Patricia made it go long because she popped in, but it was cool to have her on the show again.
And I'll be back tomorrow with another daily source code.
So in the meantime, keep your promos coming.
Promos.podshow.com.
You feed back at americancurry.com if it all possible.
Through that feedback on a server and just send me the link.
Please.
And all the episodes updates in the place to subscribe.
Of course, a daily source code.com.
Take care, everybody.
See you tomorrow.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.