This podcast is brought to you by Potio and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 4 5 5.
Sometimes an atoms on a loan and he needs his love right there on the microphone.
So here she is, yes, the lady Patricia.
The say to have some better than one, and with this angel from above, there's nothing
that they both can't do, but make your wildest dreams come true, so grab your earbuds
and jam a mirror and let the fabulous show begin.
It's atom and Patricia, yes, atom and Patricia, atom and the lady Patricia.
All right, let's move on and say, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
If I lay up there, I am on the face
If I know I want to defy the obscene, I am on the face
When the tribe will pull me down, I'm on the face
What's where my enemy's right to go for my life?
Just lie, I'm on the face, I'm overguided
Just lie, I'm on the face
Even though I want to defy the obscene, I am on the face
When the tribe will pull me down, I'm on the face
If I know I want to defy the obscene, I am on the face
When my enemy's right to go for my life, I'm on the face
I'm on the face, I'm overguided
Just lie, I'm on the face
Even though I want to defy the obscene, I am on the face
I'm on the face, I'm overguided
Just lie, I'm on the face
Even though I want to defy the obscene, I am on the face
I love that song, my Jack Fashiack
I am not afraid, I'm on the face
I'm not afraid, I'm not afraid, I'm not afraid
I'm not afraid, I'm not afraid, I'm not afraid, I'm not afraid
I always sat you nice, do you make in breeze
You want the breeze?
No, just because
It's on low and you know what I know
This my present is worrying
Should you tell her yeah?
No, I guess yesterday
Oh, okay
Yeah
I have the portable refrigerator
Yeah, it's cool. But I've got to move it a turn it off
Yeah
We're kind of excited here
at the cottage because we're yet again we're in the game. We are we are jumping in and
just barely clinging on to the lowest rung of the property ladder by our fingernails.
Yes. We're trying to hop on the property ladder. Yes. Yes. So we've we've made an offer and I tried
something different. Did you notice I tried something different this time? I just said, what's
the asking price? Okay, that's my offer. I mean, what difference does it make? I don't want
to wait around anymore. So we saw a place yesterday. We drove around the town. It's
about 15 minutes from Gilford. Yeah. It's technically is Gilford, actually. Yes. It's the
council. We're all, we're all, we're all, we're all of Gilford. Yeah. We liked it very much.
We've been looking at the picture for over a week because we couldn't get an appointment to
go and see it. Yeah, that was actually amazing. What? Well, we called. Oh, yeah. This
is on vacation. It's a lady who handles this. It's on holiday. On the holiday. So we
have to just wait for a week. Can you imagine that is that is a British or what? I guess.
Okay. It's not very good. It could be almost Jamaica. Yeah, really. Next week, man. It's
our iri. Yeah. Not a problem. Yeah. I mean, happy if somebody is calling for your house
no, just wait for a week. Yeah. Okay. We're not in hurry. Right. So, but I think it's perfect.
There were so many signs yesterday that this house was perfect for us. It started with there
was a, that was the little statue outside. Yeah, the little lady that I used to have in my
bathroom. Yes, that our housekeeper broke. Yeah, with her butt. Yes. Her scrunchies, scrunched
used butt. Yeah. And so she had the exact same thing. It's more like a bust, isn't it?
It's a bust of a beautiful lady that actually, it's almost like she's holding a towel around
her. Yeah. Very chic. A very beautiful beautiful. And it was the exact same one. It was the
exact same one. And I. Oh, there she is. Who's who? I don't know. Let's just say hi. What
do? We're like in the middle of the show here. Hello. What's going on? Who is that?
Hi, Han. Hi, Han. Oh, that's Christina. Uh-oh. It's too early for her to, uh, what, what, what,
what, what, what, what's she, you know? Oh boy. Hold on, hold on one second.
Excuse me. Well, I'll tell you something. I'll tell you something. Yeah, that's good.
Completely. I can't love you too, bye. What was that all about? Did you tell
her we were doing the show? She is netter now. What English? She is. So people are on the world
understood. She's just went to school. Today. Yeah, it's the first day, first day.
Uh, today we're done at 230. What was that all about? We're glad they're gone. So why?
Why she done at 230? I don't know. Because it's the first day and um, and it's it would
don't want too much stress on the kids. I do remember I do remember going back to school
that first day is like, oh, oh, you could put them in just and it took forever. I know that.
But um, now can I walk with with Liz home and then she will be home on time? Okay. But
so she doesn't need anybody to pick her up. So back to the house. Okay, back to the house.
Back to the house. Uh, so there was this statue. It was the lady, actually.
Call it to say that her offer had been accepted. Yes. Yeah. Good luck. Well,
she said it was accepted for 50% already. Well, that means crap. That means that means
completely nothing. Well, she was very happy. Well, wait a minute. Let's talk about the rest of the house first.
Okay. You want to talk about just the other signs that we saw. Oh, yeah. So, so we saw that lady.
Yeah. Okay. I'll move down from that. And uh, the kitchen. That was one sign. The kitchen was good.
There were, oh, so in her kitchen, it was filled with Dutch Delft Blue Croquery.
Thanks. Yeah. Coquery. Yeah. Delft Blue Birds. Yes. Sports. Yes. Plates and salt pepper
shakers and her, her son and I think was working at Mike's bike tours in Amsterdam. Yeah.
Sound like a real winner this boy. Right. What she was really nice. She was like 60 in a yoga instructor.
Yeah. Yeah. And then we went upstairs and they started opening up. She said, you go ahead and
she took us through a little tour and then said, now I'll go and sit in the garden. You can do whatever you want.
Yeah. And you can talk about it without me. Right. So I'm opening up the cabinets and the
closets in the hallway and I opened up the linen closet and I was like, I was floored. I was like,
oh my gosh. It is exactly exactly like your linen closet, which let me just detail for you. Yes.
Every single piece of linen should be folded properly with the round edge, the folded edge facing
outward. Just in the shop, just like in the shop. Yeah. And she even had her sheets and towels
and things all tagged with little pieces of paper. It's just like you. Yeah. And it had the same kind of
nice warm, whafting, lightly perfume, soapy stuff. Because I put pieces of soap in between them,
just like my grandmother did. Unbelievable. I said, yeah. And towels also. Yeah. We had brown
rounded side out. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Fantastic. So. So I said, oh my god. That's my closet.
And what's really cool about it is, if I fly, uh, it's close. It's actually pretty close to
uh, to Fair Oaks. Yeah. It's about the same distance. No. Yeah. But maybe even a little bit shorter
because we're closer to them 25. Uh, but if I were to, you know, usually when we come in from big
and hill, then we go to Arkham, which is an unused airfield, which has a beacon on it. This is,
like, I don't know, maybe four or five miles from that actual beacon. Don't, you don't have to
go all freaky. I'm not going to tell anyone where the fuck it is. Okay. I see going twitching.
How do you think of stupid? That's what you get. Okay. So let's talk about this for a second. So
I told you that this, um, gossip TV show, listen, uh, in Holland. They call it show news. Yeah.
It's sort of entertainment tonight. No. It's, it's, no. It's not entertainment tonight. They wish it
was entertainment tonight. Correct. It's fucking crazy. Do not, I mean, that's no way. Mary Hart would
turn over in her grave. She's not even dead yet. She's not even dead yet. John Tash. I guess.
But, you know, so then they report on the whole Liam thing, which is to be expected, except. And
now, I want to say I still have not heard what they actually said. I've only heard it's second hand
from you from your mom, which I have to be honest, gives me a degree of accuracy of about 40%.
Well, I, you know, it was very easy to check that because I never told her anything.
Has nothing to do with that. It's just to do with the way your mom relates what she sees and
hears on television. Well, the information was enough. The way they said it, I don't care.
Yet that makes all the difference. But, you know, so now Patricia's like, we'll see now we can't
do. We can't talk about anything fun because of course they're going to use it on the air.
And I thought about this because we had a pretty heated debate about this. And I thought about it.
I said, you know, actually, you, you, it's your obligation to the independence of free media
and, and, and our comrades side by side, using mainstream media to further our cause
because it's only promotion. People are going to say, oh, that's interesting. They don't give
a shit about what they said. They're going to come and listen to the source to the real show.
Did they, I, I'm pissed because they didn't say daily source code dot com. That's what I'm pissed about.
But not about anything else. No. So, what, what I mean is see if I'm talking, you know, right now.
No, you're totally restrictive. You're stuck with today. I'm saying, no, no, no, no.
You feel like you can't say it. No, no, when I'm talking right now, I say the way I say it,
then I've said it. You know, that's okay. But that's the way I want to say it. Right. But
if Dutch people translated and do it in a certain way because it sells so much better if you say it in
different way. If you don't, yes, it gets and it becomes a different story. And that's what I hate.
Okay. If they would, if they, if they, for example, could hear us or let them hear us in the show,
the way we say it and we, the way we tell our stories, I wouldn't even mind. Can I just say something
until I, but I hate the way they, but I didn't hear the actual reports. So I don't know what they
twisted. And you know what, your mom already translated their translated version to her,
her language, which is a whole different thing altogether. And then it came to you. You didn't,
I mean, how many times is your mom said something? We went like, huh? Remember, it was like
Julie London. Julie London is dead. Because I can't stand it. You haven't gotten like what,
you don't know what really said. It's free because I know them and they always twist and turn
everything. So it sounds differently and it sounds more dramatic. Well, of course, you read the
fucking song every single day. You think that's not the same thing. I think about that. I know.
But, but I see, I'm like, wow, that's great. We made, we made this fucking stupid TV show.
I'm pissed off. They didn't tell people where they can go and listen to it because it's just more
listeners. Isn't that what it's about? Is it about growing the audience and and showing that you
can do different things? Well, they get the information for fuck them and fuck them. But you know
that normally when they call, we don't even answer. Because I know that. We actually don't want to be
in that show. If you answered, maybe they wouldn't take stuff from our show.
I don't want to answer. Of course not. Of course not. Of course not. I didn't even know this was
interesting. Did you? Are you kidding me? Wow, I wasn't thinking about it. Well, people like it.
This is what I keep telling you. People listen to the show. They like it. They think it's,
this Liam thing has been amazing. I don't even shit about the Dutch. Listen to this.
What is poor one? How poor Liam? No, no. No, no. He's going to be okay. Listen to this.
We're alone.
Obviously, I said daughter, daughter,
obviously she's a lot.
She always likes daughter.
You're daughter.
Her daughter, I said,
God, she's,
please, have alone.
She's, she's, she's looking guy.
You know,
second, secondly,
42, 42, as big.
Okay, so that was about the beginning.
Please,
I'm alone.
Leave from alone.
So, now the message,
I told you the Dan,
uh,
Dan played,
and of course,
Dan's a real nice guy.
Yeah.
He played like little pieces of it.
Dan is another friend.
Did he, I don't know if he played the whole show for,
uh, for Liam or not.
And Liam got really freaking out.
Yeah, because he,
Liam said, I want to,
I want to listen to it myself,
you know,
but what did they really say?
Right.
And Dan said,
Oh, good.
So he, um,
he played us for him.
And he was,
he was freaking out.
But what he doesn't get
is that.
The same thing that Dutch journalist don't get.
Yeah, don't, don't.
Fucking show business.
We're having fun here.
Come on.
We, we don't go on here.
I mean,
but we don't exaggerate.
It's a real story.
Absolutely.
It's the real story.
So the only thing he has to do is grow some hair
and get some new pants.
He doesn't understand our,
your way of talking probably.
You know, he thinks he,
he takes it very seriously.
Well, you may be starving.
If you don't know us,
you know,
it scares the hell out of you.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Because all the parents doesn't,
they don't talk like we do.
No.
Really?
Yeah.
Guess you're right.
We are too old.
Poor Liam.
Show is farce.
So.
But so now Christina said he might be going back to university
instead of going joining the RAF.
I don't know.
Excuse me.
That's what it does to me.
Yeah.
It doesn't mean sense.
You, you get,
um,
acid reflux from.
Oh.
Boyfriend reflux.
Oh, you see what this guy had to say.
It's a month.
About 42 is a special number.
Number.
Uh, absolutely my favorite number.
And I don't know it.
Almost every single thing.
She's going to link to number 42.
She desired.
I don't know why.
Any of these.
Um, also also.
Uh, do you know any good podcast and volume grid locks?
Uh,
No.
What was the 42?
Oh, we were talking about.
Because I, because I turned 42.
Oh, yeah.
At 42 seems to be a really magical number.
There's your number.
Yeah.
Something else about it.
What was up here it is.
Uh, yeah.
Listen to this one.
So this, that hitchhikers guide to the galaxy.
Yeah.
Which is a book and an audio book and a movie, which is very successful.
There, um,
you know, the master says the answer to all things in the universe is 42.
Oh.
Yeah.
Here's why.
Hi Adam.
It's cool for out here again from Somerset.
Um, I just thought, you know, 42 related piece of information.
Um, not many people know that.
Um, the reason that that was Adam shows the number 42 is to being the answer to everything.
Is because he was very fond of blend 32.
T from parents.
Blend 32.
But then 32.
Blend 42.
Um, and so when he was looking for an ultimate answer.
He's ultimate answer to things in the cup of tea.
So, uh, the ultimate answer was obviously 42.
Um, a little bit trivia.
Uh, happy birthday for the other day.
And also, too soon.
Oh, yeah.
It's gone.
Yeah, of course.
Oh.
Yeah.
That's funny.
So we should try here is Sarah's blend 42.
Oh.
It's the answer to it.
And I must say for the, for the, for the bridge, the, a cup of tea really is the answer to a lot, isn't it?
Yeah.
Don't you think?
I hear that everywhere.
Yeah.
I just do.
And I know it.
I've just miscarried.
Let's put a kettle on.
Let's have a cup of tea.
I don't just been hit by a song.
I think I'm dying.
Oh, let's have a cup of tea.
Put a kettle on.
Time to put a kettle on.
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
So it looks like, um, the 13th of September.
We have our, uh, we have a big announcement coming up here in, uh, in the UK pod.
So UK.
Oh, yeah.
So I'm going to stay until then.
I think Ron's coming over.
Nice.
And then that's not sure yet.
But that we're going to find out today.
And then after that, I'm going to go back to San Francisco for a couple of weeks, two weeks, probably.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, how long have I been here with you?
I mean, too long.
I hope.
How tired are you of me?
I'm going to get the fuck out, right?
You're like, can't hear him out of here.
Oh, God.
Please.
So I can have a, a, a decent night's sleep.
Sleep.
How about the other day when I was an answer day when I stayed overnight?
I slept like a bed.
I don't know what it is.
I can tell you, you know, we need to get a place that has my own bedroom.
We don't have that in this new place.
You turn off your brains and sleep like you're in a coma.
But it's like, almost, I get everything.
It's almost you give it to me.
Maybe you should lay a little bit further away.
We need bigger bed.
Or like, a bigger bed is a pretty big bed.
Yeah.
I know.
I'm about a piece of lead between, between our heads.
So the, no brain.
So whoa.
So have you seen my mom yet in your dream?
No.
Because that's usually been dropped by.
Every being, every living being that, that passes humanoid.
It says good morning or whatever drops by Patricia's dream.
Yeah.
And it's.
They shoot, they shoot, they should say goodbye.
You know, on a certain level, they, they come and say goodbye.
So that you can let go.
How long does that take typically before that happens?
Well, it doesn't, I don't know actually.
Sometimes it goes real fast.
And I think it depends on the person that they don't want to leave yet.
If they struggle.
That's my mom.
Yeah.
I'm thinking she wanted to know.
No.
So there's so many things she wants to do probably.
So when we spread my mom's ashes at a whole calm.
It was a group conversation.
And Willow said, you know, mom promised me a sign.
Yeah.
And she said, you know, because my mom, our mom, got a sign.
It was promised a sign from Whiffy.
Yeah.
My grandmother, our grandmother, which he never got.
That's what she thinks.
Exactly.
And so Willow's like, I want a sign.
It has to be something really good.
It's, well, you know, maybe you have to define what that sign should be.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Because it comes in two ends, right?
Things happen.
And, and you know, why they happen?
And you never think that that's the sign.
You know, so Tiffany and her boyfriend.
Yeah.
We're on the beach in central pay.
They went away for a couple days.
Yeah.
And they're on the beach in central pay.
And a huge butterfly.
I'm showing you how big it is.
Oh, my God.
Right.
Settle down on the beach on the sand in between them for about a minute.
And then flew off into the distance.
So they thought that was a sign.
Yeah.
And Willow's like, that's not going to be enough.
She's like, I want the book to fall open to a page that has something in there that
Mom would have said.
Okay.
And like, oh, okay.
See, that's better.
That's a better definition of what the sign should be.
Yeah.
But sometimes you are somewhere in something drops behind you or something moves.
And you think, oh, it's the wind.
Oh, it's this.
Oh, it's the cat.
You don't know that.
Right.
Yeah.
I've gotten so much.
Because if you think something, if you see something really special,
you probably don't believe it.
I've gotten so many voice males and emails from people who see butterflies and have to
think of my mom now that I've programmed everyone to do that.
It's really cool.
The butterfly.
Yeah.
One day I'm going to do a whole butterfly tribute and play all the stuff that everyone
is sent to me.
Now, I call it the butterfly.
The butterfly.
Yeah.
Instead of the butterfly.
So anyway, so we put the off in on the house.
Yep.
And then the Linda.
Linda.
It's Linda.
Hello.
The real estate.
We'll call us back today.
Yeah.
She said, well, she was, what was she?
She was.
What?
She was nervous all of a sudden, though.
Well, the lady was actually in shock.
She was in shock.
And she's been on the market for a couple of months.
I have to discuss this with somebody.
Yeah, she's a winner.
I'm going to do this.
And how quickly I have to do this because we're in a hurry.
Yeah.
So she has to check if the people.
So the people who.
She's going to buy the the cottages.
She's going to move in for now.
And then after that, she's going to travel to France.
But if she's buying a cottage, I thought she was going to rent it.
If she's buying it.
Or rent it.
Then we're in a chain.
Did you hear?
I thought she said rent.
Oh, rent.
Because it was buying.
Then we're in a chain.
That would be not great.
She's not in a chain.
The cottage's already empty.
But she needs to find the people.
So I think she's checking everything if she can really do it.
So we're still leaving in about 10 minutes to go look at some other houses.
Yeah.
We've got to be there.
We're in Woke.
A two.
Crap man.
It's one thirty four.
You're going to call.
I'm going to call.
Is that Helen who we're going to see?
No.
It's Helen's calling.
Yeah.
Maggie.
Yes.
Graham in Norfolk.
You wanted some feedback on profiles.
I've got some feedback on a profile.
This is a guy who sent in who he is.
Listener.
Really source code.
Graham 40.
Norfolk.
Queer.
And now I want to tell you either.
Don't rush in Charlie fucked up my life.
For six years.
I used an Apple Mac.
Perfectly happy.
No worries whatsoever.
Looked absolutely great.
Works absolutely great.
But the pot father said,
I've got to use cast blaster.
So I bought a fucking laptop.
For as long as I can remember,
I've always enjoyed a cup of rosy.
Always.
You never drank a cup of rosy.
Tea.
Anything else?
Don't have a taste for coffee.
But the pot father says,
I've got to have a bleeding sense.
So I bought one.
At my sixteenth birthday,
I've got given a Phillips fillet shave.
Triple-headed electric dry shaver.
It works.
I love it.
Never used anything else.
But the pot father says,
I've got to have a bleeding Gillette with a battery in it.
And it's my brace.
I have a brace.
So I might have argued.
So the laptop catches a bleeding cold or something.
And sends out me entire address book to a spammer.
Which then everyone I know.
Everyone I've emailed.
All my friends.
All my relatives.
Get fucking spam emails.
Thank you very much indeed.
And now, of course, they're not talking to me.
I gave the sense.
I owe to my mum.
Could she likes coffee?
Your mum is a sense.
I love your sweet heart.
Sweet heart.
A bleeding thing caught on fire.
And burns me mum's kitchen down.
No.
She ain't talking to me no more.
Oh, do you believe me?
And the Gillette Razer.
Well, it was me boyfriends birthday.
I said to him,
The art darling.
Have a nice Gillette vibrate in Razer.
The pot father says it's fantastic.
He's now me ex-boyfriend.
But he's in a beautiful new relationship with the end.
Liverpool Eden Razer.
So pot father.
Thanks very fucking much.
May you always have wind.
Right up your asshole.
Folder.
That is so funny.
That's the guy that the does Linda.
Oh, really?
Yeah, that's a creative shit out there.
Yeah.
And that is very funny.
That's good, isn't it?
That's good.
I think next we're going to meet with some more independent producers.
They're very manly queer.
Very manly queer.
That's very manly.
Yeah.
All right.
Anything we need to talk about.
We need to talk about MTV Awards real quick.
Because we used to go to them.
Yep.
Yeah.
Well, actually, it was a good show.
I mean, it was not cheap.
I mean everything.
Well, expensive doesn't always translate.
No, no.
There's a lot of things happening there.
Yeah.
But it didn't flow.
It was way too much hip-off.
Yeah.
Way too much fucking hip-hop show.
And then you see the panic at the disco wins best video of the year.
Yeah.
Well, we're good.
I love that.
Yeah.
They love that.
That is so good.
Well, they're smart.
They're on the positive music network.
These guys got it together.
I love that sort of clothes.
Mm-hmm.
I love that sort of music.
I was so inject black fabulous.
Everything you did, like, didn't work.
I mean, I know all the gags and everything.
It wasn't supposed to work.
Yeah.
It was supposed to be stupid.
But it turned out being pretty stupid.
Yeah.
You know.
And I guess the part I liked the best was Al Gore.
Yeah.
Al Gore came out.
He was good.
You know, just...
They adored him.
Yeah, just...
The kids adored him.
Yeah.
Talked his, just did his thing.
Showed his slides.
Boom, boom, boom.
The one sort of movement.
The way he said it was very good.
Yeah.
No.
I mean, and it was such a brush of breath there after...
Fresh air, yeah.
You know what?
Yeah, I want to thank Jimmy Alvin.
Jimmy Alvin.
To the peeps.
Each child.
And I'm like, oh.
Please, please.
Please.
And Christina Aguilera wasn't...
I didn't like that song.
I didn't know.
No, no.
She normally blows me away.
No.
So you had to have to say that the best was...
That was a little bit too, too.
How can I explain that?
You have to be very patient to listen to a song like that.
It's not for the...
It's a wrong song.
Yeah.
The audience...
It's exactly that.
So it was not the place for it.
I don't know.
Let me say that.
So that was a pity.
Yeah, that was too bad.
I thought that a Beyonce, Beyonce, was very, very good.
Totally stolen from Janet Jackson.
But it was Janet Jackson all over.
But I mean, it was...
We were saying Jackson.
This is already on the internet.
People are now comparing the two performances.
It is completely the same.
Michael, a little bit of Michael in there.
Well, Janet's always had a little bit of...
Yeah.
It's probably Paul Abdul choreography.
And I think about it.
She used to...
Yeah, she did a lot of Janet Jackson's.
Doesn't do...
No, no.
Beyonce.
No, Beyonce stole it.
That was stolen.
I mean, I thought you meant that...
Paul Abdul did the...
The...
Goryography of...
Of Beyonce.
I don't...
I don't think so.
No, no, no.
What I mean is that Beyonce just totally ripped...
Janet Jackson's dance.
Yeah, absolutely.
So that...
And...
I wonder what she looks like at night...
What she takes off the wig.
She has no hair, does she?
I don't think she has a lot of hair.
I bet it's really...
You really...
Oh, that's the problem with a lot of people.
Like someone taking, you know, shaving off their mustache, you know?
Yeah.
But a lot of women have extensions and there's actually nothing left.
And especially when you wear extensions, your hair will fall off.
Like Paris Hilton.
Did her hair...
Didn't her hair fall off?
Well, that's why you see those girls walking around with your hair after a while.
Because there's nothing left.
Nothing left.
It's too heavy.
But talking about Algorra...
Uh...
Wouldn't he make a wonderful precedent?
Am I wrong?
Well, what are you looking for in a president right here?
Something like...
Like he is.
He's...
Well, what would be the first thing you'd want him to do?
He's so warm.
He comes over as somebody who really means it.
Who means well, who doesn't have that certain smile that you might...
But do you think when he needs to kick ass, he can do it?
I think he can.
Yeah.
I mean, because...
He comes over as a very intelligent person who thinks very deep.
Yeah, deep.
Deep, that is the word.
I wonder what he's doing.
I see that in Bush.
Bush is very on deep.
On shallow.
On deep.
Yeah.
Shallow.
And...
Well, I didn't vote for Bush.
I know that.
Yeah.
I don't know if Carrie would have been any better.
He seems to have the personality.
And I don't like that smile that he constantly...
He produced like everything's okay, you know.
And that...
I call it a smoke.
A smoke?
Yeah.
It's horrible.
I don't see any other...
I don't really know who's going to be a worthwhile candidate.
Yeah, I think...
I think American needs sort of a father figure.
Don't you think so?
I don't know.
I really don't know what we need.
Come to Daddy.
I really don't know.
I think about this a lot.
I saw that whole...
There was an al-Qaeda special on the BBC.
And you...
And you just...
Look at that.
And you're like, we're all doomed.
Yeah.
We're talking...
Forget about it.
We're all fucked.
Wasn't it amazing?
And so their conclusion was that all of this would go away.
If...
America stopped supporting Israel in the Middle East.
Yeah.
If it stopped supporting...
...radical regimes that were either against...
...islam or any radical regime.
And what was the third one?
It was like...
It sounded pretty simple all of this.
It was very simple.
Oh, and get out of Iraq.
Yeah.
And it wasn't that there was a...
A quest of...
Uh...
That's...
Bin Ladenau...
Who was it?
Somebody wanted to have a talk...
...with the president for a solution.
And he didn't want...
He said, I don't want to talk to...
I think was Iran, wasn't it?
I think...
Yeah.
Because the US...
Don't...
We don't talk to you, terrorists.
No.
There you go.
Yeah.
No.
That was a very good point.
I mean...
I couldn't believe that.
Yeah.
The does sound pretty stupid, doesn't it?
It's childish.
Yeah.
So I don't talk to you.
You know, I hate you.
So I'm not going to talk to you.
No solution at all.
Right.
I think...
I think we could bend on that.
And...
And do you remember that guy came...
...a couple of guys had...
...wemps weapons?
And they said, see that weapon?
I'm going to kill an American out with their weapons.
Well, yeah.
Because, you know, it's money-made.
The way they said it...
Yeah.
It's all making machine.
Now, I was more afraid of...
You know, people who...
The kids...
Kids are just radicalized, which is pretty easy.
You know, if you have no future...
Very nice country.
Yeah.
That's pretty easy.
So...
But I'm thinking...
Of all the principles that America stands for...
Yeah.
All the principles.
And you know me.
I'm pretty much a yank.
All the way through.
Yeah.
You know...
I'm more of an international yank.
But you are yank, you know.
A yank.
International yank.
I'm a yank.
Yeah.
I think we could certainly bend...
There's no law that says we don't talk to terrorists.
There's no law.
I think you should listen to...
...everybody...
...doesn't listen to...
Isn't it what we learn our kids?
Teacher kids.
Teacher kids?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
My kids do listen to them.
Because if you don't listen...
I'm all for that.
Yeah.
And I was surprised that...
You know...
That...
I think it was around that they've...
They've said they want to talk.
I think it would be a pretty good idea.
It doesn't have to just be America.
It could be...
You know...
...when send bush and send Blair.
Yeah.
Because these are the top guys.
Don't send condolese a rise.
I'm tired of that.
That to me is like...
You know...
It's just not the same.
You want the CEO to show up when you're dealing with a big company?
You know what I know too?
Country.
Uh...
What's that all the women that they always send...
...with the same hair?
Women with the same hair?
Yeah.
They always send bush.
I'll take a women with thin hair for 400 please.
When you're seen hair, they're much of very intelligent.
They have no hair.
Like, metal, all bright?
Yes.
She had a hair problem.
She didn't have a hair problem.
Yeah.
She did.
And now there's another lady.
It's down to hair.
I saw...
Another lady?
The one that they send from...
I think from...
Can't the lover...
No.
Great Britain is...
There's somebody.
Who was that then?
There's another lady.
A very thin...
Where they sent them?
She was now...
Over there talking to somebody.
I have no idea who that is.
Um...
And I thought...
They all have very thin hair.
So they should send someone with some decent hair?
No.
I think they...
They all brainy people with...
No, man.
You gotta send the number one guy.
The problem is...
I don't know if our number one guy can handle the conversation.
But send it.
I'll send it.
Cheney over too.
Send all those guys.
I think that'd be a really good idea.
Go have a fucking power.
But isn't it always a problem?
Also with families that don't communicate.
That don't necessarily say you have to listen to each other.
Yeah.
You know?
And also...
Marriages that don't work.
Listen.
That's always the problem.
But it's pretty impopular.
You know, you have a slogan talk to the terrorist.
That's a pretty impopular slogan.
It is.
But...
Let's...
You've got to mark it that somehow.
So the catch is on.
But I think talking would be good.
That would be a really...
If they're saying...
Let's talk about it.
How can you make...
There's no solution if you don't...
And we're stupid enough to...
Listen to each other and talk to each other.
Yeah.
You're absolutely right.
Here listen to this guy.
Hey Adam.
This is Lee.
You may not remember me but I called that couple weeks ago left
and that's it.
I am the guy in Indianapolis who...
A writer's bicycle to...
To help with this heart and mention that I always listen to your program while I'm writing.
Yeah.
And I was just now listening actually.
I stopped and took a break.
And I was just now listening.
And of course, I'm a little bit behind on your programs.
But you were on the episode where you were talking about all the...
Warcraft that the kids are having to listen to on the TV.
And that really hit home.
And I just wanted to pass on something that my four-year-old son told me about two weeks ago.
He said, Dad, did you know that a bunch of soldiers have torn up the whole world?
And that, you know, that just made me stop for a moment.
And I thought, you know, that's what he's seeing on TV.
I tried to filter this stuff from him.
I don't want to watch the news, but still it leaks in.
And he's thinking that a bunch of soldiers have torn up the whole world.
It's like, wow.
Anyway, I tried to explain to him that that's not the case.
But there are a lot of people who are trying to tear up parts of the world.
And I don't know.
It's something you can't really explain to a four-year-old.
But the images are getting through and you can't help but to wonder what impact
it's going to have on these kids.
You know, this media saturated war environment that we live in.
Anyway, well, still finding your show.
Thank you.
And have a good day.
There you go.
And I'm just going to say in the BBC documentary, they showed that the,
of the converse or that happens on the exact same side of this,
quote, war on terror, is when someone blows themselves up,
they're shown on TV, like on Al Jazeera, as martyrs, heroes.
Yeah, yeah.
It's the same thing.
You know, kids are going to go, oh, fuck.
That's good.
I want to be him.
Yeah.
You blow yourself up.
You're here, though.
So, there you go.
No, that's nice bummer.
We're all fucked.
Yeah, we are.
Colin, leave us a message.
Plus 1, 2, 0, 1, 6, 2, 5, 6, 3, 5, 7.
Put the plus in front of your, if you're storing into your mobile phone,
plus 1, 2, 0, 1, 6, 2, 5, 6, 3, 5, 7.
In London, 0, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3.
But, you know, I was just thinking all that, all that,
my English is so bad today.
I'm brain, my brain.
The part of the brain is not working today.
Let me slow myself down to your speed.
You know what we're having now?
All those wars.
All those, it, it be influenced everything.
Even your birthday cards didn't arrive.
No, that's right.
Yeah, yeah.
They've had passed everybody's taste.
You know what I mean?
Yes.
It's such a mess at the moment.
And I just wanted to stop, please.
Here you go.
Here's one for you.
Because of the very severe new security regulations,
we were just talking about this just in.
When you fly on KLM business class,
you receive your choice of one little Dutch canal house.
Yeah.
Made of Delft Blue.
We're Geneva.
Filled with a Dutch gene called Geneva.
Yes.
They're going to stop this service because they can't check,
and make sure that there's no explosives inside of this little...
Oh, my God.
Can you believe it?
All the nice things in the world.
All those little nice things that makes life so lovely.
We'll go away.
Not amazing.
It's amazing.
It's just amazing.
I'm just so sad.
And then here's something that's...
This is kind of...
You know, there's a lot of aviation people who sent me stuff.
We email back and forth.
So there apparently is a different story
to Northwest Flight that returned back to Skipple.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because I never heard the truth about it.
Okay. Well, so this is from a pilot.
I'm not going to tell you who.
And he wasn't on the flight,
but someone in his company was.
Okay.
Here's an updated version of the events of the Bombay flight
that turned around.
There's some changes from the first time I told the two of you.
I'll be careful when I fly there next week.
Here we go.
This guy sat in with the crew and the federal air marshals
of the Amsterdam to Bombay flight that turned around
at the hotel in Amsterdam and heard everything.
You'll never believe it.
The youngest of 12 men was age 19.
The media had said they were between 25 and 35.
Yeah.
Completely cracked during interrogations,
vomited on himself and confessed
to coming from an al-Qaeda training camp in Africa.
The media says they were all coming from some vacation spot.
Karen Birmingham watched 11 of them get up immediately
after take off before the fast and seat belt sign announcement
and even before the green light went on.
That's a flight of 10 that's going to be online.
Yeah.
Then they started to individually spread out
and handed their cell phones to the,
quote, head hauncho,
a guy with a little beanie hat on.
They had a total of 14 cell phones.
He took his hat off and started drawing black lines
on his forehead.
The federal air marshal in C-16B watched the entire thing
got up and then the fun began.
Can't go into that now.
Anyway, a bunch of horse crap was being said in the media.
Apparently they definitely were on a suicide mission.
But see that's what I mean.
Interesting.
It's always a different story.
They make a different story because how many times did we
ret our own story or hurt our own story on programs on TV?
And it was never ever the truth.
It was never the way we knew it.
Well, and there's also more than one side to the truth.
Yeah.
Okay.
Shall we leave it with that?
Yeah.
We've been going for 44 minutes.
I'm not going to play another song.
Well, I feel like we haven't finished though.
We're not done.
Well, you get, you get pissed off actually.
Yeah.
But not at you, my darling.
No, I know that.
And could you just update everyone on our morning sex?
Is that, uh, to your satisfaction now?
Is that, uh, everything okay there?
Well, did we?
Oh, yeah.
No, it was nice.
Okay.
That's right.
We got to go.
We got to go look at the, uh, at the other house.
Yes.
You know, because you never know what happens.
50% is not 100%.
No fucking way.
Yeah.
All right, baby.
So, uh, talk to you guys tomorrow.
Love you on.
All right, love you too.
Bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and we're great ones.
Like it on the high performance podcast,
delivery network from Podshow and line-white networks.
I love it.