For the first time ever, the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr. in one action-packed DVD collection,
own all 27 episodes, the cult hit, including all new interviews with Carlton Koo.
First thing that Brisco did that impressed us was, we're not only to come in and really read the dialogue well as an actor,
but he also did a standing flip in our office.
You flipped too for Brisco County!
If you like the kind of TV you can't get on TV, get your copy of the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr.
Available now on DVD!
So you want to pound a full bar fold it?
I would have a DSC 474.
You just gotta keep it down in the side.
She won't wave you down, gotta leave it alone.
Keep it down in the side.
My eyes hurt and I can't just put it in the middle of my heart is hurt and I can't just carry on with down my eyes hurt and I can just carry on with down my eyes hurt and I can just carry on with down my eyes hurt and I can just carry on with down my eyes hurt and I can just carry on with down my eyes hurt and I can just carry on with down my eyes hurt and I can just carry on with down my eyes hurt.
My eyes hurt and I can just carry on with down my eyes hurt and I can just carry on with down.
Hey ... don't get mad ...
How can you resist that?
Okay...
There's a healer, you just gotta keep it down inside
She won't write me down, gotta leave it alone
Keep it down inside
She won't bring me down, gotta leave it alone
I guess I didn't want to keep such a fool in my damn heart
She went in, I guess I just didn't drag it my damn heart
I didn't take it, because you just didn't want me down
I guess I just didn't drag it my damn heart
I'm sorry, but you can really just use some cowbell
I need to explore the studio space
My head is hurting, because you're still pulling me down
My heart is hurting, because you're still dragging me down
I guess I just didn't want to keep such a fool in my damn heart
She went in, I guess I just didn't drag it my damn heart
I know for matter the wonderful winner of 2006 Digital Music Award for Best Unsigned Band
Now available on the Podsafe Music Network
Hey everybody, how you doing? Welcome to the Daily Source Code episode
About 474 coming to you from Curry Cottage on a very rainy Friday afternoon
But it is Fubard
That's right, Fox Todd Uniform Bravo Alpharomia
We are fucked up beyond all repair, which means it's going to be great show
Jersey Todd's got some cool tunes, actually two songs instigated by Jersey Todd
They're all podsafes, so they're all just fantastic
The wonderfuls, which you just heard, they performed live at the Digital Music Award 2006 Fantastic
It was great because they were just like, hey, we feel kind of out of place here
We've got like no money, no nothing, no record deal
And they're the other going to be on the live telecast on the 21st of October
I think that's Saturday, some got awful time midnight
But they'll be on, and of course podsafes music network attendance means that any podcaster can play their songs
And they got another one up there called the Hillbilly song Cool Band from Brighton in the UK
Hey, damn, it's been busy, sorry about yesterday
There was just no way I was going to be able to do a show had to be in pretty early
As I said, we're doing all kinds of meetings, getting pod show UK up and running
Ready to launch in just weeks from now, of course we've kind of already unleashed
And we've been soliciting creative input from podcasters and other creative people in general
Through BTpodshow.com, we did our live from London
We missed that, the live part that is, we're going to have a number of different segments and feeds for you to subscribe to all leading up
Of course to the telecast, and just cool if you want to go back and look at Peter Gabriel yelling at us
Ah, so some good stuff, let me see, feedback first from, oh, haven't heard from this guy quite a while
Comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip
And CSB's got something new on his mind today, yes new opportunities for him
Yeah, ah, Adam Kerry, God bless America, the American dream is still a live dear green go
I wanted to remind all listeners of CSC who are not US citizens that United States, green card lottery 2006 began October 4
And we last till December 3
And you can submit the application only through the website and remind everybody that only the website with dot goz at the end of the internet
The internet domain is the official website, yes, I am citizen and fan of European Union
But I apply to this green card lottery to get US citizenship each year to myself
Just imagine that Adam, oh yeah, if I would win, I would call you my compatiot, wouldn't it be great
Yeah, so right, the green card lottery is on, we'll good luck to you
CSB there, many other ways you can become an American citizen, by the way, if you're serious about it
I'm sure we'd welcome you, I don't know if they do throw background checks, that could be rather difficult
Yeah, the end of the week, save my ass
Here's any mess
Come on, come on in, help me out with that ass
Adam, yes, it's been a short week ever, it seems like we just asked her side
Yeah, time to do it again
So, since you're warmed up, let's get started
Okay, do any of my mind?
We're down on our knees today
Okay, you might call on a second
You need to be on your knees, I'm on my knees
I'm on my knees with your hands at your side
Hands at my side, okay
Okay, leave your left side and hold yourself up with your left hand
What?
Good, now take your right leg
Oh, okay
Straighten it out to the right and push it up toward the ceiling
Oh, please
Your right arm should be reaching for the sky
Okay, it is
Now, if you're right leg, do eight little circles forward
Eight, seven, six, five
Oh, I feel it
Three, two, three
I understand
And three
Okay
And then eight little circles backward
Oh, backwards
Eight, seven, six, five
I can feel this
Three, two, one
I look like a dog
King against the tree
Okay, left
Clean over to the right
And use the right hand for stability
Okay
Left leg, out enough
Left arm to the sky
And eight forward circles
Eight, seven, six, five
Oh, three, two, one
I kind of burned down eight circles backward
Okay
I'm really doing this
Six, five, four, six
Two, one
Thank you
Fantastic
Done?
How are we doing?
I'm painless
Please tell me I'm done
We should do exercise live next week
Since you'll be in San Francisco
Okay
That is if you dare
Uh-huh
All right, asurcise.pudger.com
We'll be up and running soon
So subscribe now
So you don't miss week one
This is Amy Mack
And until next time
Amy Mack
I will exercise live with you any day
Starting down the gauntlet
Mm-hmm
Okay
Yeah, that one
You know what?
It does make a difference
I'm getting good reports back
From the women folk here at Ter Curry Cottage
Indeed
The ass is becoming viewable again
Hey Adam, this is Tom Rockold
From BuckeyeDriveDive.com.ca
Drive it around here
The center is the universe
Listen to GFC 473
And you're talking about naked pictures
That Michael Butler has
But yeah
Passing onto you
Yeah
And you couldn't come up with the word
Okay
I got a lot of email about this
I couldn't believe I couldn't come up with the word
Either when someone is holding something back
Cannot believe that you couldn't come up
Use specifically
Couldn't come up with the word
Bogueard
Michael Butler is Bogueard
Gardening
Boguearding
But kind of scrunched curious
Oh scrunched curious
Oh, we have a new category
Yeah, that was pretty stupid
You know why?
Because it's not in my DNA
To Bogueard
That's why
I come from the Amsterdam
And
Montego Bay School of Erb
And because of the Bountiful
Plentiful amounts available
We don't have to share like in the US
You know, we have passed it along
And this is how an American smokes week
You know, in Jamaica
It's just like we have to hold the Erb
And we just kind of smoke it
And it goes out, man
And we like it again
With a lighter
And Amsterdam is the same thing
You know, it's so cheap
So readily available
No big deal
No reason to Bogueard
So it's as I said
It's just not in the DNA at all
Let me see
What can I tell you about yesterday?
Oh yes, yesterday
I got a demo of the BT Vision
System
This is the IPTV
Box that there's been talked about
Quite a bit here in the UK
And I have to say
I was impressed
Now I have a skyploss
Which is
I guess kind of the
Equivalent of
Direct TV with with Tvo capabilities
You know, satellite little satellite
Dish on the roof
So this is a BT Vision thing
We pretty cool
You plug it into two places
Initially you plug it into
And by the way you get a
I guess a guy comes to your home
And installs it
It's you plug it into your aerial
Your antenna on the roof
Which just about every single house in the UK
Still has
So you can get your free view
Which we've discussed before
I don't know, it's like 30 or 40 channels
Of a digital television
And what I saw yesterday
I looked pretty damn stupid
And then you plug the other end
Into your DSL line
And from there you'll be able to
Get all kinds of stuff on demand
Pre-recorded programs
Of course there's stuff that's already
You can record yourself
And the one thing I really liked about
The interface
Is unlike if anyone living in the UK
Of the 8 million people using sky
You'll know how
Fucking horrible this is
When you go to the program guide
And sky
Not only does it not overlay
The program guide on top of the picture
You're watching now
So you could kind of see what you know
Keep track of the program that you're watching
Or see if the commercial is ended
But it's usually when we switch
It throws it full screen
And they bring up some fucking music
It's just some horrible background music
For the program guide
Where of course you want to hear the program that you're still watching
So stupid
So they've got that right
And something else really interesting
I don't know how much I can talk about this
And of course our partnership
Includes all kinds of non-disclosures
But I'm just so excited that
It looks like I don't know if it'll be the initial release
Or whenever
But it looks like they'll be
Experimenting with
Internet networking
Throughout the home
Through power lines
How cool is that?
So you basically you can plug
Anything into a wall socket
You could take this free
This BT vision box
You can plug it into a wall socket
And it doesn't matter where your DSL line is located
It'll just work
It'll just work right through the power supply
I thought it was pretty neat
And so I'm very excited about what we saw
And obviously I'm looking at that saying
Hey, what can we do with it?
Well, check this out
You'll be very happy to know
That the video format
Of course it eats MP3's
No problem
But the video format is MP4
Using the H.264 codec
So it's like exactly the stuff
That we're using in video podcasting
It's so cool
So cool
Now
I can just don't pay you
Everybody in the house
We're ready for our living
You say you are
Oh, oh, oh
Hey
Yeah
Fuck the meter
Stop, stop, stop, stop
Let's do all theおお
Don't stop, stop
Stop, stop, stop
Let's do all the way there
Turn around
So I could be caught too
We've gained zoned a line
Let's take it out
Skown
The bad place of tools
Oh then I'm up you
Stop, don't break this thing
You know I know you
You are your heart, too. You know we're getting hard
But once we're getting the back up, we're going to the witty car
It's not the 20 yards, they call their ramps on
Give it up for the team so we're getting it hard
One, two, three, here
We go make one, think real clear
To all my people getting down right here
We go party like this, all these
So don't know, there's another year
Come way more like it's just no greater
Everybody in our city ready to party
Let me hear something, oh, oh
Yeah
That's the water, what?
Wow bunch, stomp, stomp the bleachers
Now also on the pod save music network
Thank you very much, Jersey Todd, for unleashing that into the network
And also want to thank Michael Butler of course
And his counterpart in the UK, Jill Mills
Who have been working so diligently on making people aware of the pod save music
Now we're helping bands independent labels
And also some rather mainstream labels try it out
And see if we can make it work with this
Funky thing we call pod casting and turns out
Oh shit, yeah, it works
By the way, Jill Mills
Who really is the Michael Butler over here in the UK
Some subtle differences, she smells a lot nicer
She's not quite as bony
I like, I love you, man
And we were at London Live
And this is just all these bands coming in
And we're interviewing, we got, we had OJ
That would be the UK OJ, not OJ
Simpsonson, but OJ was one of our one of our host for London Live
And Olivia interviewing people
And then Peter Gabriel comes down the red carpet
And he goes, hey Jill and Jill, say come on in
Let's do an interview over here for a pod show on the live
Yeah, no problem
It was like, okay, wait to go Jill, definitely
Very, very cool
I got some other cool things I wanted to tell you about what we're doing over here
Which I think can easily be replicated in the US
But first
One, two, one, six, two, five
Six, three, five, seven, one
Five, six, three, five
Five, six, two, five, six, three, five
Five, seven, nine, five
I love it when you guys make stuff for me
That's like a present every morning I wake up
Like, oh, look, there's new intros to the show
How does it a new voice-mail jingle?
I love it, thank you so much
Hey, I'm locked out of the podcast
Don't be here, I heard something yesterday
On the polar bear podcast hosted by Andy
And I'm 99% sure it's not true
But I just wanted to check with the source
And make sure he said that he heard a rumor
That podcasts are outside of the pod show
Plus, soon we'll not have access to the pod safe music network
And I just can't imagine that ever happening
It would just, anyway, if you were to dress as leaders
Shoot me to email or talk about it a little bit on your show
I'm not precured, thanks man, bye
Is it just a feeble attempt to promoing your show on the Charlie?
What is that?
Let's stoop it!
I would make no sense at all, now I would it
Oh man
It's like, it's sometimes, and a lot of this happens in the blogosphere
And it's, it's, it used to be frustrating now
I just have to laugh at all, it's conspiracy theories
Really, all of it, no, of course not
Pod safe music network stands on its own dude
And even though pod show funds it heavily
Because, you know, it's a resource that does cost money
We've got full-time people working on it, keeping it running, cost bandwidth, etc
And we love it
It enables more content to flow throughout pod casting
And independently produced independent productions, period
You know, where the license is built right in
It would be very stupid for us to try and lock that in
There's no sense whatsoever
It's almost like, so I'm sure you if you're in the blogosphere
Then you could not have missed Jason Calacanis's comments about the Gilmour gang
That this was, you know, the adab would never let it on the air
Steve Gilmour would never dare to put up the show on edited
And of course, you know, the show where all of the quote analysts on the show
I would just have to say the guys on the call on the conference call
The best shows in a long time I have to say
You know, how stupid is that?
To think that I wouldn't allow a show to go up
Even stupid to think that I have that right
This is what you got to understand
And maybe just have to rewind a little bit back to the basics
Because people really have come up with some interesting ideas
Of what pod show is about and how we work with our partners
Who are independent producers we have no say over final content
We have no say over what you put up
The producers are individually responsible
Steve Gilmour is responsible for his show
He's responsible for the content of the show
He's responsible for anything that he puts on his show
He's responsible for what he says
He's responsible for everything
And he's also responsible for cutting it up into five different segments
Do you hear me there?
Little geek nerdy boy?
Todd Cochran
Todd, you are such a conspiracy theorist man
Steve Gilmour thinks it's a smart way to do it
I disagree, I've been pretty vocal about that
And his choices are his
As with any producer who works with pod show
And you may notice that he has the same four minutes of commercials
At the beginning of every show
I'm not a big fan of that at all
I think it really doesn't serve the purpose
And I think he should be integrating that into a show in a whole different way
But that's his decision
Now you notice he has the same advertisers
He's not getting a lot more
Advertising business because
We can only sell so much
And if he decides to do it that way
That's his foretaste
That's his prerogative
He can do whatever he wants
But you know
Then he may
You know
May not get a lot of new sponsors
To me it's almost sounds like he's phoning some of that stuff in
And I know it's four minutes and everybody knows it's four minutes
And we pretty much all skip past the first four minutes
On the other hand
Even I'm the we have those brisco county junior ads running right now
I want to make a new one
I'll make one please
I do not like the one that's running
And you know this is how we try to do it
We're changing
Media we have different distribution
We have different ways to produce
We're people are producing independently
With no Uber lords
Telling on what they can do
At the same time we also have to change advertising
That's not entirely within our control
We've had some good successes
You know look at the earthlink ad challenge
We've had some great promotions
Running throughout the network
I think the accurate target cast is fantastic
And you know
Not everyone sees eye to eye
But we still got a sell
We still got to make money come in
Because we are paying people
Anyway
Okay
So the other cool thing about British telecom
I want to talk about
Unfortunately those of you listening to serious
Satellite stars one or two won't be able to hear
Because I just got a couple seconds left
But you do have another three and a half hours
Of a pod show on serious coming your way
For this food bar Friday
And I personally will talk to you guys again
On Monday on the source code
Now before I get to
To the other bit of news I want to talk about
This is still more of a feedback coming in from the UK
Check the sound
The ad and it's the doctor here from the blood cast
I get the wrong address last time I've shown them
It's the blood dot com slash cast
I've cracked as that
Anyway
I'm just sitting here on a
Actually Thursday morning
This was Wednesday show
Are you talking about the distribution board
I just pulled us away
You say you didn't use the podcasting
Twenty in Britain
It helped you out with some of the videos
Starts and all that kind of things
I think that's what it's saying
And what was that?
Ah okay
Doctor
Why do you always call me when you're on the street
Could you please call me from a quiet place
It's so hard to understand what you're saying
It's probably because you don't want
Cossow to hear that you call me right?
Well, of course we've been soliciting
Any kind of creative
Input feedback, talent, production, etc
For several weeks
On BTpodshow.com
I believe that there's some cynicism
In the quote podcasting community
And people have a very much weight and sea approach
And attitude because we just didn't receive
All that much from
The podcasting community
You know, we received a lot of stuff from other people
Who want to be host, comedians,
A lot of comedians, a lot of comedians
Unlike the US
A lot of comedians
Want to get into independent productions
Here in the UK
Very interesting
So we definitely have made some great relationships
But when we saw this kind of weight and back
Hold back, weight and sea attitude
We really went as wide as we could
And we really cast our net as wide as we possibly could
And said, hey, you know, if you got anything
Once you come on down
And show us your wares
And that was a big part of the condition
And of course anyone would have been welcome
So there's been, you know, we've had
Think a couple thousand different submissions
Through BTpodshow.com
A lot of it video
I have to say, interestingly enough
But also music
And some
You know, audio productions
Not necessarily podcast
So it's not like we didn't want to
That's kind of what the kind of the vibe that we received
And as it turns out
It was very interesting to have
This enormous
New audience
I consider people who produce to be audience as well
Senseo
Senseo moment brought to you by pdbtpodshow.com
It was great to see people saying, hey, what the hell is this?
I was doing something cool
We're basically introducing people
To the whole concept
Which you could call podcasting
But I just like to say it's independent productions
And it's producing
And it's monetizing
And it's having a shitload of fun
Secondly,
Think of the nominations
Interesting at the podcast
Tapestry was sort of mostly non-independent for cartoons
Yeah, that is a shame
But you did the nominating
And yeah
We entered into the digital music awards
Rather laid into the process
It's the second year
But just telecom was sponsoring them
It's basically their show
They pay for it
And they make sure that there's a show
And that people are nominated
And that there's winners and actual trophies
And shit
And that it gets aired on Channel 4
And we entered into that process
Pretty late
Nominations had already been cast
By a
It's on the way
It's on the website dma2006.com
The nominations had pretty much been set in stone
What was interesting is
There was one nominee who was independent
And that was London electricity
And I can tell you
London electricity won
And I don't know if
If the actual votes are tabulated anywhere
Because it was a people's choice award
Not by nomination
So they couldn't nominate
But they could vote
And it was like
Twenty to one for the independent
So that was the great news about it
And believe me
We were somewhat dismayed
That it did indeed seem to be
Just about a whole bunch of mainstream
In fact when you see the telecast
On the 21st
I actually said that
But I believe the landscape
We very different
Get next year for the
For the best podcast of the year
At Digital Music Awards 2007
So
And the premonition
Pretty much came true
There you had it
It was
It was an independent podcast
That won the category
Hi Adam
This is Tania
We're walking down here
In the short
There's no more
It's just something I've never heard of it
It's a little beach in Southern Ireland
I'll let you adjust for a second
It takes a second
When you all of a sudden you hear
An Irish voice coming from the States
Like, okay
You got to get into the rhythm
Got to get into the kind of
The song
It's the way she talks
And here we go
Coming in here because
But I'm a student college
We've a show called
TalkCassen.au
I came across your show
I fried off in this room
To the Charlie with my
On my I thought walking along
I love it
When you listen to the Charlie
On your iPod
Walking along with your lucky charms
I found a question for you
Not before you also
Make for some shots
I want to put this to you
It's so sexy
I have a question for you
I want to put it to you
I want to put it to you baby
I'm
BT Parkhouse
What I'm just wondering
Why is this limited
Just to
To the BT market
People within the UK
Beats that say
Well
No one in Ireland
Actually one of the most popular
I must have
I'm a BT customer
And find a broadband services
One and so much better
I see that the general people within Ireland
There's so much challenge
I see it can be quite
Losing out on this
We're trying to change things
In a life at the moment
Might mean myself
First I'm a scruncher
Trying to bring the kids up
To be a soul
Or that can be
A bit of a challenge
As you probably know
You do have any children
But it's just something
I'd like you to think about
That's a large market within Ireland
Just small little islands
We do have quite a lot of talents here
And it's actually growing quite a lot
Thank you
I'm not a benefit to you
If you could maybe even think about
Just spreading the word
Share our country
Bye
Darling
I'll pay my food
Will you take your clothes off
I'm just having fun with you
Hey
First of all
What we're doing in the UK
It's podshow UK
Okay
BT podshow.com
But BT is rolling out
Wherever they have a presence
And of course
They're in Ireland
You'll see all kinds of marketing initiatives
In Ireland as well
Absolutely
What is
And why do you think that we're excluding you
We're not excluding you at all
You're excluding yourself
So no, of course not
More than welcome
And it absolutely includes Ireland
It includes
It includes Guernsey
If you wanted to
That's beyond the point
But anywhere British telecom
Is
They're going to really roll this out
And really promote it
And market it
So that will include Ireland
Absolutely
Send your stuff in girl
Come on
What are you waiting for
So Gavin Patterson
He's the
He's like the new
He's the boss over
BT retail
He's really the
Above him you've got
See you got Ian
I've been
So really Gavin is
You know is the top guy
For what we're doing in the UK
And he's young guy
He's younger than I am
I believe
And as you know
Patricia thinks he's cute
Which some other women
Who had heard that particular show
With the lady Patricia
Also agreed to
I found the digital musical
Words
So he mentioned a couple times
They have the studio downstairs
Because we actually taped a bit with him
For a press release
And they have a full-blown
Fucking studio
Downstairs
In the BT building
At their headquarters
And not only do they have a studio
With a proper control room
It's completely digital
Right down to Final Cut Pro
If you want to record something on that
But it's multi camera
And they have an auditorium
Right next to it
They use this stuff for like corporate
Videos and you know for shareholder
Meetings and stuff like that
And when I saw the studio
A couple weeks ago
I said Gavin man
I want to use this
He said well shit
You should because
It's like it's only used for boring stuff
So here's the plan
We're going to do a daily show
We're going to hijack
The British Telecom headquarters
And it'll really work
Because we can get guests in
We can get him
What the hell was that?
Oh, today's size
Vacuuming
We can get people in easily
Through the front door
We can book guests
There's dressing rooms
It's a full-blown piece of
KIT and we don't have to pay for it
It's like an internal line item
So I'm really excited about
You know this daily show
That we're cooking up
It's going to be
I believe we're going to do it live
Of course it'll be
You know also available as a download
But would it be cool to continue live
From London and do it from this corporate
Headquarters and basically hijack the studio
Just do some wicked ass shit
Yeah
Keep watching this space baby
Hey Adam this is Paul Smith
I just sent your email regarding
Pictures not showing up on Adam.podshow.com
I'm currently using IE6
And I've tried it on multiple computers
I've logged in and logged out
And interestingly enough
If I am the same computer
Use the latest version of
Mozilla
It doesn't happen
And if I go and I look at the properties
For the picture or the image
That's not showing up
I figured this out
The just now is I'm listening to it
Paul I do appreciate you sending in
Audio comment about this
I believe
Unless we've all of a sudden
Broken IE6
Which doesn't
It doesn't sound right
I believe it's a plugin thing
Let me see
It says it's looking for
HTTP colon slash slash
Sound seeing tours.podshow.com
Ford slash WP images
Ford slash Adam
Mark header
Yeah
SWF
Dot SWF
Right
So either one of two things happened
Either that particular server went down
When you were looking at the page
Which I doubt because it's working for me
In fact if you go to curry.com
You should in IE6
I guess or whatever
You should see the same problem
Because that's a flash movie
So no wonder you know you're having problems
Try reinstalling the
Flash plugins
And I'll check with engineering as well
Because you know that should be automatic
And if you have the wrong plugin
We should detect that
And we should help you download the right one
So I'll look into that from our side
You said that Mozilla was no problem
So I think that is just a flash plugin issue
Which usually is kind of automatic
And is always up to date
But a crap man
It's the internet
Hi Adam
It's Karen from Rumor Girl
Baby
Karen
Not Mary
Okay
I know what's coming
I'm sorry I fucked up the other day
Thanks for talking about us on the daily source code
Today
But you mentioned that you saw Mary and Carla
In the pool from Rumor Girl
Yeah
Karen and Carla
I don't feel that everybody is mentioned that
That time at the point that I'm going to call you Mary
So next is your my teacher is going to say
I'm not Mary, damn it
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm sorry
That's fine, I don't mind it all
But um
I loved it
Had a great time
That the seven hottest women of pod show
Including me and Carla
And we've got pictures on RumorGirls.pot show.com
You can check that out
And just wanted to say hey
And sorry we missed you
But maybe next year
Top 2 later
Bye
And I don't folder or scruncher
Hmm
I don't know how
By the way, I wonder if both Karen and Carla
Or folders or scrunchers
I peg
I peg Carla as a scruncher
Actually
And Karen I think I think she's folder
I'm so sorry about that
It's just you know that whole Mary and Carla thing
Just kind of flow so naturally Karen and Carla
RumorGirls
And I loved watching you guys at the podcast expo
But I told you that I love when you were in the pool
And you kind of flashed a little bit
Hmm
And Karen's kind of like the
All-American girl
When you look at her
There was they just released another
RumorGirls clip from PME
Which was with their Callie Lewis
And I look at that and I go like
Oh man
I have a great job
Hey there, I'm Shme
Host of Episode 3 of BG Blast
Be sure and check us out this week
As our Halloween screen promotion creeps along
And one of our listeners tells us just what it's like
At the top of one of the tallest mountains in the United States
Join us as we spin some classic tunes
By the descendants and MU 330
And talk about things that only happen in the movies
I even share one of my most random thoughts
I will see you on the show
Because that's where you'll be of course
You're gonna have to choose each other
The hardest work you'll know here is my destiny
You know that's where you'll be
You're so good
Want to know the land
Close your eyes
We'll start again
And let them pass
You know that's where you'll be
You know that's where you're going
Yeah, what's up, Adam, it's Jersey Todd, the official musical, just the shot shot.
Big thanks to Coli Brice from Area Records from the new intro high, you liked that.
So listen, I want to take you a little opportunity to review the music that I provided in the last couple
weeks, class couple of months up on the Daily Source code.
We've given you some cowbell banging music, right?
We've given you some rap music, right?
We've given you some dance music, right?
You know what I haven't given you?
Some country music, and it's a little secret, Jersey Todd actually kind of sometimes likes country
music.
Yeah, it's got to be good, it's got to be the right stuff, and well, I think I got somebody for you.
The artist is Kelly Brock out of Canada.
I like her song a lot, the song is 30 something.
Oh yeah, and I know what you're going to say, it doesn't hurt that she's cute because she
really is.
Check this out, I like the song a lot, talk to you later everybody.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, baby yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah. yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah,
We're in the world, we know you'll appreciate
We feel around, we're gone, we're in town
We say this is telling the same
You know, we're not prepared to get up, ready to get up
But third is something, yeah, yeah
Yeah, we're talking to this place
Yeah, gonna steal our keys
Yeah, stormy memory day
Yeah, we'll go, oh, oh, oh, wait
So much more to a scroll, simply f***ing good
With the accomplished everything
We said we were our sisters throughout history
Yeah, they were healthy
And sure enough soon enough to see a female president
To be with you, look at us
It's time to celebrate
We are women of the world
No, you're the free she gave
We're the real world
Jersey Todd does it again
The official music colleges of the Cha Cha
Bringing you your
Football selection
Kelly Brock
Thirty something
Yeah, I do, you're right
I'm looking at her page now
On the podcast music network
She is cute
Kind of in that rough
Like I'm gonna ride you cowboy
Kind of way
Mm-hmm
Very nice
You can find links to all of the songs played in the daily source code
The daily source code dot com in the show notes
Final thought in a second
Ten lessons I've learned while surfing the internet
Number one, entering your email address on some websites
Is an open invitation to spam
Number two, before forwarding an email about the ghost
Of a dead boy appearing in the theatrical film
Three men in a baby
Check Snopes dot com first
Number three
Spyware that informs you that you have spyware
Is not very helpful
The FBI will never send you an email
Warning about your visiting 40 illegal websites
They'll simply bust down your door
The file never ever Google the Toronto-based quartet
The barricade ladies on a computer at work
Number six, Bill Gates and Microsoft
Are not tracking this email
And forwarding it to 15 other people
Will not get Walt Disney signed to send you free passes
To Walt Disney World
There's seven, there is no such thing
As a national do not email
Registry
Number eight, there is no ousted prints
In Bangladesh willing to share $15 million with you
We're not closing one porn pop-up window
Open's 15 more and number 10
Everything as your service provider will solve most of these problems
Unfortunately, the remaining few will take some common sense
So I think a new thing I'll do here on the football
Friday is a final thought of the week
So I've been in London a lot over the past ten days
Really, really with British people
Besides the yanks who were in from San Francisco
From HQ to help with London live
They're really working with British production people
Talent management people
Artists, directors, you name it
And I've really been paying attention
Close attention to the language
Now when I say to the language
Normally you'd think about the accent
And I think I've pretty much got the accent down
I think I really can speak with the British accent
Probably would be able to fool most brits
I think I really do
And I tried it yesterday and Daniel winner
He's our managing director
At Potcho UK
I said let me give it a shot then
And so I just spotted off a little bit with my English accent
Which I'm not going to do if you're right now
And he said well that's actually quite good
But it does kind of sound like you're taking the piss out of us
And I said well you speak American accent
So he did an American accent
It sounded really like he was taking the piss out of the American accent
And so that gave me kind of a reference point
And I think I figured it out
It is not the accent that counts
What is so beautiful about English spoken by the brits
Is the use of the language
Is the vocabulary that they bring into the conversation
The structure of sentences
The complexity of how they get to a point
Which in some business negotiations or dealings
It can be quite tedious
And it's really just nice to pull out the yank in us
And say okay here's what we want here's what you know
Let's follow the money let's do whatever
You know just the way the way Americans are much more direct
But I am going to work a lot more on the vocabulary
And grammar and structure
And really the edge a lot of the adjectives are just beautiful
That are used here in common language
And I think that's the that is really
We've resorted in the US to a language of slang really
Which is okay because I like it too
And believe me, believe me the brits love hearing the American accent
They love it as much as we love hearing an English accent
But down underneath all that and this is what I've learned this week
Is just a
I'd have to say almost a larger respect
A greater respect for the language itself
And for all of the beautiful ways you can use it to express yourself
And to drive across a point
So somewhere in there I'm hoping to find the magic mix
Between the kind of the yank directness
And the vocabulary and grammar and structure of the brits
I'm reinventing myself
It's a frightening thing
Have yourself a great weekend
I'll be traveling as you know actually tomorrow
With Christina recording a new BG blast
And a pod save the queen
It'll be interesting if I can get her out of bed
And actually doing it
The most recent checks you received from pod show did motivate
But if she doesn't want to do it, what can I say?
I think she'll be there for recording time
At the studio here at the cottage
Sunday of course I'm traveling to San Francisco
So I'll be all over the map also
I think we're going to LA for a couple days as well as New York
So I'm in miss a day here or there due to travel
But pretty much it should be able to bring you
I'll show you from the curry condo
Looking forward to it haven't been there in almost eight weeks
No almost ten weeks been so long
Out of my pod show dot com to send me your love
DailySourceco.com for the show notes
Have a great weekend
Thanks for listening
Another pod show pod guest
Stick it in your ear
Get this pod cast
And more great ones like it
On the high performance pod cast
We'll bring that work from pod show and lime light networks
I love it