Think Advertising sucks.
Think you can do better?
Pod Show and EarthLink are willing to put our money where your mouth is.
Listen to this podcast or go to adchelens.podshow.com to see how you can win big
in the EarthLink make advertising better challenge.
Delta Sierra Charly 4-0-8
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Modcasting is a battery.
I stepped out of my doorstep.
When I stepped out of my doorstep.
When I stepped out of my기가.
You can buy, took a dome to my head, what a thing, what a high
Lying my hands, kicked up my feet, danced around, they got so sweet
A listen to the verse in, the music was a tree, it was a step on it
Take my blues away, it's a morning
It's gonna be up, gotta stay, what a step on it
It's come so many times, me pour, I used to proud upon my life
But I've got no too many gold, I've got gold
Open up the paper, I start to be older, I've been pre-ins
Rinse a bigger ounce or tiny in my eyes, of course, this is a myth
Said it'd be the worst one, the top of the picture for the real
It's gonna be the worst one, the top of the picture for the real
Take my blues away, it's a morning
It's gonna be up, gotta stay, what a step on it
It's come so many times, me pour, I used to proud upon my life
But I've got no too many gold
I've got no too many gold
I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if it works, I don't know if
it works for you but give me that first day of summer feelin' it's lack strit, Wednesday morning, played several times beforeabouts of the Daily Source code, usually on a Wednesday, yeah, I wonder why.
Hey Kicks off, your Wednesday here, on the Charlie good morning everybody from Northern California another beautiful day, it is the first day of summer summer's solstice, of course celebrations took place, hours ago,
hours ago. That's all due to time difference in the United Kingdom where 25,000 people
were expected to show up at Stonehenge, including our very own pod chick. I think she had
or wasn't her wedding ceremony plan today, probably multiple wedding ceremonies, all kinds
of druids and believers and witches and goblins, all kinds of stuff shown up at Stonehenge.
Hopefully we'll get an update from the pod chick. She seemed pretty happy to be there.
And we're happy to be here San Francisco winding down my trip. It looks like I'm going to go back
on Saturday for a Sunday morning arrival and I'm ready for it. My goodness. Last night,
Miami Heat Champions. That was pretty incredible. Now you know, I've been following
what is happening to me? I used to be such a metro-sexual guy and now I'm following sports
like soccer and I'm even a little bit interested in hockey, even though it's over. I think
it was the only person in America interested in hockey. What went wrong there? How can we
don't care about hockey anymore in the US? But what a great game. Fantastic game last night to see the
heat versus the Mavericks and it was, you know, we watched it at 21st Amendment that's a bar
which is right next to the office conveniently located. Interestingly enough, I think we were the
Miami Heat fans in the place. The rest seemed to be for Dallas. But congratulations to the
Miami Heat. It was a great game and well-deserved win. Lots of stuff happening at the office. Of
course, that's why I'm here in San Francisco at Pod Show HQ. As we get ready for the full unleash
of Pod Show Plus. More about that in just a little bit. Actually, we'll do a metro-sexual moment
which has something to do with the release of Pod Show Plus. But we've got 50 people in the office now.
And you know what? We've crossed that point where I think I know everyone's name. It's
incredible. It's incredible to see how quickly this has grown and this is all based upon
business, upon revenue, upon being able to hire more people to do more things, which is
the way Ron and I have always operated companies. We've never had dot-com investments. And the
investment we have now was really most important part is getting all these incredibly
smart people on our board of directors and being able to utilize their experience.
The end of the roadodex is when appropriate. But we have contractors in as well working on some
specific projects. And as a tall person or as we say, as someone who was vertically challenged,
and that can go both ways obviously. Patricia is also vertically challenged, but in a different
direction. There's one thing, actually I should say, not just being a tall person, I'm six
four. If I stand up really straight, I probably just can scratch six five, but you get used to kind
of stooping down a little bit, particularly when you have a life partner who is five, three.
I think she says five four, but I think she's lying about that. We'll ask her a Monday when we do a
show together. The one thing you miss, particularly in a position I've been together for 20 years,
it's the hugging. You know, I like to hug. And it's complicated when you're of such a vast
different height. You can come up with all kinds of solutions. And we always find ourselves
me walking on the street Patricia walking on the sidewalk to get that little extra lift or you know,
we use stairs or we use anything we can. We have some tall people showing up at the office now
who we're working with as a pod show here in San Francisco. Lisa is a contractor and Lisa's great,
because Lisa is, she's got to be six feet tall. She may even be taller. I'm not sure.
And we were talking about this the other day and her fiance is a little bit, not much,
which is a little bit shorter than she is. And I say, you know, Lisa, there's just one thing.
Um, could I hug you? And there's something about a hug hugging someone who was of equal height
of you that it just cannot be compared. And the reason I say this is because watching the heat
last night, I remember, oh man, this must have been 11 years ago, maybe, interestingly enough,
with many of the same people that I'm with now, Ron and actually this was with the KJ Chris Jacob.
We, uh, we built planet rebox.com, which was rebox, um, website. It was one of very early in the
game. There was 94, 94, 95. And we do all kinds of events and we go to the Super Bowl and we do
cybercast and we do interviews. And at the time, Shack had just signed up with rebox for his, uh,
his humongous literally, humongous shoe, uh, shoe deal. And, uh, so we, I think we went to a
camera if it wasn't land. It feels like it wasn't at land, but I'm not sure we went to interview
and, and I said to Shack that Shack, excuse me, uh, could I just hug you for a moment? And that was
probably the best hug I've ever had to hug this huge thing that was bigger than me. It was just
the, and you know, I could kind of just kind of melt away in his arms. Man, that guy is huge,
diesel, brought it home. I, uh, made a call to Uncle Don yesterday. Now, for those of you who haven't
heard the episode where I talked about Uncle Don when I was in New York, Uncle Don, who is my
uncle? Um, I see, uh, he's married to my dad's sister. Uh, he has a long standing, uh, relationship
with the US government. He was, uh, uh, I'm, I'm not sure, you know, I have to ask him because I keep
forgetting I probably muck it up, but, uh, I think he ran either the NSA or portions of the CIA
many years ago. He was, uh, security advisor to, uh, Bush senior when he was VP. He was, uh,
and this is probably the most, uh, interesting thing. He was ambassador to South Korea for a number of
years. And, uh, for the past, I think, five or six, maybe, maybe even longer than that, maybe eight
years. He's been the chairman CEO of the Korea Society. And that's, headquartered in New York City.
So with, uh, with, uh, you know, all this talk of missiles being fueled up and things heating
up in North Korea, I figured time to call Uncle Don because we got to get him on the show.
And, uh, and, and I, you know, I really wanted to do an, uh, uh, in person to interview with him
because I felt that that would just, it would be much better, but you know, shoot. I'm ready for, uh,
for a Skype call. So I called, uh, spoke to Aunt Meg and, uh, guess what, Uncle Don is in
Seoul, Korea right now. Gee, it's not a coincidence. And this guy is, uh, he's, uh, he's, uh, he, he's
important. I, I know that, uh, some, uh, maybe he won't ever be able to tell me or us about what
he's doing, but I know that he's, he's, uh, heavily, he knows the Koreans so incredibly well,
South and North, if, as if there's a real difference in the people. Um, and I know that he's over
there doing good stuff. And I know that he's extremely concerned about North Korea. So,
uh, obviously not able to get through to him in Seoul and there's all kinds of time, time zones,
issues, etc. Uh, but, um, I did get an email back from him after talking on Meg and, uh, anywhere
before July 12th, he'll be more, uh, after he gets back. So he gets back this Sunday, I guess. So
sometime next week, I'm going to give him a call and we'll just do a Charlie talking Uncle Don.
And you're going to love this guy. You are going to love him. Well, uh, when you hear his stories
and when you hear his insights and, and he's, he really knows what's going on. So I'm excited about
that. It's going to be very cool to have Uncle Don on the show. It's a family affair once again.
Hey, what's up, Adam, this Jersey Todd. And I just want to play you something from yesterday's
chat chat. It's from my personal Charlie music colleges. Jersey Todd from the Jersey Todd show.
Jersey Todd show.com. Dude, thank you so much for turning me on to this.
Daisy Cutter featuring Uncle Keith. Cool Keith. That is a big deal as, uh, Jersey Todd said
in his email to me. So listen, the official musicologist of the Charlie, I don't know. I
thought last month, I was the official solicitor, a lawyer of the daily source code. I don't know.
I've got more titles than the New York Public Library. But listen, that's not the reason I'm
checking in. The song you played yesterday. Daisy Cutter. That's actually recorded by seven
Ellen Esoteric Adam Massachusetts. Cool Keith, or as I like to call him Dr. Octagon himself,
apparently helped out with the track. And if you're not familiar with cool Keith, his sound and his
wordplay is all over that song. Seven Ellen Esoteric's new album is being released on June 27th on
Baby Grand Records. And you can check out some other tracks from them on the PMN. Now listen,
I'm not going to cheap in this audio comment with a cheap plug for my show, the Jersey Todd show.
In fact, I think that daily source code listeners are computer savvy and enough to find
it themselves. And I think it would cheapen the office of the official musicologist of the Charlie
for me to say my website addressed. All I'm going to say is that it's exactly the same as www.google.com,
except instead of Google, you should put something else in there. Hey, it's Jersey Todd and the Jersey
Todd Show, and I'll catch you on the flip side. Oh, man. A lawyer with a sense of humor. I love it.
Dude, we got to work on on your presentation skills there, okay?
Because if you're if you're an attorney and you're the your the official musicologist and you
got to be like a denny crane thing, man. Jersey Todd, that's what we need from you.
Jersey Todd, here for you protecting the interests of the Charlie listeners.
Hi, and welcome to the Macaew Podcast. Who we talk about all things Macintosh, news reviews,
and for all you mac geeks, the all important up to the minute room of meal. We only play
pod safe music from the pod safe music network. We even have a weekly, did you know segment?
We will totally geek you out with Steve Jobs and Apple fact. This podcast is produced entirely
on my brand new Macbook Pro and recorded live inside Apple's garage band and published my
Dot Mac account using IWave. So check us out today at our website at Machiphonau.com or
just look for Macaew on the iTunes music store and subscribe today.
Yeah, it's just I think you had an audio comment that went along with this where he said
uh maybe it was an email I can't remember. A little fuzzy this morning. It's Wednesday morning.
I always said, oh, you may not be in the mood for playing this promo. It's about the Mac. I know
you hate the Mac. It's like whoa, step back for a second. I don't hate anything. You know,
I still love Macs. I've got my eye Mac right here. I've got Patricia's got an eye Mac at home.
It's just the power books or the ones that are freaking me out. That's all, you know, and
power books I need to portable. I need a portable. That's going to be reliable and and yeah,
reliable. That's about it. And I just really frustrated with with the quality. I think of the hardware
more than anything with the with Macs right now, you know. And everyone said, oh, you should buy
a Macbook Pro or buy a Macbook. You know, this is what you need. You can even run Windows on it.
Yeah, I understand. I totally understand. But I'm glad I didn't because I've been reading up a
little bit on what's going on with the with the Macbooks and the MacBook Pros and we have, you know,
all kinds of things like overheating because of a plastic strip that was left in in the in the
casing. I've heard that Wi-Fi. In fact, I read Jason Kelcanus was having problems with his MacBook Pro.
And he and he's getting a little bit protrude, if you will. Because though the apparently there
was a series of MacBook Pros with a Wi-Fi is flaky and and then there's a a wine. Oh, man,
the screen wine. I've had that on an old laptops and all kinds of computers, essentially. But
then it's basically the screen. When you turn it up to a certain brightness, then it starts to wine.
It's like, no, this, you know, that's like buying a Bentley and hearing, you know, something
knocking is that's horrible. It's that does not make you feel good. So if that stuff gets fixed,
you know, it's again, it's it doesn't really matter to me. I just want something that's actually
it does matter to me because I when I took the the power book into the shop yesterday to have
David at the HQ take care of it. I was like, man, this thing is heavy. I mean, I mean, kind of
tooling around with the portage, which is like two pounds or something. It's it's a very,
very nice light machine to really use on your lap. You know, no fried nuts or anything like that.
It's good. Something amazing happened to me yesterday, my friends. Something completely amazing.
As you know, England played Sweden. Now, in the world cup finals, football or soccer, as you will.
And the history of this is very much like the like the Miami Heat actually, Miami Heat had never
beat the Mavericks on Mavericks home turf. England has never been able to beat Sweden for 47
years. They've not been able to beat Sweden. And gosh, I wish I was there because England really
got into it this time. Everyone was having Swedish meatballs for dinner and we were going to go
kicked their ass. We were going to win. And it was a fantastic game. Of course, I didn't see the game
because I was at the office. It started. I think it noon. Some people at the office showed up much
later in the day. I wonder if they were watching the match Richard Brewer. But that's okay. I completely
understand. What was interesting, though, is I was in meetings. And I kept getting text messages
from Patricia. She was actually sitting home watching the game and she was totally into it and
she was giving me the score. And she was telling me, oh, now Rune's playing and Beckham looks cute.
Oh, and there's another goal. And this is not my wife. I'm like, what is going on? She does not
watch these things. So I don't know if it's the England spirit that's kicked in. I mean,
my mother-in-law. Yeah, I mean, she watches football religiously and to have her text me with the
score, I would completely expect. But have Patricia do it. I was blown away. She was really
really into it. I can't wait to get home to see this new woman of mine. I really can't.
Hello, Adam. This is Brad Gunter from Berlin. Come back a whole new source of the
good soccer football team. Dude, you sound like you're in a freaking dungeon. You'll see if I can
filter you to make your sound better as is really horrible. Problems in having it trying to get out
the right way to say it. Um, they're not producing it from a German magazine that was about
since it will come here all the, there's magnets in there. Rep dude, would you send that to me again
because you had a really good piece there and it sounded much better when I was previewing it
before the show, but now I can't hear a single word you're saying. It was about the difference between
soccer and football and that actually he says soccer is the appropriate term for the game
because well he has some kind of explanation for it. But it stems back to the 19th century when we had
basically rugby and soccer. But I disagree. I think I think football is football. In fact in Europe,
we say American football when we're talking about football in the States, which is fine. I think
so I don't like soccer. I don't like the name at all. Football is really what it is. You play the
ball with your feet. In fact, you get penalized if you play it with your hand. It's too bad about that.
Sorry. Hey, we haven't done this in a real long time.
Yeah. So I guess the only thing really to talk about well there's two things for the
Metro sexual moment. On today's episode, it's this beard thing. Now I made a very bold statement yesterday
saying that I would grow my beard until we released or unleashed Potso Plus in public data.
Whoa. I've never really really let my my my facial hair grow to any extent. I mean it may be
over the weekend or something or maybe three days at most, but it really itches when it gets
much longer. And and I think it's starting to look kind of scraggly. So I need some advice
instead of me giving you advice. I definitely need some advice on how do I maintain this?
You know, how do I make it not look? Well, I guess part of the point is for me to look like a total
to weave by growing this beard until until we unleash. But does anyone have any recommendations for
tools to use? I mean, all I keep thinking of is that they used to have that Don Johnson like
shaver so you could still keep your stubble going. Should I be clipping it over the sink?
Which is to scum a dad used to do that. And I hate it. So discussing, but it itches and how long
will it take before the itching stops? Now you probably see in the album art for today,
for this podcast, and this was a great, I hope you had me who suggested this to me the other day.
Someone said, hmm, I try to think who it was. Well, anyway, someone suggested that with each podcast,
as the beard grows, instead of the the normal pod father picture that shows up in your
player or in your iTunes or your iPod or wherever you happen to be listening to this show,
we'll stick in a picture of the growth of the beard. Which of course means we can
dedicate an entire show to shaving it off once we're out and we're unleashed. One other thing,
this is from Ole Christian, Christian Valle. I think that's how you pronounce it. This was a
comment. It wasn't email. I think it was an email. Apparently in the catfish show,
which you can find at catfishshow.com, there's a conversation ongoing about women using men's
deodorant and why they do. Is this true ladies? And I know you're listening to the metro sexual
moment. Do you use male deodorant and why? Isn't that stuff supposed to be pH balance for us
and not for you? Inquiring minds, need to know. Yesterday, Roger Smalls had some questions about
sleep. And let me see, can I still make this? Oh crap, yeah, I'll play it now. Because he asked Uncle
Jesse our satellite repairman, you know, P-Dub to come up with some answers as to how we can stop
falling asleep. Hello, Roger. Uncle Jesse here. I understand you're having some trouble with
elective energy and falling asleep on the couch at night. Two things that I have a great deal of
experience with worry no more. The solution is awfully simple, Roger. Here is the easiest solution
to sleeping too much. Simply, schedule an important meeting. I'm sorry, let me start that over.
Simply, schedule an important meeting. Something that will affect your entire existence for
800 the next day. Hopefully, at some location there will be a lengthy commute. Then,
every time you even think about sleeping, recall that you have this important appointment in
the morning. I guarantee you won't sleep even a minute during the night. However, be really careful
in the shower that morning. It's going to be really interesting to see if P-Dub puts that
entire comment on the on the serious show. I kind of slide it right over the over the window there.
Sorry about that P-Dub. Timing is everything I guess. If you have a question,
if you need something answered, if you need advice, there's only one man you need to go to.
The satellite repairman. He takes care of it all.
The satellite repairman. Thank you so much. Everyone who's helping us change advertising by
submitting your own version of a commercial for Earthlink, who are of course sponsors of the
P-Dub podcast networks, fantastic the way this is going. Essentially, we're putting our money
and Earthlink's money. Happy to do that. We're putting that where your mouth is,
which means you get to create the messaging. What's the best way to tell listeners of this
program? I'm not even talking about all podcasts. Maybe this podcast, which is why I'm playing
submissions here, want people who are listening to this show. How do we communicate the message?
What is the best way to do it? Are there more creative ways than the traditional commercial?
Well, it turns out there are. If you go to adchalance.podshow.com, you can submit your
commercial, your endorsement, any type of audio you want really, as long as it's conveying the message
of Earthlink, and I would have to say, as long as it's truthful in conveying the message of Earthlink,
which is what really seems to work best. You can win $2,000.
Yes, great cash prizes. It's all part of our quit your day job program. It's not all that much for
a quit your day job, but damn, it's a start. Let's see how clear I can make this.
And this is what my voice sounds like. With Earthlink's true voice, the internet phone service
from the internet experts. Let your voice speak for itself. Go to earthlink.net today to hear your
true voice.
Yeah, I love it. If only all phone calls sounded like that. Could you also make it Earthlink so that
when people call me, they actually just chirp like birds? Oh, be so beautiful.
Brandon, some problems yesterday with cash blast, I told you about having the, hey, I'm still
learning all this PC stuff. Had, had, had used cash blasts, they're on an extended desktop.
So a secondary screen at the office and when I got home and I fired a cash blaster, a cash
blaster was still on the secondary screen. Only the screen was turned off. And the desktop,
extended desktop was turned off. So it was somewhere on the edges of my screen in cyberspace.
And I was, you know, I had to wheel the mouse over and try and figure out how to, you know,
where I was on cash blaster was I able to click on the, on the title bar and drag it over. And thank
you so much, everyone who sent in comments, a lot of email about how to actually move windows
when this happens. So first of all, it is an application error. Because I think it's something
the program itself can check when it starts up and cash blaster mic emailed me immediately,
laughing out loud, of course, and said, hey, man, I fixed it. So that will never happen again.
So we'll see that in the future release. Apparently, see who sent me this one. This was Shawn
Nichols. Right click on the button in the task bar for the application, select move. Now here,
this is the part that I didn't get. Then you can move the window with the, with the arrow keys.
duh. If only I'd known that one. So you could, of course, can also do it with the mouse, which is
what I had done. But if you select move, oh, you can also select move and then the mouse gets like
crosshairs. But it's a lot easier to use the arrow keys. Yeah, a lot of these shortcuts
I haven't quite figured out yet. And you know what I still really, really miss. I really missed
the Apple key H command. Wow, I noticed how much I used to use that just to hide an application
real quick to get back to the desktop. And I do use the, what is it window start key and D,
which will take you to the desktop and move all the other windows out of the way. But a hide
command would be highly appreciated. Hi Adam. This is Jim Farley. And today, while listening
to the Charlie, you gave me a great idea. It was during the Earthling Prima that you played.
You see the guy mentioned that Earthling was donating band with to hurricane survivors.
Well, I started thinking about that. You see, I wrote a song after Katrina because my
daughter and her husband lost their home and slide Eloiseana to the hurricane and they had come
to live with us here in Ohio. That's when it hit me. If you can arrange it somehow that my song
Katrina is set up to be purchased on the pod safe music network, I would donate my entire portion
to hurricane relief. My daughter and her husband are doing fine, but there are so many others
that still need our help. And I'd like to do more than what I've been doing for them by trying
to generate some real money for the cause. And the pod show listeners have proven that they can
get behind something like this with cancer and other worthwhile causes. So what say you Adam,
is this something that's even plausible? I'd like to think so. And any dollars that we can put into
the hands of the people who need it in that area, not the government's slippery little fingers,
is immensely helpful. I know this firsthand. You can find Katrina along with my other songs on the
pod safe music network. Can we do this? Well, what say you was the question? I say, yeah, of course
we can. In fact, every single pod safe song that we play on the Charlie, as a part of our rolling
unleash is made available for purchase. That is if the artist wants it to be made available for
purchase. So in this case, it's clear you do. Let me just get the song cranking while we're talking
here. So great news. It's Christmas years in the office all this week. So we're on the same
time zone and he'll be certain to contact you to make that available for purchase. And I have to say,
it's instrumental piece, but it's beautiful. And I can just see the images that you go along with this.
So I would suggest video artists out there want you to give a stab at really making this play into
something multimedia. Listen to the song. It's beautiful. You can just see the images
flashing before you.
music
Now, I'm not much of a videographer, but hearing that, I immediately want to run over to
well, used to be Final Cut Pro. Now, of course, it's Adobe Premiere. Now, I'm on Windows.
I want to go edit some video to that beautiful man. So, Christmas years will get in touch with you.
And we'll set that up. And ping me from time to time. Let me know how it's going and remind me.
And I'll play it again. And the best reminder, of course, is if we get some cool videos associated
with that, that'd be great. And you know what? We'll definitely raise some money. It happened,
you know, look at what we did with the MS Walk for the Bitties. I mean, it was like over $20,000.
It was unreal. Yeah, we got a lot of power here. Speaking of power, I promise to once and a while
explain what this whole sense of thing burp is about. Because there are lots of new listeners who
come in and they hear me burp. And then they hear me say sense to him. And they're wondering what
that's all about. This is something that we started, oh man, must be a year ago by now. And it was
really just a simple test and advertising test. I think with the conversation at the time on daily
source code was about advertising. And, you know, I truly believe that the way mainstream
advertising works is through repetition. It's how we elect our presidents. You know, if you
you have $200 million worth of advertising dollars to spend, you can, you have a pretty good
shot at becoming president of the United States. I hate to say it, but that's just the way it is.
You know, people buy different soap powder based upon commercials, stuff they can see over and
over and they can sing the jingle and they can, you know, they know the joke of the spot on TV.
And it's repetition. It really does work. But it's also a part of anchoring or neurolinguistic
programming, or perhaps somewhat called the Vulcan mind trick. And it started, it didn't even
start off with a burp. It started off where I asked you listeners to pick a point. I'm not going to
do it now. I'm not going to, I'm not going to program your mind right now. But, you know, there was a
situation. I said, pick a point, look at it, and then if then I would say Sanseo, and then
whenever you went past that point, you wouldn't be able to help think, but think of Sanseo,
kind of like a virtual billboard. And I was getting people saying that every single time they
moved the lawn and went past a particular bush, they would think of Sanseo. And then I can't
remember how we morphed over to the burp, but it just happened. And by the way, Sanseo pays me
nothing for this. I'm just a lover of the product. They should, though, man. Damn, they should.
Anyway, so it's just kind of an out of hand advertising experiment. But this stuff is working
in very, very strange ways. In fact, the lighter clicks at the end of the show, people now tell
me that whenever they see or whenever they hear a lighter click, they think of the daily source code.
And you may think they're strange, but when you really think through it, it makes a lot of sense.
And I got to come up with more of these things because, well, I'm actually influencing
people's bodies now. Hi, Adam. It's Adros from Potsworth here. A little story of what happened to
me when I was in Asda, the supermarket shopping today. I got to the coffee bowl and saw the Sanseo
and said Sanseo and burps. Just like that. I didn't need to burp before. It just said the words
and about came out. Something very, very powerful in what you're doing, isn't it? But that is
its powerful asmojo, man. I'm telling you. So, okay, everyone pay attention. Sanseo,
how many of you burped? Hey, Adam. This is Travis Goss. The host and executive producer of
the Ungradio show. And, well, I need me a little bit of help here. No, I've asked for help a lot
times for me and really didn't get much of anything. So, whenever you have a sense say a moment,
can you plug the Ungradio show? You've done it for Don Drew and everybody else. When you have
a sense say a moment. So, what about me? You know, I've been a listener to yours since episode
3-4-2. I know I'm a late bloomer right here. Better late than never. But, you know, hey,
this whenever you have a sense say a moment, take of me because, walk quite frankly, the numbers
haven't low this month. You know, these were a listening feeling a little bit insecure of myself
and, you know, I need to know that I matter. I mean, it's no that the show or that I have
is going to be doing just well. So, I said say a moment, probably be very uplifting and make
going people want to listen because whenever you have a sense say a moment, it's like a golden hand
touches something that was once dead and brings it back to life. Oh yes. Okay, that was where you
were done. Yeah, that made it very frightening. But anyways, hey, make me help me out since
day and moment. You know, in a radio show, we're on iTunes, podcast alley. We even have an online
shop now, which can be found at cafepress.com slash on radio shop. We got t-shirts, I had,
button, even got a teddy bear. So, how about it? Yeah, how about it? Well, you got your plug there,
my friend. I don't have to burp. I'm sorry. I don't know what it is. There's no burp
just today. I'll just go back to the video again for Katrina. We met some guys, actually a
methamenpebble beach when we were at the Clienter Perkins conference from this company called
onetruemedia.com and I had heard of them before and hadn't really paid attention to what they
were doing. And actually I played golf. I remember I had the horrendous 14 holes
of golf. Where everyone hid behind the cart when I was teeing off. So, Mark from onetruemedia
came to the office yesterday with John CEO of the company. Wow, man, where are we a match
mate in heaven? This is beautiful stuff. You should check it out because they have an online
video editing tool. Now, they say they have at least another year, maybe two years of development,
you know, to really get all kinds of great effects and stuff. But, um, and I was a little bit
skeptical about it until I tried it out. In fact, I will try to do something with the Katrina
video myself today. Basically, you just upload video and then you can edit the video, the sequence,
you can put pictures in, you can add different sound. A very, very simple and effective way to
yeah, to basically mix and mash and create a video. And, of course, what we talked about is
hooking it up to the podcast delivery network. Very similar, in fact, to what a cast blast
does for audio. So, um, you should check that out and go take a look at it and, uh, let me know what
you think. And, well, you'll let me know what you think by sending something in or not or creating
something for the Katrina, Katrina video. Not just another piece of the stuff. We'll have every
single day, there's a new piece of opportunity. And, for the first time in quite a while,
it seems like the comments on curry.com are synchronizing with the audio on the daily source code.
Yeah, everything's kind of going in parallel now. And the whole impetus for this is that I was talking
about getting a Sony Vio laptop. Now, there are many different models and versions,
all very complicated letters and number combinations. But essentially, Ron and I decided it was best
if, uh, if I got the same one he has, which is a high-end one. It doesn't really matter to me.
I just want a faster processor. Um, but the reason, of course, is so that I can be his help desk,
which I've been for 12 years now. So, I'm used to it. I don't mind. Because if I say, hey, you know,
that thing that's not working on our computers, how do I fix that? Um, but apparently, the fact
that it's made in Japan has rubbed someone the wrong way. Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip.
Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip.
Check it out what he has to say. All hail. So, I don't carry. Do you care about Wales? No,
I don't mean those ship shaggers, who is the only ethnic group in UK, preserved the original
Celtic language. Do you got to be so careful when you say comic strip blogger? I mean Wales.
Those big fees that are mamas. Since you and your boyfriend, your own bloom,
use now Japanese notebooks. And you want to buy new Japanese notebook. Maybe you and
whole where it should know that Japanese won't kill Wales by forcing small nations, even those
without access to flipping sea to vote for a resuming of where hunting. Japanese are succilling
if you care about Wales, you shouldn't buy Japanese products. So, do you really care about Wales?
Or about other issues that bother all those three hugging hippies from Greenpeace? I don't think so.
Proof me wrong. By playing this audio comment. Anyway, here you like the podcast creator.
It was all over the news last night. I have to admit, right on topic there.
Even the Daily Show had a whole bit on what Japan is. I haven't read into the material and I've
learned long ago not to form an opinion based upon what you see on television, essentially.
I think that that may be going a little bit too far to boycott the Sony.
Sony owns most of America, dude, in case you didn't know. Now, I'm not to share about the
whale issue, but I will certainly look into it. Hello, I'm calling from Wales. I figured that
since as a recent convert to your show, I give it a shot and see what you thought of a real
Welsh accent. So, from South Wales can be packed in my cafe again and present, waiting to go and see
a film. Can't you say go to watch it? And I'm absolutely bursting for a pee. Anyway, there has
a said in a recent convert and I kind of like the show, I think. It's the only reason why I
stayed behind to save a clock and work so they can download the show until I knock you and then
have a listen while I'm going down the M4. So, you look after yourself, hello to everyone and bye-bye.
Happy pudding, see you all. Happy pudding back at you. That's the real whales. It's pretty interesting
how they, I believe that the use of the Welsh is it a language or is it dialect? I'm not quite sure.
It's, you know, the more and more people are starting to speak it. I wouldn't mind learning a
little bit. There's a couple of Welsh podcasts and believe me, we'll be featuring those when we
unleashed in the UK as well. I've learned one thing about the UK. People do not want the impression
that, you know, all the good stuff comes from London and there's a lot of good stuff that does
not come from London in the UK. A lot of great football does not come from London in the UK.
So, we're definitely learning a lot about, I'm learning a lot about the diversity of the
country. I got to make a few trips, man. I got to fly around in the UK. Let that be high on the
agenda for the next couple of weeks when I'm back at the cottage. I'll drum up Jason who'll be
my safety pilot for who is my safety pilot for inland flights and we'll fly to some other places.
Maybe we'll meet some people. I got to learn more about this country. Seeing as I live there and
have the time. Two things that have been raging in the debate in the blogosphere.
Let's see, I don't know if you read about this story, the world intellectual property organization
is trying to pass some legislation. Now, here's the story as it's kind of being paraphrased
in reporting on the internet. I did take the time to go to the world into the weepo. Weepo,
the world intellectual property organization, and read the actual proposal, which was man,
Jersey Todd helped me out. This thing was so full of legalese. It wasn't funny.
So, the way it's been and I think I understand it now. What is being reported on now and there's a petition?
There's a podcast of petition, in fact. You can find that, I'll put a link in the show notes.
There's a petition that was a couple of podcast guilds and I didn't know that there was,
I knew there was the UK podcast association or guild or something, but there's one in Germany
and there's a couple other from around the world. They've come together and they said,
we have to stop this legislation. Now, basically, the reason why people are crying,
follow over this is because there is a secondary effect that this legislation could have and
then I want to talk about what I think the legislation is really for. In effect, this legislation
says is that if a television, I'll just take the simplest example. If a television network,
broadcasts anything, regardless, even if they use the snippet in fair use as a news item,
a snippet of the daily source code, they would, in effect, own that. So, the transmission of that,
they will own anywhere on broadcast television, on radio, but also on the internet for 50 years.
So, you know, it's clear that, well, it's clear that that is a huge issue when it comes to
pod save music, you know, creative commons, my personal copyright over anything that I produce.
I think the intent of the law is what we really should be looking at because this is going to
change number of businesses that are quite popular right now. If I understand correctly and I could
be wrong, but I really, I did put some time into it to read this stuff. This is about something
called signal theft. And when you think about it, it takes a lot of infrastructure to, and of
course, this is why protectionist laws are put in place. It takes a lot of infrastructure to get
a television signal to you. And you may not even be seeing that television signal necessarily
on a television. It may come through the internet. It could be a digital version of this signal
that is streamed or a snippet that ABC or NBC or CNN or some other three letter acronym
puts up on the internet. And I believe that this legislation is a shot across the bow of sites like
YouTube and Revere and other viral video websites. Because, you know, if you, if I had a
dime for every person that says, I don't watch television anymore. I just go to YouTube and
type in a search term and it brings up that news report or that skit or that particular thing I
wanted to see. Now, that is where the signal theft is taking place. And I do understand the television
networks and where they're coming from because it costs a lot of money to, to get this signal out.
Even if they're using other people's copyrighted works with their permission, of course,
to create their signal. See it almost as a mashup. You know, I'm using all kinds of,
all kinds of elements. In fact, maybe 70% of my show is created by other people. It's pot-sake
music or it's comments or whatever. And everyone retains their own copyright. Now, in this case,
I want distribution. I want people to listen to this show. I want them to copy it. It has tremendous
benefit to me. It has benefit to the people who contribute to the program, which includes advertisers.
But if I were old school and mainstream, then I would probably say, hey, I don't want anyone touching
this. I don't want it. It's almost the same as the record companies. We can't put a free and clear
MP3 out there. So this is about theft of signal. Because you're basically, and this is coming
from the television networks perspective, you're riding on the back of their investment to utilize
this content. Even if, excuse me, senseo on radio show. There you go. I did it.
And I believe that it is a piece of legislation that essentially will be used to try and shut down
sites like YouTube. If I'm wrong, let me know. But I don't think that this is necessarily meant as a
malicious attack against copyright in general. Although it can be misconstrued that way. So I think
let them have it. Let them have their signal protection. Because we all agree, it's fun to watch it on
YouTube. But if the network doesn't put the video up themselves of the Saturday Night Live
skit, it's in violation. We all understand that. It may not be fun, but it's in violation. So that's
their right to put that up. And of course, they would also have to clear that with the individual
copyright holders, if they have the right to even put that online at all. Because often those
rights are not associated with broadcast rights. So maybe, and maybe I do have to call on our
musicologist and our Jersey Todd official attorney of the show to give me a little more insight
and perspective on this. Just it seems like we're all yelling and shouting about the wrong thing here.
And then one other topic, and then I will shut down actually this will end with the song.
I just messed up my outline here. I do that. Okay, here we go. It's crap.
Here it is. The whole net neutrality debate. Now, I think we were talking about this about this
on a daily source code way before Boeing Boeing started talking about it. And this is, and actually
it hit when the chairman of SBC said, hey, you know, we feel that we're putting all in all this
infrastructure and all these pipes and we're basically building a huge network for other people
to make money with and with other people, I believe, is referring to Google and Yahoo. And in a way,
it could also be Pod Show. And that those providers of content would have to pay an additional
fee for the high speed delivery to the home, which commercially, I guess, if you think about it,
it's their right. Now, the overall conversation, of course, is about something called net neutrality,
meaning that anyone should be able to access anything on the internet, if it's made of freely
available, there should no be certain, there shouldn't be any surcharges on either the consumer side
or on the provider side, because essentially they're already paying for the bandwidth. Again,
I think we may not have all the information. I think that there are some rights, if SBC is putting
in huge infrastructure for better, faster network, they can certainly try in charge, whatever they
want for, they're not a monopoly, they're big, I'll give you that, but they're not a monopoly,
there are other networks. So, I think competition is, and I don't see anything anti-competitive
about this, I think that's the way to solve these issues. If AT&T is charging too much,
like if Comcast charge it too much for my internet access, I get another provider,
I would actually consider Earthling. If I don't know if I can get that here, probably can't,
I should actually, I should actually, I should get Earthling, I should be smoking our own dope,
shouldn't I? So, there's a lot of pile jumping going on, and again, I'm not totally convinced
that this is going to be horrible and bad for the internet. I don't jump all over my shit,
because again, I think that competition plays a huge role here, and we're not necessarily
abided by whatever SBC says. We just aren't. There are other networks that the traffic can
travel over. If those networks aren't fast enough or good enough, you have two choices.
You know, get more people to work with the alternative networks and build them up and help
them get the billions they need to fill out the infrastructure or someone has to pay,
look, someone has to pay somewhere sometime. Ben with is just not for free. Ask any podcaster
who's, you know, who all of a sudden gets a hate of success, and they're on their, you know,
web hosting account, and all of a sudden, if a couple thousand people show up, you run out of
bandwidth, and you know, it's not free. The stuff is just not free. We want to think it's free,
because blogging is so virtually free, but that uses up so little bandwidth. In fact, we already
have this whole net neutrality situation with the cell phone carriers. I mean, we can do incredibly
cool stuff with networks. We can send all kinds of great things down the pipeline, but you have
no access. You have no direct access to the cell phone networks, because you got to go through
the cell phone operators, and they will charge your nuts off to get anything onto their network.
This is why, yeah, sure. We can do some things, and, you know, if, if you want, you can certainly
download a podcast through your 3G mobile, but then look at your bandwidth bill at the end of the day,
or at the end of the month. It's going to be humongous because, yeah, you really only get a gig in
and they have all these fit-quote fair use policies of how much you can down. There is no free
lunch in this world. So, you know, something immediate, yeah, maybe SBC will do this in the future,
but something really immediate when it comes to net neutrality is the darn cell phone operators.
The network operators are, they're, I'm not going to say they're evil, but they are definitely
not playing a fair game for anyone to just do something, because they're protecting their network,
because they'd like to charge for, well, look, here, here's a perfect example. What do you pay for
a text message? How much do you pay? 5 cents, 10 cents? 1 cents? I don't care. You can't, you can't,
almost can't measure what that costs. It's so low. It's 0.0000001 dollar to actually send that
text message over the network. But what's happening? Net neutrality kicks in, which there isn't any,
and you pay 10 cents to send a text message. So, this is not something new. You know, this is,
and by the way, the cell phone company spent billions, billions on their networks. They have to
make it back somehow. So, if I have to pay a little bit extra, I'm used to it. Do I want to know?
Do I like the fact that someone has actually made a song about this whole thing? Well, yeah,
course I do. Hey, Mr. Telecom, man. God say the internet. Don't change my reality.
Keep that neutrality. God say the internet. All I want to be is to read your tunes,
where I get my music, and I get my news, where I hook up with the creep, or I find my shoes,
don't bring me down. It's a no time to tell about a mother and a man, where some of them
folks in our congress want to send us back to the days of the party at the press. And slow us,
believe us. Hey, Mr. Telecom, man. God say the internet. Don't change my reality.
Keep that neutrality. God say the internet. All I want to be is to read your tunes,
where some Republican brothers, people joining this band, folks pissed off, all over this land,
all over this land. Don't cry for the wealthy channel, man, with their hands in the pocket of the government.
The free market kicks pass, as long as free market means, you've all your money to them.
You want your money to them. Hey, Mr. Telecom, man. God say the internet. Don't change my reality.
Keep that neutrality. God say the internet.
Keep that neutrality. Keep that neutrality. Keep that neutrality. Keep that neutrality.
Keep that neutrality. Keep that neutrality. Keep that neutrality. Keep that neutrality. Keep that neutrality.
But say the internet. Don't change my reality. Keeping that neutrality. God say the internet.
Hey, Mr. Telecom, man. God say the internet. Keep that neutrality.
Here we go, Javier, you are so hot today
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Don't say it, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Don't change my reality
I'm gonna go out there, you're so dirty
You're my dog, I'll say it
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm gonna go out there
Okay
I'll say it, yeah
I love it when people are creative
But this is, it's a bit over the top Britney Spears
What does he have to do with it?
It's almost like an American folk song
The good old US god save the internet
Internet ain't going anywhere, come on
I'm gonna also alarmist if you're against this stuff
Find a representative you can vote for
And call the other guy and tell him why you're gonna vote for some other person
That's what works you, we all have voter fatigue in this country
I like the fact that you're making songs and we have all kinds of groovy protests
But, you know, get into the political system
That's how you want to do it
Ten cents per text message, okay?
That's a bigger problem right now
You know, we're being, look at your cell phone bill at the end of the month
It's ten times your internet bill, ten times
And, you know, why?
Well, because these guys got to recoup their investment
And if you feel that they've recoup their investment far enough
You know, and that they're just ripping you off go to another provider vote with your wallet vote with your vote
Oh, hey, that's it for today. I'm off to the office
I think we got another game starting in just minutes
So I'll continue to watch the football and I appreciate all of you for tuning in
By cast Lester
Of course you didn't really tune in. It's a podcast you downloaded you subscribe
Talk to tomorrow everybody bye-bye
Such an amateur another pop show podcast stick it in your ear
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from
Potcho and lime light networks. I love it