Think Advertising sucks.
Think you can do better?
Pod Show and EarthLink are willing to put our money where your mouth is.
Listen to this podcast or go to adchelens.podshow.com to see how you can win big
in the EarthLink make advertising better challenge.
Delta Sierra Charlie 406, another sunny day in San Francisco.
I love you, big heart fag.
Even if your balls might sag.
I had a miss as your favorite purple dinosaur stopping by to tell you that I
want to put my fist in your ass.
I'm going to be in the Bay Area next week and I was hoping to binge you over a table
and pump you harder than a Mexican oil.
Good day, good day.
Let's sing another song, shall we?
Adams ass feels real tight.
I could bang him day and night too.
Well, Adam Gurney thanks for spending time with me.
Maybe next time you can come over some afternoon for cake and crumpets
and I can tea bag you with my big purple going first.
Good day, good day.
That would be great.
Bye bye.
See you later.
Oh yeah, not entirely family say.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
Transmeters?
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need nuss.
Thinking transmeters?
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Honesting is Adam Gurney.
Can't find a pulse, can't find a heartbeat.
Nobody will sense a lie.
Packin' you live with your eyes closed.
To you tonight you're alive.
You don't want to see, you don't want to feel.
You don't want to touch you in the body.
I know you're keeping away.
In the darkness, you may as well.
Stickin' life into your heart.
You may as well.
Put a puppet in your head.
Send yourself on fire.
Catching things will be dead.
We'll take you, believe when you get hurt.
All right, you never love her.
To you, if we're no don't you can.
We'll take you to this day.
You don't want to see, you don't want to feel.
You don't want to touch you in the body.
I know you're keeping away.
In the darkness, you may as well.
Stickin' life into your heart.
You may as well.
Put a puppet in your head.
Send yourself on fire.
Catching things will be dead.
You may as well.
Stickin' life into your heart.
Put a puppet in your head.
You may as well.
Send yourself on fire.
Catching things will be dead.
Open your eyes, breathe in the air.
Just looking around, laughs every breath.
Only once it's only one life.
Don't you know that you're still alive.
You don't want to see, you don't want to feel.
You don't want to touch you in the body.
I know you're keeping away.
In the darkness, you may as well.
Stickin' life into your heart.
You may as well.
Put a puppet in your head.
Send yourself on fire.
Catching things will be dead.
You may as well be dead.
Voice your fuel from down under.
Better off dead.
A request from my official audio library in Tom Scrooting, who lives in Australia.
It's a made of his.
And you can find him on the pod safe music network.
Voice your fuel.
Hey, good morning, everybody.
It's Monday and it's another beautiful day in San Francisco.
It's going to be beautiful and warm.
No doubt about it.
How you doing?
Hope you had a great weekend.
If you're dead, hope you had a great father's day.
If you're not, and you still have it at, hope you gave him a great father's day.
Everything good here in the condo.
It was the weekend.
I don't think I saw a single solitary cloud at all.
It was just so incredibly nice.
Yesterday morning, I slept in a little bit.
So around 10 o'clock.
I got a, I got a text message from Martha.
Ron's wife.
And she said, I am taking the two dads out for brunch.
Dad's who's kids aren't around this father's day.
Martha and Ron's son, August in Miami.
I think, and of course, I'm away from home.
So that was really nice.
Went to the Ritz Carlton and had,
the nice father's day brunch, which was just fantastic.
And it's so good to see that even though in this very posh,
Schwab sophisticated hotel and everyone's, you know,
Schwab and having a nice sophisticated brunch,
which was fantastic food, of course.
Really great to see that on the screen right there,
above the, what was the, it was above the eggs.
Right above the eggs was a flat screen with,
with the, with the, with the football match with the soccer match.
Fantastic.
I think America has finally caught on to how cool football really is.
Uh, of course, we called football when we're from Europe.
But you know, I'm talking about soccer.
See, what I do Saturday.
Saturday, I really slept in.
Man, I was, I was so just incredibly tired from,
from, I don't know, from the, from the, from life in general.
Is that, is that possible?
But anyway, got, got a rock and show lined up for you.
Lots of feedback.
Lots of, well, thank you very much.
I have a feeling it was Mark Yoshimura Nemkoff who,
who was good friends and is real tight with Barney.
Appreciate that man.
That's perfect way to kick off anyone they show.
If you want to stay up today with all things Apple,
then you should subscribe to the all about Apple podcast.
Each week, we talk about Apple news, rumors, product reviews,
and we run several unique segments.
We just finished our first episode and we'll be on the road for episode two and three.
Making live stops in Las Vegas and New Mexico.
So visit iTunes podcasting and search for all about Apple.
We'll have a domain name coming soon,
but for now, just search for all about Apple in iTunes.
Hope to see you soon and hope you're subscribed.
Right on.
Speaking of all about Apple,
I think I really gave this PC a workout over the weekend.
Yeah, I guess Saturday, a lot of time was spent.
Oh, of course I know what I did Saturday.
Oh, my nuts.
Of course I went to the, to the Valley Tab,
or to hang out with the Boys and Girls from Pod Show to watch the USA.
More about that later in this show.
Lots of cool feedback from people.
But I really gave the, the laptop a workout.
And I got to tell you, so far it's holding up.
I haven't had any weird crashes or anything really funky happen.
I've been putting it through the test.
It gets a lot less hotter than any Mac I've had.
So I should have taken the power book to the, to the genius bar on Saturday.
I am so tired of this.
I think what I'll do is I'll just ask David from, from Pod Show HQ.
If you can take care of it because I really don't want to see it back for a while.
You know, I'm kind of like a jilted lover.
And yes, I've got my new, my new sexy friend.
My sexy girlfriend, the Porter J.
Hey Adam, this is Rodrigo.
I don't think I'm on the resident enjoying the boobs test.
That's you.
No, this is so cool.
We had a conversation.
I think it was maybe last week about when in the UK in London in particular,
when the weather heats up, it's just,
oh man, the women just, everything is, is, it's a boobfest.
Okay, it's just a boobfest.
It's a wonderful time.
Everybody's happy and it's all hanging out.
Who has been having fun in Pod Show Beta?
But to tell you folks up there, it is good.
I mean, both Pod Show Beta, Pod Show Plus and the boobs.
But I've got a question for you.
I've been telling you about Pod Show Plus.
And I can't wait to have them on the inside to start building up my entourage and
share shows with them.
But how will you be releasing Pod Show Plus?
Will it be like Gmail or rightly by invitation only in the beginning?
Or will it be open to everyone from the get-go?
Hey, I mean, Pod is talking to her about Trinity.
Let us know how she's doing.
Love what you're doing.
Keep on casting.
So Rodrigo is a buddy of ours who lives in London.
He's from Brazil, I believe.
Met him, by the way, when we were in London a couple weeks back.
Nice guy.
And so he's in the Pod Show Plus Beta.
Very good question.
How are we going to release it?
Well, I guess if you were to compare it to Gmail or rightly or anything else.
I guess the golden tickets really is kind of how we've gotten a couple hundred people in and
start using the system, start banging it, start ripping it apart.
So the plan is to just open up, which is really scary.
You know, because the minute you open up, that's it.
You know, it's your asses out there.
And of course, a whole bunch of stuff.
You know, a whole bunch of stuff is going to be wrong.
And I'm going to work and people will say this and say that.
So we're just going to balls to the wall and it's coming very soon.
And it'll just open up.
And it'll open up on all sides.
For Pod castes, of course, the Pod cast delivery network.
Excuse me.
Sen Seo.
The Sen Seo moment brought to you by Digital Flotson.
So we'll open it wide up and it's weird not far off.
We're getting very close.
You can hear more people who are in there.
We've been testing it.
I like the Rodrigo is using some of the language that we're using.
Like, I want to get more people in my entourage.
Oh, yeah.
But even more important Rodrigo.
Thank you very much for that London Boob report.
Hey, Adam Curry.
I would just listen to your daily source code from yesterday June 60.
I don't want to say yay for the hot chicks and London in the summer condom.
I'm going to be there next week.
This is the Pod chick.
And I hope I can just see you.
But I probably won't put it there.
Okay.
I know that you are with me and spirit as you always are.
Very helpful.
Thank you so much.
And I'm pretty much about it.
My convertible in the bikini right now.
And now I have a ball.
I'm kind of that.
Hot chicks.
No summer condom here too, baby.
All right.
Make them soil.
Hmm.
Pod chick.
Yeah, you made me smile baby.
Lovely.
More of that, please.
More UK boob feedback.
Not a problem.
You know, in the US, we have a real problem with that.
Of course.
Because we can't be showing any of that.
We can't even talk about it.
You can't even say the word nipple on the radio.
I mean, I just think about that.
Maybe you can say nipple on the radio now.
Maybe since the Janet Jackson Ward drove malfunction, you are allowed to say,
when we are an MTV, when I was on the Royal Wii was on MTV,
there's no way we were, you could not say nipple.
You could say nothing, not even close.
Let alone what you're about to hear.
Something that you would never hear on terrestrial radio ever.
This is a conversation that was recorded.
You know, we have, you have all kinds of technology at Pod Show,
and we have all these different satellite offices.
Now, PW Fenton, of course, you know from digital flotsom.
If not, you have to check out his podcast, digital flotsom.org.
He also manages all the serious satellite production,
so that every single day there's another show for you.
Four hour block of shows on serious satellite,
one-o-two.
But somehow, while he was having a conversation,
I think this is with Brian Know of the Frank Truth podcast,
which also is heard, I think once a week on stars one-o-two,
we can't play it as a podcast because it basically contains
copyrighted music from Frank Sinatra.
And this is not your family, don't like that.
But check out this conversation that was accidentally recorded,
and I do put the emphasis on accidentally between PW and Brian.
Hey, PW, it's me, Brian.
Hey, Brian, what's going on?
Dude, did you hear that Adam ran into some trouble with a training
out in San Francisco?
Yeah, that really sucks.
It's going to cost him plenty, too.
Well, it's weird that he's being so open about it.
Well, I don't know why, I mean, we've all been there.
So you don't think that's a little weird?
Why? That sort of thing has happened to me many times over the years.
What's the big deal?
Man, I'm so happy to hear you say that.
I've been feeling like I'm the only one in the world.
Can I share something with you?
Sure.
Well, I've got this one drawer in my dresser,
and it's just filled with these really special
tetties and beautiful lingerie.
And every now and then, I like it.
What?
Well, Granny, transmission.
He was talking about the transmission on Trinity that went out on him.
So, dude, tell me more about this lingerie.
I have to go now.
You guys have waited once time on your hands.
We've got to find more work for you.
Always willing and able and curious to hear your feedback.
Voice mail phone line numbers.
A new jersey is 2016256357.
Probably the best number for you if you're using Skype out since I believe it's still
still Skype out free month or whatever.
And the new Skype.
On the PC, I have to say, is quite remarkable.
The sound quality and Ron has one of these newfangled
VIO laptops.
I'm kind of jealous about that.
It's got the built-in camera.
And that shit just works right out of the box.
Amazing.
Even though I don't have a camera, which is one of those things.
Usually, if you don't both have a camera on both ends of these video
conferencing tools, then it doesn't work.
I don't know what those guys are doing in Estonia.
But they're doing a good job.
In the UK and London, we also have a phone line for you to call
02076813753.
Probably if you're calling from work.
Or if you're twine like the hippie chick.
Hey, Adam.
This is twine like the hippie.
I'm calling it about the drink you mentioned on DSC405.
The snake bite.
The heck drink reminds me of an Irish car bomb.
Drinks that also will make people crazy.
To make it, fill a shot glass.
Half and half, fill a Irish cream.
Jamison Irish whiskey.
Then you drop this shot glass into a glass of Guinness.
Shug immediately.
Delicious.
Oh, an Adam.
Remember at a previous Charlie where you asked me to kind of boil an ampoule
because you had been a very bad boy.
I remember that.
And that I'd let you know.
I'll be at the poorville media ex-sobixier.
So if you're continue to beat that on the Charlie,
I'll be half to pack in the special pad.
I'll put in your name on it.
Oh.
You, me and Barney, baby.
Yeah.
I really don't.
And I think I do remember twine like the hippie chick.
Send me an acopicture.
Will you?
Yeah.
I remember back in the late 80s at MTV.
We didn't have email.
We didn't feel it.
No.
I did have email, actually.
But no one else had email.
Very few people.
And they used to be just big postal bags of mail that would come in.
Unbelievable sacks.
And I had a dressing room that had a, had a, had a, had it's own bathroom.
And there was just no way you could read it all.
It was just so much.
And often on that was it to dial MTV.
I think was the, the show that is now TRL live was a total request live.
So that used to be called dial MTV.
And it always, I'd solicit pictures there too.
And you know what?
I used to get them.
I was yes.
We were 20 years younger back in the day.
Hey, this past weekend.
How, how do you think our boys did there in Germany?
Our, our US football team.
I thought it was phenomenal.
Well, phenomenal what these guys did.
Richard Brewer, hey, who, a lot of the podcasters.
Certainly those were on the Podgeo podcast network.
No, had, he's a former Brit.
He actually became a US citizen about four or five years ago.
He's mad about football, of course.
And mad about beer.
And, and he set up a kind of like an informal meet for us all to go hang out
at the Valley Tavern.
So I kind of stumbled out of bed.
I actually caught the kickoff of the game here at home, which was at 12 o'clock
and then hopped in the cab and, and screwed over there.
And it was great.
We were actually all standing in a bar, drinking, watching the game.
And it was, it was cool.
Here were Americans totally into the game.
I've never seen this before.
And, you know, the guy in the cab was like, hey, you know,
have you heard what's going on with the game?
It's, it's exciting.
It's really, really cool.
And as I told you, I think that this game is perfect.
It's perfect because there's, you know, there's perfect for US sports.
You know, it's, it is fast pace.
There is, there's, you know, some real, there's some aggression on the field.
And you can get pissed off yourself as someone just watching the game.
Particularly if you've got a, if you've got a ref who's handing out yellow and red cards
like crazy, that was a bit outrageous.
And then to, to wind up playing, you know, a draw, one, one,
with only nine guys versus, uh, versus 10.
I thought was great.
Although it was kind of funny.
Uh, you know, people know I don't drink rarely drink.
So, uh, but of course when you're in, you know, when you're in the tavern
and you're watching the game, you've got to drink something.
And so Richard said, yeah, you want to drink?
So yeah, give me anything.
So I'm like, yeah, I figured give me a pint or you know,
something big and manly.
And what do you give me like a, a raspberry vodka?
What's up with that?
Hey Adam, this is Chad from Vancouver to say,
work listening to the Charlie and I just wanted to say,
uh, I hope the American team has, uh,
I don't know.
This is some kind of hemorrhoid pillow,
or something because they're going to get butt fucked
more, man.
Let's just be honest.
Uh, this is interesting.
Americans are not ready for soccer, dude.
So, uh, anyways, uh, can't wait to watch the game.
I don't know what I'm going to download it or watch it live either way.
Uh, I'm sure I'll be watching the American team get butt fucked.
And I'm always saying that because the Canadian team didn't get it in a pissed off.
Anyway, uh, I love the show and, uh, keep it real.
Oh, boy.
All right.
Well, clearly, they didn't, they didn't get spanked.
They did a great job.
And now if we can only beat, uh, what does it do?
We have to beat Ghana now, of course.
Turn out to be a lot stronger than anyone expected.
So I put you to play that one on Friday with man.
How wrong were you?
I boys did a great job.
Hey Adam, Chad from Canada here again.
You watched the, uh, American versus Italy game.
Yeah, there you go.
I spiked the draw there, but you got to admit to it.
It only totally fucking raped American.
No, that's not true.
What are you talking about?
Not at all.
It comes to the offensive line there.
They, they definitely had the advantages.
Casey Keller is probably going to be, you know, one of the best gullies out there right now.
He's unbelievable.
Anyways, I just called to, uh, give my feedback on the game.
I definitely think it only had the better offensive line there.
But, uh, I don't know, man.
That, that gullies was unbelievable.
Now, on both sides of gullies, I'm unbelievable.
Yeah, indeed.
This is a good game.
I like to get draw and, you know,
but everyone's in a while, I like to see somebody get spiked.
Anyway, um, don't take that dissectional.
No, I think you have sexual repressed problem to a friend.
And by the way, isn't a World Cup soccer just a fantastic use of television.
You know, we've got all this, all the other media video, video media stuff figured out.
We know what we really want to be seeing when it comes to video.
But for sports, yeah, that television stuff got admit.
It does kind of work.
Hi, Adam.
It's Jordan from Grand Prairie, Alberta, Canada.
Now, you might think I'm talking to you in the middle of a post-World Cup game mob.
But you'd be so wrong.
As it happens, I live in a small city about 50,000 souls called Grand Prairie.
About 500 kilometers from Edmonton, home to the Edmonton Oilers.
Now, the Oilers have made a comeback of a winning streak to force a seventh and final showdown from the Carolina Hurricanes.
As you can see, the crowd here doesn't seem to care what's happening in the World Cup,
so I guess it's like Einstein said, things are relative.
Well, with jubilant honking horns to all sport fans out there,
whether it's hockey, cricket, basketball, or football, or football,
shoot a kill-in, keeping broadcasting in the center of pop culture in Grand Prairie, Alberta, Canada.
This is Jordan.
Oh, Adam.
Yo.
Thanks for all your hard work keeping this new media of podcasting free.
Not like beer, like speech.
Right, I'm in.
See you later, dude.
They're actually people who tell me that besides the sense,
they didn't say, oh, subliminal programming, that whenever they hear someone click a lighter,
they think of the daily source code as well.
Ah, it's work and my evil plan is coming together.
Travis Martin says, hey, Adam, I'm an Omni Outliner user myself,
but a friend once asked me to find him an app for windows that was comparable.
Now, this, of course, was the only piece of software that I really missed using on the,
on the power book was Omni Outliner, a fantastic outlining tool.
Just drag and drop files in, and you can play him straight from the outline,
or just it really worked.
And I spent a good deal of time in the past week trying to find an alternative.
There was, I don't even remember half of the tree.
Oh, so it was the one that I'd been using.
Oh, second.
Let me check.
I already deleted it from my, I already took it off.
Anyway, so Travis turns me on to this new thing called Keynote,
which, of course, is not to be confused with Keynote from Apple,
which kind of makes it all that much funcure,
because Keynote is a presentation tool, and also kind of has an outline or built in.
So I went to the website, and of course, you'll find a link to that in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
or at curie.com when we cross post.
And you'll see that I think the product that's discontinued the developer who was working on it,
no longer is supporting it.
But, wow.
Hold on a second.
If you want to hear more about that particular application,
you'll have to listen to the rest of the podcast at dailysourcecode.com.
If you are checking us out on stars 102 on serious,
and we've got Pacific Coast Hellway coming up next followed by Madge Weinstein.
I'll see you guys tomorrow, okay?
Take care.
It's like window closed.
So I go over to the website,
and check this out.
I download this thing.
This program, Keynote, is unbelievable.
It's exactly what I wanted.
It has two, it has dual pains.
So you can have your outline in one,
and then the notes that go along with each node in a different one.
It will let you, it will link to files that are on your disk.
So that's relative, you can drag and drop stuff in,
and then if you want to see what that particular file is,
or listen to it, you just click on it from the outlineer.
It has tabbed view, it has all these amazing features.
Like how can I, how can I ever live without all this?
And it resizes and you can have a vertical view.
So instead of the tree outline on the left and the notes on the right,
you can have the tree outline on the top or the bottom
and the notes underneath or above that.
If you're interested in outlining,
and just for me it's the way I put the show together.
You know, it's fantastic Keynote.
Great stuff.
A couple more conversations to complete with me talking about the so-called illegal,
although it is highly disputed now.
The drink snake bite, which is often consumed in the UK.
Some say it's illegal, some say it's not, the jury's kind of out,
but it is a drink to be tried.
Hi, I don't know if this is David Worthier.
I like the Snipsing Real Life.
I'm just a listener living the Charlie East since November of last year,
and I hope you can get more podcasting.
I have a couple of points on DSC 404.
You've had a conversation with a gentleman who really is podcast,
really used to post-sign music.
Yeah, and haven't had a quick look at the post-sign music network,
fact page.
It looks well.
It's a thing on detail to me.
There was also a comment on DSC 405,
which is a nice and signal post-sign music for commercial use.
Yeah, this is good.
This is actually, we've gotten into some good stuff here about the podcast,
and music network.
We kind of go over this once every couple of months,
but I think it's well worth it.
This was regarding putting up a companion feed.
Oh, I forgot who was doing that.
Anyway, the guys who were doing that immediately stopped,
and they said thanks, now we understand better.
Yeah, if you go to the FAQs,
the frequently asked questions,
not all those questions are actually asked.
And I think we do need to update them.
If you go to the terms,
which really there's only like three bullet points in the terms
that pertain to any of this stuff.
It is very clear,
and it's almost written in English,
not bad for a lawyer who put it together for Brian,
actually who wrote that up for us.
But I agree,
I think we probably should put a couple more lines into the FAQ,
just so it's abundantly clear.
But it seems to me a lot of reports
on the DSC,
and this my ship is more of a tacky time nature.
You don't necessarily have good legal skills.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What do I mean?
Speak for yourself, man.
Come on.
Speak for yourself.
Perhaps you could think of getting the fact that you expanded a little bit,
perhaps give some concrete examples of how podcasts
may or may not use public music.
Okay.
It's a full.
I was wondering also why more podcasts
don't use Bitcoin to distribute their programs.
There we have the old bit-torn question again.
Well, you know what?
It would make so much sense.
Wouldn't it large media objects?
The reason why is because this is one of those crazy things about technology.
If Apple would implement Bitcoin on iTunes,
I think you would see a lot of traction for this.
And then all of a sudden everyone would be building this stuff in.
But I don't believe Apple can ever do that
because Bitcoin has just has a huge piracy,
illegal connotation and aura hanging around it.
And Hollywood would go nuts.
And Apple of course has done the deal with Hollywood,
which we all should be extremely grateful for
because otherwise none of the...
I mean iTunes is cool.
If you're looking for licensed music.
If you're looking for some easy way to buy.
Yeah, I mean yeah, there's all kinds of issues with the DRM
and you can't play it here and can't play it there.
But so they've done their deal with Hollywood.
Do you think Hollywood would like even just the notion
that Bitcoin has built in?
These guys don't understand what technology is.
They just think Bitcoin thieves.
And of course, Bitcoin is often used for theory as well.
There are lots of legal uses for it and it's just a technology.
But that's the reason.
So Apple would have to implement it and then it would gain traction.
And then it still remains to be seen as to how well it would work.
I've had varying results with Bitcoin.
Some stuff is unbelievable.
And by the way, BitTorrent on the PC definitely better on the Mac.
I just thought that it would have made distribution podcasts.
We're putting too much of a load on people's servers and all that easier.
I don't know if there's something you've looked into.
But it's just an idea ahead.
Yeah, well, of course, when we open up the podcast delivery network.
That won't be an issue because you'll be able to use that for free.
And there's unlimited storage and unlimited bandwidth.
And go ahead, eat all you like.
Next up for the sleep lights.
Your correspondence on DSC45 was right on the button.
This is remarks with regard to sleep lights.
To ask for points though.
If you ever find yourself in the service of the rest of the UK, be aware.
So I did own here as much stronger.
Especially in the form known as scumbee.
You might like to think of it as the scunk of cider.
Please approach it with caution if you're not a regular user.
Oh, and if you do order a part of sleep lights.
Make sure you drink it in a reasonable length of time as it tends to go a bit.
And the fluke and sick is less than or more than 20 minutes or so.
Final point, pops over the cream.
Really missing pops over the cream this week.
Christine got great taste in music.
And if you just don't talk over the intro's note.
Trills of songs along some porn characters I could mention.
Anyway, I don't keep up with the work.
Still loving the Charlie.
I'm not a pilot.
I do work in ATC.
So also, and I would bother to be a secret at all 100.
Oh, I can have.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, I got chills on that one.
The ATC dude, fantastic.
Love you guys.
Need you guys.
Can't go without you.
You've saved my ass many times.
Quick give me a QDM.
I need to know where the hell I am.
Yeah.
Snake bite.
Okay.
When I get back to the UK, we're drinking snake bite.
You know what?
I'll get Jimmy over.
I'll get Jimmy our next door neighbor.
He knows about that stuff.
He's got to be.
Those guys are drinkers.
My neighbors.
I'll ask him.
I was going to make a real snake bite.
We'll drink one together.
We'll do a sound seeing tour.
See how that goes.
Pretty good comment about pot safe music.
Just in general, not about the network.
But about why you listen to it.
I'll jump in once and a while.
Good.
Hey, what's going on there now?
This is Dan Patterson from the creepy sleep show.
And hang it out on the Sunday afternoon.
Listen to Friday's daily source code.
And thinking about them.
Bringing Marshall Claw and understanding.
Maybe that's cleaner.
I think both written and 60.
But anyway, man, I'm thinking about pot safe music.
And the phenomenon there.
And I don't know if you know, I'm a broadcaster.
I would do a seven and a midnight shift in a local rock.
You're a professional radio pronounced to cater.
You have all of the Lawrence welka albums.
And, you know, I'm always trying to think of the program from the point of view of the
Listen, which, you know, the broadcasters are supposed to do.
And a pop.
That's what broadcasters are supposed to do.
Yes, that's true.
But something went wrong about 15 years ago.
Well, one thing that's just constantly reiterated.
I've had program directors are just going to banging my head.
It's familiarity in music.
But even if it's a new song, it needs to sound familiar.
You know, people are very comfortable with certain chord progressions and certain melodies.
And pop music will kind of repeat itself.
You know, some people complain.
And people think that's pop music.
Wow, what an incredible insight into mainstream radio, huh?
And that is true.
Program directors and music directors at radio stations.
They'll say, hey, man, it has to have some kind of familiar sound to it.
It has to sound like this.
It has to have a certain beat.
It has, of course, pop music in general.
Those are kind of the rules.
But you're so right.
Which, of course, is if that's all you got, which is pretty much what we wound up with, is boring.
But regardless of familiar song, it's a good song.
But also familiar band, you know, the od of you not feeling shit.
You're first here in a major record label or far stackable.
But if you do make it, if you do sell a lot of records,
you're obviously going to be preferred in radio over to over than over artists that aren't because they're.
And isn't that interesting?
You're obviously going to be preferred.
Why?
It's true.
But I don't think it's that obvious.
But it's interesting that if you sell a lot of records,
then you're going to be more favored by radio stations to play you.
Why?
Hmm.
Let me think.
Could it be a financial interest, perhaps?
I'm familiar.
The pod show, or in the pod show, the pod did music network has a similar conundrum.
And that is the most of the bands and most of the artists are unknown.
And it's been very, very interesting to watch more established,
but the HIPLATE labels look from credibility at the tap of course.
And you know, let's see the whole rancid get-up thing running on the pod show,
plus right now.
It's very interesting because not only does that bring legitimacy and credibility,
validation from an album.
But it might also help shows in terms of their, you know,
if you can play a song by a well-known army.
And you can play a song by an up-and-coming that lessen our artists,
and then play a pod stage song that most people don't know or wouldn't have heard.
It seems like that would be great to be artists as well,
that affiliation with the note, excuse me, with familiar sounding music.
Anyway, man, this is Camden.
I'm getting ready for a writer's conference on Tuesday.
You can check it out on the blog for bcb.com.
Richard and Aaron, both are very helpful,
just one of the content, thanks.
I'm out the door, take care, yeah.
So about that familiarity, okay, a couple things.
First of all, in pod casting, we have something really wonderful
the radio doesn't have, which is the fast forward button,
or the pause, or even if you wish, rewind.
You can go back and listen to it again.
I can't tell you how many people say that,
oh man, you know, I skipped through that song.
I didn't like it.
Which is exactly what I'd expect you to do, you know?
Now, about familiar familiarity,
about songs that sound like something else you've heard,
I disagree.
I really do.
What's happening with pod safe music for me,
is I'm hearing songs on other podcasts,
and that's when the big, oh wow, moment came from me,
when I went, wait a minute, I know that song,
and then you start to be able to sing along with the lyrics,
you know, the familiar, the songs that sound the same.
It works, it doesn't matter.
Sometimes you only need to hear twice,
and then already you're humming along.
That's basically a song that could become a hit.
It has what I would call the music cure,
not the molecule, but the music cure.
It's got something in there that makes it all happen for you,
something that eats away your brain,
and then it just keeps running around,
and you can't get rid of it,
and it's different for everybody.
So, I have to disagree about that,
because, you know, yeah, repetition works,
but I don't think we need the repetition.
We've been hearing in mainstream media,
at least it's a lot richer if you can hear a lot more.
But there is something to be said about being played
alongside more established bands,
or bands that you've heard before.
And, you know, I signed up for Napster,
because it came on the laptop,
just to see what it was like,
and, oh man,
we're so deprived,
we really are all this great music
that is just not getting out there through this medium.
It's not getting out through radio either.
I mean, there's no way that with the formats,
the way the formats that radio have today,
that's just no way you can play all that stuff,
which is really, really bad for our culture.
It's horrible, I mean,
you know,
we know that kids who are growing up now,
listen to radio much less if at all,
so where are they going to get all their musical history from?
I mean,
I grew up listening to the radio in the United States,
and in the Netherlands,
and listening to pirate stations offshore,
and listening to radio Luxembourg,
and,
you know,
and I know little lyrics to songs from
almost all the songs from the 50s,
60s, 70s and 80s.
The 90s,
I kind of lost that I got busy,
and all this internet stuff.
You know,
so what are the influences going to be?
What,
you know,
when you look at the pod save music network,
look at any artist,
and they'll tell you who they were influenced by,
and it's a part of the bio for the sign-up.
And, you know,
when they say some,
I was,
I always have to laugh when I see,
you know,
young guys,
whose influences were kiss and ACDC,
you know,
but,
what's the next generation going to grow up listening to?
You know,
are they going to hear these songs at all?
Will it just be sporadic?
You know,
that's really, really bad.
And it's a shame.
Pure shame.
The pod show ad challenge continues to rage.
Submissions now are really flying in.
I think it's because we're playing some of them
and people are going,
and they can do better than that.
It's like $2,000 you can win.
But more importantly,
help us change advertising.
Let's make it better.
And,
so people are now creating kind of produce spots,
which I'm liking a lot,
but they're still room for all kinds of stuff.
It can just be you talking about Earthlink.
Check this one out.
Whether you're just starting out,
prior a season and traveler,
let Earthlink be your bridge
to the world of the Internet.
Like an old friend
that you can always depend on,
and will always be there for you.
Earthlink,
always.
Always.
Up to the Internet,
AdChallence.podshow.com,
sending your entries.
I like that one.
And it's so cool because,
basically,
this whole competition,
this whole challenge,
is a commercial,
but for me,
it's just content.
Isn't that what advertising
should be?
Shouldn't it just be another form of content?
Found a comment on curry.com from,
this come from,
the Guildford pub drinker,
who says,
hey Adam,
oh yeah,
that's right.
I was looking for a pub.
I hadn't yet found one in the UK.
If you want a pub in the area to adopt,
have a look at the onslow arms in
Clandin.
Yeah, that's about five minutes away.
It's a 17th century pub,
perfect place to park your jag outside.
Now,
that of course is quite a contradiction in terms there,
because yeah,
it's a perfect place to go drink,
but does that mean I have to go up to drive there to drink?
I don't know,
that's a really good idea.
Maybe I'll take Jimmy there,
and we'll walk to Clandin,
and we'll try out the snake bite.
Holger,
I'll heart says hi,
very interested how some people
make money off of everything.
Oh,
this is about the German Chancellor.
This is great.
I think I mentioned last week,
or maybe the week before,
that the German Chancellor is now doing a video podcast.
Holger sends me a link,
where it turns out that,
this is great.
The actual costs being paid by the German public,
I guess,
because it's tax euros,
is 26,000 euros
for the four editions of the podcast.
Oh man,
somebody really did a good one there.
26,000 euros,
and take a look at it,
it's like,
the money's not on the screen.
Let me tell you that.
Maybe some of it's for bandwidth,
but it's a funny story.
You got to read that.
There's always someone out there who's going to,
who's going to make some money.
All right,
not family safe,
but it is time for,
hey,
shit.
Oh,
Cranky.
It's not working.
What is this?
Let's try this.
Does it work now?
Comic strip.
Yeah,
he's back to his old antics.
Hey,
yeah,
Adam's like,
very hairy.
Here is,
coming to the blogger,
now,
in second life,
as comic senior.
Speaking of second life,
I come to second life on,
on weekends,
just to meet people.
And yesterday,
again,
avatas,
in second life,
asking me,
is this rule
that the fucker
Adam carried
good board
with second life?
And it's not coming anymore?
So,
maybe you could,
at least a second life question.
Speak.
No, I don't know.
I must say,
I've been a lot more busy,
and,
normally,
uh,
I have time
between
one and the afternoon
and four
in the afternoon,
when I'm in the UK to do other stuff.
So that's basically after I've done my show
and gone through all the emails
and San Francisco hasn't woken up yet.
And that's a perfect time.
They just chill back
with a nice sense sale
and,
and see what's going on.
I've been on,
I've been around,
you know,
I'd kind of bop in for a couple minutes at a time,
uh,
we've been working on some stuff,
which I guess,
I guess this week,
probably will be able to,
uh,
to talk about that.
A new place to come and hang out.
Oh, yeah.
The work never stops at Podshow.
You know,
I'd rather think.
How it's done,
kept his promise
and addressed the problem
of internet streaming.
So both,
how it's done,
channels,
100 and 101,
uh,
now being streamed
24 hours a day,
seven days a week.
Yeah,
Good for you.
For serious subscribers of fucking course.
What about fucking potential on serious?
Why the fuck?
It is not yet being streamed over internet.
Don't build it together,
Adam Kerry.
And address this problem once and for all.
PS.
I am serious subscriber.
And I listen to what's then sometimes,
but it's really speaking,
he's the victims of sexual practices.
They take the most parts of his show,
and it'd be boring.
But he's,
uh,
what's in the news,
Robin?
It's brilliant.
So,
fuck you later,
Kerry,
spamming later.
Yeah,
comic strip blogger.
The F bombs are getting a little bit old,
man.
You got interesting stuff to say in good questions,
although that's serious stuff is so old.
I think we have a meeting with them,
phone meeting today,
or maybe it's tomorrow,
go over some stuff.
I'll ask again,
it was streaming.
I know it was streaming,
and then it got unstream.
Not quite sure what's going on with that.
So,
sorry, man.
Hey,
there, Adam,
and all you daily source code,
junkies.
My name is Adam Crowloff,
and I am leader of a band called Captain Paradox.
We recently uploaded a few songs
to the Podsafe Music Network,
and it's freaking great.
The reason why we decided to use this
and it's the first place we went to
is because of the licensing agreement.
You start reading the licensing agreements
in the fine print on a lot of these other sites.
It's fucked up,
especially my space.
If you upload a lot of these other sites,
it's fucked up,
especially my space.
If you upload anything to my space,
even if you deleted,
it remains the property of Rupert Murdock.
It's wrong,
it's fucked up.
That's why I like Podsafe Music Network.
So, I'd just like to say,
hey,
thanks to Adam Crowloff.
Thanks to the Pod Show people,
thanks to Podsafe Music Network.
We've been played in California,
we've been played in the UK already.
It's awesome.
So, please check us out,
Captain Paradox at the Podsafe Music Network.
It was also got our own site at
CaptainParadox.com.
Thanks again, Adam.
Peace out.
I got to run.
It's just about 420 here in the steel city,
Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
Yeah, yeah, there it is.
What's that?
Right on, man.
Well, listen.
It's just people, dude.
It's just people who are loving music.
That's what it's all about.
And being able to talk about it and me,
I'll just say, I love this song.
I'm going to play it for you.
And I do like the tune you sent me.
Upon the Podsafe Music Network,
Captain Paradox on your daily source code.
The television man is the child of the media.
The television man knows a telephone can feature.
The television man.
But we give us what he sees.
The television man knows about the bird.
The television man.
Always knows the score.
Still he wants more.
The television man.
Soaks his problems and now.
The television man has a healthy respect for power.
No man, they got him.
Right where they want him.
The television man.
Watch his life free and act.
There's a bunker in our beds.
The television man.
Sit on the fence.
For a war or a CNN.
The television man.
Was proud of his man.
Doesn't need to leave his chair.
The television man.
She's himself on the air.
Can make a friend through the phone.
The television man.
Does it rely to the Lord?
The TV.
Can.
The News movie.
One thing I haven't addressed is the
Podsave the Queen Podcast.
Here's Teenagers for you.
Ask Christina to hook up a Skype headset.
She's like,
I might have my computer's crappy.
She wants to do the show, but she wants the sound to be good.
She doesn't want the, you know,
now she's getting all picky and stuff.
And yes, of course,
she can use cast blaster herself.
But she spoiled.
She's just spoiled because she's not only child,
and we love her so much,
but she spoiled because of the sound, you know,
and I've got the studio here.
I really need to set up another studio.
That's what I'd like to do before I leave.
Before I leave San Francisco,
I get a studio set up here,
and I'll take my gear back,
and then I'll have something in both spots.
And then also I'll kind of have like a constant and consistent sound.
So Podsave the Queen probably not until,
or probably not for another week until it comes back
to a apologies from Christina and from myself.
All right, everybody.
What time is it?
745.
Time to get dressed.
Oh, maybe that's more information than you needed.
I got to get out of here.
Feedback to adamaccurry.com.
DailySourceco.com for the latest podcast and the podcast feed.
Have a great Monday, everybody.
I'll see you tomorrow.
I'll show Podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the High Performance Podcast
to Livery Network from Podjo and LineWight Networks.
I love it.