Ah, the festive period once again. It's time to give each other presents and receive presents
and say thanks and then put them on eBay.
M-R-M-P-D-D-D-P-T-P-O-D-O-D-O-O-K.
Delta Sierra Charlie 5-1-Niner.
Was introduced to me.
The music melted through the end.
I love the category.
I've all the other people there.
If it wasn't Halloween, don't tell me if these two exist.
We're all equipped by me and you.
That's not true.
We just can't try them, but we won't let you.
I love you so unique.
I know it happens every day.
I can't see that one to me.
Andy Stone, in the coffee shop, blended.
It's on the pod safe music network.
And that was suggested by...
Hold on a second. I got a holy mail here.
First of all, let me say.
You can probably tell there's a difference in the configuration of the sound today.
And not just the difference in the configuration of the studio, but a difference in
configuration in my face.
Yes, today.
See, boxing day, second day of Christmas in many parts of the world.
I awoke to find my left cheek somewhat swollen.
It's not exactly what's happened, but I'm pretty sure there's a route of one of my teeth.
It's affected my sinuses.
I don't know, man.
It's not pretty to look at.
Since I was up at 6 a.m. anyway, the pain basically woke me up.
I forget I wanted to get the show out of the way and get it all crank.
So kind of a mellow start.
I was going to say that was sent in by Andy Stone.
Just listen to this about that record.
I really liked that track.
I really liked it. He says, um, do you know how to inform
my epic recording artist Danny Malone from Dodding for Pearls?
Who later made an album for Atlantic with Elliot Easton of the cars in the early 90s?
It's handling vocals on my latest bird inspired melody and hook driven for song project.
And so he goes on to explain what's going on.
But of course, you can find it the pod safe music network.
Which means if you have a podcast, you're free to use that on your show.
Hey, everybody. How you doing? Hope you had a good Christmas.
I'm sorry. I just don't have all the energy because literally the left side of my face
is all taught and and puffy.
So I can't do my normal.
My normal upbeat up tempo crap coming to you from the curry cottage.
Of course in the affluent suburb of Surrey.
This is the daily source code episode 519.
Had a fantastic Christmas actually.
It always seems to happen.
Whatever I'm nice and relaxed and everything's all chilled out.
And we're just hanging out with the family.
That's always when I get sick.
We're going vacation.
The first three days of course.
I'm going to be sick.
But otherwise, it was great.
Of course, I did all my well.
Let me rewind back to Friday.
We had the BT pod show holiday party at the UK crash pad in Shortage and London.
A lot of fun.
I'd never really been to a Christmas party in the UK.
So this was without it out my first.
Man.
You brits really do like to drink and it's not like you're drinking a lot.
Well, you are.
But you just it's like people are literally excited about drinking.
And you know me, I'm not at all a guy who likes to drink.
I smoke my pleasures.
I had a glass or two and it was a lot of fun.
Getting kind of wasted with everybody.
And there were people there who represented shows that are on the BT pod show.
I think actually a Neil done a pretty good job.
He invited some other people who aren't.
We don't are in a member of the network.
But a lot of fun on the less you from story nori was there.
That was cool to meet him.
I think I've met him before actually.
But I actually got to talk to him this time.
Just to chill out a bit.
A Scott from the night nurse show.
He's very funny.
Sweet guy.
And let's see.
So I was one of those days where I was able to, you know, arrive at the train station.
Both coming out and going home.
Just minutes before the train left.
So it was fantastic.
I was home around 10 o'clock, 10.
30.
And that's really when everything just kind of started.
Just the chill out mellow mood.
We had a fantastic Christmas.
Just the three of us.
Since we really hadn't been together for a couple of weeks.
Very nice.
And usually we, you know, Christmas is pretty much our own family affair.
We rarely celebrate that with the other members of the family.
It's just just Patricia Kristina and I.
And of course, we got Kristina all kinds of cool stuff.
Which is always fun.
Patricia and I went shopping on Saturday.
Yes, Saturday went shopping together.
And we got her, well, the one thing she really wanted.
Which isn't, it wasn't a huge, a huge request.
Was an Nintendo DS light.
Of course, the pink version was somewhat of an extra request.
We had to run around town a couple of different stores to find a pink Nintendo DS light.
Those things are pretty awesome, by the way.
If you have two of them that connect wirelessly.
You can connect to a Wi-Fi and play with people over the internet.
The graphics are quite astounding.
How they fit all of that for 99 pounds into into one little box is beyond me.
But the gift that she has been using the most.
And I love this about our daughter.
I gave her a book.
You know, I love giving away books.
I spent a lot of time in the bookstore.
I got a book for Patricia, which is the Victoria Beckham book,
which is actually a very well-produced book.
Great pictures.
If you're into fashion.
It's all about fashion and style.
It looks like a fashion, a team of fashion editors from a magazine.
Put this book together.
It's really pretty.
And for Kristina, I got was a Jackie Collins novel.
She loves reading trash like that.
And this one was called a titled Hollywood Kids.
I thought she'd get a kick out of seeing what she is not yet.
But soon can become.
And let's see.
So, oh yeah, of course, we got the karaoke machine out.
That's always cool.
Sing along on Christmas.
And yesterday, Boxing Day really just took it easy.
Watched a lot of television.
There was some great TV on here.
Both Christmas Eve.
Christmas Day.
And Boxing Day.
Second day of Christmas.
It was just really nice, except, of course, my face would start to swell up.
And all of this just days before we start our big move to the new curry cottage.
I'm Steve.
I don't know what's like in the States.
I don't know what's like in your house.
And it was actually, but you know, you can.
It's a bit of a tradition that when you move yourself into a new house.
You have a, what's called a housewarming party.
Um, yeah, just close and all the address and the assignment will be there with a few bones of beer.
Cheers, man.
Bye.
Yeah, okay.
That's a great idea.
I'm sure, Patricia will love it.
You need to come over and stop some potato chips right into the woodwork.
You know, it's, um, it's a small courtesy, but I'm happy you're willing to do it for me.
Oops.
By the error.
Hey, Adam, what's happening to do this Kevin Reeves?
Dude, this whole thing about Patricia and a record.
This is a perfect opportunity for a bunch of us to get together.
And she could release jazz versions or valid versions of a lot of the.
Top tunes that are on the pod safe music network.
I'm sure that Matthew evil got some stuff that could be read,
cut and rework.
Jeff, this has stuff that we recut reworked.
Common Tyler myself.
I'm sure there's a bunch of them that we could do.
And then it would be automatically pod safe.
Everybody would obviously, you know, sign a waiver to make that work.
And, um, man, let's do it.
Let's, let's make it happen.
So, uh, just, uh, I don't know.
Let's open some dialogue about it.
Let's see what we can do.
All right, man.
I'll check me out.
Kevin Reeves got net.
Have a good one.
Bye.
All right.
Yeah.
Of course, buddy.
Very happy holidays and happy new year to you.
Kevin Reeves.
Just check them out of the pod safe music network.
Kevin.
This whole story has really gotten some legs.
Now, um, another one of Patricia's, um, celebrity.
Wimmit was he, uh, is he a judge or, no, he's just, he's one of the celebrity dancers
on the dancing with the stars, which by the way, aired last night.
Uh, highest rated program of the evening.
Uh, although Patricia did not come in first place.
In fact, I think she came in dead last.
Uh, of the contestants, which, uh, I'm sure she'll come on the show tomorrow
and explain why.
And of course, I knew that she came in last.
And I also know what happens during her second dance.
So I've been sworn to secrets so I can't say anything.
Um, but, um, uh, one of her, uh, her co, uh, celebrities on the show
is Edick from Tang.
And he's a very well-known record producer in the Netherlands.
He's been around for about 20 years, I think.
He's produced, uh, some pretty big, uh, hits, you know, very 80s, poppy type stuff.
Um, he also approved some damn goods, uh, uh, good album with Patricia at one point.
And, um, they've kind of taken this idea of these songs and taken a little bit
further.
You see, there's a huge hole in the market.
Um, uh, if you, if you, um,
consider that there are so many people who actually take dancing classes.
And that there's just not enough new music, good material, um, available, uh,
to dance to.
It's always the same kind of songs.
And of course, you know, you need your, your quick step and your fucks
trot and your wallets and your samba and all that stuff.
And so that they've been kicking around this idea of dancing with Patricia.
Which I think is a fantastic idea.
Uh, so I'm, I'm just kind of stepping back.
I have no idea what's going to go on.
I love the idea.
Although, you know, you guys all stand by yourself.
You know, you, you've got such great careers.
You've got such great music, uh, all on the podcast music network.
I, I think Patricia should figure it out herself.
And, uh, now, of course, she's still going to do this thing with the, with the
Jeff Smith.
And I know Jeff has been really busy.
And he's coming back to with the rework version of his, uh,
of the song that he, uh, that he wrote for for their duet together.
And that's still a project that we're working on.
But, uh, I'll keep you, uh,
I'll keep you up to speed on what's going on with the dancing with the stars project.
I'd like the idea because, you know,
that's something that there's a very definite audience for.
You don't have to have a number one radio hit to actually sell any CDs.
Um, and now I'm just presuming that this wouldn't be a podsafe album.
Because it'll probably be a lot of standards or maybe a couple of new songs,
which I hope she would make podsafe.
Um, but that's a very different market than hey, you know,
we have to get played on the top three radio stations in order to get enough exposure.
And there's a huge budget for marketing.
And then maybe we'll sell, uh, you know, 100,000 records,
which is pretty much the state of affairs today in the music business.
This business is dying off.
And I'm thinking about, um,
on the last show of the year, really, uh,
looking back at what's happened to the music industry, um,
and perhaps making a few predictions for 2007.
But first, we've got to deal with some of this podsafe stuff.
Okay, Adam, you have some spleen and to do on DSE 516, we hear.
If they write them, that's fine, but I want to be able to release them podsafe,
which means, you know, they're probably not going to make any money.
What was that again?
Probably not going to make any money.
Now, what do you mean by, they won't make any money?
I guess that means that the whole podsafe music network is for nothing.
And music podcasting is a waste of time.
Sorry, Adam, but I don't agree.
And wish you had chosen some better words.
No, I think you misunderstood what I'm saying.
I love the pod.
Come on.
I've been part of the podsafe music revolution.
We set up the podsafe music network because we believe in it.
However, I really don't believe we're going to see massive multimillion selling CDs
or tracks anymore in the near future.
Again, this is something I definitely want to talk about at the end of the year.
But if you put it all together, if you look at the way record companies are making money,
they're not making money on CD sales alone.
It's on the publishing.
It's on licensing.
It's on merchandising.
And of course, they also take a piece of the touring.
If there's any money available in that.
I mean, there's so many different avenues and bands and artists are independent companies.
And now they have all the tools to do this themselves.
That's the whole point.
The podsafe music and playing music on podcasts is just a small piece of it.
By itself, I don't think it.
It a career of great wealth.
This, of course, is going to be a couple of huge breakout hates that just happened.
That every, you know, this viral is like viral videos.
Of course, that's going to happen.
But because we now have tens of thousands of podcasts and hundreds of thousands of tracks
supply does it mean that people will be making money hand over foot, probably not,
not just based upon the track sales.
But when I see the relationships that have been built up, the relationships between artists,
fans and people who want to promote them just want to help them out for free by playing
them on their podcasts, that's where the magic is.
And that's where there's a hell of a lot of good things to be done.
And yes, indeed, money to be made.
One, two, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven.
You know, when he said, you got some slain into do.
For a second there, I thought it was going to say, you got some splendour to track.
And of course, portions of the day show brought to you by splendor, the substitute for sugar.
You know, I haven't heard from people about splendor in a while.
Are we still mixing it up?
Are we still trying different flavors?
Are we still trying to come up with a great new master's solution for making my senseo
coffee taste even better?
Love to hear from you.
All right, this is Ron from zip71101 podcast located at zip.punchow.com.
Last week, I spoke to Rock and Roll legend Dale Hawkins.
He wrote and recorded Susie Q and 1957.
And that was a smash hit.
Guitarist James Burton, who was only 15 years old, played those famous guitar licks.
Susie Q was also chosen as one of the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame's 500 songs
that shaped rock and roll.
And I've got the interview with the legend, Dale Hawkins.
Zip.punchow.com.
All right, I did a source code episode 519.
Our Gile Pems.
Yeah.
I think you should buy us a drink.
Yes.
At least.
I've never felt this good in my entire life.
Make me some of the spaghetti.
Yeah.
We are the Gile Pems.
We're the Gile Pems.
You know I have to drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink,
drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink
drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink,構, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink drink, drink drink, drink, drink , drink, drink, drink , drink, drink, drink, drink, drink
I'm feeling positively nauseous from the massive quantities of ibuprofen I've been taking
as well as a swishling suit gargling with salt water and all kinds of other medicines I
feel horrible. I have a feeling it's going to be a rude canal or some crap like that just
oh something I don't need today at all. So anyway I have no idea how this how the setup sounds
I worked all day yesterday through the pain I want you to know. I've now I was in preparation
for the move I had to start cleaning shit up in the studio and I have had so many different setups
over the years. So many different mixing boards and configurations and it was a complete spaghetti
factory behind the podcast console. So now what I've done is I've set it up with the Yamaha
the Alpha Whiskey 16 Golf. Remember that's the digital mixing console. I've set that up and runs it
and has some inline processing and I've really I'm not just not sure if it sounds right yet
but I did work on a whole bunch of sounds and setups and I've got the old what is that this
hold on let me take a look at it. Yeah the sound crap for board. I've got that one set up kind of as a
headphone mixer so that I can hear exactly what's going into cast blaster which of course is
still a part of the setup and I even resurrected an old power book G4 for some multi track stuff.
So it's it's kind of looking good and literally half of the wires I had I was able to put into one
of the boxes. So now when the movers come of course this is a story I've convinced Patricia I was
really busy doing. I was really just reconfiguring the studio but I told her it was like preparing
for the move but it is true that now when the movers come I know exactly what wires I need what
plugs what to extension cord they all go into one box all of the computer stuff can go into the
you know boxes right nearby and it'll be completely ready for unpacking because let's be honest it's the
first thing I'm going to unpack. Hey fans of daily source code come and check out our holiday
Christmas video podcast at rockinrolltv.net also seen at rockinrolltv.podshow.com. Happy holiday!
Sharon Ross. I had a mid-cert Patrick from a not so what did I say?
What did I say that? I meant Sharon Bam of course. I had a mid-cert Patrick from a not so
affluent suburb of East Sussex just wanted to make a comment on your remarks regarding fog in the
DSC 518. I'm a commercial pilot based down here in Gatwick and I fly the Boeing 737 400 series.
How hard is that? I fly the Boeing 737 service series Rura and in common with many of our
colleagues in the modern airplanes of today we can in fact land automatically fully automatically
without touching the controls and we don't need to see very much we need to be able to see
something one light at 50 feet that's our reference. And as is not a very modern airplane if you're
getting to something more sophisticated like say the triple seven they can land because they got
better systems more at London sense on. They can land with no visibility, no lights, nobody's seeing anything
and the whole airplane will just touch down, land, stop itself on the runway on the centre line,
no trouble at all. And most of the modern airplanes can do that even the smaller air buses and everything.
Oh nearly forgot. Yes, of course you are. Oh pilots are full. Now that's not true. Not all pilots.
Yeah, I stand corrected on a couple of things that I said there. So I knew that modern aircraft
could do that. I actually wasn't aware that they could completely do everything and come to a full
stop all by themselves. That's pretty fucking amazing technology. Although I didn't know that a lot
of aircraft certainly can take you all the way down to the runway. I didn't know the 737
was capable of doing that. I also have received numerous reports from people that yes indeed there
are many airfields with ground radar. Skippel airport in the Netherlands has ground radar.
Thank you Alexander for that. Although I'm not sure if if he throw has that a crap to
satellite window closed when I wasn't looking. Sorry about that serious folks.
At Brittany Mason who you probably know from second life has started a podcast. It's very
interesting. It is a second life podcast. You'll want to take a look at it at Brittany Mason Show.
dot pod show dot com. Very interesting. She speaks for the first time. Oh man, excuse me, this
shit is getting to me. I think I got to play one last song for you. Then I'm going to get
ready to go to the dentist Fiona's nice enough to see me at 1215 which is why I'm recording
early at figure. If work needs to be done, if we need 50 hour maintenance job, you're not going
to want to listen to me after that. Dancing to moonlight.
Nothing like a little bit of Japanese jazz fun kind of Wednesday morning. Casey Saito from the
pod safe music network. Dancing moonlight. There is so much interesting stuff.
Really should check it out. Of course, links to all of these artists in the show notes at
dailysourcecode.com. Hopefully tomorrow things will be on the mend. The swelling will have been
reduced in the cheek and we'll be back here to talk about some more stuff. I'll get the lady
Patricia on to talk about dancing with the stars and the dancing with Patricia project. I love the
idea. I really do. Alright everybody, thanks for listening to my complaining. I'll be back tomorrow.
You know where to find me email me adamantpodshow.com dailysourcecode.com for the show notes.
Take care everybody. Bye. Another pod show podcast. Stick it in your ear.
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT pod show media network.
Howard by pod show and limelight network. Control your part in the show at btpotshow.com