Delta Sierra Charlie three three four a warning. This podcast is not family safe. So either turn it down or jam those buds deep into your ear.
This is the band scamper from the scamper podcast as scamper.net.
That's right. We're rock band. We do podcasts. We're awesome. We do it all.
We really do. And what we have for you today is our own tip for Adam Curry's Metro sexual moment.
Especially tailored for all those guys out there in bands. Guys, if you're in a band, make sure you thoroughly cleanse your penis in between groupies. Otherwise, you'll be stuck with that low self esteem smell.
And it gets all over your sheets. It's really disgusting fellow. So thank you.
I'm gross. Not worth it.
Hey, by the way, do you think that Adam Curry still gets the groupies?
Of course, he still gets groupies. He's Adam motherfucking curry.
Hey, do you think he still gets the thresons with Kurt Loader?
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic. It's Adam Curry.
Hey, man. Who needs groupies when you've got titties?
It's a feedback friday everybody.
Delta Sierra Charlie is on.
I started in front of me.
Taking in all she could see.
It's a feedback friday everybody. Delta Sierra Charlie is on.
I started in front of me.
Taking in all she could see.
Cracking on her sugar cane.
I leaned in and I caught her name.
So big.
Sierra lands through her arm.
And I miss her over hands.
Though she's on.
When I'm glad to hurry, she'd've been gone.
So big. Oh, plus is on.
So big.
Saved it.
She's got an ocean, and I feel so old
She's looking all around, so I've been just so old
So big, so big
And once again, I've watched her go
Down the stairs through the next picture
I felt the sand breathing from my glass
Time was slipping, so I had to move fast
Come to where I said it in the room
I'm so sorry, I never said I know
She gave a smile and we talked till dawn
I felt the ocean, so big
So big, so big
So big, so big, so big
So big
Now that is a Friday kick off song for the Charlie
Hey everybody, Daily Source Code
Thank you for tuning in, pressing play
and getting with it, oh this
I didn't even a chance to announce you're going to be on the show yet
Go take your coat off and come back
I just came in
I know you did
Well, so I said it was a feedback Friday
I have lots of feedback that I'd like to get to
But Patricia did promise you would drop by today on the show
today on the show. And the reason for that is because I asked her because you know how long
have I done this show now without her? Like, once last time you're on the show, huh?
Huh? A couple weeks ago. Three weeks ago, at least three weeks ago. Two weeks ago. Yeah.
Show is boring without you. Oh. Yeah. Look, man, you completely set up. Look, I got your
mic set up. I got your headphones, check the headphones, see if they sound good. Check them
up. Yeah. Hello, hello. Can you hear me? Yes. Can you hear yourself? Yep. Yeah. There you go.
Very professional. Just the microphone. You got to move it. As a singer, you're used to that.
A finger. Yes. For those of you who don't know, this is my lovely wife, Patricia, who gave
me the avocado and shrimp with cocktail sauce yesterday. You love the cocktail sauce. Yes,
I do. Yes, I do, huh? Welcome. Thank you. What are we going to talk? We're going
to talk about some stuff today, right? Yeah. And you know what? Yesterday. No. Yeah. Yes,
then when we had dinner, I started something and you said, I said, I said, she should be quiet.
But what was it? I don't know. I look, you're supposed to be the professional for
an instigator. No, I don't know. No, I don't know. No, but see the thing is, is it was funny?
This is what I'm going to get when we get my chair. You want to chair? No. You want
to sit down? No, I'm young. You're old. Yes. No, the thing is, what I learned from the last
radio show is if you have a guest on, you don't want to, and this is what everybody does
at every interview is they talk in between either commercials or the records or something
else. And then by the time, okay, let's talk about that. You know, it's like then it's
not spontaneous. It's not funny. It's not interesting. No, I didn't even say it, but I started
it and you said, save them for tomorrow. I think it was about the grannies. That now that
was the, you know, I call them the grannies. Yeah. And you know why? Do you know what happened
with the, well, it's the Grammy Awards. Yeah. It was on the same time in the States as idols.
Yeah. As I, or American Idol. Yeah. Twice as many people watched American Idol as
watching the grannies. But I have to say it was a bit boring. Yeah, of course it is. It was all the
same people we've seen for 20 years on the damn show. It was always the same and it's like goodness.
Yeah. Yeah. It was extremely boring. And the version we saw last night on Sky, half of the show
was cut out. We didn't see Mariah Carey perform. We didn't see that. Oh, she did perform. Oh,
I did that cut her out. I don't know because it wasn't high definition. Oh, no, it's boring. And
you know what? Always Mary J. Blitz always has to sing with somebody. Do a do it. And she's
ever forever. For whatever. Well, she there again. I didn't see her last night. We're seeing
so off key. Oh, Mary J. Blitz. It's me nauseous. Yeah. And she's not even that bad because she's all over
the place. You know, the only thing she is, she's she's she's just got she's interesting to watch.
Yes, she has to move and get here. But that's okay. So that makes it valid. But now it's still.
But as a singer, you know, it's a little bit exaggerated. I'll really know. Yeah, because it's always a
little bit too high what she sings and that she's a little higher. It's better to sing a little bit
to low than to high. To high is a little Sydney. I think that too high all the time. And then
what is also my problem when I'm watching is and it's also with movie stars. You know,
they're great, they're fantastic. They have great, they have a great attitude in movies or on stage
or on the video, no matter who they are in the stars. Yeah. Then when they call their names out,
when they have a when they win the war. And when they win a war, suddenly they're just idiots.
They don't wait to go. They have these. They have these like, I'm not worthy kind of shoulder hanging
you know down. They walk like like idiots. Well, let me let me ask you something. Have you ever
suddenly they're not, you know, that's actually in that good and that talents at any more.
What is that humble? They're being humble. They're humble because oh, I don't deserve it. Oh, I don't deserve it. Yeah, right? Well, first of all
They probably don't deserve it
Okay, but I've never won an award in a group in a big setting like that if you I don't know what that's like
I don't know if how I would be more stand up. I got finally
Yeah, that's true. I'm about time. Yeah, you know
Yeah, that's true, but it was you know, and it's wonderful. I would be very happy
But you know that's stupid stupid. I'm not worthy kind of you know
I didn't like the telecast last night just for the the television direction, which was done by Ken Erlick who I know and I've worked with who I think is just not a good
Television director
No, no, no, I mean it's like you can you can almost see you know like and congratulations
Mariah, who do we see Gwen Stefani you know the way around and it was the fun the funniest thing
There was this awesome awesome drum battle beat this was really good
I thought this was amazing. You know me in the drum cadence with the with the bands. I love that
So it was Kanye West and Jamie Foxx
Yes, right. I mean it was fantastic
choreography everything it was just outrageous and it was like just boom boom and from from Kanye back to Jamie and then you know
And then these like I think five or seven girls came out and they dance and that's guys came out and they dance
Charlie there's yeah and and and just the very very end at the very end
So this like this is big climax
What's the shot that Ken Erlick calls for a shot of James Taylor?
Yeah, it was like it was a shock. I was like, you know, I was seeing the hippest most movable people on the earth
You know Kanye and Jamie Foxx very talented and then all of a sudden and James Taylor talented
But it was like
Oh my god, who's that it's like what was that? No, it was a shock man. I would. I don't know
But you know, we're idiots. We're we're television and music idiots. So that's that should bothers us
No one else cares, huh? Believe me. It doesn't matter the moment if you irritated that's entertainment
Yeah, absolutely and and that you know
There's so many people who are irritated by by this podcast
That's entertainment. I think it's wonderful my friend
The comic strip blogger your friend too, by the way. He's done some very nice cartoons of you
Oh, that guy
Oh, he hates me
He gives me wrinkles
He sure does give you wrinkles. Yeah
I this I played for you yesterday
You unplugged
Everybody
Whereas it hears I played this for you yesterday. I just want to play it for the listeners because it was so cool. We know what it is
We're talking about this thing here. Check this out
Hi Adam
It's your old buddy Leanne from the list of these bitties bitty cast
I wanted to send you this audio comment to praise you for your metro sexual moment
Women have been discussing this thing for centuries and that's why we smell so nice and look so pretty all the time
It's about time for you guys to have your own avenue to personal grooming
Thank you for helping all our future boyfriends fix themselves up
For the record pink is good
We like
On another note we thought you might enjoy this moment of bitty cast we recorded it Jim Caruso's cast party in New York
In the podcast episode 56 downloadable at bittycast.com
We're speaking with Eric Bergen of greenroom radio dot com. We know it's hard when people think you're an evil overlord
So perhaps this will lighten the mood a bit at dschq
Signing off with much affection and hope to talk to you soon
Oh, let's use sleep without a hurry if you have a chance
If you want that list
I met him
and
Well, that was an easy answer
He's a sexy man
I wouldn't do anything different my boyfriend ever in my life
He's a sexy
He's amazingly tall
And he's a really
really I'm blushing he's a really charismatic
How do you like their maples, baby?
I love that sir
This is not good for you. It's fantastic. Are you kidding me? I could beat up all the time finally someone does something really nice
Everything's up girls. Yeah, that's great. That's the best part about it
That's the best part. Oh, yeah, I love the beaties and they say that's why we smell so nice
You forget that
What happened? Don't smell that mess
We want more more nice. I try though. I really really try
Yeah, you but you forget about it now and then yes, you know, it's now and then it's now
Never
Yeah, you know, hey, I'm on the list. I couldn't tell the names though
I didn't know who was who that's what was a bummer. I was trying I heard a mandamonico
But I who was it that said yes right away. That's who that was a very fast. I'm not I'm yeah. That was like yes
Like
Desperate see at least in your constant
Oh, these are not the the band to anything. There's no these. No, these are the civils. Oh, you want to know who that was
You will never know
See, that's so nice about it. There's our don't tell him
Oh, come on. I love that I love the biddies. I could I know I could never have sex with them. That would be so wrong
You really appreciate them
That's why you can't have sex with them. But be don't be surprised if if I've valentines today
I'm not ready for valentines. I don't be surprised that you know I love making if I call it holy yeah
Oh, man. It's okay, huh? It's okay. Hey guys. I'm scoring here. Yeah. All right. That was that was really nice though
So yeah, that was really really how you feeling? Yeah, it's a beautiful day. Look how gorgeous gorgeous the weather is it?
The first time in we can see we can see that. Oh, look at that. See that?
How beautiful. We see the mountains for me here. Yeah, beautiful castle. There. Yeah, it is beautiful
Don't don't say too much about where we are because you know Roger Smalls will we'll find us
You know you're not worried about a guy like that. Are you now? No, really? I don't think so. Okay. Well at least he doesn't take I'll be pictures
Like that magazine. Yeah, exactly. How come a guy like Roger Smalls doesn't work for a paparazzi? Yeah, magazine
Yeah, yeah, he takes some good pictures. Oh, yeah, that's a new thing. Yeah, I heard that from other
celebrities and do you know some celebrities? I guess I'm watch TV and
The real celebrity and I heard that and we know that because we experience that
It's a new thing
They take pictures, but they want to take bad pictures of you. Well, of course. That's a new thing of course
See you know years and years ago
Yeah, remember that how they can't be that long because you're so young
Talk referral would like to have a wonderful great beautiful picture composition even while that is a great picture
You know you're proud of that no
It's not it doesn't work like that anymore
You're proud of it if the ugliest picture that you can make from somebody you take from somebody
Well, that's the you know why though. Yeah, it's entertainment. You just said yourself it's entertainment
Yeah, but that's what here we are again. I said at the last time that's because we're in a
Totally different mood these days
You know people want to hear and see
Nasty things and set faces sure from from the start sure actually rosin bar was on it still rosin bar
I don't know whatever. Yeah, I guess whatever. Well, she was on a morning show this morning in the UK
Really she's I think she's plugging a sort of a children
DVD that she made is the dog okay
You know it's beautiful weather. He sees all those dogs in there. Oh, he wants a garden play
But then he could take him out this little and she said something
That she she talked to her rabbi and time ago long time ago couple years ago and that really changed her
Because he she asked him something about
I don't know and he said you know what we're going to start start
Changing yourself and be a little bit nicer
Because she was asking something about believing and I don't know what he says first start to be a little bit nicer
You are not nice
That's what she said. Yeah, yeah, she was nice and then she actually she said yeah, he was right
I wasn't nice and lots of people around me were nice
And even her stand-ups were not nice nice people laughing because they were not nice. Yeah, but exactly, but yeah, I think that right now
There's a lot of frustration
People are upset about a lot of things and it's much safer
Much much safer to attack
Someone other than the problem that you may really be dealing with I see this and I know how this happens because I'll be reading an email an example
I'll be reading an email
I'll be doing something oh, and it's probably something that's irritating me. That's what it happens
And if there's an interruption and someone asked me something
I'm still in that in that mood. I'm short. I'm abrupt. I'm not nice. No, that's right. Exactly. You should kick my ass
And those ends said you know
She bent a couple of people around her that are
Not nice and she's much nicer her kids are nicer and
And
And it helps she said and if if everybody would do that and think about it the whole world will be a little bit nicer because at the moment
People are not nice right the sea. I don't believe that will ever happen the world has never been a nice place
But it's never been a nice place come on if we start with ourselves humans are a bunch of murdering
Thieving flandering beings what I said the last time isn't it more and more?
I think I still remember people were nice. No, that's because there's more and more newspapers to read
There's more and more channels to see it has to be filled up with something
That's what it that's what's happening. Well, maybe that makes us grumpy because we know too much
There's something that I want to read this to you
Daywiner wrote something I don't often quote something from him, but I think he's right about this where is it?
This is more about the internet than anything else, but it's the same thing
most of the vocal people on mailing lists web logs and wickies are more fans than creators
It's as if we confuse the baseball players with people who sit in the stands watching a baseball game
Baseball game sure both wear caps and want their team to win, but one actually does something about it while the others express an opinion
Yeah, there are a lot of fans but relatively few people who actually do anything
And that's really yeah, you know, these people who write in the sun in the mirror and all these you know
What I don't even call newspaper tabloids. Yeah, you know, I think they're all basically fans
You know, they don't actually do anything. They don't actually you know, have any
Any capability usually don't have any capability in the areas that they bought off
Smart or you know, well, that's what okay, so the writing something smart stuff has been replaced with getting a scoop exactly and the scoop is then then
You know, that's your journalistic credentials if you if you and sometimes of course you create a scoop out of nothing or
Miss information that that
changed to
Yeah, but that's okay because the good thing about the internet is you can turn it off
Yeah, that's right. Yeah, yeah, it was a Harrison Ford we saw on
On the John Stuart show yeah, yeah last night. Yeah, and he said he's a very analog guy
You know internet computers. He says he thought it was all just one one big boy to create a whole
New demographic of people have to come to your house to fix it. Yeah. Yeah
Pretty good, too
I got to do a commercial here. All right. Okay. Oh, this is really this is great. I didn't even told you this
Discommercial by earth link
Which just so many people have said they don't like because it sounds like a traditional commercial
Yeah, I'll play for you first. Let's do it for a second. Yeah, do you believe anything is possible?
We do where are flink
We believe in an internet that's safe from virus isn't scammers. We're earth link
We believe your personal information should be just that personal and we believe your internet should be a friend
Not a pho
We're a flink
Make this smart choice visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you earthlink
We revolve around you
Okay, sounds more like a cult
Really that's interesting come to us come to us
Now like you very happy
Well so exactly so people have all had all different kinds of reactions and they feel that you know as progressive
podcasting is
That this is not on the same level of change
And so and it's just been yelling and shouting and name calling and all kinds of really really aggressive
Language about this and what I've said from day one is hey look you know
Here's a company who stepped in and says okay. I'll try and support this podcasting thing
Let's see if it works for us. We'll try and figure it out and we have an ongoing dialogue well yesterday
They actually ordered it up a whole new campaign
and they don't want
I can't I can't really say what happened to the people who came up with this idea
Of this come of the cult commercial yeah, but now they want something completely different
They want the listeners involved so they really list within two months this is huge company
All of a sudden said you know what we do have to change advertising why because if I listen to it
I it feels like I can trust it really yeah, what is it? I'm totally oh that's very interesting
Yeah, that's very interesting. It sounds very trustful
Really yeah for me that's fascinating
So you would buy you would buy earth you know what or did you understand what it is what earth link is?
Yeah, okay, would you mind sharing?
That's okay. I mean, I'm not gonna ridicule you you don't have to know about internet stuff well
Like a sort of provider. Yeah, yeah, exactly. Yeah, so you trust them because of that that's very interesting
it sounds
It sounds very I can trust these people they they sound very friendly
And honest and no I have not a that's screaming. I'm so fed up with the screaming always
Really
Okay, you mean the in your face stuff that I don't like that really I'm fed up with that well anyway, so I think what we're going to do is we're gonna have
Listeners create the commercial with a lot of listeners
Oh, yeah, oh, this is it. Well, I mean the commercials run all over the pod show network it's all over the place
So a whole I got to say goodbye to the satellite people you were on the satellite honey. Oh, yes
Steve leads is probably listening to you as we speak. I see
Miss you PCH is next for those of you checking this out on
Syria stars 103 we back Monday with another daily source code six
Eastern 3 p.m. Pacific and
Right goodbye
Okay, yeah, that's like old technology. We got a shut up when they're done. Okay. I have to eat some whipped cream with Steve you remember
I said don't eat a whipped cream. You may have a heart attack
Steve leads what it you makes me laugh. Yeah, well, I'm going to see him on Wednesday in New York good
Yeah, I hope I'm gonna have dinner with him. I love to watch TV
Oh, yeah, that's right cookie monster. Yeah, that's how he eats well, that's really interesting
That you like that commercial yeah, so there you go. You know what you need to get on the podcast alley forum in yellow and shout
Yeah, I think I'm in that mood that I I want something nice. I want something friendly
Oh, everybody shut up. You know
I'm so fed up with it
Makes me so tired
I want some light and friendly and nice voices and not screaming at me and you know
That's the dark
He doesn't know yet needs to go to doctors
Yeah
Because he's been pooping and now it's a lot
Being like chocolate. Yeah, that's very nice. I don't know what's going on. He sniffed on something outside
I guess yeah, but yes
Thank God, he's a small dog
You know
Yeah, because we still got him absolutely
You know, we love him today. Absolutely
You're a cute boy. So I'm gonna miss you
And I'm gonna miss you especially on Valentine day. Yeah, yeah, that sucks. I'm sorry. You always spoil me
You know, this was great. So I
Said and you when we're doing our plans the other day
our travel plans because you're going away
I'm coming we're going we're crossing each other midstream whatever and then and you know
Was who realized that we wouldn't be together in Valentine's Day and you said
What you can always buy me a bag
What
Buy me a bag feel as we'd love
Listen guys, let me give you a tip never at this couple things you got to know about women
This is a special now
Hold on a second
Very nice guys remember
The butt is never big and
Whatever you do
You will always buy the wrong bag
You buy bag on your own time
Way but I would have told you where what and you know, which
What does so then it's like
Yeah, then it's not from the heart. It's like a it's like an assignment
You know, yeah, but for like get me something. It's really fun. Give me some night quail
Yeah, it's just you know, it just came out before I knew it's my love just enough
I mean it has to be some something commercial involved has to be a piece of merchandise
Fill the bag with love. I'll fill it with some love baby. I got some love for you
Oh god
But we we women we do love our bags. Yes
All women I don't think so the bag is the new black dress
You don't need anything any more you need a good day. I hear it a nice bag just as as I should not be buying you a bag
Do not buy me a laptop or any type of computer. I mean you know you'll buy the wrong one
So there it is yeah, but I do buy you bags for you computer
Yes, you do
And I do buy you computers
So what's your point
So when will I when will I see you again?
um
Do I see you on Friday Friday, but you have Friday before you go to your sister because Patricia's gonna do something pretty fun
You want to talk about that?
Well pretty fun. I mean
I'm very happy to announce that my sister's gonna open a shop and
Accessory shop and
Accessories like headlights and the mirrors and
Accessories for women and jewelry and all does that include bags or brands? I mean not not like and bags
And bags and bags lots of bags
So that's an icing brought to them and
Of course, I help to with that so I style some beautiful pictures
You know to give to the press so that we can you know
So what does the press so what does the press do watch this you those pictures will go to the press and what would they do?
They're neatly going get their own pictures that look like shit
You watch
They don't have many pictures of my sister thanks for that, but no if they get it for nothing
That's true. Yes, for us
But has to be excused that we want to be the only one we didn't think can
But you know we're trying to do it as perfect as we can and then on the 18th of
February
I will open the shop for her
So we will I actually gonna cut a ribbon? Yes, I will cut a ribbon. Yeah, really
Unless you to get as many press there as we can
Horrible for me because they're gonna ask so many other stuff, you know, they're gonna ask me nothing
You really love your sister to do this man. I really do this
We got to go through all the answers and what we're going to do
Yeah, and then what about the long city?
Yeah, and of course, it's true because I'm in New York and now we this is what they sell
I hear he's in New York again and then
Yeah
He's he's in his apartment in
Sometimes it's all I'm saying
No, I'm not sure
It's me on all my boy toys. Yes, he's leaving you
He's leaving you
No, tell the truth. He's leaving you. There's a lot of things they can say about us, baby, but
No, I don't think after 20 years they can break that part up. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, we can live with that
They might report that I that I stepped on the dog's head because it was barking too much
I could not happen any moment
Yeah, I'm gonna put on a place song. Okay. Okay, please song
This is a grainy and um, they just uploaded a whole bunch of this is what I like about the pods hit music network and about
Talk now don't worry about let me tell I want you to listen to first it's okay
Yeah, oh yeah in the in the in the in the sealed studio now you've closed the studio door that I'll make a huge amount of difference
um
So you can put a song out it doesn't have to be a part of an album
But you can also put out five different mixes out 20 different mixes these guys keep uploading different mixes live versions
All kinds of course of course it is and
We're supposed to be able to sell stuff. I thought I was gonna go live yesterday, but I guess it's not so
When I you know this week and probably or today whatever then you'll actually be able to buy the MP3s
With your credit cards so you can support the artist. I cool is that
So this is sex in the box from grainy
Thank you
Fairland all right
You try
Everything and the put to make you for yeah
If I said those mistakes that I made were in the past if I could take it out
I would do this all again if I could
Like
Yeah
Super relax
Kind of the fox is I'm using the music I said to lace
Some kind of drug that keeps me from looking away
I
What I did
Me anything
But could have you back one day all the things that I would
To understand
If I tried everything and the hope to make you for yeah
If I said
Those mistakes that I made were in the past if I could take it out
I would do this all again if I could
I
Will
You
Tell
Everything in the book to make you for
So if those mistakes I made it put them in the past if I could take it out
I would do this all again if I could
You know I
Will
I
So of course you're sitting there. Look at your MP3 player your iPod going
You tick
Remind it's not sex in the box
No, okay, what was good? I'm on crack. It's not is not very good. I love that
That's great.
It's really cool.
Um, but we're going to do something else you want to do.
Oh, oh, the breakups, the big breakups.
See, I live in the potter sphere, blogger sphere.
So I really don't keep tabs on a lot of Patricia's world.
Oh.
Oh, that's you.
What do you mean?
That sounds like...
Let me finish.
Oh, okay.
However, comma, however, when something happens to Heather Lockleer, I start...
That's your girl.
I pay attention.
Yeah.
What the hell happened there?
Well, Adam, she's free.
Dude.
Don't you love Heather?
Yeah.
What's so nice.
Everybody likes her.
She's in the forest.
It seemed like, you know, it was like the...
Well, what's the matter?
I don't have...
It's gone every time.
Well, then stop.
No, because if it's on the...
It's still not.
It's gone.
Hey.
I don't know.
No.
What do you mean?
Um, yeah.
I'm back.
Okay.
Yeah.
Then touch the wire.
I will not touch the wire.
I touch it on purpose because I didn't hear anything.
Don't touch the wire.
But anyway.
Yeah.
She's so nice, isn't she?
Everybody says she's...
Maybe that's why she was only in Boston legal for three episodes or something like that.
Yeah.
Why?
Maybe because, you know, shit was hitting the fan.
I don't know.
I mean...
What is it?
What?
I don't know.
Why do guys not...
I guess she kicks him out every single time, right?
That's the way.
You don't know that.
Because she's not telling.
Yeah.
And Cheryl Crow split from Lancelot.
Well, that is a surprise.
I have to laugh when I see Cheryl Crow because I met Cheryl Crow.
I'm going to say 1988.
Yeah.
When Michael Jackson was doing the bad tour.
And she did the backups.
Yeah.
And I went to Kansas City.
And she had...
Remember Steve Stevens, he was the guitar player.
Yeah.
And it was like the really tall black hair or wavy black hair.
Really long hair.
That was Cheryl Crow.
And she was completely different attitude.
It's so remote.
Email punk music.
No, no.
No.
Really like hard rock punk.
Yeah.
With long black.
I think she had the long black hair.
But remember there was also there was another chick on stage with him.
Yeah.
So really good.
Wasn't the guitar or...
No, that was Steve Stevens.
I don't know.
Even with another girl who played some musician.
Yeah.
But she was doing back then.
But she was a nice girl.
She fantastic girl.
Very sweet.
But nothing like what I saw last night on the ground.
He was like, oh, whatever.
She exercised like crazy.
Oh.
But I mean, I didn't see her that naked when I met her.
No, but...
But just the whole...
Just the whole...
I don't know.
It's just different.
Yeah.
Just different.
Something's going on there.
Yeah.
Bono's the same though.
Amazing.
That guy.
Just...
I can't believe that guy.
The way he thinks...
See now, we were just talking about, you know, like crazy.
Don't know.
I'm not worthy.
He's the opposite.
Yeah.
You're right.
That's not good.
He wins an award.
He turns around to the audience and goes, hey, everybody.
Yeah.
I won.
Of course.
Like we would do.
Yeah.
Now, but this is too much.
Okay.
This is too much.
He is so full of himself.
Yeah.
I don't know about this guy.
I don't know.
And I think he...
He means...
He means well.
Of course he does.
And he did good things.
I think so.
Mm-hmm.
I never know what...
What's really...
What is it?
Why not do it?
What is he doing?
Sounds good.
Yeah.
It sounds good.
And he's talking to everybody but doesn't help.
I don't know.
It doesn't help doing nothing.
That's for sure.
That's true.
That's what we said yesterday.
I mean...
He's trying.
At least he's trying to be...
Nice.
Yes.
Correct.
All right, baby.
I got to go.
We got lots of people who got to go to work and stuff and do important things.
I was listening to our crap.
So...
Will you listen to my show on Valentine's Day?
I will.
Which I'll be bringing to you from the way of the Yorker.
All right.
Okay.
Thanks for stopping by.
Well, thank you for having me, my darling.
Okay, baby.
Is tonight the night?
People are puking with me.
Yeah, I know.
Okay.
All right.
I love you too.
Everybody.
See you on...
I got to go do the lighter thing.
See you on Monday.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.