Like, Cmon Scoop, it's DSC 44.
Right?
Right, I'm worried.
He he he.
With $16 million worth of airplane straps to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Oh, I'm testing his bedroom curry.
Show myself to my heart and swallow your heart.
To know what makes it easier to stay.
Can I hold your heart and my hand?
Let me never walk onto me.
And my love for I'll tell you.
I love you.
Trust me.
You've fixed your hand.
To make sure it's right.
I haven't lost.
It hurts so much.
Can I hold your heart and my hand?
Maybe never walk onto me.
But it's so hard to believe.
Yeah.
Can I hold your heart and my hand?
Maybe never walk onto me.
But it's so hard to believe.
That's what I'm talking about.
I think it's what I'm talking about.
Perfect for Nemesis Army.
I love that.
It's perfect.
It's short, sweet.
It's got the power in it.
And it's on the pod safe music network.
You can find it at music.podshow.com.
Or in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Nice ending guys.
Hey, how you doing everybody?
It is Tuesday coming to you from Curry Cottage.
It is the daily source code episode 484 crappy day outside.
A lot of stuff going on on the inside.
As you can tell, no lady Patricia on the show.
I forgot.
I'm sorry.
I forgot that she's getting a flu shot today.
She gets that every year.
She believes in him.
I don't.
Of course, I got the flu and she hasn't had it yet.
I don't know.
I've just read.
I was reading in the financial times.
As I was prepping for the show today.
Haven't my bagel with cream cheese and reading yesterday's newspaper.
You might as well have yesterday's newspaper.
Newspapers are outdated anyway.
I think five people have died in Israel from influenza shots.
And it seems that they've all come from the same vaccine pool.
And people have freaking out.
Understandably.
Because you are injecting yourself with the form of the flu virus in the attempt to make you immune for it.
And usually what happens is Patricia will feel shitty for a day as opposed to the ten days that the actual influenza takes.
Okay, we'll track it.
We'll see how it works this year.
I mean, there's different batches on different years.
Exciting stuff in today's show.
I've got an old friend of ours stopping by to bring us something that we haven't done in just a little over a year.
But it has been a year since we last heard from him on the show.
So that's coming up in just seconds.
I also want to talk to you about Pete Townsend and stuff we're doing.
Actually, I had a great call today with.
Oh, was his name home?
And I have it here.
Michael, this is last name.
Michael Fuller.
Michael represents aim, which is an organization of independent record labels here in the UK.
And we talked about, you know, what we could do with with their members.
I think they have about 40 or 50,000 tracks that they have up on aim.
And they do have a podcast license.
Although.
People, I think, are using it.
The uptake hasn't been all that great because it does cost.
I think 500 pounds every six months.
So we've been discussing back and forth seeing if we could we could do anything together.
And I must say, I'm bullish on the conversation.
I, you know, they could still only recommend it to their members.
They wouldn't be placing things automatically for a number of reasons.
Mostly legal, of course.
But it could get very exciting.
It could really add a whole new slew of great music from fantastic labels to the podcast music.
That works to keep your eye on that.
And I've got, I've gotten new girlfriends.
There's no doubt about it.
I have girlfriends.
They are from Ireland.
No, no, they're not girlfriends in my beds.
Not BODs.
Yes, everyone has corrected me.
On my Irish, Limerick slang.
It sounded like it was BOD, but it's BOD.
You kind of slipped the R in there somewhere.
BOD.
My bird.
Hi Adam.
Hi there.
Daisy and 10.
We're driving around.
Going to the supermarket.
We were listening to your Limerick slang.
Well done.
We think you did really well.
But we want to carry it up on one.
It's a thing.
As you were saying, your B.A.
She's...
My B.A.
It's not BOD.
It's BOD.
BOD.
It's that we have in Dublin.
We call them your moths.
My moths.
My shirt.
Moth.
We also have terms like Philly.
My hoth.
Or she's a better hoth.
Better hoth.
Of course, Tanya.
Philly.
They're all their terms for women.
This is crazy.
If you tried to use any of those words in the United States of America, for your
girlfriend or your wife, you would be sliced and diced in a second.
You can't call your girl a Philly.
Moth.
I hope you didn't say Moth.
It's sure it sounded like you.
We have like B.A.B.
Tanya.
I'm taking up the Americans' wagons all our time.
Yeah.
Listen to you the whole time, of course.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
And we're just walking over to our local supermarket called Super Value.
Super Value.
Jumping us to Super Value.
Hey.
You see how well those jingles really do work?
They knew it.
We're inside the supermarket now.
We are going to look for some splendour.
We're now trying to find a nice sexy assistant to Moth.
You have to assist us in finding it.
It's up there with us.
Yeah, he's kind of looking at us to see what the fuck we're doing like.
Trying to hide you?
No.
I don't know.
I'm trying to hide you.
Anna, are we now?
Hi.
Yes.
They have splendour.
Yeah.
That's good.
Well, splendour can be used for all different things.
So I do a lot of all of them.
I'm baked in biscuits.
And it does the taste just as good as sugar.
Yeah.
Let's go, so.
I don't know where to the cashews.
Oh.
I see some cute ones.
We just use our charm and get past them all.
Come on.
Okay.
Here we go.
Hi.
Thank you.
I'm fine.
Really?
Thanks.
Here we go.
Mission accomplished.
That's it.
Bye, Adam.
Oh, my fillies from Ireland.
Thank you so much.
I was expecting you to run past the cashier.
So if you could steal the splendour.
But this is amazing.
So splendour is available in Ireland.
I haven't been able to find it here.
If anyone has found it, you can't please let me know because lots of experiments
I'd like to do at home.
I'd like to have Patricia try it out.
Thank you.
My fillies from Ireland.
I'll call you that.
Those of you listening to this particular program on serious satellite stars channel 102,
which is one over from the Howard Stern channels.
You will not be hearing the pod show on serious for the rest of the week after today.
Due to some preemptive programming.
Which means we got fucking bumped.
Let me see.
So tomorrow Wednesday's 6 p.m. Eastern is when normally the pod show on serious kicks off.
It'll be Dave Marsh with Bruce Springstein, which I'll gladly step aside for the boss any day.
Not a problem.
Then Thursday, Candace Bushnell with Judith Regan.
Not quite sure what the show was about or why we're being preempted for that.
But I know the names.
They belong on the stars channel.
That's for sure.
And then on Friday.
And this is an interesting one.
The 2006 California governors and first ladies conference on women to the carrying that live.
And if you're wondering, well, why does that happen?
You know, the satellite technology, although incredibly cool, there's only so many channels
that the serious can actually create out of the bandwidth that they've been allocated.
And of course, a majority of the channels are music channels.
So it's got to fit in somewhere.
And we're happy to step aside for the rest of the week.
I mean, not like overly joyous.
But we're happy to do it.
Particularly for the boss, not a problem, they're whatever.
I've tried out this.
Have you heard about this, jaja.com?
Yeah, I'm always looking to screw the man whenever possible.
Of course, the phone company man is the man that's the most fun to screw.
And I saw this.
I was actually, here you go.
Here's how podcasting works.
I was watching the scobal show, Robert Scobal of Microsoft fame.
And now it's a pod tech has a podcast.
And he interviews different CEOs and leaders of, I guess you'd have to say, web 2.0 companies.
And then also let's them do a demo.
And I ran across this, jaja.com, which is spelled J-A-J-A-H.com.
So, Julia D'Alpha, Julia D'Alpha Hotel.com.
And essentially, what these guys have put together is something that I'm so happy about this.
You know, Patricia calls her mom and her sister and her mom and her sister.
You know, several times on a daily basis, which easily easily can add up to 30, 40 pounds on a daily basis.
Because it's really expensive to call the Netherlands, particularly from the UK.
So I'd hooked up with Skype.
And I have to say Patricia really got into it.
And I got her Bluetooth headset, so she could use it wirelessly,
at least in the kitchen, in the neighborhood of the computer.
And then she enjoyed it.
The quality, of course, not always that great, particularly on the other end.
There's always, you know, a complaint or two.
And those of you who use Skype, you know, were used to it.
And we, excuse me, since, hey, it was blend up.
You can usually get past it.
But this jaja system, the way it works is, you have a number of telephone numbers,
which you can be called out.
My blackberry is an example.
It's entered as one of my, it's entered as my mobile number.
All I do is on a web page.
I fill out the number that I want to dial.
I click call.
And then my phone will ring.
I pick it up.
And then you hear a voice saying, jaja is now connecting you to your party.
And then, you know, the phone starts ringing and you have a conversation is normal.
And it's literally going from my blackberry to the other end.
I'm using my existing phone with any other phone that I am calling.
Of course, the cost of that call.
In this case, now remember, I'm using a US cell phone calling to the Netherlands.
Cost 0.025 cents.
So it's, it's an unbelievable 0.25 dollars, I'm sorry.
So it's two cents.
It's like two and a half cents a minute, which is pretty much the Skype out rates, I think.
I don't think that there's much difference in any voice over IP service that you can get rate wise.
And, you know, these guys apparently have a voice over IP switching infrastructure set up,
so that they can handle all these different calls.
Now, some calls are going to be more expensive.
Just like Skype, you know, you've got zones.
And if you call a mobile phone, it's going to be disproportionately more expensive.
But the cool thing, as I said, is, you know, you use your existing phone.
And I, and I said to Patricia, she said, okay, try this out.
And she loves it.
And she doesn't care how it works, you know, but she totally understands.
And she's already building up on a dress book.
And you can actually get a mobile version, not for the blackberry, but for Nokia and Motorola phones.
And essentially it's just an extra address book.
And it does the same thing.
You know, you just choose the number, click call, then your phone rings,
and then you're connected to your other party.
And you cannot beat the price because it's the same price as Skype.
But I think it's very, very, yeah, very user friendly.
So, well, whenever Patricia's on the show, which hopefully will be tomorrow,
sometime this week, we'll get the load on and we'll find out if she's really enjoying it all that much.
And if it's working for her.
I did a conference call this morning, you can schedule conference calls as well.
Even in advance, you just fill out the numbers you want.
And you can even say when when it's supposed to call,
and then your phone will ring and the other parties are connected.
If I can technology man, I love that shit.
I love it to death.
Okay.
Last week, I mentioned that it would be great to do another one of these.
And something we haven't done in a year and a few days,
we actually stopped at number 68.
When we last did this, not daily source code number 68,
but the 68th time we did this, we had the stop.
I had the stop because we're going completely pod safe on the daily source code.
So, only fitting that it be brought back just on this one special occasion
with episode number 69.
Swasal Nuff is, of course, a beautiful number.
Just kind of on a mark.
I'm so happy that young pullet decided to do it.
And I would love to be able to continue with these.
I think that we're at the point now a year further in time.
I think we're at the point where I can actually have a licensing conversation
with Ask Captain BMI about doing this feature in the daily source code and paying for it.
I'd love to pay for it as long as the price is within reason,
so that we could do more of the one and only hit test.
Hey Adam, young pullet here with another hit test for you.
Hey baby, how you doing?
Wow, it's been a year and a few days since the daily source code listeners have heard me say these words to you.
I must say it was kind of surprised when the other day when you played the no-time generation song
of which I did the mastering you suddenly said you wanted to try another hit test.
I don't know what the rules and regulations are right now, but what the hell?
So I created this one.
Today's hit test has four intros.
Right on.
And of course, also four answers.
I can't afford and you're used to.
It's still a bit weird.
Come on, man.
Let's do it.
Let's have some fun too.
Here we go.
All right.
Intro.
Show them our second time around.
I think.
Second time around.
And this is number two.
I think I have to give up on that one.
Number three.
Yeah.
You can bring that one back.
I'm not going to fuck it up again.
That would be Patricia with Saturday night.
I'm not going to screw that one up again.
And the final intro for today's hit test is number four.
Is that hanging on a string?
Uh, loose ends, new shoes, new shoes, loose ends hanging on a string.
And that's it.
And now let's see how we hit it.
It's left.
It's four answers.
And answer number one.
It's a new one.
I do one.
First time I've used this single in the hit test.
Okay.
As answer number one.
Show them on.
Second time around.
Woo.
I know you don't belong away.
Baby.
With me.
You're looking still.
Be proud.
You're looking.
You're still being fast.
You're looking down.
It's so much, it's a great year on the stop.
It's really nice.
Alright. Now we got to get to number two which I did not know what it was.
I'm sure I're going to be kicking myself.
Just second time around.
Well, this second time around is very short time.
it was a very short time because it's a one-time only thing sort of thing.
Shalomara's answer number one, the second answer is not a first.
You've missed this in an earlier hit-up.
No surprise.
Feel fair and then go.
That's in tight.
It's a shit.
I can't believe I missed that one again.
So make sure that you're ready when you're not cold.
I got it this time, I got it this time, buddy.
Number three, in today's hit-up.
A song by your wife.
1979.
And please, Adam, tell me you didn't screw up again.
Of course not expecting something like this.
In this one time only, it's just one year after the facts.
Answer number three, Patricia and set it in ice.
And this is the fourth final answer in today's hit-up.
I'm going to say new shot.
Also one you've missed.
Real loose ends.
I'll be singing on a train.
I get a point for the title at least, I don't know.
Answer number four, the final one, loose ends and hang in on a string.
Well, I got, well, that's hit for this hit test.
Two and a half out of four.
Number 69.
Man, so much has happened in the last year.
I haven't added the audio in this way for a long time.
I want to a sweeper's audio imaging and mastering.
That's more the work I'm doing lately.
So if you need something, check it out.
It's at youngpooled.com, JNPOLAT.com.
Well, it was kind of weird recording.
Hit the score, Adam.
How was it for you?
I hope you enjoyed it.
And maybe until somewhere in the near future,
where this can all be legal again.
We can have fun playing music on podcasts.
Not only podcasts, but like you said, music from the soundtricks of our lives.
Well, thank you for playing.
Maybe until the next time.
So take care, and until then, bye-bye.
Back to test at gmail.com.
Info, youngpool.com.
TNPOLAT.com.
Yon, you've outdone yourself, my friend.
Thank you so much.
That was fantastic.
Big smile on my face here right now.
Really big smile.
I would love to do this more often.
Oh, be so much fun.
Wouldn't it?
The music from the soundtrack to your lives?
That's what it is, man.
We're missing all this good.
I love podcasts, music.
I love independently produced music.
I love everything that we can play in podcasts.
But I really, really do miss even just those snippets of those songs.
You know, and just a triggering memories and thoughts in your brain about when you heard that,
you know, the first time you heard it, the most recent time you heard it,
which was probably a long time ago.
As I said, we're, you know, I'm really ready to get into negotiations to be able to do this type of programming.
It would be so nice.
So if we pull it together young, then definitely my friend.
Most definitely, we'd get that together.
Let me see.
Oh, yes.
I wanted to play this promo for you because it's so fucking weird.
Hello.
I'm here to plug a new podcast called Freelance America.
You see, some of you over there in our former colony obviously don't feel free enough,
and now want to work for yourselves.
I mean, how much freedom do you people need?
You live in the land of the free.
You lead the free world.
You've even been known to eat freedom fires for goodness sake,
and far more of them than is good for you, frankly.
What more do you want to run around naked,
flapping your arms while singing Belinda Carlisle's live your life before you?
Not everywhere can be like San Francisco, you know?
Well, anyway.
In case you haven't already guessed, Freelance America is a podcast all about freelancing,
providing tips on motivation, tax issues, and marketing yourself.
Oh, and it's free to download.
Obviously, check it out at freelanceamerica.lipsin.com.
That's something.
Personally, I think one of them table manners is a much bigger priority.
Dude, I don't think the United States was ever officially a colony of the United Kingdom.
I think that people left to go found the new country.
You really can't get that straight dude.
You colonize a lot, but not the good old USFA.
Clearly, Yanks versus the British.
And now we're from our spine here.
It's the Yanks versus the Brits.
We'll drive each other crazy, but everybody knows that it's a parent to see.
They're just like you and me, it's the Yanks.
And the Brits have to adapt.
The Yanks versus the Brits.
Mind the gap.
Boy, we're going to see a lot of that Yanks versus the Brits stuff in the next coming weeks.
In November, when we launch BTpodshow.com, we're going to have so much cool stuff there.
It's really, of course, there already is a plethora of UK content available.
By the way, a shitload of, you know, we've really been trying to flesh out what we want to highlight in channels.
And, you know, we feel that there's just like onpodshow.com.
There's a lot of mainstream content, which is very good.
Oh, sincere.
With Splenda.
A lot of BBC stuff, which is good.
Some of the newspapers, like the Guardian, do some really good podcasts.
And we're going to be mixing that up as usual.
With, you know, as much independent stuff as we can get our hands on, obviously.
And we've already been working together with a lot of people.
And here's something that I'm trying to pull together, which is, I think, going to be very exciting.
This is through our serious satellite radio contacts.
The Who is currently on tour.
And Pete Townsend's girlfriend, Rachel Fuller, has, who, I think, she's a, yeah, she has an album out as well.
Had an album out, she's a musician as well.
I might add, she's somewhat younger than Pete, and very feisty.
They've been doing shows after the Who shows, usually with the, with the artists who open up for the band on that particular gig.
They've been doing it.
Let's see, on the US tour, they were doing it in the back of their air stream trailer.
Some of it's in hotel room, some of it's backstage.
And literally, you know, Pete will hop on the guitar, and everyone's jammed along and singing.
And so, you know, at this very moment, we're now discussing, how can we get these episodes featured on BDpodshow.com.
And how can we, you know, and there's more new episodes to come as the, as the second, like,
a second, like, a second or third leg of the tour kicks into gear.
And so, I've been going back and forth with Rachel and with the Who Management and, and, and,
Kerry, who, who really is working with me on this right now.
She sent me something extremely cool to want to play for you because, you know,
how often do you get to hear some classic, classic Pete Townsend live, unplugged, and completely unrehearsed?
I've been given the permission to play this on the show.
Check out Baba O'Reilly featuring Pete Townsend.
We're, look, I'm trying to put on on your side, but it's okay.
Okay, now, with the favourite legs in this tiny little attic room.
Right.
It's just a Pete Townsend.
It's a wonderful, yeah, with honor to be here once again with Mr. Pete Townsend.
Baba O'Reilly.
There you go.
Two, one, two, three, four.
I'll get my fucking tune, I'll let it out.
I don't need to find someone to prove to me.
To prove or not.
I don't need to be forgiven.
No, no, no, no, no.
There we go.
It's only teenage waste.
So I'll take my hand.
And drop us out from美.
And down the fire You don't melt my shorel.
And after this is here The happy ones and the em.
Let's gather together before we get one shoulder
teenage wasteland
time they're teenage wasteland
here we go
we're just going to let that
hover out into
the world
flaming lips
Pete Townsend Rachel Fuller
I don't know
wait until you see the video that
this is so fucking unbelievable
really really cool
I'm very excited about pulling that together
just imagine having that stuff
to look at and listen to
this is my second day of
being back
got to tell you the jet lag is always
just a little bit heavier on the second day
first day
you're like yeah I'm punching through this
not a problem
I can make it
I'm doing good
but even last night
is Christina insisted that I watch
scary movie 4
where they're which I did
and yeah I was like
those and often I'm like
dad you're not watching
it's the best part of
I have that but
so a little rough around the
edges today
tomorrow I'm sure will be better
daily source code dot com for the
show notes everything listed in today's
program
an adamant pod show dot com for
all your love
all you're loving
just send it to me
talk to you tomorrow everybody
bye bye
another pod show pod guest
stick it in your ear
yeah this pod cast and more
great ones like it on the high
performance pod cast delivery network
from pod show and line white networks
I love it