This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 3-7-8.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just happy that so many eaks have found a place where they can feel safe and secure,
and certainly not be friends by anyone large and muscular who may or may not be a professional wrestler.
Meanwhile, girls will know the Wursuit challenge besides looking at each other.
All the facts add to me are here.
Cause they may be an Navy cast in Google,
We got past time to rise and shine
Just another day in this life for mine
And take a deep breath
My lungs still took a past
He's got to be a good day
Wow!
Because there has to be stretch out my arms
I sail out my worries
You've been aided
No end of the possibilities
These are mine
It fills my blood
Yeah, my soul becomes cold
There's a swing from the firemen monster
And with time
I finally feel fine
Days as it should be
Of my own design
There's no alarm clock
Need to when I'll rest, sleep and dream
Mind to cade in with them's arm
All that I need nine
Truth to bad day
And I hunched to creep
Because you can't have a good day
Unless you believe
Every day good and bad
Hope you'll be around
So let's focus on listening
To the pockets
Sounds a little bit higher
No one will talk about the bad day
Oh my friend
All the facts out of me are here
Then be next to jail
I'll go to jail
Well, no, no, no, no way
No one talks about the bad day
Oh my friend
All the facts out of me are here
Then be next to jail, I'll go to jail
Yeah
We're getting late
The sun finds a little rise
And the home shadows stretch out
But we're scared flies in
Think we're in the boom
Cooling the conversation
Comcenting
The moment of meditation
The old days playing back in the mind
The whole of people in the faces in this moment of time
The summer
Wearing smiles on the spot
The wind and misery
Because someone finds tomorrow
While others become history
And where do I put into my people
For all the artists
For all the stars
Or the solar lights are darkness
Could we be dumb as any of you
Can be this hard
Has learned about respect
Between the close and the pharmacy
I mean the farmer
In the season of the harvest
Or the solar seats
And I leave where the harvest
Now everything
Goody, man, won't be around
So let's focus on this
No, the bottom is not allowed
Yeah
No, no, no
Talk about the bad day
Oh my friend
Oh the bad day
Rollin' rollin' corin' rollin'
Explosion
Oh my friend
oh my friend
With twists and습니다
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, Oh, yeah, I, uh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, ah, yeah,
That's why I said, yeah, oh, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day,
good day, old day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day and good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day, good day
want to be remembered for anything. It's to have some association with this happening in
pod safe music. That would be it. This gives me so much joy. Hey everybody, it's the daily
source code coming to you from Curry Cottage. It's been a busy morning off to the dentist.
We'll talk about that a bit. Actually, I think we were pretty good show lined up today. I got
some good feedback, some good topics to discuss. Of course, a little bit of second life stuff
in there. Can't resist since we had him humongous party on the rooftop of Curry Castle last night.
And I'm so happy to report that I finally received my first
first car story from a listener. I told you about my my first real car, the Lansia or Lansia
or Nalsia, or whatever it should be. And I have another one, which is a pretty good story,
actually. Listen to it. Yeah, and this is Joel Ben from the thinking and driving podcast,
a thinking and driving dot com. You know, I'm just listening to the Charlie from
Thursday and apologies for not doing the number. But you were talking about your first car experience.
And I'm driving right now in my 2005 sign XA recording studio that I record the thinking and
driving in. And you know, I report my podcast while driving every day. And your story about
your your mess half with your front tires kind of reminded me of my first car first car. I named
Eddie was an 86 or an 87 Hyundai XL hatchback. This thing was like driving a tin can. I mean,
it just had no sound dampening. It was a real basically a lawnmower engine. And at the time,
I was freshly graduated from high school and was was entering my what I thought was going to be
my professional acting career. I was working at a theme park in Virginia called Kings Dominion.
It's a paramount park. And I was 18 years old and I got actually got a job working for Nickelodeon.
Which is a Viacom company. Great God Viacom. And my part was I worked in this slime bowl. It was
the Nickelodeon mega-mesomanian. I was a slimeologist. If you remember from early days of Nickelodeon,
everything was this green slime. And my part was a professor, Philbert Horachio, Petton Posh,
Limeology. And I'd spray paint my hair green. And we're a lab coat and basically make a big mess
up on stage and play with kids. It was a best job ever. But anyhow, I had this Hyundai XL hatchback,
grateful dead stickers all over the back and all kinds of stuff. So, you know, it was a total
little hippie car. Well, I'm driving home from work. My hair is spray painted green. And I'm driving
maybe pulling, you know, 60 miles an hour in a 55 and this comp pulls me over. And for those
of you in Virginia, you know how, you know, the attitude of the cops. They're a big good old boy
thing. And he pulls me over. And as it's, he's the professors there, probably. Because, well,
aside pulling out of the, the mutant park there, you got the bears on the back, you're window.
So, I know you got weed or drugs or guns or something in your car. So, go ahead and tell me where it
is and on, you know, there won't be any problem. I said, well, you know, I'm sorry, you know,
I'm coming from work. I don't have anything in my car. He goes, I saw those bears in the back,
your car. And that means you got weed. So, tell me where it is. And I said, well, you know,
you won't find anything in my car. And he grabs me and says, you just implied permission for me to
check your car. So, he puts me in his, in his cruiser, he calls in the back up two other people
show up and to other cops. They're digging through my car. I'm pissed off, you know, I, you know,
a total of use of power. Anyway, I had a baggy in my glove box full of green tea because I was a
big tea drink right at that time. It was, if I remember correctly, the, the leaves were dried and they
were twisted and these little knots. I mean, you know, totally look like bud. And so he comes over to
me and he says, I found this in your car. So, how did you take this stuff? And I looked
on straight in the eye and said, well, officer, usually I put a little bit of cream and sugar in.
So, that was, he, he was, none too surprised about that. There, none too happy with that. But there
wasn't anything in my car. I could get in trouble. So, uh, pulling up to a traffic circle here. So,
that was my story of, one of my stories about my very first car Eddie, my, my little hatchback.
Needless to say, I've upgraded my car a little bit since then. You know, I, I've been recording
a podcast for, you know, a little over a year and a half. And just thank you for bringing that
memory back to mind. I was phenomenal. So, anyhow, just like to say, say to everybody out there,
don't think and drive, leave that up to me thinking and driving.com. Thanks, Adam.
I do great story. I'd love to know how I was listening to that. I made me think of my own story
with the weed and the authorities. By the way, portions of this podcast are not family safe.
And other portions are brought to you by download with Heather and Janelle,
download.acubu.com. Go figure. In 2000s 2001, I had a fractional helicopter, a fractional ownership
helicopter company with a partner, a friend of mine. And we had this beautiful Augusta 109 E power.
It's a six passenger, two pilots, single pilot, IFR, autopilot, dual turbine engines,
flying limo, beautiful machine. And Ron was in Paris. And he was on a little tour of Europe
with his, with his bride, Marta. And if he did, I'll all come over to Paris. I know there's a
a small Helly port, just outside the, I don't know, the fourth quarter or something like that.
And I'll meet you there. So, I fly there with the Stu, who was our pilot at the time. I didn't
have a license myself. And I'm in the back. And I had my, my at the shade case with me, not caring anything.
But of course, you know, I've had stuff in the at the shade case. So we land, it's a very small little
Helly port. And there's Ron waiting for me. And next to Ron are two guys and a dog. So before I can
do anything, the two guys, the Jean-Dame and the dog, or, you know, we want to search the helicopter.
And like, yeah, go ahead, you know, fully aware that nothing's going on. Well, the dog takes one,
one with inside the chopper goes, I'm starting to bug it out. And my, and my, he loved my bag. Of
course, there was nothing in it. But he could, you know, the dog was spot on. And this French guy,
man, he was like, you're small drugs. I said, I don't know, I mean, you know, but not caring anything.
And he just kept on searching. And eventually I just left and nothing happened. But it was, it was
one of those moments, you know, that was just really funny, particularly when you know that you're cool.
Hey, feedback is much appreciated from y'all. We have voicemail numbers. I haven't figured out how to
put my personal reading on to it yet. So you'll get kind of a dry, leave your message, please.
In Jersey, 201-625-6357 or in the UK, 0206-7681-3753, that UK number is not as good as I wanted it to be.
Is it? Hi, out of my name is Laura. I'm a loyal listener from Southern California. And I'm calling
because I just heard that message that you got from the prison in Chino. And it cracked me up so much.
I've tiered rolling down my cheeks right now. That was so funny. So keep up to good work. And
it's been a pleasure. Take care, bye. All right. More from that collar,
Marc Yoshimotor Nemkov later on in today's Charlie. You know the artists.
You've heard the music.
For a way from you. But do you know what inspired this song?
Hi, I'm Ed Roberts from the brand new looking out the window podcast and looking out the window.com.
Looking out the window peaks inside the musician studio to find out what inspired them to write their songs.
I was on a motorcycle trip through the Mississippi Delta.
You know, what's their song? And it was really actually therapeutic because it kind of got all that
junk. You know, up and out.
Came down in Nashville and this is about the girl that I had to leave behind.
It's an intimate look inside the music that makes their songs all the more meaningful.
Take a look at their inspiration. You just maybe inspire yourself.
You get the blues today. Want me to do the same thing. Just get rid of them.
Enjoy a lot.
Looking out the window podcast and looking out the window.com.
If you're a podsafe artist and want to get involved in the project, visit looking out the window.com
and look for the artists yet played link. Hope to see you there.
Excellent idea. Looking out the window podcast, another fantastic addition to the podsafe movement.
Again, when I die, please just credit me for that. That's all that I care about.
And of course, burn me to a crisp. And from the ashes, I want I want to be good daily.
So I want to picture of me tattooed on Madge Weinstein's ass with my ashes. Is that possible?
Hi Adams. This is Eric West with the beat, San Francisco, a podcast out of San Francisco
for gay, lesbian, transgender, etc. etc. etc. I'm a black gay man, living in San Francisco with a podcast
about just that. I wanted to thank you for your show number 372, in which you got all over Madge.
I agree with everything you said and would never consider you a bigot. I've been watching you since
your early days on MTV all the way through now, your podcast on Listen to Every Day. One comment I
did want to make is on your show being a daily show. And yeah, if you could keep it under 40 minutes,
it'd be great. My commute is less than 40 minutes. I'm a lucky person. I live and work in the same
city, not too far away from each other. Once again, thanks for your show. And if you get a chance,
come on over and listen to the beats in San Francisco. I only do it about once every week or week and a
half. Don't have a whole lot of time for it, but I'd love for you to hear it. Thanks a lot and keep
up the great work. Bye now. My here, yeah, I only get to do it once or once every week and a half
as well. Just too busy with podcasting. Okay, you may think I'm moving along really fast today,
but it's with a purpose because damn there's some good feedback. Dear Dear Adam Curry, this is your
fan, one trick pony. I'm just laying here on my bed, thinking about you. Because you see you
inadvertently maligned me on your April 21 show, the rant about Richard Show, and believe me,
all of us in the proudest fear are just thrilled that YouTube boys have made up, but please allow
me to correct some small misconceptions. Now, here's where the confusion started for me.
I really do like it when you're pissed off, and I really do like it when you go off in the rant,
and you're a one trick pony. That's what you do best. Give up all the rest. Okay,
give up the Florence Nightingale bit. Give up trying to be Howard Stern. Give up trying to be funny
and video because you're not. You're one trick and your one trick is good and stick to it.
And before you go any further, I did want to apologize for that. That was not fair,
and that was a direct attack that was unwarranted and based upon no proof at all. So I do apologize for
that. To magic in this case. Adam, I am one trick pony. I am a burlust dancer and a podcast
star extraordinaire. Less dancing. More Florence Nightingale bit. I think you're probably thinking
of my Florence Henderson routine. Now, I do understand you're encouraging Richard to continue his
one trick pony behavior. We love that, but can you please at least give some perhaps to the original
recipe. Otherwise, you are so in for a spanking, ponytail. So that is all I got to say except
there's one other way you can make it up to me, which is direct all your listeners to visit me
at onetrickpony.com. That's O&E, TRYCKPony.com. Man, I don't know. I actually considered not playing
that promo taking the spanking instead. Good morning, Adam. This is Logan from Southwest Florida.
I just got two listening to you Charlie from Friday. Well, this morning in my part, we're all
dealing with it, but I wanted to ask you a question. I know that you're a person who enjoys
a year, but I'm a few years older than you are and I just recently changed the job and changing
the job. I had to take the usual, you know, drug and alcohol tests. So that then I had to study
for the test and had to abstain for like a month and a half or so, which is really a pain in the
air. But anyway, what I would like to ask you, you know, you smoke. Who told you that?
So you require the employees of Pod Show to take a drug and alcohol test?
Dude, if I did that, we'd have no Pod Show. That would be a question.
Yeah, okay. Very much respect to you and your family. I enjoy it in listening since February.
Don't have any intentions starting on old podcasts, but I am a listener and my right time.
The only thing, buddy, is what someone do the best of the week of the Charlie. So people can
download and stay on Saturday and just all your highlights of the week. You know, maybe a
hour, hour to half long, but just raps it all up and cut that all the little thumbs.
We have no show left over.
That's a good idea, Logan. I like that a lot. That would be very cool, actually. But
be more than happy to highlight a best of, but you know, someone's going to have to do the work.
And I think that will be significant work. But yeah, you kidding me, that would be freaking
awesome to do that. Yeah, right on. Had a conversation with my dentist this morning about
smoking the old herb, because you know, I thought you didn't smoke tobacco. I said, you know,
who said anything about smoking tobacco? She said, ah, okay. So we had a pretty interesting
conversation about it. And she was pretty much on on my side of the fence, which I liked very much.
Okay. A little bit of talk now about second life. And I know I've been going on and on about this,
but since this thing is available for Windows and Mac, second life.com, you really should just check
it out because in five years, we will really know we will be using this type of architecture.
I believe for a lot of our day-to-day communication. And, well, you know, it's crack. Okay,
we all know it's crack right now. And what's happening is there's just fantastic world where
you have everything that you can imagine, you can make, you can dream up, but there's infrastructure
of money flow and land and ownership and rights and stuff like that. And I see so much opportunity.
And I don't necessarily see it as, oh, let's go all sitting a circle and listen to a podcast.
But once again, what happened last night, where I think we had at one point almost 50
different avatars, people, on the rooftop of Curry Castle, partying, I really got to figure
out how to how to play Podsake music. I got this box of free tunes and what's cool about it is
when I start playing it, everybody in proximity hears it. And if you walk away from it,
it actually gets softer and it's a stereo vibe. So if you are to the right of me, you'll hear it
in your left ear and vice versa on the left side. It's outrageously cool. You can dance,
you can chat, but then all of a sudden, all of a sudden, ladies and gentlemen, who should crash
the party? But Madge Weinstein, beautifully, beautifully animated as the bloated lesbian.
And so that was very funny, of course. But what I really, really liked is Kachia was there.
You know, Kachia, she has done all this great video work for us and does my headers on Curry.com.
She gives such great head there. And Madge says, hey, is that Kachia, the video chick from Holland?
And so they paired off and they went off into a separate corner and had a conversation. I mean,
that doesn't happen on just regular instant message systems. This was something extraordinarily
cool. In fact, I know that at least five people who were at the party got laid last night
in second life. And yes, that's an uneven number. But hey, it is second life.
He had a mispedient one from World House Radio, aka Desdinking on second life.
Ah, shoot. I'm not going to be able to play this whole Desdinking part for the sad light window
is just about the shot on us. Tonight, the big pod show, a music rewind coming up between nine
and ten. Marcus Couch brings you the best and pot-safe music from the best pot-safe music
podcasters. Make sure you stay tuned for that. Gilmour Day of the Dawn and Drew,
you used Radio and Pacific Coast Hillway before that. I'll be here tomorrow for you guys on
Sirius 102 with the Chacha. Let's continue now with with PD or Des as I know him.
Just wanted to comment on second life again. It's amazing over the past three days. How much has
popped up around the capsule? It's kind of like one of those secluded beach places where it was
nice and clean and very quaint when it started. There's stuff everywhere. It's like a circus.
But anyway, I hope to see you on second life soon and hope you're construction there.
You got the best for a lot next year or a cast or you're going to build something on there,
maybe a high riser who knows what. There's the neighborhood has changed quite a bit.
But anyway, I'll see you online on second life. Bye-bye. Indeed, it has changed quite a bit.
And a note about that. Now, just as in first life, real life, you have to respect other people in
second life and none of my neighbors and all of a sudden I have sprouted quite a few, including
my good friend comic strip blogger with his lighthouse to the right who has not once dropped
by the castle because, as he says in the comments on credit.com, he didn't receive an invite.
So I did make sure to invite him because I think that people would really get a kick out
of meeting him at a party. But I have neighbors, people. So could you please do me favor and not
be flying through other people's castles and houses and messing about with their stuff and
sitting in their chairs and stuff? Otherwise, everyone has to lock their shit up and it's just
not, it's not cool. So a little bit of respect for the neighbors if you don't mind because
they actually did come and complain. They were cool about it, but it is a neighborhood and
it is kind of looking pretty gaudy. So if you wouldn't mind taking your crap with you,
your cages, your sex machines, gosh, there were some awesome stuff there this morning. I left the
the rotating pod show headphone headball above the castle. So it's a little more of a beacon and
you should be able to find it a curry castle just to go to the search command in second life.
Adam. Yeah. Hey, this is James from Naval Cast and Face the Music. Also known as Jimbo DeSoto
in second life. I want to thank you and curse you for introducing me to second life.
From the first day you described it, I knew I was only going to have to try at once to be addicted.
I even told a friend of mine to try it out and tell me about it because I knew if I tried it,
I wouldn't be able to stop. Well, I broke down about a week ago and now of course, I'm hooked.
I can see huge potential in second life. You know, it's not that far removed from podcasting.
I think that'll live happily together in the future. I can see after all both are based heavily
on user-generated content. You make it sound like it's all about sex. But I want to set the
record straight for all those listeners of yours that are thinking about. I don't care what you're
about to say next. At the end of the day, everything's about sex, okay? But it's all about
it really isn't. It's about life. After all, it's called second life, not second sex.
Everything that makes life interesting, exciting and fun will also be found in second life sooner
later. I'm a designer by nature and a code monkey by profession. So second life is like heaven.
The coolest part about second life to me is that you can build and design stuff and then
script those objects to do interesting things. Podshow definitely needs to buy an island and then
hire me to design some cool pod casting objects. Well, that's all I've got to say. See you in
world. Yeah, okay. I'm done with that. Totally messes with your head. Totally sets you up
differently than you'd expect. It's not really a game. It is interaction with other people. It is
very much like real life. Here's, now I've been on, you know, for a lot like 12, 13 days now.
Here's a couple of observations and some things that I really, that really I don't like about the
system. If you, so here it is. The first one is if you form a friendship with someone which is
essentially is like becoming, you know, you're both on each other's body list. You can at that point
be tracked by your friend and you can teleport to your friend no matter where they are in second life.
Now, that really takes a whole lot of respect because I have business meetings. Seriously, I'm
right now doing some interesting business stuff development in second life. We're not buying
an island, but you better believe we're buying something. You better believe we need much bigger
infrastructure for what I expect we can actually do with this. I mean, cheese. Think about, you know,
the pod safe music artist performing live and then being able to meet and greet them later.
You'll find the experiences almost as good as the real thing. Almost as good. Certainly, a heck of
a lot more convenient. So, you know, I've been in meetings, I've been other places when all of
sudden someone who's on my friends list drops right in, you know, and it's rude and you really
have to treat that with respect. So what I've done is I've cleaned up my friends list. Everyone who
added me as a friend, I've pretty much removed every single one of you. Not because I don't want to be
your buddy and hang out, but before I give away friendship, I have to know that I can get that
respect because the interruptions are not fun. And what I don't think is anywhere or something,
you know, I like to be in second life. I'd like to be able to listen to podcasts in there,
do my email in there, watch some video podcasts, maybe invite someone in if I see something cool.
It's a great way to share media by the way, particularly that song stuff, man. Just I click on the CD
that I have on my hand and everyone can hear it. You know, that's a very, very cool way to share
audio and the same can be done with the video because people have demonstrated that to me.
But I'd like to have like a cone of silence, you know, so I can just pull something down,
where no one can see me, no one can hear me, whatever I'm doing. And this is not about sex, by the way.
But of course, that would be an integrated part of the experience. But you know, because I can't
have sex now, you know, anyone can can just teleport down on me and take a picture, you know,
I'd be the laughing stock. I could just be spin, Martin posting that everywhere. No, no, no,
we're not going to, not going to. And so I'm completely
celibate. Second life, celibate, SLC, Sierra Lima, Charlie. Because of that, you know, so
it would be cool if there was some way of pulling down a cone of silence. So if you're not
on my friends list, you obviously can't track me. And then the I am's cranky. Oh, man.
There's just, and I don't, there's no way to shut them off. You either shut off every
all communications or you shut nothing off. And that's a real bummer. So, you know,
I just have I am's coming in all the time. It's okay. I'm learning to ignore them or respond
when it's appropriate. But, you know, if I don't respond, it's because I'm probably doing something
melts. And I am very, very excited to tell you that what we're doing. And it'll be under the
pod show banner. I think it's going to be just, it's going to fit perfectly with what we're doing.
And I hope we get lots more listeners coming in. Pod castes, of course, very welcome because
you guys are enthusiastic and you bring such an incredible network of people and music and entertainment
and fun. And I want to be able to, uh, bad of oops, hold on. I want to be able to encapsulate that
as it were, into something that anybody can, can really enjoy and experience. And also,
we'll, we'll help you learn. Okay. So, I'll keep you up the speed. I say within about 30 days,
we should have something up and running. I'm just not going to tell you where or what or how, but, um,
very, very excellent and exciting opportunities. Hi Adam. This is Doug from Grag Radio. I've got
a couple of thoughts on DSC 377. First of all, you gave a little bit of advice to the comic strip
blogger on how to tell a woman from a man in second life. Got to throw a thought out there for you,
bro. For many, many years, I've realized that I am probably the least qualified man to
dress myself. Okay. If you send me to the store to buy a suit, no problem. I'll come back with
something that looks so sharp. You could cut butter with it. But, anything less than a suit,
I have no clue whatsoever. I don't know what's hip. I don't know what looks good on me,
and to tell you the truth, it's kind of boring. So, I go with my wife, Susan. She's also my podcasting
partner, and you'll probably remember telling her how hot her voice was, a dozen episodes ago,
but that's feedback for a different day. The thing is, Susan can pick stuff out off the rack
that will look great on me, which never would have caught my eye. I just never would pull them off
the rack and think, hey, I'm going to try this on. I think women in general are much better
at dressing their man than their men are. The thing is, I've had a lot of gay friends in my life too,
and I got to say, I have as much fun going shopping with a gay man as I do, going shopping with my
wife, because they have that same talent. So, here's my thing. I'm a little worried that comic
strip blogger is going to use your shopping test as a litmus for whether a shopper is a woman or a
man. I just got to throw it out there. If you go shopping with a hot chick, and she's picking out
great stuff for herself and for you, well, you may be dealing with the horse of a different color
will call it, just a little warning. Alright, point number two, you've implied a couple of times
with your exploits in second life that's doing something to your brain. And I'm right there with you.
I'm really digging it. I signed up a few weeks ago, and it's just an incredible amount of fun,
and it's mind-bending in its own way. Here's what I think's going on. Now Susan and I talk about
metaphysics on our show quite a bit because it interests us. I think the second life is an excellent
tool in training your brain to accept the fact that whatever you conceive of can be made reality
with just the mere thought. Think about that a little bit. You decide you want to be a little
thinner, a little taller, you click a button, bam, it's true. What better training could there be
for your brain to bring your thoughts into reality? A couple of little side notes, by the way,
I can't find curry castle doing a search. I don't know if maybe your search fell off the edges
or if it just hasn't gone into effect yet, but I'd really like to do a fly by and check out the
construction efforts. Secondly, maybe I want one of those pod show t-shirts. Where do I get one?
Maybe he could dance and one my way. I'm all over the place supporting the t-shirts, baby.
I'd be more than happy to be a walk-in billboard for pod show. After all it's done for me,
she bet. All right, if you get a chance, go listen to rock radio, g-r-ok, r-a-d-i-o. That's all for now.
For 20, brother. I'm out. For 20, my man. Hey, the t-shirts are on the rooftop. So just,
you should be able to find it in the fine command, search for curry and then space castle.
And there's a box of t-shirts right on the roof. Thanks to d-troll-up who put that together.
She made the box. She made the t-shirt. It's really fantastic. She was at the party last night as well.
And you can just open up the box and pull one out. So they're free for all and may you enjoy.
Number four, a chilled selection of their tracks from Wimble and Kiss.
And they're new. I'll be free and easy.
And previews and brand new tracks from their upcoming album.
What's in a blue moon?
You're free.
Yeah, you're alive. You won't want to miss this.
So come on down to downtown Phoenix at the one place.
Also, before you, our Mr. Meba and novelty of DK Seduce.
And did I mention, it's free. So come out and enjoy.
More details at lovespirals.com.
Adults at tones of NGB.
Yep, I'm pretty sure that Angie's going to be one of the first people I know personally who will perform live
in second life. And wouldn't it be cool if I could provide a really nice club atmosphere,
cool, mellow place. We could customize it just for the occasion.
And I'm counting on you Angie to figure out how this stuff works. Okay.
Hey, by the way, that the start of the show, I used a bit from from the most recent rocket boom
who have now started with an Earthling campaign all week long Earthling commercials on rockadboom.com.
Well, worth looking at some good stuff. Well produced, I might say.
I might add. And for those of you looking for a great deal on a domain name,
do you know who the hell I am, dot com. Unfortunately, it's taken.
You can get a discount. You purchase a domain name for $6.95 just by using the code DSE Delta Sierra Charlie
three upon checkout. You'll get your domain name for a mere
$6.95. Hi, Adam. It's Glenn from the Zedeshone Cape Town, South African. I thought
it sounds engine or your comment regarding your Yanks versus Brits segment on your show.
Oh, wait a minute. Hold on a second. Let's do that differently then. Let's do it this way.
Let's do this. And now a word from our spine here. It's the Yanks versus the Brits.
We'll drive each other crazy, but everybody knows that it's apparent to see.
They're just like you and me. It's the Yanks and the Brits. The Yanks versus the Brits.
Mind the gap. I had him with Glenn from the Zedeshone Cape Town South African. I thought
it sounds engine or your comment regarding your Yanks versus Brits segment on your show.
I've got to say that I'm with the Brits on this one. Being South African, although we have our own
cultural identity, we do follow mostly the European trends, although we cannot ignore the fact
that in some ways the Americans do have an influence on us. Well, a lot of our programming on TV
in the movies. We watch originates from the USA. Of course, there is something that the
rest of the world likes to mock the Americans about. I've been to the USA before in one thing that
it's me every time ago there was how nationalistic the Americans are. If it is an American,
it isn't good enough. Oh, dude. Whoa. That's a shot across the bow, my friend. Particularly
from someone coming from South Africa, I'm from the African's, but I don't know how it is.
Quite simply, I was quite surprised when Coldplay did very well, over there.
And come on man, English music has always done great in the states. We love it over there.
The thing is, uh, is the last layer to the alphabet. The rest of the world pronounced it as
state. Yeah, well, you know, that's just silly. Okay, Z is just dumb. It's not a zebra. It's a zebra.
Where does that come from? By the way, why is that different? Why do we say Z and you say Z? Could
someone please enlighten us? And we know about Z. But we're, uh, they only know it as Z. And
hearing Z, it just confuses them a lot. One thing I've noticed too, over the years, it's
how ignorant some Americans, as well as other foreigners are about South Africa or Africa for
that matter. Meach in the word Africa and connotations negative, although, uh, like poverty,
HIV AIDS, civil wars, etc, spring to mind. I think the funniest question that we get asked
is where the wild animals, like elephants, tigers, and lions, uh, romance streets. Whereas the reality
of that is that such animals are actually roaming in wildlife reserves around the country.
And, uh, where our cities are booming metropolis with skyscrapers, tall roads, suburbs, etc.
There are a lot of positives about South Africa and I think it's tough people to take some time
out of, to just to see them and see what a great country South Africa actually is as well as Africa.
Well, Adam, you said you wanted to come to Oz one day, but how about coming to Cape Town
and hooking up with a flatter under the peninsula? And instead of drafting dots, we can do a
lack of brine instead, or if you guys know it is a barbecue. Well, and before you come, you can take
a listen to the Zedesh Show at the Zedesh Show.com, so trust in iTunes, cheers.
Dude, if you said the Zedesh Show, you'd have more subscribers.
And I thanks, I appreciate it. Makes a lot of sense. But what you're saying about South Africa,
I live in Uganda as a child, not quite South Africa, but yeah, I wouldn't mind going back.
And people do have a wrong perception. It's like a rack, you know. I went to a rack and it was like
an eight-lane highway from, you know, all the way from Kuwait, from Kuwait to pass the board
all the way up to Baghdad, and you know, who knew, and you know, big universities and
used to be there, of course, and probably now most of them are closed, sadly.
And Thomas Vincent sent in a Gmail, just finished listening to Delta Sierra Charlie 377,
had to wonder, are you going to the Netherlands for your dentist visit? We all know the legendary
reputation of the British and dentistry. Thomas from Flagstaff. What is that all about? I think that
the dentist, I'll go to a British dentist right here in Gilbert. I think they're great. I think
they're very skilled. Patricia's getting some work done, and I'll be poor, but yeah, I think they're
really good. But I must say, just look at Tony Blair, man, why doesn't he have his teeth fixed?
It would really, really enhance a lot. I'm going in for some major work, but my problem is timing.
I need to have at least three weeks. All in one go to get it all done. I can't be flying off
to San Francisco. So desperately, desperately trying to schedule that one way or the other.
Give me more. If you got any more yanks versus the Brits, interested to hear what you have to say.
I had him. This is DJ Max. My podcast really isn't worth promoting. So I'll just say I'm from Toronto.
I just wanted to say happy national masturbation month to you and all your listeners.
Normally, I play songs related to the occasion on my online radio show, like beat it by Michael Jackson,
or I touch myself by the divine holes, or even that's the hold by Kim Mitchell.
But since the music industry frowns on getting free advertising, I can't play any of those songs
on my podcast. So I did a little search on the pod safe music network and I can't seem to find anything
that would be appropriate for the occasion. So I'm wondering if you or any listeners know of any songs
it would be appropriate to play during the month of May on a podcast. So if anybody has a song,
your own song or anything off the pod safe music network, maybe you can send me an email at
djmaxrl at gmail.com. Thanks. Oh, and since I spend quite a bit of money on gasix,
I think I have the right to say tailwinds. Hey, first of all, happy masturbation month to you, my friend.
I was not aware. I did not know this was an official holiday month that we of course need to
recognize. I do understand the problem with finding pod safe music for in that genre.
I'm quite sure that there are people listening who will come up with something. If anyone,
if anyone has it in in Jeff Smith, we'll probably come up with some ditty. Dude, you have to put
together a collection of all the stuff you've done Jeff Smith. Okay, put it together. I'm sure it'll sell.
People just love this stuff to bits, literally. So I do have something that Mark Yoshimoto
Nemkov sent me from Pacific Coast, Hellway. It's a video and I'll make sure to put a link to the original
source into the show notes for today daily source code dot com. It's not entirely about masturbation
Well, my father says you nifty. It's not you put a photo layer and we both agree that
human rights abuses are unfair. You understand you're feeling and you're not afraid to share
and I think I could do something with your hair. You smell nice and you're groovy and we both like
foreign movies. My mother says you have that touch of glass. Well, I can see a shining future
where we'll die a log and nurture. But there's one last thing I feel I need to ask.
Do you take it in the ass? Do you take it in the ass?
Because you're beautiful and curvy, but I'm less than glad I've heard of you. There's no way
you and me are gonna last. Do you take it in the ass? Do you take it in the ass?
When it comes to brands you've got a bottom line to play the bottom. I'm afraid I'm gonna
have to take a pass. Well, you're adorable, reliable, but is you're in a spiral? That's the
information that I need. When you would do it, if you love me, if you're nervous, what about me?
You'll be able to control the death and speed. Do you take it in the ass? Do you take it in the ass?
Because I've ordered an shipment of the relevant equipment. I've got lubricant and
hoppers and some breaths. Do you take it in the ass? Do you take it in the ass?
If you need more information on this type of penetration, we can always take a course
for this class. You see, I'm not the kind of fella who can get up on the nail and no one
hit a little color in my sex. Well, how they fight just so happens that I've brought my
nails, wrap on and some meds, go a little height in the effect. Ready?
Do you take it in the ass? Do you take it in the ass? Do you take it in the ass? Do you take it in the ass?
Do you take it? Thank you very much Mark Yoshimoto. Look off, I'm looking at the video. Actually,
you heard the audio only. Wait until you see the video. It's fantastic. Where have these guys
been, huh? Get that on the pod save music and network ASAP, please. Sorry, I did warn you that
this pod cast is not entirely family safe, didn't I? Okay, keep the comments coming on the phone
lines 201-625-635-7 or the UK-O20-768-1375-3. Adam and curry.com for you feedback,
daily source code.com for the latest on this show and of course the ongoing thread and
conversations at curry.com for 20 everybody buy another pod show pod cast stick it in your ear.
Get this pod cast and we're great ones like it on the high performance pod cast of
Liberty Network from Podgeau and Lime White Networks. I love it.