This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
This is Bernie from Bernie's World and you're listening to Delta Sierra Charlie 461.
Hello darlings, bubbles do you want to see my naked pictures darlings?
Exclusively here on that Delta Sierra Charlie 461.
Thank you guys and if you leave out of me tomorrow, still I'll always want to see what you want to know.
I couldn't take it anymore, just to know that it'd be full and no more.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey , hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
It's way, I don't care if it's not too late
I've been no taste thinking of you
It's all the thought you could get through
I fell to you for days and days
I can't hold my knees and die
Oh, I can't take it anymore
Just to know that we've more than no more
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
For South Carolina, very Brit sounding there
The FireAbs Hey, Kate
So number 461 of the daily source code
It is just barely Thursday here
And you got it kingdom in the affluent suburb of Surrey
Everybody, how you doing?
I'm a little off schedule here
Been in London the past two days
I already hinted at it yesterday with a or was it
It was more than yesterday
It was like the day before kind of yesterday
What it doesn't matter if it's in if you live in Australia, it's Saturday
I hinted at it and indeed we announced our partnership with British telecom
Today, which was very exciting
Of course, those of you in listening to the daily source code
Have known about my conversations with the CEO
Talk about my visits there
And there was no real big secret
But this was really an opportunity for us to introduce
I think yet another way of British audience
To podcasting and to the whole concept of independently produced
Video audio, whether it be music or show or vlog or video podcast or movie
Whatever it is
And we have really big plans with British telecom
Of course, I'll put a link in the show notes
The official press release
It was great
And I don't know
I'm woefully unprepared here
Let me see if I might have my notes
Hold on one second, let me just check
I do have my notes
What was so cool about this
Is we set it up so that, of course, when British telecom
When they fart, the press shows up, right?
So this was really an opportunity to show the press
That what really is possible with serialized independently produced content
I say, I had a list of all the crap
I'm just organized
I thought I had a list of all the journalists that came
Well, you basically can't think of a publication that didn't show up
Let's put it that way already, lots of postings online
And so I was going for two days
I came home today
Really, really, really knackered as we say here
Just due to total lack of sleep
I'll tell you a little bit about the problems we had
And I had the other paper workers still downstairs
And then you know that bio of Ron, bio of myself
The press release and a bio of Gavin Patterson
Gavin is the
BT consumer managing director
He's really in charge of all the everything that goes to consumer's homes
Including the forthcoming BT vision
Which is their IPTV project
So it's a broadband falls under his jurisdiction
Shall we say?
And the first thing Patricia says, man
And she's getting ready for bed
So we'll have to talk about it on maybe Friday's show
First thing she says, well, he's kind of cute
I have to say Gavin's not a bad looking guy
I have a feeling that he's younger than I am actually
But it was awesome
He had three monstrous plasma screens
And I used visual communicator
That's the software I used for my video show
There's a live mode
And it really, really worked well
Good questions from the press
I have to say that we were still
Actually the event was being held at the
Sanderson Hotel, which is one of those
What is it?
You know, way too hip
Is it an inshregor
I think who did that hotel
You know, basically they get old
Ugly furniture
And then throw a sheet over it
And then it's cool
Well, this hotel
I might add not provision by BT broadband
Actually by easy net
Because believe me, I was all over the network
Tracing and looking for stuff
It was driving us up the freaking wall
All last night
And I was on this till about 2am
Really nice admin who of course
Has a lot more on his plate than dealing with the Wi-Fi
Throughout the hotel
And he got a hub and a hard-wired connection
Well, the problem stem from a couple of things
The main one is it appears that there are some hotel personnel
Who had little bit torrent servers running
So he would cut him off
They'd turn him back on
Then he started and they had to block the IP addresses
At one point he actually turned off all Wi-Fi access
And the entire building just so he could say that they actually
Could provide connectivity to the outside world
But it was horrendous
His whole hotel was interesting
But you got to be careful
You have rooms with no walls
Yeah, their walls are made of glass
And it was after I almost
Seriously injured myself three times before I figured out
This little button you push
And then a curtain opens up
In front of the glass
So you don't do exactly what I was doing
I didn't see much of the room anyway
Something else I learned
Windows has a very interesting default setting
If you have a virtual private network
By default
It will always route all of your traffic
Through your virtual private network
And that's the default setting
Now if you never use the virtual private network
Then it doesn't really even matter
I mean actually
When you think about it this is totally
Tenfold
And now it's tenfold
The tenfold
You'll have
Moment
Big wind up
Sorry
Yeah
So the tenfold I'll have moment
Is that the virtual private network
Which you can set up in Windows
Which of course I have with the pod show office at San Francisco
And there's another default setting
It will automatically redial if the connection is broken
And so I really learned about this
When this connectivity
Tho tell, kept crapping out
And then I'll kept popping the connect to the VPN
Connect to the VPN
And the virtual private network
And so now I understand that
Why my mic
I set up this VPN
I don't know a couple weeks ago
And I thought my bandwidth sometimes was really weird
And the reason why if you just kind of imagine your head
I'm connecting to the internet
From Gilford
That connection is actually going through the internet
All the way to San Francisco
And then my computer for all
Technical
From all technical aspects
Believes it's actually connected to the secure private network
And San Francisco
And then it goes out and then gets my request from the network
So obviously this traffic is going around the globe
Several different times
The wonder was a little bit slow
So Andrew Grummit got on Skype with me
And he walked me through how to get rid of it
At one point I was so frustrated with all the connectivity problems
At the hotel
It's okay
Let's just get rid of the virtual private network
That's really easy by the way
Right-click delete
Problem solved
To the phone
At moment
Yeah
So anyway
Go to btpodgeow.com
If you live in the UK
And you want to get you should out there
We've lunch with that today
And we'll be rolling out
Well we'll be rolling out of course a full-blown system
Obviously targeted towards the UK market
But obviously integrated with the existing podshow plus system
And there are changes coming there as well
So a lot going on
As I said, a little bit knackered
But very, very satisfied
It's been a great couple of days
I'm going back tomorrow
We actually have a board of directors meeting
Since Ron is here and Chris is here and Aaron is here
We're going to hop on a video conference
And do that tomorrow at 5 p.m.
Watch out, scruncher alert
Adam, I don't have much time
Here in the voices you've planted in my head
I'm sitting here in the nunch room
At work and next door to me
I hear the unraveling of many roles of paper
And one word comes to my mind, scruncher
All this time I've never understood that but now I do
What I know
I don't think so
Forever I am a folder
Interesting, you know, I just realize now
That I never asked Gavin Patterson from British telecom
If he's a folder or scruncher
I think he's a scruncher
I don't know, I'll have to ask him
I think he might be a scruncher
I think a lot of telco guys are scruncher
It's beacon of podshow plus
Hi Adam, this is Martin from Reading
Long time daily source code list
Now I suppose you could call me a hundred
Because I can't actually remember the time
When I first started listening or how I do
I found out about you
So anyway
A cool idea
I've been playing around with podshow
Yeah, you found out about me
Didn't you read it on Craigslist?
Under escort services
There's no doubt loads of other people have
And I noticed on this view you can build your own channels
Which result in getting feeds
Which you can also see in iTunes
Well I've got a nice neat rocky sound bridge
Sitting on my side border home
And I thought it would be really cool to be able to play
In my channels using the sound bridge
Now I think actually thinking about this
Probably possible using iTunes
And a bit of cludging and this and that
But actually it would be really cool to be able to do that
Just by using the streaming radio function that it has
So there's one for your
Clip that people to think about
So there you go
Oh yeah
Scruncher
But I did try folding
I just can't go the time
It's just part of your complicated
Sorry
To complicate today
I don't know
I'm not familiar with the soundboard product
But is it one of those
It's just like something that you connect to
To your network and then it can receive
Streaming radio channels
If so
I believe
The smart people at Podshow have already thought of that
You'll see next to every podcast
Every show
Every channel
The same place where you've found you
When you go to play your channel
You have a little advanced options there
And you can choose iTunes
You can choose the raw XML
But you can also choose Windows media player
Or real player
And I'm pretty sure that
From what I'm hearing you say
The soundboard probably should understand
How to accept
What is it?
An M3U or a file
I think that's what it is
The real player
Can access
So try that
Try copying the link
That is under the real player
icon
Or it's selected as the downloader
For your channel
And I think that link will actually just work
You could also try the Windows media link
Because in essence, although the protocol is not really streaming
It will bring in the MP3s in a streaming progressive fashion
And play them as soon as they can
So give that a try
Let me know if not to send me some details on the soundboard
Or whatever the heck is you're talking about
And I'll see if we can figure out
Because yeah, I love stuff like that
I have to take it back by the way
What I remember I was talking about the Nokia
And the N61
That Nokia gave me to try out
I still won't use it as a phone
But wow, this is a fantastic podcast listening device
I really have been deprived
And I've had this thing in my bag all this time
I was using it as a setting up for a demo
For British Telecom
Earlier, there was a Friday
And it has Wi-Fi built in
And GPRS, so what is that?
Two and a half generation
It's not quite 3G yet
But it's basically fast enough to bring in
Smaller podcast and reasonable amount of time
And I've subscribed to my daily news channel
And I have, you know, like the New York Times front page
And it also do video by the way
Quite happily it'll do MP4
Not a problem
And it's great because the biggest problem with the iPod
Always, you know, it's got to be charged
iTunes has to have everything downloaded
You have to have connected to it has to be synced up
So either you have a religious habit of plugging that in
Every single night
With this thing is like, oh, you know, I'm in the car right now
Or I'm on the train
Let me just check my channel, you know
And you can set it up so it automatically connects
And keep your channel current
Or you can do it right there on the fly
Plug in the headphones
Or even through the speakerphone
Actually quite a nice device
Not being paid to say this by the way
Just for the run
All right, let me guess
You're talking about BT
Of course it has the address been going on
Same things like that
But then those sort of home broadband
Here we got what is fairly eventually built
TTTV
And I think that's what you're doing
British telecom
Or I don't know BT over the world
Whatever it is
But I'm not saying
You've revenge on me
These are the, I think it's that
Well, I'll find out
But if not, it's never was right
Anyway, that's very significant
And
That's very significant
Yeah, BT vision is what they're going to do
I think the end of this year or fourth quarter
Or whatever, which is going to be
Television
I think what it is
Now I haven't actually seen one of these boxes
But there's something in the UK called free view
Which is amazingly popular
And what free view does
Is it takes regular television signals
Just out of the air, out of the ether
And
And recognize that it's digital
And coded signals that are traveling over that
Over the air signal
And you get like 30 channels right off the bat
All digital, super quality
And then of course if you plug this thing into
Your broadband connection into your phone
Socket
Why then you're going to get all kinds of groovy stuff
And it'll be connected up to your television
I think it's also going to have a
PVR personal video recorder built in
It's going to be an interesting
And I think very fun content device
Let me see what we have here
Seven minutes left
Okay, you know what?
If you want to call in, leave a message
Or if you want to call in, leave a new phone
Jingle
Call the DSC
In the USA
That's plus one
6256357
In England
The UK
It's plus four four
That's plus four four
If you're a scruncher, a folder
To fingers or a holder call now
That's still cracks me up
If you're a scruncher, a folder to fingers or a holder
Sales Weasel Greg at Pod Show HQ
Sent me a very cool interview with Leo Leport
From what is this ad age
Which is an advertising industry publication
With Leo Leport of TWIT
This week in tech
And it's actually it's fantastic podcasting
Because I haven't seen it on any of the podcasting news sites yet
I think it's probably because it's, you know, it's really
It is an industry publication
I'll just read a couple of bits from it
Leo Leport didn't expect to become one of the largest independent podcast
20 began recording as conversations
With former tech TV
Tech News Guru with former
The hell is that?
It doesn't need, it's not even a fucking sentence
Tech News Guru, Leo Leport is launching a podcast advertising network
Tech News Guru, Leo Leport is launching
What is this?
Why is this copied five times?
Anyway
In conjunction with was it pod track
This week in tech is now running ads
And as you know, I've been in the city
So I haven't heard the most recent episode
Or actually the last three episodes
So I didn't pick up out of myself
But
They're now running ads for Dell
Team Mobile
And Visa
I had a couple of other things here
Adage says
What's adage digital?
So maybe it is online
So now you ask people to donate
Like a paid subscription
And you're taking advertising
Is this kind of like a magazine model
Interesting question actually
I thought it was compelling
Mr. Leport says
We're very much like a magazine model
Where the paper and shipping will be paid for by subscriptions
And ads paid the staff and help you make a profit
Unlike broadcasting
Every additional person cost us money
Because of added bandwidth costs
Which is also very much like a magazine
You do want growth
But you have to think about what it's going to cost
You actually
With more like public radio
Where your listeners are your supporters
But you have corporate donors
Who donate things like bandwidth
And also advertisers or sponsors
That is not like public radio
I think someone wrote that down
Kind of wrong
We're doing it on time here
I want to make sure I hit the satellite window
Just right
Adage says
How is your audience?
Now this is really interesting to me
Because just reading through this whole article
I see that Leo is answering questions
That were
The way we were answering
Probably a year ago
Which is great
Because I think that we definitely
Were early or right on time
With really the full-blown advertising model
And not just like an ad sense
And certain commercials in the podcast
But really having the host involved
And turning advertising into content
So Adage says
How has your audience received the advertising
Mr. Leport says
Well, there's some pushback from audience
Which includes a lot of tech enthusiasts
A certain percent of them think we should be doing it for free
But we're not the free software movement
We're trying to create a product
I'm an old radio guy
And like the old fashion radio model
With the host doing the ad live in the program
Like Paul Harvey Charles Osculade
It's folksy less intrusive
Gives advertising great benefit
Gives advertisers great benefit
Because it's an endorsement
It's us saying we like Dell
And it doesn't feel like an ad
It carries more weight
Americans kind of get it
Because they've heard Paul Harvey
I don't think Paul Harvey is the best example anymore
Okay
But it is true
You know I like the endorsements
I like talking about products in the show
I love it
I think it's perfect
But that did catch my eye
You know I'm a big fan of
The BBC automobile magazine show
Called Top Gear
In fact Jeremy Clarkson
The guy who
Well he's co-host
But he's kind of like the main host
And I don't know how much of the production he does
Or how much how involved he is in that
But he is definitely a god here in the UK
When it comes to
Well many things particularly
Automobiles but other manly stuff as well
That's kind of his whole image
And Top Gear runs in the BBC
Which means there's no commercials
And because there's no commercials
There's no car manufacturers advertising
So they can really there's no benefit
To them saying you know one car
Is better than the other or as they often do
On top gear saying the one car
You know really does suck compared to the rest
In fact this show is so good
And so well produced
And I'm sure it's very expensive
To produce
Because they do a lot of really really nice
Produce packages
And they really showcase these automobiles
And all kinds of
Very innovative and creative ways
It even won an Emmy award
This is how good this British auto show
One and Emmy award
But of course again
Because there's no advertisers
There's no automobile manufacturers
Who are advertising
Which is really what makes most
Programs if you look at the car market
When there's a show about cars
You know they usually suck
Because you know they're not going to slam a car
Because then the advertising pulls out
Now with this week in tech
I think it's interesting
That they would accept a commercial for Dell
Because you know
And this is just after the laptop batteries
We're exploding you know
Which of course was bad for Sony
Who created the batteries
But you know if something else happens in the future
Will they risk losing that sponsorship
You know I'm all for advertising
I'm totally for it
I think advertising is content
With content changing and with distribution
Changing
Advertising has to change along with it
But I am very very wary of
And I think I love the advertising
Visa, fantastic, Timo will
You know when you're talking about tech
And these guys really do talk about tech
I think that there could be a conflict
So that caught my eye
And then I was reading through this article
Just a second
I just got to say goodbye to everybody on serious
I'll talk to you guys
Was it tomorrow for Fubar Friday
Oh man they're going to miss some good stuff
As I was reading through this article
I was like wait a minute
And I went to
PortableMediaExpo.com
I think it is which is for the podcast
Expo coming up
Oh crap
That's very soon isn't it?
Um
He has at the end of this month
It's like weeks away if not days away
Which I really don't think I can attend
Just because of logistics
I really didn't know if I wanted to go
And all
But legal report is doing the keynote
Again this year
Now I remember last year
I was asked what it was doing
A whole
Conversation
And all kinds of back and forth
About Ron or I
Doing a keynote
And what the set-up kind of was
Which I didn't like too much
And actually Jason Calcannis
Calcannis
Filmed in
It was kind of having two keynote
You had the alter commercial keynote
Which I believe was what my job was supposed to be
Which I really just didn't
Whole bunch of reason I didn't want to do that
That's you know that's a year ago
I don't care
And then Leo Leport was going to be kind of like
The balance for that and talk about
Non-commercialism
And really about
The passion of podcasting
And so they did do this
They did have Jason Calcannis
Start off first last year
The keynote
And then Leo Leport
And thank God for the internet
Because I went back
And I was able to find
Not just the audio of the keynote
But also video
And the video doesn't have
Great audio of course
So technically I was just
String the two together
But the video was very nice
Because he had some funny slides
And it was a very funny
Very funny speech
Patricia walked
And while I was listening to it
On the couch earlier
The seedings
Oh he has a very nice voice
It's been a radio for 30 years
But I pulled a couple of
A couple of pieces from the keynote
It's just really really interesting
Listen on
I'm meeting people that I've been listening to
For a year and more
And it's just so cool
For us to get together like this
It's really exciting
And I'm really glad to see what Jason said
Because as talent
We win the game
Isn't that nice
So I'm not going to talk about the business model
I have no interest in the business model
Oops
Here it comes
People ask me all the time
What's your business model for
Twit and I refer him to the Vorac
The Vorac said podcasting was
Bunk and then he's got on Twit
And he said I love podcasting
It's the next big thing
And I asked him how we're going to make money
And he says you don't have to worry about that
Business model will appear
Fine with me
Because you know the truth
And the truth is
And what I'm here to tell you really
Is that don't worry about the business model
I'm only going to have 25 minutes
So I'm going to move pretty quickly
Here through this
But I know you came
If you came here as a podcast
Or you came to find out
How do you make a successful podcast
And successful means different things
To different people
If you're Jason
Maybe it means making 25 million
Dollars
To me it means making a great podcast
That people listen to
And I'm not going to worry about the money
Now Howard's got his pay day
I am
I just cut a whole bunch of pieces together
So he says he's not going to worry about the money
And maybe this was
Because he didn't quite understand
And for those of you who've been listening
For over a year
We talked about bandwidth so much
I could not
Almost an episode didn't go
Past me why I didn't say
We've got to be so careful
Because success can mean instant failure
Because of the bandwidth cost
And at this point I don't think Leo
And I had spoken to Leo
I tried to get Leo signed a pod show
At the time
I really did
I still love to have him on the pod show
Network
But I know it's very
Very tricky
Because indeed
Just like his magazine
Metaphor which is not bad
You know the more
The bigger your audience is
The more it cost you
Which is really why streaming failed
When Dan with Cots were just much much higher
In the late 90s
So what he did then
Is he played a piece of Howard Stern
Ragan on pod casting
And then he gets back
And he really
For someone didn't want to talk about money
And his keynote talked about money quite a lot
Jason said he's got his half billion
So he's not threatened by pod casting
I would submit
That if Howard were getting into Brady
Right now he would be much happier in pod casting
In fact that's what that diet tried
Was all about
Was how restricted he'd been
How excited he was to go to serious
Because he'd have no restrictions
Howard you're going to have restrictions
Somebody pays you half a billion
Dollars they have expectations
Trust me
And I don't think it stops
With half a billion
By the way
I think if someone pays you
Any amount of money they have expectations
Absolutely
This gets back to my top gear example
If you're doing a movie pod cast
I think taking advertisement
If you're doing a critique of movies
Let's put it that way
I think that
Taking advertisement from movie companies
Mind being a mistake
Yeah
I do the daily source code
This is all about stupid stuff
I don't see any advertiser
Would be a conflict on this show
Take the money
Be on you
I don't care what
They own you
Howard really
If he didn't want all that money
And I can understand why he might
But Howard would be happier pod casting
That's what's the beauty of pod casting
Nobody tells you what to do
And I would submit
You know we're talking a lot about business models
That's what this whole session is
All after this
How to make money
You keep in mind as a pod cast
If somebody gives you money
You owe them something
D-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-Eeeeeeeee!!
And I think the joy of pod casting for me
And I think maybe for some of you
Is we don't want to owe anybody anything
We want to do what we love
We only owe our listener
An experience
Now I listened to the listeners
But I don't want to have to listen to advertisers
Cause they haven't
So Leo, I just wanted to point out that you might want to touch on this because a lot
of stuff has changed when you do your keynote this year at the Portable Media Expo.
I think you definitely should talk to people about why you change your direction here.
And I understand why, but as I told you a year ago, we saw that this would be an issue.
And so I'm glad you're solving it, definitely, different interests.
Don't you think?
Yeah.
The listeners will tell you what you want.
So we've already said on Twitter, we'll never take advertising.
Oh, let's just listen to that again.
Advertisers, because they have a different interest.
Don't you think?
The listeners will tell you what you want.
So we've already said on Twitter, we'll never take advertising.
The lesson here is never say never, my friends, which is crazy because when I hear Jason say
that the Engagit podcast making them a couple hundred thousand a year, I'm done on cheese.
What have I done?
Right.
Now, there's something else that our listeners want.
Before we do this, I just, I threw this in last night because I just got some stats.
There's a company called pod track that is, I think a pretty good idea.
If you're looking for advertising, their idea is, and I've talked to Mark McCree a few times.
Maybe some of you have.
I know one of the things he did right was talk to podcasters.
They're going to match podcasters with advertisers.
Again, I'm okay.
So I definitely would like to hear more about that.
I think if you're, and pod track, some would say, oh, you know, they're competitive.
I don't think so.
The space is so incredibly huge.
There's so much advertising, so much independently produced content.
We need, we need lots of other companies doing this.
But I don't think a match of delcomputer to this week in tech is a good idea.
I just don't.
And I think you can see very easily why that doesn't seem like a good match.
I think VC might be a very good match.
Chute, you know, well, at least guys do talk about a lot, you know, I guess it all
comes down to the execution.
You know, when we get paid to talk about the little man movie, I told you, I hadn't seen
the fricking movie.
I didn't see the movie, my ad consisted of, you know, like four different times
me telling you, I hadn't seen the movie yet.
That to me is content, that's, it's commercial content.
But it's different than the advertising.
I think that the Twitter is doing.
But one of the things they have is a free survey that you can give your listeners.
So I put this up on the Twitter site on Tuesday.
We got about three or four thousand responses.
So I thought I'd share some of these with you.
First of all, this is the age demographic, and you can see the majority.
The only I did about 30 minutes.
So this is just like a 20% of the entire community.
Our 25, 34.
This is actually about what you'd expect with a big chunk, 35 to 44.
And there's five, 75 year olds listening.
I got a little nervous when Jason started talking, because as soon as money gets in
the equation, it changes everything.
And I was, yes indeed.
Big lad, he ended as he did, which, say, the talent is in the driver's scene.
Whether you want money or not, ultimately it comes down to that.
Mainly, it's all summarized in one word.
Your passion.
That's what people come to your podcast to hear.
That's what you should give them.
Don't worry about the business model.
Don't worry about how you're going to make money.
You're doing this because you love it.
Don't forget that.
Podcasting is a breakthrough because it's cheap and easy to do.
And anybody who has something to say can say it.
In less God forbid, you get an audience.
I don't think that was very good advice.
Subsequently, in the years since then, there's been many, many podcasters who have literally
run out of bandwidth, podcasts, hostings, companies have gone down.
We've brought these people into our network immediately just to keep them going.
Of course, it's much more stable now, but you can see what can happen.
This could happen anybody.
If any show just starts to take off, bandwidth is an issue.
And then, you know, if you want to offset that with commercials, and obviously, I think,
you know, having a commercial podcast, you can still be very passionate about what you're
doing.
I'm passionate about the commercials we do.
Let's speak in a voice.
Haven't even done any today.
What do I have to do here?
The Accurate Targetcast.
Right.
Accurate.podge.com.
No, I saw the test drive girl video for driving the Accurate Art.
He actually couldn't check that out.
Test drive.
Grilled.podge.com.
But it's an interesting car.
It talks back to you a lot, kind of like the Jaguar does.
Except the, I think the price is a little different.
Probably, it probably drinks as much gasoline, go juice.
But anyway, I think it's, I'm very happy to see a big media property, because that's
what I consider to be, it's really a media property.
I'm happy to see it following in the business model that is being established.
And I'm going to be listening really closely to what the execution is of their advertising.
And Leo, again, obviously, if you would like to have Podge show try a couple matches with
advertisers, you know where to reach me.
Fuck it.
I'll call you.
All right, everybody, anything left?
No, the only thing left is a little more pod safe for music for you to take out on this Wednesday
night Thursday.
I love you every single day.
I love you from the moment that away.
I love you all the new 11.0.
I love you wherever you go.
I love your hair and your smile, your teeth and your eyes and your thighs.
You're so much more beautiful than me.
We should be together, we would be so happy.
I picked you up and down the streets.
You are walking next to me.
Hand in hand, we walk along.
We'll be so happy people will say it's wrong.
I love you every single day.
I love you from the moment that away.
I love you more than you will ever know.
I love you wherever you go.
You took an order against me.
The magistrate said that I was naughty.
Within a thousand feet of you I cannot go.
I watch you from the edge of the exclusion zone.
Yesterday you were wearing pink.
You went into the park for a drink.
You had scotch and coke with the man named Brett.
Brett is dead because Brett was a threat to me.
I love you every single day.
I love you from the moment that away.
I love you more than you will ever know.
I love you wherever you go.
There isn't anything that I would rather do than spend the rest of my life with you.
But they want to send me to jail because I sent you my love in the mail.
I want to keep you in a box of beautiful box with velvet lining and a hole in the lint.
So I can slip your food.
We'll be together.
It will be so good.
I love you every single day.
I love you every single way.
We'll be together just you and me and the woods in the cabin in a box for eternity.
I love you every single day.
I love you from the moment that away.
I love you more than you will ever know.
I love you wherever you go.
I love you every single day.
I love you from the moment that away.
I love you more than you will ever know.
Of course, it's hot safe.
It's from down on.
It's the gorskees and every single day.
A nice song, just like it, it was really sweet.
I think I played them before.
Internet girl, that was the song that I played by those guys before.
All right, everybody's on off to London Town tomorrow again.
But oh and Ron and I, I think it's probably been about a year.
We've been a strategy guest as well and we keep threatening to do one.
But I think we actually might pull it off this time.
Unless we get really busy as usual.
All right, I'm off to bed everybody.
Thanks for listening.
DailySourceCode.com.
That's where we can find all the links to everything discussed in today's show notes.
And Adam and pod show.com is, uh, we can email crap to me.
Talk to you tomorrow everybody.
Bye bye.
49, a folder, a happy listener.
And this is when you are your best.
When you're talking about all your experience in music.
So the just solo guitar, I love it.
When you, I know what I just played was you going up.
But you just do an excellent job of just bringing it all together and tying it together.
It's a joy to listen to you every day.
And thank you very much.
Take care, bye.
Last.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network
from pod show and limelight networks.
I love it.