This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 384.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky and crispy.
I like to think I'm flying into this show.
Fantastic.
It's Adam Curry.
Mingi moves.
That's right.
I'm Mingi.
And I'm going to do this.
Mingi and Harvey.
And you know what?
If anybody doesn't like the cowbell, well, they can just take it.
Say what?
I didn't listen to my podcast.
It's a gun.
Well, I'm the Charlie.
But after going to play the cowbell well,
I just got to hear what you tell us.
So I'm thinking it meant keep it rocking.
I'm going to run.
It is the record.
It almost means laying on the radio.
It's turned.
It's our shot of a cliff.
With the disposals of melody that might just catch their ears.
Well, yes.
I'm Mingi.
It's the world.
And I'm going to run.
So I'm just thinking it meant keep it rocking.
So I'm going to run.
We're headed straight for the woods.
We've got to make no time.
We'll all be getting played at all the days.
Maybe we should go on and stretch.
We're getting used to whether or not we're crazy.
We're the next one.
And we're going to run.
So I'm going to run.
So I'm going to run, run.
And I'm going to run.
So I'm going to run.
And then no one will run.
So, you have to run.
other ones. We're slowly going to ramp it up. And of course, this is if the artist wants it
obviously. So I just play whatever I want to play. We contact the artist. If he wants
to put it up or he or she or they want to put it up for sale, then we're going to open
the system up just a little bit wider. So we're starting folks. It's kind of like a staggered
thing, pod show plus, pod say music network. It's common. It's common. It's common. We'll
get some tissue. It's common, cranky. Kind of a funky day today. A two o'clock continental
time. Dutch time. My mom hears the results of a latest scan. So of course everyone's
nervous about that. So that's kind of funky. Also going on outside the neighbors across
the street. And to be fair, they did tell me about this, but I hadn't really contemplated
what it meant. They're putting in a new front door. So you may from time to time here various
bits of drilling, sawing, hammering. Okay. And stuff going on. And it's a hump day. You know,
so we're kind of writing the middle of everything. But I got to tell you, I have to have
catch up days or response days or whatever we want to call them because I start off one or two
threads of conversation. Nobody listens at the same time. It's all delayed. Some people are
more than a week. I'm not going to say behind, but that's the nature of their listening
habits. So they're just on a different schedule. And so comments come in also kind of staggered
in a way. And so what was discussed on Monday, some of it even on Friday, is really now coming
through on the voicemail lines and the audio feedback today. Except, of course, for this bit from
just the other day. Adam, it's not a report to Serbia. Just got done listening to the latest
daily source code. And you mentioned the toilet, the first water of your ass. And you said it
is mostly for women. Well, no, when I found out about this toilet, I have Crohn's disease and
you know, you go to the bathroom a lot. Well, when you wait too much, is this too much information
that you're about to give me my friend? You get sore. Do I found out about it from a lot of my friends
that have Crohn? They're highly recommended to toilet because like you said, you feel so fresh when
you're done. You know, I'll probably regret leaving this message. Yeah. But okay, you know,
like I said, I don't really think it was made strictly for women. I think the whole
of the day when you should be more clever when in our daily lives. Because if you think about it,
if you took a shower, but didn't use water and you just like toweled off, you wouldn't feel very
clean. Well, that's my two cents whatever the hell it is. I was in one. Well, we didn't say yesterday
is that we've actually owned two of said toilets. I forget exactly what the make in the brand was,
but we had them in the bunker in Amsterdam. Yeah, man, I loved them. And this actually is probably
a topic for more Metro sexual moment because you got to be clean down there, guys. Oh, god.
This is this show is getting off on the wrong foot already. Hey, Adam, this is Nick from Germany.
Not dot com just Germany. In the Metro sexual moments on Charles 383,
you said that you missed toilets that shoot water of your ass. And I remember that my uncle actually
has one of those. And he told me that in Germany, they're called popo duchin. Oh, Donald,
let me just write that down. Popo duchin. And that there is a website where you can get them.
Oh, let me guess. Popo duchin dot com of point d. It's www dot popo duchin dot d. And I don't know
about your German skills, but since you speak Dutch, I figured you might understand some of it.
If you don't, of course, that'd be happy to translate it for you. And also, since you haven't told
any stories about you being in Germany, at least since I've been listening to the show,
I hear by asking to do so, because there's gotta be something, please. Well, that's it.
So far, thanks for doing what you're doing. And bye bye.
I do thank you for the for the link. Yeah, Patricia, I definitely going to get new to it.
You know, if I, if I was an Amsterdam right now, and we still had the bunker,
I would do a sound seeing tour of this apparatus for you because it really was wonderful.
And the minute you even just sit down on the seat immediately,
nice soft suctioning action to remove any vapors and odours. And then when you're done,
you just hit a little button on the side there and a little thing comes out and turns
swivels up and mists, not spray, but mists, this lovely warm liquid.
There where you want it. When you let go of the button, that thing retracts and then
cool. That's right, the blow dryer. I miss it. Maybe Popo Dusha is something very similar.
Crap. For this next comment, this is actually one for Patricia. Hold on a second. Let me just
open up the other mic. Okay, she's next door. Getting ready. Hold on, let me see.
Can you come for one second? Please, come on the show.
All right. Yeah. Our officers are located very near the studio you see.
Okay. Here, the earbuds for you, baby. Okay. You want to stick those in? Because you have to hear this.
People talking about, um,
says, Dr. Ready to laugh. Really? So I have two. But I think that a combination of
it's not working, is it? Can I help you with that?
These are so tiny. Yeah. You got to put it in that way first and then swivel it and then
jam it in and then hit you on the head there. Yeah. Let me do this one. That's what you do.
People hate this, by the way. They say, I don't care about your wife's ear buds.
Except when they drop in your cleavage. Yeah. Okay. Listen to this. Hi Adam. This is Steve. I'm a
listener and a pot-safe music artist. I had a couple comments. First, thank you for playing
Kevin Reeves. You've played it before I forget Kevin Reeves. Also for sale. I believe as of today.
On the pot-safe. Yeah, we're starting to sell. Every song we play on the source code will be made
available for, well, if the artist wants it, obviously. Yes, sure. Do you know that Kevin Reeves is
blind? Not that it makes any difference. But it's interesting. No, I didn't have that. No, because you see
you saw the video, right? And he had no Stevie Wonder vibe going on. No, no, no. The international
sign for blind pianists. Please, you got a shake to head. Yeah, no. He didn't have any Stevie Wonder moves.
No, no, he had no moves in fact. No moves in love. God, what a good song, huh?
Is that how he was a great song? So buy that for your mom, mother, the pot-safe music. Okay, so he's
happy we play Kevin Reeves. The songs are a couple of different times and every time I've heard
that I said, wow, who is this? This is fantastic. And just random is what I said to get his album.
Just continue to play that kind of artist who has great voice, great music, greater range
when it's just the whole package. Love it. I'll check out Simon James who you mentioned and I hope
you keep your word and play him on a future show. Another really deserving artist. Yeah, I will.
Now, I've got some not so great feedback that I hope won't offend you or a Patricia on your
last show, Daily Source Code 383. You'd have to purchase your baby record something for the
pot-safe music network and she was really against it. Now, I'm not going to pretend to know what's
in her mind or the reason why, but, you know, to me, it can across this really elitist.
You know, what does she meant this or not? It felt like random. I'm a professional and, you know,
this is for these little people that are one of these. And if they want to play with this little
hobby, that's fine. But, you know, I get paid for this. That's anything. And you'll maybe a little bit
of shame for saying, well, you know, I think it's silly for an artist who's had a career to build
back and try to recapture it against the youth. I think that's stupid. You know, if you've got a voice,
if you love music, why not? Why not go back and do it? You know, have some courage. If
back in the game, put some music out there, let people enjoy it. I mean, whether the couple
months ago you played Colin Rays, Hurricane Jane, I hadn't heard of that guy in years since
this song, Love Me, and I really liked at the time. And I reconnected with this artist in this
music, because guys still making relevant cool music that I loved. And just because radio doesn't
play, it doesn't mean it's not good and doesn't mean it's not professional. So I I'd love to
be discovering that. And I love hearing that, uh, Nancy might not have heard so while I'm seeing
what they're doing now. So, but you're, please, please reconsider. Think about recording something.
I mean, if you don't have fun doing it, just think about how you feel when you hear these
great scream and artists with wonderful songs, you know, the joy that that brings, you know,
bring some of that joy to someone else. Come on. It's not for yourself. Do it for this
man. All right. Again, this is Steven Stewart. It's in one. Bye. Okay. Oh, that's so nice. He's really upset.
Well, I thought I think he misunderstood. Yeah, I think that's not, uh, that's not what I mean
professional. I don't need days or anything or, you know, and looking down and other people,
not at all. Now, what I mean is my, my, um, I come from a musician family. My, my dad is a professional
musician. He always had to work really, really hard to feed us. And, uh, when I started, it was actually
normal that I had to work to, you know, once I came from schools and, you know, are you any musical?
Yeah, I have musical talent. So why not? So I started to work with my dad and we work really
hard until four or five o'clock in the morning. This is when you were 15, 15, 16 years old, yeah. And,
you know, sometimes no day off just every day. Do I get to break out the violin? No, no, no, not at all,
not at all. So that's how it started until somebody came in one of the jazz clubs and saw me. And
then I was, uh, in the meantime, I was between 17 and 18 years old and I got a contract. So from
then on a record contract, a record contract and from then on, I recorded, um, so you really had,
so you went straight from school into, uh, night clubs, night clubs working, working hotels. Did you
like it? Uh, yeah, I liked it because otherwise I wouldn't have done it. You know, I had to
choice. Do you want to do it? Okay. Well, we need a singer. Do you know all the songs? Yes, I know all
the songs. Not just singer, but you would play the clavays and the, uh, marimba. Um, the, uh,
yeah, seal of all native. Is that a little far? That's not a marimba. No, that's not something
out. That's from wood and the clavays. Yeah, this is from, uh, and cowbell, metal,
everything, and even in the, um, when we had a break, I, I was a drummer. You know, two of,
three of us, we were sexy. Yeah, three of us would have a break and then, you know, they
needed music in between. Um, it was a different time. So I worked really, really hard. It's got nothing
to do with it. I know that, um, but, um, so then when I started to, um, record and had all the, I had a
lot of hits, uh, and, and did a lot of gigs. And so for 40 years, that's 40 years. 40 years,
I was in show business, had ups and downs and flops and hits and everything, um, good
many times. Great time. Great time. Did everything I want every music I tried because I'm,
I'm very multiple, uh, orgasmic. No, there's so many, so much music and, and so many things
that I like. And so I tried everything from classical to disco, from jazz to hard rock,
everything because I love it or I love music. So it's got nothing to do with that. Um, but I noticed
that life goes really, really fast. And sometimes I lay my bed and I think, oh, there's so many
things. I actually would like to try. I wish I was a designer. I wish I would, you know, all sorts of things.
Okay. So, you know, and, and let me just say, because the listeners don't really know this, but you
really are, you know, exploring your creativity in many different ways. Because also when I, um,
did my performances and when I did my gigs and, and had, and made beautiful video clips and
everything, I designed all my clothes myself with my sister. Yeah, you guys do in the shop now. We love
that. I, the, the most wonderful thing was being creative in the studio. That's what I like most of
it, which is what I offered you, by the way. Yeah. I love that. And, uh, creating the, the look,
you know, uh, your style and everything. Yes, these sort of things I love. And now, now you're working
on your offer. Yeah. And musicals and halloween. Several offers? Yeah. From, um, and actually,
I regretted that I never did that, but it just came a wrong time.
Yeah, I came at a wrong time every time, the last of I had was a couple of, it was actually six months ago.
Was it the whiz? Was it the whiz? Was it the whiz? Was it the whiz to do that?
The whiz, actually. Mr. Von der Ender asks me every time. He knows, he knows I can do it.
And I really regret that that never happened. So that's that's one thing. I regret a little bit.
For the rest, I like to do other things. Okay, so it's not it's not it's because I think that I like to know
Before my life is over. Oh, baby don't talk like that. No, it's true because I know it's goes so fast. I feel like a teenager inside
But that's of course not true. The truth is that I'm 57, you know, but in my head between my ears, I feel
30 or something, you know. And so because it goes so fast, I want to do other things. I have other
But it wouldn't take that much time on your life, but it's just not a creative direction. No, right now because in my
In my guts, in my body, in my the feeling that I have is I did it all. I tried it all. I've really enjoyed it. And that's it.
Regrets, just musicals. Yeah, that's the only thing that never happened. Otherwise, I've done everything.
Well, there is really good news, though, Han. Oh, yeah. There is good news about all of this. It comes to a good and sweet ending.
Adam, this is rubber head again from rubber room radio. This one comment about Lady Patricia and her
reluctance to do a pod safe tune for the pod safe music network. And you were trying to work away
around this problem by saying, hey, I'll get you some musicians and I'll get you the right lyrics and all that good stuff.
And we just want to hear your voice. Well, you know, in that same show, she basically already recorded a
pod safe tune. Don't you remember this?
Why don't you just put that on the PMN? I mean, I would download it. I'd buy that for a dollar.
This is great. I call it the cowbell Patricia remix.
I'm so talented. Put that on there and watch the money flow in, man. We're going to be rich,
right, Adam. Have a good one. Thanks. We're going to be rich. We're going to be all the by the two or three
pop or do her do her. Oh, you know, something, you know, what I also liked and doing that with my dad because he's a great
musician riding commercials. That's a lot of fun. Yeah, you got what? Hey, listen, we have this ad challenge coming up.
Yeah, for Earthlink, which means you get to create your own commercial. Can I be the judge?
Interesting. Interesting. You could be, you could possibly be a judge. I was thinking maybe if you'd
like riding commercial so much, let's write one. Let's write a good one. You could be a winner.
Oh, forget being a judge. Just be a winner. See that. I can't be a judge. I'm not a people.
It's you. I'm not like, oh, I want to do anything. I can do better. See, I'm not like that.
So there's so much talent out there. That's for sure. Yeah. That's I need it every day. I'm amazed.
Yeah, every day from here. I took this very often and fulfilled the dream right on a dream of mine.
And then I'll let you go. This is worthy from a geographical location from Kansas in the United
States of America. I was just listening to a USC number 383 and it's good now, but notice when
a Patricia's earbuds fell in between her lovely breath that you referred to those breaths as
guys. I find this a little disturbing. I'd like to have an explanation for you for that.
I've never heard this referred to as guys, quite job as it actually. Anyway, great show.
Keep it up and a good shot man. How's that? Later. Yeah, why are they gone? Well, I thought about this.
And I thought, why do I say that? Because when I come home from San Francisco. I'm not
being a bra right now. That would be correct. See how beautiful. Oh, oh, oh, so when I come home from
San Francisco is an example. I say hi baby and I say hi guys. Yeah, sure. So now I figured out where
came from. It's not that hard actually. Oh, remember Magnum PI? Yeah. Remember Higgins? Yeah.
Higgins had two dogs. Yeah. Yeah, dobermans. Yeah. And then whenever Magnum would be like,
you know, the dogs were threatening to bite him. He'd say hi guys. So I think they are new.
Your breasts are like, they can attack you. No, they do. Okay. All right, baby. Thank you.
But I don't want to take up any more of your time. Hey, I apologize for my parents today. Oh, I love it.
Really? It's the baker. The Italian baker. Would you like some pasta? Yes.
Yeah, even the beard though, because the beard is is the beard is pretty heavy. Yeah, that I don't
like, you don't like beard at all. It's only because it only. I don't need a facial scrub.
Or any other type of scrub for that. Yeah. Yeah. But is it the look you don't like as well?
No, it's okay. But look, it's pretty rugged. It doesn't hurt when I kiss you. Yes, it does.
Yeah. Okay. All right, baby. Thank you so much. All right. Everyone appreciates it. So it's not
It's not a lead. It doesn't mean to be. No, I know. I knew that. I just wanted you to say it.
Now, before I forget, I've been holding this piece of paper in my hands for weeks now. I want to thank Paul
Sabie, who connected me with Captain Dan, who, of course, we've talked about a great length
on the Charlie from our flight to Rotterdam. And, uh, and I keep on forgetting to to mention him.
And I, and I actually had this piece of paper next to me yesterday. And, and I forgot it again.
So, uh, yeah, Paul, I owe you more than two beers by now. Mate. Okay. Paul Sabie, everybody. Thank you
very much, dude. Really appreciate it. And if I have a window CE gig for you, of course, I'll put
you at the front of the line. You're crazy. All right, Pacific Coast. Hellway is next for those
you listening to us on, uh, serious stars 102 followed by East Radio Don and Drew, the Gilmore daily.
And then, uh, the Frank Truth. I, uh, I was wrong yesterday. That's today is the Frank Truth.
I'll see you tomorrow. And meanwhile, here on the Charlie, we're moving forward. Why is the world so
corrupted? Why is it so terribly negative? And all we can hear about every day is bombs and weapons
and the failing economy and greed and money? Well, who the hell cares? Me and my two
compatriots of granted a show that lets you get away from the typical bellycraft that goes on.
And yes, I know all kinds of crap goes on. And it's a show for the people that like to get away from
it all and hear great skits, rants, raves and all kinds of really cool stuff. Um, and actually we have a
new advice column where you can actually submit your own questions to and now we'll currently run
a contest where you can win your own skit on the show. It's going to last five or ten episodes. So
that's pretty sick. All you have to do is go to www.thepodcast and idiots.com and click on the
sidebar and you can subscribe in many many many different podcasts and clients very easily.
So all you need to do is go check out three idiots and a podcast at www.thepodcast and idiots.com.
Once again, that's www.thepodcastingidids.com.
Three idiots podcast is proud to be produced and recorded on a map.
Probably no less. So we tried out some hypnosis stuff yesterday. Jeffrey Schaefer sent in a
Gmail out and listening to the May 9th show and laughing my ass off. You in Patricia just too funny.
I listened to you show a lot last year around episode 300 got too busy to continue. But here I am
again listening to show while I'm my one and a half hour train ride one friggin way.
Keep up the great stuff. If you're ever headed to Japan, especially in soccer, let me know. I'll show
your on dude. I would love to come to the the Eurasian basin. Gotta go to Australia. Gotta go to
Japan. I'd like to go to China in person. Okay, PS those hypnotic tones fuck me up for like two
minutes, man. I was writing an email totally focused and then heard those tones and it was like
you erased my mind. Scary stuff. PPS just reread my email before sending an out damn. I sound like
a loser. Sorry. That's okay. We accept losers here. Elaine says those tones set off a migraine.
I get nasty migraines and have for 20 years when a migraine is building around 10 hours prior to a
full blown migraine for me. I become very sensitive to bass sounds and ammonia like odors.
I get a metallic taste to my mouth and very photosensitive. So I'm rather sensory triggered.
The last tone you played actually pierced my head like an ice pick right above my right eye.
I could put a fingertip right on the location. I wasn't even using headphones just my computer
speakers. Man, I don't know what it does to other people but I sure won't download the program.
Actually, I thought it might be great when you mentioned it. Wow, thanks for the warning, dude.
Well, I did warn you and it didn't work as far as I'm concerned. I'd say that's two strikes against
the whole idea. I apologize. I really do. But luckily there is some solace.
Darepool, Patrick Darepool writes in another way. Here we go. Wait, that's not the right one, am I?
I'm sorry. He wrote a whole thing about about the US Iran Iraq oil thing. But he actually sent me this
link to a site called warpmymind.com and they have MP3s for download. Now I registered
but that doesn't actually let you download any of the cool stuff. These are MP3s that apparently
give you sexy dreams and all kinds of other stuff. I'll get those up for tomorrow.
I have to get my credit card and everything all arranged. But I just want to get started with the show.
We'll try, I'm not going to try those piercing tones anymore. I don't, and if we do anything with any type
of mind control stuff, I will definitely warn you beforehand. But I do want to try out the sex
dream stuff. So I'll look for that. Maybe Friday will be a good day to try out the sex dream sounds.
What else are we talking about yesterday? This is all just responses. It's amazing.
Amazing. Oh, about sweating, night sweats. Hi. P-dub. My darling P-dub sent me a, sent me an email.
I presume it's okay for me to read it. But he says that he's a huge night sweater.
Ross, cause it covers everything I contact because it's soaked in the morning. Oh, man. Oh,
P-dub. That's disgusting. On the other hand, I think I need to sweat at night. I always feel
great in the morning after a good sweat. Yeah, you know, I have to agree. Now last night,
no sweating. Here's what we did. Well, actually, I saw this email come in from George B. The third
George Burnett. Adam used to have the same issue when two things were in effect. One,
two, a high of a thread count of your sheets, 300 plus Dernia, I guess it is,
makes the sheets very hard to breathe yet. We've actually, that is one of the things we discovered on
our own and two sleeping naked. If I slept naked, I would get the sweats every night. Put on a
shirt and or boxers and you'll sleep like a baby. And you know, and I have I've slept naked all my life.
I think I had pajamas and I was like up until like six or seven. But then once I discovered
what was going on down there, I didn't want anything in the way. And I've slept naked ever since
and last night, slept with shirt and boxers and absolutely phenomenal, no problem at all.
So thank you very much. Thanks for sharing both of you. Voice mail feedback numbers,
201 in New Jersey, 625, 6357 in London, 02076813753. Hi, Adam. This is Janice from Minnesota. And
I'm going to try to keep this brief, but I have three comments. The first is about audio feedback.
The phone is a great idea. I've been wanting to leave you an audio audio comment for a long time.
But I have to say that I've been hoping that when you unleash Pacho Plus, it includes an easy way for
ordinary listeners who don't have Pacho's podcast to leave audio comments record them and leave it
and send them to their favorite podcasts. I think pre-recorded comments have the potential to have
higher quality, not just audio quality, but also kind of slot quality and content quality.
Hmm, I hold on a second. I got to interrupt there for a second. So first of all,
yeah, we're looking at several different ways to provide simple feedback from your computer.
If there's some Java applets, there's Macromedia flash stuff. There's a couple of ways to do it.
And we're probably going to partner with one of multiple parties to do that. So absolutely,
a cast blaster, we could also do a miniaturized version of the cast blaster engine could certainly
handle it. So that's another option, although that would only work on Windows and not on a Mac.
But I disagree with what you say about audio comments that are done in high quality, that the
content is also better. I totally totally, totally disagree and besides that, even lots of people
drive around without the recording stuff. If you're listening to my show on the go and you want to
just respond right then and there, well, it's fresh. I think the phone line option really is the best.
I'm hoping that. Oops. And I just have to mention, if you call the phone lines,
I still haven't figured out how to put in the personal reading. So you get the very
impersonal, leave your message now, send a fax, whatever, press 5 to page. Just leave the message.
You call the right number. That will be in Pledgeau Plus. My second comment is just a suggestion.
Just like you play promos, it might be interesting to have a feature in the daily source code
where listeners suggest they have a podcast. I have a couple of suggestions in that and within
that, first of all, I was listening to daily source code for several months before I discovered
digital flotsome and people may not realize that the satellite repairman who was voiced
they hear when they first listened to DSC has a fantastic podcast of his own. So I would suggest
digital flotsome for your listeners and another, you know, I hold on a second. Good idea.
Absolutely a great idea. If there's a podcast that you want to promote, I'll accept that.
Please, I was talking to Brittany the other day. You know, my second life partner?
That sounds so fucked up. And she said, you know, I really love the promos.
It's interesting. So you know, the problem is, is someone who promos sucks so bad or they're
so long and not entertaining and just, you know, just doesn't grab your imagination at all.
So, you know, listeners, get creative. Please, I'll accept it through the phone line too.
Doesn't matter. Just, you know, it doesn't have to be a big montage. Just really mean it.
Sell it. Sell it to me, please. I listened to every week. Of course, daily source code is number one.
But another podcast I listened to, inside the net, in last week's interview,
they suggested that a future episode and I don't know if it's the one that's posted today
or not would include an interview with the creative second life. So I thought you might know about
like to know about that. Anyway, my final comment is just about the length of the podcast.
I know a lot of listeners have said 40 minutes and I have to say that I think one of the
beauties of podcasting is that you can vary the length of your podcast and I'm happy to see that
you've been doing that anyway. So anyway, keep up the great work at them. I really love the daily
source code. I enjoy my commute because I have something great to listen to every day. So thanks again,
take care. No, you take care and thank you so much for calling out in. And I'll check that out.
I'm familiar with the podcast, but what was that? Those guys. I'm familiar with that. I'll
definitely check out that episode you mentioned with the creators of Second Life.
Spent a little time to yesterday. You know, I'm just about ready to start pulling it all together.
I was thinking maybe we do, and now this is just, you know, what can I say?
Yeah, maybe I shouldn't. Maybe let me pull it all together. Friday we'll talk about the big
bash that we're going to do Friday. But there is some other SNL stuff to talk about today.
Hello. Hey, Roger. Now I'm at the go for home in Second Life. Yeah, yeah, it's pretty cool.
Hey, where are you been? It's been three weeks since we heard from you. Yeah, yeah,
since sale. Yeah. Hey, Roger, myself. I got to go. Yeah, so I changed my
hometown. Yeah, I thought you were buying. Hey, CSB. Yeah, and we move the bedtime story
towers so you can see curry castle. And now we have a matching son in a house. Yeah, it's pretty cool.
ACSB, don't forget to stop by the bedtime stories. My kids will go from home in Second Life.
Yeah, you can't miss us. We're right there by where you live. Right by the tower.
Remember CSB, once you do go for, you never go for anything else. Sorry about that. Just
little go for human. Hey, like I'm trying to phone. Check out this cool matchup. I got from the
pod safe visit network.
Okay, by the way, uh, there's not a day goes by
that I don't get 20 emails at least of people looking for the castle.
So, for some reason I got delisted off of find, I'll put it back in again, you should be
able to find it.
I'm going to move the whole place today onto right in the middle of four plots, which
I've been able, thank you very much, Gabrielle, real for letting me buy your land.
So now I have enough to really, because you have all these limitations of how many
prims, what they call them, you can, you know, put on to a piece of land.
So if I'm covering four, then all four corners will count in a different land, then I
think you can actually combine all the land together.
So, uh, all I want is just to have more, more place to put stuff down, you know, so
we can have more fun.
What's up, baby?
I was listening.
And I thought, uh, I think you need to explain every time and over and over that you
are not talking about real life.
I said second life.
Oh, yeah, but do people know, maybe new listeners?
Hey.
Excuse me, this entertainment expert, okay, the hell is that?
Well, because you're talking about plots and buying plots and I think buying plots.
People who listen to the show either understand, you want to produce the fucking show?
No.
Okay, well, I appreciate it, but it's, that was, that would be like me coming in and saying,
I think you should do that and see instead of D, this is my art.
I don't care.
I just, I was curious.
Now I understand what you're saying, but I can't reintroduce every single time.
I'm not a topic that we discuss, but no, no, no, come back here, please.
And front of the microphone where people can hear you.
Yes.
I understand what you're saying, but first of all, people aren't stupid, don't underestimate
my listeners.
The figure, the, the, the, the, the whole thing, the, the whole thing, it's, not only
a second life, but when we talk about things, I don't go back and explain everything
all the time.
I mean, some things weren't re-explanation, but this has been on the cover of business
week.
People have heard about second life.
It's not, they're going to look for it.
That's how it works.
All right.
Okay.
If you ever wanted to disturb the man behind the curtain again.
Oh, you called me, too, in the middle of something, doesn't matter, does it?
No, no, but I'm, I'm, that's why we're married for 20 years this year.
Part of, but part of it is, if I go back into explaining what it is, I'm not explaining
what, saying real fast, oh, I'm going to talk about second life, what they call them virtual
worlds, I guess.
But there you go.
That's what I mean.
All right.
Yeah?
No?
Okay.
Bye-bye.
This is worse than the guy that Howard Stern had to deal with, who had to go WNBC.
I guess you stopped listening to me.
Diet, I don't know what I was saying.
Oh, I see how it is.
I go away for a week.
I'm locked out of Curry Castle.
This is Angie, just in case you forgot and see if you can any blow jobs from this avatar.
Angie, Angie, this is all a virtual world stuff we're talking about, of course.
Now, actually, I tried to find you because I'd love to have you be one of our first showcases
in the palace.
And I think I've got all the technology bits figured out, of course, what we need is a live,
I will not say a live live performance, but a live recording of a live performance or something
like that.
And I'm just messing around with all kinds of permissions and learning myself.
And you have only been in this virtual world for two weeks.
Don't get up, it's tough with me now.
Please.
Hi, Adam.
This is Franco from Rock-Cast detail.
I'm talking on behalf of all detailian podcasting community.
We really need pot show plus.
We are very annoyed by the lack of visibility that use music store deserves for independent
podcasts.
Here, in Italy, we have many, many very good podcasts, but none of them on the first page
of the eight-use music store.
And top 10 top 100 standings on it use are occupied only by foreign podcasts, especially
mainstream media, retransmitted as a podcast.
They are pod squatters, they are only two of the five-space squatters.
They are just to take visibility away from independent people doing good stuff.
But we want to succeed or to fail only based on our skills.
And we don't need this kind of bottlenecks.
We really hope pod show plus will give us some solution to this problem.
And we hope that there will be ways to select podcasts based on language and not only
by topic as the ITU's music stories.
Oh, one more thing.
If you're looking for some good foreign podcasting tunes before you go there, all right,
dude, here's what I want to do.
Because obviously the problem is we're all American ignorant Americans and ignorant
Brits for that matter.
But certainly when it comes to iTunes, we're just not good at thinking about global view,
I guess.
And that's for another yanks and a Brits some other time, but I'll make this deal with you.
If you put together a segment, make it, I don't know, five minutes or so.
And in English, introduce the different bits of your three favorite Italian podcasts.
And then actually put in a little piece of those, which of course will be an Italian,
it doesn't matter, you know, we'll get the idea, if you set it up properly, I'll put it
right in the pod finder, man, we'll put that on the homepage of iTunes, okay?
So that's the deal I make with you, my friend, my me go, whatever you say in Italy.
We have a lot of very good pod safe bands here in Italy.
One of my favorites is a skin that's Sierra Kilo in the November Gulf, and one of
their songs that's non-chapuniente is on the pod safe music network.
It would be a very good tune to play the cowbell on.
Okay Adam, that's all for now.
This is Franco or Castitalia Seninoff.
Franco, Franco, Rocastitalia, great man.
Well, of course I went to the pod safe music network, and I can just hear Chris Rockwell
cursing at me now because I already made the promise everything that goes up on the show
is made available for sale.
Like, I'm hoping we can do international artists by now as well, so dude, I'm taking
your advice.
Let's play it.
Next to me is Pasi Raston.
We have a lot of very good pod safe music network, and I can just hear Chris Rockwell
and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris
Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell
and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell
and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell
and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear
Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I
can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rock
Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can
just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris rockwell and I can just hear
Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell and I esta now but I wanna just hear Chris Rockwell and I can just hear Chris Rockwell again
to definitely cut me a five minute piece
and we'll put it in a pod finer, be a lot of fun.
And you got to give me the artwork
and the links and all that crap too
because it's in a hands-pod cast for iTunes only.
So we'll fight fire with fire, okay?
Don't tell them, and though.
All right, everybody, interesting Wednesday.
Good start today.
I'm early, so I can get all the other stuff done.
I want to get done today before San Francisco wakes up.
Got lots to do, got to book the tickets for our trip
and stuff.
And, oh, don't forget, if you're looking for a great deal
on domain name, go to godaddy.com, use promo code
dsc3 upon checkout and get your domain name
for $6.95, that's not it.
Was that five and a half euros these days?
It's lovely.
No, wait a minute.
Uh, yeah, this five and a half euros, I guess.
Something like that.
And of course, as always, I'll give you download.accu.com,
Heather and Janelle, still doing their show,
talking about, well, you know, chick stuff.
I'll see you tomorrow, everybody.
Adamaccurry.com, dailystoresco.com, take care.
Come on out, buy cash, Lester.
Yes, Lester.
Another pod show pod guest, stick it in your ear.
Get this pod guest and we're great ones like it
on the high performance pod cast of Liberty Network
from Podjo and limelight networks.
I love it.