This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want to hear content with AdAS domain name?
This show will give you a special code, get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie, three, six, six.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I've been sitting here for so long.
I've got the music, but I just ain't got some.
Go, I feel so dead and safe.
I can't attend, but I can't find out where I am.
I need a memory from this commodity.
Somebody tell me if I'm fine.
I really want to shine.
I don't think I'm fine.
I saw this dream on the night, so I can shine.
This is a cold, lonely time.
I keep on making up reasons why I just can't find the rhyme.
Oh, I know something's got to give.
Some found deep down inside of me.
That's been dying just a little.
Without feeling on my skin.
There ain't no way in hell I'm ever given in.
Because I really want to shine.
I really want to shine.
I think it's time to shine.
If I could only turn on the fire when I shine.
I'm sick and tired of holding out on me all the time.
I'm waiting for the day when I can't be the one to shine.
Because I really want to shine.
I really want to shine.
I'm waiting for the day when I can't be the one to shine.
But I really want to shine.
If I could only turn on the fire when I shine.
We got thirty knots wins, gusting.
Wish it was shining.
Kevin Reeves from his brand new CD, it's about time.
On the Charlie, daily source code, 366 coming to you from Curry Cottage in the affluence
suburb of Surrey, it's Gilford and yesterday, Kevin Reeves sent me his new budget, album
CD.
He sent it to me in a big zip file, wow, man, fantastic, really, really great stuff.
I don't know how much of this is going to be put up on the podcast, music network, but this whole
album is just fantastic and it's funny because he sent me this nice package and it has
a little thumbs data, but I don't know, can you just import this whole thing into iTunes and
will iTunes understand that it's an album and put the, I guess not, hold on, there's
liner notes in here, let's check it out, all the credits, okay, who else worked on this
slow, Sean Moremello, cool, my goodness, lots of cool people on this, Joe Bragg, Ian
Beard, you know what I'm missing, I'm missing lyrics, I, in fact, I miss, you know,
we've talked about that before, I miss just folding open that double album, you know,
and I'm just rub the seeds out and then, oh yes, beautiful, read the lyrics, read the
liner notes, it doesn't matter man, it's all good as CC would say, fantastic, music
going to play some more from that brand new album, a little bit later on in today's
source code, lots of great technology coming my way today, I'm feeling good, like really
good, first of all, I have to tell you that I'm getting up late this week and probably
through, I don't think Christina has to go back to school until Wednesday, so we're just
enjoying getting up around, I don't know, 930, we're still just a little bit messed up
from travel and even that one hour difference, even if you stay in a different country
in a different time zone for just just a day, it's, you can really, I should have kept
my sunglasses on as, as was suggested yesterday by Tom Scooting, I'm going to try that
out dude next time we go to San Francisco and the next time I believe we'll be somewhere
mid May or the third week of May, Patricia's going to go with me because there's a big
conference, actually there's two conferences we're going to, one I can't tell you about
because it's one to secrecy, but I think the 24th and the weekend of the 24th and 25th
of May, there's a cleaner, perkins CEO weekend, so all the CEOs and founders of companies
that they invested in get together and play golf, I guess, so it's a pebble beach, so
I'm pretty sure they're going to be playing golf, I don't think I will be, unless Patricia
and I get hooked up with the neighbors before then and are actually able to, you know,
to get around a couple of holes and not look too foolish, but that's going to be fun,
it's going to be a lot of fun, just the two of us in the sun, in the condo, hanging out.
So back to the technology, it's just, no, no, I'm going to hold off on a second, I'm
going to hold off on that for one moment. First, let's talk about the box, the best
of Charlie's, I wanted to thank everyone else who sent in best of Charlie's because
they were too many that were sent in to actually play in the amount of days that we
had, so we're saving them up and we'll definitely use them, should there be a future
date where, you know, sometimes right, I can't make a Monday work or something like that,
then I'll throw in a best of Charlie for sure and everyone who sent in a box will definitely
get some pod shows, swag, whatever t-shirts and crap we've got laying around, which isn't
a lot, but it's a thought that counts, right? And I was so convinced along with many other
people that it was PWFent and who had created that final best of Charlie number six,
the mystery mashup, but no, no, actually, how can we even be talking about PWFent without
having his jingle playing? I mean, come on, that's what this thing is made for, right?
Once again, he's going to set the record straight, he hit the sideline repairman.
Hey Adam, Uncle Jesse here, I am very flattered that you give me credit for being the
DSC mystery mashuper, but I've got to confess, it wasn't me. The actual creator of that
particular best of Charlie was afraid that it might be a little too mean towards the
pod father, so I kept that contributors identity a mystery. It would be wrong for me to
reveal the identity of the mystery mashuper. So as always, let's all get home safe and we'll
all meet back here real soon and talk about some more shit. So long, Adam, Uncle Jesse out.
All right, Uncle Jesse, go check the steel wheelie, make sure we still got some shine. Mark
Yosha, what a name cough and the Pacific Coast help players. That's responsible for that
mashup. I loved it. I really did. And Angie B heard the call. She's got something to say about
it all.
Why, no, Adam, I don't play the cello. Sorry to disappoint you. I used to play electric
guitar in a band though, so I'll try to find a picture to send you. Oh, hey, did you
happen to hear PW's latest perfect head? I did a little intro form and I think you'd
enjoy it. You should check it out. Say, if I send in regular, I'll tell you. I'll have
nothing to do with PW effect and then perfect head, Angie. I don't care what you've done
for him, okay?
It'll comments. Does that mean Jeff will make me seem song to? Hmm, what do you do?
Yeah, well, let's replay that. Hold on, let me just pull that back one second. And regular
audio comments, does that mean Jeff will make me a theme song to? Hmm, what do you do?
I don't know, Angie, but you're surely fishing. Jeff sent me a nice little note. He says
that indeed he's been hired by other people to create theme songs for him. So there you go.
More money flowing through podcasting, loving it, completely loving it. So Angie, there's
a surefire way to get something done is to contract Jeff. And otherwise you are completely
at his mercy. Such as I'm often at the mercy of this man, comic strip, comic strip, comic
strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip. Happy Easter, Adam Curry. 2006 we have, and it is a bit
hilarious. Happy Easter, all of us, of the SC, and with nights to NGP. Bad flu, spoiled
Easter eggs. And fronches till he valor, frog legs. Nukura weapons achieved Iran, of which
USA is not a big fan. The future looks scary. So we have here Adam Curry. At least
this little fucker, Easter bunny. He's copying with his eggs and his funny, fuckier,
a piece, Easter bunny. It's still funny. Wow, comic strip blogger. The poetic version.
Excellent. I just don't know what to say, CSB. You could really hook comic strip blogger
up by getting him a great domain name to point to his website, comic strip blog.com. You
can get that a go daddy. And I'll cost you $6.95. I think he uses code DSC3. There's three
different options you can use. DSC1, DSC2, DSA3. And that'll get you a discount in any case.
Maybe you register something cool and point that to CSB site. He's back though, isn't
my goodness. Okay, technology time. Let's talk about some cool stuff. First of all,
I found a link yesterday to something called humanclock.com. If you haven't seen this,
go to if you're in front of a screen right now, punch it up humanclock.com. What a great
idea. The concept is it's a community-based project where anyone can submit pictures of hours
and minutes of the day. So I haven't actually done the math, but you need to 24 and then
time 60, I guess. Okay, that just broke my brain. Can't figure that one out. But they have enough
of them so that when you pull this clock up, and it's basically a meta refresh. So the browser
just refreshes. It shows all different versions of the time. So if I look over now, I see a, I see
that it's 130 pm here in the condo. And the picture I'm seeing is from San Francisco, California.
A picture of a road with yellow letters that says speed bumps. And there's a little sign that
says one colon 30 and there's people walking by. And so now, and you actually see a little timeline
underneath, which represents the seconds. And so in one more second, it's going to refresh to
131. Let's see what the picture is now. Oh, cool. 131. It's kids building blocks where 131 is spelled out.
And that's from St. Claude, Minnesota. It's great. And I can already see a million different
widgets. I mean, I shoot. I would actually buy an alarm clock if if it had that built into it,
there would be so awesome. Check it out, humanclock.com. It's just another one of those awesome
ideas that we're putting together as we have the tools and the infrastructure available and
on all these cameras out there and just creative minds and creative ideas fantastic. So that was part
one of the technology happiness that met me today as I surf through Gmail part two was
that cast blasters now connected to the podcast delivery network. It's fucking this is so awesome.
Now, of course, this is all still in the close beta. So you can't actually see any of this
working yet, but you've been seeing the actual files working for quite a whole second. Is that
a bitch that's the satellite repairman saying where the hell is the show? Let me see.
No, cool. Okay, I'm going to tell you what that is in the second, too. Oh, there's three pieces
of technology to talk about today. So now with cast blaster, you enter your podshow podcast delivery
network credentials and then immediately recognizes that you have, in fact, I have two shows in
there. One is the upload for the daily source code. Another one is for something I call Charlie
Chat, which I'm really just using is a kind of a testing bed right now. So it scans your count.
It knows how many shows you have. You can select which show. And then all you do is just fill out
the stuff you were filling out anywhere. Your show notes, which, of course, are baked into the
MP3 file when you save it, when you save the file. And of course, you can still save it locally,
which is recommended. But then you hit upload and show notes, descriptions, everything's all shot
off to the pdn. The MP3 file is uploaded. Nice little status bar there. And you're done. That's it.
And even that, just a one small step, it makes such a difference in the production because
you know, it's like you used to have to, okay, save it. And then you'd upload it and then you'd have
to enter your show notes and copy paste. And it's going to save me at least 20 minutes if not more
on a daily basis. I'm so happy. Thank you, Mike. Thank you Andrew. Thank you Chris Rockwell.
Guys, great freaking job. Great job. And then the last piece of technology that just bug me
out today. I love it. It's Google Calendar. Last night, I received an email with a login
to Google Calendar. I think this came through Steve Gilmore. I'm not quite sure how it was Google
gesture is very, I have no idea how he got into the loop on this, but I really don't care because
this is what I've been waiting for. Almost as completed, Mike, my, my, my, already undying love
for what these guys are doing with email. Now to connect calendars into Google is just phenomenal.
It's, you know, of course, it's all Ajax. So, you know, there's no refreshing of pages.
Stuff just gets popped in. It understands natural language so you can say lunch tomorrow with Patricia
and it'll automatically, you know, know that that'll be noon tomorrow, or you could say at 3 p.m.
or you could say on Saturday or next week, you know, so it has some of that natural language
understanding of just want to enter something really quick. It can import your iCal calendars.
Also, anything with the iCal format. So, outlook and also apples, iCal, it understands that.
It can also do CSV files. It can export so that you can actually subscribe to it in other calendars.
I mean, it's, they did it right. Everything that is there. Excuse me, Sensei, which I am
consuming, as we speak. And it'll also notify you of events through text message to your phone.
And that's what just came through Google Calendar SMS verification. Please enter and then
there's a code as the verification code in the, okay, it didn't finish the whole message there.
So, one of what that's about. I was waiting for that to come in. I, I had already told it to
configure it last night. I guess that's, well, of course, it's bait and it's still busy. But so,
you know, now, whenever there's something going on, immediately, it'll send a message to my phone.
I hope at least it'll send it in the timely fashion. I'll test that out in the next couple of days.
And the only thing I need now is a mobile version of it. I've given you a mobile version and guys,
I would pay for this. And I'll just say one more time, please, please Google, please, let me buy more space.
I need more space. The idea is so, look, you can index my shit, you can search it,
you can give it to the, to the authorities. I have nothing to hide, but please give me more space.
So, I can port more shit on there. I'd really, really would appreciate it.
Technology, loving it today. I'm going to play a song for you, which I, I found in, but it was,
I think the most played yesterday on the podcast music network. And the reason I'm playing
is because during vacation, although we were completely, I was certainly very relaxed,
really unwind, pretty much unplugged from the net, except for some blackberry stuff. But,
you know, what can you do, right? That's what it's for to kind of sneak a peak once in a while.
But there was also really no mail coming in to speak of, because people kind of left me alone,
which is highly appreciated. But we were, you know, watching a movie, I'm trying to think
what the name of this movie would. I think we just can't like the tail end of it. And it
involved a scene where a father mother and daughter are being attacked by this crazy couple.
And they're being attacked in their house, and they've tied them up, and they've set them on fire,
and they break loose. And then, so, you know, so there, this crazy couple is trying to get the,
the kid, gosh, I wish I could remember the name of that movie. Christine has gone otherwise,
it asked her. She, she would know immediately. And then the, the husband
um, creeps up behind the mail of this, of this crazy couple, and waxing with a two by four.
And at that very moment, I said, oh, man. Oh, that would, that just, it almost felt good.
Which, of course, was kind of frightening, because what happened is I saw, it was,
so played so well. And the cinematography was done so perfectly. It was very, and we're talking,
like, half a second worth of, of film, really. But it just gave me, I was like, wow,
I would really like to just wax someone with a two by four. I really, it's in me,
which is kind of scary. And it was just, it's aggression that was like coming out and just,
on the verge, and Patricia Christina said, what do you mean? I said, well, there's just a couple
people that I would really like just to whack with, with a, with a piece of wood that would,
I, it would make me feel so good. Now, of course, I, I don't really intend on doing that,
but it did spur me on to, to actually play this song, which might help get some of it out of my
system. Matt Sumo, guys. So many ways to kill you.
I could be with switchblade, or I could use them shedding that, just break out the Terminator.
I can't catch up to you, yeah, I can't give you the rest of the course, just jamming me in your head.
Or I can wax you with the Oasis cheese, so I've covered in red. It's about to lead one more time.
If you want to be a long time, then anything, you're so mad. There's so many ways I can kill you.
Shut up, you shit, you're sitting in your left, because I don't want to hear you.
But if you don't just run out of love, there's so many ways I can kill you.
Yeah, well, I can clear you with a toy in your head, or I'll keep you with a sound.
Probably not the Hyundai, but I can still pick it up.
I can clear where they hit you run, or you're visually in country drive.
Run your down, and score it up. Your ass stuck under my four-wheel drive.
It's never gonna be one more time. If you want to feel the want to, then anything, you're so mad.
But there's so many ways I can kill you. Shut up, you shit, you're sitting in your left,
because I don't want to hear you run.
You don't just run out of love, and there's so many ways I can kill you.
That's the break, y'all.
Well, death, and destruction, score another hit on the wall.
When the jacks attacks the stacks, wax with an axe to print the backs of the black jack axe.
So many ways I can kill you.
So many ways you can die.
So many ways I'm gonna get you.
So let's just rip it up one more time.
Burn it up.
I'ma suck on it.
Shoot some manslaughter, shoot you stabbing.
Keep it to the assassination floor.
I'm gonna miss a girl, but I'm gonna strike the lynching to kill you.
Take this layer, and hit me, and wipe down with a mask.
Fix the ears, and some fucking speck.
Boys and excuses.
Just to do pop off, wax, but just get jess.
One more time, if you wanna feel the one, two, one.
Bad attitude, think you're so bad.
But there's so many ways I can kill you.
Shit, I'm a shit.
It's a little bit cause I don't wanna hit you.
And I, if you don't just run out of love,
yes, many ways I can kill you.
Mad sumo, from CC's neck of the roads, Massachusetts.
From his buy on the pod save music network.
When he's not drinking and womanizing, mad sumo,
delves into the rock blues and electronic genres
to deliver brilliant music you can dance to.
His music has been played in many podcasts and indie movies
across North America and now the world.
Oh, thanks to the pod's hit music network, very cool.
All right, of course, links to that in the show notes.
For those of you checking us out on serious satellite 102.
Today, right after this show, which is ending in just mere seconds,
we'll bring you Pacific Coast hell away,
followed by East Radio Don and Drew Gilmore Daily.
And if all goes according to plan a new digital flauntsum
from my very own Uncle Jesse side-light repair man,
PW Fenton, followed up by Michael Butler with the rock and roll.
I don't know if he does the rock and roll geek show tonight.
If he does the indie cast,
he does something just for the serious listeners, not too sure.
So that's what's coming up, and of course,
I'll be back here tomorrow to bring you the thank god
it's Friday edition of The Daily Source Code
on the serious stars 102.
We're by the way at the New York Auto Show this week with playboy bunnies.
Now see, there's a drawback to all that podcasting stuff.
Okay, they're gone. Just you and me now.
Tired of the FCC filling your head with tired-born,
fluently correct radio,
centered in the language of your host's,
and limiting what he can listen to,
try the unradio show.
We are un-centered, unpopular, and a lucky life just like you.
After all, you didn't move out of your mom's basement to listen to
popular radio, did you?
Hell no, stick it to the man in the FCC.
Listen to us.
It's really, what else have you got going for it?
I don't know if it's a David Graham door sitting in the window.
I'm looking for a work placement of a minimum of 40 weeks in a software development role
in the South of England, and I thought your listeners could help me out.
I'm studying the peating at Bournemouth University,
and one of the requirements of the third year
is to take a year's work placement.
I have an experience in a number of programming languages such as
C, Java, PHP, P, P, B, Oracle, SQL, and many more.
And I'm also familiar with software such as Windows 2000 Server, Linux,
Slawless Unix, Dreamweaver, and a David Photoshop.
If you are a listener, and your company has never employed a work placement student,
the main benefits are that we are cheap labour, as our students are used to being poor.
I want to start any time between July and September 2006,
and you can contact me at this RayCatch email address, d1169254 at Bournemouth.ac.uk
That's about B, O, U, R, and E, Mouth.
And I can send you a CV.
Thanks, Adam. Let's see if podcasting recruitment works.
Good bye.
Let's certainly work for us with some of our jobcasts.
And it's interesting because Christina said the other day said,
Dad, I also have to do a work placement.
Just to do it, I think in September or October,
which is what we in the States would call an internship,
and I'd say, well, once you come out to San Francisco for a week,
and being an intern at Pod Show.
And apparently, that's not allowed, or I'm not quite sure what the deal is.
So she's looking for something locally, and I said,
well, I really don't know anyone.
And the people who I do know, honestly, Christina, I don't know if I would want to recommend you,
because damn, you can be pretty lazy.
She's just, no, no, no, not for other people, only at home.
Is this a teenager talking or what?
So if you have any thoughts for work in my, my daughter, pretty hard,
I would definitely support it if you've got a gig for her somewhere in October,
also a word, and no pay necessary, obviously.
Well, you can give her a couple of shilings if you want to.
Well, I was going to say something else about that.
Oh, wait a minute.
Ooh, I just got, okay, Google tests notification starting at 1,400.
Yeah, so I just, while the, while the song was playing,
so many ways to kill you, I verified my email, I verified my email address,
or I verified my text number for the Google calendar notifications.
So it just popped up in the browser, which I've configured that way.
So what should happen next?
Wait a minute, that should probably happen in three more minutes,
because the official time is 142, I guess my blackberry off or my, one of the two is off.
Okay, so we'll see if that comes in, I'll just put the blackberry down there for a second.
Oh, I remember what I was going to say, lots of feedback, lots.
I mean, I must have received at least eight or nine different emails from UK podcast
or saying, yo dude, if you guys are coming, I'm going to do some pints and darts, count me in.
So I immediately shot off some email to Rosie at to HQ and she's going to set it up and get
it on a calendar. It's not going to be a big extravagant thing. I think we're just going to find a pub
somewhere where we can all just hang out and, hey, how about the old Vic? Maybe the old Vic is
available. I hope we can just crash out in the corner and just hang out and talk for a little bit,
but won't really have time for much else, but at least we can share some, some thoughts ideas
and some beers. I think that'll be just about perfect. Okay, I got, what is it?
Another two minutes. Okay, I'm going to play another piece of audio feedback from Shmey and then we'll see if
the Google notification came in on time.
Hey Adam, this is Shmey again from thenaudcast.com. I'm a 14 year old podcaster living in Oregon.
I've been loving podcasting so far. I sent me four audio comments recently. You played the
first one. Thank you so very, very much. I just wanted to call in. First of all, I couldn't
give a crap play this on the show. I really, really do want you to hear it though. So
this isn't a plea. I just being homeschooled. I have a decent amount of extra time on my hands,
more than a normal kid would, and I am honestly willing to put that time to our podcast.
Yeah, I already am, but I think the stuff that you guys are doing at Pod Show is so innovative and
so amazing. I'd really love to become a part of it. I'm also a musician. This is my music
playing. I have some stuff up on the PMN under Shmey, and I would, I would just love to help out.
So if there's anything I can do, if I could join the Pod Show family,
a little prematurely and help out with tests and all that great stuff, I'd really love to.
So please reply to this. Tell them what you think. And so far as I know, you don't have any
teen podcasts in the family. Do you love to be the first one? All right, Adam, hope you're having
a great time and Portugal. You can find mine at my podcast, TheNodcast.com. I continue to love
the Charlie, and I'll see you later. Bye. Yo, Shmey, the interesting thing you said that you're
homeschooled. I'd love to hear more about that. And sure, we can definitely talk about
about the U.S. team podcaster on the network. We've actually talked to a couple of them,
but it's kind of tough because we really need to have your parents consent. And so we need to
actually talk to them on the phone and make sure everything's cool. We've had some cases where
it was suggested. Well, you know what, one just call my mom on Skype. Yeah, here's our Skype
name. Yeah, right. Like we're really going to talk to your mom or your dad. But Shmey,
yeah, send me an email and I'll pass it on to Richard Brewer. Hey, and let me know about
that homeschooling stuff. I'm very interested in how long have you been homeschooled, how old are
you, how does it work, and how much time are you allowed to do podcasting every single day?
Just how do your parents manage that? Maybe we should get your mom on. Or is that
incredible? No, no, how have I made it incredibly lame all the sudden? I'm not suggesting that.
Maybe not such a good idea. Like very time now, 146. Okay, so this is not working the way I'd
expected it. So I should have received a notification from the Google Calendar by now. See,
this is the thing, you know, if you want to rely on this stuff, it's really, it's really got
I think I had the notification set to go 15 minutes before the actual event. So maybe the
text messages are sent on a different schedule, but we'll just keep that there. Well, it was at the
end of the show for today anyway, but one more interesting piece that came in. Adam, I hope you've
enjoyed your vacation. I've certainly enjoyed listening to the box sets that were available while
you were gone. Reason I'm talking to you today is I have been spending the last few hours
preparing the company I work for is television Emmy nominations that for our particular region are
doing a month here. Yes, I work for a large media conglomerate. But as I was going through the
National Academy of Television, Arts and Sciences webpage, I noticed that they had just released
the nominations for what they call first Emmy Award for internet cell phones and iPods.
So I quickly went and looked at the list of the nominees and they were filled with content produced
by Fox Mobile Entertainment, America Online MTV. Where's Tiki Bar TV? Where is Geek Brief TV? Did we
not know about these? Did you know they were giving Emmy's a way for iPod video? Or is this just
yet another way for big television, big media conglomerates to pat themselves on the back for how
well they have embraced podcasting and the iPod revolution? Well, that's a very good question.
I think that you have to be a member of the Academy to actually be recognized. And I'll look
that up. It may not be very hard to become a member of the Academy. There may be some dues,
but I think it's pretty much a club. And that's how it works with clubs. You have to be a
member to be considered. But if it's not too hard to join, I'm pretty sure next year we'll see some
some user-generated nominees. I sit in a about a weekly staff meeting here from our big company where
they're discussing how are we going to get on board with podcasting? How are we going to provide
our content to iPods in video? And I started a podcast about a year ago when my wife and I were
planning our wedding, called the Countdown to Chaos podcast, that I carried on for
approximately until you were married. Dude, I remember that one. We 25 or so episodes kind of through
our wedding planning. So I got to know a little bit about podcasting. Not nearly as much as you do
of course, but I sit in these meetings and even though we're a large corporation, we've got some good
content, I think, especially in the video realm. And I'm excited just to get the stuff out there.
I'm ready to go back to my desk and start ripping stuff and starting coding it and getting it
up on the internet for people to download. And just at the corporate level, it takes months and months
of research. And how can we do this? And what are the legalities of that? And can we show this out of
this market? And et cetera, et cetera. And so it's very frustrating to want to be in there and
kind of know what it's like to be at the ground level and just sort of be hamstrung by the fact
that I've got a big corporation. It's kind of driving the boat here. So very envious of you guys
out there at Pod Show. I think you're doing a great job and don't get yourself so big that it takes
meeting upon countless meeting and committee to vote on everything you want to do.
I keep it the great work. Thanks very much and I'll keep listening.
No, thank you very much. And when you think we're big enough, and hopefully not too big,
because I agree with you there. But that's not really, I mean, I'm sure that your company can do
stuff pretty quickly when it's in your own company's field of expertise. So it's just, you know,
fear uncertainty, doubt, stuff like that that always makes it tough. No one wants to get crushed
for making the wrong decision. And boy, our lot of decisions being made these days. I look at
Disney ABC. That's going to be pretty cool. I wonder if they're going to, if Disney ABC is going to
limit access the way it currently works in iTunes. And I have a US iTunes account. So I'm able to
download lost and pay for it, of course, and watch it. I caught up on two episodes just the other
day. But anyway, when you think we're ready for you, you know, ping me. It sounds like you got some
skills we could choose in our media company. Most excellent. Okay, looking at the human clock now,
I see 1553 degrees Fahrenheit, coolant temperature, which means it's 153. And now,
oh, that's interesting. Oh, this is the wrong one. Somehow they got the wrong one in there.
It says 134. That should be 154. Oops. They mislabeled a picture there from Canada. Oh, well.
And not always 100% fantastic here at the cottage. Yesterday I spoke to my mom. She had another
checkup yesterday. For those of you who've been listening to the Charlie for a while, you know that
she was diagnosed with lung cancer. Almost a year and a half ago and had one long removed. And
it has been doing quite fine and then a tumor popped up in her side and had that removed and it
came back and she's had chemo and she's had radiation. And she's really just trying to regain a lot of her
strength. And yesterday they did a test. I think it's an echo. I believe it is. And they saw some kind of
anomaly on her remaining lung. So that means there's going to be a new scan, which will be done
in two weeks time in the meantime to help her regain her strength even quicker. She's going to have
a blood transfusion tomorrow. She's in great spirits. I have to say she's she's fighting this all the
way. And she's promised me she's coming flying with me in a couple weeks. So that might be the
death of her. But she's great. And I wanted to play a song for her. One that is on Kevin Reeves
knew album and it just it was so fitting. I figured that yeah. And she has that great new bronze
top as she calls it with Wi-Fi. So while she's down stairs in the living room and she doesn't have to
walk upstairs to go check stuff out. I'll send her the link to the show so she can then hear the song
as well. Again from Kevin Reeves. It's his mother on the daily source code. I have been down.
Like my lives came in. And I can't seem to find the lives about. And I've lost my direction again.
And I'm feeling lonely at the end of the day. I know that my son is phone call the way.
Because it's here. Mother, it's my way. It's so when it's been sleeping and it's here.
Mother, take my broken heart in your safe. You. And I'll trip to wait. Nothing more can I say.
When I love you.
Here I go. Here I go. I am making a sound that came for me. But I know that I can take
my broken heart in your safe. You. And I'm feeling lonely at the end of the day.
Tell me the name. Don't kill up the fight.
Mother, it's my way. It's so when it's been sleeping and it's here.
Mother, it's my broken heart in your safe. You. And I'll trip to wait. Nothing more can I say.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Do you see a nice creamy sauce over this because of this morning? Is this a reward?
Oh, this is a sort of yeah, and you're too skinny for my taste. Oh, you're too skinny for my taste.
That's for my feeding you. Really, thank you. That's a lot of energy.
And the presentation with nice little rugal assailant there.
The silver spoon silver fork, I'll put it right over here. Oops.
I already got some cocktail sauce on my mic cable.
Thank you, honey.
Okay.
We're done with the show anyway, sir. Yes, but messy.
Thanks, baby. Love you.
Oh, my life sucks, huh?
Okay. Tomorrow we'll do more. We'll do a thank God, it's Friday.
Send me any pod save music songs that you think will be good for the for the celebratory festivities.
Manjana and portions of today's podcast were brought to you by Earthlink.
A little secret.
If you send email to adamaccurry.com, it goes through an Earthlink account.
It gets forward to an Earthlink account because I love their spam filter.
And then it gets forward to my Gmail account, who of course have another spam filter on top of that spam filter.
So it's getting better.
Maybe I should put one more in the chain and I'll really have everything I'm looking for.
And also portions brought to you by.
I'll give you, check out Heather and John L's podcast at download.acview.com.
That's ACU VUE.
Alpha Charity Uniform Victor Uniform Echo.
And thanks to once again to Mike and Andrew and Chris for us.
Because I'm going to be uploading this show for the first time directly to the PDN and I'm loving it.
See you tomorrow everybody.
Bye-bye.
Another Pod Show Podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it.
On the High Performance Podcast delivery network from Pod Show and Limelight Networks.
I love it.