This is Soccer Girl. I just listened to the first episode of Shadow Falls and it's scared me
crapless.
This podcast is brought to you by Potcho and GoDaddy. Want killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Daily source code episode 435.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Hello, I am Carrey. Thanks for playing Liberty Jones on your podcast Daily source code.
Heavenly Liberty Jones works in the shop that she owns.
Lessons to music like swing. When there's no customer's in,
just because she don't like to drive. Take the sea as step by.
And these are thoughts on the sides to the river at night.
Turn my face.
This is the old something why don't you come for me. Take me away from my face.
She's got a dream to arrive.
And this name wouldn't lie.
If things are lonely, desire.
This is the worst of fate why don't you come for me to tell me your way.
Keep the lines.
Please let your so far. I wish you would buy. We could go buy back to my place.
Please let your so free. Why don't you come for me. Take me away from the place.
I'll give some joy. When the face of life is so true,
she won't dream that I know.
Heavenly Liberty Jones, Heavenly Liberty Jones,
Heavenly Liberty Jones works in the shop that she owns.
I could play that song 10 times a day. Particularly now, I've a customized intro to it.
Love it. The shakes, Liberty Jones, you can find on the pot set music network.
Hey everybody, it's Friday. Welcome to the daily source code coming to you from Curry Cottage
in the affluent suburb of Surrey in Guilford in the United Kingdom.
No lady Patricia today because today it's all music promos and crap you've called in.
Hi Adam. I'm Kate Alyson from the UK. We all know the association you've generated between
the birth and the sensei. I'm wondering if you've got some other associations going on that you haven't
told us about. I asked because I got a bit behind listening to the Charlie. I know I'm awful.
But I'll listen to four episodes yesterday and I think you've got a subliminal message
going on in your dozzet times. So I had a very, very hot dream about you last night. You know what
I'm going to ask for Adam, naked pictures. Okay, that's it. Apart from you today, I'm a folder.
Hi Adam. She dreams hot of me and she's a folder. It doesn't get any better than that.
Oh yes, of course. I'll send you naked pictures. Do you send me some of your first?
Huh? Don't send them to Adamaccurry.com. That crap's not working anymore. Adam and pod show.com.
I have so much just to run through. That's what I'm Jewish and I talked about this morning. I
was saying, you know, why would we just do a show together on Monday? And let me just run through
everything. I must have, you know, 30 different things I want people to hear and it's promos. It's a
cool music. People are sent in and it's Friday. So we shouldn't have to think too much. I promoted
on Curry.com yesterday. I blogged about my sister and her husband in Italy. They're now producing
movies, a little mini movies with her kids in Italian with English subtitles. You can find that
at minimovies.podshow.com is totally cool. The first one is Robin Hood. It's very, very cute. Please
have a look at that. Pod show garage is now officially launched at garage or garage.podshow.com.
I'm just reading the legends. So you know what it's about. Welcome to the pod show garage.
Here, the pod show mechanics. We're posting updates, bugs, fixes, tips, tricks and solving
problems from podcasters and listeners in regard to the pod show plus website. Have a question
posted comment below or send us an email. We'll find the answer for you. And you can also
subscribe to their to their weblog garage or garage.podshow.com fantastic resource. I have a feeling
podshow Joe is behind that. A couple of people sent me this about Wikipedia. And I'm not going to
play the whole clip. This must be old actually. I thought I saw most in the past three weeks.
I saw just about every Cold Bear report that the show that comes on after the daily show with John
Stewart and he's talking about Wikipedia. Let me just play a little clip here. All right. I got an
angry email from some nut job in Oregon today. Apparently the city of Portland does not put
hashish in their baby formula. My mistake. All right. Oh, opening my while crafting my scorching
reply. I forgot whether I usually call Oregon California's Canada or Washington's Mexico.
So I went to the internet and cyclopedia Wikipedia to check their extensive entry on this show.
I love Wikipedia. Any site that's got a longer entry on truthiness than on Lutherans has its
priorities straight. Anyway, turns out I called Oregon both California's Canada
and he's coming to a point here. He's coming to a point here. Washington's Mexico. But thinking
about it now, that's giving Oregon too much credit. They're more like Idaho's Portugal.
So what I am going to do, he pulls out a laptop. I'm going to just log on to Wikipedia here
and I am going to change it. You see, any user can change any entry. And if enough other users
agree with them, it becomes true. No big laugh. No big laugh from the crowd because I don't think
they quite understood it. But that is exactly what's happening. Whenever a whole bunch of people stand
around something that's then it becomes true on the internet. I've seen this time and time again.
And there's this whole, I was in Wikimedia conference going on. I think it's in Boston.
I'm pretty sure it's in Boston. And I believe that they will come to the conclusion at the end of
the day for anything to be reliable. Really, I think I really do believe you have to have
some kind of editorial that becomes believable. It just doesn't seem to work when it's
done in a social manner. It always results in the flame in a flame war. Nothing else ever really
comes of it, unfortunately. Hey Adam Curry. I think I dial the wrong number a second ago,
but I am your new biggest fan. And I'm just interested in that contest for a try and
need an iPod. And that's so cool that you're given in one since you started the contest. But
Godfather, please help me. I registered and I don't know where to post the URL of the one that I
registered. Because the name of the website that registered can hopefully to win is www.do not
get a iPod off of eBay or Google win one from Adam Curry. And the whole little joke about that is
when you go that would say, I'll pull up one of those banner ads that is just a scam that says,
oh, win an iPod or whatever. So love a show, keep it up and I'm a scruncher and I think I'm not sure
my arms will hold it, but I don't want to find out. I think you should find out. I need to know if
this is a hereditary or not. Apparently not. If I listen to you, if your mom's a scruncher,
you're a folder or vice versa, what was your dad? We've got to know these things. This is important
and remember, it is for science. So I started checking early this morning. I know I promised I
would announce the winner of the tronydsnipod.com contest today. Very simple contest. If you're
just tuning in, Troy started with tronydsnipod.com. And I kind of like the whole concept and
asked listeners to go ahead and register the most creative, most interesting, most funny, etc.
URL. And of course, extra points for what it actually points to for what the URL, what domain
pops up when you type in that URL. And I didn't get through them all today. So you have
a whole weekend now to finish posting a daily source code.com because I have to check every single
one and see if it's actually real. A lot of people put it as Troy had already warned me. A lot of
people put in entries that aren't actually registered, the just ideas. Well, the whole point is you
kind of have to register. It doesn't have to be with GoDaddy using checkout code DSC3. You could
probably go over to earth Lincoln figured out there or to any ISP or any domain register. I really
don't care. I really don't care, but you have to have it registered. And so I guess Monday,
when the lady Patricia's back on the show, we will bring you the winner of the iPod in the
tronydsnipod.com contest. Voidware prohibited by law. And I'm the final judge, right?
Mark need day and night.
Here is the room with your hair a little. There's a tiny problem about the usual.
It's about Mark. Yoshi knows he wants his face. He said he's labelled as cast.
He can't read his without his age writers. Mark need day and writers. He's a bad
he does with a pathetic show. Sticking up serious radio. He's getting obsessed with
give them the girl who do a daily show. That kicks ass without the help of a writer.
Eight fucking writers. Mark need day and night.
Mark need day and night.
Mark need day and night. Mark need day and night. Mark need day and night. Mark need day and night.
Mark need day and night. Mark need day and night. Mark need day and night. Sometimes there's a
And I'm going to need a broveskeet.
And I'm going to need a broveskeet, but the hell is a broveskeet?
That's heard that one, who wears this?
And I'm going to need a broveskeet.
I have no idea what you're saying there.
I thought the thought was, although not pod save very amusing.
And if Mark needs eight riders, then I'll get him six more.
Having this Saturday, August 5th on the Ed's Mix Bad Podcast.
A very special episode indeed.
The story is behind some of her early music as told by the rock goddess herself.
So fear, Ramos.
Hi, this is your host Ed Ovet, and I'm psyched.
It is an honor to invite you to come along for the ride, as we explore together some
of Sophia's life's story.
Sophia has especially prepared the audio content in this show exclusively for the Ed's Mix Bad
Podcast.
So how cool is that?
Don't miss a single word of this multi-talented artist as I present her majesty, Sophia Ramos,
coming to a podcast you're near you on Saturday, August 5th, 2006.
On episode number 44 of Ed, Mix Bad.
Hello, I've been Roger here, I was just leaving you a message to ask if you want to
any help next time you go flying, now don't have any experience with flying a plane, but
I did it to drive a car once until I crashed it, but I'm sure it's not easy in the sky,
there's not so many people to run over, I'm sure if you want to say some of your drugs
to 10,000 C, I can hold you a shaft straight while you get your morphine out, you want
to join Richard Branson or Buddy Harley, the big bop her as well, big names, the societic
with celebrity aviation, and just let me know which day you're free, and I'll come up with
you.
Roger, so good to hear from you dear, maybe we should forego that trip, I'm not quite sure
I like the company you suggest we should be here.
Adam, this is Peter from Suffolk and Cool, yeah you heard it right, Suffolk and Cool.
When I started my shows six months ago to play in a collecting mix of only the finest
new music, I took a pride in listening to each and every one of the 50 or so new tunes
coming on to the PMN every week.
Life was good, we even met up for beer and darts at the brick layers arms, I would have
him to the draft, you and Ron and Chris seem such good eggs despite your odd colonial
accents, not from Patricia seemed even better eggs, then there was talk of giving up
the day job, ah happy days.
That was then, this is now, I'm still panning through the new tunes to find the very
finest gems to pop discreetly into the years of the Suffolk and Cool listeners, but
man am I getting tired and techy, with over 400 new tunes on the PMN since last week's
show, where am I supposed to sleep?
I never seen my family, the cats won't speak to me, and I've given up the day job because
I've just no time to do it.
So please, musicians, can they break, are just controlling yourselves, you're driving me crazy?
The only seller I can find is listening to great music, which is all on the pubslave music
work.
Yeah, I didn't have a thought about that as I heard your comment, I think it's almost
time we set up some streaming servers, I think it would make a lot of sense to create
a couple of streams that you can just listen to, and this may be for people who are producing
podcasts, well, it could also be for people who want to discover new music, but what if
we had just a continuous stream of the new songs that come into the podcast music networks?
So maybe there's, I don't know, let's see, maybe 30 or 40 songs in rotation, and whenever
new one comes in, the oldest one drops out and just continues that way.
So if you kind of left that on during the day, in the background, you might actually hear
something you like, or we could do it by genre, but I agree, there's no way you can
log in anymore every morning and just listen to all the songs that there's just too much
coming in, which of course is, you know, why you might want to go take a look at songs
that are getting the most pod play, click on the shows that have played those songs,
because there's a high likelihood that they'll have more songs in there that you like,
and on each song, you can see which other shows played those songs.
This goes for producers of podcasts as well as for listeners.
So once we get that all integrated into pod show plus, it'll be even cooler when you can
actually have an identity as a band in pod show plus or as a label, or check this one out,
how about as a venue?
Hi Adam, this is Gus Koveta from a betterdaymedia.com, and to MiamiPodcast.com.
You know, I was sitting here, finally getting a chance to catch up on some of your recent
episodes from the daily source code, and I started thinking as I was looking at your
picture on iTunes, man, this guy needs to get some sun.
He says, why does it go?
Hey, I figured, you know what, he spends most of his time either in the UK, which is not
the sunnyest place in the world, or in Northern California.
So I thought since he probably don't have time to get away and get yourself some sun,
maybe I should bring a little sunshine to you.
So why don't you sit back, pop open a cool one, put on some sunglasses, and click on over
to my new show called the MiamiPodcast.
Basically every week, I'll bring you the latest information on what's happening here in
the Magic City, and who's it happening to.
Also, every week, I'll feature some great pot-safe music by both local and international
artists.
So if you can't get down here for your tan, listen to our show at the MiamiPodcast.com,
and I'll try to make you feel as if you were here.
So for now, Adam, child, and keep up the good work, man.
And folder, scruncher, see, almost the perfect audio comment, close, very, very close.
Oh, to New York City now, the David E. Polito, known as the, that guitar in the central
park, dude, man, person.
But you don't think he's overpaid, but you're at the profits with 36 billion, so when
you retire, you give him 400 million co-hexons.
You've been raining the public routine, because you have what they need on, so you pay
your success, so I'm seeing you, you're the portrait of Grito at some.
I've seen you on CNN, I've never seen such oily men, double-talking world, and think
it suffices, make funny excuses, both these record prices, you know the truth you
cannot sell, the same reason my dog licks himself, you say you said prices on supply and
demand, but let's just be honest, you do cause you can't away some, when you merge
you became an example, and you double the way, oh, it's on, you could drift into warming,
that's global, clashes melting away, oh, it's on.
The bucket once makes sense, but now something's off, it's since your secret meetings,
it takes chains on, but so it's on, you just take and you take and keep taking, and your
concern is a scam, oh, it's on, it's so clear, but look for a bit of your making, that you
don't give a care more, it's on, getting rich on the back of this nation, and double
your home, it's on, he bought screwing the next generation, I say screwing, oh, yes, he's the
guy who plays this guitar in Central Park, he's got a podcast, he's got tons of songs of
the pot-set music network, his name is David E. Polito, links to him of course in today's
show notes at dailysourcecode.com, awesome dude, although of course I have to disagree with you,
just to take an unpopular stance, yeah, you see those big profits, the oil companies are
making, what you probably will see in the next five years is huge investments, and it'll
come from those profits, those profits don't go all, don't all go directly to shareholders,
it's not all paid out in dividends, there's a huge reinvestment, I know personally at this
juncture of two different oil refineries that are being built, and they're not being built
by one oil company but by several because the cost is about $8 billion per refinery because
now they're doing a liquid, liquid to petroleum refining, this is the way it's going to go until
until there is no more until of course we have sucked the earth dry and that's not the oil
companies fault, that's our fault, it's everyone's fault, new, for not using alternative means of
energy. If you're on serious right now, you'd like to talk some more about that top shit,
you'll have to download the rest of the show at dailysourcecode.com, coming up in the pod show,
though, on serious specific coastal way, Dawn and Drew, in over your head, which you talk
rather for the scenes in yeast radio and other Scottsigler extravagans into wind up your Friday
evening. Bye, they're gone, I mean that though, I mean that about the oil companies, yeah,
sure it's a bummer, we're paying a lot of money, now to fill up our gas-guzzling machines, which
you know, I've taken my own personal steps, I'm driving Trinity, I'm filling it up with
vegetable oil, which is not cheap, by the way, it's more expensive than regular diesel,
significantly more expensive, but at least I'm not paying an oil company, so I could make it myself
if I wanted to, so that's up to me and that's up to you as well. Believe me, these oil companies,
all these big profits, it's not necessarily like they're all going into a couple of people's pockets
because the reinvestments will come and they haven't been huge cash cows, all their existence,
that also is not true. So, what it's fun, you know, it's fun to have someone to yell at
when you can barely afford to a Philip de Homme! Hello Adam, and all my fellow Charlie Ice,
I'm Mike Pico, voice of Scotty Oz and the Children of the Gods podcast. I still have a day job,
and at my day job, I have a great guy who does some part-time work for us. He, along with his fellow
team members, we're currently training to participate in the Orlando Triathlon on September 24th
as representatives of the leukemia and lymphoma society, and their mission to cure leukemia and
phoma, by Loma, and Hodgkin's lymphoma. Eric, that's the name, is doing this in part because
cancer has stricken very close to him recently. I won't go into details here, but please go to
www.helpaskyourcancer.com and make a donation to help Eric and his team get this event.
I told Eric that I was sending this to you and Adam, he said that voicemail updates were a
phone or are not out of question. We've seen podcasts and do a lot of good for good causes in the past.
I think we still have another one in us. I think we can do it again. One last thing, if I haven't
sold you on a yet, I'll leave you with this. If you don't get cancer yourself, then chances are
someone so close to you will that it will be devastating. Please help www.helpaskyourcancer.com
I were definitely going to cure cancer. I'm sure of that. I don't think my daughter
when she's mature. I don't think she'll have all the same problems that we have here.
And of course, anyway, we can help happy to do it. Oh man, since my mom passed away,
I've had so many different offers of, you know, to join boards of directors and stuff.
I think that probably the best way I can help is just by giving it exposure. Of course,
it's not just cancer. It's all kinds of stuff. But we're getting close to solving a lot of these
things. Research is going very, very fast. And I have good hopes. I really do. I think that
in 20 years we'll have cancer like no, no, not about it. Hi Adam. It's Ralph, with a comment about
jig and the skewing of story stories. Oh yeah, let me explain this one for a second.
This actually goes back to what I said at the beginning of the show about Wikipedia.
So Jason Calacanis, who you probably, well, if you're in the blogger's career,
Potter's career, then you might have heard of him if not, then you probably don't know who he is.
But he started web, I look, I've known him for a long time. He was at Silicon Valley in New York
in the bubble days. And even pre-bubble days. He's been around for a long time. And I consider
him a good acquaintance. He, um, so he started weblogging and then he sold that to AOL. And now he,
I'll just, I'll popularize what people are saying. He's recreating dig at netscape.com. Whether you
think that's true or not is irrelevant, that's just the easiest way to explain what he's doing.
If you don't know what dig.com is, you have to go to digg.com to understand. It's kind of a social
bookmarking site. So there's a community there and they dig stories and articles and the ones that
the most people dig rise to the top. And of course, they get a lot of attention. And that spreads
out throughout the network effect that these stories can get. You know, they show up in email
and you're aggregator all over the place. And Jason's plan, which I think is a very interesting one,
is to hire people to really start seeding these stories. Let's call, he calls them navigators,
I think, so kind of like editors. Exactly what I said, I believe you do need in any social scenario.
Well, I mean, even here take blogger con as an example, the uncomference, even blogger con has
discussion leaders. Now, it's very hard to emulate a discussion leader on a website other than
having giving that person moderating tools. So they can shut someone up, i.e. do not give the
microphone away, which is a big rule of these uncomferences now, so that someone can't hog the
microphone except for this discussion leader. So I think it makes a lot of sense that you have people
who moderate these conversations. Now, there are of course also marketing companies out there who
are paying people to go and spike stories that are about their companies to get those rise to the top.
This is exactly what I said. This is what happens in any free open system where there's no
penalty from its behaving. We actually run our own technology news website aimed at the Irish market.
It's www.electricnews.net.inn.ie. I have to say I have some concerns about companies
paying to get legitimate news stories pumped up in these social networks. I think it can be
a terrible way of skewing what's news and what's not news. It's that challenge about trying to
ascertain what is a genuine news story that stands up on its own merits and what this essentially
being pumped primed and is essentially nothing more than a editorial for a company that has a
little mention somewhere and then gets pumped up to a level that's way beyond its merit.
I think it's wrong, but I'm not entirely sure what you would do to stop it. I'd be interested
with other listeners have views on how you would be able to actually prevent social networks
like dig from being skewed like that. I can't see any easy way around it. That's why I thought
it's always a folder. I think it's very much real. I think their own really only is one solution.
You have to have editors and maybe that's where it all boils back down to weblog. Someone who is
providing links on a weblog. Robert Skobel for the techies is a good example of that. I read
scripting news every day. You don't have to agree with or like the editor, but I think that's
kind of what you're looking for is you find a person that you think is trustworthy for whatever
reason or even if you know they're not trustworthy for whatever reason or you know they have secondary
agendas. Maybe we should be concentrating on a Wikipedia like open forum about editors.
Well, of course, that would be a weblog about weblogs about weblogs. So really, when it all comes
down to its social bookmarking sites, really cool idea, but humanity just doesn't work that way.
Sorry to say. Okay, getting you ready for some cool stuff to listen to over the weekend.
The strip podcast, which you can find at the strip.podshow.com or I think it's the strip.com as
well. Why don't I know these things? Link in the show notes, of course. They are members of the
Podshow podcast network. We got so many now. I got to have my cheat sheets. Actually, I found out
about this through a press release through one of our own press releases. They've got a fantastic
show that you have to listen to this weekend. I think they already have a new show in the works,
but you got to listen to this week on the strip. She took off like a rocket. Her first two albums
producing eight top 10 hits, winning five Grammys, and selling a combined 15 million copies.
But Tony Braxton's recent career has been less than stellar, so she's looking for a return
to prominence by settling down for a long-term headlining gig at the Flamingo.
See, it's chat with a sexy shunt who's coming up. Then we review the Red Rock resort in casino.
Alright, so you got to listen to this with Tony Braxton. You want to hear someone who got
completely screwed by the record business, and literally for her multi-million selling album
wound up with $2,000 in her pocket. And memories of a lot of great limo rides,
plain rides, hotels, and studio recording sessions. But you might want to check it out at
the strippodcast.com. So I know it was sent to me via email. Some of the checkout from the label
no less, but it is on the podcast using that word.
I met Ronel Tray coming home from a top I know she hates it and I said, it's used
my favorite to your half-time. I believe I made it. She said, six o'clock, but if I was you,
I wouldn't worry about that. Because in this life, there ain't no turning back.
Cause nothing less forever. So let's keep it real. Let's make a most of everything that we've
built. It's after such a change. No, there's a way. I know you can't say, but hey, I'm glad
it's okay. And just like sitting down watching the way. It's so much more I want to say.
But want us to grow. I don't want to say, hey, I'll see you around. But that's just the way
it is sometimes sometimes you get laid down. Cause nothing less forever. So let's keep it real.
Let's make a most of everything that we've built. It's after such a change. No, there's a way.
I know you can't say, but hey, I'm glad it's okay. And just like sitting down watching the way.
There's so much more I want to say. And let's remember watching the way.
Ooh. Oh oh, oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh, let it take. She's walking away. Nothing less forever.
So let's keep it real. Let's make a most of everything that we've built. It's after such a change.
No, there's a way, I know you can't stay, but hey, I'm glad it's okay
And just like sitting down watching away
There's so much more I want to say
Nothing's in store, nothing is real
Do what you want, do what you feel
I pick up the phone, but there's not a sound
It's something to hear, got my feet on the ground
And just like sitting down watching away
There's so much more I don't want to say
Nothing's in store, nothing is real
Pretty cool, huh?
Rich Kronen, find him on the podcast and music network
Links in today's show notes at dailysourceco.com
Nothing lasts forever
I like that song
I've been asking you to call in and introduce yourselves
As listeners of the Daily Source Code
I've got quite a bundle now, and I want you to keep doing that
Because when we start up next week is listener of the day
Yes, listener of the day, and you'll get a pod show
I think I'm on the show t-shirt
So I want to send one out every single day
And just by highlighting one listener
So call in to our voice mail number and tell us who you are
How old you are, what you do, where you're from
And of course most importantly, if you're a scruncher or a folder
So we can keep telling you of that
So yeah, I'm learning about you guys
And already I know that the audience is all over the map
It's phenomenal
I'm not going to play any of those today
I have a couple more comments that came into the voice mail line
Which you can reach out
Go ahead, get a pen
Get it, just open up a little note pad thingy
Or a sticky note if you're on a Mac
Or if you have your mobile phone
Enter this number and you can save it in a second
Plus one
And just put in there
I don't, you know, a DSC comment line or something like that
Just save it into your phone
And whenever you hear anything on the show
You can just pick up your phone and call right away and respond
You don't have to wait until your
Back at home or back at the office or a near computer
Or you don't have to send in a complete voice mail comment
You don't have to record anything with any
Cast Blaster stuff you can just do it straight
Straight from your phone
And we also have a number in London
2076813753
Dude, I left your message on the other
Another number
And it's pretty quick, though
I just have to say that it's stopping at this cruncher's man
We just don't want to get shit on our hands later
Dude, I've never said I hated scrunchers
Some of my best friends are scrunchers
Hi Adam, it's Neil Ford from the UK
Just calling regarding the Gmail hack that you discussed on
Or 33
The trick with adding the kind of sub email
Is not so much that it will automatically get filtered into your spam
That's that you can actually write filters based on specific email addresses
So in your example that you could have a filter that added a label or whatever
But it also means that if you start to receive spam
And one of these sub addresses
You know who stole your email address
Or where it's been
Scratchful
So it's going to use it in that way
If you sign up for something and you put the class whatever in
Then if you start to receive spam
You know that that site may very well have sold your address
In which case you may not wish to deal with the new future
So that's really what I think the previous comment was about
So I think that helps my view to find it a bit better
Take care, I'll end the scruncher
Roger was waiting for it
Great Neil, thank you
Yeah, no, I didn't do a very good job of explaining that I agree
I just think it's kind of cool that Gmail actually accepts the anything you
You can modify the email address and it still comes into your regular Gmail
I thought that was really the cool part about it
And of course from there you can set up filters or no
Basically track back what's been happening with your email
But I tell you man, my email has been out there so long and so many places
That is published that I'll never ever get away from it at curry.com
So again out of it podshow.com
It's probably the most reliable place to get hold of me
I am still south here calling from some of the new places
Welcome back to the UK
Thank you
I'll just listen to Charlie Thursday
August the third and you start up with Andrew Gold
It's wonderful and that's a lot of text on
And I just take out Andrew Gold has his own web podcast
Did you know that?
No, I didn't know that
I subscribed to it, I don't know what it's like
But it says explicit on when you load into our changes
It says explicit Andrew Gold
Swears
It's nice
Anyway, welcome back to have a good chat
Folder scruncher, folder scruncher
Do not leave a voice mail comment
I'll let him know if you're a folder scruncher
Yeah, I gotta check that out Andrew Gold
Explosive
Sure, he's explicit
Some of his little lyrics are, they know 50 cent lyrics
But he does have more than two songs you know
Hi Adam, welcome back to the UK
This is an attack
Long term listener and owner of the award for the most perfect comment
Thanks for that
That was very nice
I think you probably know I've worked in TV
I've done for many years in the UK
And it's interesting to hear you talking about top of the pot
On the show the other day
You know, the show the music has been going for
It's almost something years
And it's a bit of a world-wide phenomenon now
Because some of the pot is one of the main things that I've worked on in my empty past
And I remember in the 80s
We've talked about musicians and backing tracks that play live and songs
In the 80s when this whole thing came up
They had to sing live
The musicians you needed decided that backing tracks would have to be re-recorded as well
So there's the musicians who played on it
We'll also get paid
And the whole thing sort of didn't generate into a bit of a fast
Because I remember one occasion I was this batch to the happy road studios
So I had a sense of a two-hour session with the holidays
So we're re-recording a re-release of
Getting heavy, my brother must have been sort of late 80s
I guess
And they played it through a few times
And the engineers ran a cool friend's tape on it
And the thought of the end of it
The right company were not in stood at all in having some crappy session
Without any chance of a remix going on TV
So for all of these to do was
I'll tell you in a bit of a bit of a column
Because engineers just give me a different tape at the end of it
And remember on that occasion they gave me a tape
That was a different colour
On a different size spool
So the one on the grass is going round in the control room
So it was a little bit obvious
But that was why in the end
When the sun went out on top of the pots
The end was out sounding like the record
Which is all of those companies are interested in the end anyway
So I'd like to share a little story with you
And also to say that this comment
Because I don't have my entire cast
Then you mentioned the wonderful, wonderful, regularised zones
By Lynn Parsons at Lynn Parsons.net
So I know it's on your favour
It's the regularised zone if a new show is doing
And I know you would absolutely adore it
Thanks again
Full disclosure
Hey that's it
You know I should have talked about that yesterday
With Patricia when we were talking about top of the pop
So I do remember some some guys from the record label back in the
Whole
Early early 80s actually telling me that exact story that I
You know it's not a problem at the top of the pop
We'll just go there and we'll sit in the studio
And record something we give the old original tape anyway
What a waste
English people should be up in arms
Hundreds of thousands of pounds
Wasted on just sitting around the studio
Pickin' their nose pretending to play
And just because of some stupid union rule that
At the time just made no sense
And it never was really adhered to
Of course
Good story dude
And Lynn Parsons you better believe it
Yeah, I like her a lot
It's definitely check out her pod
She says she has two
I didn't I haven't heard about the new one yet
I'll check out the was it red light lounge
I'll check that out for sure
And I'm trying to hook up a meeting with Lynn
For some pod show UK stuff we're doing
I'll give you the next week of the week after next
So I'm looking forward to that
And please remember to end with
Folder scruncher
Just about at the end of today's daily source code
Wrapin' up the week
But of course, no week is complete
Come on
No week and certainly no Friday is complete
Without hearing from the lawyer with a sense of humor
We know him as Jersey Todd
You're outer
I'd like to make a motion
To rock this mother out
You're on her, please don't bang that gavel
You can try this cowbell out
Let's all give a nod
To the hardest work in the lawyer
He's Jersey Todd
And then he's Jersey Todd
Oh yeah
You're on her, what do you say?
He might even win this case
Jersey Todd
Yeah, yeah
It was Jersey Todd
All of them
Jersey Todd
Shut up now
It's Jersey Todd
Oh yeah, you don't hate this type
Yo, what's up Adam?
Yo, for this Friday
I got one of the podcast icons for you
His name is Kevin Reeves
You know him, you love him
You played a song shine
You played a song mother
Well, he's back
He's back when the new song on the podcast
If music now
We're called Throw Me Align
But more importantly, his new album
It's all about time
It's finally out
And you can get your copy for ten bucks
I sent him to CD Baby last night
And I'm going to get mine too
So from the podcast
If music now work
This is the man Kevin Reeves
Check this out
I don't know
It's the sign of the time
For this year I'm going straight to take
I don't know
If I'm losing my mind
But I'm lost in the blind line of taste
Is there any way I wanna hear
Is there some way to make this clearly?
Because of you
I can't sleep anymore
Since you walked out the door
And you left me
All I do
Is to stare at the wall
Thinkin' no thoughts at all
Except for memory
While you wanna drive me insane
But I ain't wanna kill me so much pain
But throw me alive
Because don't think I can't make it on my own
Throw me alive
I pray that I've my die
Even on the long road
So be silent
Tell me that you're still in the wind
I can't feel
Don't know darkness from light
Don't know daytime from light
On this race end
Is it real
Or will I wake up from this
And the mist of your tears
And embrace it
What the hell am I supposed to do
I don't think I can make it
Without you
But throw me alive
Because don't think I can't make it on my own
Throw me alive
I pray that I've my die
Even on the long road
So be silent
Tell me that you're still in the wind
With me but throw me alive
I pray that I've my die
Even on the long road
So be silent
Tell me that you're still in the wind
I don't think I can make it without you
But throw me alive
I can't make it on my own
Throw me alive
I pray that I've my die
Even on the long road
So be silent
Tell me that you're still in the wind
With me but throw me alive
I pray that I've my die
Even on the long road
So be silent
I pray that I've my die
Even on the long road
Give me one of these a month
I'll be a happy man for the rest of my life
Kevin Rave just throw me a line
Another song you can find on the Podsay music network
Kick and ass
And that's good
All right everybody
So I've given you lots of stuff to think about
To listen to and talk about over the weekend
Looking forward to see you back here on Monday
And by then I'll be rested
I'll be rested
A bit woozy
Woozy from the jet lag
We had all kinds of meetings and stuff that happened
Just as usual Thursday morning yesterday
So we're kind of continued
Looking outside it's like typical
This is what you call British weather
It's not cold it's really nice actually
It's in the mid 70s
And you can see from miles and miles and miles
But not really there is a cloud base
There's the hot looking neighbor
We have a neighbor
And she's an aerobics instructor
And she has a hot red sports car
And Patricia's always baggin' on her
Oh man I wish Patricia were here
We could talk about her right now
Because she always has a belly shirts on
Let's see
She's just pulled up into the drive
And her little red sports car
Let me see what she's wearing
Oh man Patricia would be laughing
She would be laughing if she were here
Hold on
Come on
Get out of your car
She's divorced
I should have mentioned that too
She's divorced and lives there with her daughter
I think her daughter is maybe five or six
I can't see she's getting out of the...
Oh there we go
Hmm she died her hair
It's lighter
Now let's see what is she wearing
I guess
Her aerobics outfit
No it's the long white pants
With a...
It looks like a string tank top
Hmm
It takes so little to make an old man happy
Hey everybody I'll talk to you on Monday
Take care everybody
Another pot show pot cast
Stick it in your ear
Get this pot cast
And we're great ones like it
On the high performance pot cast
Delivery network from Podjo
And line white networks
I love it