This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
The show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy.
Delta Sierra Charlie 3-9 or 5.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky ingredients yet.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic kids, Adam Curry.
Have the bags and off they go.
Though they might be quite far from home.
The world is their oyster and she is his pearl for sure.
It's Patricia and Adam said I'm for another world tour.
New Yorker's San friend without her just wouldn't be right.
Yes, she's the real reason for Adam to come home tonight.
But when they're away and they both want to play at the flick of the wrist or a puff on the split,
they can find their way around.
Paint their whole town for sure.
It's Patricia and Adam said I'm for another fabulous, wonderful,
full-of-filled extravagant happy ever after world tour.
We've seen them on TV our whole life.
Super Friends were the woman stones were larger than life.
I can be like anyone I see.
I'm a record at a bum sleeve.
This is everhoo.
Dolls and the mounds of cash never on TV.
We are, we are.
We are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are.
The last summer, the sea, the heroes.
The last summer, the heroes.
Over the 1970s.
The end of the box, it is a doubt tonight.
Rock and roll to make some of the emancipation kiss alive.
You'll see back of me.
God stars in the dream release.
London, town, have the hell bent down.
Going to bed in the sweet.
We are, we are.
The last summer, the sea, the heroes.
The last summer, the heroes.
Over the 1970s.
See, no one will know.
Way we are, we are, we are more4
In the summer, that's all.
No one left to come.
No one's survival for the 1970s.
The last summer, the sea, and the heroes.
The last Summer, the sea, and the heroes.
We are, we are, the last of the civil heroes, we are, we are, we are, the last of civil heroes, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are,
we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are
Rock, Rock, Rock!
Hey everybody, how you doing coming to you from the Curry Condo for the first time.
I have the lovely lady Patricia here with me. Hello dear.
Hello.
It's only taking us about three days to put together the studio.
Oh boy, sorry about that.
Yeah, I got to watch that. There's something wrong with the process.
Dad, we're in the kitchen.
Yes, that's true.
You can just, you can even hear it a little bit.
Can't you, you can hear the, you can hear the sink.
You can hear the sink.
You can hear the sound of the sink.
And the garbage disposal.
Yeah, um, no, actually, um,
When was the last time we had did a show?
Was it, uh, it was,
Cricky.
Wednesday?
Wednesday morning from the private show?
Shit on your pop and all over the place.
Oh, yeah, no, you know the show.
It was the show.
The show we did for everybody.
Oh, Wednesday, New York.
Yeah, and today is, uh,
Was it really Wednesday?
Was it Thursday?
Jesus, I don't remember.
No, no, no, I did.
No, you did.
Friday show with Charles in, uh, in Monterey.
Yeah.
Charles, what's his name?
Oh.
Charles, uh, you know, what's his name?
Yeah.
So, um, in the meantime, we've traveled a bit.
Uh, we've been, uh,
Well, you know, we've been in Monterey.
We've been in San Francisco.
Uh, tomorrow we go home and throughout those past couple of days.
We've actually managed to get a new power supply for the, uh,
For the mixer and we got a, um,
To the other microphone works and we got you headphones.
Yep.
To Patricia to.
But when I arrived here in San Francisco,
My body didn't know where it was.
No, it didn't.
No, it was like hello.
Can't.
Oh, no, it was not San Francisco.
No, no, no, no.
By the way, I really, I wanted to dedicate the last of the superheroes to, uh,
For the first time.
Because Memorial Day, you know, really is about, um,
Remembering, uh, fallen soldiers who've defended, uh,
Our country, who've defended your country by proxy.
Yeah.
And it seems like it's really one big sale is what Memorial Day has become.
Yes.
You know, it's just like a go shop day, but.
And barbecue.
Well, that's good, too.
But, you know, just I think people forget barbecue your memories.
Yeah.
Very close to the, uh, to the men and women in service.
Oh, absolutely.
Especially after my, uh, my tour of Iraq.
Yeah.
My, uh, that was.
Did you hear about the journalists?
Oh, yeah.
That's the CBS crew.
Well, now you're going to see, you know, now you're going to see
Body's coming home.
You never see the US service men and women and, and, and, and, and the
Brits and, well, we saw some Brits coming on, too.
No, I know we didn't.
You saw them and body bags in.
Well, yeah.
In confidence.
Well, yeah, confidence.
Really?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a big ass deal.
Mm-hmm.
So now, of course, we're going to see this from the camera crew,
which is, it's, it's, it's deserve for everybody.
That is.
Disaster.
It's horrible.
Yeah, it's horrible.
Yeah.
Um, oh, but, of course, we saw, um, just getting back to Michael Butler
and the rock and roll.
Wow.
We saw.
You want to, I'm sorry.
Let me just call.
Yeah.
We know real quick topic here is street all.
Oh, okay.
Keep talking about it.
Well, it was an, a lovely evening.
And we saw three bands.
And, uh, and actually the last one was Michael Butler's.
And I was really surprised.
Yeah, it was.
This band is so good.
And good looking.
Yes.
Indeed.
You know, because these days,
I think that, um, a lot of bands, you know,
which are really, really good.
Yeah.
I want something to.
And when I, you know, sometimes it's just geeky and very technical.
Very good.
Very musical.
Not hot, baby.
Not hot.
So, and, you know, that's a shame.
And so when I saw Michael Butler's, um,
Ask.
But, but.
Michael Butler's.
Yeah.
And it makes it a singer.
Everything.
I mean, they really, they're hot.
They're very hot.
What a great band.
We're referring, of course, to the, uh, pod safe rock show,
Yeah.
Which is put on at the red devil.
Jesus.
What is this?
I don't talk about it.
Let it go.
But people are hearing this.
Oh, no.
No.
I hate when, when.
I know.
But percentage and jokes talk about it.
Talk about how shitty the sound is.
Yeah.
Okay.
Unfortunately, it's just, but don't say it.
I'll try not to.
So this was the, uh, the pod safe rock show with the red devil
lounge in San Francisco.
That was Saturday night actually.
Yeah.
And, uh, and we went and, uh, it was freak accident.
The freak accident was up first.
Uh, big mic on drums.
Yeah.
I saw him.
And then, uh, it was griddle.
Yeah.
Who, uh, you like griddle a lot too.
Very much.
And, uh, and then, of course, it was, uh,
uh, Michael Butler's band, rock and roll.
It was cool.
It was a good show.
Fantastic.
Great evening.
I still wish we had more audience there.
Yeah.
It just, what was that all about it?
Well, it was a lot when we came in, but then, you know,
uh, American heartbreak didn't go on until what until, uh,
11, 30 or something like that.
I thought that was too late.
Yeah.
I thought somewhere something that stuff.
But I expected more people.
Yeah.
For a band like that.
So good.
Do people know for all three bands.
Yeah.
Do people know how good they are?
Well, I think someone does.
They, they just got a Japanese record deal.
Yeah.
We, oh, this is so cool.
Um, this is Japanese or Chinese.
Who knows?
Something, something Asian.
Something Asian.
So, um, we're listening to, um, uh, rock and roll geek show.
What was it?
166.
So this is done.
Was it, this was done the day after the show?
I think after the rock show.
Yeah.
And I, I, I actually cut it up on.
I promise we're going to play this for a list.
Listen to Michael Butler here for a second.
This is funny.
There you go.
Yeah.
You got the bag's dog house in honor of my status in the household.
It started out.
I'm, pardon me if I whisper.
I don't want to get in.
Yeah.
Caught, want talking about this.
So the whole show wound on this subject may be me whispering.
So forgive me.
And I apologize if you don't like this kind of talk.
But I am trying to be honest.
My life is an open book like that.
I've heard Michael Butler do these shows before.
Yeah.
the first time I ever heard him he was it was at a blogger con I think was two years ago
and he was in his hotel room all alone drinking beer and recording talking about being all alone
and drinking beer. I love men like that. I said so the day started off fine I went to the
dog park with the wife came with me everything was going great something happened I think I was
I was getting ready to take the kids to have dim sum lunch like we usually do on Saturdays
and about that time the lovely wife decided to start cleaning the house and
somewhere in this is clues as to what it did wrong. Let me listen let me just kind of
went downhill and we laughed and went to he went with him to the dim sum he did the dog
what the dog walked you know what they usually do but then she was cleaning the house and then
he says he went downhill and now listen now it comes. Okay dim sum and came back and I had to go
mix some acoustic stuff that Billy said I had to go while she was cleaning the house and this
was actually a family day I guess she thought you know it was a full family maybe you know
a little bit longer you know what Michael tried to do he tried to do what all guys do
it's like okay I promise the band I'm going to go I was going to go mix this single whatever
so I'm going to do a whole bunch of real family things in the four hours before I have to go
there and that's what I think that's what was going on. Bandroom in Billy's house
because we have a Japanese we got a Japanese record deal coming up I'm not going to say who it's
with right now because I don't want to jinx it like it's with Japanese records before like I said
before with the liquor and poker things so I'm going to keep that in my hat who the label is
said Japanese label it's not a great deal anyway okay so that's what then then that's what
did this you know she is already of course understanding what what he's doing and trying to
respect that and now she thought she's going to have a nice day with her husband and the dogs and
I don't know what she had the plans and then suddenly he had to do he had to go mix the single
Japanese records and she said they will go again it's all about him again something like that
which's pretty good and we're and when you're on a Japanese that he's not talking about any
you know yeah yeah it was made later let me fast roll I'm going to drop these flyers off to the
flyer guy and then I'll be home and there's like any drop of the flyers of the flyer guy
so never drop off flyers of the flyer can possibly ask for you know if you're married you know
how this is you know I don't know the only thing worse than being yelled at and punched is
the silent treatment so and going what it's all and not knowing what it's all about his wife
punches in oh that's what he said the only worse thing than being yelled at and punched oh my god
you hear that and I said that's the silent treatment so and I said so are you mad at me and
then all hell broke loose you know how dare me ask on that anyway you have no clue
you know when you say sometimes are you mad I said anything wrong based you know oh yeah
and that's not like any clue to us when when when girls go like that no there's nothing wrong nothing
at all now them would we're just disappointed that's it you know how I'm really pretending not to
hear that that's happening but it's really pissing me off yeah well why don't you just I don't
know what's going on but that maybe hear me am I am I still on the show or is this was something
you've done you are but do the success of yourself on the show now you've sabotaged my microphone
you go let go back a little bit on your you're in the mic you but that's what I'm used to
yeah but not today it's very difficult see there's very much better keep a distance okay
see you hear that you hear immediately it overload that is because you're doing it too yeah
no that's the whole point if you're laughing and you're trying not to laugh you're laughing
I will laugh next to my socks no I wanted to I wanted to thank Joe Klein
who did all the on stage announcements at the at the pod save rock show dude he was he was
hyped up he was really really what did you say over Yana continued in English um like an
yeah like a teenage girl over Yana no did we see you don't have that no okay it's a
no that only exists in okay in Dutch some older teenagers were there and he was one of them
I'm really I'm really really not happy with the sound sorry no you don't understand it's
can't you hear hold on one second don't move don't wait wait yes you do don't move
right okay so that's much better we just we just stood here for like 10 minutes 10 minutes trying
to figure this shit out so I just pull all the processing out so I guess it sounds okay now doesn't it
okay it sounds okay nice nice yeah I'm sorry I'm sorry so doesn't I want to get back to
Joe Klein you said something in Dutch which says no translation for okay it's a pity
but the point is he was very enthusiastic and it reminded me actually a lot of me
like you know 15 years ago that's what I mean yeah but he was not and he he was like bill
grand man he was up oh he was and it was cool he did a great he also did that promo that we played
in New York the one of one like that every band should have one like that shit yeah a person who is
so proud of the band so anyway I'd say that was a very successful successful show yeah
we just learning experience I still want to get lots more audience maybe we need more time
to to wrap up for the show I'm not sure that could be it yeah I mean we didn't play the
promo until until Wednesday so the Wednesday before the show yeah okay so do you want to talk
about Monterey yeah Pebble Beach will we work oh what's it Monterey yes what day is it I know that
two days this must be Monterey dude I thought Pebble Beach was there the name of the town
uh no it's Monterey and then there's Monterey Pebble Beach and this was the end the end
there's a song about Monterey right I'm sure there is so yeah so did you have any fun
yeah I had fun with you and with Marta but yeah it was it was different because I don't know
anything about golf or you know well the golf thing was only just just one afternoon but
but very nice people I'm I met some very nice people to uh at the table at the dinner table
you're your biggest fan yeah Ray Ray Ray Ray Ray Ray Ray Lane is Patricia's biggest fan yeah
so Ray immediately I'm his fan too but see Ray's got a great rap though because the first of
all he's like oh you know I love I love the Clinton story I love what you're doing you're so much
better than Adam you know you didn't totally he says you know without you the show was just
less good you bring out the best than him but and then later at dinner he's like well you know
I was thinking about buying that forty million dollar house over there yeah he was pointing it out
you see that out there I tried to buy that forty million it was a bit too much he said
little bit too much yeah man Ray Lane is on our board of directors he's a partner at the
China Perkins and he's been in in the technology industry for a very sensitive man I like that
he was a metronome man he is he's a metronome man he is we were actually talking
moisturizer for his face oh really oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
man shoes let's do the metro sexual moment for Ray really he was talking about about moisturizer
yeah we were talking about because he looks pretty good for his age all right yeah yeah so I said
you know what you do about it he said well I take care of myself as it do you use some some
products for your face because a lot of men think they don't need anything but just like leather
just like flowers flowers need water and we need some moist on our skin and then that keeps us
looking a little bit better and he knew all about it you knew all about it you know he knew all about
very good you know what's interesting is now now I have no control over the mix
I can't turn it off I can't turn it up or down really
fuck this is gonna drive me fucking crazy listen I start the song I start the song and
I have no control I can't turn it up or down I can turn it on or off just like lying
fucking stupid but anyway no okay to be quite honest I have I had the feeling this is the
shittiest show we've ever done this is sucking so bad oh that will motor slowly okay I think I
fixed it now I'm so sorry do we have anything left to say about Ray are we just done oh we're
just completely fucking done on this shit hate it hate it you love that don't you want to get off
I'm all hot and sweaty and I'm just like I just want to go you're so sexy when you're angry
no you're not it's not true I'm anything but I'm anything but sexy when I'm fucking angry
oh my goodness so I had a great time though yeah we had a great time it was it was we learned
something too yeah we learned that 730 in the morning to watch Al Gore's new movie is very early
we learned that yeah it was pretty cool though they had a quite especially when you have
oh yeah no kidding yeah it was cool though they had a question a question and answer session
with with president Gore by ex ex ex vice president Gore but it was vice dot satellite do you hear
that yeah I'm just I'm not supposed to get pissed off when I hear that I think I think the power
supplies fucked up or something something's wrong yeah let's just play something from somebody
or something and I can't see we can't know where man the treasure this is my completely
many listeners they gave a source code I listened to a with a 391 this morning
well 392 the one from the hotel anywhere when you had breakfast that was really cool
that was the coolest show so far I've listened to you're kidding you're probably 70 or 80 of
them so far and this was really good because it was the most relaxing there was no
no music no pushy add just one fucking mic that worked for us you know and and I also heard
the people were irritated by us but I was cheating us eating yeah that was one of the things
people didn't like yeah yeah nothing like that I really enjoyed it even more so because I had
breakfast at the same time oh okay yeah that was special and you should do this more often I think
you should have breakfast very much and leave some German in by the way Patricia your German sounds
really cute I heard of the other day on the previous shows yeah thank you thank you
and she didn't go with nothing you like I'll tell you something
ah this is uh this is actually uh this is actually uh yeah yeah if you want to leave a uh comment
voicemail numbers in New Jersey 2016256357 in London O2O76813753 you know that sounds on earbuds
a little iPod earbuds when when that that happens you know but no I understand you're trying
to tell me to talk past the microphone but it just doesn't work that way I have it to talk
into the microphone and what's happening is the microphone is overloading the mixer and I don't understand
why it's your microphone not like a friend your microphone is sucking too in case you had an
notice okay anyways so on the way back we stopped by Carmel that was nice oh that is so beautiful
but it's almost like it's not for it's not for real it's so it looks a little bit like
like yes yes yeah totally that's it's yeah but that's the way it is that's the way it is
how old is the carmel carmel I don't know not as old as this fucking microphone and mixer that's
sure see you laugh and then the whole thing over modulates again it's a it's a real problem on
I know you don't understand I know you don't care uh then we drove to San Francisco
and see oh that was that Saturday no it was Friday Friday we got in Friday late Friday night
and did we do we even eat Friday night I can't even remember this has been like a huge
world tour we ate crackers old crackers oh yeah no no tell what why don't you tell everyone
what you think about my my bachelor pad the condo now that I've been living here for a while
yes I expected lots of a mess one big mess and lots of wires yeah and because you make you make
a mess I have wires I like wires yeah yeah you're like a lot of wires and not wires just
nice wires no it's one big spaghetti thing yeah you know but I know wires just came in and everything
looked nice thank you thank you lovely bed thank you yeah I'm really slept well
and did you nice nice clean I have a happy mind to start the whole fricking show all over again
I cannot stand this you you listen to this I'm not even taught I'm inhaling I'm inhaling and it's going
like that do you want to start the show over so we just do the whole fricking show over again
because this is I don't mind fuck it it's not funny look hunt I've done this a million times
I've I've said this thing up I've do it didn't exactly this listen it sounds like shit
I don't laugh at me it's not that's not fair I missed a sad light window by the way that's
over for those of you no longer listening here's what you're not going to hear because I didn't tell
you that it's coming up Jesus Christ okay let me do a promo let me just do a promo and I'll see
if I can fix it during the promo hey it's Cali Lewis from Geek Brief TV he creeps a video podcast
you can watch on your computer or I pod with the video we cover tech and gadget news in a way that's
fast fresh and the loads of fun don't let the main fully it we have viewers who are hard
cry to you guys and programmers but we also have viewers who are busy moms who just want to keep
up with what's happening in tech thanks to potra podcast network and marketing partners like
godaddy.com and our thing and especially thanks to all of you who watch we're quitting our day
jobs to produce the brief full time yeah thanks for checking out the brief at Geek Brief.tv and
wait I'll see what's coming next okay you there yeah hello does it work is this thing on kind
yeah so yeah we had a video chat with Christina and my parents is that cool doesn't it doesn't
I chat just rock so so incredibly hard yeah it's a nice to look in your own kid kitchen it's going
look at looking your own kid this is going on and see your home and everything and it's great
we heard from my mom that Christina is very sad oh this is a sad story this is very sad because
she had say two or three boyfriends a boy now she's actually just starting today
and much too much oh it's those not even on yeah emo voice you know she likes that emotional
my listeners know what emo is yeah I'll excuse me are our listeners we'd with the long hair
I understand because I used to like those two when I was so young and so she goes from one to another
wait let's talk about the guys that you used to like when you were young who was that they
looked a bit like that because that was the 70s and we're back into 70s with the trend and we
totally are so they all look very familiar to me and so she then suddenly how is it was Owen and
then Owen was gone oh no it's Jack she says now it's Jack so now it's Jack and check I met him very nice
he's very happy happy emo okay I don't know if he's an official card carrying emo he seems a little
bit too happy you know what I'm saying maybe it's only the hair but he thinks he is so so she
she had a lot of fun with him you know I heard a laugh a lot and and I suddenly he announced and
he just heard it I think yesterday or something that his parents and he are moving to Spain
into in two weeks time not just you know that's like they're doing it now they're moving to Spain
so a Christian has very upset oh man and they didn't and his parents didn't tell him she didn't
even cry when my dog died where when our dog died she must love this Jack guy a lot so
so since they were moment brought you by dog and Drew yeah so she she cried a lot lots of
tissues and that's my mom yeah so yeah so we called her on the on the eye chat and that's
her to her because she said to her well we'll fly to Spain well of course of course I don't want my
dog on happy I'll fly I'll go to Spain so problem we'll go to Spain and she said no it's not necessary
we broke up it's much better it's much better to break up it's not it's not when it's real love
you should go oh wow yeah no you know it's but we're going visit it so let's go for a couple
days I don't mind yeah yeah we had some other kid encounters of the third kind oh we went to
it's a Greg Lawley's house my friend Greg who lives here in San Francisco outside of
the A one in the company that's my only other friend here yeah he cooked a sort of a heart attack
yeah oh my god there was great shuttle real and it was big big potatoes with not just like normal
big potatoes not triple triple refrying whipped cream cheese bacon bacon in the whipped in the
big potato so that's not good for this mommy and what else did he had and it was cool though his
mom was there and his son Zachary and his brothers two kids or sisters two kids it was full of kids yeah
Patricia's like oh I want that one I want that one oh can I take that one yeah a little little
Japanese kids I love them oh yeah Lee and his family were there yeah it was pretty cool man we had a good
time yeah and now we're almost ready to go home this is actually the first night we've been together
alone yeah and look what we're doing we're sitting here listening to shitty ass setup well
you want me to do this oh I know right now it's just it's not the way I wanted to finish the
week I wanted to finish the week with a great show with yeah but wasn't it nice to be all by ourselves
we're alone without a teenager it's funny it was um I said to you today make a lot of noise
yeah that too that was nice yeah but we can't do that later tonight we can't make a lot of noise
because of overload the system oh shit but it was it what it was it's um it's funny because
this is the first time we've really been away from our teenager for an extended period of time
together so this is you know 10 days a long time for us and it feels very much like the old
exactly yeah when we just before Christina was born well in New York it's 20 years and I
have to say I'm still very much in love with you oh baby even though even though Ray would buy
you a $40 million house for you to live in he didn't offer that oh okay yeah I love you too yeah
and I'm sorry about the shitty setup I thought I had everything else right now it's always so
perfect but it might as well suck once in a while that's life okay so um yeah is there anything else
we need to besides the fact that you know I'm confused now because I had things in my mind but
because of the whole you know you were a different mood now yeah I mean you want to do the show
over and I'll fix it yeah but that's not what our show is all about we just talk to each other
you cannot just force it and and do it again that's true you know was there anything you want to
talk about it you can you remember any of that stuff because I feel there was something but
there was something in it I mean who knows you may not maybe able to understand us this is so shitty
oh well look at this and you think about it yeah I had them Simon here from Sam Idol
thanks for all of you letting us know about the American Idol finals being had taken
base at the moment with somebody called Taylor um that was very interested to hear that because
I was wondering why I was getting family hits on a Sam Idol website for people searching for
Taylor Idol podcast but now I know so I've gone into you on my podcast with somebody called
Taylor Marley here's a very famous American poet but I hope that there are a lot of people
are searching for stuff about somebody in the American Idol called Taylor and they're coming to my
website so that's great and also very very keen to hear that you're um that you're setting up the
yeah the poster UK company because I'm very much looking forward to the opportunity of the
potentially joining pod show but um unfortunately the American contract that I've been sent
I just can't sign and so yeah great to hear the poster UK is happening okay thanks for
this assignment from Sam Idol thanks Adam bye he's got a great show the slam idol podcast
yeah it's really good yeah oh and I saw the office what did you think today oh I just have to
respond to what's can you even hear me yeah I hear you loud and clear yeah um he's uh we're
now that we've pod show UK we have to do all like like UK contracts and stuff this is a real
this is really happening there's a lot of work we got to do I know we're like oh shit yeah the
guys in the UK we might as well have a UK contract duh we're so incredibly smart the office here
it was surprising it looks very very trendy very good actually it was the same style as a W hotel
it is isn't it yeah it is a bit the same style you know with the screens the
same as the bathroom but for us it's very fun you know yeah very fun this is what I mean
yeah it works no it totally works yeah it looks very nice so that that was um good to see
lovely and I had a lot of fun with the Marta today you guys were shopping yeah when shopping a little bit
for Christina yeah for ever 21 or you know that's that's a store for little stores yeah so I
had a whole bunch of stuff for there so we're gonna hope we can make her with happy yeah just by
being home should be happier that we're there I hope so tomorrow we go home and uh Wednesday I'll be
back with a show this is gonna be a long flight it's gonna be a very long flight you've done this
flight that you've done this San Francisco to London flight with me yeah oh and oh everyone
knows we're gonna paperwork done that's cool oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we already told everybody
I'm just gonna play one last song I have I'm not in the mood this I can't work like this I can't
like be talking and have to consider how loud I'm talking and just doesn't work for me because
listen that shit pro yeah I'm a pro with a piece of shit setup
ok
I've never been the same a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been
a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've never been a kid, I've
So I watch movies in the darkness
In a regular night's peak
And above it all is subterred
There are so tiny dreams
But I don't speak Chinese
So I'll just never understand
Why you don't have any more
And why your boyfriend wants to kill me
Can I watch this film?
And for the morning
Or when I have to come back
So I can't hear me or anything
So I can have a bridge to see
Or not depending
How I explain at the multiplex
And what is playing at the movie
I need a Chinese phrase book
Yo, freak accidents
You like that, didn't you?
Yeah, they were playing that song when we came in
Oh, you know what?
I don't know if this is what everyone else has been listening to
I've been listening to a whole different mix
I'm not kidding you
I hope what I'm hearing now
I hope that's what is what actually was recorded
Because it sounds great
Now I found it and I found the actual mix
I was listening to shit before
So maybe it was just me
Oh, Christ
I'm sorry
No, it doesn't
You know what important it is to be able to hear yourself properly
You know what it is like a singer
As a singer, you know what that's like
You can ruin your whole album
Have you actually ever had that happen?
Has it ruined?
Well, I'm going to go up and produce it
Produces that never got the right sound
And it's on the album
And every time I hear that album
I never listened to my own stuff
You don't even have your own stuff anymore
But might I listen to it
Yeah, should it happen?
Then I think shit, yeah, that was not a good sound voice
Yeah, big gale was the only one
He was the only one who could make the sound
Yeah, that's right because I don't have an easy voice to record
What are you talking about? You have a great voice to record
You're just, no, I've been in the studio
When you when you wanted that sound right
And you're just relentless
He's like, you want the reverb to be a certain way
Folding into the echo, all kinds of stuff like that
You want that sound
Yeah, but your voice is very easy to do
Yeah, but do you like sound of I've made for you now?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah
Okay, you know what? I'm also tired
You are? Yeah, I'm tired
I hear that for the last couple of days
And you know, you're so much younger than I am
And every time I hear you, I'm too dull
You're going to hold on a second
And what am I mean? I'm never tired
What did you do today? You had a wonderful day shopping
Well, Ron and I sat in the office
You said on your house? No, excuse me
It has nothing to do with sitting on your house
We were concentrated, we had three different meetings
People who gave up their memorial day weekend
Like we did like, you know, I would have wanted to go shopping
Or you were moving
But that's nothing to do with it
It's brain power baby
Is that when makes you tired? That makes me very tired
Yes, are you kidding me?
Of course it does
Any brain things to do
You know, you're tired
And you know, remember I took you for walk
Going to peer to
Or whatever it's going to be
I sit on the market
Please come with me because I haven't seen anything
Oh, no, you haven't seen anything
I haven't seen anything
But here in front of the
You know, the view, I see the view
I've taken you around, I showed you
Places, I showed you Greg's place
Showed you what it was like over there
Yeah, we went through Carmel, always we drove
But finally, finally
I saw a little bit more than the spot
Where your flatties were
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So, I said, let's go and go out
It's beautiful day, let's walk
I was tired
I'm tired again
Well
How cool is my car, though?
Admitted
Well, it's a smell of French fries
It smells like...
I forget what it was
But you're like...
You and your French fries
Get yourself over here
Yeah
Trinity is awesome
Did that car start on the first go
After two months of sitting in the garage
I was impressed
Thank you
Don't you love my car
What did I say?
No, it looks just as shitty as your airplane did before
Before I redesigned it
Yeah, yeah, yeah
It's cold, they're a whole thing
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
We're going to panper out, we just haven't gotten the whole thing together
Yeah, I hope somebody's going to do something about it
Because
It looks horrible
Yeah, I see everybody looking at me
Oh, poor girl
Poor girl
Yeah, where's their trailer
And did you smile at them just like that without your teeth
Who is my favorite smile?
Exactly
I adjust, by the way
All right, baby
Let's just put this show out and see what people think about the reality of podcasts
Sometimes it just blows chunks
Life is not perfect
This is one thing I got to say
Yeah
Remember those earthlink commercials that everyone hated
Not everyone, but just by everyone hated it
I'll just play it for you
Just to remember what it was
Do you believe anything is possible
We do
We are a flank
So
Just let go into first
I don't know, everything's messed up, I have no idea
Um
He speaks like that
So we got a lot of response and people said, you know, we don't want radio commercials, etc
So now we have earthlink, you know, who's
I'd have to say a pretty forward looking company
Yeah
They, you know, we had meetings with him, we talked about it
We discussed all the feedback that we got from people saying they didn't like
These commercials
Yeah
And they said, okay
Um, we're in, we'll, we'll, we suggest that the ad chat, the ad challenge
Uh-huh
Which is make your own commercial
Uh, for earthlink
And it can be a jingle, it can be a commercial
Could just be, you know, someone just telling a story about earthlink
It doesn't matter endorsement, you know, like I have earthlink
And I love it
Or whatever
And so we, so that, and you can actually win big cash prizes
And real cash, real money, real prizes
So go to adchallenge.podshow.com
And uh, enter, uh, you can sign up without, uh, without entering just yet
But, you know, sign up and then you can enter by sending in
I guess you just upload an MV35
What a great idea
Yeah, well, thank you
Well, thank you very much
That's the kind of labor that Ron and I do on Memorial Day weekend
We're sitting in the office, we come up with all the great ideas
Keep the peeps busy
Exactly
We're going to ask you to be on the jury, actually, to be a judge
Okay
Yeah
I was thinking, it's between, it's between you and Peter
Well, because you know that I sang a commercial for years
That's true
Well, you mean, maybe you do the commercial judge
Flops
In between, flops
While the record weren't selling
The commercials, you know, it was, it's very, um, it's very creative for me
And you know what, I was the singer that just walked away
If I didn't go, exactly
Exactly
You know, I think this commercial is shit and socks
I'm not going to do it
You just want to go out of the studio
Yeah, yeah
My dad used to say, if you think that
The things that you have to do like, you know, the backups or a commercial
Is not musical, you know, I don't know if I can translate it
Musical, responsible
Yeah, if it's not, um, if it's not responsible
Musically
Musical, musically
Musically, responsibly
Responsibly
Right
Leave the studio
And as with most commercials
Patricia left the studio
So I would say
They just gentleman Patricia has left the building
Yeah
This is just, you know, shit
It doesn't sound good, it's not, it's not good
It's not correct
Exactly
It's not perfect actually
It's not correct
Because people can be kids
Yeah, I hear so much of that
So, uh, and then I left
So, I, I'm very experienced
I think I did about a hundred
A hundred different commercials
Yeah, but you did
Yeah, I did voiceovers
And that was in between the flops
What did you have?
What do you have hits in between the commercials
To pay my rent, I would do that
Sure
Oh, yeah
I'd still do it
Some chips, crisps, whatever
You didn't call them to genes
Detergents
You did detergents
Yeah, and I did
She got some of the machines
Butter, butter
Do you remember any of them?
The butter
What was the butter?
What was the butter one?
And who's fine?
Who's foreigner?
That's sewing machine
And a motorcycle at the same time
Interesting, you know?
And, you know, like, very, um,
The butter that keeps you, um, lean and mean
Was that they sell?
No
No, Eira
Eira, what was the jingle?
I can't remember
Oh, come on
I don't know
Fun
Oh, and panties
Panties
Oh, yeah, the legs
The legs one
Yeah
Because we call it strange
But in Holland
Panties is a pente
A pente, but real quick
Right
And you don't remember any of the jingles
Yeah, Pente of Sorbella
And they, they would see me walk
See my legs
Oh, you did the visual commercial
Yeah, and the sound
Yeah, so these
Really?
Yeah, but you don't remember the song
Do you remember how much you got paid?
So, Bella, I don't know
I don't know
Oh, not much
No
No, not much
And beer
I did beer
Skulling to National
You remember that?
I remember that
Yeah
Oh, baby
Yeah, yeah
I'm so happy
So, I'm so happy
So, I'm very good
I'm the judge
Okay, I got to
I got to be person
I got to be good
All right, I got to clear this with the
With the powers that be
We have to have a meeting about it
At the office sitting on our asses
Man
But I think you would be good
Okay, so too
All right
At challenge.potcho.com
All right, let's get out of here
Let's stop before I break something
Before I throw it out the freaking window
Yeah, we have to be careful here
And then we can relax and start our last evening together
What time is it?
Nine 25
I can do a lot of damage
I can do a lot of damage, baby
Okay, I'll thank you for putting it with my shit
Yeah
Yeah, okay
You're welcome
Will you come back on later in the week
No, you Friday
Come on the show
I'll fix the sound
What I can do it for me
This is the one and only time
That's right
And I thought I was working
We're going to do it in your little studio
Yeah, we'll do it in the cottage
Okay
Now I think
So you guys tomorrow
Yeah, no tomorrow
Yes tomorrow
We'll be Wednesday
Wednesday morning
We got into I can still do a show
For a for Wednesday
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm the guy that doesn't work at all
To work very far
No, this one's going out for tomorrow
Because it's all ready tomorrow
In the end
Always ready tomorrow
So this one will be for Tuesday
And then we flight
Tuesday after noon
So we're in Wednesday morning
And then Wednesday morning
It's still so early in the US
That I can do a show
You know me the the guy that doesn't do anything
And has no reason to be tired
I'm very curious
I do it every single time
Whenever whenever I come home
I do a show
I know
I know you're very good at it
Okay
Just check
Can wake you up
And you do it
You do you trick right away
I love you too
Okay, babe
Okay, no you love you
God damn it
Here it is
Another pod show pod cast
Stick it in your ear
Get this pod cast
And more great ones like it
On the high performance pod cast
Delivery network from pod show
And limelight networks
I love it