Hey, this is Don Miselli.
And this is Drew Dhamkis.
From The Dawn and Drew Show.
Check out ShadowFalls.podshow.com.
It's so spooky you might pee your pants.
GOO-A-A-A-A-A-A-A!
This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and Go Daddy.
Want Killer Content with a bad-ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Okay.
Hey, this is the other Carmen John Carmen from the G-Spod.
That's the Golf, Sierra Papa, Oscar Delta.
And you're listening to Delta Sierra Charlie 4-5-1.
D-S-C-4-5-1.
Get it in ya.
Sometimes some add-ups all alone.
You need to love right there on the microphone.
So here she is, yes, the lady Patricia.
The say to have some better than one.
And with this angel from above,
There's nothing that they both can't do.
But make you wildest dreams come true
To grab your earbuds and jam them in
And let the fabulous show begin.
It's Adam and Patricia.
Yes, Adam and Patricia.
Adam and the lady Patricia.
I'm a paranoid schizophrenic with surround sound speakers.
They're everywhere, they're everywhere.
I'm a cell phone to a megaphone to my headphone
And I'm still alone.
They're everywhere, they're everywhere.
And I like to talk to you right now,
But it's me on the other mind.
I'll call you back when we're the man
I'm the use gives me the sign.
And I know you think they're all acting
To get you for the really antagonist.
Can't you see?
Everywhere, everywhere, everywhere.
Everywhere, everywhere.
I'm a militant environmentalist in four exploders
And I'm a true man, and I'm a true man, and I'm a true man
I'm a xenophobic, tapioca foam, and I'm a plump, full bacon course foam
And I like to talk to you right now, but it's me, I'm alone mine
And call you back when the spaceship lands in 1949
And I know you think they're all out to get you, but they're really out to get me
Can't you see?
They're everywhere, they're everywhere, they're everywhere
They're everywhere, they're everywhere
I'm a fighter, I'm the boy, except he sent me in
Who's always meeting
And I'm a true man, and I'm a true man, and I'm a true man
And I'm a true man, and I'm a true man
And I like to talk to you right now, but it's time for me
Call your back, my head's cut out, but of course that'll be too late
And I know you think they're all out to get you, but they're really out to get me
Maybe every way, they're everywhere, they're everywhere
They're everywhere, they're everywhere, they're everywhere
They're everywhere
Ah nice little mini
Another mayonnaise
Strikes
Jim's Big Ego from the pod save music network
From Massachusetts in the United States
Why did you find Disney?
I found it at the pod save music network
Wow
Jim's Big Ego compares itself to such major players as the Great Wall of China, the Grand Canyon, Antarctica, and other things you can see from space.
Okay, I don't know where they give the name from.
Very good.
It is that the Daily Source Code episode 451 coming to you from the affluent suburb of Suri known as Gilford in the United Kingdom,
at the Curry Cottage with the Lady Patricia.
Hello, how are you?
Hello, darling.
Good to see you on the show.
Well, I saw you this morning.
Yeah, I know, but on the show.
Uh, good to see you on the show.
Um, because we got some stuff to talk about.
Yeah.
You don't have your tooth in.
It's not tooth.
There.
My molar.
I know when you get your new ones.
Are they done yet?
Has it been six months yet?
Almost almost almost there.
It is painful.
This whole process.
Yes, it is.
It takes so long.
That's why you don't see Hollywood celebrities from months on end because they're sitting in
Alabama on the beach where they're where their face all chopped up.
I know, I know.
They're teeth at least.
But it's necessary because teeth are so important for your general, for your general health.
Exactly.
For the inside of the outside.
Yes.
Um, got a couple things to talk about.
Then I want to talk about the sweet 16 party.
Well, start about this morning.
This morning.
I told you I'm going to tell them.
I wanted to wake you up with some lovely angel kisses on your.
Inormous.
Menhood.
Uh-huh.
Really?
Yes.
I wanted to wake you up.
Well, you know, I had just that urge.
Why didn't you?
Because you weren't deep sleep.
Yeah.
Well, that would be what I do when I sleep.
You weren't deep sleep.
In coma.
And I could see that it was not a good time.
And after that, when I, you know, just cut a little bit with you.
You know, I hated in the morning.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Not anymore.
Fuckers.
Yes.
But that was only after you told me what you had let that's only what you had told.
So unfair.
So this is after you told me what you didn't do.
So how fair was that?
Yeah.
Because I can.
Maybe you should try the angel kisses and see,
Do you think that I would respond incorrectly?
I do that now and then, but yeah, it's for you it's I know and you come out of a coma
Okay, all right, let's just hold on a second back up because this is I'm gonna get a really bad reputation from all this shit
You think so? Yes, there are lovely men who would love to excuse me. There was no offer
There was no offer there was no initiation. There was an all I'm hearing about is what you didn't do
But what you thought about that does not count
But I do it now and then and and do I ever say go away?
No
No, well you announced the this morning. I am not a morning fucker right, but you know
I'm not you've known this for 20 years and I'll tell you exactly why because when my eyes open up
Yeah, first I think oh
I'm glad I'm glad the open my split. No, no, I think I'm glad the Patricia
I'm glad that my eyes open because I've learned that from you. I'm like oh, that's another day
What day Tuesday? Hmm. What do I have to do and then within five seconds of waking up?
I'm already thinking about the show
I'm thinking about appointments. I have I can't help it so that that's not a very sexy mood
It's different but that's after I'm awake
So you're your prime opportunity
No, you take longer to wake up. It's your prime. I know, but your prime opportunity is before I wake up
So there's nothing wrong with that. I have to do it when you sleep. I'll tell you what. Why don't we try it again tomorrow?
Well, you're
And let's see what happens. Okay, show is that a deal? Yeah, okay, all right
We've got people have been calling in over the past week at plus one two zero one six two five six three five seven
Which most people now seem to have in their cell phone because I'm getting a lot of but but calls
You know people sit on their cell phone and then it calls them home
Really a lot of those but but phones. Yeah, you've got phone B. Yeah
I heard you a couple of times. You heard my butt phone. Yeah. Yeah. Was it any good?
You were going on about flying
Captain Dan boring
Mental
So I thought after what
It's not you were actually listening to see if you could hear any fine and then he's like well how boring is that boring
He's not doing anything exciting legal. I can't trap him doing anything
You're horrible. See what he said you're horrible. I'm gonna take your key lock off
So I can get some from you too
Yeah, I have a key lock. That's right. All right. Here's the here's one call. It's what can I add
I'm very soon again
I am here in a really cool one all the day. I was just reading the paper
Okay, this is what I know because I had to listen to it four times
He's saying oh, I don't miss it. I was on holiday reading the paper
Okay, okay
What the week I think whether it's an image in that video six
So they're finally reporting on the video sex
Yes, they finally got it
Find things out before
Before the people say it's true
You know people find things out before other people
Yeah, especially before a journalist to do you know
And they're the one who who have to do the research
Just remember you ever do you heard it here first I know on the daily source
Finish this comment you won't get said what people find in the big news
I'm down already
I have no
Yeah
He's a he's a Bruton holiday. Yeah, yeah
I'm gonna wrap up this whole Carmen Tyler naked picture thing we talked about it last time
I know I'm done with it. I'm done being people keep sending in stuff
So just a couple things I want to say the first thing actually
Remember I told you about that press release that we put out about this seven hottest women in podcast thing
and then it was just like
People were saying you know you're using sex to sell podcasts and it's and this is wrong and it's like
What is going on and then I received this call
Hey Adam it's Karen from RumorGirls.com
I wanted to thank you and Pod Show for the recent press release that stated Pod Show becomes home of the seven hottest women in podcasting
I knew Pod Show wasn't talking about our looks even though we are all quite sexy
Because if you were talking about our looks
Would you have wanted to add Madgy Weinstein to the list? Thanks Adam
Yeah, exactly exactly
We want to see her naked. Oh, I don't think so
I don't think so. Hey Adam it's Carmen Tyler. She is
See that I'm kind of this topic of conversation on the daily source code
Which is kind of funny, but I kind of feel like I need to respond to your requests for nude photos of me
Well, the answer is pretty much
No
The most you'll get for me is like as to I'm super sure from when I competed or
Or maybe a photoshoot that I did or possibly like the sheer pageant gowns or a gown that I have that kind of gives the illusion
But I'm not really nude
So I'm sorry about that, but you know, I still love you, man. You're so awesome and I hope you have a great day
And I'll talk to you later and one more thing
Just to let you know Adam
I'm a folder
Okay, that helps
Oh
I feel better
But you know she sounds so sexy
I know exactly this is my entire point
Yeah, and I have to say that she doesn't need to be afraid. I've been naked a couple of times
It never hurts me never or my career or career or anything
I mean nothing just I got a lot of money for it
And don't don't give her any ideas. I don't want to pay for the naked picture. It's a kick
Such a kick
But I'm really not disappointed. Do you want to you and I might pick your honey?
I have a couple of yours
Okay
I'd still carry someone in my wallet some naked pictures. We're on the road. That's good. I love to be naked
I don't know what the problem is in America. You know being naked naked is a lot wonderful
I agree more naked feel free. It's a freedom. Let's ask the the neighbor with the with the big houters and the red sports card
That's asked her to be naked over here. She probably will
She waived at me the other day
Yeah, but she's the neighbor
She was like, hi, how are you doing? Hello
But I'm not too bad and not too sad about the lack of pictures from Carmen. Yeah
I'm a little confused as to why some of your Christian listeners are upset with naked bodies
If you read the first book in the Bible, God actually gets very angry with someone called Adam
So can I pull and then covered himself up with a loincloth
So I think if you want to avoid God's wrath, then get down so I'll spam drop your pants and give me a power book
Just listen it to send to naked photos and I found one of mine taking three years ago
So I've seen that in later four years
I'm the one on the left who smudged against the window
The one on the planet holds in the trophy that's my uncle
I just wanted to help you get the ball rolling and so I think if you look closely enough of the focus
So you'll see that's what my uncle's doing too, right now
I'm not gonna show you this picture. Oh, you got it. No, it will freak you out
I'm not gonna show it to you and it's really him
Well, I guess
Is that much to see, there's not much to see. No, I'm curious
Good to hear from you, Roger. Thanks. Appreciate it
Okay, this is gonna take us into the sweet 16 party
Yeah, yeah, I'm George's discussion of your story about your daughter Christina's 16-year-old birthday party
I start listening to you show away back one way you're playing with your eye river and and fighting with Christina to get out the door one morning
That's the same morning. I was listening to your show and that was when you were in Rotterdam
And then I had to get it to school on time. Yeah, so I recorded the whole thing
Lot of parents identified with that. Oh, yeah, at the same type of discussions with my teenage daughter getting out the door that morning
We just kind of laughed that you were having the same discussions. We were we just had that morning
So it's like that he's short ever since that and let me tell you that's so nice to hear that to know that we're not the only ones
I think parents really love it
I enjoy hearing that parents have the same issues with their teenagers
I'll always compare our stories with the Erika the taxi driver
Amsterdam
We do have a couple of daughters and and the same same story
Judging that you know I've got two teenage daughters and it seems like
a team to this
right now team seem to have these
These are ways to communicate. I am a voice mail
I said
So phones and all that they just seem to be more accomplished and in developing relationships
They're a little less inhibited also because of that so maybe they don't eat drugs
It alcohol so much to lose their inefficient so I
I just think my daughter seems to be you know still your responsible teenager
But they seem to have a better head out of their shoulders than we did
Yeah, I agree
Appreciate yourself. Thanks. Bye. I'll just support it. Bye. Yeah, I agree with that. Yeah, yeah
I would like to compare it to the 16-year-olds in my time
I was a fucking schmuck. Yeah, I was pretty worldly because I was doing part of radio and stuff in Amsterdam
I'd go there and you'll hang out with a lot of interesting people until deep in the United
Playing smart you weren't it
By 16. I was getting that's what I'm so worried about. Yeah, I think well
I did know a lot of shit when I was 16 and I'm sure Christina is very wise to a lot of
So much what is this?
I don't know if it's good. I don't know so we had her sweet 16
Her birthday party Sunday, which was good because it was a bank holiday on Monday
Yeah, yeah, and the UK which means everyone has the as the day off
Everything is closed shops are closed the whole thing is show the whole country shut down
And she invited like 50 or 60 kids a thing. Did you have 50 friends when you were 16? I didn't she has over a thousand friends on my space
You know, and I have to say because I was very nervous the day
Well, but that's related to your childhood. Yeah, yeah, I know you have a childhood trauma where you had a birthday party
Yeah, and all the girls said let's not go. Yeah, and then no one came one bully and you were sitting there with with your
meeting with my next
You understand that this is all about you as nothing to do with no I know, but it's your trauma
It's in there and she said I'm gonna I'm gonna be between 15 and 60 friends and I thought oh my god
I hope they're coming
She was so nervous. I was so nervous the whole day and she was getting dressed up and she looked lovely
Yeah, it was an alicine one in length until I I couldn't believe when you know the ear showed up
A couple of girls had big long and
Bunny's most of the girls looked incredibly hot. It was
It was horrible
Because you know you I found myself like looking at these girls and like oh my god. Oh my god
No, no, yeah
You told me you said oh my god
They're so sexy, but I shouldn't actually it's it's bad and wrong. I know
You can't deny beauty you can't deny sex appeal. Yeah, and but it was not I know what you mean
I saw it too. So we rented a room at the stoke
Yeah, she's a pop-up very very difficult to arrange this doesn't happen often at all in fact
I'm what I'm not in great Britain
Yeah, you cannot get you cannot rent a place that'll have teenagers that just don't want to deal with them
And of course Christina saw it on TV MTV the the 16
My super sweet 16. Yeah, she's like daddy. I want M&M
Yeah, right and
I said yeah, they're not used to that for example. It is a lot of money for a lot of parents
You know to give a party like that and let that's one thing
60 people will have a drink and and it's next this is that this is the real core of the problem is the drink
Because when you're when you're 18 you're legal the drink
When most kids are already drinking when they're 15 at least they want to drink well they are drinking because you can get it
And so what was interesting about this so we did not serve alcohol. We did have
A free bar. We had food. We had balloons. We did the DJ no alcohol. So while the kids, you know
Went out and had a drink around the corner went to the other end of the show there
Anyway, so what then it's not our problem and and they won't get a problem
But I was amazed because everyone had really good time despite the lack of alcohol and they were like 70 kids there
It was outrageous and they and they and they went and you know only a couple crashes
And you know we got rid of them pretty quickly. That was no big deal
No one was fighting no one was puking and it was yeah. It was really enjoyable
They had a great time and I have to say good kids. I love those kids. You know, I mean sweet kids. It's interesting
You know, they do act grown up which is just no new for us in general to have these punks
You know and these kids like pants fallen off their ass, you know tattoos up and down their arms
Yeah, harm is to Mrs. Curry. We could talk to you having week apart
It's a weekend
What was it? Who was it this had them yeah I'm having
What was it Liam? Yeah, so one of the because we had you know
I won't say bounceers, but we had you know people who could
Throw you out if we had to yeah and and so I think it was Liam who had trouble getting in
You said well, you know they thought it was just some some kind of outside
And I said well, dude, how about the tattoos and the piercings that'll probably you know make it a little more difficult in life
You know be prepared for more of this yeah, then of course Liam is our daughter's new girl a boyfriend
Yes, how wonderful. Yes
Yes, 21 fantastic. I'm just totally loving that yeah, yeah, and I just said she's asking me over and over
She wants an approvals. She says do you like him mom? Do you think he's nice and I say
See she doesn't want to hear the truth
Yeah, I don't dislike I have a theory about it by the way. I have a theory. I think he's a little bit too
He's old too old too old too old. He's too old. Now 21 he's too old. Yeah, but I don't trust him
Yeah, I'll tell you why I have a theory about this. What so he he walked her home yesterday
Last night, right and from wherever they were in the in town he walked her home and then
State for a couple minutes and he left but before that he came up here and this is the kind of guy that he's he's a slime ball
Yeah, yeah, that's nice
Well, we already said that at the party when he came to us. Hi, Mr. Mrs. Curry nice to hear slime ball lovely there and he walked away
We said slime ball. Yeah, you know and so he was a little so here's his history
He's been to university which is don't confuse that with you know like he's got a PhD
He's done one year of university. It doesn't mean all that much now
He says he's going into the RAF which I think is great going to the Air Force please far away from my daughter
But he's been on the road for the past year or so as a guitar tech for this is now
It's now getting into the story. He was a guitar tech for a great big fish or some band like this
That Christina thinks is a really cool band
Are you with me now? Yeah, so he walks in here. What is a guitar tech?
It's the guy who tunes the guitar and hands it to the guitar player. Oh, sure. It's a roadie
It's a different word for a roadie. Oh, okay, so but the guitar tech sounds so much better doesn't it?
And so he walks into the office here and he's like wow well impressed with all your
Gold and platinum records and he's like cheap trick and you know he could aerospace and
Yeah, I couldn't believe the Michael Jackson CD and all this stuff. I sent a huh and he's like yeah, you know
I've I've produced these like kind of fumbling about stuff. He produced or whatever and and then we got into this conversation
You know about him going to the RAF and I'm trying to try to draw out of him what his real future plans are, right?
He hasn't actually enrolled in the RAF yet. He's still trying to figure out what he wants to do and I really got
a sense that he was trying to hit me up for some connections
And it was like really apparent, you know, I'm like um wait a minute. All some the bells went off, you know and like
He said something and didn't move on to a topic kind of waiting for me to say hey, I can hook you up or something
Maybe yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
If you want to hear the rest of this and you're listening to us on stars series stars one o two you'll have to go to daily source code dot com to download the rest of the show
So
I think yesterday I really figured it out. I think that he may be look. I'm not I don't want to say he's using Christina
But I think that
He thinks it's very interesting. Yes, very interesting. There's some kind of show this connection
He knows what I do. He knows who you are. Well at the party he was wearing Christina's watch
And I said oh, just Christina's worked. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He said it's amazing all those diamonds and I said they're not diamonds
He said no
Diamonds. I said no. There's spot-off ski crystals. Oh
So oh, she said it were diamonds because Christina you know she doesn't give a shit about diamonds or
Yeah, and he's very polite
You know, he's he's too polite. That's the whole problem. I know
You know, I've got the same thing. I think are you for real? Yeah, and meanwhile I see these guys like like Tony and Dan and furgo
Man, I would give my left not to have her go out with those guys those guys are interesting and and really sweet and of course as Patricia
As Christina would say they're not really handsome
Well, and I disagree because I think they all have something yeah
Interesting, you know, we cannot force no of course not go out
But I really want to kill my own I really want to keep my eye on this
Suddenly we said we thought we both what I
Don't know about this. I don't trust it. It's too tonight. I didn't like it at all
Do not oh you have such a nice house Mrs. Curry. It is amazing. It looks so amazing and I thought you know
It's almost like this he it was almost like he made the wind up and he tried to pitch
Last night by saying yeah
You know, he's really looking for a gig and trying to you know do some more guitar tech work and yeah, but you know
Maybe the RAF so this guy is not going into your force. This is not an Air Force guy. Oh
But he he shaved his head already for it
Fool shit. Yeah, that's has nothing. I hate to I hate it. I love it men with hair
You told him that didn't you? I mean sorry, but for people you tell him that?
Yeah, I said grow some hair looks horrible grow some hair shrink your penis
away from my step away from my teenage daughter
Yeah, and it's so sad because I look at her and she said mom because she really she runs my opinion
But no, she wants you approval approval and it does not want your opinion now approval. Yeah, but why I mean
Because she knows because she knows that this guy is not so I need some help here
Want to know what do I know just go with the flow or well you have to I mean you can't do anything
But I do want to I just don't want it to be really disappointed because this guy might turn out to
I just and I know Christina is very smart and she is very intelligent
She's very little a little bit older than other maybe 16-year-olds
In some regards in in in a certain way and so that's why she likes to talk with older
kids and older boys so I
Don't know anyway
It was a good party. I'm so worried
I'm so worried but the party was a great success
But it was and I'm so happy for her that she had her sweet 16-party
Yeah, you know because it when we lived in in in in Belgium she was quite along with her horse
She had her horse and she had a couple of friends but not as much as and many as she's
Apparently quite popular
Yeah, and you know and I look around the room and I know most of those kids too, which is nice
Yeah, and the and the and I got to say
Very well-behaved and all very nice kids. Yeah, and they're and they're you know anywhere from 15 to 19 and they were thinking us at the end of the unit
It was very actually scary
Incredible. Yeah, they're all thank you very much for inviting us for having me and we could party
Well, that's English for you. I have to say and that's very nice, you know
Although Americans are like that too, and then there were some playgrounds some plaque is out in the parking lot
Honk and their horn and midnight
Like yo Eminem
It's real I say no, I'm shut up. I'm shut up. I'm an amp
They look like I know Eminem
Okay, well enough about this. Yeah, I got some feedback for you here. Hi Adam. This is Charles Media wine guest 30 years old from London
Just in the future and yourself chat away on my bit
Always catching up on the get see
Which is also not going to see the crown jewels which I always thought the crown jewels
Were the the power of London, but then maybe there's crowns and jewels and dresses and stuff
Bucking up house who knows I'm not interested in that I guess because I'm a great. Let's face it
Why would I pay money to someone rich to go and look at their wealth? It doesn't make sense to me
There you go. Yeah, that's what I thought too. But you did it. Yeah, I'm not a Brit. Oh, this is true
Yeah, I'm just you know visitor you do pay taxes visitor
Miss visitor
Council tax you know, have you ever heard of it? Yeah, you should do believe me. You pay taxes
No, I mean, I'm not a Brit yet. That's what I'm five years until you come you want to do that in five years
I think so. Yeah, it takes five years and then they check. I'm fed up of being Dutch
I think that they do they want to hold for the country. They bring you know all the yanks come and look at their shit
Bring it a lot of you. Hey, baby. I don't know oh my god
16-year-old. Hello, baby. Hello, you're bitching about me. I totally heard it from Donald
Not about you. Don't mention about Liam
We're talking about Liam. We weren't we were not bitching about Liam. No, not bitching what? Discussing
He is a big slime ball come a little bit close to the microphone. Yes, it is
He is he's a slime ball. What are you going to go? It's town. I'm going to walk. Don't tell me who you're going to see
I'll tell you he said hi. I'll give you a regards
I want to find out when he's going into the RAF
That's what I want to find. What about your allowance by the way? Don't you have an allowance? I get that in a few days. So you have no more money
No
It's like mom give me money. I need money. I'm just going to buy some foundation. Foundation for a face
Foundation because the foundation could be also in here
So anyway, we're not saying that we dislike Liam. We just think that he
feels like other guys might be more right for you
And I know you don't give a shit. They're not ugly. I know you don't give a shit. I don't give a shit
But this guy yeah, I do
Furgus, that's why I love him. I love Furgus. You like to Judy Garland. I love does he cry when you do
I love him. I love Furgus. Furgus is the man for you. I will buy you
He's saying he's on west west side store. Of course he did
Listen when when you're 18 and you want to have an apartment if you're living with Furgus, I'll pay for it
Well, but it's Liam. Will you buy me a box? You're not going to live with Liam. That is not happening
That's worth in care of it. No, it's not going to happen. You kind of wanted to get one of those
Caravans in the backyard
What? What? Can you have cable? Free view. Okay, free view. But
So, but he's a guitar tech Christina. What's what's the name of the band? No, he played guitar in the fan
Yeah, but he was a guitar tech for a real big fish real big fish. Oh, who are that?
He was so, but he's a he's a roadie. He's not a roadie. That a guitar tech is a roadie. He was a guitar tech once for one band
Yeah, but so I talked to him yesterday and he's he's like falling over me
Slime dripping out of the corners of his mouth going like, oh, I'm so impressed with all your it's because he's golden platinum
Impressed yeah, but I just get a feeling he's a little too much nice. He's from Birmingham
Oh, is that it? Yes, are there slime balls? No, so what's he doing now? Does he have a job?
He does but I forgot what it is
I wasn't listening. Wait, so this is the guy that your boyfriend you don't know what his job is. What?
Not a boyfriend yet. What even is not your boyfriend yet? Not yet. Oh
So we can still intervene. We can still intervene. Well, but he still he doesn't want to be your boyfriend. Oh, he does
But because I haven't said this yet. Very good. Keep it that way.
But wasn't you working in the coffee shop for now, but he's going back to Birmingham. So yeah, when is he going back to Birmingham?
Where is he living? I just want to know about it. There's a Birmingham, but right now he's staying at gas because he's only here temporarily
And who's? Gav. Do we know Gav? He had the balloons.
That's his buddy. That's Gav. Wait, but that's not one of your buddies. Is this it is? Oh, okay
You gave the drunk guy who let the balloons go at the end of the drunk. Yeah, and I was just that the
Blond would destroy too. Oh, who was that then? Who's Gav? Gav is the big guy.
Yeah, he's all right. Yeah. Oh, the fat gav's cool. Yeah, he seemed okay. Yeah, he's okay. So he's staying at gavs and then and then
How long is he how long is he gonna stay there? He's only staying here for this week and he has to go back to take care of his mom
What's wrong with his mom? She had some sort of hip operations. She was on the phone tour
Okay, and then he's gonna what is he going into the RAF? Well, he has to do his training first
I know what one he's doing is training a January
I can try now
Yeah, bring your room over here. Mom will train his dad. He's a nice guy. You're just
I'm not saying he's not nice. Do you understand why first of all you're dad, okay? So you're just saying why bring it on
That one of those part of it. I think there's a difference between 21 and 16. No, because they act about 16
He acts did he have a car? No, he doesn't have a car, does he? He could drive you out
He doesn't drive here and Gilbert, okay? Good
Very happy. Can I go in the car with Dan? No, no, no, why?
You can get a driving lesson soon. Yeah, but Dan's a good driver. You're Dan.
On the the mortgages filled with girls who went with a good driver. Dan. All right, so please now
I'll pick you up. I'll be your personal show for you can take a cab you can do whatever you want
Don't get in the car with anyone please. I beg of you. This is after school special
This is an after school special
Seriously, you don't need to go in the car. I'll come I'll come pick you up and I'll drive behind Dan
And I won't say anything. They're no experience. No, that it's just the experience baby
That's what you need first. Can I go please? Can I go please? Can I go please?
Do any of this sink in? Did any of this sink in? Did any of it go meet Liam? I'll see you later.
Hi
Lucas, I love you
Oh, I don't know. I don't ever want to taste Liam when I kiss you
Please be tight. I've been on time for dinner this time
Nice money. Okay. 630
6 and 7
Dan and Dan and Dan
Went so much trouble. A lot
And I'm pulling up her t-shirt every time. Yeah, I know that. I'm pulling it up. I'm pulling it up
I mean
All right, let me just take care of a couple of things here portions of this podcast brought to you by
Acura listen to the target cast for the Acura RDX SUV at acurapodshow.com
And this is the third finalist in the earthlink had challenge. I don't have to explain what this is right
How memories everyone hated the original commercials and then we said I'm making yourself
Yeah, so this this may be the $2,000 prize win. No, earthlink got some bad press
One day announced that they were installing a free mune wifi access in New Orleans
Jeer about this or eat it in the news people started blogging and saying great now they have free internet
But no food or shelter
You know, I said that was somehow earthlinks fault. Okay. Now if I'm a large company looking to do something to help people in need
Okay, and I know how to do a thing
Internet service for example
Don't you think that's what I'd bring to the table and offer up?
Maybe
Why would earthlink offer to rebuild houses or provide food when they have no expertise in those fields, right?
I for one think it's great that they're doing something down there
But you know who fought them the telcos the cable companies of course
Then you about a new internet provider give earthlink a try at least they're trying to help and not get in the way a progress
That was pretty good. I like that one. Yeah, that's good. That's good
I actually didn't even know earthlink tried to do that
Mm-hmm. We could train a victims
It's almost one year since Katrina. I know and still fucked up down there. Oh, very it was just on the news
Yeah, but you know about people are still walking around with with no homes nothing. No help. No job nothing
They're crying. Yeah, yeah, yeah around crying and if you see
How it looks over there?
We haven't noticed but there's no coverage so people forget about it people forget about it because you know
It's more important to hear about it. Yeah
I'm thinking about it all the time. Yeah, of course. I mean
No, I'm not thinking about all the time, but if I see the pictures I think that's my point is you only think about it when you see the pictures
Yeah, actually yeah, you do
Okay, what are we out now? Well still no no house
No house
Look at the quality of your problem
Yeah, just said there people in in Louisiana New Orleans who have no house really no house no
Yeah, and now you're complaining about not having a house. Yeah. I know we're gonna take a look at one today though
Was that seam or place or whatever it is? Sydney Sydney place yeah, wherever that is. I don't know
So I guess the two houses we put bids on
We're not gonna get I don't know you know what we didn't hear anything from the last one
Every time we
It's too low playing this game
You know what I'm not just not gonna pay that kind of money for a piece of shit that we're gonna it is a piece of shit
But now but now we're looking a little bit beyond the town center
Yeah, maybe looking at five miles outside of gilford and that did open up a bunch of possibilities didn't
Yeah, we're a little bit of you know fed up with because looking in gilford and they don't want to move
They don't move
Been here for 20 30 years. They don't want to go any of them. They don't want to move and they're right
And when they do finally move they leave you know a piece of shit
Yeah, and we have to pay a lot of money for it
Well, and then in addition you got to fix it up to the way you want if you just want to
Gilford is popular
Very popular
Yeah, very popular. I think wherever we go as long as it's not Birmingham. I'll find with it
nowhere near that fucking medium guys
A new song from panic on the disco on the podcast music network. I write sins not tragedies
Think it like this one
The
This way, I'm in technically a merry-to-save
Well, this calls for a song
For the champagne
Oh, wow, the fact
Well, I'll look at it this way
I'm in technically a merry-to-save
Well, this calls for a toast
So, for the champagne, for the champagne
I like time in, with the having few people ever heard of
Closing a garden door, no
Much better to see, it's kind of pink
But this is the voice of the rest, and now I lay
I like time in, because I like to keep people ever heard of
Closing a garden door, no
Much better to see, it's kind of pink
With a sense of love
So, for the champagne
I like time in, how the people ever heard of
Closing a garden door, no
Much better to see, it's kind of pink
With a sense of love of the voice of the rest, and now I lay
I like time in, having few people ever heard of
Closing a garden door, no
Much better to see, it's kind of pink
But this is the voice of the rest, and now I lay
I like time in, how the people ever heard of
Closing a garden door, no
Much better to see, it's kind of pink
With a sense of love of the rest, and now I lay
I like time in, how the people ever heard of
Closing a garden door, no
Much better to see, it's kind of pink
With a sense of love of the rest, and now I lay
Feels like I'm going to sing the song
A beautiful song, I'm going to sing the song
And I got the disco, wow!
Wow!
That good
Oh, 7 years brilliant!
I wonder if they played on the regular radio in the picture
I love it
Yeah, I tried to see those guys. They were they were supposed to play in San Francisco
I was there last time. Yeah, what did they do? I loved that cello
Charlie's not a thing. Oh, I'm always crazy about that. Yeah, it does sound so much
Since Elo
Yes, since the days of Elo
You're old again. Yes, I am
But they'd always did it. They would have actually the first who did it. Elo. Yeah, hello. Yeah, yeah, just one love it
This is this was really good. Very good. I like you like that go to the podcast music now work on this
All the songs bullshit. You know you won't I'm gonna find this song. Hey, Adam says
Who the heck told me this?
Orbital box
You think it's difficult to move or buy a house in England try the province of Quebec, Canada in the city of Montreal
All least and rentals are regulated by the municipal government contracts expire every year on June the 30th
Everyone who has to move has to do it in that period Montreal goes crazy with moving trucks
No, yeah, so just like here when you have a closing you could have five families moving on the same closing
No, they were the rentals like everyone's moving around on the 30th of was it 30th of June?
It's completely nuts. Yeah, interesting at their direct. Yeah, it is. Yeah
All right, baby. Well, this was a very nice parenting moment a parenting podcast
Just help but we are parents
It was no I think we're very cool. Yeah, well, we woke up and we said crap. We're parents. Yeah, I know
And I always wanted to be a mom
But now now it starts
You know, I just imagine that so mass hole on a podcast keeps saying that he wants naked pictures of your daughter. How would you feel?
Yeah, yeah
I got I got an email from Carmen's mom
You're dead. Yes, I did she's a you know a Carmen found out about podcasting through her mom. Oh
I'm what do your mom say
Did you hate you? No, no, she's really nice, but yeah, there's some mom mom tone in there
I caught it. Oh, no. Oh, yeah, she's she's got a beauty page and daughter
I'm sure she pushed her into it
Well, that's what you got. I mean, and people what's exactly about her naked that you know, he's a little bit
She didn't say anything about that. Yeah, so we'll talk later this week
It's a good one, actually. What would you say? What I think about somebody wants to see your daughter naked?
No, I think about these things all the time. I do realize the trash that comes out of my mouth
Believe it or not. I do actually think about it after I've already said it. Are you you know?
I know you you don't believe me. It just sounds good. No, I don't mean it. No, I don't mean it
He wanted to talk for the guys. Oh, I don't mean it
No, I don't mean I'm just being honest. Yeah. Yeah, that's true. That's all I'm doing. You just a man
That's it a man. It's a man
world
Okay, so thank you for joining me once again. It was so nice. Oh and thank you for having me at any time
Make sure you check out perversion for profit my video show
Yeah, you can find that at pfp
Papa fucks truck papa
That pod show.com. I had a preview. Did you like it? I loved it. Yeah, we got a little a shot of you at the cottage
Doing a fly by we got that in there. Yeah, yeah, yeah, I don't think I'm saying okay
All right, everybody talking tomorrow. Bye
I forgot to do this very important stuff
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from podshow and line-white networks