Good morning. Good afternoon or good evening. This is Trucker Two Times and I am
listening to the Daily Source Code number 480C.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio
content in my ears. I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Like on Scoop is still to see our truly 486.
Well imagine as I'm facing the pews in a church called Resort and I can't help but to hear
I can't help but to hear in exchanging of words. What a beautiful wedding. What a beautiful
wedding. This is a bright day to a way out. But what a shame what a shame the poor
I think we are married to save for this call for our death.
Well look at it this way. I mean, technically our marriage is saved.
Well let's call for a toast. So for the champagne for the champagne.
I can't help but to hear in exchanging of words.
I write sins, not tragedies, panic at the disco, heard that song this morning on radio
one and thought, I got to play that and guess what I can because it's on the podcast
music network.
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
Football Friday.
We were fucked up beyond role repair, winding up the week coming to you from a curry
cottage later than usual.
I actually haven't been entirely true for you guys.
I posted on curry.com that had some stuff I needed to take care of.
Yesterday I was indeed in the city, so sorry, it's the blackberry after I moved that.
Yesterday I was indeed in the city, a whole bunch of meetings winding up with even a dinner
meetings, I didn't get home until around 11.30, half-11 as we say.
And I said that I had more stuff to do today.
Actually, I'm going to be working in the city over the weekend today with something different.
And I didn't want to tell you until after the fact, because I didn't want anyone really
to know that today I had concocted an evil plan with the win commander, win commander William
of course my flight instructor, who had finished a huge bunch of maintenance on my aircraft
the Delta Shira and it was an Antwerp which of course is across the pond there in Belgium.
He had done that while I was in the States in San Francisco and it was ready.
Now he was happy to fly it over of course, but that usually means that he has to be flown
back and then the aircraft has to come back again.
It's only about an hour each way, so it's actually fun to do that kind of back and forth
ferry.
Now, he's being a Friday, there's no way that Captain Dan could accompany me for the flight.
So William and I had decided that if the weather was nice, I would do my big channel crossing
solo.
And I did it.
So I got back around five o'clock, so right now it's like six, six, forty five.
And I'm still just totally buzzing.
I hadn't told Patricia because the last thing I wanted was her being worried all day.
I didn't figure it now, I'll tell her later.
And I was surprised that she hadn't figured out that something was up because she knew
William was coming over, she knew I was going to go flying, but I don't think she really
thought it through.
So how was William getting back?
So I flew him back, first we did a couple, I did a couple of solo landings over on the
continent, just to make sure I was comfortable with a different weight distribution being
by myself.
Oh, that aircraft is such a performer when I was just one person, man, that thing is fast.
And so I took off from Antwerp, went up to flight level five, five all the way past
Manson, went through a little bit of IMC, which means I was in the clouds for a little
bit climbing up to that flight level, which is essentially five and a half thousand feet.
And maybe about a minute or so in clouds on the way down, and it was very busy, it always
gets busy, particularly Friday afternoon, everybody's coming home, you get that corridor
from that link to Big and Hill, Farmboro, another big place where lots of private jets
go in.
And of course, then I turned into Farrogues, which is our little Biggles Airfield.
And everything was great.
And of course, the last two minutes are the most important because that's when you make
the most mistakes and really football, which I was not planning on doing.
There was kind of, everything was fantastic and I'm going downwind, ready to turn on
to base and then finals for my landing.
And yeah, some other guys like saying, oh, the aircraft turning five all these low is
very, very low.
I'm like, and you think about, and you hear that, and I knew we was talking about me.
And like, whoa, what am I doing something wrong?
I look, and I'm 900 feet, and so, and he just gaping through the radio.
And I just said, excuse me, I'm 900 feet, very comfortable.
And even the tower said, hey, aircraft is a perfect height, no worries.
It was just, you know, God, why do people do that?
It's a fucking stupid.
And he was like more like an accusatory tone than a warning tone.
Anyway, nice move landing, and then told Patricia, call everybody else.
So I'm still really, really buzzing.
This is a big deal for me, certainly, probably for any pilot, because there's a lot of unknowns.
It's, it's a lot of water, a lot of water you're flying over.
So anyway, still got tons of stuff to go through with you today.
I've done the preparation, but as I said, I'm still kind of literally with my head in the
sky.
So let's just discover together what I've got lined up for you here today.
Okay.
You were, and this is Donny and Donny from Jezzy.
You were, and I heard you were in New York, and you didn't stop by and say hi to the boys
in Jezzy.
Come on, you got a Jezzy number.
Yeah, Jezzy number.
I don't know what's up with that item, but I happy ADSC486 anyway.
Well, he didn't say hi.
He didn't even call me.
I don't know what's going on.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I apologize.
I was sick.
I told you.
I had the flu.
It was really horrible.
There's a whole bunch of people who are angry at me.
Oh, you were New York, it didn't call.
I was freaking out with the flu.
It was horrible.
I felt so shitty, and I'm just now finally kind of getting over it.
Of course, I didn't get a flu shot.
I told you Patricia got a flu shot.
She didn't get sick.
She did feel kind of a little funky for a few hours in her arm hurt a little bit.
But that was it.
Although a lot of people have sent me comments about getting flu shots.
Hey, Adam.
Long, long, long time listener.
First time caller.
This is Gary LePoint from Colin from Michigan in the United States.
You were just talking about the influenza, the flu shot, and mentioned that it's a different
batch over here.
I'm pretty sure it's a different batch, depending on where you're calling by location.
Also, which I've never really understood how to mix a different batch up for this section
of the U.S.
and a different batch up for a different, for another section of the U.S.
So, just because you mentioned that, made me think of it.
I've never called and I've had your number in my speed dial ready to go when I had
something to say.
Thanks.
Thanks for putting on a great show almost every day.
I mean, it's a great show all the time, but the show is only almost every other day.
And I'm a folder.
Thanks.
Bye.
I don't know.
I hate it when people say, like, almost every day.
You do great.
Almost great.
You can't quite get a show at every day.
Yeah, crap.
Life gets in the way.
No, I'm saying.
Speaking of the voicemail number, standby to jot something down here.
I wonder.
Would that sound better with cowbell?
Sounds the same with it without.
60, a plus one, 201, 65, 65, 65, 7.
More about the flu shots.
Hey, yeah.
It's the way for model.
I'm just listening to 484 and you made the comment about not getting a flu shot.
I've got a flu shot for many years.
And yes, I'm trying to time I have felt happy.
But I haven't had the flu.
Now, as the report in the financial times about the people dying from the flu shot,
yeah, this was, was it a couple of folks in Israel, I believe, died after receiving
their flu shot like five, all from the same batch that's what this call is referring to.
Some people do die every year from flu shots and other shots and vaccinations because of egg allergies.
Usually these people don't know their allergic to eggs.
The other thing, and this is what drives me up the wall, is journalists will tend to
sensationalize stuff.
How many people in Israel died from influenza last year?
Think about that one.
Anyways, but I hope the good work.
And yes, folder and maybe a little bit of even when it comes to people and miscutes, statistics and signs.
Be cool, man.
Bye bye.
You think?
Maybe just a little anal?
Yeah.
Well, I don't think financial times is not reporting on it as some sensationalist party,
but it's worth noting they came from the same batch, so probably from the same manufacturer.
And that can usually mean a recall.
Man, if you see what's happened to fucking Sony, I mean,
we're calling 8 million batteries now.
I'm still waiting for them to recall the battery on my laptop and my bio, which has not been overheating,
has not burst into flames yet, but it's also not been put on the recall list.
But yeah, the thing about eggs, that is kind of interesting.
I didn't learn about about the egg part until, I think maybe six months ago or something,
all vaccinations.
And of course, this is in regards to the avian bird flu, which we don't hear a lot about.
Isn't it time to scare us without again?
All vaccinations, all vaccines, essentially, are created in eggs, which is why stuff can't be created very, very quickly.
It literally has to cultivate in eggs, which is, I think, 1950's technology,
and there's a lot of work and a lot of money going into trying to figure out how to cultivate
vaccines outside of eggs.
But I guess that would be why people then essentially die if they're allergic to eggs.
That sucks if you're allergic to eggs.
Cranky.
Let me see.
Oh, yes, little promo.
Aw, I'm modem.
www.ordiancrossings.com.
Music production qualifications online.
The best place on the net of pro-ordian news, interviews, and tutorials.
Hangouts, make friends and discuss production techniques in our mighty forums, from digital oil
to mixing and mastering.
We have a course for you.
All you need is a computer and a design to learn.
www.ordiancrossings.com.
A way into the business for you.
Yoza.
Very professional.
I'm looking for a...
This is a problem when you're in the city one day, and you're crossing the English channel the next.
You don't get around to the email.
I think I have two Gmail pages, so that's about 200 emails.
I quickly just scan through and see if there's anything I wanted to put in the show.
I really need to get it out, obviously.
This is something that really, really tickled me when it came in.
This came in yesterday morning.
Hi Adam.
I'm not going to say who...
I'll skip one.
Hi Adam.
I just wanted to say thanks for playing building our own future on your podcast show.
And big in me up.
Thanks for the help with the tour dates as well.
If I can be of assistance, best wishes.
Howard.
That would be Howard Jones.
I thought that was so awesome.
Because of course, how are Jones?
I know him from the early 80s.
I've played so many of his songs on the radio.
I've played so many of his videos.
I know.
Actually, people under a certain age don't know who Howard Jones is.
And they've played the song form, which of course is in the pod state music network.
And go, that's pretty cool.
And some of them say, oh yeah, I think, oh, oh yeah, that's the one.
That's the guy.
So not only is it just fantastic that he sent that note,
but then there's a PS to it.
PS, he says, I'm a folder.
I never thought about Howard, but make sense.
Here's building our own future.
Time for us to sneak down and talk.
Try to build on your understanding.
What we feel is we all today.
The moment we talk to each other.
Between the light and the dark side.
So take a step in this place.
Got a real building our own future.
Just for now.
Day by day, free to choose a life.
It's better for all of us.
Putting people's lives at the top.
There's the first consideration.
Changing in the heart of just one of the world of things.
Time makes us.
Don't give it up.
To the face of the force around us, we decide.
Between the end and the outside.
So take a step in this place.
Got a real building our own future.
Just for now.
Day by day, free to choose a life.
It's better for all of us.
Sons and colors.
When there's a father's words,
When there's a brother's words,
If there's a brother's words,
So take a stand in this place
God will build in our own future
Just when I want to take my day
Free to choose a life
This is a musical genius
I gotta say
First, it's a folder
Our Jones building our own future
He's on tour, tour dates will be
You can find those in the show notes
DailySourceCode.com
Or even on his own page
The pod set music network
Which of course you can find a link to in the show notes
I don't know how much of the production
How it does himself
But oh man, that snare is just
BAM!
It just slaps away so hard
I love it
Love it
I was just thinking
Defolders and scrunchers
Prefer in macar windows
I don't know if you're a folder
And you've been a dick neck
For most of your computer use
Until recently
But I'm a folder
And I'm a mac guy
So everything about that
Everyone
Very interesting
Is it?
Is there a correlation between being a folder and a mac user?
Hmm, let me think about that
People talk about it baby
Sam doing it wrong, doing it wrong
Don't you ever blame it, don't worry
Because I'm a white and white
And white and white in my bone
Come on, sing along now
Because I'm a folder
I'm a scruncher
I'm a roller
And I'm a buncher
But do my business on the throne
I'm a sitter
I'm a spanner
I'm a left-right hander
It's nice to know
I'm not alone
I don't know man
I don't think so
Because that would mean
There's only 5% of the population
Is a folder
And I think it's much much higher than that
But
You know, and I'm a windows guy now
Still a folder
But I think it's a very, very, very valid question
I'm sure everyone will be happy to tell me all about it
If you're a mac user, do you follow the scratch?
Hey Adam, I was just driving, my parents are driving
And I'm in the back seat
Listening to the daily source code
Listening to your tea town to stuff
It was really interesting
Right next to me there was this little pool
The dog freaked out
I guess he was hearing the tones out of my iPod
Maybe I was listening to a little loud
But that was cool
The dog was freaking out
And then when I turned off the
Turned off the door
The dog just calmed down
And this was a car across the way
All right, thank you
And a folder of course
Keep up the good work
Thanks, bye
Dude, dude
This is really interesting
Okay
Whatever you're listening to the show now
You're in your MP3 player, your computer or your iPod
Yeah, iPod, I guess
Right, because even I have
You had your headphones, your earbuds
Okay, go get your dog
Man, go get your dog
What I want you to do is get something to record with
Okay
Do you have anything to record with
Like a recorder?
Otherwise just call in the voicemail number
Okay, we'll use that as the recording
I'll give you a second
Cause I know you already have a pre-program
So I want you to call up
Now get your dog
Okay, get your dog close
Let's see if it actually is true
If the dog really is responding to
To Pete Townsend
Okay, hold on a second
Now turn it up to about the same volume you had
With the flaming lips and his tongue
And let's, and I want you to record the dog's reaction
Okay, here we go
I'll just play a little bit of Bob O'Reilly
Pete Townsend the flaming lips
Live
And in acoustic concert
Here we go
Okay, I want to hear this dog yalllan
Oh
Is he responding yet?
Well, is he responding?
Come here fight up
Come here
Excellent
We'll see that turns out
Okay, I don't know if he's calling from Bucket
He's calling, I heard you can't find one down
There in the, in Britain
All right, let's watch that
We found that our spondon
There's cut you neatly amongst the coffee creamer
You would spend, I see it near the sugar
The sugar set the juice
But because I'm a new flavor pack
Actually cut in between the creamers
Where I'm a coffee
So they can have my job on it
I pick up some two to that spondomooker
It's tough
Bye
Okay, time to get serious on your ass
Of course
It's actually, I think it's not too serious
It's kind of cool for a food bar
I
I received a comment from bicycle mark
And bicycle mark was talking about
Citizen Journalism
And I gave out
I think was Wednesday's show
And I basically talked about my
My opinion, my thoughts about Citizen Journalism
And what it entails and what it means
And what it's for
And if it's functional, if it actually works
If it does anything for us
And
I got lots of feedback
I haven't even gone to the voicemail for today
And I'm sure there's a ton more
So I think this will probably be going for a day or two
Let me just quickly restate my opinion
Now the, the concept of Citizen Journalism
It's okay
You know, I've no problem with that
What I said was it's like sounding off
And it is sounding off
It's giving your opinion
Sometimes it's exposing
Or it's shining a different light
On an issue
And it's usually related to politics in the world around us
Or the world around you
You Citizen Journalists
Which is all fine
And certainly a great contrast
For what the mainstream media
Is either able or capable
Or willing to show us feed us, etc
And there's all kinds of manipulation and stupid stuff
Going on in mainstream media
And there's a lot of manipulation and stupid stuff
Going on in Citizen Journalism
I don't take anything
More than face value initially
But my entire point was
I want us to get ready to move on
We're great at
At the being voices of opposition
Voices of truth
Co-Truth
Voices with a different type of flashlight
So it's shining on the issue in a different way
I think we're really good
Bicycle Mark is great at it
What I'm looking for is people who are going to go do something
Do something and then use our alternative media
To get there
Very much like mainstream media
Uses advertising to a like presidents
Can't we get someone to use this platform
To get into office
But really use it
Not have some guys set it up
But it being an integral part of their leadership platform
Let me first play you bicycle marks re-tort
Not really re-tort
But his response to what I was talking about on Wednesday
Hi Adam
Bicycle Mark here again
Just wanted to continue the discussion
That you sort of began or that we began
On the issue of people
Regular people
Using podcasts to do what I call citizen journalism
And you perhaps rightfully criticize the name
It is subject to criticism
But I wanted to continue the discussion and say
In many ways I think podcasting is a perfect venue
To make alternatives to the media
You called it sounding off
In fact, you're somewhat right
It is a lot of sounding off
But the beauty of this as you've so often have said
When it comes to music and other art and areas
The beauty is that we don't have to just take the mainstream
What they give to us, be it the New York Times
Or CNN
Granted, they have a staff and they have some standards
Although those standards are very questionable
As we've seen them reduced in the last few years
To a very low in some cases
The beauty of podcasts as you well know
Much like blogs is that we can do our own reporting
From where we are, with what we know
Or using all the resources available to us
Resources like people in our lives
Or that we meet whatever
And in that sense, we can provide a news report
Yes, that report could have opinion in it
And we make no secrets of it
I think in podcasting we've always been honest
As you have
So we'd make no secret of our bias or our opinion
But the job is for the listener
Just like with weblogs
The listener, the reader, or the viewer for a video blog
Has to go and decide for themselves
And hopefully consult multiple sources
That's the way this works, right?
In some ways I know that you know what I'm talking about
But I wanted to bring this up, I wanted to continue this discussion
Because I think it's a very important area
When it comes to society and podcasts and media
I think there is a role and it's growing
But very slowly and yes, we're completely drowned out
By the mainstream podcasts that provide some good
But although also some questionable reporting
So I'd like to hear your response to this
And I'm certainly up for anyone else's opinion
In this whole discussion
But citizen journalism or podcast journalism
Like radio journalism only in a new way in a different style
I think it really does have a place
I hope so I've been working on it for quite a while now
See you later
So of course it has a place
And of course it's opinionated
And of course it's going to be right and wrong
Just like anyone else who's reporting
Guess what I'm saying is
I'd just like to see a leader actually use
Use the media, the mediums
That we have shown the way
Showing the light on how this can be used
For all types of ideas and platforms
And movements
I'd just like to see one leader once
Just really use the technology
A couple of them maybe blogging
It's like I've got a lot of email from people saying
What's his name?
Well I'm totally blanking on it
Barack Obama, is that it?
Barack?
He's got a podcast
Oh cool
I'm starting to really like this guy
Hi, this is the podcast for May 4th
See that's exactly what I mean
It's just a not dedicated to it
And it doesn't just have to be politics
Here's an example of what I mean
I'm going to give you an actual example
Of the type of citizen journalism
I don't want to call it citizen journalism
Of a use of podcasting
That is someone doing something
And getting something done
And podcasting it and letting everyone else know about it
Which I think is much more powerful than just saying
Hey, it's fucked up and swars you land
Boy, it's no good
People are dying
Now this is the kind of stuff you want
Adam, how you make it?
It's Paul Nichols in podcast pool.com
Listen to your show where you talk about
Citizen journalism
And I think you said
Why do people really do stuff with this?
You know make a difference
Well I accept
Probably a lot of people don't make a difference
But some do
And just by way of a quick demonstration
Really I suppose
I'm flying to Swaziland next week
To go to the AIDS orphanage
I did that last year
Took the laptop
And the many of this player
Everything
Thought it'd just be a great thing to talk about
But it suddenly dawned on me
When I was there
The plight of these poor kids
Have lost the mums and dads
And literally are dying on the streets
Talking into the microphone
Literally sat in a mud house
The most bizarre sort of experience
Gosh it
Just moves me to tears
Thinking about it
Blimey
But for that
But for sort of talking about that
People wouldn't have heard
About the plight of these poor kids
In Maban
And I just wonder you know
People are doing this
Probably up and down the place
It's just that that small pockets
And people don't really hear about it
But gosh it was so well received
The BBC broadcast that
We raised some money
In fact
And built a children's home
On the back
On the back of going out
They're not necessarily with the podcast
But folks helped
And just very quickly
Podcast conference this year
John Buckley
Who
There's a great podcast
called Disident Thoughts
Great podcast
Very intelligent guy
Talks back in spurious theories
But in a very sensible way
Very thought provoking
He's leading the discussion
So charmers there from the open rights group
Chris Philanx from BBC
And they'll makin' tough from the Guardian
So you'll get your chance to listen to
What sits in journalism is all about
But if you tune into my show next week
PodcastPull.com
You'll really see this in action
Okay mate
All the best
See you
Bye bye now
Yo mate, thank you
Fantastic
See this is exactly what I'm talking about
He's not just sitting in home
Saying oh it's really horrible
These orphans
He went there
Okay
He actually went there
And used the medium
While he was involved in it
He was in the middle of it
By the way
I do this much of that as every other person
I read something in the news
And I sound off about it
You know
And that to me is really a form of citizen journalism
Now
When
Oh when it comes to podcasting
I'm really using the platform
And I practice what I preach
You know
I do what I say
And I mean what I say
I say what I do
I do what I mean to say
I really do it
I mean the middle of it
And that is when it becomes in my mind
Much more compelling
Like a Corey Lidal
La
Sounding off about that
Of citizen journalism
And even I wasn't
Right
And at least not the first time
But what I think what I found was
That as I started listening to other
podcast aviation podcasts
I was finally able to hone in
And what it was all about
And I was able to aggregate that
And I was able to contribute to my knowledge
The conversation
Really in the middle of it
So I'm going on
So if you're in politics
I want the same thing
And if you're going to
And I really think that that is
That's a big issue in the United States of America
Is everyone is happy to sound off about it
From the cab driver to the podcast
Or
But do something
Run
Why not
That's really important
I will definitely
Anyone who's going to run
Seriously for office
I don't give a shit
What party?
What ticket?
Anything to promote the shit out of you
If you're right in the middle of it
And if you're
If you're really using the
The medium that we have
To get the message out
It'll work
I know it will work
There's a I got another like
Three and a half minute comment
I'm going to save that until next week
It was pretty funny though
Here I'll let you hear the beginning
I had him this is Jeffrey the gay expat
From the gay expat
I got to play that one
Jeffrey the gay expat
Jeffrey
Well
I won't do that
On Monday
Because what am I?
What am I at now?
Thirty-five minutes?
Yeah and I still have
Oh shoot
Oh second
How could I have not done that?
I didn't even queue up
The official musicologist
That is of course
Very bad
Almost
I can't here we go
Okay it's ready to go
But first
This
Oh Adam
This is also
But I
In some of California
I have a Young Spursus
Ah
Well since you have that
Now we're from our spine here
It's the Yanks
This is the Brits
We'll drive each other crazy
But everybody knows that
It's apparent to see
That just like you and me
It's the Yanks
And the Brits
The Yanks
Versus the Brits
Mind the gag
I'm for you
I've been watching a lot of content
On the Discovery Channel recently
And they have a lot of segments
That were originally BVC segments
So they are your broadcasts
Think that you're in the state
And I've noticed that the announcer
The narrator of these pieces
Very often
Uses a multiplier
To indicate less fat
For example
There's a show about Australia
They said Australia has
30 times less population
In England
And they do it regularly
And it must be a British isp
Because it sounds completely flat
To my ears
I would say for example
Australia has one 30
The population of England
I would only use a multiplier
When it's more
Like I would say
That you know a hammer
Cost 3 times as much as a Toyota
Or something like that
So
I'd be interested to hear your observations on that
And those are the listeners
To the Chacha
And you can also catch my podcast
www.selfoc.com
The people places of handsome politics
Of South Orange County California
Take care
Okay
Hey, that sounds pretty interesting
I'll check out your podcast
You may be one of those people
Who's not just a citizen journalist
But actually doing something
Very interesting observation
Totally agree with it
And it really caught my ear
When I heard you talk about that
That does seem to be something
Very distinct distinct different
In our language
With the Brits Will indeed say
30 times less
Whereas I think your times always
Seems like the outcome should be more
It's interesting
And there's probably a couple more
Like that
By the way, someone actually said
Yesterday, oh
I heard you kind of slip into
An English accent there
When I said
Actually
Does that sound British?
You can try this cowbell out
Let's all give a night
To the hardest work
And lawyer
He's trying to tie
And then he's jersey tied
Yo
What's up, AC?
It's jersey tied
The official musicologist of the Chacha
Hey, and listen kids
The only way to be a musicologist
Is to check out the positive music network
Every day
And well, you know I'm a freak for it
And you know, every once in a while
When my boss is talking to me
Or a client, you're happy
Appyapyapyap in a way
I go over to the PMN
And check out what's going on
And I got to tell you
This has been some week
At the positive music network
I'm telling you
There are bands popping up
All the time that blow me away
And the one that stuck out to me
The most this week
Was Bill Vavino
And Bill Vavino
And his band is from Jersey
Of course
I mean, come on
I ain't Chacago tied
I'm Jersey tied baby
And the song that he put up
They're just absolutely blew me away
The song has changed your mind
I think you're going to enjoy it too
Happy footballer Friday
Everybody check this out
You're the one I'm dreaming of
And it gets too hot to wake up
But you know
All I want is you
Every time I get a phone
Upon the floor
I'm staying in trial
Since I trust him
Into the night
And you lock it deep inside
But this is a passion for burning deep
I just can't hide
But you know
Your face all is only
Do you think that this won't get somewhere
Will you remember that love
This would be a
Do you see our songs
Together deep within your heart
But you're a scary boy
And you can see the other side
Don't want to understand
If I could make you change your mind
Don't want to be afraid of getting in
Don't want to walk away again
Don't you keep saying that a love once never true
Can I share a part of you
But there is nothing you can do
But you know
All I want is you
But you lock this deep inside
Can't wait like this won't get somewhere
Will I remember that
Do you think that this won't get somewhere
Will you remember that love once never true
Can I share a part of you
But you know
Your face all is only
Do you think that a love once never true
Can I share a part of you
But there is nothing you can do
But you know
Your voice all is only
Do you think that a love once never true
Don't change your mind, don't want to be afraid of getting it
I know it is your music
Don't change your mind when you're on your own
But I can't find it's your own thing I will
Take it slow, so please don't go
Keep your distance and push back to my feet
I'll take it slow, so please don't go
You are the same, be on the side
I want you to understand
If I can't you change your mind
Don't want to be afraid of getting it
If you can't see me on the side
Don't want to be on the side
If I can't hold you in one more time
Don't want to be afraid of getting it
Yeah
Of course it's from Jersey
Change your mind, don't want to be afraid of getting it
Don't want to be afraid of getting it
that with that, but they, of course, are the ones that are extremely successful
of doing it. Now, there's a big difference between what we're doing at the
Podjo network, and we're a new media company, probably one of the biggest
new media companies, the type of media and advertising that we're doing. So let me
just explain Google tracks relevance, so they'll look at a web page or yeah, I'm
sure that they can skim or scan through a podcast, transcribe the words, and
then insert an ad into that or the front of the back or whatever, and therefore
provide relevance. And that'll be worth something, and they'll do it on a cost
per thousand basis, a CPM, and that is a very, very lucrative, very successful
business. However, the business that everybody is after, the Podjo is
successfully embedded itself into is so-called brand advertising,
loyalty-based advertising. It's a really big deal.
You know, we already had a commercial in this show. Now, it's no secret splendid
sponsoring the Daily Source Code and a number of other podcasts on the network,
and you know, what's great about it is I don't have to do anything, you know,
I just talk about the product, I tell you that they're a sponsor, and here's some
ways we could have fun with it. In other words, turning the advertising into content,
and I have just tons of people talking about splendor. You know, the Gilmore gang
was like eight minutes of splendor. This is fantastic. This is the type of loyalty
that advertisers are really looking for, big brand advertisers, which is why you see us
with big brands, accurate. You know, Johnson and Johnson brands,
splendor is a Johnson and Johnson brand. This is big, big stuff.
And so just in basic form, I just want to say here's the difference,
where Google tracks relevance and then places advertising relevant to that,
pod show and the programming associated with a network, create relevance.
We treat every single show or podcast, whatever you want to call it as a media property.
Something needs to be marketed. Packages, the audience should be grown.
No, make no mistake. We've always said, I've been very clear. We're all about the commercial
aspect of it. And that bond between a producer or host, or which, of course, is often,
you know, the producer is the host, is the runner, is the writer, is the technician.
That bond between that producer and that audience is worth so much more than a cost per thousand
basis. We don't even sell on that. Now, is it all that? No. Some of it, of course, is also a blanket
sweep of 10 to 22nd promotional messages, like the Go Daddy stuff. You know, listening to this podcast,
you'll hear information about how to get a great domain name at a killer price. And so,
you know, I'll say, by the way, that's, you know, for 695, you want to get your domain name for a year,
use checkout code DSC3, boom advertising. You know, like people are doing that,
you know, many people registered domain names who've heard this on, on a pod show pod cast,
it's outrageous. They're about to up the renew their deal with us. And for the UK as well,
going to a special promotion for the UK, I hope I didn't blow anything by telling you. So I just,
I just wanted to say that. It's, um, it's a, is a very big difference. And fantastic, the Google is
going to be doing that. That's great. There's, you know, there's a lot of room for it. We don't focus
on that. Almost do not focus on that at all. In fact, our insertion technology, we really use
for golden tickets, which we'll be coming out with. Actually, there was one on, um,
uh, what was a Jennifer show? The Guild of Fork? Was that it? Uh, she's going to kill me.
I want a second. I don't want to get killed by Jennifer. I want to make sure, uh,
am I stupid? Uh, wait. I'm in Gmail. As you can tell, trying to find it, uh, crap.
Well, anyway, they did a, uh, was it a, a Folgers golden ticket giveaway?
And here it is. Uh, and the Guild of Fork, a food philosophy. Ah, I'm sorry.
Slat me. Slat me with a wet towel. Um, you know, so that's another way we incorporate insertion
technology, but do it in a whole different fashion. Uh, and that golden ticket stuff is so much fun.
We kind of do another fucking golden ticket on the daily source code. All right, everybody.
Time to wrap it up. Yes, you know, I day.
Well, uh, of course with all this talk of citizen journalism, I could easily talk about
citizen journalism. I have some kind of political statement to make, but I'd like to say something
else. Today, I did something that really pushed my own limits, uh, something I'd never done before.
Yeah, it's a rich boy's game, you know, flying across the English channel. I get all that, but
it was a definite, I've really moved some barriers, um, to push myself to do that. And let me
tell you, and I am reliably informed about, uh, drugs. There's nothing that beats that high.
The high of pushing yourself further than you've ever been, whether that's in your relationship,
whether that's in your work, or your hobby. Oh, yeah, politics. Whatever it is, when you push yourself
at extra mile, it just feels so good. So this coming week, I please urge you. Find something
you have not done before. Maybe you've considered you've been thinking about for a while and push
yourself, push yourself at extra, extra inch or extra yard or extra mile and do it. You're going to
feel fucking great. All right, everybody, that's it. Have yourselves a great weekend. I'll talk to you
again on Monday, daily source code.com for the show notes. Adam and podshow.com for your emails
and, uh, take care of yourself, bye, bye. Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.
Yet this podcast, and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network
from podshow and line-wight networks. I love it.