This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want a killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sheriff, Charlie, three nine or two.
Good morning, everybody.
It'll stay.
Be careful.
Hello, my dear.
Good fall.
Am I Muslim?
Yes.
Look at your pancakes.
Good night, Ken.
What?
Could there be any thicker and bigger?
You want thick and big, baby?
It came to the right place.
Okay.
Hold on.
Yeah, what?
Sounds good.
Okay.
Well, you wanted it.
But people listening.
You asked for it.
You've got Adam and Patricia on the road.
We are in New York.
Yeah.
Just woke off.
Yes.
And it's Monday morning.
It's going to be busy day for me.
Why don't we have to alternate this?
Okay.
Because only one of us can talk and one of us can eat at the same time.
Well, I can eat in talk.
Do you have a proper?
What do you have on?
What is your own?
I have a very healthy of course.
Of course.
Because I want to live a little bit longer.
They're me.
Trying to catch up to me.
Can't catch up.
They're not leaving any syrup with those.
Yes, they did.
Yeah.
Where's the glasses, son?
Yes, I'm right.
Guess I'm right.
Not done.
So I have a mushy, which fruit in New York.
Oh, so that's cold.
Yeah.
Okay, good.
And you have...
But of no pancakes, thick, thick, creamy, juicy, nasty ass pan.
Can't get them anywhere else.
Not you on your ass pancakes.
You can't get them anywhere else, but in America.
Not like that.
Not like this.
Yeah.
They look like sort of a pound of puffs.
That's how big they are.
So we started our trip Saturday.
Right?
Yeah.
Saturday coming from London to New York.
We're going to be here.
As it turns out, now a little bit longer than we expected.
We're going to be here through Wednesday.
Wednesday was flying to the West Coast.
How is your flight over dear?
The wonderful Virgin Atlantic Express Upper Class Extrasigalza.
That was very cool.
That was very good.
It's relaxing.
And you can lean down a little bit in your best-top of whatever it is.
It looks like a best-top.
You're a special little bathtub.
Yeah.
So it's nice.
It's nice actually to stretch your legs.
And you feel much better when you come out.
Yeah.
And okay.
So actually, because of the air pressure and the pressure sometimes bothers you.
We didn't have any problem, right?
No, I do.
No problem this time.
No.
Okay.
So arrive in New York at the fantastic W hotel.
On time square.
Now if you don't know the W hotel, it is what we would consider to be a boaty hotel.
No, they say, no, no, because they have more of those hotels.
And you explain to me then it isn't a boutique hotel.
But it looks like a boutique hotel.
That means that it's very trendy.
Non-traditional.
Let me call this non-traditional.
I hate it.
I'm a traditional girl.
She's giving me a normal bathroom with a bath stop or anything.
But then this Chinese, what is it?
Japanese.
Well, it's a lot, there's a lot of black.
Yeah.
A lot of chrome.
Grey, chrome, black.
The nightstands look like a nice cube.
Yeah, it actually looks like the Apple cube computer.
Yes.
A nice cube.
A nice cube that lights up in the, when you want some light and anything.
It's contemporary.
Look at the refrigerator.
Yeah.
On top of, I don't know what it is.
Yep.
Yeah, instead of a nice mini bar that's built into a cabin.
Yeah.
It's actually just sitting on top of a thing.
I just don't get it.
I just don't get what the excitement is about rooms like this.
Well, it's, I don't know.
It is not cozy.
No.
Not at all.
It's impossible to put your stuff away from home.
Don't you want that when you are traveling.
I want that.
There are many people who don't have a nice, I mean, this is nice.
I mean, it's not, it's not a bad hotel.
I'm just, you know, you've got to love the consistent house music.
Quite prop a whole place.
Yeah.
Not being able to see in the hallways of the elevator because the lighting is so thin.
To hide, of course, the crap.
Yeah, because if you, if you really, you know, look very carefully.
In the bathroom, you see that it is, it looks shitty.
Mm-hmm.
It looks really shitty.
Oh, yeah.
You cannot get rid of your stuff.
You don't know where to put it.
No, no place to put it.
No.
No shelves.
There's no shelves.
But it's a really cool looking wash basin.
It's round.
Yeah.
You can't even put your soap on it.
Just glide it off.
And, yeah.
So I don't get it.
So that was the hotel.
It's a piece of it.
I think it's a piece of shit.
Okay.
Just like that.
I have no other explanation.
No explanation for it.
No other explanation.
I hate it.
But it's nice to hear.
Would you please don't hold back on?
No, I don't.
No, no, no.
So before we get to today in tomorrow, it's a Ron and Marta are here as well.
Ron and I have a whole bunch of stuff to do.
Way too much to do in two days.
Oh, here in New York.
Well, at yesterday, actually, we went out for, so we were up very early.
We woke up at like four, four, thirty in the morning.
Yeah.
And then we had already had breakfast by, shoot, seven, thirty.
And then we went out walking.
Yeah.
A beautiful day yesterday.
We walked all the way up for Central Park West.
Oh, we were looking for it.
When we first moved to New York, we stayed for a month at the Mayflower cell.
Yeah.
And it was gone.
It's gone.
It doesn't exist anymore.
Everything is changed.
Columbus Circle has changed.
Because that was where we used to live.
Yeah, that was the 50s and Broadway.
That was where we arrived here.
In 1987.
Yeah.
And it was nice to look at the windows of the Central Park.
And it was overwhelming.
All this building around the buildings around it.
Yeah.
It was 1987.
We're talking about just yesterday.
And now, it was just gone.
It was really gone.
Beautiful buildings actually next to it.
And we were looking for the Dakota.
We couldn't recognize them.
No.
I don't know for some reason.
I mean, it's seventy-second stream.
Yeah.
And it just...
I remember it being more impressive on the outside last time I looked at it.
But then you hung it right into a strawberry fields.
Was you never seen?
Mm-hmm.
Wow.
It was a nice feeling.
But it didn't look like a strawberry field.
No.
I thought...
I wouldn't...
You really thought it was a strawberry.
Did you really believe it?
Well, maybe something pink or red.
No, just a thing in the middle that says a man.
No.
It's sort of concrete, concrete thing.
Hmm.
It's like a mosaic.
It's a mosaic.
But it was just a thought.
It's the thought that we had to be behind it.
Yeah.
So, lots of people standing there.
Just looking at it.
Just gazing at it.
Yeah.
Wow.
I wonder what they're thinking.
But if you were a piece of a thinking about John Lennon.
But you do get that feeling in your stomach when you're standing there and saying,
Wow.
But then I say it right away.
It really sucked.
Oh, that it was so useless.
Yeah, it was so useless.
But that's what I'm saying.
People go there and they think about John Lennon being shot.
Where am I?
I think he would have preferred people thinking about a world without, you know, what the song
Imagine is about.
Wow.
And I think everyone who goes there just thinks about, you got shot.
Yeah.
Wow.
And there was the AIDS walk, which,
Yeah.
I kind of walked a little bit with it and then back the other way.
And we hooked up with.
My ex-managed John Focardberg.
Yeah, who was just, it just happened to be in New York City.
Yeah.
And that was nice.
And he mentioned that the whole show business, especially in America.
And of course, especially in Holland.
And everywhere, actually, it has changed so much.
Totally different.
Different way of.
Well, yeah.
That is true.
The music business, particularly you said, you know,
and unless you're into hip hop and R&B, there's no money to be made.
And it actually looks pretty funny.
Because what was it for the way?
How was you talking about Alicia Keys?
Yeah.
And he's out work.
So Alicia Keys needs to get a hit.
And then she'll have a song.
And then ludicrous will show up for $250,000.
There's no rap on the song.
And then all of it.
And you'll get royalties and points on the album and everything.
And that's how you actually make a hit these days.
You got to get a singer and then you connect it up with someone.
That's good.
This one.
This person in a rap.
Someone's doing the beats.
But it's definitely, it's not what it used to go.
We know that.
Yeah.
I know it sounds always so old foggy.
So old foggy, you may say.
It's not used.
But I still love the pure, honest music.
What are you talking about?
Well, that comes from the heart instead of,
Oh, rap and hip hop.
Yeah.
You're right.
That's what I mean.
Yeah.
No, I agree.
That is the part that bothers me too.
It's still manufacturing hits.
Yeah.
It's such a thought behind it.
Okay.
And then.
Martha surprised us.
Yes.
We can't.
She had tickets.
For the, um, I'm broccoli.
I'm Judy Roberts.
Um, a three days of rain.
It's a play.
It's not a play bill there.
Yeah.
So this is actually a big deal because, well, first of all,
she's a Academy Award-winning actress.
You know, it gets $20 million per movie.
Yeah.
Although her last two movies have been Oceans 11 and Oceans 12,
which is not exactly exactly what you want on the run.
What do you think she does this?
Why?
Yeah.
Just two babies at home.
Why not enjoy that instead of two?
Well, if you read the article, which I did, she said that she, she had the opportunity.
It's only, she's only doing it for 12 weeks.
So it's a very, you know, it's very short run.
Three months.
They call it 12 weeks of rain.
12 weeks of rain.
Well, the reviewers actually said two and a half hours of Julia Roberts,
which I've had.
The reviews of mine.
I keep them staring at her.
Oh, my God.
I'm looking at Julia Roberts.
Really?
I didn't have that at all.
I'm beginning to have.
I did.
I checked her.
I checked her out.
Well, before we get to the checking out the run.
The reason she said that her twins are now one and a half.
Hmm.
And she said she had this opportunity, because she's,
they're going into that terrible twos,
as she says in the, in the, in the interview.
Mm-hmm.
And she felt that she had this opportunity.
Yeah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
But it wasn't like some artistic thing.
She wanted it.
Yeah.
That doesn't say that or she didn't know she's not gonna admit that but it's always isn't it that
Actors actors always wanted they they want to say I
Was in the theater
Yes, when I back in the days when I did and therter
You know something they they want to say that just once in their life. They want to say no
I don't think you can say all actors want to do that. I'm most of them. No
Why I do a year or the lot. I did some theater
Yeah, well in England. I'll just say that or I come from theater Broadway Broadway
But anyway, um
It was very interesting
Yeah, well, it I have to admit that you need so much patience when you're sitting at when you're sitting in a in a theater
Nice theater, by the way. Yeah, very good. And
You know the actors really are it is it is a better experience than it was a different experience
The actors are only 15 feet away
Yeah, you could run up and you could you could jump on stage if you wanted to it was nice and cool
You know, it was the air conditioning was on high
God still people can turn off their cell phones, which is very very irritating
Isn't that embarrassing and not not once for like three different people? Oh my god
Yeah, that that's horrible and and they just keep on asking you
Every time it starts but
I have to say that one of the guys I really like wasn't that what's that pole rod? No, that was the guy that we thought sucked
Okay, so it's a Bradley Cooper was actually the guy who
He was really good. He all he had to invite all of a sudden he had a great monologue
When he came on yes, suddenly it opened up and so oh, okay now it's okay
But the story in general is
Very tiny little tiny if you've ever who if you're red or seen
Like death of a salesman. Yeah, it's something like that
Speak the blue with Madonna with Madonna
But it's I don't know it for me
It's interesting. I'm glad I saw it. Yeah, but it didn't add anything
It was not like wow the story. I'm so you know
Moved by nothing
No, it's not a moving story. It's actually very light nothing special
It's just a part of somebody's life. Well, that's what it play usually is it's just a couple of days
But I don't know I want to feel some excitement
Didn't you feel me next to you baby
That was it
I knew it next to me
Um, but I think it was good
The tickets were out. This is the hottest ticket on Broadway. I would read justly expensive and completely packed
And it's just it's so funny because you have such a beautiful theater
a play which
Peace which is it's definitely drama no doubt about it. It's a real dramatic piece dark
Some interesting stage effects. I like you know that because it is three days of rain
So lots of rain actually coming down and what did I say why does it doesn't go but then it's so
Typical only in America
Can you then then there's intermission and then we all go sit around and and eat raisinets
You know anything this soul of raisinets you can get a screaming bar made. Yeah, you yeah exactly you can get a Merlot
or a Shabley classic cup
Beautiful senior
Beautiful old English theater. That's how it looked and then she's shawy
That'll be $20. Yeah
Well, then we all came back and then
Run and I
apologize for them for the eating sounds. Yeah, otherwise it gets cold and we have hopefully
And it's the timing is all messed up
Everyone forgets that that actually takes time and effort to create a show and there's like a million meetings and I say oh by the way
You know, we still have a show to do
Yeah
So we were done this morning with like one o'clock. We were done with our presentation which were
Which will be on in a couple hours from now
And my body is a bit confused. I have to say five o'clock. I woke up. Yeah, well you went to bed early because we were we were downstairs working
You wouldn't sleep at like tennis. I have to get used to the sounds of the traffic in you
Got about that
So I'm going off to the conference
A bear stirms internet thing but the bear stirms has been our bank for a long time
So it's important that we do this for them
And that's lots of other interesting companies who are at this thing today
And what are you going to do? Yvonne's coming because it's amazing. So your ex manager was in New York and now
And now today Yvonne's arrived and she has to go to
To the jailo company
The jailo company so that is yes. She has those
She sells those shoes and you know and those clothes and she has a whole lot of clothes clothes
Yes clothes too. I post this perfume. No, no, no. It's perfume clothes shoes everything
And she does that together with her associate who is
Jay love them
Who is Tommy Hilfe here said brother oh by the way
When we arrived Saturday
Frontage of the of the of the newspapers. Oh, yeah a picture a big brawl in New York Tommy Hilfe here
Who was what?
Actually kicked Axel Rose's ass in a nightclub
I know
Somehow Tommy was there celebrating someone's birthday or his birthday or whatever and then Axel Rose came in with his
You know Axel Rose course of guns and roses with his big bravado and whatever and there was some scuffle
Tommy Hilfe actually kicked his ass beat him up and
And Axel Rose couldn't I guess they were separated before Axel could get any punches and
That's fine. Okay, so he'll figure his brother
Yeah, well, you should be able to get the inside dirt
He would jade out make sure he vone gets the inside dirt now. What happened with the rose?
Oh, okay. Yeah, oh, no, that's okay. She has an appointment tomorrow. So today we're gonna just stroll a little bit
Through Manhattan but so tomorrow. That's exciting because
Iván's associate from Holland is gonna
How do you say that English?
It's actually
Wouldn't it quite the license? Yeah, sorry. Quite the license for Europe for Europe for all of the james
It's exactly exactly because they needed somebody in in Holland and he wants it in Holland or Europe
I think it's for Holland first and then maybe a couple of other can you go buy it in Europe? Can't you somewhere now not yet? No
But you can buy it in England
So it's not gonna be England but yeah England is always the first one to get everything
So that's gonna be very interesting and Iván is a company named him accompanying him
Because Iván's English is very good because she used to live in England and
For nine years and I have to say her English is perfect beautiful you're English is not bad either
No, no, no, no, yes, yes, don't say that. I'm trying but I still notice that I'm translating in my hair
Yeah, because it has to stop well the only way to stop is for all of us to start this is what we did when we moved
I have my days. I have to say I have days that they might have my brains really thinking
There's yeah, and I have days that you know coming from the phone or speaking to my
My family and parents that's something that it's it's almost like and computed and you know
It's your Dutch yeah, you have to push it back and then the English comes
So it's not easy
Green Green now it's not easy being Dutch actually for many different reasons for a plethora
I know I know I know I don't feel Dutch
No, what do you feel more a sort of a tutti-free thing a tutti-free?
Yeah, sort of everything a bit of they similar to that
Well, when you're in America, you I think you felt pretty pretty good
Oh, yeah, yeah, I know yeah, you know why
The American language is easier it's slower that's very easy to understand that British English because
Yeah, the British English they just swallow everything and go so fast
Then I have to say couples and pardon yeah, excuse me, you know because I have to think what what you know
But you always said to me, don't say just yes, but let them repeat it again
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I don't know what they're saying could you never know I don't get
I was like you know something to your friends you think
But no just say pardon. I don't I didn't get it can you repeat that again until you get it that's very good message for me
Okay, so
tomorrow
Tomorrow I have a so today you're gonna be with Yvonne and tomorrow
Tomorrow I have another early meeting right after that. Yeah, like nine to nine to ten and right after you and I are going way down town
Yeah, downtown maybe
And we got to get some paperwork squared away for
For my for my immigration so that I don't get thrown out of the UK
That's gonna be fun. We have three different offices. We have to visit downtown three different three different queues three different windows
We'll have to oh yeah, so
I don't know if we want to sound they're gonna push you around
You know how much I love them one window to the other
And then and so I love extra time which thing in extra day in New York
Yeah, so we have time if we need to do anything on Wednesday and then Wednesday at two thirty
We fly to San Francisco and then we go and we arrive at five thirty and we go straight to Pebble Beach
So we won't go it's only an hour from the airport. Oh, okay. Yeah. Oh
So you were not gonna sleep in San Francisco when in our own bed? Yeah, but yeah, right?
We only put well, no, we're gonna be in Pebble Beach for a night for one night
two nights, but we first wish we sleeping no because that would only if we left tomorrow
Oh, that's right. Yeah, and now we don't but we have to because all these offices here that we need to go to close it three o'clock
And you have to it's a big chill. Yeah, so if we don't do it then you'll be very lonely living in the UK without me
Yeah, you lonely without you
My parents are good at home. You check with them. I check with them. Yeah, and everything is okay
Of course Christina. I last minute everything in the morning my mom has to get used to that
She said oh my god, you know the car was waiting for her and she was still doing things and even doing her homework in the morning
Well, she said I am a grand mom or oh my like I said in how and what they said
I forgot it and I have to and she said my mom gets she got oh she gets crazy
Especially older people, you know, they want to do everything purifers
So that's a little bit hard, but everything is fine
The weather is very cold in anything like that at the moment
So that's set for them. I wanted to have them to have a wonderful weather, but it's not
Okay
Tell me the joy you couldn't eat it all
Yeah, I
I was not able to not be able to eat the last there was huge
Bouther puffs
Okay, so we'll keep you updated on our travels and we get to I say when we will maybe Tuesday night
Or when yeah Tuesday night for what depending on how we do on Tuesday
We'll set up all the microphones and the mixer and we'll do a proper show
If you'll enjoy it, you don't have to if you don't have to know I'm here. You wait and I mean I'm here for you
Those you listening to us on a serious stars one out two Pacific Coast Hillways next and
We'll see all of you tomorrow on the journey. Bye. Bye
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from Podjo and line-light networks. I love it