This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts and GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy!
Dilsa's here at Charlie 460.
What are these things?
I don't know about these things.
I'm a lady who's here and I do ladies thing.
I attend the operators.
Drink fluffy kittens and shit.
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls, please put your hands together for the Delta.
See ya da Charlie.
460.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm testing his new career.
I know just what I'm trying to do.
Good I can oppose my stupid ass over the ground.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
$13 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
$16 million worth of airline strapped to my ass.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
$14 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Let's dance taste our tangerine
That's our ch например
It's an unpredictable
It's a world-fatable
It's a pomegranate
What a ferocious world
Do
You're not running
How heavy is that, first?
Theory and motion.
Wake up.
This is the daily source code episode 360.
As you can tell from the sound,
very different sound today coming to you from
Hyde Park in London.
You can probably hear the den of the traffic in the background.
Let me just shut up for a second so you can listen to the sounds of the park.
Can hear some birds.
This is actually a great proof that you can make fun shows,
even if you don't have the big ballsy compressor and microphone,
etc.
Actually, I'm going to hold the...
This is the love microphone that I usually carry with me,
so I'm going to hold it up in front of my face to give you a little better clarity.
The show is being done like this today.
Well, stayed in the city last night in London
as we have a pretty important announcement tomorrow.
That'll be Wednesday, the 13th.
Wednesday, the 13th, pretty important announcement here in the UK.
So I'll be staying here tonight as well.
Well, you know what that means?
It means I'm on the road.
Cast blaster is with me and that's all I got.
Now I must say, I have the headphones, the Patricia bought,
her headphones, I took those with me and man.
It's such a difference to create the show
when you're completely encapsulated by the sound,
because these really lock off all exterior sound
and you only hear basically what's coming in.
So I'm going to give you a little bit of a hint of what we're announcing tomorrow.
I'll give you a preview of that.
And of course, plenty of feedback from you guys.
Yo, Adam, this is Paige from the sneakart FM podcast.
I just had to stop and listen to the DSC 459
because I just have to say,
this is brilliant podcasting.
This is so nice.
The interview with Ken Clark and stories about the old MTV days.
Yeah, it's just very nice to listen to.
Even though I don't get most of it, you're saying,
and all the names don't ring any bells for me.
So here's my profile.
32 podcaster being listener for two years,
being a podcaster for eight months,
due to you and Don and Drew,
and Folder.
Yeah.
I knew it.
Oh, man.
Actually, it just started to drizzle a little bit here in the park.
So I was sitting on a bench and I've moved underneath the tree.
Well, let me see if I can use my bag as a backstop there.
Okay. Oh, yes.
Now I can lean back a little bit.
So I've got droplets on the keyboard.
Even though I'm under the tree,
it's getting a little bit heavier here.
Now what can you do?
So tomorrow, as I said,
and I mentioned this,
I think on yesterday's show as well,
there's going to be an announcement for the UK market.
And of course, I can't tell you,
I know a lot of you listen one day later,
so I can't actually,
so you'll probably know the news by now
if you're listening on a delay,
which is part of what podcasting's about.
So you'll probably already know what's going on,
but I do want to give you just a little bit of a tease.
I've bleeped out the appropriate name,
so you won't be able to figure out what we're actually announcing,
but it is pretty cool.
Check this out.
Today, we're announcing that pod share
are creating a new type of network.
Combining incredible wealth of content
with the ability for the audience to become part of the show.
Now with pod share,
we're combining the power of broadband
with the technology behind podcasting
to create tomorrow's network.
In the process,
we want to give our customers the chance
to become involved with both an audience
and as contributors.
Now, how does that sound?
Does that sound like fun or what?
Uh-huh.
Do well on that.
Well, Parkie checks in.
Hi, Adam, it's Parkie.
I was going to win you a Monday to see
let you know the results and the experiment I was doing,
but I just had a very bizarre experience
in the same experience in Greenwich and London,
and I just thought I'd run you in a bit early
and let you know.
Now, the first part of it was I didn't experiment
with this.
Well, you know, I'm a folder.
Everyone knows I'm a folder.
But I tried this scrunching stuff.
Ugh!
Ah!
Now, the one we're going to go into anymore detail
but...
Dude, whatever you do,
do not attempt scrunching
without a trained professional nearby.
Oh, yeah!
Anyway, the weird thing was,
I was in St. Louis
and I'm wondering up and down the aisles
and I'm listening to today's show
that's Friday,
so early on, Friday came out
and I was just singing
10-4, 10-4, 10-4, 10-4,
at moment to myself,
very quietly,
and a guy just went,
don't you still scope?
Anyway, I had a little chat with him,
he's listening up from around here
to sort of let you know.
Very bizarre experience.
Still a folder.
Always will be a folder.
Bye-bye.
Thank you, Parti.
Wow, interesting.
That is...
What are the chances, huh?
What are the chances
that you'd be walking through
the aisles of St. Louis
singing along.
10-4, 10-4,
at moment.
I guess there's something
to this podcasting stuff after all, huh?
What do veteran broadcasters
think of podcasters and podcasting?
Join me, Trucker Tom,
on Monday, September 18th,
for an interview
I did with veteran broadcaster,
Haley Rose.
That's where podcasting comes in.
It allows us,
allows other people
to get into the business
because there's nowhere
anymore for new people
to start out
and to be back.
You have that opportunity, Tom.
I give it to you.
Listen to the perspective of a broadcaster
who got his start
in the Golden Age of Radio
and helped pioneer the genre
of Talk Radio
as we know it today.
And I've been in broadcasting
ever since in one way
or another,
I've produced television shows
in the early days of television.
You know, I've been a freelance performer
for many years.
I do radio,
television shows.
I've had my own TV shows,
and I've got my own radio shows.
I've had a very long career.
On Monday, September 18th,
find out about UFOs,
electronic voice phenomena,
and the unexplained
at www.truckerTompodcast.com.
You can check out his video cast, too.
He's doing something that I think is
just fascinating.
This is on as I think it's his
boom, boom, video podcast.
He tapes
a certain legs of his journey.
A trucker Tom, of course,
being an actual trucker.
And he,
and so he speeds it up
and times it out to fit in with pod safe music.
And I got to tell you,
it's kind of trippy.
So essentially he's creating music videos.
So you couldn't just subscribe to the feed
and hear some great pod safe music tunes.
And if you have a video playing device,
you glance down,
you check it out.
And you've got some visuals to go along with it.
And sometimes the timing of the turns
and the road and the traffic patterns
and the flow and he really does speed it up quite a bit.
Coinside with the music in the most eerie way.
Now check that out.
Remember of our pod show network family.
Talker Tom.
Call the D.S.C.
In the U.S.A.
That's plus one
6256357
In England
The U.K.
It's plus four four
That's plus four
2 07
If you're a scruncher,
a boulder
to fingers or a houlder call now.
What?
What was that?
A scruncher or a folder?
Wait, let me listen to that again.
A scruncher folder to fingers or a hold.
Hold on.
Let me check.
Let's see.
What was that here?
Let me rewind that.
If you're a scruncher,
a boulder to fingers or a houlder call now.
Yeah.
Keep those voicemail jingles coming in.
I really love them.
Hey Adam.
Nick, you're here.
It's from Radio Post Apocalypse.
I just just thought I'd weigh in on the editing debate.
Like you, I don't really edit my show.
It's not like I'm aiming for some highly natural sound rating.
I'm just lazy bastard.
I mean, it's why I'm using cat glasses in the first place, right?
I mean, it allows you to do everything in real time.
You don't need to do any post editing at all.
And it's not that throw that in there.
Later.
All right, sorry about the sound quality there.
I guess I didn't pull that particular one through my processing.
When I get it from the voicemail,
usually it sounds a bit better.
But yeah, you're a lazy cast blastered.
That's what it is.
Users of cast blaster are cast blastered.
Speaking of which,
I want to wind up this whole Joseph Jaffee across the sound thing
that's been going back and forth.
For those of you just catch, and this is really ended,
because, you know, we've had our fun.
For those of you that haven't been following along very closely,
Joseph Jaffee has a show called Across the Sound.
It's a new marketing podcast.
And he interviewed Ron Blumenty,
and he split the interview into two parts.
And after playing part one, he essentially said on the show
that he was holding part two hostage until I gave him some love
and some traffic and some link love, et cetera, et cetera,
which I, you know, of course took some offense to.
It was like, hey, dude, you didn't say I had to do that.
So that went back and forth.
And on the most recent episode, I think it's 53 across the sound.
Joseph really lays it all out, and he says it was a joke.
It was intended to be a joke.
He wasn't serious about it.
Okay, I'm willing to buy that, but of course,
you know, some punishment has to be dulled out here.
And let me say, I got a whole bunch of interesting,
interesting punishment suggestions.
Let me see,
was this newbie, is that newbie, as for Joseph Jaffee,
I say you lock him in a closet and make him listen to the entire
Keith and the girl archives, interesting for sure.
Adam, please be a really great hearted person for give that.
Is that microphone cut?
Yeah, I'm gonna change that.
Go.
Okay, sorry about that.
That really sucked ass.
Okay, batteries have been changed.
Oh, I think the sound is even a little bit better.
All right, let's get back to where we were with Joseph Jaffee.
Let me see, here we go.
Have him do a five minute video on his podcast,
where he tongues a picture of Phyllis Diller,
while playing Lawrence,
well, music in the background,
wearing a hopping t-shirt.
I think we already did that one.
I didn't like that.
There were some other suggestions, though,
check this out.
Hi, Adam.
This is Karen from Virginia, just casting a vote
on the punishment.
And I think that the best punishment
would be to let him listen to a continuous loop
of that first jingle for the phone numbers.
Actually, the second one is really good.
Thanks for sharing it.
And we'll be now and always have been a folder.
Bye.
Oh, you almost said scruncher, I could hear it.
Yeah, that may be a little bit too harsh
to listen to the original voice mail loop.
I don't think we can make anybody do that.
Hi, Adam. Hi, Joseph.
This is Rich Gettarsky, a marketing consultant
and podcast producer in Sweden.
I offer you my thoughts on the curry versus Jeffy game.
Just make things clearer.
I'm a little listener to both of your shows
and therefore entitled to submit my voice.
First of all, I and many others,
oh, you guys so much because you pot father
and that's Adam,
hasn't only helped to realize podcasting,
but also pushed it forward,
made it respectable and defined
range of podcasting formats.
And Joseph has done similar,
sometimes thanks,
but in more marketing oriented context.
So how can you pay back?
Perhaps a small tribute is by answering
Adam's call for punishment
and to Joseph's quest for it to send
or not to send question.
I'm a sweet.
We're known to be fond of mutual agreement
and common sense,
or coolerly stated,
love peace and understanding.
The key words here should be
respect and forgive.
If the whole thing was called by me
to understandings on one side of the podcast,
then apologize publicly.
If not, then respect each other's feelings
and forgive the other one.
There are too many people out there
punishing each other back and forward.
And if Adam doesn't want Joseph to play
the second part,
even though that outcome wasn't agreed on
beforehand,
then Joseph should respect Adam's demand.
And guess we all lose a bet
because it's the second half,
it's at least the first one
we still have some good prospects.
And one last thing.
Now it's a few minutes after
one coffee a.m.
And an hour ago,
I wanted Adam to listen to Joseph's
latest episode of Across the Sound
and I got this idea to use Skype
and start a conference with me
and both of your podcasts
calling lines at the other parties.
So I had to get up to the context
and do not the PC,
start Skype and talk.
Hope it worked.
So that both of you guys
got the same comment at the same time.
Just one pile of things
to stress the value of my input.
One word,
except there's starts with an app.
Folder?
I need chance.
Okay.
Yeah.
Now of course I want Joseph
to air the second part of the interview.
I thought it was really good.
And he thought it was good too.
But I do have something in mind
for our friend, Joseph Jaffee.
And this really comes from this entire
episode he did explaining
about why he did what he did
and what he did.
I apologize to his audience,
my audience,
me, the world,
whatever.
One thing was really funny
is that he said that when he was
walking through hallways
of just around the street
that people who knew
and would say,
Ben Oberbitch.
I think it's incredibly funny.
So here's the punishment
that I've come up with
and we're going to keep it really light.
And this is right in line
with the Sensei of Vulcan Mind trick.
So I want you to really jam those
ear buds into your ear
or if you're listening
on the computer.
I want you to turn up the sound
a little bit.
Maybe you should close the door
first.
So nobody hears you go ahead.
I'll give you a second to go
to get up and go close
the door to your office
or wherever you are.
Okay.
Turn the sound up a little bit.
Now,
I want you to close your eyes
and visualize
the name Joseph Jaffee.
It's a really cool name
because it starts with two jays
and it has a nice flow
to it visually Joseph
Jaffee
with the pH
and the double F
Joseph Jaffee.
Now
from now on
whenever you see the name
or hear the name
Joseph Jaffee
you will immediately
think
then overbitch
Joseph Jaffee
Hello
I've lost all
one of these here
just calling
Joseph Jaffee
and I'm supposed to call back.
This is why I haven't
called lately
because I'm pretty happy
with my satellite service.
You see
I got pretty good reception
but now
I'm getting
rather flaky
reception
I was trying to watch
some internet
ponotes
and some regular television
on
and
I need
well, it's not coming
in the way it was.
So if Uncle Jaffee
could come have a look at it
and maybe
never have
next door
I really appreciate it
and
while you're at it
go listen to
p580.com
Okay, full goodbye
Alright
Thank you very much
Well, of course
if you're having trouble
there's only one guy
who could really come down
and help you get your
porn reception
back in order.
His name is Uncle Jaffee
He's the satellite
repairman
coming after you
satellite repairman
What's he gonna do?
He'll fit your misconceptions
and answer questions too
in the universe
and he can't move
for you
satellite repairman
whew
here
close
my body
heavenly
liberty
Jones
works in the shop
the Cheyote
listens to music
like swing
when there's no
thing
just because she
don't like to
drive
take
to see a
step
find
and
to
set thoughts
outside
to
the river
at night
this is the
also
you
why don't you come
for me
take me
away
in my place
leave it to
you so far
I wish
you were mine
we could go
back to my place
leave it to you
something
why don't you come for me
take me away
through the right place
oh
she's got a team
and I
and
and then I
would imply
you
so lonely
desire
leave it to you
so far
why don't you come
for me
take me away
through the right place
leave it to you
so far
I wish you
what but we could go back
back to my place
leave it to you
so far
why don't you come for me
take me away
through the right place
oh
Oh
Wings in the shot movie Sheo
Disass neg unreasonable
进 gang
saved
Displug him
S.C.S.R13
The Shakespeareも
Nobody Zone
S.C.S.R.S.R11
Episode Number 4
And 60
They believe it coming to you from high park in London. I'm Adam Curry, Adam at podshow.com
DailySourceCode.com is the is where you can leave your comments. And well, I'll be back tomorrow
Probably another show from London
Who knows from the hotel room?
I got to upload this thing take care everybody. Bye bye.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast
A delivery network from podshow and line-white networks.
I love it.