This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want to hear content with badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 3-6-8.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky drinks.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Hey everybody, it is Monday.
And my play list is packed.
I'm a crank up from the sunset.
Get the blood pump.
You're drilling and rolling.
One year.
Coming at you.
I'm a chicken distressed last little way that I get things done.
If I'm not a depression then I sleep too long.
And I hang around like a bum.
I'll think I'm going nowhere and that makes me nervous.
Everybody's at a good, maybe I don't feel alright.
Everybody's thinking about me.
Some of the things are good.
It's a little thing.
It's a way to warm up in a distance.
It's a little thing that it is.
We're trying to get down on my caffeine for something.
So we're going to get up.
I just have one cup of coffee and I like to have another cup of coffee with my breakfast.
None of the way to work.
I like to get a cup of coffee.
I like to get a cup of coffee that you get with the donuts.
I never get the donuts.
Let's have a cup of coffee.
I'm going to get to work.
I like to have a cup of coffee.
Because I like that cup of coffee.
We're talking on the phone.
Jim's big ego compares itself to such major players as the Great Wall of China, the Grand Canyon and Artica and other things you can see from space.
However, when pressed to label their music,
they name their genre of music on pop for the unpopulous.
Like a lot.
Think about eight or nine tracks up there right now.
With some great title such as,
They're everywhere.
Better than you.
Cut off your head and asshole.
Oh, did I mention this show is not family friendly?
Or usually isn't very family friendly?
Hey, everybody.
Hope you had a great weekend for some of you in Europe today.
It's actually a holiday.
It's a bank holiday in the UK.
I believe, which means banks are closed.
By the way, the banks are starting to suck everywhere.
I used Barclays Bank for Internet Banking.
And all of a sudden, they decided, at least I didn't get the memo,
that the maximum daily amount you can transfer or pay someone is 2,000 pounds.
And they've lowered that to 1,000 pounds.
Dude, I can't even pay my rent.
That way.
I have to pay my rent over 3 day period.
And yesterday, of course, was the big bill day.
I love doing that on an Easter Sunday.
It makes me feel really good.
And some of the bills you just have to cut a check,
stuff in an envelope, which is one of my least favorite things to do.
And I just like doing it on the net.
But they've lowered that limit for some reason.
I've got to find out.
Find a bank though.
Let me pay my bills, please.
So I did have a fantastic weekend, though.
Even the bill paying wasn't too bad.
Saturday, I got a bright and early,
wink commander, William, brought over the Delta Shiera,
my Cessna 182, RG.
It's the November 277 Delta Shiera.
He brought it over to Fair Oaks.
And I met him there with Captain Dan,
Captain Dan, who lives in Waybridge, I believe,
not far from Gilbert.
And he was brought to me online.
I put a call out to shoot.
Who wasn't who put me in touch with him actually?
Let me see.
I put a call out that I was looking for a safety pilot
to make the channel crossings with me.
Just because I'm relatively low hours,
a little over 200 hours in experience on fixed wing.
And he wants someone who can basically save your ass when necessary.
Let me see.
Who the hell was it was a listener who hooked me up.
I do remember that.
Hold on a sec.
I'm just looking through email here.
Shoot.
Oh, man.
How can I get fine this?
Well, anyway, Captain Dan really nice guy.
He's from New Zealand actually.
There you go.
I'm still trying to find out who turned me on to him
because that was a total email thing, crap.
I'll find it.
I'll know by next time I talk about Captain Dan.
So New Zealander works for Kellogg.
Now he doesn't fly for living anymore,
although he does still teach his instructor.
Kellogg is a subsidiary of Haliburton.
I mean, as a dude, give me back my money first of all.
So anyway, so we had a nice chat,
had some, the big breakfast as they called at that,
you know, it's like Biggles man, this airfield.
It's great.
It's got a little cafe, like coffee shop,
and everyone's in there eating bangers and mash and stuff like that.
And this plane's taken off and I got to take some video.
That's what I got to do.
I'll take some video of pharaohs.
I shot some video of the Delta Sheriff itself
just a quick walk around, which I may post later today,
just so you can see her.
Looking so cool with that new interior.
So the point was William came over, brought the plane,
then Dan and I are going to fly, William back,
and then fly back from Antwerp back to pharaohs.
Although I did put in a little detour since I was in Antwerp,
it's only a hop skip and a jump to Rotterdam,
and from there only a 25 or 30 minute cab ride to my mom's house.
So we filed a quick flight plan to go to Rotterdam,
which is a sizable airport, by the way.
It's got a real runway, it's got an instrument landing system.
It's lit beautifully.
They land 737s there.
The vacation flights usually,
trans obvious, takes off and lands there.
So, you know, it's a serious airport.
You got to know what you're doing.
And which, of course, I only have to do what I was doing.
Dan had never been there before.
We had all the charts and maps and everything in the frequencies.
So we took off.
Now, I've never done this trip by myself,
including all the radio communications into Rotterdam,
and I royally fucked it up.
I was looking for point Oscar.
It wasn't on our map.
Literally, I could not find it on our map,
which, of course, is our own planning mistake.
And so I wound up, you know, hanging a sharp left,
thinking I'm not going to continue any further.
Because, yeah, low and behold,
if I had continued for another three minutes,
maybe, I probably would have had a trans obvious,
737 in my left flank.
But they were very, very helpful.
Said, oh, now look over.
Look over to you, right?
Do you see the runway?
Yes, I see it.
What are your intentions?
Said, well, if you'll have me, I'll like the land.
So that was all, all good humor and everything was cool.
And I went to see my mom, who she really is in good spirits.
She's afraid.
But she's fighting this thing,
very, very courageously.
And so I'm just planning on,
if I can, pop and over every weekend,
or as often as possible,
maybe during a weekday, if I can find another safety pilot
who can also fly on weekdays.
So she's, she's hanging in there for sure.
She's definitely, she had some color on her cheeks
and looked a lot better.
And then I got back to Rotterdam.
So it was just a short visit,
but I think any visit is good enough.
Just to see each other is cool.
And then as we're taking off,
he'll like this.
As we're taking off all of a sudden,
I'm not, I actually were still in the run-up.
So the plane hasn't actually lifted off the ground.
And I can feel something's wrong.
I'm looking at my gauges.
I have no power.
Or not, not the power sufficient,
or that you would really want,
although I was very close to rotation.
So I aborted, which is something I never done before,
but you know, immediately aborted the take off.
And it was something,
there must have been some kind of contaminant in the fuel.
Because we ran her up again on the, on the taxiway
and cleared out whatever the problem was.
And then we took off carefully,
left the gear down for a while,
as we, as we stayed within proximity to the airport.
And everything was fine.
So gear up and then off to,
off to Ferroaks.
And as I arrived there,
they said,
guess what?
We've got to spot on the hanger for you.
So I couldn't be happier about that.
I'm going to try and,
try and get a flight wedged in on Wednesday or Thursday.
This week, just some local flying.
Really to get just to get used to,
or build up the hours.
And then Saturday,
most likely,
now Ron and Marta and Chris are all coming in for our London week,
which we'll talk about later in the show
for the Britcasters,
or the UK podcasters, I should say.
They'll be coming in Saturday morning, I think.
So they'll probably be pretty fried.
And I'm just going to let them all recuperate on that Saturday.
And then I'll go and see my mom.
So,
anyway,
as I said,
I'll probably post a video of the Delta Shira later today,
just because it was, you know,
I found my camera.
Remember I was supposed to take it with me on vacation.
Sitting here in a whole different bag,
taking away.
And we're looking forward to a pretty exciting week.
We've got,
we're going to start opening up the data for our first listeners.
We're going to do a developer cast for that,
or a dev cast, I should say.
So,
that's also coming up on today's daily source code.
I could actually do three shows out of just all the stuff
that I've received today.
I kid you not.
Let's see.
Have a,
I got a couple of promos.
And this one actually fits into the flying,
something that I've been thinking about,
is how we can incorporate this type of content,
not the flying content,
but an important subject when it comes to aviation.
How we can incorporate that into podcasting.
I think that this podcast might have it cracked
or this system, I should say.
For weather information,
24 hours a day,
podweather.com,
internet partnership radio.
Number one,
and streaming severe weather coverage.
Internet partnership radio.
When it comes to severe weather,
we give it to you first.
You're listening to a breaking news update.
The potential for a few long tracks from tornadoes
in the super self underscores.
This is potentially a very dangerous situation.
And for live nationwide,
we're just looking right now at the satellite,
further,
blender,
and you definitely got to thunderstorm here.
And you've got some good lighting, right?
One in the past is night,
probably 4.81 is in the same.
I think that's going to go to weather right up.
It's going to indicate that it's a visual kick
raising a tornado.
It's very dangerous.
With a reputable storm chase,
or in the field with live,
report.
Look at the latest analysis.
So in that case,
hey Michael,
we've got a second tornado on the ground
to my north of my local internet partnership radio.
The only station to bring you live
is if you're weather coverage,
nationwide.
And after the event,
you can go to podweather.com
and download the chase video along with the entire audio
that's going to be brought to you all
by internet partnership radio.
There you go.
So all of your weather information,
whoops,
podweather.com.
Podweather.com,
everybody.
There you go.
Adam says,
Alex Wunschel
had a big laugh listening to the
mashup on the best of Charlie's
reminded me of my Adam Alex
mashup I did last September
in the 26 show on
pimpmybrain.de.
Hope you don't mind using yours in the show.
Here's a story,
a list of my show complained about my
endless umms and sent me a mashup
of my umms with more than a
minute worth length in length.
So at the time,
I decided to check the pod
father's umms versus mine
and lo and behold,
I won.
I got 81 umms in my episode number
24 and on your episode
of 31st of August,
you had only 55 umms.
Anyway,
I decided to let you hear
a little mashup of your umms
from daily source code
232.
And it is August 31st,
2005.
It's,
we had a,
um,
and,
truly the sign of a professional radio
pronounced a cater.
She just shuts up.
up, which I've tried to do as well. I think the silence is much nicer than the umms, but
man, you get used to that. It's hard to break it. See, I'm trying already. Steve Runners
on a big mission today from the forbid, forbid, forbid, forbid, forbid, it's podcast. I
can never remember the exact title, but you can find it at SteveRunner.com. Today he
is running in the Boston Marathon, and the guy's wired. He's going to be podcasting
the entire marathon, which seems to me you should get an award just for that, just for
talking while running, the marathon note less. At the same time, he has some kind of special hookup.
Every, he has a whole bunch of reporting points. You can read about it on SteveRunner.com.
Reporting points where when he passes that, I think he presses a button or something and then
an email goes out if you're subscribed to his list. He presubscribe me so I'm happy about that and
you can sign up for that as SteveRunner.com as well. And he's running in a pod show T-shirt,
which is fantastic. He sent me a picture. It's really, really cool. It's one of our ugliest T-shirts
by the way. It's not an official pod show T-shirt that's as one we'd actually want to give away to anyone.
I'm not quite sure how these things got into, got into circulation, but I really appreciate it's
Steve and he wouldn't take any sponsorship from pod show, which I offered. So what we'll do is we will
donate our sponsorship money to the following cause.
Hey Adam, it's Lian from the Las Vegas Bitties. We have fantastic news to share with you.
You know that the Las Vegas Bitties are doing the MS Walk here in New York City on April 23rd
at the Sunday. Well I wanted to give you an update. We have smashed the goal of $10,000 and have
already raised $12,900 as of this morning Friday April 14th. Thanks mostly to pod cast listeners
around the world. Our goal is now 15,000 and it's looking scarily like we can make it.
So if anybody out there is listening, you can go to www.bittiesforever.com, that's with the number
for, or you can go to bitticast.com, BIDDYCAST and click on the link to the National MS Society
to raise money to combat multiple sclerosis. This is amazing news for us. We're feeling really thrilled
about the whole thing. And if anybody else is going to be in New York on April 20th, a few days
before, we're going to be having a mad party at Joe's pub to celebrate the release of our
DVD and to celebrate the umpteen million dollars that we had just raised for MS research.
I hope you're well. I hope you had an awesome vacation and that nobody called you and evil
overlord while you were gone. Rock on. My girls do nutrition Christina continuously call me the evil
overlord. So the 23rd not just the bitties but also CC Chapman's going to be walking in that
and we will, as I said, we'll donate our sponsorship that we're going to give to Steve
Runner to the MS Walker, fantastic. And I do believe you guys can shatter the 15,000 mark.
Maybe even more. We did pretty damn well when we helped out Lee Wilkins with his dogs. We raised
I think 1,500 bucks very quickly. This is what I mean. That was like a year and a half ago.
Jeez. Time flies when you're having fun. Later in this podcast I'll tell you how you can
sign up to get into the data of podshow plus and the podcast delivery network. We're starting
off looking for listeners who are interested in development. We're going to set it up with a golden
ticket. Yeah, it's the most democratic way. So we're going to have a special podcast for
developers and the developer means you can you understand HTML and what is it? What's the
word I'm looking for? PHP. Thank you. That's really all you need to know. So almost anyone who's
really interested and motivated can participate in that and speaking of the golden ticket,
remember we handed out a golden ticket which was supposed to be an AV remote for your iPod.
But our winner, KJ did not have an iPod. So we sent them an iPod as a winner. Just proving that
people really do win on the daily source code. Thank you. I'm curious. I'm curious. Okay, you know,
you can't play with the iPod Nano. Yeah, steady. Thank you. Thank you. You sent me an iPod Nano,
a two gigabyte iPod Nano and you've got an inscription on the back that says two can from Adam Curry.
Keep podcasting, dude. I will. I will keep podcasting hopefully forever to the death.
Well, okay, it's not get too serious here. But yeah, dude, thank you, man. I was just standing there
in my BVDs and the doorbell rings. Actually, there was a knock on the door and it was FedEx.
They showed up and first thing in the morning, just before I got to work. So I get to load your show
on when I haven't heard today. Load that up and I'll listen to it on my way to work. Cool. Cool.
So dang, man. Thank you. Can't say it enough. Really.
I'm probably saying it too much. Dude, can. Thank you very much for listening, man. That's
what's all about. Really appreciate that. Nice touch, huh? The engraving on the back to Ken from Adam.
I think that has something to do with the, with the pod show HQ folks who are thinking on their
feet to have it inscribed. That's very cool. It almost, it probably should have said from
daily source code or stay tuned or something like that or stay subscribed. But the whole idea of
engraving the the iPod Nano as a prize is good. That's Sam Aaron Rosie. Someone up there is
thinking about stuff. Do you believe anything is possible? We do. Where are flink? We believe in an
internet that's safe from virus hidden scammers. We're Earthlink. We believe your personal
information should be just that, personal. And we believe your internet should be a friend,
not a foe. We're Earthlink. Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net and discover what
our internet experts can do for you, Earthlink. We revolve around you. Speaking of revolve around
anything, ladies and gentlemen, here he is. Once again, he's got his suit on. He's ready to close
that window. Please, say hi to the satellite fair, man.
You'll fix your misconceptions and answer questions too. There's nothing in the universe that you can't
do for you. What a satellite repair man. What a satellite repair man. What a satellite repair man.
That's right, everybody. It means P-dubs about to close the window for a listeners checking us out
on serious stars 102. Still to come today after this program in just seconds, Pacific Coast
hellway. Then you got a full hour of match with East Radio Dawn and Drew after that. Then
it's Gilmore Daily. And today we bring you the DVD weekly between, it was at 9 Eastern 9
and 930 Eastern and CC Chapman Ola will finish us up. I think he's going to do another
U-turn cafe tonight, although I'm not too sure. So enjoy the rest of your pod show line up on
serious. And we'll catch you tomorrow right here on the Daily Source Code. If you want to hear
more of the show, just go to dailysourcecode.com and hear what you're missing out on as of now.
That's right. It's just us again. You know, I think it was Friday. I played the song from
360 and what was the name of the song, resume. I really liked it because it was 13 performers in
the group and it was, it was R&B and I think the Podsive Music Network was at a certain point,
certainly very, very alternative rock heavy and that's definitely shifted and I liked that
balance. I mean, I found even fantastic classical songs, all kinds of good stuff there.
And I liked the the whole idea of kind of giving my resume. I'd like to be your girl. You know,
it's an interesting lyric. It was kind of cool. And I just played it because I was looking around
for stuff and it just popped up somewhere. I can't remember, well, you know, it's like that
social media network stuff on the Podsive Music Network. You never know how you find it,
but once you pop around from song to show, from show to song, from song to show, then all
sudden you find some stuff you like. And I got this message over the Easter weekend and it
really touched me because I had no idea what 360 was all about, but have a listen for yourself.
Adam, this is Wes. I'm the director of the music recording program at the Richmond Police
Activities League in Richmond, California. The the program that the 360 group came out of and I just
wanted to send you a shoutout and thank you for playing our song Resume on your DSC number 360
plus seven and show. And I got a couple of kids with me from the program. We just had a little event
today. Saturday went out to a little place, little theme park to have some fun. Anyway, what's not
real obvious about the group is that this was an after school program that was started in 2003
by myself with the goal of teaching kids how to use computers to make music. And I wanted
I wanted them to make the best music that they could. So for for those years, we basically spend a
lot of time going over our music and feeling very proud and building a sense of community and
kind of forming a little family. So I'm really, really proud and really happy of all the work that
they've done. And to the community of podcasters out there, I also want to thank everyone out there
who played our music because every time you play one of our songs, it motivates the kids in the
group to continue doing this stuff. So thank you guys for doing all of that. And the two members
that I have with me are loaded and looness and I got looness on my left. The wheel. The wheels.
And I got loaded. So you guys want to give a shout? Yeah, you know, just want to give a shout
out to the whole bag. You know, we come when we're on the rise right here. Give a shout out to
my city rich man, you know, from central to south side, you know, some of our bea dogs and everything,
you know, we keep keeping the flame. And so yeah, we just want to say thank you, you know, to you
and the listeners for listening. So our music that we have, you know, we're doing big things,
great things, you know, loaded, loaded made the beats in the music for the song that's
up there called love. So if you have a jump on that song, it's a really good song. I highly
enjoyed me. And then, then looness. Yeah, man, check it out. You should blow the looness, man.
Just want to thank you for being able to be able to play our music. You feel me,
not a lot of people get the opportunities that we have. And you know, just for you to be able
to be able to play our stuff. And for us to be able to hear it, you feel me. It's just a great
irony for me. And I respect you for what you do. As well as I see that you respect us for what
we do. I want to thank all who played our music, any kind of our music, any pieces of our music,
you know, me. Thank you all because you got people that put the flame to the fire. You feel me.
Gotcha. And then, uh, real psyching me. And if you can't be about it,
yeah, I mean, don't do it. You feel me because this music thing has a lifestyle. You just can't
get it over. And I just feel me. It's not about the ice.
Man, I'm telling you, man, it's all about the music, man. How you feeling inside? Because, you know,
everything we sing, everything we rap is real. We see it on the streets every day.
All we live it every day in our lives. Give me so I want to give a shout out to y'all.
Shout out to the Bay Area coming up on the 40s catch right now, man. Real good.
Real good. Real good.
It's been for real, man. It's been for real, man. It's been for real where it's all started.
You feel me. Much a lot of money. The worse you feel me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, that's what's up.
All right. With that. Thank you, guys. Um, but don't forget, it's www dot losspants dot
com 4 slash 3 6 0. And, uh, please come back and take a look at the website and make any kind of comments
you want on the blog. So thanks a lot, Adam. Hello. Holla. Holla back at you.
Now, you know what those are true American heroes? That's that that is the America that I love.
You know, just trying to make something happen, trying to get some positive going and, you know,
what it really worked. I had no idea what this project was about. Um, when I played the song,
it was just a great jam. I loved it. Uh, so I'll be sure to to play more and other podcasters.
And listeners too, go to the music dot podshot.com. Look up 360 and you'll be able to hear a whole
bunch of songs that they've been working on in that California. Okay. So UK podcasters pay attention.
Please, the point is, we're going to have some draft and dots, which is what we've been talking
about for the past week. Um, we have Ron coming over his lovely wife Marta and our, uh,
copied it to the copy of business development Chris Jacob. And we're going to be in London,
uh, we'll say they're they're arriving Saturday. And I believe Chris is staying all week and Ron and
Marta are going back on Thursday, probably, probably Thursday or late morning or early afternoon,
because we have a couple of meetings lined up, some stuff that made a term and, or will determine
how, uh, if and how we want to do anything in the UK market, um, expensive over here. We start
looking at what it costs to actually run a business and you got a time, you got to do that
times too to come up with the dollar amount. Uh, so what we wanted to do is we wanted to have a,
a get together just to hang to meet with some of the, the forces in UK pod casting. And we've been
discussing this for the past, uh, maybe even the past couple of weeks. And so now we have a date set.
It's going to be Sunday, um, because they, uh, they come inside a day. They're going to be totally
wrecked. I want to go visit my mom anyway. So Sunday, why don't we all meet in London or the London
area? So the only thing we need now, and I'm just going to pick a time. I'm going to say 3 p.m. Okay,
let's just say 3 p.m. I'm not a good, everyone who wants has to come from from, excuse me,
since say, oh, from further away, give some chance to get in. You know, it's not to, you know,
not to messed up traffic wise. Well, of course, there'll be Sunday, so it shouldn't be too bad.
Anyway, he don't have to pay that congestion charge. Uh, all we need now is a venue.
Now Ray Lane, who's one of our board of directors sent in his suggestion, Ray is listening a
lot these days. He's in real time now, almost. He's given me feedback almost every day,
which is putting me on my guard. He, uh, he suggested Wigan Penn, which is in Surrey. Now, of course,
Surrey's pretty big, but I could figure out whether it was. If anyone knows if Wigan Penn is a
possibility, or do we want to go more into the London area? What I suggest is we've got our dates,
Sunday, 3 p.m. Maybe the UK podcasters can get together and hash it out on Britcaster.com,
or whatever wiki I saw that was up and running, and just give us the right venue. We're not looking
for something fancy, schmancy. I don't think we want to rent out a whole place. I don't know how many
people are coming if we have a head count yet. I'm just looking for a corner of the old Vic,
personally, for draft and darts. But let me know. We can certainly put together a little budget if we
have to, if it looks like so many people are coming, we have to have some extra space. I'd like
you guys to help us out. So don't email me directly, set it up, you know, get the conversation going,
and what I'll do is, here's what we'll do. After, after all this set and done, maybe Neil Dixon
can send me an email and let me know, you know, what the final two or three choices are,
or what the options are, or just what the decision is, because we have no idea what's going on
in this market, where you can get beer and play darts and have a good chat. The music can't be too loud,
you know, we want to have ambiance. You understand what I'm talking about. It's funny because I,
I looked at Neil's website, his blog this morning. Neildixon.com, and he has a post here,
which really blew me away. The post title is Britcaster.podshow.com. There, that'll start the
tongues wagging. He says, in the past few days, since the word going out about Adam Curry wanting to meet
UK podcasters and my well-timed Skype interview with him to be available soon, I've now had five
conversations. Yes, five of varying degrees of seriousness and intensity, asking when Britcaster.com
will sell out in some way to a London UK division of Podshow Inc. Truly astonishing. He got to read that post.
Dude, we haven't even set foot on the shores here and already we're the evil empire.
My god. Well, Neil, I hope you post that interview soon, because we talked about exactly
this type of stuff in that Skype interview. You don't have to edit it either. Just put the
whole freaking thing out, dude. No reason to pare it down. Let everyone hear every single piece of
that. I think that'll be really good, including the part where you stopped because you were afraid
that audio hijack pro would crash if you didn't start a new audio file. Please do that, will you?
So everyone can just hear what's going on and not start, oh man, I thought we were more sophisticated
over here. The slam idol podcast, which is recently celebrated is one year anniversary, is now in
the midst of the voting process on contest 10. The contestants are Mike McGee. The sound of
a heartbeat and laughter in all the time it takes to learn to fall from the sky. Down the hall
and right into love. Why is it, right? That we have a president who has blatantly
defrauded the people of his country at the ballot box twice, Haran Alkalaga.
I have learned that stupidity is not an affliction, but an addiction of mine until
real eyes. I have a problem in remedy, yet with comments.
Health and lifestyle have been rearranged. My feelings for you have never changed. You've made
a choice to distrust and dislike. And David Goodchild. Brainspokes, brainspokes, brainspokes,
brainspokes, brainspokes, a bread. My stain in angels telling an A and crying. You could list
all the poems and cast your votes. At the slam idol website, slam idol.trypot.com.
If you have not listened to the slam idle podcast, go there and check it out.
It took me a while to figure even out what was going on there, but if you like spoken
word, if you like intense poetry and I'm talking modern, really modern stuff, you'll
like this.
In fact, I want this stuff on the Pod Show podcast network.
I really like this idea and just thought the content is so amazing it blows me away.
So check that out, the slam idle podcast and it's time to vote for your favorites.
Hey Adam, P.D. Love from Love House Radio and the Daddycast.
Have to tell you, this past Friday I made it out to Nashville for the Pod Safe Showcase
with Matthew Eble, Kevin Reeves and Jeff Smith and that was a big thrill.
It was amazing to, well, first of all, to see them perform live, but also just to meet
the guys and I mean, just the nicest set of guys ever and it just, in talking to Matthew
before the show, it just seems that this is something that could be done all across the
country and maybe that, you know, Pod Show could get involved in sponsor some of these events
and kind of have like the the Pod Show music series or the unlabelable.
Whenever I hear the unlabel, I'll keep waiting for some guy to hop out of the woods
going, it's crisp and clean.
Anyway, just, you know, we were talking about it and it would be great to do these
things all over the place.
I mean, you have pockets of Pod Safe artists that are all in the P.M.N. all over
the country.
You see, he's got the group up in Boston and just to have something where they can get
together and do a showcase of all the Pod Safe people and the thing is that this,
the, all artists just represent it, podcasting and the P.M.N.N. and everything right along
with their music, it just goes into the whole community between podcasters and the musicians
and everybody.
So, again, it was a great event, you should have been there and I'm sure you can hear it
once they get all the good audio off the board.
I've got the, the crappy audio from the crowd on my site, but, you know, it's, it was a great
event and just kind of sparks some ideas and I'll throw in my hat and the ring if I can
do anything to help and kick off some of these Pod Safe Show cases all over the place.
So, just wanted to pass that along to you and again, if you can find any way to do it
and need some help by all means let me know.
I'm at lovehouseradio.com or thedaddycast.com.
Thanks a lot Adam.
Peter Loaf.
Thank you very much, man.
Yeah, we've been talking about this.
I've been talking to Matthew about it and this has been going around the offices quite
a bit.
Now, what's not going to happen, most likely won't happen.
Pod Show does doesn't have the money to sponsor a series of Pod Safe Music shows.
There's no real revenue model yet that take it sales, but, you know, I don't think that's
really or, you know, or we could be selling your CDs and take a cut and don't want to
do that.
It's just going to cost too much money.
Just giving an idea and we had a chance and brother love perform at the portable media
expo.
They stood on a, on a riser had like a flashlight on them and there was a little bit
of PA.
I think that costing a five grand right there, you know, it's travel costs and it's all
that stuff.
So, it doesn't just way too expensive.
However, we have been working very, very hard on a big sponsor who actually has venues
where we could set this up in multiple locations.
So it would be a professional venue.
It would be probably these venues anywhere from 500 to 1500 people.
There would be people already in the neighborhood who would wander in.
It's, you know, there's food and drinks and all kinds of great stuff like that.
And it would be sponsored by, by a big entity.
And we've been working on that, which means that, you know, musicians can get paid even.
Maybe some travel expenses taking care of all that groovy stuff.
But certainly for, you know, pay, play for pay and for promotion.
We're still working on the, on the contracts, still working on this deal, but we'll let
you know about it as soon as possible, of course.
And I'm pretty, I'm pretty confident it's going to, it's going to happen, just had to
call about it last week.
Now, of course, when you have a sponsor that, you know, there's a lot of stuff that you've
got a massage and mold into one, so you don't wind up with like a really lame name for
the events or something like that, you know, when people put up the money, they always
want to have something back in return.
So we're working on that stay tuned, more info about that coming here on the Charlie.
Wouldn't it be cool if you could get instrumental music, just to listen to, or for background
music on your podcast or just do whatever you wanted with, I could say you wanted some
rock ability.
We'll be some sort of techno stuff, some blues, some R&B, some stuff with some groovy
organ and stuff with a good beat, something a little bit, spacey and melancholy.
Well, you know, it would be cool, and you can get it.
If you go to podcast.painmachine.com, I'm Derek Miller, and I've made all this music, and
you can have it for free.
You can put it on your podcast, you can mix it up, you can mash it up, you can burn it
to CD, you can do whatever you want with it, just give me credit and share it around.
You can subscribe and get a new song whenever it's ready.
Join thousands of music fans and podcasters around the world, listen to the pen machine
podcast, or look it up at your favorite podcast directory like the iTunes Music Store,
or the Podsape Music Network.
That's podcas.painmachine.com, thanks.
Derek K Miller, man, we are so in sync with the vision for mashing up our art, I really
feel that you're on the right track, the Jeff Smith is doing the same thing, you know,
yeah, go ahead, you can take this stuff, you can do whatever you want with it, give me
credit, and if you're going to make money off of it, please cut me in, you know, no
to find me, let me know.
We're going to work that out.
And within what we're building, the social media network that is known as podshow plus,
that is going to be a part of it, and we already have some of those pieces working.
And remember, I've talked about, you know, social reward and economic reward, where,
you know, just getting the credit is the social reward, and people saying that was cool,
and then if there's any finances that come into it a sale or transaction of some sort,
of course, everyone who was contributed to this would want a financial reward, we,
George's Russian scientist, I think we're talking to him this week is getting very close
to being able to identify pieces as they've been matched up so that we can, you know,
deconstruct that and make a lot of that credit, both social and financial, completely
automatic.
Does that make any sense?
It barely makes ends to me, but I know that we're getting somewhere close with something
very, very cool.
So, I think we just continue to keep matching as we go along, and man, are we matching?
We're matching up arms and arms, we're matching up music, and that's why I just make sure
that you give out the credit for now, and we'll be good.
Hello.
Uh-oh.
Forgive me, podfather, for I have sinned.
I've missed a couple of episodes of Charlie right after your vacation since I too was traveling.
So you may have addressed this previously, and if you have, I apologize for bringing it up
again.
But hey, this is Chip from Top of the Potsay, so over at crushland.com.
I was curious to know if you're going to try out the new max off where it runs windows,
and that way you could run cast blaster on your Mac.
It's even make your life easier, so you don't have to carry around two laptops.
If you are going to try this out of this curious, if Bootcamp was going to be more to
you're liking or parallels was, and querying minds want to know, let me know.
You know, I haven't loaded that yet.
I've learned that you don't want to mess around with too much stuff down at the OS level
with data.
I've messed up some pretty good installs doing that.
I did, however, see that there was some other project.
I think K2 sent a note to me about that.
Let me see.
There's some other similar application, hold on a second, Kevin, and let me see Bootcamp.
There's something similar that's out there that I believe is, no, that's not working,
that I believe is open source, and it actually allows you to load both the here it is.
Shoot, no, that's not what I'm looking for.
It allows you to, I'll find out and I'll put it in the show notes.
What it does is it allows you to load your Mac OS and then run actual windows applications
in a window inside Mac OS.
So you're basically loading up both OS at the same time.
And that, now that to me seems like something very interesting.
I'm not quite sure how far along they are in the project and the process.
If all the drivers are supported, et cetera, it may be much simpler than it was in emulation
mode because all that stuff basically already works with windows with a dual boot.
So it should be possible.
I'll find, I'm sorry for the bad preparation on my part there.
I'll find the link to whatever that application was and I'll put that in the show notes.
I'm going to try that one because, yeah, duh, it would be so super cool.
You know, I run two computers when doing the show.
I have my, to Shiba where I run cast blaster, that's the main music unit.
And then I have my Mac where I'm running, I'm the outliner pro.
And that's where I have the rundown of everything that I'm going to do in the show.
Actually, the files are embedded within that outline document.
So when you export it to a folder, it actually exports all the files.
And then you can import them right into cast blaster.
So having that on one machine, yeah, no doubt will be totally cool.
But I have no idea what the support is.
And if anyone has loaded windows with boot camp on their Mac, let me know if cast blaster works.
Okay, you can find it at castblaster.com.
Hey Adam, grab a cup.
This is jam and Dave Jackson, this smiling host of the musicians cooler.
And why am I smiling?
That's right, the musician's cooler is now the newest member of the pod show family.
It's simple.
The musician's cooler is where musicians come to trade advice.
For years, I've produced the musician's cooler newsletter.
A newsletter by musicians for musicians found at musicianscooler.com.
And with the development of technology, it rapidly evolved into a podcast.
We've interviewed hundreds of successful musicians and entertainment lawyers,
booking agents, photographers, promoters, and authors as we spotlight new techniques and new
technologies to help musicians get more fans, more gigs, and more music sales.
We've shared mentoring moments with heavy hitters in the music industry,
as well as leaders and pioneers who provide state-of-the-art tools for musicians.
So again, that addresses musicianscooler.com.
I'll see you over there as I take the musician's cooler to the next level,
as the newest member of the pod show family.
And in the immortal words of Randy Boffman of BTO, he won't see nothing yet.
Stay cool.
It's not the toilet flush.
Dude, welcome to the network.
Great to have you here. And yeah, I really did what's going on at the musicianscooler.com.
You should check it out for sure.
portions of this pod cast brought to you by Ackyview.
Check out Heather and John L's pod cast at download.ackyview.com.
ACU-VU-E. Speaking of my list in the Omnioutliner Pro,
I'm only three quarters of the way through it.
I think we're going to go just a little bit long today.
Hey, Adam, this is Travis Goss, one of the hosts of the on radio show.
Thank you for playing my promo in Charlie No. 366.
That was really cool if you had to do such a thing.
And I got a question.
I'm really interested in joining pod show.
And I'm sure my co-host would do the same too.
But I was wondering, how does one go about getting a contract?
Because I think this show that I have is very, very, very...
Well, it's okay, I suppose.
But I like to really, really blow the lid off of this thing.
But I'm just wondering.
How in the world is one get a contract for pod show?
Can you pull a few strings just like that?
I mean, I'm a big, big fan of pod casting.
I think this is a wonderful medium.
And whatever strings you could pull to get a contract
sent over here would be wonderful.
Thanks, Adam.
Keep up the good work.
You know what?
The Charlie rules.
Oh, thanks, dude.
Let me just pull a string here.
Let me pull that one.
Okay.
If you want a pod show contract, contact Keith and the girl.
Dude.
Now, there's multiple levels.
I believe there's four.
And what I'll do around, see if we can do it the Thursday,
will announce the actual levels that you can utilize
or the different ways.
Level is not the right description.
There will be different ways you can become a part of pod show,
work with pod show, or just use pod show stuff.
And one of the ways is you can just,
if you want the pod cast delivery network and you want the services,
the basic technology services that come with that,
you can just buy it.
You don't have to do any other business with us other than pay us
on a monthly basis, and you'll get all the functionality, everything.
And I actually believe that there will be people who will just want to buy it.
Then that's going to be a very simple arrangement for an add insertion.
You'll have one tag at the beginning of your pod cast
and a tag at the end, and you use everything for free.
And then there's two other pieces that, well, one,
you have to be invited into, essentially.
And there's a number of factors and reasons why you could be invited
into the network to participate in bigger promotional deals.
One is you just ask.
So you're kind of on the right track already.
I had them.
Yes.
This is Marta, the podcast diva.
Pick me up on my podcast.
It's all about Marta and me.
You can also find me at it's all about Marta and me.com.
Give me the girl, baby.
Yeah, she sent me a picture.
I got to post that in the show notes.
It's a cutout.
Strategically cutout poster.
Yeah, that's how to get in my good side of it.
From the pod save music network, Henta, mirrored love.
I kind of find you, the longer you may see,
you'll never find time to wait tight.
There's only one now, and that's to find with you.
There's only one place that you can hide.
Holy, your dreams become a little brighter.
Holy, how do you open the ring box?
Oh, we're gonna find it.
But gonna find the hell right now.
I think it's in my mirror.
Oh, love, yeah, the ring ball.
We hold up.
Yeah, the ring ball.
I think it's in my mirror.
We hold up, yeah, the more tight you're gonna watch.
You're the people who shone.
I'll hide tight gonna watch them all the way.
Untie the lead, let your be shown.
I gonna watch them, watch them all the way.
Holy, your dreams become a little brighter.
Holy, how do you open the ring box?
Oh, we're gonna find it.
But gonna find the hell right now.
I think it's in my mirror.
Oh, love, yeah, the ring ball.
We hold up, yeah, the ring ball.
Oh, love, love, love, love, love, love.
I think it's in my mirror.
We hold up, yeah, the more tight you're gonna watch.
I want to watch you in my tent.
I think it's in my mirror.
We hold up, yeah, the more tight you're gonna watch.
You're the person you're the first person.
You're the person you're the first.
I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror,
I take it to my mirror, I take it, to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it as my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take makeup, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, I take it to my mirror, take
Hand to let me know if you're performing anywhere in the in the in the greater gilford metropolis
I'd love to come and check your stuff out for sure
Information coming up on the golden ticket to get into the pod show plus and podcast delivery network just minutes away
After this from David Epolyto. Hey Adam, it's David Epolyto that guitar man from central park in New York City
I just wanted to reach out to say thank you for driving that that lead covered wagon into this new frontier
You know, I'm an independent musician. I have been for years. I'm a very very lucky man. I love my life
But all of us for years have been trying to find different ways to get music out there to people, you know, and
And it was actually the guy who runs my website's idea to join the pod safe music network
We joined in the first week of March
Two days later where we were getting played on podcasts all over the world now. I think we've been played on
36 shows maybe more probably more. I've made friends with some of the podcasters
I've talked to other musicians and turned them on to it and they've they've all joined the pod safe network
It's just a very very exciting thing
Actually, I'm wondering we're debating now the pros and cons of I think my next CD might not be a CD
We might just make it downloadable. I can't wait to start really selling music on the network. So
I just wanted to say thanks again. Keep it up. It's all a very very cool thing
No, dude, you are cool
You've been bust in your ass for years in central parks on days mainly I believe and yeah
This is how the stuff works now if you had 36 podcas players song let's say that the average
podcast, you know, you played it on the source code. So that's gonna up your average quite a bit
Let's say it's a thousand let's say it's a thousand listeners
36 thousand people who have heard your music of course. That's gonna translate into people coming to see you donating buying your
Your CDs and yes, of course
I know that they're going to buy tracks
MP3's free and clear no DRM off of the pod safe music network. I'm I'm so confident because we're seeing it work
With artists who are already testing with and it's really really working. I mean hundreds for tracks. It's just freaking awesome
And I believe that we're
Anyone who comes into pod show plus I think you'll also
Around the third of May you'll also have the full
Access to buying songs. I think I'm not quite sure. I have to look at the at the schedule
But as you can tell we're starting to release stuff so we're starting to
Get people into the networks starting to let people
Experience it for yourself so
Stay tuned to the source code stay subscribe because we'll be bringing you more opportunities to try
Out as we start to unleash an unveil everything over the next 14 to
Next 14 to 30 days before we're a completely open in public beta and anyone can jump into the mess that we're making
Including the French band with bastard who sent me an email
Adam nobody's perfect it's one of those lazy French bastards who's writing to you
That's what my English is so bad. I know I know all that bad bar
And as a lazy fellow I can't figure out myself how much ban with I'll need to start my podcast
I went to go daddy.com and I feel that 500 gigabytes per month would be more than enough
What's your point of view on that is go daddy a good hosting platform for a young podcast
The answer is go daddy is great for domain names. It's great for web logs. It's great for
Your email and and yes if you have
If you don't aspire to huge amounts of downloads of course, it's fantastic you can even get discounts
By using one of the DSC codes DSC one two or three when you check out and
I think today I should put again in the show notes. I should put a link as to what you exactly get but it's great discounts
So yes absolutely
Now if you expect to grow then you may want to check out the pod
Pod show podcast delivery network
But that may not be until a month or so
Depending on how fast we get everyone start rolling in
So definitely once you take on a monthly basis and then see if you like it and see if the works out and see if 500 gigs a month is is enough
It wouldn't be enough from me. I'll tell you that. I'm moving to her about it's unbelievable. What's what we're shipping out the door on our pdn
Let's see what do we have here
Sorry so far
I need a photo for the cover of a tree pod
And I need a by next Monday
I'm not funny exactly what I want
It's an identity theft privacy type of shot
I'll send you the details
All right, come in. I'll do it
Find out how a simple photo shoot goes completely wrong and teaches this photographer a few lessons
Or two or three
Listen to the whole story on the next photo cast available at edd hidden dot com
It's podcast
Hey Adam this is Dave from the David matcho. I was trolling through our server logs the other day and after a few who has looked up
So I realized we had a new listener one Adam Curry from Gilford, England. So if that was you checking out the show man
We totally appreciate it if anybody listened into the Charlie wants to hear our show
You can check out www.dave and matcho.com. Thanks a lot take care Adam. Yeah, my IP address is so well known now
And although I think I thought I had changed the
The Nick info on that so it just says uh was it say
Curry co or something or silicon pole or something like that
Apparently that hasn't changed everywhere
Wouldn't it be cool if you could actually identify your listeners that way?
That is a part of what pod show plus is when someone is listening to you and I mean listening
You know you can call it subscribed if you want and that's a part of it
But if they're in your audience you're gonna see it and not only you're gonna see it just by a name
But you're gonna see someone's picture and you're gonna be able to find out more about them and see what they're subscribed to and what pod
See if music they're listening to and this is how the social media network is gonna come together
So I like the fact that you're thinking that way. I hate the fact that all my
Information is still openly available on the net that way
But the the concept of knowing who your audience is and being able to put faces to them
Oh man, I'm really you know because it's all closed
I only have what I only have like 23 listeners
Within pod show plus who are listening to the daily source code because I'm basically crossposting everything
They I in fact I'm actually using that system all the time and then I cut and paste stuff out into my wordpress blog or to the daily source code.com
feed
But it you'll love it. You really will it's extremely cool now
to get into the
podcast library network and to
Start messing out messing around with pod show plus and everything that we've been building for the past
10 months
What we're looking for first up is for developers who are interested and who would like to contribute
And there will actually be some some opportunities there for both social and economic reward for you
And here's how it's gonna work now already I've gotten a ton of email from developers who want in and when I said developer
I'm really talking about web development skills that include HTML and PHP and maybe a little bit of CSS
But even that's not necessary. So that's just that's millions and millions of people. I know that so many people understand those two
technologies very well and you'll be able to contribute making modules for pod show plus which you can whip up in
in five minutes or five hours and it's just depending on what complexity you want to put in there
But it's really really simple you get an SDK
There's going there's a developer site developer dot pod show dot com and to get it rolling
Today I'm going to do
I don't know if I'm going to do two separate Skype calls or or one I'll start off with Andrew Grummit
Who was really leading our developer program and who has extensive knowledge of everything we're doing in the underpinnings and then
Excuse me
It's because I've gone over an hour already. You know now this and say it was talking back to me
Also want to talk to Kevin Astrosky
known as K1 who has really been the the the managing developer on on all of this stuff and
They'll start and it will just make a separate podcast to make it a separate podcast feed
You'll be able to find that easily and we're just going to you know just talk about what's going on
What what kind of opportunities are to create cool stuff and then obviously we're going to put in I think
50 golden tickets in that podcast so there may only be a hundred people who subscribe to it
That means that half of them will get an invite and we're going to make it really really simple
We'll probably even well
When you hear the the golden ticket then you'll know exactly how to get into
Into the system how to get an account and how to get rolling so
That will be posted up on curry dot com later today
I was you know when Kevin and Andrew get in that'll probably be
Was it to 5 p.m. My time so I probably won't post it until this evening UK time
But you'll certainly be able to subscribe to it by tomorrow and and it doesn't matter
When you subscribe to it because let's say only 25 25 people subscribe
Actually not have to think about how we're going to make it work you're going to do multiple episodes
That's right multiple episodes. I think I will do it separately with Andrew and separately with Kevin. There you go
So even if you subscribe now and you don't get the golden ticket by the next episode you might be eligible for the golden ticket
And we'll just keep it keep it going until obviously we can start letting everybody in and won't take all that long
But if you want to get an early want to get in start helping us out and doing some cool stuff and maybe making some coin
Keep an eye on curry dot com for the link to the developer the dev cast
For pod show plus and the pod cast delivery network now to wind it up. I've got a promo and
One more piece of feedback from comic strip blogger who has been all over the situation with
Member states of the European Union
Allowing or not allowing other
Member state workers to come in and
freely cross the border and and work in a different country and
He is I believe of Polish descent and
The polls are in high demand across Europe because in Poland
I think your monthly salary may be no more than about 500 bucks a month
Whereas they can make
1500 a month in other
Member states of the European
Union now of course these are different countries but the concept of the European Union is
Just like the United States where you can go from Connecticut to New York and you don't have to show your passport and you can
Work just as happily New York as you could in California or in Texas or in Maine or wherever
And the Netherlands is I believe all countries are supposed to allow this as of January 1st
2007 most countries already do the Netherlands
Doesn't at the moment they've limited it to 35,000 I believe I'm not an expert on this and
There's a lot of polls who would really like to come to the Netherlands and to work and and it's interesting because I saw a whole documentary on this just the other day
These are highly educated people these are doctors these are teachers these are librarians you know these are
People school in law people school in
police work and you know they're literally working in
In jobs that you know and only for limited time so they'll come over to a country like the UK or Germany I believe
and they'll work in
In a greenhouse you know potting plants and they'll do that for three months they'll load up on cash
And then they'll go back to Poland and they'll take the rest of the year off which is of course
Not the way Poland should be run but it's working you know and everyone seems to be happy
And the Netherlands was supposed to make their decision I believe
In the past week and since there's so much political turmoil in that country they they pushed it off and they said well, you know what
That can be looked at at the end of the year
That probably has something to do with elections and you know where the it's just shifting of power that's going on
No one wants to
Win or lose is important debate and topic depending on what side of the fence you're on
So that is actually I really do enjoy reading that that thread that conversation thread on
Curry dot com which is where it seems to take place between a couple of Dutch posters and comic strip blogger
And today he sent in well, you know, it might be a little set about properly since we're way over
comic strip no penalty for having fun
comic strip
whole different blogger today
Let me convey a final message to numerous Dutch fuckers to your podcast fucking final
I am not black, but now I know how African Americans were feeling when they were first to slave labor at
Plantations in USA and get no freedom of movement
I know because Netherlands the nice me and other new use it is freedom of movement too
I am not muslim, but now I know how muslims who are living in Netherlands are feeling when they have to live
in a country that treats them as strangers and when native folks the Dutch give them absolutely no respect
I know because Dutch don't give me an respect to
yes
by end of April 2006
Netherlands had to give their decision about opening for new use citizens and their answer and decision is
no sack of you lesser people
two years have passed since big bank EU enlargement
not to confuse with pencil enlargement and Dutch still are racist pigs and not liberal
they are extirting or fucking lovers of humanity as they try to portray themselves
fuck you Dutch
Now blogger I understand how you feel although I don't think your comparisons are really on par there
because slavery, working in slave is a little different than not being allowed to work somewhere else
so I gotta call you out on that
you know this is not the Dutch are not racist I don't believe you can say any people is racist
but there's a lot of protectionism going on I was in a took a cab from Rotterdam Airport to
Bullscope where my mom lives about 25 30 minute journey and I got one of these really typical
Rotterdam cab drivers I got his card as well by the way I said core next time I'm coming in
I'm calling you because you're my man you're doing ground logistics from Rotterdam
fucking awesome this is in your typical you know 250 pound guy bald head earring
you know looking like Mr. Clean kind of has a fine ord that's the the Rotterdam football team
for those you don't know has a fine ord flag in the back window
total Rotterdam guy and they've had huge immigration issues and integration issues in the so-called
multicultural society in Rotterdam and I'll just give an example of how I think protectionism can be
often misconstrued by words of course with racism so he does about 150 euros a day on a good day
driving his cab and they recently about a year and a half or two years ago they deregulated
cab the the the the taxi business so anyone can basically become a cabby it's much easier
to get into it you don't have to pay huge license fees etc you have to take a test but
now what that did of course is it fucked up the whole taxi industry and now there's way too many
cabs and what you see is that there's a shitload of immigrants is what I'll call them people
from other countries who have immigrated to the Netherlands who have the proper paperwork
have the proper vehicle but they're you know they have basically no work because there's just too many
cabs and if you go to light supply and Amsterdam now anyone who's who's going to go there in the
neck and in the future you'll see it about 10 o'clock at night there will be 150 cabs lined up just
waiting for rides and they'll be waiting for hours because you know there's too many cabs and you know
the one cab goes and three more cue up in the back so of course what you see there is a lot of
illegal activity and what the these these new cab drivers often resort to is illegal activity such
as you know dealing drugs or other types of you know they do drive around but they're probably
you know delivering stuff that is illegal and into into stuff that's no good but they're using
the the same system to um longer their money so you know you just make sure you drive some miles
and then you say okay today I made 400 euros which is about the 500 bucks and I'm going to you know
they actually say to the you say to the tax man here's what I made on the made 400 bucks every day
this week every day this month every day this year and so I'll pay my taxes but that's illegal money
okay so they've just wandered that perfectly which of course is works great in a cash business like the
taxi cab business here's hello geos almost done I was just in the middle of the
oh thank you what do we have today today we have a lovely cold glass of milk we have nice
presentation again dear yeah getting front of the microphone please I hate it when you stand in the
middle so we have a sandwich here which has ooh avocado and smoked salmon yeah and in salad on that
and that is in the middle we have a nice row of crisps which is English for potato chips
yeah and the napkin nicely folded thank you on that's beautiful I got a question from a
Jennifer she wanted to know the cocktail sauce you put on the avocado filled with shrimp yesterday
would you that your own cocktail sauce yes oh would you please tell her how you made it is mayo mayo
any mayo you like favorite mayo ketchup a little bit of paprika powder yeah
paprika powder yeah and a little bit of whipped cream in there oh really yeah and actually
actually you need a little bit of whiskey in there just a dash just a dash but of course
us it being the drinkers that we are we have zero whiskey yeah but a real pink cocktail sauce
is being cocktail sauce is just just a couple of drops just for the whipped cream in there a
little bit really whipped cream and interesting okay so that's it thank you you're welcome
I'm going to finish up my rant and then I will enjoy my lovely lunch yeah because there's it's a
mixture of salmon and tuna tuna salad made by your daughter yesterday oh that's right she made
that for all and we have our own recipe with little pieces of apple onion and celery
mix with a little bit of lemon mayo am I lucky guy or what
who said I heard another version of remember we were watching Denny Crane yes he said the woman
I just met is and he said he's angel in the bed in the bed room and a horror in the kitchen and then
David Spader says isn't that the other way around and he says not last time all right baby love you thank
okay back to the rant so you've got the the real cab driver who's doing 150 euros a day and you've
got the illegal guy who's doing illegal stuff the guy who's doing illegal stuff doing 400 a day
laundering his money so what happens is the tax man then says to core the legal guy hey
how come you're only doing 150 we're all these other guys are doing 400 we think you're trying to
duct taxes you understand the problem so the Dutch I think are very poor at voting their
conscience very very bad at it you know you get the government you deserve as it's a democracy they
can vote for people to come in to come out I the whole party system I'm not a big fan of
in the coalitions and all that but you know whatever that's their system it's been working
for almost a thousand years so that's that that'll be good three quarter of a thousand years
whatever it is incredibly long time hundreds and hundreds of years but what it what's the easiest
thing to say it's to get those fucking people out of here they're the problem we're of course the
policy really is the problem and not the people lead me not into temptation all that groovy stuff
so I appreciate the feedback there CSB even though I don't agree with it 100% kick kick again one more time
yo how are you doing this jersey Totten if you want to win a copy of Danco Jones is
sleep at the enemy you gotta come over to the jersey Tot Show it WWE that jersey Tot Show.com
I'll tell you all about how you're going to get your copy this is an unbelievable album it rocks
it is your summertime anthem right now so come on over to the jersey Tot Show at WWE that jersey
Tot Show.com and remember people really win on the jersey Tot Show
really loving those Danco Jones kids now
I love all right I'm sorry we went way long today some people like it some people don't
like it I hope you got out of it what you thought you would get out of it for today Adam and
Curry dot com for your feedback daily source code dot com for the the feed for this podcast and
for the latest episodes and I leave you of course with ours I just love when I hear Mike doing that
I'll talk to you tomorrow everybody take care about mine another pod show podcast stick it in your ear
get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network
from pod show and limelight networks I love it