Already a hit state side, now you can check out the following podcast and good old
blightybtpodshot.com, single-handedly making a man's for giving you Madonna.
One show at a time.
In a world, we're men, we're comfortable shoes, and not much else.
Prancing around in his underwear and his egg boots in the morning.
That's not right.
Where Dutch pop stars are stopped by paparazzi.
I don't think I've seen it this bad.
And where the world seems to have gone crazy.
Hey, John!
She walks squeeze her by.
It's squeezing the butt.
One man stands out.
Oh, I said sail with some splendor.
But look, nasty.
One man heads the call.
Wait a minute, aren't we, uh, as another, uh, how was it?
One man delivers an entertainment show just about daily.
Wow, okay.
That is story.
I just have to organize my thoughts because it's so much.
Story, Adam Curry, as Adam Curry.
I'm sure you enjoy it.
But Trisha Pie, as the pop star.
This guy has the greatest.
He's got a good good ass.
Tied.
Beautiful.
When do I get to meet asshole?
I even missed her ass.
She's ever, I mean, he's not gay.
And Christina Curry, as McColle called good.
But Christina was actually a all alone.
Is a drama filled with heart-pounding action.
As she calls me from the airport, she says,
okay, I forgot I'm not medicine.
But you have to know, as, uh, as someone who has some minor cardiac issues,
heart medicine is pretty important to take with you.
A story that has everything.
Obsessions love, uh, disappointment, sorrow.
It really, the emotions run the gamut.
And you can only find it in one place.
Delta, Sierra, Charlie, five, one, six.
Sometimes an atoms on a loan and he needs his love right there on the microphone.
So here she is, yes, the lady Patricia.
The say to have some better than one.
And with this angel from above,
there's nothing that they both can't do.
I make you while this dream has come true.
So grab your ear buds and jam them in.
And let the fabulous show begin.
It's Adam and Patricia.
Yes, Adam and Patricia.
Adam and the lady Patricia.
We're usually generated content as become times person of the year.
One man has taken the reins to lead the revolution.
Guiding podcasting to new horizons has only an experienced pilot care.
The, uh, what are we moving from the east side of Gilford?
No, the west side of Gilford to the east.
Uh, let me just check again.
Now, from the east side of Gilford to the west side of Gilford.
Oh, hell, somebody load a BF-5, 16.
Researchers in New Zealand have proven that there is a link between cannabis and mental illness.
Oh, yes.
Has anybody seen the map queue the music?
I a-va-a-la-a-a-la!"
Though you see what I see, do you see a lot?
I do you see?
Do you understand?
She said that life was through the little land.
Do you see?
We're up to the sky and in a lap
Do you see what I see?
All the stars start dancing the night with a tear
As we go through a kite with a tear
This break is a kite
I send a little lamb to the shop for more
Do you know what I hear?
Ring through the sky and shop for more
All the stars start dancing the night with a tear
As we go through a kite with a tear
This break is a kite with a tear
Let's bring you something to go
It's not like you know where I am
You know where I am
You know where I see where I am
I saw you here
Set the key to the people that flew away
Hales and you are high say
Day for peace and people that flew away
Oh, listen to what I say
Hales and you are high in the sky
He's sleeping in the night
You know where I am
Hales and you are high in the sky
You know where I see where I am
That's what I am talking about
Gilpar do you hear?
Gilpar do you hear what I hear?
I could have been me
That's exactly what I was going to say
It sounds so much like one of your songs from the 80s
Just kind of your range and your singing
Yeah, yeah fantastic
In fact there is a song you did that sounds like it
Wasn't it from that stupid Disney album you did
It was a song on there that sounded just like it
What the hell was it?
It is a certain middle part that sounds very much like it
What?
Oh boy
Oh boy she is doing it in the lowlands
Sorry
Oh it's probably one of the albums here
One of your massive library of albums
Ladies and gentlemen, the one and only Patricia Pye is back
I've got Napster so I love searching for songs
It's our favorite song
I love this song
We should play it
Hey baby, how you doing?
I've been to the moon and back
That's how it felt
Let me just see where we left off the conversation
Last time we were talking was that when I picked you up
Yeah, and we came back after the rehearsals
And I told you to story about falling off the...
Yes, you had to sing
So hitting the other stool and hitting my kick
Kidney's right
So it was wonderful
Right
So you got better
I got better
It always was a little bit sensitive
I could feel it
So I asked the guy not to squeeze my kidneys
Don't touch the kidneys
I wouldn't know where to find your kidneys if I was looking for it
But he does
Every time he was I could feel it
So we did that different
We had a different routine there
I think we did very well
Okay, so wait a minute
So I got to reset the stage
Your Patricia is doing dancing with the stars
Actually I just did dancing with the stars
Because we're done
It's two special year and episodes
To be aired in the low countries
And one is on second day of Christmas
And the other one is New Year's Eve
And so you had to do two dances
One was a wall
And one was a somba
And you did this with a professional dancer Remko
Who is not gay?
No, he has a very tight ass
That's so best, he is a professional dancer
He is not gay
They always think the dances are gay
I have no idea
Very devoted I have to say
Very, very
You got to be man
If you want to be professional in that field
And he is a national champion
And also a world champion
Exhibition dance
Is that like the forbidden dance
Exhibition dance is beautiful
Exhibition dance is like all you can free style it
And no dangers and looks beautiful
So now all the gossip television magazines tabloids
They're calling the calling your family
They're calling me on my private line
I know
And so of course all we can really tell them
Is well, once you just go listen to the podcast
If you really want to know what's going on
So we have the exclusive here of all the dirt
We're not allowed to talk about the actual results
But I have to say I was very proud of myself
And I know now that I'm a Samba girl
Samba girl
Yes
This me, Samba's me
You really like this dancing thing, don't you?
It is so much fun
I didn't know
I didn't know when I started this but
It is I have to say it's a lot of fun
And for the women ladies
You're losing weight like
Now let me just tell you
You came home
Yesterday, God you look so hot
Thank you
Yeah, your ass was tight
Not that it isn't tight otherwise
But you lost pounds
I lost six pounds in one week
Yeah, I believe it
So with the other week, I think all together
Maybe seven, seven and a half
And you lost it all in the right places
Because everything that's supposed to be nice and plump
It's still nice and plump
Oh, baby
And we were happy to see each other
Yes, we were
Mr. Happy was happy to
Yes, baby
So it was a good week, it was a good experience
And you know, all the attention
And all the paparazzi was there
And of course, it's in a good way
Because we had different situations
Paparazzi and gossip
They all hate me
No, they don't
They hate me
No, no, no
They think it's fun to make fun of me
No, no, no, I mean look at David Beckham
Do they hate him?
No, they were talking about him too
After a
Well, you know, after he lost the world cup
Yeah, they hate him
It's a little bit of news of that moment
And then they forget all about it
You're so interesting
I can I can tell you
Because everybody's asking about you
Oh, tell me more
Every talking about me about you
And especially I noticed that they're still talking about the Adam's family
And that thing
What flipped out your bathroom?
Oh, you mean
Oh, no, bath a robe
Yeah, this was on a reality show that we did
And they're the men
So they're jealous of my penis
They're very jealous of your penis
Yeah, it's a stuff like that
So how are you doing?
I'm doing fine
And how's the Adam doing?
Hamdo, are you guys happy?
Yeah, I know why you're happy
That's what they say
Yeah, and that's the typical man
That's the only thing they can think of
You sure they don't mean my wallet?
It's not the plane they're talking about
Oh, really?
Yeah, that's okay
Well, that's pretty cool, I guess
So, but yeah, it was fun
What I wanted to say
It was a lot of fun to have all those
People asking about you, of course
And all the attention was nice
Actually, I did this time I enjoyed it
I enjoyed it
Oh, no, they gave me a kick
Now, did I understand that they've asked you to be on the series
The regular series of like eight different dances
To really compete in the real competition
Yeah, and actually the way I feel now
I would love to do it
But that's not now
So it's going to be in a couple of months
And who knows what I'm doing then?
So I don't know
Well, I think if they can
It's quite a compliment
If they can work it out logistically, I think you should do it
I think I can, I can do it
If I don't, don't worry about you
I'm not going to see
You have nothing to worry about
I mean, I'm in the condo in San Francisco
Me, my hookers, and my computers
You know, I'm all set
My hookers
Yeah, you know, it's absolutely right
I really missed you when I was in San Francisco this time
It was really hard because
You had great parties
We had some fantastic parties
I knew you would love to be
Then we had the Clienter Perkins party
Which you would have hated
The hell is that?
Oh, parcel force
Yeah
It was like, you know, it was
Mainly men
And it was all bankers and stuff
And people who wanted to, you know, get richer than they already are
So it was a good network
It was good for Ron and I
Yeah, it was a networking party
You could have been my trophy wife
That would have been cool
Okay
Because, you know, there was just like
I'm very good at that
There were no good looking chicks
Oh
Except for Marta was there
No Marta
And Ray Lane's wife is very beautiful
Yes
And
Let's see, then we had our Christmas party
The Pod Show party
Yeah
It was a lot of fun
We had Santa
We, you know
We had an after party at a club
Yeah
Oh, I know closet to sex
Well, I certainly wasn't invited
If there wasn't
We weren't in a closet
I jumped out of the closet
Years ago
What are you talking about
Please
So, and after which went to the club
Tell me about
There was a club right
So we had the W Hotel
Which is a great hotel
I mean, you know, it's kind of typical
Modern hotel
And it was great food
Which I think is
It's not very typical anymore
The people serve food during a holiday party
In the United States
It's more like you have a drink
And then
Yeah
Yeah, yeah
So, most of the time
Finger food
Well, we had a buffet
Oh, yeah
We had a full buffet
And that was good
And then the club
Downs I forget what the name of the club was
And, you know, so we went in
And we got a court like a VIP corner
And, you know, and got champagne
Yeah, we were in the club
And we had some real people who could really dance
Yeah, so we didn't look like a bunch of fucking gigs
We had Kevin Appes
From the high-fee show
From the Tony Costas
Are you out of your fucking mind?
You didn't dare
No way
You're so good in your John Toffors
I think
Oh, yeah, here it comes
Yes, yes
No man, it was outside smoking
Spliff for you talking about
I don't know
And, after that, you didn't even
No, there was no dance
No, I don't know
I don't know
There was no dance
No, I was home at
By 1245
I mean, this is the big party night out
Wow
I don't know
You know
And that's all what happened
No, and then we had, well of course
We had a lot of work
We were doing a lot of stuff during the day
And then there was Ray Lane's
60th birthday party
I think he would have liked that
Mmm
Yeah, was at the table
With Tim Shriver
From the Kennedy clan
His mom started
Check this out
I didn't know this about the guy
His mom
Yunus
I think
Yeah, Yunus Kennedy
Shriver
I don't know
I'm started
So Maria is his sister
I think Maria Shriver
Okay
Because Schwarzenegger
Was supposed to come, couldn't come
Oh, that's a pity
I think the Cardinal of California was there
I mean, really, some interesting people
Right
And so Tim Shriver's mom started the special Olympics
And he's been
I guess the co-chair of the special Olympics for 20 years or whatever
And that's basically what he's been doing with his life
Wow
Yeah, and you learn a lot about people
And Ray Lane has been doing all kinds of stuff
For the special Olympics for years and years
So it was kind of interesting
Very interesting
Yeah, and they had good food and
Nice content
And the platters
Yes
Yeah, you told me that
It was like
Oh yes
I'm the great
Pre-tender
Almost second
Wait, wait, let me see
I didn't pull you down this time
Yeah, yeah, usually
It's always six is fingering
See
Yeah, well, like Abba, right?
Okay, let's see if we can
Yeah, I'm the great
Pre-tender
I'm doing well
Doing well
I need you
It's such
I pretend too much
I'm lonely
I know the lyrics
Okay, anyone
One can say
But they have a lot of other
Yeah
Other massive hits
But it was kind of fun
But I can't
I don't know
Well, what?
Do you know this one?
Oh, okay
Challenge
Hold on
I don't know
You're running
I were bugging out
Because we actually knew most of
So, do you remember this one?
This is a classic
Do you remember this one?
This one?
Yeah
It's 12 at a time
See?
Oh, it doesn't
There's another one
It doesn't
Here's another one
The plotters did a lot of
This isn't
It's sad that we can't really share
These with our public
Because it's illegal
Whether it should be a part of your musical education
Oh, what we're doing in that
My two loved ones too
Here it comes
Okay, so I'm just reminding you
Some of the plotters songs
Do you remember this one?
It's come back
Oh, no, but there's more
There's more
These guys are
Yeah, I mean the plotters
You want to know plotters
How about this golden oldie
On this fantastic
20th century masters
The millennium series best of the plotters
The magic touch
Yeah, those were good times
Aren't they Patricia?
Do you remember the days of the plotters?
Yes, or is it?
I don't know
Two young for the plotters
But still we've got more on this fantastic compilation
You never, never know I can
Oh, no
And then of course there's the one that everyone loves
So sing along to on their karaoke machine
It's this classic
Oh, no
Anyway, so
Indeed, yes
So there was basically one guy from the original plotters
Who had a wig on that I think was made
One plot
It was a plot and I think that he had a wig on
Which was the hair of the four other guys
Who?
It was like a cap man
And he was in an 80
But he was like, hey, remember us the plotters
And then he had like young guys
Who could really sing their ass
Oh, well, that's nice
Of course
And he had an ugly, ugly, ugly ass white band
I'd like balling guys with stringy hair and shit
But it was good
And they played the temptation songs
It had a whole bunch of things
They really had that
So it was a party
It was a party
Our friend test
Yeah, it was definitely cool
And your ray, of course, was severely disappointed
That you wanted there
And he really wants to make Christina too
I'm disappointed too now
Dude, I mean listen, we got hang out with this guy
He's got a fucking G5 jet
Great
He's got rays on man
Come on, we got a wave
He was flying over the dense floor
Yeah, no
Yeah, well you were apologize
Now you were excused on me
I had a lot of fun
And I'm very happy to hear that you have fun too
Who'd have me
I had the most fun yesterday
Before you came home
When you're parents
First of all, your dad is a trip map
So I'm sitting here
He comes up here and walk in the studio office
And he'll look at the console
I did a big thing that he built for me
Which I love
And he knows that
And this thing has to fit up
The staircase to the third floor
It's a dozen dry now
Well, he had measured it
And he said, if he saws this piece off right here
Yeah
Then the total length is 60 centimeters
Which of course gives it more than enough room
To get it up the stairs
Yeah
So he's been up here
Like every half hour saying, can I start sewing?
Yeah
Dude
It's like, oh my shit
What are you doing?
He said, well, you could just take all your stuff
And put it over there
And like, dude, look at this spaghetti of wires
I said, don't come here
It starts sewing
Sorry
How about Friday?
Because I have to go to, well, we have a holiday party in a shortage
The London office has a party on Friday
Am I inviting?
Of course you were invited
If you want to come, yeah, I'd love you to come
All right
You don't really want to come
What do you want to go without me?
Well, yeah, it's an office party
Oh
That means
Nothing
Oh, yeah
You're more
It's like a...
Well, wait a minute
For the folks on serious satellite stars 102
If you want to come to the office party
Then you'll have to download the podcast
The dailysourcecode.com to hear
To hear the rest of the story
Okay
Now we're doing lunch first at 1 o'clock
Just for the for the peeps
Then at 4 o'clock
Some of the people who are working full time at the office
And a couple of the folks
Then
All of the people who signed up with the network have been invited
In the UK
They're all coming in
So that'll be at 4 o'clock
So it'll be kind of a full day
You may not want to be a part of that
Anyway, so your dad kept coming up
And I said, how about Friday?
He said, no, that'll be too late
So you're leaving Saturday
No, no, no, I have to saw now
So I've barely been able to keep him away
From sawing the desk in the two pieces
But the funniest thing
Was yesterday
Your dad had emptied out the entire refrigerator
He was resetting the shelves
And your mom freaked out
Yeah
I mean, I should have, I should have video taped
It was so, so fun
Our so funny, I know
It was absolutely hysterical
Once this starts with each other
And once my mom gets mad
No, then it's all over
That is quite
I know
I'm not like that
If I had gone ahead and cleaned out the refrigerator
And changed the shelving without your approval
I think
Well, I do what you would say
What's he doing?
No, you would have said, what the fuck did you just
Yeah
All right, let me play a little song here
This is
There we go
I got somewhere else to be
I'll be leaving here
It's 6 a.m. to see my family
All my sweaters they've been packed
Bit of cold
Won't make me crack
Once I get there, I don't know
I don't care how I'm coming back
Cause I would walk a thousand miles
I would walk a thousand miles
Through the snow rain
Or bitter cold to be back home
For Christmas
I've been gone too long to say
But I'm coming anyway
Anyway, I can't leave this town
And get back home today
But I'm coming anyway
Anyway, I can't leave this town
And get back home today
Let the snow fall through the air
I got eight long hours to spare
I'll be waiting at the airport
Bar for three but I don't care
Cause I would walk a thousand miles
I would walk a thousand miles
Through the snow rain
Or bitter cold
To be back home for Christmas
But this long flight
Don't bother me
Three man and shepherd's came to see
The baby born this morning
Lows away from their locality
And angels sing in clear patty
Lucia
The Christ is coming here
And they'll play with no strangers
The way that's still
The time and to find me
You know we found me
So I would walk a thousand miles
I would walk a thousand miles
Through the snow rain
Or check out lands
A traffic chance
And I would walk
A thousand miles
I would walk a thousand miles
Through the snow rain
Or bitter storms
To be back home for Christmas
I would walk a thousand miles
Through the snow
The rain
Or bitter cold
To be back home
For Christmas
Matthew Weeble
Live
That's from 2004
Isn't it though?
I can just imagine that in
Can you imagine having a husband
To do that?
Can you do that?
I wrote you
You take your dress off
And rub you
And I would lay on the piano
Of course
And I would listen
Oh, wouldn't that be great
Yeah, I wish I could do
I'll lay on top of your laptop
If we had our fucking piano here
Then I could do it and I could pretend to play
We have a piano
Yeah, but piano will do it
I mean it has the automatic stuff
Can we just get it here?
We're going to put it here
No, we'll see
We need a different house
Oh, my piano
I want my piano
Yeah, we should do that more often
The
Sing along
The best of his
Yeah, I'd be kind of funny
No, I mean we could make it into
It's kind of like Saturday night live
Yeah, so we actually know all the songs
And we could do
What other songs do we know like
Good old stuff that we actually know
I don't know, I'm going to check that CD
What are you doing?
What are you careful?
It's a big jump there, baby
But just getting off of the bar stool
You need a whole, oh, you have your CD
I don't have your CD
Let me see if I got it, he would you make it
I got it downstairs
While you're doing that, I want to tell you about a new sponsor
On the Daily Source Code
It is for the movie
Sony Pictures movie
The Sony Pictures
The Motion Picture
Stomp the Yard
And this is from the same company
I guess it also from Sony Pictures
who sponsored the show with Little Man
Remember we looked at the trailer for Little Man
Yeah, and it turned out to be a huge hit
It was like number one movie
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
So now we're so successful
We're not from potions
What else does that do?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
We're really
And Tony Costas of Costas World
Is doing an episodic podcast
About the movie
Which you'll want you to check out
It's called Stomp the podcast
find it at stompthepodcast.com, and let me see, I think, I think you still has the first
episode up, and yeah, that's the one where he has the candid conversation on black
college life, black Greek organizations, and the impact it has on culture, and of course
it's all about the upcoming release, Stomp the yard, and Splenda, are you done yet
because I can do commercials all day? Splenda, who challenge you to figure out what your
flavour is by combining wonderful Splenda flavours, you know what Splenda, you know what Splenda?
No, you don't want Splenda, is it?
No, what do you say? Thanks for listening to the show.
No, I don't.
I know, clearly, Splenda is, it's the sugar substitute, oh, of course I know that.
You do know Splenda, yeah, it's so sweet, it's very sweet, you don't need that much.
You don't need much, no.
No, no, no, no, I know where they are.
Well, they have no, in Hazelnut, French Vanilla, and one other flavour, which I can't remember.
You haven't tried that?
No.
You should try that, because what people are doing is they're mixing the flavours together.
Oh, nice.
Yeah, but I agree, you don't need a whole packet, a whole packet is way too much.
Yeah.
Okay, I know where it is, it's in kitchen downstairs, the CD.
Oh, okay.
Want me to get it?
Right now?
No.
Uh, uh, uh.
Give me heaven cover me.
That's it.
From a brand.
Ah, yeah.
Ah, see, it's it's from Berlin.
Yes, oh.
Yeah, it was Berlin.
Okay, it was from my album with all the movie songs.
Oh, that's the one.
Was it give me heaven?
Give me heaven, I thought.
Seven.
Yeah.
Can we just chat about my life?
No.
Was it on a night?
No, cover me.
I think it was called cover me.
Oh, I see.
But I mean, the album, time of my life,
that's why it was on.
Right, exactly.
I don't.
I've only had the single here.
I've never been to me.
Don't.
I don't think you're in Napster.
It sucks.
Let me see.
If you're in Napster, baby.
What shows up on a do your name?
I do have a house over here.
You know, which what do you have from the other.
You want to play that again?
Give me that.
That's so fucking funny.
No, this has never been to me.
Oh, it's on top of it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
A second one.
All right.
You got to set it up while I loaded up.
You got to tell me you got to tell me.
I already did.
I haven't known.
Another one's heard the show, man.
Look, the half is hot, baby.
You got to tell me how to judge it.
Especially in the heart.
In the UK.
Yeah.
It was your all the time.
What was he doing here?
Yeah.
But anyway.
So people were asking me, do you know the half?
I said, yeah.
I know the half.
I sang with him.
I fucked him.
Nice.
I sang with him.
And my producer went to LA to record his voice.
And because I couldn't go that.
And that's the first one.
Then the second song is with half.
But anyway, my producer came back and he said, well, that was hard.
Together.
Yeah.
Because he thinks he's a better singer than he is.
Oh, boy.
So he was like.
All right.
Listen.
And constantly.
Hey.
Yes.
And they just, you know, had to clean up a little tape.
No.
But we got it.
It's the half man.
Finally we got it.
We got to re-release this.
Yeah.
And I was his guy.
It's on the, on the track.
No kidding.
So he had to sing what I already sang.
It's the truth.
Oh, yeah.
I love to you.
Because that's mommy.
And that's mommy.
Yeah.
I love to you.
Doesn't he do a, hey.
Just remember.
Yeah.
Everybody.
The half rock.
Yeah.
It was a.
Confused him for so long.
Now.
Oh, yeah.
I found someone to stand in our way.
It's kind of a disco.
He track.
Yeah.
And he was so off.
You have no idea.
I want to hear you guys rip it up.
Now with passion in our eyes.
I did.
It was pretty good.
I did all the back up, too.
All the more.
Yeah.
The core.
Tell me.
Yeah.
Okay.
He is the just remember part.
Yeah.
That's pretty good.
Can I skip the head for a second?
Yeah.
Let me know.
He has.
I'm here with time of my life.
I never feel this way before.
Somewhere you must really kill on this track.
I don't know.
I did six voices.
So that's all you.
Yeah.
No.
I did it all.
Yeah.
Good time.
Oh.
That's funny.
Yeah.
It's nice to have that.
Yes.
Well, baby, it is good to have you back home.
I look forward very much to a wonderful Christmas.
And moving.
Oh, I don't even want to think.
What is the actual day that we're packing up, do you?
The first week.
We're going to pack.
Yeah.
And the second week.
We're going to bring everything to the other house.
Oh, boy.
They're going to move everything.
You know, I've started on changing all the addresses.
Oh, I've started on the way.
Yeah.
I have changed that in the past week or two.
All right.
You know, it's going to be fucked up because you know the internet's never going to work
on time.
No.
You don't didn't even check it.
You have.
Uh, internet there.
No.
Well, the capability.
Yeah.
But you have to have it all connected.
And it just takes fucking time.
We're going to live in a mess in the first week.
So you know that.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
But you know.
And the cats can't go outside for six weeks.
Oh, no.
I have to stay in some sense.
I know.
Excuse me.
No.
I don't want to think about it right now.
Oh, I cannot stand.
Yeah.
You're still coming down from the sense coming down.
Dancing with the stars.
Yes.
Okay.
Dancing with a star.
When do we get video?
I want to share it with the world.
That's a fashion.
Honey.
What?
Video.
Yeah.
I said.
Video.
Just give me a DVD.
Well, they.
People want to see that shit.
I know.
Um, I don't know.
They're going to do the editing show right now.
Yeah.
We should re-release that man.
That's good.
I tell you.
This could be a very big hit in the UK because I love the half.
And Germany.
And nobody has this track.
No.
Nobody has it with the half.
Hello record companies out there.
Yeah.
You're already dancing right now as a big hit.
You're right because of the of the musical.
Yes.
Why don't you call them from Kota?
Why don't you call them say, dude, you mother fucker.
Release this shit in the UK.
And release it.
I don't know if you can release it.
So you tell them that I don't like that to do that.
Yeah.
Because.
Well, you know, it's not going to make any difference.
I mean, you could get on top of the path.
Yeah.
Because you are still.
And curry.
The ex.
Very big big DJ.
Who made Michael Jackson big.
Oh, yeah.
I would love to release it.
I don't think you can do it because.
Who wrote it?
You can ask him.
Give me the CD again.
No, because it's not his.
It's not his to give away.
That's true.
It would be who wrote it.
Prevent.
Denecola and Marko Markowitz.
Oh, we have to call him.
We have to call him.
Hey, Denecola.
I didn't call him.
We're great to do.
Yeah.
So we can't release that.
When you do these fucking covers man do something original.
You got to do some original.
That we can release it.
I had another request from iridfontaine.
Of course.
Yes.
That's my fontaine.
What was his request?
Well, he said actually he wants to make.
He's a producer.
He's a very good producer.
You did the Robbie Neville stuff with him.
Yeah.
Danger.
Danger stuff.
And well, they had a couple of.
World hits.
Very good.
With stuff they wrote or something.
Yeah, you're up in my tie, and he's here.
Hey, stop, read.
Yeah, all those, well, I'm more.
Is that still one?
I mean, they ride great songs, too.
Yeah, keep talking.
And well, they, Eric said he wanted to make an album
with me with a big band.
That's good.
Because we were talking about what I would like to.
So it's just one thing I would love to try.
Sex with another woman with my husband.
Exactly.
And that's end a beautiful, big band to album, which
great, very chic music, you know,
glass wine, piece of cheese.
Oh, wine and cheese.
Why is it cheese?
Perfect wine and cheese.
Yeah.
You know, and a candle.
And your ass.
Oh, Adam.
Yeah, I'm looking for my tie.
That's so new to you.
My tie is not naughty, naughty.
My tie is not on that.
It wasn't that big of a world.
But dangerous.
Well, dangerous not going to be on Napster.
I'll tell you, they've only got him like a million songs.
I mean, how many songs in the world have come out?
Hmm.
Anyone I'm saying?
Yeah.
Let me see.
Danger.
Eric is a whole bunch of dangers.
Honestly.
No.
It's not going to be in there, baby.
So do you want to do that with him?
Well, you know, well, let's talk about it.
I don't know what he is.
But again, something that can't be really.
Can we do original songs?
Does that mean you can?
Let's do original songs that you can really,
part say, if you don't want money, you know,
there are so many beautiful, beautiful ballots
and beautiful old songs that still, you know,
are gorgeous to sing.
Yeah, but I'm just being selfish.
I want to release something odd, say.
So, okay, let's put it this way.
You can do an album.
Favorite is still misty.
And there are so many beautiful misty.
So why don't we do this?
Why don't you, once you say yes, I'll record the album.
And of course, yes, I talked to me, your manager.
As your manager, I'm telling you what you can do.
So I think you should, yes, you should absolutely
should record an album.
And but at least one, preferably a couple of the tracks
have to be written.
Written.
If they write them, that's fine.
But I want to be able to release them pod safe, which
means, you know, they're probably not going to make any money.
Well, they're beautiful new jazz songs and beautiful, you
know, ballots, which you can sing the way we did that in the
early days when we had the big bands in the beautiful.
This is it.
Real violence.
No, see, it is wrong.
Oh, it's over.
Yeah, it's a joke.
Now, this is football room dancers.
Get on the floor.
That's your dad's band.
Enjoy.
Yes.
The John Pioor.
They're all 17, 18 years old.
Look at me.
I miss helpless as a kid.
I'm a tree.
And I feel like I'm clinging to a cloud.
I can't understand.
I get dizzy.
Yeah.
Just holding your head.
It's nice, baby.
You're so good.
Walk.
Way.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Right.
So, there are so many beautiful songs.
So, first we have to do the half release after the half release.
The half.
Baby.
The half is hot.
He was in a couple of programs, a couple of shows here on the TV.
And I thought he was very funny.
Because he finally figured out.
He figured out that, yeah, you're better be, you know, funny about yourself.
And you know that thing.
Don't take yourself so seriously.
And he doesn't.
You know the thing I showed you last night, which we can't exactly say what it is that video I showed you.
Yeah.
The project we're working on.
We actually almost got the half to do it.
Really.
Oh, he could have done a good job too.
Yeah.
The problem is he has some commercial interests for a competing product.
Yes.
He does.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
So, unfortunately.
Signed a contract.
Yeah.
Oh, you knew that.
Well, that's good.
So, unfortunately.
The internet thing you mean.
Yeah.
He's doing this sort of internet commercial.
I don't know if it's, no, no, no, no, no.
That's something else.
No, no, no.
He has another commercial.
Oh, yeah.
Which is for a competing brand.
Okay.
Doesn't matter.
Anyway, we almost had him.
I was pretty sure.
This guy is good too, right?
Yeah.
It's probably my favorite, my favorite.
Let's not say anything.
Yeah.
All right, baby.
It's been 45 minutes.
Gotta stop.
Okay.
People have no patience for us after 45 minutes.
No.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, you want to say happy Christmas to anyone.
Because I'm sure you won't come on the show before Christmas.
Very, very merry Christmas.
Well, you don't know.
Maybe I'll just hop in.
Merry Christmas.
Beautiful days.
Be very, very nice to each other.
Good times.
Like a candle for the people that you miss.
And don't forget to buy the fabulous 20th month, 20th century
Platters.
Yes.
Collection album.
But are we going to back?
Are we going to be back for New Year?
Yeah.
For the New Year's, yeah.
Then the two weeks that we're moving, I'm planning on doing the best of
Charlie, which means people get to put together their own favorite shows
of compilation of shows.
Well, we're going to be all by ourselves, the three of us.
Yes, we are.
But we like it that way.
Yeah.
We like it.
Very quiet.
Nice meal.
Hmm.
Some snacks.
Just enjoy.
Oh, at him.
Well, you can think of if you see my body.
Oh, I'm trying hard not to do baby, but.
I know.
Oh, people get nauseous by me.
Yeah.
All right, babe.
Stop.
Thanks for coming on the show.
Go out.
Go play with your parents.
Okay.
I love you.
I love you too.
Bye, everybody.
Oh, wait.
Shit.
I don't know if I don't do that.
That's right.
Bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT pod show media network.
Control your part in the show at BT podshow.com.