Think Advertising sucks.
Think you can do better?
Pod Show and EarthLink are willing to put our money where your mouth is.
Listen to this podcast or go to adchelens.podshow.com to see how you can win big
in the EarthLink make advertising better challenge.
Delta Sierra Charlie 3 9 or 8.
Thank you for calling Enron.
Please listen closely to the following options as our menu has changed.
If you wish to serve a subpoena on a current or former Enron executive, press 1.
If you are an Enron shareholder and would like to learn how to turn your Enron stock certificates
into decorative origami, press 2.
If you are Enron 401k plan is worthless and use likes and tips on how to survive your retirement,
eating nothing but mac and cheese, press 3.
If you are an Enron executive and would like to find out which prison inmate will be making you his bitch, press 4.
If you would like to invoke your constitutional right against self-incrimination, press 5.
If you are Dick Cheney, press 6.
And thanks for nothing, Dick.
If your company is looking to hire someone to record your voice mail menu options, please press 7.
Or stay on the line and an operator will assist you.
Thank you for calling Enron, the world's greatest company.
Thank you.
I wake up around 3.
I head pounded, I take a look around me.
I'm surrounded, my stuff will make it to the city.
And it sounded like I will never breathe.
And I'm drowning.
I don't wanna leave.
I hate working with cash, I must achieve.
It makes work, it's time for my family.
My soul's hurt in the same mind as the need.
That's what's up, you must not put it in this.
In the world, only God can fill me up.
I won't put his love on the temptation, just strong.
I need to pray if you want to change the path you're on.
Just say, you need to wake up.
I forgot what's important now.
Wake up.
Cause money ain't everyday.
All I do is break all day now.
Wake up.
I gotta do it for my family.
I forgot what's important now.
Wake up.
I'm losing my sanity.
Got the one that could save me.
Wake up.
I gotta give my life together now.
I look around, all I see are snakes.
And there's that still hate cheat.
I know it, everybody knows it.
I see that face and there's no good.
Cause it's like still hate cheat.
I know it, everybody knows it.
I just got lonely.
Make me a servant.
I ask for mercy.
I don't deserve it.
Cause I'm a slave too.
I'll be hurt if it catches my eye.
I need to change.
I'm always chasing.
I don't have money.
People will kill for.
There's never enough of.
I don't have money.
There's nothing but misery.
There's nothing but emptiness.
In the world, only God can fill me up.
Put his love.
But the temptation just strong.
I need to pray.
If you want to change the path, you're wrong.
I need to wake up.
I forgot what's important now.
Wake up.
Cause money ain't everyday.
All I do is bring my name out.
Wake up.
I got to do it for my family.
I forgot what's important now.
I'm losing my family.
Wake up.
Got the one that can save me.
I gotta give my life together now.
I just got a new whip.
I need another one I just got a new crit.
I need a bigger one.
I just got a new job.
I need a better one I just got Tangis.
Already spent.
Do you want what I got to do to eat?
It's all the game.
That's important.
Down the street.
It's all the same.
Same song.
And it's the same beat.
On the race.
On the TV.
It's nothing but emptiness.
In the world.
Only God can fill me up.
Put his love.
But the temptation just strong.
I need to pray.
If you want to change the path, you're wrong.
I love you.
Wake up.
I forgot what's important now.
Cause money ain't everyday.
Wake up.
I gotta do it for my family.
I forgot what's important now.
Wake up.
I'm blue.
I'll say it.
Wake up.
Cause the only one that's the same beat.
I can't make it like that.
Wake up.
Baby.
Since you weren't here before the show.
Yeah.
Let me just adjust yourself.
Let me see.
How's your headphones?
Yeah.
You're the one with the problem.
No.
I got no problems.
Hey everybody.
Baby source code for Friday.
How's your jet lag?
My jet lag is fine actually.
Yeah.
You actually.
You always have a jet lag.
Yeah.
I live in consistent consistent jet lag.
Yes.
So how are you doing?
I think you balance that out with the spliff.
Uh-huh.
Oh, absolutely.
Yeah.
I know.
It's called a self medication.
I was fine yesterday.
Actually.
Hey, I feel good.
You felt good.
But you really went hardcore.
Because we got back from San Francisco on.
What day was it?
Day before yesterday.
It was.
It wasn't a two day.
No Wednesday.
We left on Tuesday on.
Yeah.
We were Wednesday.
And I was conking out.
I was laying in the chair with a laptop burning my nuts off and fell asleep for an hour.
No.
You slept deeply in the in the plane.
Only for an hour in the plane.
I didn't sleep a lot in the plane.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, this plane could be going down.
Could be descending at 5,000 feet per minute.
It wouldn't even notice.
Uh-huh.
No problem.
Oh.
Yeah.
So then it came home.
And so I never slept.
And why didn't she?
Why didn't she just go to sleep?
I just wanted to stay awake.
I don't want to miss anything.
Oh, okay.
Can I?
Right.
And miss out to anything.
So then I came home.
My parents were here.
Started to talk right of it.
We have no idea how you feel.
They can't remember it.
Isn't that what parents are for though?
I don't know.
When you're 80, you don't remember any more.
How that fell.
Only only 15 more years, huh?
What?
Then you'll be 80.
Oh, don't.
How does that feel, huh?
Yeah.
You imagine that?
Well, you know what?
I wish.
And I hope.
Wishing.
And hoping.
And wishing.
That I'll be 80 and healthy.
Absolutely.
As well as as healthy as they are.
Exactly.
And then your daughter was already complaining about us.
Yeah.
We'll be bitching even more.
Oh, I'll be out before you know it.
That's what she said yesterday.
Yeah, that's right.
She says, I'm leaving the house when I'm 17.
Uh-huh.
Why?
You can't ever clean up your room.
You can.
Exactly.
Yeah.
And I'm a little more practical.
Okay.
So what are you going to do for like friends?
Have you ever seen kitchen?
You're just making a cracker?
Yeah.
It's like World War II.
Battlefield.
After she made one cracker.
Yeah.
So anyway, I'm pretty much on schedule.
Because I slept those hours and then I stayed up until like two.
Well, everything went well until we went out yesterday.
Well, you already want to get to that now.
Hold on a second.
We can't go that fast.
We want people.
You got to build it up a little bit.
Yeah.
But now I feel really shitty.
It's so funny because I said the Patricia said, look, we have to do the show now because
we're going to miss the sound like window p-dubs waiting.
Everybody's waiting for the show so it can be put into the show.
And I said.
So you're sadly said, no problem.
Just let me put on some makeup.
Uh-huh.
It's audio.
It's a sound.
Don't scare you in the face.
Looking like shit.
Oh, you're on fire.
You never look like shit.
I don't know about not having the, the temporary teeth in.
But don't pinch and ignite.
I know.
Well, on Trucker Tom is something to say to us.
Yo, Adam and Patricia.
Trucker Tom here.
I think I've come up with a new name for the Carlos.
You should call it Lady Patricia.
And the guy.
I love the interactivity that goes on between you and Patricia.
There's something about listening to two people that really are buddies.
Forget the fact that you've been married 20 years.
You really are buddies and you just seem to go together so well.
And there's something that's really charming about that.
Something that's fun to listen to.
So Lady Patricia and the guy.
I think it's appropriate.
You see what's happening.
You can find my podcast at Trucker Tom.
And then Trucker Dude.
Hot chill.
Trucker Dude.com.
Yeah.
I thought that was in your shit.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
You don't seem to understand what's happening here.
Is you are completely taking over my limelight.
It's gone.
It's fading.
I'm pot fading away.
As much information as you always have.
But it's so imagine.
It's a double edged sword.
You know, it's like I have all the shit that I really want to do.
You know, people send feedback.
Which stuff we don't have time for when we're on the show together.
And, you know, promos and all that stuff.
And then whenever I do those shows, you know, people love the fact that I'm playing promos and feedback.
You know, Adam, you're kind of boring without Patricia.
You know, it's like, I can't, um, um,
F-do-fi-do, F-do-fi don't.
Oh my god.
What's okay?
Well, thank you.
It was so sweet.
Oh, man.
I, I so want you to meet Trucker Tom.
You guys be so funny together.
He sounds very nice and sexy.
He's very sexy.
Oh, he is.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
If you like guys with Skolls tattooed on to the back of their head.
Sometimes.
No, no, no.
Woo.
And officially, I know I showed this to you last night.
last night but I'm just gonna hold it up again. You are now officially a nerd. Yeah. This is, uh,
I'll put a link to it. It showed up on Valleywag, but Tom Morris made this, uh, this great, uh,
photo montage. What are the nerds doing? And it's like, uh, Mike Arlington and, uh, Cory Doctro,
Steve Rubel, Steve Jobs, Jason Calcana, Steve Kilmore. I mean, good company. Yeah. Uh,
a whole bunch of old guys and me. Yeah. Yeah. And the Cory's are in sunny California. This
beautiful picture of us at, that was at the gig, I guess at the, uh, at the three bands in the city,
the rock show. Yeah. Yeah. So, but it says, what are the nerds doing? You are officially a nerd. Oh,
good. Well, I think it's a big compliment to be called a nerd. Yeah, yeah, because I always, you know,
I was talking to Marta, Marta Ron. Ron's wife. Ron's wife. And, um, she said, um,
we were talking about our husbands. Oh, boy. Oh, I wish I had a little microphone on you then. Yeah.
And she thinks that Ron is a really sexy man. And I know that the women always fancy, uh,
Ron Bloom. Yeah. That's true. He has something. He has that, uh, comes into the,
male, macho, shining, she's around. He has that. And we were talking about our husbands.
And I said, well, you know, Adam, remember, what was that? What did we bubble bubble bubble bubble?
And you bubble bubble bubble bubble, this is a rondo. That and slow down. Let's hear what does Adam
do? And what does wrong do? And what is wrong do? We're talking about when they get angry,
when they're tired, how you have to be understanding because they're so busy. It's so hard to
live with us, isn't it? We're living their lives. Oh, man, give me a break. Yeah. You know. Well, that's,
that's your, your, um, excuse me. Um, this investment. You also, if you, if you're your,
your man, your husband is, uh, doing something really good and, and, um, uh, it's successful.
And I don't know what I think you, excuse me. It's, it's, it's all to, to back him up and be there for
him is your investment. And by the way, that works the other way around as well. That's what I mean.
Twenty men who, uh, invested in their wives. That way around, yeah, investing, helping them in
what way they want you to help them. And I have to say with this, with this venture that we're doing,
you have been incredibly, uh, investful. Oh, it's something. Yeah. You've, you've, you've,
become natural. No, but, you know, it's the little things. It's like, okay, so we're
on. I'm going to go to San Francisco for two weeks. And then you're like, okay, that's a shame.
That's a pity. But you're not, you don't do like, oh, I miss you and come on. What you do kind of
at the end of each trip. Of course. You know, every time the moment you did, if you didn't know,
it would be like, yeah, I was talking about what we said about our husband. And then
Marta mentioned, she said to me, Adam is such a nerd. I don't see him. Uh, so there's nothing
sexy about him. Yeah, how about that? And yeah, yeah, I can't see him being a great lover.
Or because I said, Adam is wonderful. Oh, but don't him. Wow. Yeah, it's wonderful. And I can't see him
as a good lover. He, he's so nerdy. I said, yes. Exactly. Exactly. Now you hit it. Now you hit it because
nerdy guys. Yeah. Are the best lovers. The, the man that you don't think anything of or
I can't see even doing, you know, something. Yeah. Those are the guys. They're still, you know,
very sexy. They're good. They're good. They're nerd. Because we've had time to study.
It's Latin, sexism. It's, it's hidden, hidden, hidden sexuality. It's sexuality. It's sexuality. Absolutely.
Absolutely. It is one big surprise. After not. Emphasis on big. So they go nerdy. Big, big, big. This one was for you.
Big surprise. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're glad he's young. He's another message round.
That's his father. It's bigger than nerds. That's his father. He's back. I had done this. He's
Mr. The Family, Ed from Tom's End. I just happened to become a shit blogger's news agent.
And the film I mentioned, it comes to it bloggers, because it comes into my news agent.
And I'm actually into it. That makes it women's feeding goats. And you're supposed to have
to buzz as well, presumably to practice. So by now. Roger's doing something weird. He's,
so he called into the voicemail line instead of sending his usual thing. And he's like
got like this feud going on with comic strip blogger. Yeah. So I'm not quite sure. And he's got this
new phone. And I don't know. It's a whole thing that's going on. Well, what was he saying? That he,
he knows, uh, we're comic strip blogger, blah, blah, comic strip blogger. There's some chocolate in his
butt. Something like that. But I'm telling you, I just, I thought it was me.
Huh? Listen, airing this. You thought it was you that you were Roger? No, it was me hearing this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. That's exactly what he said. I don't know. I'm just trying to go with
the flow with those two guys. I don't know. They're into some kind of feud. Oh, okay. I have no idea
what you're doing. It's interesting for us. Yeah. You know, Roger's small is the ultimate nerd.
So it, you know, that's why I put that in there. When you're talking about. I've never seen a,
it must be one of a hell sexy guy there. Roger? He never knows. Well, you know, surprise.
Uh, I think that although you may not have seen him, he's probably seen us. You know, he does like
sneak in, sneak around the bushes, the trash and stuff. So. So as a surprise for
your parents, primarily for your dad, actually. Oh, I'm not going to listen. This was it. That was it,
yeah. Oh, are you expected more? Oh, yeah, I'm not. I don't know. No, no, this is it. This is it.
This is it. I'd like it when he sent it. I hate it when he used the voice mail, though. It's
very hard to understand. Yeah, very hard to understand. It's funny, though, because the more I
listen to Brits, I can almost hear Roger's smalls in every single one thing. I'm not kidding. Yeah.
I'm not kidding. You listen to like them. He could be Roger's smalls easily. Yeah. So,
well, even going to Saintsbury, it's still sometimes very hard to understand them.
Uh, Brits. I have to say hundreds, a hundred times a pardon or excuse me. Yeah.
Say it again. Excuse me. And I say it as long and I want to hear what they're saying. Who was it that I
called the other day? Um, that I actually had to ask like five times. Yeah. Oh, you know, it's
much, it's a much, it's mold. It was an, uh, it's an Indian woman, I think. Oh, maybe it was the
part of something different. Oh, that's very hard times. Oh, man, because yeah, because they're not
they used to hear it here. Yeah, of course you get used to it. We don't know that accent. Well, I do
know. Yeah. That's for sure. That's so sweet Indian people. I like them. All Indian people.
No, most of them that I met here are very nice and very polite. I think most of the most of them are
Pakistani, like the drivers who drive for GM cars. Yeah. They love you, man. Oh, they do.
Oh, they love you. I'm nice to them. I have a feeling, yeah, I have a feeling that, um, that they
are treated in the UK. Yeah. Pakistanis are all treated as, yeah, they do get a bad deal.
And because I see guys getting out opening the door for you, bowing, waving to you. Like, wow,
I'm a princess. You, yeah, you've got them. But I talked to them. I want to know where they're coming
from. Do they have a wife? I want to know. I want to know. You know, how they live and we've always been
like very, very, very interesting. But it's very interesting to hear, you know, actually the
life that they're living and what it's all about and where the parents are and the families are.
We know where their families are. In the big house in Pakistan. No, they're in woking.
Some of the families are in woking. That's it. Some of them woking. It's interesting because
all people are interesting. That's right. That's right. That's right. That's life. Yeah. So as a surprise
for Patricia's parents and primarily for your dad, um, I got tickets to the Sinatra Show at
London's palladium in London's West End, which was last night. And, uh, and, you know, I don't
even know how to categorize this show because it wasn't a musical because, you know, there's really no
no dialogue. It wasn't, uh, it wasn't a concert because, of course, you know, it wasn't there.
Sinatra, but he was there. Yeah. This was just a show, I guess, we'd have to call it. Sinatra
in the palladium. That's what the show called. So the way that this works is there's a, I think
I counted 27 piece orchestra. Yeah. Right. And they're on stage in, you know, in a like a bandstand.
Fantastic. Old guys, right? You know, older older musicians. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What is old?
Well, I mean, um, I think they're round about 40 to 60. Right. Oh, that's what that's
come to be. So the best jazz big wind. You mean jazz jazz jazz. Yeah. They, they know how to do it.
So then they had a, um, kind of like a ballet. I'd have to say, uh, another slime.
No, of course, lime means they would be singing. And they did sing some, but there was more dancing
and props on stage and setting the move. Now you have to know that my, my dad is a great musician.
He is, of course, he had big bands, especially in the time that Frank Sinatra was big. He also has
the God-given talent and it is God-given talent, uh, for arrangements. Yeah, arrangements without any
instrument. Yeah. You can just do it in his head. Yeah. You can just do it in his head. Yeah. Music in front of
him and he writes just like Mozart. Yeah. He'll write like arrangements when he hears in his head.
I mean, yeah. It's unbelievable. It is. So I'm very proud of my dad and he's one of the best jazz
saxophone musicians from Holland. And well, he's getting old and he's miss, he misses, you know,
play. He doesn't really play anymore. Well, yeah. He does now then with some, with some.
Now those guys are old. Those are, it's like, you know, sorry. Well, that's one of the, the,
um, the little, the little CDs that I made with my dad's big band were all, they were all, um,
uh, 80, 70, 80 and even over 80. I could actually play that if you want to. Yeah. And I did that
especially for my dad because he wanted me to sing with him again. And I thought, you know,
it's always good. So anyway. He's your daddy. Oh, cute. Yeah. You should be pleasing your daddy.
So the end of song was, of course, the daddy. Okay. Oh, yeah. I'll cue that up. We'll play that in a second.
Okay. So let me, let me finish explaining what was on stage. So there's probably 10 women, 10
guys who were, you know, dancing, singing some of the choruses, some interaction. I mean, the real
thing is every single song. And really, I don't know, this could only have come from the
Snatcher family because it was really Snatcher talking about his life. Yeah. I'd never heard this
interview before ever. You know what this was from? Yeah. It's from, uh, C, it was a CBS
static. C, yes. Yeah. I thought CBS, um, interviewed at the ever gave, but never used it. Nobody ever
used it. So they found it again. Yeah. And used it this time. So it was brand new. And why he tells
all stories. Yeah. No, it was fantastic. And then what they did is they had the screens that were
dropped down. All different sizes. One was completely horizontal, uh, you know, thin vertical ones.
Yeah. And, and hold on. Let me get there. Let me get there. Yeah. Let me talk about the video stuff.
Yeah. Oh yeah. Exactly. The video. Yeah. Technical stuff. Um, these were high density screens.
I mean, these were, um, I must have been DLP or whatever. I mean, you know, the screens. It wasn't
being projected. It was actual screens. It was beautiful. And so they did two things, obviously,
because they had all those before a whole bunch of performances, uh, class, some of the
some performances actually recognized what they had done is they had keyed out all the background.
Sometimes they put different backgrounds in. And, and the audio, they did a fantastic job with
basically getting rid of the original track and the band on stage would play, um, the, you know,
their own version. We're playing the track. Well, now here's where I wanted to just say something
about that. Oh. As good as, and, and it was technically, this was an incredible show.
And a whole thing ran on autopilot, because I was watching the control booth that could see it,
you know, on the other side of the theater. It was just one person with all the computer.
Drinking coffee had his feet up on the desk. You know, the thing was just rolling around.
I was looking at it. Yeah. Of course. Yeah. Um, there was a, um, uh,
there's a monitor, um, on the, on the balcony. Yeah. So that the, uh, the, well, I guess we'll just call
actors on stage so that they could, you know, see the conductor when, because the conductor, you know,
he had the click track and he had all the cues and, and you know, so you can see exactly when
when you have to start to sing. Yeah. So that guy was very, very important for the show. But what I
did notice, it was his show, actually. Well, boy, speaking of geeky nerds. Yeah. He was definitely
a geeky nerd. Yeah. You know, even though it was technically perfect in an all fit,
there's something about, uh, and we've seen Sinatra, one of his last concerts in New Jersey.
Yeah. There's something about him interacting with the band, um, you know, the way only he could,
you know, you may think. Hoppically go over three, you know, three, um, beats, whatever, bars, beats,
bars, that I missed. I really did not have that, you know, Sinatra. Of course. And no,
well, but that's the first, you know, I can sing every single Sinatra song. I have the last time
I have all his and Lawrence Wilkes albums. I remember we saw him there, and I saw him before that,
in Las Vegas, coming up through the curtain, but then through the band. All right, through the band.
I came up. I didn't even have something you was there. Yeah. That's typical. And then you could
see, I was in the second row, you could see his blue eyes. They were so blue. And I thought,
no, no, no, you know, they're all blue eyes. Very, very blue. And he looks, it's almost like he looked at
every person in the audience. You feel so, um, like you, you get attention from him. It's wonderful.
Well, he was probably looking at you and at the guys. No, hey, darling. Not really. It was amazing.
And that moment I understood why this guy was so big. So that is exactly what I missed last night at the show.
That was just, it's not there. Okay. That's my turn. Okay. And I speak now. You just talked a whole
time about the whole Sinatra show. No, I didn't, I didn't explain what I thought. I wasn't done yet, but
please, go ahead. Okay. Please, please go ahead. Well, I think the most important thing is
that he could have even done it without the dancers. For me, the dancers were not even there.
And yes, there's something. Looking at him at the screen.
Yeah. I can't say something. Yeah. Here's the problem with the dancers. And I studied this
for three songs in a row. Yeah. Not one of the women was hot looking and not one of the guys was
hot looking. It was not not one single one. Could I say, oh, man, I was waiting. I was waiting. I was
waiting. No, no, no, no. It was very sexy. Which one? She was a little bit fuller and she played
that very sexy woman on the piano. You know, that Roger Rabbit with a short hair.
Jessica Rabbit with a short hair. No long. Long blonde hair. There are wigs. Okay. But that's what
they're all wigs. No problem. I didn't think. Not one single hottie that the dancers and the
singers were looking like movie stars. I should have looked like movie stars from
these days. You know, like an Ava Gardener, like a Brigitte Bardo, a like a Malamon row.
They didn't have the glamour that I found on the screen exactly. That I'm in so much. I'm in
holding it. And then underneath there was a little bit of black and white, a little fade out
thing going on for me. Remember the shows that I also have on tape for myself from the 60s,
the black and white. Not many. You know, one camera and it was only a little bit dull.
Switching the lens together goes up. Not that feeling. I got that feeling again. Like, you know,
a sixies TV show that was still not really, you know. Well, so part of that of course
could have been intentional because it did start in the 40s and it got went all the way through
the 60s. And I think you cannot draw too much attention. But it was not the dancers didn't
belong to Sinatra's world. Here it is. I got, and they tried to do that. They really,
because all of the Sinatra footage was black and white. And they didn't. So they were very colorful,
actually. I think the contrast didn't stop. Bryce, lady, you won't let me talk at all. All right.
Okay. Go ahead darling. No, you please. You clearly have a lot on your mind. I'll wait.
Well, I think they didn't have, they didn't study the way they performed in these days enough.
They were in English. They were English. That was. They were there, too. They were in 40 and 45.
But the, yeah. But so some of the actresses won played me a ferro, which was actually pretty good.
She had the haircut and everything. And kind of that attitude you want to slap her for.
But there was, you know what I mean. And then there was, there was two or three other
pieces where the female, some of the female actors would sing along just a little bit with them.
And with it or speak along in an English accent, that didn't do it for me. I was like, no, no,
that's, that's just, just wasn't right. And why was she doing a duet with him?
Ah, because they had to have at least one duet in the show.
I mean, he's done duets. And actually, you know what? They had that whole piece of videos.
Nancy was there. They had that whole, they had that whole piece of video from Bono.
Yeah. Which was that at the American Music Awards. It was some award show. Very good.
It was a damn good speech. I don't know who the, the speech wrote that. He wrote that.
He wrote. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. The tough. That definitely wrote that. That was a good speech. Wasn't it?
My God. Yeah. And we're not big Bono fans. No. But listening to that, I was like, wow. Wow.
Totally. Yeah. Do you think you didn't even talk about that? Absolutely. Of course we didn't. We didn't talk
about the show at all. I wasn't allowed. No, I don't want to talk about the show. No,
yeah. Um, I have your CD. It's not pod safe. You realize that, right? So we could get arrested,
go to jail and be Bubba's bitch. Is that daddy? Yeah, you want me to play that one? Yeah. Okay.
Hold on a second. So you want to set it up? You want to. So my dad is being big band with me. Just,
you know, for my dad. Well, I mean, you do a little more set up than that. I mean, it's an actual CD that you
believe. Well, a couple of songs we recorded real fast in a studio in Rotterdam. She dumped Rotterdam.
And we gave it away when I had my cosmetics because made a company for Christmas, you know, just.
So the band is, it was actually your dad's big band at the time. Was the big old band? It was a big,
small big band. And the guys were all 80 years old, right? Yeah, but great musicians. All right. Let's give it a shot here.
I'm playing this off the other computer. So I have no idea what kind of luck we'll have. Here we go.
Daddy, gee.
I'm swelling, say we're skills, we pay with labels. Daddy, only want the best for me.
Here's an amazing revelation with a bit of stimulating. I'll be in your great sensation.
I'll be on inspiration, Daddy. I won't have read you, car.
Champagne, caddy, red, daddy.
Oh, we want the best for me.
Here's my dad.
Here's an amazing revelation with a bit of stimulating. I'll be in your great sensation.
I'll be on inspiration, Daddy. I won't have charge of counts and sex for large amounts,
Daddy. Oh, we want the best for me. Daddy, gee.
I'm swelling, say we're skills, we pay with labels. Daddy.
Oh, we want the best for me.
Here's an amazing revelation with a bit of stimulating.
I'll be in your great sensation. I'll be on inspiration, Daddy.
I won't have read you, car. Champagne, caddy, red, daddy.
Oh, we want the best for me.
Here's my dad.
Here's an amazing revelation with a bit of stimulating. I'll be in your great sensation.
I'll be on inspiration, Daddy. I won't have charge of counts and sex for large amounts,
Daddy. Oh, we want the best for me.
Oh, we want the best for me.
Yeah.
That's sweet.
You're so amazing. Half way through the song, just like, okay, turn it down. I've heard enough.
No way, man. This is awesome.
Now, one thing that really irritated me about that song, no, about the CD.
I about to know about the Sinatra.
Oh, can I just kind of just back and out this for one second then?
So Patricia Pye and the John Pye Orchestra with Daddy written by Bobby Troop and in memory
of the fabulous Julie London who sang the song originally.
Yeah. Yeah. Don't give me that look.
Is she dead? Yeah.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Yeah, she's dead. The people who represent her music, by the way, are not dead.
Remember how much they charge us for using that for a TV commercial Holy Cranky?
Let me tell you.
Great stuff, great stuff. I love that to you.
And isn't a good that I them such a lazy bugger that I hadn't sent that to that guy yet, but I still had it.
Yeah, maybe now I'm going to send it. Well, he has it.
He doesn't know. I'm going to send this to you. He wants the CD. He's a collecter.
So one thing that I always hate because in a musical,
Yeah. That's why I didn't do a musical yet.
Now you know that can you talk into the micro musical people? Yeah. They sing.
They all sing like that.
Everything is like that. And you always know. Especially like that.
And you know exactly when they're going to go into a song, right?
Because then they start the movement starts to slow down and then all sudden.
Oh, they start to sing. But oh, you hear me. Yes.
In the conversation. But the girls who sing and I think if you have a show about Frank Sinatra,
you know, make sure that if somebody sings in that shows, sings exactly the way you
sang in these years. Yeah. Yeah. 40, 50. And so they, they, I don't know what
sound was. But the moment they start to sing, it was all like, I can occur.
Doesn't go with and the hands, and that I'm speaking Dutch because my parents are here.
And then they do a piece of and do sisters kind of thing. Yeah. That didn't work at all.
The little costumes aren't. Now, I am the best. First of all, those costumes were wrinkled,
ill-fitting. And you see that too. And some of the shoes were wrong. I hate to say,
but I've gotten a real eye for things and clothing. And he's really dirty. That's for dirty.
Did you see that too? Okay. The Frank Sinatra had. But in general, in general,
this was a good show. No. No. What I wanted to finish that. And so they did the end
sisters thing together. You know, the suits. I didn't fit that well. You see those little things.
Little things. Little things. Little things. I see those things. And I think it seems to me that they
paid a lot of attention to the technical parts of the show. Exactly. And just, and then it's
right. And it's like they had some choreographer who was only responsible for the choreography. But
no one looking at the total picture and saying it doesn't quite all match the nail together.
The harmonies from the so-called Andrew Sisters kind of thing that they did wrong. Wrong harmonies.
Yeah. Wrong harmonies. Because the Andrew Sisters' harmonies were wrong. The lead.
Now the lead. No, no, no. In these days, the lead was always in the middle.
Then you had the third force, the higher, the third harmony was up there above the middle.
And then you had the lower voice under there. So the lead was always in the middle.
Right. And the lead sometimes took over from the other. That they shifted, right?
Yeah. Right. Right. Right. Right. Right. Right. Right. Right. And that made it so fantastic.
And they got it all wrong. And a lot of people have that wrong. No. We made a study of that and we did
the best thing and we had an award for that. I don't have, I don't have any star sisters stuff.
Well, that's time with you next time. Next time I want to go to jail.
In general, though, how would you rate the show?
I really enjoyed it. But that's because I'm a for in Sinatra fan.
Yeah. And I think that even he's set his charismatic. He's great. He's one of that. We never will.
We never, never, never will have another Sinatra. We won't say that. But not like that. You know?
Yeah. The guy lived, lived to sing and his voice and easy sings very easy. And I so I enjoyed that.
And even I said, I told you already that even without the dances would have been a great show.
Yeah. You know, because he's still, even not being alive. He still did it.
So ladies and gentlemen, the Patricia Pi rating for Sinatra. From one to ten?
Yes. Very big eight. Oh, okay.
And that's because of the two points is because of the dancers and singers.
Oh, really? It would have been a ten if they would have been a ten if that was a little bit more perfect.
Yeah. Now, it's a bit poor. If you plan on going to the Sinatra show,
it's at the London Playedium. Yeah. About half a block down. There's a cafe.
But go and see it because it's amazing. It's definitely see the show. But if you're going to see the show,
do not repeat, do not go into cafe logic, which is half a block.
We were like, look at six, 30. We have an hour before the show. This is a cafe.
So why don't we just pop into the cafe and we'll have a quick bite to eat. It took us four.
It took him 40 minutes for fucking sushi. Yeah. I mean, and they were very apologetic.
But they're like, oh, yeah. Well, all of a sudden, all the people came in the same time.
Well, you're in the theater district. Hello. You're next to the Playedium.
You know, you're going to have people in there. You noted they have to be on time. That's sucked.
That really does not stand. So we missed the actual half of the opening number.
Yes. They let us in, which is nice. Yeah. But it's, oh my god. When you talk to them and I said,
can we come in a little bit late because we're still waiting? But that was unforgivable. Let's just
just put it different. I sent you to go talk to them. Because I know if I go to talk to the guys and
say, hey, if we come in later, is that okay? They'll look like, it's screw you. But when you walk and
you look killer last night, you had your new shoes on. You had, you didn't take it. You're handbag.
I was in the French tonight. You were told they were, you know, they, they probably were saying,
you have to go to the back stage door. The back stage door is there. You aren't you in the show?
We weren't in the show. She had a new good shoot shoot. What did you say?
Well, we went with the train by train. As we say, pardon me, ma'am.
Is that the cat the shit on your shoe?
Oh, yeah. Okay. So, but in general, it was good. And in your dad, he was, he, the
morning he said, I was stoned. He said he was completely stoned because the music
got into his head. And he was, he was separate. I can see it. He was separating the arrangements.
Oh, yeah. He was listening to every single bit. Edge of his chair. Only staring at the orchestra.
Yeah. That's right. And he, just to see my dad, and that's where we, we went actually,
to see my dad enjoyed the so much. Nice, huh? So much. I know that was just, that was the most
beautiful part of the evening. Hey, Adam. This is Jeff. Just out of Nashville. Can I see?
I was calling this message, actually, is for Christina begging her to start her own show.
Because I live in Nashville near Nashville, which is a town full of shitty music. They're very
few rareties here that are actually good, such as Matthew Eagle. And anyway, I need to know about
some good music. So please, please, I beg you, start your own show. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Oh, thank you. Everyone from Nashville to go thank you very much. I think
she's going to do it today. Yeah. Right. Who's this? Dude, did you eat my French vanilla
strawberry yogurt? Dude, dude, don't, don't eat someone's yogurt. Hey, dude. I didn't even eat it.
No, I didn't eat anything. Did you eat my French food? I did. I had the generic brand of corn flakes.
I thought I didn't even like it. Oh, did you eat the white? Hey, did you eat it? No, she didn't
hear it. No, it was on that phone. Listen to this. Give her the headphones for second. Give her the
headphones. Don't go away on. Don't you dare leave. Just put the headphones on. Put them on. Put them on.
I'll play it for you here, comes. Hey Adam, this is Jeff. Just out of Nashville, Tennessee. I was
calling this message actually for Christina begging her to start her own show. Because I live in Nashville
near Nashville, which is a town full of shitty music. They're very few rareties here that are
actually good, such as Matthew Eagle. And anyway, I need to know about some good music. So please,
please, I beg you, start your own show. Thank you very much. There you go. Okay, I'll do it just for the
people Nashville. Are you going to do it today? Yeah. Just bring up some MP3s. We've got the theme song.
Christina's really worried about, well, will I be boring? I don't think you'll be boring.
I am kind of boring. Just talk about the vanilla stuff your mom stole in eight.
Okay. Okay. So we'll do it later today. Okay. Okay. But dad, I'm going to go to a gig later.
What gig? I'm not sure yet. What time? At the back line? Yeah. What time? Seven. Did she clear this with you?
I did. I didn't plan on with you yet. I ran it through the authorities first. The real
the real boss, the real word. Okay. We want to do the show before you go then. Okay. I'll go get some stuff right
now. Get a couple MP3s and we'll just do a show. It'll be fantastic. Okay. Go out. Here mom.
You yogurt steel. Yeah. And it was actually not light. And I don't like that. So you shouldn't eat that eater.
I'll be playing a song on them. I'll play a song and then we'll wrap up the show for today. Okay.
Well, you don't want to hear the song. You just rip your headphones off like that. It's the booty voodoo.
She got the smile and you move. She's got the bruise.
Down with the girls. They all say, oh, we love you. They love you. They love me. Let's go with the bruise.
Man, come on. Let's get this circus done.
They do get the booty. She has the booty voodoo. You got the booty voodoo. Now come here kids.
When you think of those, they just say, we'll let us have a laugh and say, yeah.
They all say, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Hey, hey, hey, hey yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah , yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, uh, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah
She can not stir originally from Australia now from California
Leakholder with the foodie and the booty foodie coming up next on serious stars one-o-two
We've got Madge Weinstein's East Radio followed by Pacific Coast Hellway Dawn Drew then the Gilmore Daily podcast and we wind it up with which it all
rather for its groove grass
Right here on one-o-two
So I will see this weekend, huh?
You know, it was nice that our daughter went to with us last night. It's she and she enjoyed herself
And walking around with her. I noticed nobody's looking at me and
You guys look killer together and you're walking through water loostation
Wow, that is the new and improved
Yeah, yeah, it's a perfect mix of of you and I isn't it
Yeah, okay, well, what does that mean we look so good?
Oh, it's you got the good things from me and the good things from you. Yeah, so yeah, that's right. Yeah, it's true. Yeah, you're long legs
That's about all that's good in me. I guess
You're brain
Hey, baby, so I won't see you this weekend. I'm gonna go see my mom and since she's in the hospital and visiting hours at the end of the day
You too late to fly back some staying overnight, so yeah, well, I've seen enough of you. No
Actually thanks. We had a great time. Didn't we?
We had a fantastic time
We had a fantastic time. Absolutely
It's good to do that now and then. I think people without
With children should should do that absolutely get away get away go do it. Yeah, and
And I'll see you at the palace big opening night Saturday night and and Monday will be back. You're gonna be on the show Monday
I might okay
I love you. I love you, too
Another pod show pod cast stick it in your ear
Get this pod cast and we're great ones like it on the high performance pod cast delivery network from pod show and line-white networks
Love it