Dilta Sierra Charley, 3-3-0.
$16 billion worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Transmores?
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need nuss thinking crazy.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding.
We got a whole fresh week
that we can look at with great resentment.
It's Monday everybody how you do it.
This is the daily source code.
No sign of weather, not a cloud in the sky.
Taking it easy, I was doing just fine.
It's got as my witness.
I was minding my business when she knew.
In the tenest like it, drop it to the breeze.
Face like an angel exes along as she pleased.
I'll never forget it.
I got all caught up in it.
She was the object of my affection, then.
When changed direction.
Like that, you shutters in your doors.
But you love your phone as your lawyer.
Mercy when she raised down on you.
You've been telling you've been warned.
You don't know what you're meant for.
She's a perfect star.
Once she comes, you'll never be the same.
So you better stay away from her, I can't change.
She held like thunder when the sky opened up.
I started shaking when the lightning struck.
My poor heart was breaking.
Where they removed.
She was making them.
She blew right over just as quick as she came.
She probably don't even remember my name.
I'm a romantic speechless trying to figure the pieces.
Just another seduction in her path of destruction.
Like that, you shutters in your doors.
But you love your phone as your lawyer.
Mercy when she raised down on you.
You've been telling you've been warned.
You don't know what you're meant for.
She's a perfect star.
Once she comes, you'll never be the same.
So you better stay away from her, I can't change.
So you better stay away from her, I can't you.
Once she comes, you'll never be the same.
The way from Hurricane Jane, once she comes, you'll never be the same, so you've got to stay away from Hurricane.
I can't get you shutters and your doors, but in a hurry, you've got to stop.
Lord and mercy, when she race, I don't know you.
You've been told you've been warned, you don't know what going for.
She's a perfect storm, better stay inside, where it's safe and warm.
And once she comes, you'll never be the same, so you better stay away from Hurricane Jane.
Once she comes, you'll never be the same, so you better stay away from Hurricane Jane.
Colin Ray, Hurricane Jane, on a Spirion Spearion Records.
You can find that at the pod save music network.
Nothing like a bit of country to get you going, eh?
Find that at music.podshow.com.
It's Monday, everybody.
How you doing?
Whole new week of daily source codes coming your way.
My last week here in the cottage before it's off to New York.
London, San Francisco, Netherlands, all kinds of traveling coming up.
It's going to be very, very busy couple of weeks.
Let me see.
Kind of slow start today.
I tried to watch the Super Bowl last night.
It was on Sky One.
And it started, well, of course, the pregame started at 10 a.m.
10 p.m.
And the actual game kickoff didn't start until 11.30.
So I sat there and watched, I sat there and watched most of it, actually.
What the hell was going on with the sound?
I don't know if we were listening to a different feed of stuff,
or if it was just crap, I mean, tell me, please,
but the Stevie Wonder pregame show, dude.
It was like, here's just stone.
And you could hear microphones were all over the play.
And the music track was just that.
The track, no one was actually playing in the instruments live.
But they could not get the sound right.
It sounded totally crap.
I don't know if it was wireless mics interfering with each other.
Actually, I did see that they were using a particular type of microphone
that I would not have chosen for just stone.
Nor for a read the Franklin and Aaron Neville, who did the star-spangled banner
same thing.
You know, and Aaron Neville's already, you know, he kind of has a wimpy voice.
It was just, it was like there was a gate on it, or some just, it was messed up,
and it was horrible.
And then, of course, I watched a kickoff, and I was like 12, 15,
and, you know, the first quarter just about ended, and I can't handle it.
So congrats to the, to the Steelers, of course, coming from a short stint
and West Virginia at school, both the Steelers.
And, of course, the penguins are teams that I followed quite a bit.
And not bad, the way the sea hawks presented themselves, I think.
That was damn good.
And I read this morning, because, of course, I didn't make it to halftime.
Because, gee, we really needed to see the rolling stones.
I'm sorry, the stones now in my mind are officially just pathetic.
You know, they agreed to do all this stuff, and I didn't see the performance,
so I can't really say too much about it.
But apparently, sensors deemed too lyrics too sexually explicit to be broadcast.
They were cut from the three song shows.
Starting me up in rough justice, we're subject to censorship, says the BBC.
The satisfaction was left intact.
Again, what did they pull out?
You make a dead man calm, is that it?
Isn't that why we haven't been playing that on a radio for 30 years?
It's just crazy.
And that the stones would agree to do that.
It was just, that was just disappointing.
Do people really care about the rolling stones anymore?
It just seems like, let me Patricia, who grew, you know, back in the day before I was born.
You, well, I was born, but before I was cognizant of what was going on in the music world,
you either were for the Beatles or you were for the stones.
You rarely were for both, you know, you stood behind one of those.
And Patricia was definitely a stones fan.
She was just, she was like, this is dumb.
This is no good.
You know, the press conference, there's, I don't know.
Whatever.
That's fine.
To each zone, I guess.
Lots of work being done over the weekend.
And just the end of last week between PW Fenton and Cast Blaster Mike.
I've been bitching and moaning about my computer apparently not being able to keep time,
or at least not being able to keep time and sync with other computers,
specifically PW Fenton's computer.
Didn't know if it was cast blast or didn't know if it was this countdown time,
or everything seemed to be all over the map.
And, well, some work was done.
And Mike is going to explain it all himself.
Hi, Adam.
It's cast blast or Mike.
With a very boring story, so I'm not sure if you're going to play this.
But at least, you know, how it works.
Just wanted to explain the time of problem.
Everyone's been talking about.
Yes, there are different timers in each,
B.C.
There is the clock, which is what you see in the screen.
You see in the bottom right corner of the screen,
which runs even when the P.C. is off.
And then there are several timers in the hardware,
which only run when the P.C. is on.
And then there is the timer in the sound card,
and often there are more than one,
one for playback, one for recording.
And they are all not calibrated,
simply because it's too expensive.
The problem you had with cast blast
was actually in the error of,
of me of Mike.
It was a little rounding error,
and the more it added up.
And so in the end, after in your case,
24 and a half minute, the error was five seconds.
But it wouldn't have been too bad
if you would have watched that timer.
But anyway, I fixed a bug,
and now it's accurate up to a microsecond.
And it's independent of the clocks and timers in your machine.
It's basically the time pro in the MP3 file itself.
So if serious uses an accurate timer,
and playing the file,
which they do as a P.C.
and then all problems are fixed now.
And it's far more accurate than it's necessary.
So I'm going to send you new beta soon,
and you can get that a try,
and hopefully we can like,
heat up alive a little bit,
a little bit better.
No, yeah.
That's my mission.
That's it for now.
Bye-bye.
Cast blasted Mike on the microphone, everybody.
And he did indeed send me another special
podfather edition data.
And it's really cool because now in the title bar
of the window of Cast Blaster, it actually has a countdown timer
that is counting back.
I can see 13 minutes and 49 seconds now.
You pre-configure that under the Configure tab.
And what's really nice is one minute before the time expires,
the whole window, the Cast Blaster,
basically starts to kind of flashing glow,
not irritating,
but enough to catch your attention.
So we'll see how it works out.
I mean, the theory behind all of this is what Mike has now done
is he's basically taking the dividing the samples by the sample rate
and that should equal the time exactly out to a microsecond
or something like that.
I'd be couldn't get a little more precise,
Mike only a microsecond.
And so this should play back exactly the same amount of time
as it was recorded.
It's cool.
It's great that we came up with this issue
and we're able to fix it really quickly.
I like doing that.
That's the kind of development I like.
Lots of talk about this about AOL and Yahoo,
who are going to start charging,
I think it's a quarter cent per email cent
to anyone within their network using their email system.
The details are intricate,
and there's basically there's a white list
and then there's a guaranteed delivery list
and there'll be a read receipt list.
It seems like,
yeah,
it seems to me like not the best way to do this.
I think drawing the analogy to the old postal world
really misses out on a lot of exciting things that we could be doing.
And already a lot of people said,
hey, you know, why don't you just use RSS for that type of stuff
which is basically the published and subscribe mechanism
that podcasting use and web logs use it with your newsletter.
And I think that that as an underpinning
and you know, a way to basically unsubscribe
from a stream of information coming in
rather than trying to figure out how to block it.
Of course, it makes total total sense.
But we're going to have to do a lot of work on the interfaces.
The first thing we have to do is hide RSS.
You know, that's maybe this is where the stuff like newsletter
and the plugins that you put into your outlook.
The basically make the new stories look like email messages.
I think that's probably the way to go
and then of course you still need to figure out
how people discover and subscribe to things that they're actually interested in.
I do believe that people will subscribe to RSS feeds
of just commercials.
In fact, I do it all the time.
I subscribe to promo.podshow.com
which is nothing more than a feed of commercials.
I love listening to it.
From time to time, I pick something out and play it on the show.
But we have to do a lot of work on hiding it.
Wait it with email.
If you want to make it basically email that you can unsubscribe
from commercial messages, then we're going to have to do a lot of work.
It's really the same magic that I always intended RSS to,
that's always the way I intended RSS to function with podcasting
because you don't see it.
You know, it's just keep it away.
And of course, it is still very, very prevalent.
Right up there with the VHS and beta
and all those other wonderful acronyms that we come up with,
that we think consumers are really interested in.
Lost it update.
I don't know if I told you, but on the 28th of February, 2005,
my suit against the publisher of magazine
and the chief editors,
is two of them of magazine and Netherlands.
We'll come before the court in Amsterdam.
Very bullish about this, obviously.
Professor Lawrence Lessick has checked in
and said that he's available to do anything necessary
to help he thinks it's very important, obviously.
And this is being followed very closely by many people,
many of them lawyers who are interested to see really what
the power of the creative commons license will be.
For those of you who don't know what happened,
a magazine basically took my pictures off of my flicker page,
which are very clearly marked with a creative commons license
of attribution non-commercial share-like.
And I want to ask me, and of course, they're completely commercial.
In fact, they promoted the fact that these pictures
were on the inside on the cover full page.
And in my mind, and this is something that I'm working on
with my team on, we have to draw the analogy and say,
look, you know, if you download one song illegally
and you're caught as a consumer,
immediately you get the RIA and their settlement bureau,
nagging your ass, you know, they'll give you anywhere from
15,000 to $150,000 fine.
Which is, by the way, is not a court fine,
it's just they say that that's what they're going to sue you for
and then you can usually wind up settling for $4,000.
And I feel that if that can be happening in today's day and age,
then it should work the other way around.
When mainstream media becomes so arrogant,
they think that they can take stuff from us.
Well, they're going to find out what that means.
I can't mention the person who sent this to me,
but he says it's been listening for about 10 months now.
This was my question about Defra.
This is the agricultural department that has a building
very close to the cottage that has these huge cell phone towers,
which may or may not be affecting our health,
the jury is definitely still out on that.
He says that most of the building is now occupied by IBM staff.
He works for them as well,
following the outsourcing of Defra's IT last year.
He works there about 50% of the week.
Hey, neighbor, how are you doing?
Not sure where you got your information about the mobile mass in 2007,
but all I know is that as part of the outsourcing contract,
IBM will not allow to relocate X-Defra staff
from the site for three years,
starting October, 2004.
I think the picture beyond that is still unclear.
If you hear anything else, I'll let you know.
Okay.
And so I wasn't allowed to say who we was,
or give any more clues and understandably so.
We don't want you in trouble,
because you are my deep throat across the street.
Hey, and on Saturday, Christina wanted to go visit Owen.
Owen the emo her boyfriend,
who lives in South Hampton,
which is about 40 miles,
so all in all about 55 minutes to an hour's drive,
and Patricia and I said,
ah, what the hell, you know,
of course we'll take you down.
We'll drop you off and we'll go mess around
for a couple hours.
We'll find something to do.
And as we neared South Hampton,
we saw the signs for Bournemouth,
and I've heard many things about Bournemouth.
It's really, it's on the southern coast of England,
and it's kind of like a co-type situation
where the warm golf stream flows through.
And there are even palm trees,
another tropical foliage to be found
in that particular part of the UK.
And it was really only what?
There's another 30 miles or 40 miles from South Hampton,
so we dropped Christina off.
It was shitty weather, unfortunately.
Right, right, man.
By the way, I'd never driven the jag
for such a long distance.
What an enjoyable car.
Oh, man.
Particularly the,
was it the predictive,
is it called predictive cruise control?
Not predictive.
Maybe it is what that's called.
Where basically maintains your speed,
based upon the speed of the car in front of you,
what an enjoyable way to drive,
and just a nice ride.
We set the cruise at 90 all the way down,
and it was like we were doing 50.
It wouldn't have made any difference.
It was quiet.
We could have a nice conversation.
It was comfortable.
Of course, this is a huge highway,
so it was really quite okay to do that.
What are the, what actually are the speed limits here in the UK?
I mean, what is the speed limit when it's not posted?
I'd like to know that.
I know that in some zones at 60,
it's 50, I've seen 30 signs,
but I really don't know what it is on the,
on the open freeway.
Hopefully, I should know this, of course,
being a licensed driver.
But Bournemouth was really nice.
I've heard a lot of people kind of slide it off saying,
oh, you know, it's where old people go to die.
But I liked it.
You know, we had tea,
overlooking the ocean and the beach,
and there's a great airport there.
Bournemouth,
international airport,
which has an ILS instrument landing system.
Hey, that might be a potential place to build,
to build the next house.
Which, of course, is still,
you know, at least a year away from now,
but very interesting, very interesting indeed.
Let's see.
Hey, Adam, this is KFC from the pod chick show at pod chick.com,
and also on the pod show now.
Thank you so much.
Hey, I wanted to tell you that I'm just a series
as those quasi-poly guys are.
And I would love,
I mean, love to be on before the beep of,
hey, the satellite window is closed.
So if you could please do that,
we could save a lot,
a little goats,
because you know how that little goat got it?
Well, there's lots more little goats out there,
and I'd hate to see them lose it.
So if you could get us on,
we're very serious about it.
So, make them smile.
Help me out.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
We're our flank.
We believe in an internet
that's safe from viruses and scammers.
We're our flank.
We believe your personal information
to be just that, personal.
And we believe your internet
should be a friend, not a foe.
We're our flank.
Make this smart choice.
Visit earthlink.net
and discover what our internet experts
can do for you.
Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
Okay, all you, this is out there.
I only have one advice.
Quit your job.
I've got to make a mortgage pay.
I'm here.
I've got a wife and kids.
I'm telling you.
I listen.
I've got expenses.
Good work.
You can have that job.
I said,
I listen to this podcast on business success tips.
I quit my job.
I'm now rich in payments.
I get laid all the time.
I have lots of fun.
You can do the same thing.
Hey Adam.
This is Chef Mark from the remarkable Palette podcast
in New York City.
And here's one of my kitchen quick tips.
A tip for poaching eggs.
Add a splash of vinegar or lemon juice
to the poaching water.
Just before adding the eggs.
The acid in the water will help to quickly
coagulate the egg proteins
and keep the egg white from running all over.
Ensuring an attractive poached egg.
For more tips, recipes,
and interviews with food professionals,
listen to the remarkable Palette podcast.
You can find me at remarkablepalette.blogspot.com
or on the iTunes directory.
And now back to the daily source code with Adam Curry.
You'll buddy.
That's kind of confusing.
So there's a Chef Mark in New York City.
And then of course there's Chef Mark in San Francisco
who travels all over the place to London
and did the big PIA for us.
That's confusing.
I think that you guys should do a three round mud vessel
battle it out for the name.
And it's both spelled the same way.
The satellite window has about two and a half minutes
before closing.
So those of you listening to this podcast on
serious stars 103.
Pacific Coast.
Hellwide coming up in just moments.
East radio with Madge Weinstein.
Don and Drew.
All the kids.
They'll tell 10 p.m. Eastern 7 p.m. Pacific Times.
Syria stars 103.
I did want to just say,
you know, well, everyone's listening.
They said this is Bruhah.
This violence really.
About pictures of the profit Mohammed has caught me
a little bit by surprise.
I had no idea.
First of all, I had no idea that there's a law.
That says if you disgrace the profit Mohammed that you
should be killed.
And apparently it's also illegal by Islam.
Muslim law or Islam to even depict the profit at all.
Boy, I think we're certainly learning some lessons here
because the outrage of this is sparked is I'd say
concerning at the very least.
I mean, if someone's pissed off at a newspaper here in the UK
as an example or in the US, what typically happens is there's a
boycott against the publication.
The publication is held to account.
And yeah, someone might throw some rocks and some firebombs
and maltov cocktails at the offices of the newspaper
that offended anyone at this group.
But instead, everyone's taken to burning embassies.
This is, I didn't expect that, which means and probably
of the thousands of people who demonstrated outside of these embassies
and torch them.
I would wager that a large portion didn't even see the pictures.
And that they were just driven by pure emotion and anger
and feeling of misunderstanding.
And this is a problem.
It really, really, really is a problem.
Because this just shows you how many people are extremely offended
by this and are willing to take violent action.
And it's much, much more than I ever anticipated.
We're going to continue talking about this on the podcast.
But first, I want to say goodbye.
Hopefully, exactly on time this time for the satellite window
to our serious listeners.
We'll catch you all on the Tuesday's edition of the show.
Boom, exactly 24 minutes and 30 seconds.
We continue now.
And I really don't know what to say.
First of all, I'm kind of looking for other Muslim leaders to stand up
and call for some calm and for some thought about this.
Clearly, everyone has to learn.
And it has to go from both sides because we're very used to being ridiculed
for anything here in, I'll just say the West.
I don't even know if that's correct to say it that way.
But shoot, I got ridiculed all the time.
People make character chores and say nasty things.
And I don't go out and threaten to kill anyone.
If they say it about my family, about my parents,
about what I believe in, what else is there?
Maybe that's a better question.
What else is there that we should know?
What are the ground rules of other things we can't do to avoid this?
I'm not saying we have to, but I'd really like to know
where the pressure points are going to be.
Because for me, the big question is,
did the Danish publication know about this?
Did they know what kind of outrageous was spark?
Were they doing it just to prove a point?
That's the stuff I'd like to know.
And let's keep our eye on this.
There's something going on that we need to pay attention to.
Linda Smith sent me an email saying that she's having big problems
uploading her feed, getting it to work.
Actually, I have a whole segment.
I want to talk about a whole bunch of different people
who've been having trouble getting started in podcasting.
Linda says I'm getting very discouraged.
Recording it was easy.
I've already spent $80 in a very good microphone.
One recommended by podcast solutions.
I await its delivery even as I type.
And then she set it up a show site at blogger.com.
Worldwide eroticlove.blogspot.com.
And this is one of the got me.
It would be an honor to be promoted or praised on your show.
I call you the John Peel of podcasters.
You remember the British rock DJ John Peel?
What he did from any British rock bands?
He died.
He's dead.
I don't want to be the John Peel of anything, please.
Let's listen to a little bit of Linda because it kind of caught me by surprise.
Everybody.
This is got us, Linda.
Live on erotic podcast tonight forever.
Berkeley, California.
Just what the heck am I supposed to say now?
Why believe that a quality sexual education is going to be a
American and the world's the safer place.
Far better, more active.
Far better, more effective than.
Ask this only program.
You see, so far I was like into it, right?
I'm like, okay.
This, this is interesting.
Let's listen to it.
Don't they tell you just say no.
Is, why take a sexual education.
And entertain it.
And every y'all says sexual.
Please, keep you put me.
You can set the adults only.
Anyway, what the heck am I supposed to say next?
The podcasting book tells me you just focus talking to one person.
So the heck with it, am I supposed to pick somebody who I love?
Why am I really hot and sexy?
My darling favorite rock star, jibby page.
Oh, jibby page.
Beautiful, sweetest, sexiest, silkyest lips.
Oh, my darling, your jibby page.
I want to ride your cock.
Oh, no.
Right.
So, and it goes on for like another minute and forty-six seconds.
I think it definitely gets some attention.
Linda with your podcast.
Let me give you about the URL again.
Was it?
But this is, I was just interested to hear how many people are definitely having issues
getting up and running.
And they're following the books and the websites.
Worldwide eroticlove.blogspot.com.
That's it.
So that'll just be an intro to a couple of different types of feedback I got.
Here's one from Frank and apologize for emailing you like this.
My question regarding the website aspect of podcasting.
I know about blogger, lives in a feed burner, but I have no clue what these do.
It seems like I need a combination of several of these services.
I just don't know why.
I have a domain name register, but I don't know what to do from there.
I would like my webpage to have its own email and its own name without a dot
Lipsin dot com after my own domain name.
And then it just goes on, you know, to basically clue this about how to get this started.
And you know what?
It is rather daunting.
There's a lot of steps you have to take.
This of course is what we set out to solve with the podcast delivery network and the pod show podcast network.
And we now have, I think, I saw the last list about 20 people beta testing now.
And again, this is two sides.
This is a listener side that seamlessly because you can be a listener.
You can be a podcaster at the same time.
So kind of flows seamlessly into each other.
And it takes away all of those problems.
In fact, if you use cast blaster and I have that set up now, you'll just record, you'll hit publish and it's done.
Your show notes go in, your feed is taken care of everything.
Everything is completely done.
So look forward to that coming.
I think we're about ready to let some more beta testers and I looked over the weekend and even more stuff that started to change.
So it's definitely getting very, very exciting.
More questions about the pod safe music network and the podcast delivery network.
Hey, I'm Russell Henson here.
Just wanted to provide a bit of feedback on my experience trying to join me at
music.putshare.com as a new podcaster.
I'm trying to put together my first astronomy podcast.
And I wanted to include some pod safe music in there.
So I went to the music.
The pod shared a calm to try and find a sample.
I could put in and put out for people to have a listen to and give me some feedback.
And I find out I can actually download any music that I can insert as an audio file until I sign up, which is all good.
But going through the silent process, I find I have to have all my details such as my podcast name, blah, blah, blah.
And my podcast feed, which has to be a valid feed, all sorted out and ready to go.
Maybe I'm doing things back to front to everyone else, but I'm trying to get all the audio together and have a show done up.
So I can then create my feed and my show and my links and all that sort of stuff.
But I can do that unless I'm already signed up and got the music.
So I'm feeling a bit lost here.
Do I need to sign up first to get some music?
Have I got something wrong here?
Do I just have to go with some dummy audio loop for now or something or other until I get it all sorted out?
And then I can add the music later.
Not sure, but it's just confusing to me and not that might be some confusing to other people signing up as well.
So just sort of put it out to you see if you had any solutions, if I missed something or whether that's the way it is.
And I just have to keep with it for now.
Okay, thanks a lot.
Well, yeah, that is the way it is.
For right now, you would have to cope with it.
The reason why we did that, of course, is the pod safe music network is really intended for two groups.
Initially, for podcasters and for artists who want to make their music available for podcasters to play.
So we're going to we presume that you have a podcast and you have details of that podcast when you register.
Otherwise, you're invited to do anything you want browse through the site as a listener, which means you can't download the songs, but you can listen to them right there streaming.
Just click the little play button next to any one of them.
Now, of course, another feature of the podcast library network means you'll have a single sign on one log on and it will log you into podcast alley.
For all, you know, if you really want to get down to the dirty in the backstage business of podcasting, that's the place to go.
Seamless log into the pod safe music network.
Oh, man, it's a double-senseo show.
And so all your details, of course, that's another step you won't have to take because, you know, obviously when you sign up, you're a podcaster.
We have all your information about your feed, et cetera, and the details of the show.
So you're automatically registered and in fact, it's a couple more extra widgets that will become available.
And it's just what this next comment is about.
Adam, this is Chris from the fallout at Disciple Zero.
That's z-e-r-o dot c-r-x dot com.
I've been working on some radio software, and we've got some pretty cool ideas.
We're planning on making a slightly stripped down version, basically pulling satellite keys and such.
Anyway, we're thinking about putting in a newsy interface to the PMN.
So it could automatically register plays and pull music, pre-cash, and that sort of thing.
So, so people didn't have to worry about that kind of stuff.
Question I had for you is, is there a way to pull RSS feeds of categories or searches,
since in an XML format, rather than scraping the web pages.
Thanks for your time, Adam, and don't bother checking out the file quite yet because we're still working on switching our web hosts and such.
So it can actually support that.
Thanks a lot again. Have a great show.
I love the idea, and we actually have set up a developer program, specifically for stuff like this.
And first of all, yes, the answer is yes.
The whole, everything is all based on XML.
So you'll be able to get RSS feeds of searches, of categories, of songs you've played.
We even have modules like that for the show sites automatically.
It'll, it'll, uh, throw up a list of, uh, of the song, the last songs that you played,
or the top songs and the positive music network.
So of course, whatever this tool is that you're making, which sounds really cool and secretive.
Uh, yeah, a go to a podshow, a developer dot podshow dot com Andrew Grummit, who, of course,
you probably know from juice or iPod or lemon.
He, uh, worked from day one, basically, on that project is now running the, uh,
the developer community at podshow.
And in addition to, uh, whatever your, your radio tool is or your recording tool,
you can also tie it directly into the pdn.
And so, um, you can post directly, uh, into the pdn from your application.
Same thing, api is available and nothing really new or fancy as far as I know.
It's all based on open standards.
I think actually for the pdn, we're using the, uh, the meta web log api.
So you'll be able to, to, to scrunch it in no problem.
Uh, I suggest you drop by a developer dot podshow dot com and, uh,
give Andrew a shout and, uh, and start the dialogue up there.
I'll be more than happy to hear from you.
And finally, uh, Bruce, I guess Bruce basically says the same thing, uh,
looking to, um, looking for RSS feed output of searches.
So for instance, uh, and, and by the way, I'm mentioning all this because I know that the guys and
gal's developing are not listening in.
So, um, Bruce's idea is, for example, genre would be hip hop upload would be,
you know, within the past seven days, download count would be less than five.
Uh, et cetera, et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
Um, and yeah, I think that would be, that would be an awesome, an awesome tool to add for,
uh, for podcasters at the Apothecate Music Network, you betcha.
Um, okay.
Oh, my goodness.
Where are we at now?
Okay.
Look at your iPod or look at your MP3 player or look at, you know, whatever it is that's playing,
you should now see, and if not, I want you to email, you should now see the time at
36.
35.
37.
Okay.
That means that the countdown timer is working.
And, oh my gosh.
Stephen Hawking is.
Hello.
Adam.
I wanted to commend you on your use of a biodiesel algorithm appeal.
Your efforts to help the environment with Trinity are much appreciated.
And, I'm sure that will help offset the four miles per gallon of your
bedding with your gas.
Guzzly, well-selling to Jaguar of shit bucks.
Excuse me.
Jaguar.
Anyway, keep up the good work.
Tailwinds.
Buddy.
Sensei.
Hello, Adam.
This is Pick from the Pickcast.
I am my podcaster originated from Hong Kong, but right now I'm staying in Canada from
my study.
During my Christmas vacation, I travel back to Hong Kong to visit the new Disneyland.
On the other hand, I also met with a group of podcaster in Hong Kong.
Pa from the CMM podcast.the idea that we should get the podcaster in Hong Kong to make a song.
So, we did it.
We transform on a podcast into Chinese version.
And we even make an MV on that.
So, if you are the listeners of Daily Sauce Cook, wish to take a look at the music video,
as well as listening to the song, you can check the alpha pause website, which is
CMM.HK.
Thank you very much, Adam.
See you.
Yeah, no problem.
You gotta listen to that.
It happened on a podcast in Chinese.
It's freaking awesome.
Absolutely.
Warning.
The following promo and welcome message from Soccer Girl Incorporated is definitely not
family-says.
Soccer Girl Incorporated.
You're one-stop shop girl.
You're podcasting.
Fuck me the snooze.
Yeah.
Near the highway by Eleanor's middle school, your protege has been through like 45 interviews.
Your stomach muscles are shredded completely.
Your candy corn candies are no longer appealing.
You hate all the same.
You need something crazy.
More crazy than will to be babies on acid.
More crazy than people who get long fake nails.
Though they're pretty crazy.
Those nails are dangerous.
Seriously, though, you should come listen to Soccer Girl Incorporated.
SoccerGirl.podshow.com, which is known official podshow podcast.
Just between you and me.
I don't think they know what they're getting themselves into.
If you're feeling down and you're running out of drugs.
Just come listen to my show.
And make you feel like you're on me.
My stomach muscles are completely shredded.
Yeah.
Soccer Girl Incorporated.
A proud member of the podshow podcast network.
There are a whole bunch of people who ran out of ban with the Soccer Girl was one of them.
Did her host go down?
I think that's what happened.
I don't know if she ever actually was able to get her files and her posts back.
Which really sucked.
But she's now assigned up with the network.
And we welcome her.
No, of course we know we got into Soccer Girl all kinds of crap with you.
And I love it.
I love it.
You know, I got you.
I got you, baby.
I got mad.
I got dawn.
I have such a harem of women.
I love it.
Of course, if that's not entirely your style.
You could also check out Heather and John L.
Accuview are underwriting the entire podcast at download.accuview.com.
They had an interesting guest on.
It's funny because I read a lot of crap in the forums.
I wonder if people have actually listened to the show.
Now, I didn't listen to the first two episodes.
I caught the third episode.
I have the first one.
Apparently they did a sound seeing tour of a contact lens shop.
Obviously, to satisfy the sponsor and boy, that got a lot of flag.
But I think they're learning.
And, you know, for all the yelling and shouting that's going on,
I think that we should be really happy about what Accuview actually
Johnson and Johnson is doing.
And listen to the episode number three.
There is only one mention of the sponsor.
I found a very appropriate time, very appropriate man.
But they actually had a pretty cool guest on.
They played some music from the podcast and music network.
But they're starting to come into their own three episodes.
Give them a chance.
And yes, absolutely.
I don't mind getting paid to talk about that.
Because it's worth it.
Check it out.
One last audio comment and one last positive music song for you today.
Yeah.
I don't even have a podcast.
Guess what?
I am going to jail because of podcasting.
That's right, Adam.
And what did I do to deserve this?
Well, it's not that I talked about politics or religion or anything like that.
Apparently, as it turns out,
you just can't say anything negative about anyone or anything.
For example, if a company produces a lousy product,
you can't say that.
Or if someone cheats you or does something wrong or illegal,
You just cannot say anything that's negative in any way whatsoever.
In my case, I mentioned in one of my recent episodes
that a one of the local media organizations has started podcasting.
But I said that they shouldn't call it a podcast because
what they do is they just take content from their existing media
and put it on an RSS feed and call that a podcast.
So, you know, I said, you can't call that a podcast, right?
So apparently, I can't say that because now they can sue me
for everything I'm worth and more.
As if that's not bad enough, it seems that podcasting itself is illegal here.
Any form of communication that can be heard by the public
must be regulated and licensed by the government.
And Adam, if you think you have problems with ASK at BMI,
thank whichever God you pray to that you're not in measure.
Because here, these people have the right to shoot you.
That's right.
A couple of months ago, a street pedal was shot in the chest
for selling pirated music and DVDs by the local trade enforcement officers.
So I just want to point out to you, Adam,
that I'm not being negative about anything.
I just want you and all the other podcasts in the US and the UK
to feel so much better tonight, knowing that you can say things like
f***ing use and sale without going to jail.
So thanks for everything, Adam.
And I hope you forgive me if I don't hear any more DSTs
because I don't think they're going to let me download podcasts from jail.
Thanks for listening.
Back to you, Adam.
So I don't know if that was real or spoof
the bleeps was self-centered.
And so I won't name the place where this audio comment
apparently came from, but it's a place where if you spit on the ground
or if you actually can't buy chewing gum there.
So most of you probably know what country I'm talking about.
I don't feel good, dude.
That makes me feel really bad, actually.
It's like it just boggles my mind that there's a government.
And actually in the country you're in,
I think in some ways a progressive government,
in some ways not obviously,
that there's a government that can actually create a law
saying when you talk to the public and at large
it has to be licensed by the government.
That's pretty scary stuff.
And you know what?
I think that could definitely spread.
I think that could go, that could spread across other
democracies, no problem.
So yeah, so I'm definitely counting my blessings
and thanking my lucky stars.
But I do not feel good at all that this is happening to you.
So if it is true, let me know.
And let me know if there's something that I can do.
One last song I was perusing through my playlist
on the Pod Save Music Network.
I'd added this one a long, long time ago.
I think I've actually played it before.
It's nice for kind of a great day outside of Curry Cottage
and Gilford.
The amphibians and rain came down.
But yeah, I want to stranger.
You're maybe selling your soul
to the devil with a dangerous face.
And don't give your soul to a stranger.
You call us the same as we're in the deal with the devil
and tell those names.
When it's falling down, it's falling down.
And let me know if there's something I can do.
It's falling down, it's falling down.
So yeah, so I'm definitely counting my blessings
Why sell your dust so cheap?
And revisions in every day, they're got a lot of dust in all this way.
To run, run, change your face so neatly.
I think it's on your heart.
I don't wanna say goodbye.
I was the one that went into my eyes.
When it's broken down, it's all in time.
It's all in your sight.
It's all in time, it's all in time.
Just like the sky.
When it's the sun.
When I look close, when the sky is falling.
I think it's on your heart.
When it's the sun.
It's the way you go away.
Why do you go away?
Don't give your heart too strange at all.
You're never sorry to me, to be honest, may it stay.
You'll never be as sure to me, tomorrow.
What's more than dan months going on.
It's all in time, we're going in prison.
It's all in time, it's all in time.
It's all in your sight, it's all in time.
I think it's on your heart.
You'll never listen to me.
When I look up to the sky, it's full of air
Where is the sun?
When I look up at the sky, it's full of air
And Fibience Rain came down from the podcast music network, music.potcho.com.
You know what?
Thank you all so much for listening.
Thanks for all the feedback on the audio, on the levels.
I'm running a little bit hotter today, running the sound a little bit hotter just to
see if that, if that coincides with everybody.
So you're not being blasted away by other stuff being played on your computer because
you can have to crank the volume up so loud.
I'm actually considering some day this week to do a complete reconfigure of the stereo
valve processor.
I think that that's really where a lot of these problems should be solved, certainly
in the home setup, so some mucking around is an order.
Hey, dailysourceco.com is where you can find the latest podcast and of course the podcast
feed.
Curried.com for general stuff and of course your feedback through adamaccurried.com.
I'll be here tomorrow for the Tuesday's edition of Delta.
Sierra Charlie.