Delta Sierra Charlie 3-5-4 Hello, welcome to my underground layer.
I brought you all my 12 deadliest allies here today to discuss my plan for taking over
the world.
Realizing that there are millions of computer users in the world, my plan is to create
software that everyone uses, but is frustrating at times to use.
In each year, I will rule out new versions, promising stability and satisfaction while integrating
software with other products that I create, therefore creating a monopoly for users
around the world that will have no choice but to give me money, time, and time again.
Yes, number two that Sierra has already happened, Bill Gates, the founder of Microsoft
has continually put out computer operating system that is at times frustrating, and Microsoft
has also been investigated for abusing their monopolistic powers.
All right then, plan B. As you know, millions of people all over the world have been purchasing
iPads and downloading music for their enjoyment.
I wish to make downloadable content freely available to these legions of podcast owners that
content will be so enchanting and entertaining that the drones will become my slave army
and do my bidding and I will take over the world.
What number two?
Surer that two has already happened.
Sometime during 2004, a man named Adam Curry and others created a medium called podcasting
that is very popular and lots of people listen to his podcast.
Craypes, why didn't anybody tell me this?
I need the info.
Don't be a boon here.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jar.
Adam Curry.
You never moved on without me.
Maybe one day we'll see things the same.
Feelin' sorry, I ever felt this way.
Feelin' sorry, no one else to play.
Yeah.
Time of my sight and a couple of dreams that no one understands for me.
Feelin' fine with me is sad for dreams and no one understands for me.
I've never saw it coming.
I expected it to be somehow.
Feelin' sorry, I ever said I can't.
Feelin' fine with me is sad for dreams and no one understands for me.
From Florida, Burman and no one understands good morning, everybody.
It is the daily source code coming to you from Northern California, from San Francisco here
in the Cori condo, I thought I'd share another beautiful San Francisco sunrise with you.
Not sure if we're gonna have one today, what is it time here?
It's 6.31 in the morning and once again, I've gotten my ass out of bed to share the
Podsafe tunes with you and all the crap that's going on.
Big day today at Pod Show HQ, our Board of Directors are coming up to our place this time
around for our Board of Directors meeting and let me ask you a question.
If you had invested close to $10 million in a company that creates Podcast, would you listen
to their shows?
Would you check them out?
I mean, even on your way to the Board of Directors meeting, do you think that it would be
a smart idea to just listen and see what one of the founders is doing on his Podcast?
Well, my friends were going to test that.
The special Board of Directors, word of the day, is frog.
So those guys better be coming in and better be going ribbit ribbit, no one I mean.
Let's see.
Oh, there is so much to talk about, but I also have a lot of stuff that I will metro section
a moment on today's show, I've been saving up some bits for that.
I was going to say, oh, yeah, yesterday we had a great meeting with British Telecom.
This was great.
I told you the Muckity Mucks Rawl in town and boy, were they all the British Telecom broadband,
the CEO, and the CTO, and the CIO, and the president of retail sales, and it was really,
they were in some kind of, I'd have to say, they were really in a working meeting and
we were invited to come over and talk.
And we did just that and we kind of walked into a room full of, you know, how it's almost
like one of those board rooms where they're working on some huge merger or takeover
everyone's in short sleeves and there's pizza boxes everywhere and it's kind of, it's
a little bit smelly as well, like kind of old socks smell.
Well, that was exactly the room we walked into, but there was a lot of energy, a lot of
smarts and a lot of good thinking going on there.
And they didn't sign us to any non-disclosure agreements or, you know, as we say, NDAs,
no damage announcements.
I'm just going to respect that we opened our kimono as a little bit to each other.
You know, we didn't, not completely, but just a bit.
And wow, they're doing something really interesting.
So I have very high hopes for for user-generate content in the United Kingdom, which
is really freaking convenient because I live there half my life.
Sometimes it seems like less than half my life, but wow, stuff to do.
So I would say that's very exciting news for the UK podcasters.
And I guess we're going to meet next, not next week, the week after next, when everyone's
back in the UK and continue the conversation.
So as I can, I will keep you up to speed as best as possible.
Okay, those of you new to the show, it could be that you're listening to this on serious
stars 102.
It could be that you're listening to this podcast for the very first time.
It could be that you're saying, huh?
Metro sexual moment, huh?
What is this guy talking about?
Hi, my name is Happy, and I live at bedtime stories my kids love.
Once upon a time Adam asked for some frequently asked questions to be covered for the ever
growing daily source code audience.
The whole point is he's saying that people who come into the daily source code who are
newbies probably don't understand a whole bunch of things you're talking about.
And even though I do try to reiterate very briefly before I start off on a rant or
a story, it seems that the the main things that are, you know, that need some explanation
or that we need an FAQ or a cheese would be great to have an audio FAQ, wouldn't it?
I got to think about that.
Well, newbies, let's start with the basics, the Charlie.
It all started when listeners started calling the Daily Source Code, the Charlie, which was
the shortened version of Delta Shira Charlie, which are the call letters for Adam Curry's
plane.
Start out as the Daily Source Code, then the DSC, then Delta Shira Charlie, and now the Charlie,
not the Chacha, or the Chuck, or a nickname for your never regions, just the Charlie.
This is Happy, and I'll see you later with more Charlie, frequently asked questions.
Oh, the go first, thank you very much, kids, I love it.
Okay, so now you know a little bit more about this show, and I'm sure we'll be receiving
more Daily Source Code frequently asked questions, and of course I'll be posting those
onto a special area of the show site in the show notes so that you can get to those quickly
if you're brand new to the show.
Lots of conversations going on about unleashing the pod show pdn, and along with that,
we kind of can't just release the podcaster side.
We kind of have to, the way it's all integrated, release the listener side at the same
time.
Really want to do that next week.
The only real gating factor here is the email tax barrier, so we can't actually sign
people up for registrations reliably until all that's in place.
Servers are being, we're putting yesterday, I think, tomorrow configuration starts.
People are going to be working through the weekend because there's just a whole bunch
of things that get put in at one go.
Actually, I think we're also looking for another person to help maintain that.
I'll have to get that from, from a Brian Longus, left to get that, and I'll pass it on
for you.
There's some very specific SMTP in the email skills that we're looking for on a continuing
basis.
Zach sends me an email here.
Adam, I was at the Flash Forward Conference in Seattle on the day of your court case.
It was a three day event.
The second day of the conference, the day before your case, Larry Lessig of Creative Commons,
gave a presentation on Creative Commons and the Read Right Internet.
I was hoping you would mention you as a current example of the license holding up in
courts, but it didn't seem like he knew it was going on.
I just finished listening to the Charlie and meant to ask afterwards, but he was swarmed
with others asking questions, so didn't get around to it.
We'll be awesome to get some sort of opinion from Larry himself on the outcome of your
case.
On the Creative Commons, Canada weblog, actually posted a link to that yesterday, they did have
an interesting rundown of, and I guess that they're now our translated documents because
it looked like they, or they had translated the documents and called it a win for Creative
Commons.
But here from Larry, I did send him an email on the day of the court case and he responded
to that, so he said that he was going to look at it and he said, you know, have you posted
about it, and I sent him all the links, still haven't heard from him, and I'm hoping
that I do, you know, I was just doing a Techno-Roddy scan, and you know, lots of people
are now picking up on the news and very happy that Creative Commons holds up, a little
disappointed about the value of the stuff we're creating here online, but so be it.
It's a start.
It's one of the ones, of course, to sing tailwinds because it's a student pile and so
that is it.
That's there's an FAQ for you to go first about the tailwinds.
I did all this preparation last night, and I guess last night, I was chuckling when I
had read the email from Devon Austin Dorf.
Adam, hope you're doing well, not too jet lag.
Today's Charlie waiting for me, having to listen to you, blah, blah, blah.
My wife just gave birth to our daughter on the 24th of February, so I've been a little busy
as you might imagine.
It's expected to do it for your 43rd birthday
from your old pal Caden and his new little Sis Kenzie.
You know what?
Hopefully you can do it for my 42nd
because otherwise we'll have to wait more than a year.
Making me older than I am, man.
I'm 41, 42 in September.
Okay, chord case, but okay, I wanted to add
to the list of things I know are getting filtered out
by the big email providers.
Gmail invites, do not make it to Yahoo email accounts.
I know this firsthand because it took me
asking three different friends to send me an invite
before I finally got one to work.
And that was only on my work email.
And now here's the need of his email.
As you know, I'm a huge fan of the Roger Smalls
jingle and now I've become a fan of this comments as well.
The whole Roger versus comic strip blogger thing
makes me nearly tear up every single time I hear it.
Have you determined where Roger does his recording?
It sounds like an aluminum or aluminium recycling center.
As for CSB's rambling, barely coherent rants,
I think Dawn said it best a few shows back on the Dawn
and Drew show.
He sounds like Count Chocula,
or as you mentioned people have been saying,
man, yeah, even Patricia thought that, but it's not.
And you'll listen to the MS Mobile's podcast.
This is exactly how he talks.
Seriously though, these two guys at a whole new dimension
of comedy to the Chuckle's Charlie Chip, Charlie, yeah.
Okay, I think right now, Roger has the edge
and the competition for the DSC comedy crown,
though particularly with his Uncle Jesse reference,
I would likely change my tune, however,
CSB mixes a Cooter reference.
Mixes into Cooter reference,
and I think just to Rihla Pink lug but Bitmore you
really should commission the Jeff Smith
to produce a theme song for the satellite repairman himself.
Oh boy, there's a lot of loaded stuff in there
is called comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comics strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic
Okay, time to reset your brain. Remember you have to kind of focus in on the accent. But once you get to it, man, there's gold in them words.
I had them carry. Because the point you have now in USA, fucking around you are. Well, USA is more
fun than Europe for sure. But I don't know whether you have noticed that Howard Stern is being
sold by less moon vests. The boss of CBS may be potential folks could help poor Howard Stern
because correct me if I am wrong. Many revenues of potential are coming from serious. And if
Howard Stern will be fucked up by the lawsuit, then serious gonna be fucked up too. Please,
Howard, you're...
Ah, it's the new sign off. Yo, thank you very much, Robert.
Clothing strip.
Comic strip.
Alright, is everybody ready?
Yeah, another spot where we could use an FAQ. This is the place where us guys hang out and talk
about things that we normally would talk about in public. And sometimes the women folk, the
shaylas check in as well. Here's an old friend of the show, Matt's not grass says, I don't
know, I was wondering if you could put the call out for no's hair advice. I'm a torn between
plucking and trimming. Trimming seems to be okay for short term, plucking last longer, but
hurts like a son of a bitch. Any thoughts? Yes, screw those closet cases who are distancing
the metro sexual moment. They sound like they're not secure in their own man who would
keep it up, man. Yeah, absolutely. Well, now this is a question that has not a reason yet,
but I have to agree that it's, you know, plucking versus trimming. Now I'm a guy that I like
to trim. I have one of those circuit, well, I have a couple of devices actually. I want
of those circular things that you're like sticking your nose and you turn it and it kind of rips
the hairs out, not a great feeling, but hey, that's where my dad used for, you know, all my life
growing up. So I guess that's why I'm kind of stuck looking at that. Then I've heard that plucking
those hairs actually can cause tremendous infection and it's not a good idea. And so what I've
been using recently is a little nose hair trim. It runs on one triple A battery. You know,
you just, you know, it has a little, a little, what do you call it? Like you find on the back of
electric razor, you know, and just the saw teeth that are moving back and forth really fast. What's
that called? And you just kind of stick it in there and twirl it around and it cuts everything off.
And that, that has really been something that works for me. But if you have other thoughts about
nose hair, please let me know. And particularly, I want to know if pulling them out or
squeezing or yanking if that is potentially dangerous. Yeah, and this is rust from the raising
giant spot cast and I want to give you some feedback for the Metro moment. So I've been inspired by
all the talk on the Charlie about the gelette fusion razor, the M3 power. And so I have
ditched my electric razor. I've been using since I was 16 years old and purchased the M3 power
and more recently the the fusion. I can tell you that I will never go back to the electric.
The regular razor, these my skin, much smoother and also, along with the razor, I purchased the
gelette complete skin care products and has made a huge difference in my skin. So just the
information and come by and check out my podcast at racingjiance.com. That's raising,
thanks Adam. All right, dude. No, thank you very much. It's interesting while you were talking.
Of course, I've heard you wrap before. I ran off to the bathroom here at the condo
because Patricia picked something up for me the other day, which I think it might be what you're
using. It's the Gillette fusion hydro cool after shave gel or as they say in French.
Gel après rassage. Cools the skin. Allow rich with hydrating
emolions. My goodness. I can just feel the emolions work and you know what I mean. I got plenty of
emolions. And I must say this is, you know, you always have to use some kind of after shave
balm before you actually get down to the moisturiser. So you should be using two products
apra rassage. What is it? Rassage. And this stuff is pretty cool. It's kind of like a gel.
It has an easy dispensary, you know, you just kind of squeeze it out and rub it on the skin and
it say it really has a nice cool minty feel to it. And it doesn't dry up all crackly and stuff.
So there's a bit of moisturizer in there. And I have to say, so far I'm liking that.
Before this I was using the Nivia after shave stuff. Oh my goodness.
Excuse me, terrible. Hey Adam, wanted to share two new products. I'm using. I heard someone
mention a sugar scrub on your show the other day. Bath and body works has some great products.
The sugar scrubs may be a bit rough on the face but they're really good facial scrubs that get
the same results. Here are the names and links to the products I'm using from Bath and Body Works.
For the body, a Roman therapy sugar scrub that relaxs Eucalyptus Spearment version.
And for the face, C.O. Piccolo, honey almond scrub. Where does that work again?
A molyent formula. Please, someone help me? Maybe the podictionary can take check in. Let me know
what emolient means. And oh, please tell me that there's a different pronunciation for
the U.S. than there is in the UK. Yeah, this is Eric Skip from the Bletchcast Colin in with a moment
for the Metro Sexual Moment. Metro Mo. Moment. Mo. Yeah, let's just call it the Mama. The Mama.
I'm going to Mo for the moment. So, like many guys, I am, let's say, blessed with an overbundance of
hair. Everywhere, but the top of my head. Certainly, if you've ever watched Greye for the straight guy
you'll learn about landscaping. And the process of kind of trimming that hair and bringing it
down to something manageable. Managed hair. Let's get started. I'm sick of shaving. I don't want
to get to your, have stubble places where I shouldn't have stubble. And if I just trim it,
then it comes back so fast and it doesn't really look that much better. So, I decided it was time
to go out on a lemon try. Nare for men. This isn't something I would normally purchase, but I was
desperate. I wanted something that was easy, that was quick, that didn't take all the time that
shaving took. So, I give them the shower with my new Nare for men with nice cucumber sand and
avoided it and smelled cucumber and good. And I applied it literally to the hair on my chest,
figuring that it would help take it down. And I went on my shoulders and as much as my back as I could.
And then started to wonder how the heck I was going to reach those parts of my back. I couldn't reach
anyway. So, I waited the requisite a few minutes and, something like the stuff wasn't smelling
so good. No longer cucumber-scented. It smelled a little bit more like wet cat. I had plenty of
time word away, so I stood there waiting waiting. And you know what, now the stuff smelled more like a
chemical burn. I started to feel itchy. I didn't really know if I was comfortable with that.
And slowly the itch turns to a slight burning sensation and it was certainly smelling
something fierce now. It was time to get this stuff off of me and I stepped on this shower and
started to rinse and scrub. Now, if you've ever witnessed this stuff in action,
it doesn't just go where you put it. Not only everywhere that it touched, but everywhere that
I hear that it had touched. Came this little nuclear blast of grossed rotting hair. It started on
my chest and then those hairs became all gummy nasty and stuck to my arm hairs which then
rotted off. Which, well, gotten the place that I'm not going to talk about on your podcast.
When all was said and done, I was left with a tiny naked patch on my chest and then kind of a
a weird leprosy-like, fearless bundle of patches everywhere else. Thank you, near for men.
Well, that's my story. I know it's a little long, but hopefully it'll help someone out or
someone can inform me on how you're supposed to actually use that stuff. As always, we're finding
great independent artists and getting them to go pot safe. So if you want to hear what's coming to the
PMN, check out the Glitchcast in iTunes or at GlitchNIC.com slash Glitchcast.
Well, you know what, I think that I've mentioned before that I am definitely a user of the
nair products and it just doesn't just have to be nair, but they all pretty much work the same way.
They burn your shit off, and I like to use it on the nether regions because that's just the way I
like it. But in general, the only way to do this is you apply it, wait no longer than eight minutes,
but probably no less, really no longer than eight minutes, and then hop in the shower and then you're
just going to wash it all the way. You've got to use a face cloth, get into every single place that
you wanted the hairs to disappear from, and then you'll be safe. Oh, and don't forget, after you do
the application to wash your hands, otherwise you're going to wind up with the bald hands,
another thing that just may not be desirable. Hey, people keep it coming to adamaccurry.com,
so that soon, next week we can check in once again and talk about our Metro stuff.
Speaking of Metro Sexuals, Mark Yoshimura Namcoff is coming up next on Sirius starts one or two
with Pacific Coast Hellway. And let us continue here on the Charlie, we have some new additions to
the Pod Show family. This is one of my girlfriends. Yes, just listen to this voice, man.
Drive your notes. The newest member of the Podcast delivery network is none other than me,
and GB, hostess of the brand new chill cast.
Sit back, relax, let me sue you and groove you with the silky smooth mix of independent music
that's just right for chillin. From downtown voter deep house, tripop to Dreampop,
electro lounge to old school jazz, you're sure to hear something that really sets a mood for
relaxation. So grab a bottle of wine and listen with a friend. Come check it out.
It's chillcastupodshow.com. And GB, you ladies and gentlemen, from the love spirals,
friend of the daily source code, now a Pod Show Podcast network member, the chill cast.
I cranked up episode four last night here in the condo. It was just great.
I can really get into the chill vibe, particularly when you have Angie B with their
solitary dulcet tones rambling through my MM50 speakers. Angie, good to have you aboard.
And more friends joining the network content. This is really going on.
Oh, Adam and daily source code listeners. This is Trucker Tom, proud to announce. I'm joining the
Pod Show family of Podcasts. When I was compelled to start podcasting back in December of 2004,
I had no idea where it would lead. I only knew it was something I had to do. From the
best in Podsafe music, interviews, soundsign tours, the discussion of human behavior,
along with occasional video podcasts. I try to keep every daily episode fun and upbeat.
With something of substance for every listener to look forward to, all mixed in with heavy doses
of Trucker Tom, philosophy. It's safe to say I deliver content that isn't available anywhere else
in the world of Podcasts. Check me out at truckerphoto.com and now also podshow.com.
Trucker Tom, I've never actually seen his rig. Trucker Tom, here's a guy. Here's a guy
who needs to be sending in some more stuff for the Metrosexual moment. A guy who was on the road
continuously is very involved with his skin and I can say that quite safely because he has tattoos
on many, many, many parts of his body, including basically like a shaved heads on the back of his head.
It's basically has another face tattoo a skull on top of his skull and he's just a sweetheart. He's a
great guy. I missed him last time. He was at the podshow HQ, so hopefully we'll hook up soon again
really soon. But Trucker Tom, if you're out there listening, you're the guy that's on the road.
As a part of the backbone of the United States, which really is true. I mean, geez, we could not
do without Truckers. The economy would die within an instant. Trucker Tom out there on the road.
How do you take care of yourself, man? What's the life like? Well, of course, if you really want
to know what the life is like, then you just need to listen to Trucker Tom's podcast, but maybe
you could send something for the Metrosexual moment. It's going to be a short show today. As I said,
getting ready to pop off to the Board of Directors meeting, Wayne checks in, Wayne Thoom Adam. I don't
know if you remember, but a while back someone asked you to help explain to people that podcasting
is something that doesn't require an iPod or special equipment to enjoy. You explain this and told us
that we could extract out your explanation and burn it to a CD with a podcast to help introduce
people to podcasting. Yeah, I should actually, we'll make that another part of the audio,
frequently asked questions. I'll pull that bit out again, because someone, I forgot who did it,
but it wrote a nice piece. I read it on the source code and it turns out that lots of people,
including Wayne, have actually done that. They've cut that piece out, edited into in front of
one of their favorite podcasts and have a URL handy where to send someone to go learn more about
podcasting. Wayne says, I'm a programmer and was with the CEO of my company trying to explain
to another CEO, what podcasting was, I got blank looks all round until I pulled out a CD with your
explanation and played it. The first crump comment I heard as they were listening to you was,
hey, he's got a good voice. I can just imagine it, your boss is sitting there and like,
oh, he's got a good voice. After hearing you and some more explaining for me, I ended up
making a good impression. Thank you so much for saving my job. The following audio comment is
without a doubt, not family safe. It is not something that you may want to listen to. If you're
easily offended, though you really shouldn't be. Mads Weinstein ranted at me last week and
yes, it's some really nasty things and just was not showing much love. Luckily, we've got more
people listening to this show. Then they do love me. Hi Adam, this is Rebecca from Tranny Recradial,
responding to Madge calling you a Tranny Fucker. First of all, I want to say that if you were a
Tranny Fucker, I would be the first in line. Second of all, if Madge was calling Tranny,
I would like to believe, and matter of fact I know, the transgender community would be honored to have
her in our ranks. Third of all, I have to inform you and your listeners that Madge has already agreed
to some hot Lesbow action after I get my surgery. So that would make her a Tranny Fucker.
For the rest of you that want to join those ranks, visit my website, Trannyrec.com.
I'll bet if you thank you so much, I feel so much better now and I'm sure for sure she would take
that as a huge compliment. I have been be down, my heart left for broken, but I still feel the light
and the sunshine is due. I have swallowed my pride, but my heart has salvation,
there will always be shelter when the storm rolls in, and there's light,
there will be hope to rise on my feet again, and with this hope I'll find the strength
to rise on my feet again.
The highway that here begins in the valley of a thousand trees that I never realized.
Strength is my soul, silence is mercy for the stream of control,
hallelujah I cry, and where there's a light that will be home to rise on my feet again.
And with this hope I'll find the strength to rise on my feet again.
It's so bright, it's so bright, it's so bright, it's so bright, it's so bright, it's so bright, it's so bright,
it's so bright, it's so bright, it's so bright, it's so bright, it's so bright, it's so bright,
there will be hope to rise on my feet again, and with this hope I'll find the strength to rise on my feet again.
From Colorado, Graham English, on my feet again winding up Charlie for Thursday.
Tomorrow, thank God, it's Friday, addition tomorrow is going to be a really busy day,
going to do a Gilmore Daily with Steve Gilmore, oh I'm sorry, now that's next week, oops, that was wrong.
What we're doing to tomorrow is Cali, that's right, Cali Lewis from Geek Brief TV is up in San Francisco,
and we're going to do something together. Cali was voted one of the top 10 sexiest geek chicks I saw.
So what do I see that yesterday? It was going around the office, she is so incredibly cute,
and then I was listening to her on podcast four on one, as I was drifting off to sleep, which of course
what better way to do that and with Cali's voice in your ear. Very interesting, interesting history
about what how she got into podcasting her first site was, I believe, crappy Christians,
or the first podcast with crappy Christians, which I have to go back and listen to now.
But they start off listening to Don and Drew, when I say they, it's Cali and her husband,
which of course is the only bummer thing about Cali, is that she's married.
So I guess I'm going to be on the show, I don't know what we're going to do, but I have some
questions for her. All right, everybody. So I'm off quick, triple S, we know what the triple S is,
don't we guys? And then I'm off to the office, and tomorrow I will report back, see if our board of
directors walked into the conference room, going ribbit ribbit. And I thank you all very much for
listening to the show, check out dailysourcecode.com, we can find all the latest episodes,
and of course the podcast feed. And for any feedback, any ideas you got fired off to adamatcurry.com,
I love the audio comments, okay? I'll see you tomorrow, bye, bye, bye.
Another pod show podcast, stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the Hyperformance podcast of
LibreNetwork from Podjo, and Lime White Networks.
I love it.