Hey, this is John Miselle.
And this is Drew Domkiss.
From the Don and Drew Show,
check out ShadowFalls.Podshow.com
It's so spooky you might pee your pants!
This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
There you have the very secret episode of The Doubt Time.
There you have it.
K Strong
Cathettes
Point the player
Ted Da Nidel in a player
Learn to play
Feel the same, I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help
I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help only but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but all I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but stop but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can't help but I can
I don't want you to see, I don't want you to see
So let me
Rusted smile, poison yes
Hit the fever in the face
Lift the light, love to hate
I can't go play
Why don't you see, I don't want you to see
It's only me, I can't
It's only me
Rusted smile, poison yes
Hit the fever in the face
Lift the light, love to hate
I can't go play
I don't want you to see
When you hold that day
From New York City, Blake Morgan
Why don't you see from the pod save music network
I told Patricia, hi baby
Listen to who's singing along and tell me if you can guess who it is
Brian Adams
Oh no
We wish
Michael Butler
Almost as good as Michael Butler
Lenny Kravitz
That's why
Brian Adams doesn't sound like the Beatles
No, but the voice
You hear him in the background
He's on the chorus
He might play guitar
I love those drum fills
That was so functional
Yeah, very functional
It's not too much
Not too much
This is a good moment to do a little drum fill
Not less than too much, you know
Very good
Baby, how are you doing?
Yeah, doing fine
Last time when we spoke
I mean, you're not fulfilling your contract at all on the show
But last time we spoke
I'm not feeling my contract
No, you can't appear
I didn't sign anything
Oh no
No, not yet
No
I make you sign so much stuff
Just sign here, baby
Don't even think about it
It's important, just sign
Just sign
You don't need your glasses right now
First of all, we know everything's in your name
Actually
Tonight we're having cocktails
And dinner
With our banker
And two over colleagues in London
So I'm going to be the guy sitting with four babes
Yeah, which is nice.
Rainy, babe.
Yeah, but she actually she called me and she said two things.
She said, is it okay if I wear blue jeans?
Because I really, I'm so happy if I'm not wearing the banker suit.
Oh, she wants to look sexy.
Yes.
For you.
And she said, and I have some paperwork.
So, do you mind if, you know, you just tell me when it's okay to pull out the paperwork?
Yeah.
I don't worry about it.
So, no, but last time we spoke, we had, you know,
a terrorist threat and your sister was here.
Yeah.
So, took a long, long time to get to Rotterdam, right?
She left, yes.
Oh, Amsterdam actually, and then Rotterdam.
Yeah.
Let's see.
She left the house at 3 o'clock.
What time was she home?
10, 30, 11 o'clock?
Yeah, just about 10, 30.
She's like eight hours to get home.
I could have flown her back and forth twice.
I know.
And stopped off for fishing chips.
Yeah.
And gotten you some flowers from the gas station.
I could have done all of that.
My sister is a little bit afraid of these sort of things.
Flying and, you know.
It only hurts her, sir.
I always had to protect her for everything.
Well, this is why she's such a pussy, because she always protected her.
I know.
No one had to do it.
Did anyone ever push her and say, go do it?
Well, they were afraid to do that.
Would mean they would?
No.
No, but yeah.
I mean, didn't want like you push her.
Well, we tried.
I don't know what she's afraid of.
To die.
Death.
Yeah.
I got to tell you the older I get, the less afraid I am of death.
I really.
Is that so?
Yeah.
And quite honest.
I always think, you know, I came so far.
What should I do this?
Nothing happened until now.
You know?
Oh, but I look at it exactly the other way.
I said, look at all the things have done so far.
Yeah.
So if I do this one more thing and something happens.
It doesn't matter.
Oh, I think I have to.
Look at you.
You're so young.
Let me tell you.
Oh, oh.
I just got an email.
This is horrible news.
It's about death.
Sophia.
Oh, Sophia best away.
Yeah.
It's Ron and Marta's little Yorkie.
Oh.
She was in hospital for about a, what?
More than a week.
We can have almost two weeks.
So no, no, operation.
I think I didn't get the details.
Ron just sent an email.
I think she, I think she had the operation.
She had a collapsed trachea.
Something like that.
And these dogs are so small.
So that's what I wanted to explain.
It's a, it's a York's Yorkshire Terrier.
And if it's really a small size dog or animal or little cats doesn't matter, baby cats.
I always hear the same thing.
If there's something wrong that gets sick, it's hard to help.
Of course it is.
It's so tiny.
It's so small.
You know.
Yeah.
And they have a breeding thing.
It's, it's very hard.
Yeah.
Well, then, and when they get nervous, then it gets desperate.
Yes.
Exhaust rates.
Exhaust, it makes things harder.
Yes.
Yeah.
Oh.
We're seeing a year ago.
Ron's dad passed away.
Yeah.
Jesse passed away.
My mom passed away.
So fee passed away.
Yeah.
Other people around us.
How many people have we not seen pass away in the past two years?
Maybe 10.
Do you think people who we know?
I mean, not necessarily friends, but yesterday, could I not know?
Yeah.
Another area.
Well, it's radio.
It's radio.
It's radio legend.
Let's not know why.
Yeah.
Wasn't the on the pirate ships as well?
Wasn't he certainly as well?
But I know they just back to that.
I did the last radio program with him.
Really?
Yeah.
He's last radio program or the last one.
The last radio program.
You know, doing music, talking about music and something with the stars.
It was the last time the stars.
I actually performed in his radio show.
Right.
And that was the last time we said goodbye.
So, you know, I just like, I hate that.
It's like all these people dying.
Yeah.
That's what my mom and dad say.
Well, they're 80.
So, yeah.
Yeah.
They're burying all their friends.
All their friends.
It scares the hell out of my mom.
And that's why your mom was like, fuck.
And I'm getting an Adam's plane.
Oh, we're calling him donuts.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
She's bending.
She's going out every day.
Yeah.
She takes my dad and said, come on.
Let's go out.
You know, really?
We think about that.
That is really so cool.
If you can spend all your money right up until your death.
And then just go.
Yeah.
Well, that's what I say.
Your kids don't worry.
Don't worry about your money.
Just spend it.
Exactly.
I mean, don't need it.
We don't want it.
I don't think your kids need it anyway.
No.
It's yours.
They should spend it.
You went for it.
I mean, I'm definitely not thinking like, oh, you know, I want to make sure my daughter said,
I want to make sure my daughter knows what to do in life.
It can take care of herself and doesn't have to rely on there.
Well, I think the only kids get their money right away from the parents go actually wrong
first.
Possibly.
You have to work.
You have to appreciate it.
You have to do something for it.
You're much happier.
You do something.
And you work.
Yeah.
All those kids in Hollywood.
You hear it from the start.
They give a money here.
Go.
I mean, you can't come.
I mean, let's just take the star equation out of it.
I mean, that kid to grow up with show business parents is different.
That's different.
It's different altogether.
And quite honestly, most kid to grow up with show business parents have no money.
Because most people show business don't really actually have money.
It's they have the fame which you think they have money, but it's not really rich.
Let's say rich then.
Not the famous.
It's just rich people.
Rich people.
Yeah.
It's not good.
You have to teach your children to teach your children well.
To actually work for it.
I think it's so much happier.
Let's move off of death for a second.
Interesting.
I just had my yogurt with so many tricks and branches.
I put so many seats in it.
I probably have a flower garden in my stomach by now.
You know, there's so many things that I could have said just now.
A flower garden.
No, you would seeds in your yogurt.
There's so many seeds in there.
Because they say so good for you, but I think.
Well, don't eat that shit, man.
That's what horses eat that stuff, you eat.
That's not real food.
That's good for me.
I hope.
Listen to this.
Hey Adam.
This is Lindsay Curve from the Great Board of City of Carlisle.
Carlisle, by the way, is located about nine miles from Scotland.
We are inish.
All I want to do people with disagree.
Hey, the youth.
But yeah, I gave you a telephone comment.
A couple of weeks ago about the fact that I was going to be a daddy.
And the very fact that we conceived our first child to the sound of you and Patricia.
Now, when you heard that comment, you wanted to know some more details.
Yeah.
Well, I'm not going to go into full details, but put it this way.
It was playing in the background as the lights were low.
The candle flickered.
And we made sweet love to the sound of the daily source coming.
So in honor of that fantastic moment, and when the child is born,
it will be forever known as D.S.C.
Sure, three hundred and seventy.
I thank you.
Oh, by the way.
Yes.
Fold it.
I thought he was going to say, if it's a boy, we'll call an Adam.
Yeah.
If it's a girl, we'll call him Patricia.
But no, we'll call him D.S.C.
It's one of the most popular names Patricia I heard.
Yes, they still.
That's funny.
I saw somewhere there was a chart, and you could, and you can look at names.
And it was basically, for the last, I think, last hundred years.
You could look at the popularity of the names.
And Patricia actually was still there.
But you can see the peak was around 40, between 40 and 45.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And Adam was around 1970.
You know, I was born in 64.
And before Christ.
Yeah.
It was very popular back before Christ.
It was the, it was the name.
It was still a beautiful name.
Beautiful.
I hated so much when I grew up.
You still hate him?
No, no, I like it very much.
No.
Yeah.
No, it's very sexy.
Adam.
Here it is.
It's very beautiful.
Adam.
The English state.
Oh, please, Adam, eat it.
Adam.
What?
What did you say?
No, I'm not confusing.
My goodness.
It just came out.
It's goodness.
Congratulations to.
I was thinking about.
I'm tired.
I'm not going to say it.
Oh, is there no?
Immigian.
Oh.
That's why I heard a lot of you living in the UK who have watched Big Brother,
which is ending tomorrow night and of course we're big fans of the show.
And we've watched it pretty much really justly.
It's all was hated it.
But this time.
Yeah.
Imagine who was this beautiful Welsh girls.
She was a former Miss Wales.
gorgeous.
She was voted out last week.
And so nice.
Very proper.
So I received an email yesterday with a link to a sex tape that had image in on it.
And it's like a parasitalton like sex tape and it's really her and she's really getting it.
Yeah.
And you recognize her way of talking.
She even says, oh, baby.
Oh, baby.
No, baby.
Oh, Adam.
Oh, baby.
Yes, he does.
So I'll definitely put a link to that in the show notes.
You've, I mean, I think we're the first ones who know it.
I mean, wouldn't the English papers be all over that if they knew that?
I don't know if it's maybe in the paper this morning because that's possible.
Yeah, I haven't gotten a paper yet.
I don't think so.
I think this is this is still pretty underground.
But this is when this gets out.
I mean, yeah.
And it's, it just goes to show.
Well, actually, it doesn't do anything because look at Pamela and this and look at
I will never look at Pamela Anderson the same way.
Yeah, or Tommy Lee for that, man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She looks so sweet.
I want to make it.
I once watched that whole tape.
It was, it's an hour long.
That video.
Yeah, Pam and Tommy.
And it's really boring because it's them on.
It's basically a vacation.
Why are you watching it whole hour?
It was on a hotel, uh, spank division.
Wanker vision.
Wanker.
And I'm like, oh, watch that.
He, hun, Tommy Lee, the fucking horse.
Like the guy in images video.
Excuse me.
Did you see that thing?
No, everybody will go and watch.
Just give me your professional opinion.
Uh-huh.
It looked nice.
Yeah.
No, it looks huge.
Yeah, it was big.
Yeah.
I don't know if everybody likes that.
Like what?
Too big.
No.
No, no, no.
I can't speak for that.
Just a regular nice, normal one.
Nice, nice knob.
Nice, nice, nice knob.
We'll do generic knobs.
We'll do.
Okay.
Congratulations to Don and Drew.
Second year in in a row.
They won the best, uh, they won the podcast award.
Uh-huh.
For was it comedy, I think?
No, uh, mature.
mature.
Not comedy with you.
Not mature.
Yeah.
mature comedy.
Uh-huh.
Well, they're not all about comedy.
They mature.
But so they want for the second year in a row.
Lovely.
And C.C. Chapman with accident hash for best podcast music show.
So, uh, very happy about that.
Yeah.
I didn't even get nominated, huh?
No?
No.
Absolutely not.
But um, I mean, that's a surprise.
Are you in the competition?
No, I tell you.
I mean, I mean, I'm the anti-Christ people like me.
No, you're not in the competition, I think.
No, I mean, I'm not.
I did not get nominated, so I couldn't win.
No.
That's why I'm not listening.
You always blame me not listening.
What, now, what are you saying?
What are you saying?
You're saying you don't listen because it sucks,
or because I'm not nominated.
What are you saying?
Well, please.
Well, no.
Uh-huh.
No.
Okay.
It's not because the don't want to listen because I have no time.
But, uh-huh.
And I'm not, you know,
I'm not into listening to the, uh-huh.
That's okay.
It's okay.
But what does that have to do with the not being nominated?
It's teasing you.
Uh-huh.
Make my ass sweat.
Don't do those things.
Do not like that.
Well, you can be very serious though.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Um, oh, this is funny.
You know that video show I did, the, um,
perversion for profit.
The one that, uh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now, what did you think of that?
Just honest opinion.
I, I loved it.
Yeah.
And the podcast or news website.
Mm-hmm.
And they say, uh, well, Adam is now, uh, uh, uh,
testing out video.
But it's amazing.
How crappy it looks for all the millions of dollars they received in, uh,
in venture capital financing.
Oh.
The fuck is that?
It's supposed to be like we're doing stuff ourselves and doing it.
Yeah.
The way we want to do it.
How simple it is.
Hell, is that all?
The podcast or news website?
Yeah.
Exactly.
And it's, didn't say, test.
Of course, well demo it's demo demo and I said it's a test. I'm just testing it out. I thought it was so funny.
Oh, thank you. I like that. It was so funny. I was there and I didn't see what you were looking at and I didn't tell me at all.
I didn't tell you that you were just quietly filming everything. Yeah, I had a lot of fun. I don't mind criticism in fact it kind of gets me going but then for
I do mind. Well, of course, but it energizes me, but when it comes from, yeah, it's good when it comes from us from the podcast and community
Yeah, and they say that it looks shit because you should have spent millions of dollars on it like what the fuck are these guys talking about that's exactly what we're not doing
Then it's just they can watch television and I don't know. That would be easy. It would be easy to spend money and make some. Well, you know one thing they didn't get it
Well, no, they didn't. Here's something we are spending money on the high. This is Brian. No. Join us in studio C for a chat with the most dangerous mind in podcasting
The creative genius behind pod shows incredible new dramatic series Shadow Falls. Marky Yosimoto Namcoff
Mark tells us how the idea for the show came about talks about the creative process and production and sends the praises of a man called
Join us with this unique peek behind the curtain of pod show LA's runaway hit. You'll find us at studioC. podshow.com
I've I have the third episode in love his voice. This is Brian. No, yeah, you know who he is right from the Frank truth. Yeah, he's got an incredible voice
Yeah, don't give many ideas
So Shadow Falls Monday episode three comes out of Shadow Falls and it's this is a real kicker
Yeah, this is really going to be good for those you listening to us on series of stars 102 Pacific Coast Hellway is coming up in about two minutes after that the award winning Dawn and Drew
Followed by soccer girl incorporated digital flotsom with the weekly the weekly flotsom emo girl talk with Martina Butler after that it's a 30 nine o'clock match Weinstein with East radio and we winded up with I think it's
I don't know which episode is of infection Scott Siggler, which is another fine well, what do you call potty potty Oh book. Oh, yeah, oh, that's a nice word potty Oh book. Yeah, that's actually a website and we're I think we're doing
So Scott really he's a writer so he wrote a book and then he he created an audio version of the book of two books actually now and so he released one at potty
Oh things potty oh books calm off to look at look it up. So now we actually work together with them to re-release it and just and then that's what's great about these things is you can just you know people just keep coming fresh people
It's not timely, you know, you can you can listen to it anytime. So that's good. Yeah, it's good. We got some good shit going on. Yeah
I'm so tired. Yeah, I know. So tired. Well, you know, we haven't actually stopped for anything. We haven't. I haven't. Yeah, after a mom passed
We launched a site a ran back to San Francisco for not just two weeks three weeks came back running around and then of course. So we thought we took you for a tour. That was nice Sunday just a little bit, you know, relaxing
Are you mean to captain core captain core. I had a great time. Yeah, I had a fantastic time. That's just, you know, it's just a nice
Relaxing afternoon. Yeah, it was nice looking at the beautiful gardens. Yeah, well, we didn't actually walk around in the garden that much because it was pissing rain. Yeah
So and I went to
To see the Queen's dresses. Oh, it
Since she was a tower major and beautiful. It's beautiful and the palace. Let me just say goodbye to the serious listeners because they're going to be listening to Marca in about two minutes by
The palace is unbelievable and you know what I was walking the dog. This is Buckingham Palace. No, it's not it's a buck. Yeah, that these are this is Buckingham Palace
Isn't it the one in the city? Yeah, Buckingham Palace. Buckingham Palace. Yeah, I don't know that she has a couple of passes. I don't know
The big one are Queen. It's just I think one she doesn't even look like a bungalow. Yeah
Excuse me, that would be your queen. Yeah, my queen lives in the right house. Yeah, I think White House. That's my queen. Oh,
He's such a nice. He's a mine. So yeah, so I was walking the dog and I was talking to a lady who had also sort of a terrier, you know, you always talk about it on the dance
Yeah, and
So I haven't seen you for a while. Have you done that? Oh, I looked, you know, I went to London with my sister and we went in the palace and it was so did you know this woman?
You just well, you know just from high passing with dogs and now that's the dog. You know that's dogging is what they call that here
She's probably looking for sex. She's the elderly lady and it's nice to talk to all the people. She was definitely looking for sex
She's walking a little bit
Difficult, you know, so yeah, she just had sex could be me, you know, if it's it now
God and I said and you know, you know how I think it's a privilege this this to live in this country
I so adore it. So I was very nice
I was so impressed about you know the palace and there's beautiful things and there's beautiful furniture and the crowns and the jewelry
And she got angry and she said yeah, and I hate it really. Yeah. Oh, don't need it
It's ridiculous the stuff that they have really
Yeah, but they found that forever. That's that's their family property. Oh, she's against the royal family
Really. Oh, you don't I don't think you find many of those
Especially she was you know an elderly lady. You think she's proud lady very English
I kind of what makes her own person
What did she want it what does she like then? Well now she just hated you know the thoughts that the thought that they are so filthy rich
They have such a beautiful beautiful
Jewel recollection gold silver
I mean furniture have no idea is and she said they have it stacked away even more
Yeah, but more isn't isn't that up to them who cares for these are also present because if you read it
It says a present from this queen and a present from that. Yeah, sure. I don't understand I don't understand
Look at us. I mean look at my stuff
Yeah, yeah, I mean you've got a car as well. It's all paid for it. Got it from everywhere
But I don't understand that at all. I don't understand who cares. It's not like they're any happier because of all the shit
They've had a lot of problem in that family. I mean and they got thousands of thousands of people
People walking through you their garden. Exactly. Thank you exactly. They need the money
They need the entrance fees. Yeah, they do. It's a good point. It's a lot of money. It's not cheap. What is it cost?
That's for $2,000 50 pounds, $50,000 50 pounds, $50,000 per person, $2,000 to be old. No, I can't be happy
I think $25 per person, but it depends on what you want to see if you go further and you look for garden
Look at the rest of the house. For 50 pounds, I want to build a tug on Charles's ears
Because there was also you know only the dresses or you go on and go. Really?
It's all a cart menu. Yeah, very strict everywhere security cost a lot of money. The whole thing
And also to buff it up to keep it nice keep it clean. Yeah, I think you know there's some taxpayer money that goes to that
And some of the stuff that you see is from 1600s and very dusty and I love that. I love that dusty stuff
No, not the dust stuff. You know that it's so old you can just can't believe it
Yeah, so that was interesting. Okay. I always do these things with my sister and sometimes with you
But I like that. I like to see I like to go to museums and you sort of things
I have to see so much more actually from England
Well, this is what my plan was is for us to go fly around a little bit and see some things
But the weather well, I really haven't had the time in the weather. She don't have the time
Well, I will. I hope this Saturday. I'll get to do my my touch and go landing practice
I just want to you know spend a day doing that and then I'll be completely confident to take you anywhere
Don't want to go on the touching go
No, you do not want to do touching goes with me
It makes you so nauseous come down go and I'll go
Yeah, so I was in London Tuesday
Yeah, day before yesterday
With Neil Dixon who's at Potcho UK and that a whole bunch of people
Creative people who are going to hopefully will be working with and one guy
I'd actually played his song off the pot safe music network
Probably maybe only a week before and he came by and his name is Jimmy Golding
Have you heard of him?
No, no. Anyway, he recorded something for us
Hi, this is Jimmy Golding. I'm going to sing a song for Adam Curry and Lady Patricia
It's cool not a day goes by. It's a love song and I hope you like it
Not a day goes by when I don't think of you
There's something about you
Knock a bell, that's ringing
You really got to me I can feel my heart unwind
Got a smile running through me
And I can't get you out of my mind
Not a day goes by
We don't think of you
Without you, I'm blue
I miss you
Not a day goes by
When you don't feel my heart
We've been too long apart
I miss you
I wake up in the morning
You're singing in my head
I'm thinking about you
When I'm lying in my bed
I can't wait to see you
And it's just a matter of time
I got a smile running through me
And I can't get you out of my mind
Got a smile running through me
And I can't wait to see you
I'm thinking about you
Without you I'm blue
I miss you
And I can't wait to see you
I'm thinking about you
When you don't feel my heart
We've been too long apart
I miss you
I'm doing it to do it to do it to do it
I'm doing it to do it to do it
Now to take a spin
I can't stop thinking about you
That's so sweet
He's very, very hip
I was thinking
While I was listening about waking up with a smile on my face
This morning I woke up with a smile
And I looked at you
And you looked worried
You weren't awake yet
I saw a sort of a worried look
Well I got lots to worry about
That's what men do
I got lots to worry about
You can wake up with a smile anyway
It's not worry
It's responsibility
But all kinds of stuff we've got to do and things we have to take care of
You have so much on your list
And we have like 65 people in our company
I feel responsible for them too
That's just a lot of stuff
But I'm happy
Yeah, I'm very happy
Just not when you wake up
I wasn't awake, I was asleep
That's not fair
We were awake and then you were still a little bit in waking up
Let's replay the event
Shall we?
You woke up with a smile on your face
And because you wake up
Because I look at you and I think it's so wonderful to wake up next to you
Thank you
So I of course subconsciously know that
That you're awake so I start to wake up
And what is the first thing you said to me?
It's a beautiful day
I know that would not be the first thing you said
Do you remember the first thing you said?
I was sitting on
On the bed
Three play the movie in your mind
Oh, I've been up since eight o'clock trying to wake up
Because I was thinking
About the car
We have to take the garbage out
Was the way I heard it?
No, not like that
No, I was asleep
I don't like that
I was asleep, but that's so when I'm kind of waking up
It's like, yeah, I have to get up to the garbage
But you know, why?
It was a whole time before that
And I was just waking up looking at you
Thinking of the stuff and then I thought
What day is it today?
It's garbage today
You really should not go walking outside in your nighty like that
Because if it's not some Dutch asshole
Photographer who's going to take a picture of you
It's going to be Roger Smalls who's going to jump out of the bush
Go and help Patricia
I always look at them
I always hope the neighbors out
Because he has such lovely legs
Mr. James
Really?
Yes, gorgeous legs
More gorgeous than mine
Yes
So I say, good morning neighbor
Love your legs
Love
You know what? English people
Don't get that
You know, don't get that
You don't quite get that humor
You got gorgeous legs
And he looks at me
Doesn't know what to do with it
You know what we were talking about
We had no video evidence yet of the so-called terrorist
Who were
You know, that caused this entire scare
And I said, well, you know
I basically said, well, you know, maybe it's an illusion
Kind of like the fact that we never landed on the moon
Yeah, yeah
I still believe we didn't landed on the moon
I don't think he said that
I'm sure we could not
Don't start anything, please
But listen to this
I don't know, just as it's for 40
When you're off on a bit as a tangent to when you mentioned to it
You say that you don't believe that we ever walked on a moon
Now what I find interesting is
NASA has recently lost the original footage of that event
Okay, has it lost a bit of film
One was called it over coronation stream
Tell how about that
Is that true?
Well, I don't know, I mean, I'm going to presume it's true
I haven't actually found any new stories about it
But how interesting is that NASA can be
Well, that is a nice view
I'm lost the footage
I have even tapes of me in 1976
Well, they didn't have zoom lenses
They had the switch of the lens
I'm turning around
1966 and 67
And I don't have anything from that
Well, I mean, of course, but they're talking about the original footage
You don't have the original footage
It doesn't matter to me, it's fine if we didn't walk on the moon
Well, there are more people saying that
I'm only 400,000 miles away
From my own seat on Richard Branson's spaceship one
Oh, get out of here
Shut all
I think we only need like 18 more months of traveling back and forth
Between here in San Francisco and I can fly on the spaceship
Really?
Wow, I'll go obviously
How cool would that be?
I don't want to do that
But I want to sit on his shoulders
That's the only thing he can carry me
I like him
Richard Branson
So it's Richard Branson, it's Jimmy, I look worried
Maybe you should be shopping around, maybe
Looking for some other guy
You know, I love you
You know that, that's why I can say these things
This is true
Nothing will happen
Only one at a time
At a bed
Oh, man
I will never look at image in the same way
Do you enjoy imaging?
Looking at that, looking at
Pamela Anderson in your hotel room, do you hear me about that?
No
But that's completely different
It's different
Of course
I have no problem
She means it
Can't trust any bitches
You guys think else babe, we should wrap up
No
I am a softie
I just heard that
To softie
Well, the way I treat my daughter Christina
Oh, you want to bring that up?
No, well, don't bring it up, but I didn't say anything
No, no, no, no
I'm a softie, I know
I just, because I always hear that teenagers
You don't listen to me, you don't treat me like, you know, an adult
You treat me like a child
And I try to treat her like somebody who's intelligent
That's right, you know, it's exactly what I heard
I was standing up here, I'm listening to the conversation
You're bickering and yelling, I'm like, wow, that just sounds just like the way you talk to me
Like adults talk
It does not work, she's 15
She thinks she's going to be 16
Because if she, if I talk to her with the don't, I want you to be hated
No, I'm going to, I said yes, I want you to be home
First, you would you didn't hear that?
That was the start
I just said, I want you to be at home
You know, like we spoke, we talked about that yesterday
You know, you know, no, no, no
Because I have to be at the physical therapist at that
So I'm going to be in the city, I'm going to be staying at that
No, I said no, and then I start to be frustrated
Because she's not listening
Maybe you didn't give her a reason
You should've said, I want you to be home because mom and dad are going to see
I said that, I said that
So then what, you know, then it goes wrong and then all I hear is like
Christina!
And I have to say, look, would you like a sweet 16 party?
You don't have to raise your voice at all
Yeah, I know, and you know what?
I don't think about these things, I don't think about bribing
Yeah, but it's not bribing, it's not
It's fucking fair, she wants us to do all this shit for her
She has to do something for us, it's called give and take
It's called living together
In a community
You can learn that in life, if you are nice and if you are giving and if you just listen to people
And you can get so much more out of it
Listen to me for a second now
If you drove down Epsom Road
And where you're allowed to go 30 miles an hour and you're driving 46
Which you did twice
And all that happened was the police would call up and say, oh Patricia, please
Please don't do that
Will you actually really think of it all the time?
Bullshit
Unless you see that big yellow thing, which by the way is interesting, you have never seen it
Yeah, now you do, that big yellow speed camera
It's just the way it works, there has to be people go away from pain and move towards pleasure
And so when you teaching is not just learning on one side, you have to do it both ways
I mean, you just know that it's like that
Okay, unfortunately, unfortunately it's because I've worked with
That's my daughter
Go ahead pick it up, I'll finish my thought
Unfortunately, it's because I've worked with
You know hundreds and hundreds, almost thousands of people in companies
Hello
Listen to this
Hi, excuse me
Oh boy, this is not our daughter
Who's this?
Who?
Eddie
Bye
Who's Eddie
Oh, Ellie
No, I don't know an Eddie, that's all who's Ellie
Ellie is Christina
Yeah, it's a friend, because I'm looking for somebody
Oh, yes, I remember, okay
So anyway, so what I was saying is the reason why is because I found out
Through working with more than a thousand people
Yeah, you use a lot of people working with you
But it's give and take and it's real simply, look if you don't do this, this will happen
And you don't have to get angry, it's just, and if you don't like it, then you will freeze
Who'd you say it covers it?
And if you don't do that, you're fired
I've never said that, never, take that back
I've never, ever, take it back
What?
That's in a television program
I've never said that, anyone in my life ever
No, that's true
I've never threatened with firing up
Never, not, don't even make jokes about that
Oh, it's not true
I fired people
I've never threatened with it, it's unnecessary
If it's that far, if the only consequences you'll get fired, then it's like
Doesn't work that way
Yeah, so that's all, it's the way
But if you don't do your job, you know that
That's different, huh?
So I don't have to tell anybody that
No, that's a tell anybody, if you don't do your job, then dot dot dot
What happened?
But with a 15 year old who was still exploring life, remember how stupid we were at 15
I mean, when you were 15, I was, I had to lie a lot
I was still in my dad's telescope
Yeah, I know
I had to lie a lot, and I regret it so much
And I had to because otherwise
You wouldn't go anywhere
This is what all 15 year olds think
Regardless of whether it's true or not all 15 year olds think
So that's why I don't want her to
Anyway
So because of those types of situations
Where you are trying to treat Christina as an adult, which is
I think really at this point in those situations in impossible tasks
Because she just doesn't have the skills yet
I don't think you can develop
At 15, you just not develop
But because of that, I think you have less patients with me
Maybe
Yeah, that's why I'm so happy to fix it with Christina
She thinks so, absolutely
I haven't got any patients for you
Less, less
It's okay, it's normal, but then I can understand
Because it's like your daughter is acting like a shit
And then I can be a little shit lit
Oh, yeah, you know, I have to
What?
Two, two people
Two young people
Two youngsters
All right, we're wasting people's time at this point
No, they recognize it
Yeah, I think they do
People have been calling in, telling them about themselves
Just calling into the voice mail number, which I should give
Let me give you the voice mail number to call in
Plus 1, 2, 0, 1, 6, 2, 5, 6, 3, 5, 7
Or in London, 0, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3
And it's fascinating to listen to people
The people that listen to this show are average age
About 33
Yeah, it's mature, I'd have to say
There's a lot of 19 year olds who are listening
But there's also a lot of people who are
45, 50, some 60
I'm really very, very happy with that
Because I believe if you look at the advertising market
Well, you're the over 40 and I'm the over 50
Right, but if you look at the advertising market
What is advertising always aimed at?
17 to 24
The shoppers exactly, 17 to 24
But these people who are 35 and up
They've got money, dude, they've got three or money to spend
And they buy things and they're
And particularly
For some reason source code listeners, man
They've got really high jobs in government and
Nuclear power plants, you know, it's just amazing
Yeah, so I'm going to do a montage one of these days
And put them all one after another
And so far, I'd say about 60% are folders
Versus scrunchers
You hadn't heard that?
No, you're kidding me
Dude, you got to hear the extended version
I had to play them for you
Oh man, you should listen to this show, it's pretty good
Yeah, let me play, I'll play the whole thing for you
You'll totally
Hold on
I'll see if I can find it
I think it's this one full, I'm just trying to
You remember Slow who did
If you ever do a Christmas?
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So here it is, check it out
For the role of toilet
I'm sorry
To the role of toilet people
That's a different one, I have so many people who've sent in folders scrunchers
Oh, the thing is, everybody does it
Everybody gets, as to go
You know, who's everybody recognizes it
But I stopped so long ago
With the, you know, really talking about folders
Yeah, and they're still talking about
We'll not stop
It is, actually.
Yes.
Oh, my can't find this now, home on the second.
Oh, here it is.
The folder.
Oh, man.
This is so good.
Check it out.
Oh, I was doing it wrong.
Well, don't you worry baby, don't worry.
There's such a way, been wiping, wiping, wiping my bum.
Because I'm a fuller, I'm a scruncher, I'm a roller, and I'm a buncher.
I do my business on the throne.
I'm a sitter, I'm a standard, I'm a left-right hender.
It's nice to know I'm not alone.
How cool is that?
Fantastic.
It's not pot safe, of course.
It's so cool.
Even up without their air.
No, of course not.
Nope.
But I'll take that risk.
Come and arrest me for that, please.
What a great headline.
Adam Curry jailed for folding her scruncher.
Even the queen, I wonder.
Even, oh, she's a folder scruncher.
Scruncher, totally.
Can you see that face?
She doesn't care.
And look, look at Charles.
Come on, scruncher.
Yeah.
You know he's a scruncher.
All right, baby.
I've got to go wash my hair, so you can do it.
Yeah.
And then we're out of here.
We're going to Big Smoke.
Yeah.
Big Smoke.
Big London City.
Yeah.
On the train.
Yes.
Can you still ask me?
We're taking the train.
Are you crazy?
I'm thinking about high shoes.
What kind of shoes do I wear?
Because if I have to run for the train.
No, we don't have to run for the train.
If you can get out of the house.
If you get out of the house on time, we don't have to run for the train.
It's just carry me.
Okay.
All right, baby.
Thank you very much for joining in.
Would you please join us again soon?
Thank you very much.
Well, I was entertaining my sister.
I mean, I was a long time that I saw.
Seeing her.
And so wanted to entertain her a little bit.
Yeah.
She had fun.
Fantastic.
All righty.
So tomorrow we'll have the Friday festivities.
Thanks.
Thank God.
It's Friday.
Send in Europe.
I'd say music picks for me to play.
Which of course I ask people to do because I'm too lazy.
And it helps.
And so I'll see you maybe Monday or Tuesday.
Maybe.
Okay.
I'll be there.
All right, baby.
Thanks for coming on the show.
And tomorrow I'll try and wake up with a happy face.
Okay.
Adam.
Thank you.
I love you, baby.
Yeah, babe.
I love you, too, babe.
All right, bye.
I'll show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like you.
On the high performance podcast delivery network from Pod Show and Lime Light Networks.
I love it.