Think Advertising sucks.
Think you can do better?
Pod Show and EarthLink are willing to put our money where your mouth is.
Listen to this podcast or go to adchelens.podshow.com to see how you can win big
in the EarthLink make advertising better challenge.
Good morning from Amsterdam.
Today is July 3rd, 2006, and I have sad news to report.
Yesterday my mom, Valerie Gail Clark, passed away at age 67.
I spent the last hours notifying family and friends.
A task I expected to be actually a sorrowful one.
But was astounded by the wonderful response we received.
Everyone has so many happy and loving memories over.
As listeners of the Daily Source Code, you've been an integral part of this journey,
which started almost two years ago with a discovery of our illness.
With mom's permission, of course, have been able to keep our extended family
of Charlie listeners updated on her progress.
And throughout this time, your emails and outpouring of love
have been so helpful to her, to my sisters and to myself.
So I also want to share this moment of closure with you.
In her last days in the physical world, she was with her three children
and her life partner. She had a very peaceful passing
without pain and filled with love, humor, and happy memories.
And my mom was very outspoken and determined as all who know her will confirm.
And she insisted that her favorite radio station was on in her final hours.
And packages in that request was her private message to me,
which I want to share with you.
You see in our last talk together, mom told me that I was always her favorite son,
which she said often and is great because I'm her only son.
And then she said she loved me forever and ever.
And she repeated that several times.
Now listen to the lyrics of the song that was playing during her passing.
Yeah.
The moment I wake up,
before I put on my makeup,
I say a little prayer for you.
Though I go in my hand now,
And one dream was just too well now,
I say a little prayer for you.
But my love forever,
you stay in my heart,
and I will love you forever,
and never,
we never will hold on,
I will love you together,
that's how it must be,
to live away,
and I'll be with only,
in heartbreak for you.
I'll run for the rest here,
or running on a thing that looks fine.
I say a little prayer for you.
And we're got just take time,
and I'll through them,
but come and feel right now.
I say a little prayer for you.
My love forever,
you stay in my heart,
and I will love you forever,
and never,
we never will hold on,
I will love you together,
Together, let's go, it must be the little wind
That you would only mean heartbreak for me
Whatever, whatever, you say in the heart
And I will love you forever
And ever, we never know what part of how
How are you together together?
Let's go, it must be the little wind
That you would only mean heartbreak for me
But don't let me mean it
Don't be embarrassed and no one's body
Please love me too
I'm in love with you
And some afraid
Say you love me too
And be with me once again
That's all my friends
You know every day I say a little forever
I say it, I say it a little forever
You know if mom were here today
She'd be very concerned about that song
Not being pod save
I can just hear her warning me of impending peril of breaking the law
Like I've heard her do to me so many times in the past two years
So I also want a pod save song to remain in our hearts
And we think of this beautiful woman
Full of grit, courage and passion
And I think we all know someone just like her
I've been down
I've been out
And I feel like my lives came in
And I can't seem to find
My lives are bound
And I'm lost my direction again
But now I'm still lonely at the end of the day
I know that my son is phone call the way
Because it's here
You're all the way
It's my weary soul
When it's been steeped
And it's here
Mother, take my broken heart
And you'll save me
When I'll strip away
Nothing more can I say
Then I love you
You're all the way
Here I go
I end the making
Sound that can walk away
But I know that I can take
Because you're sharing me all the way
I'm feeling lost in the dead of the night
It's telling me to hang on
Don't give up the fight
Because it's here
Mother
It's my weary soul
When it's been steeped
And it's here
Mother, take my broken heart
And you'll save me
When I'll strip away
Nothing more can I say
Then I love you
Mother, take my broken heart
And you'll save me
I'm feeling lost in the dead of the night
It's telling me to hang on
Don't give up the fight
Because you're sharing me all the way
I'm feeling lost in the dead of the night
It's telling me to hang on
Don't give up the fight
We move mother, we smile, we smile, and it's been a lie
We move mother, takes my mind, your safe care
Butterflies are free, I love you, Mommy
Get this podcast and more great ones like you on the high performance podcast delivery network from Pod Show and Lime Light Networks