This podcast is brought to you by Potcho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charley, 425.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this show.
I'm just kidding.
I'm crazy.
One hit.
We got it.
I got it.
We have clearance plans.
Roger Roger.
What's our vector, Victor?
How are you?
Very cool.
Missing clearance over.
Over.
Roger.
Gotta sew.
But you may do.
That's what it's all about.
Gotta sew.
And that you may do.
Love you.
What's all about?
I'm not sure.
I'm a surfman.
I'm a hero.
Think I'm wild.
No, we got a soul.
I'm a human.
That's what keep it kind of.
Gotta sew.
I'm a human.
Way out of your mind.
We have no limit.
Watch the other side.
I'm a muster.
Gotta go to the station.
But to me, it's real.
What's not right now.
We keep it kind of kind of.
I know what we got.
It's a soul.
I'm a human.
I keep it kind of.
Gotta sew.
But to me, it's true.
But to me, it's true, but to me, it's true.
Boring each other.
I like the way, it's true.
Welcome to the Curry condo.
It's a daily source code coming to you from Northern California, another beautiful day.
With some tunes to kick it off from Jersey.
It's rocked down baby with a soul connection.
Sounds like it could have been from Athens, Georgia.
Don't you think? A little bit of BJT2's vibe in there.
Wow, not much to report about yesterday, I'm afraid.
I don't really remember much of yesterday.
I was so completely wrecked and tired from, you know,
the jets at life of flying and drinking.
Oh man, I was destroyed.
Still got a lot of stuff done though.
Actually had a pretty good crap, crap mixer.
Had a pretty good chat with the folks from Barefoot radio,
which I think airs, that air, I don't know when it goes on.
They do stuff live and then they also do stuff as a pre-recorded podcast.
Check them out at BarefootRadio.com.
So it is bright and early Friday morning.
I'm so looking forward to the weekend.
I cannot wait to get more than five hours of sleep.
That would be really, really nice.
It's so early every day when that alarm clock goes off.
Man, ready to kick it for you.
It's Friday.
We got the party going on.
We got, um, how many?
I got like four or five different songs.
So let's move right on through in a couple of pieces of feedback.
Some of which are more entertaining than others as usual.
Hey Adam, this is Travis Goss, the host of the unradio show.
And I was thinking about your podcast earlier today.
And what I thought about was episode number 398.
There's released on June 2nd.
And that was the episode where Bare Lady Patricia was your guest.
And three quarters away through the episode.
You played a song of hers called Daddy.
And I did not know until that time that she was a singer.
She used to record songs back in the 60s and 70s and 80s.
Possibly in the 90s.
I am not.
Maybe possibly in the 50s.
Oh, I'm so sad Patricia's not here to hear this.
She always says, I know it gives a shit about what I was doing.
And then one can't say about it.
Oh man, I hope she's listening to this at home.
Idiot, this is where you fill in the gap for me.
So basically, I'm a guy who listens to hard rock and metal and also anything that's gothic.
But when I heard her sing that song, my foot was tapping.
I was like, wow, that is so fucking cool.
I'd say, man, you wrote yourself good one because I give anything as whole world
to have a girl like Patricia 5.
So anyways, what I'm asking is, are there any albums of hers that you could recommend?
I'm pretty sure that most of them are out of print.
But that's what internet is for.
Finding all this stuff.
I'm more than willing to go on eBay or go to any online record shops and try to find her albums.
Okay, well what you need to do is go to redbullet.nl.
That's the record company.
Either that or EMI.
You got to go to the Dutch EMI website or she's had like three or four different record companies.
And I think we've discussed before we don't have her back catalog.
We really don't.
It's just, it's just, there's so much of it.
Just, you know, you leave it in this house and you give it to that person.
You forget about it.
And yeah, you can have this CD.
And before you know what, you have no CDs, no records, no pictures, no videos, no not just memories.
So what would you recommend for me?
And also, a couple more things I like to mention.
Just listen to Shadow Falls.
Genius.
Mark.
Dude, you created one of the coolest podcasts ever.
It's like a throwback to all days when we had radio as a means of entertainment before there is television.
Of course, as well, well, well, well.
The, when radio was, was like fun to listen to.
Yeah, back in the day, when radio was entertainment.
Yeah, I got to tell you, man.
We had so much fun putting this project together.
It's been many months in the making, but it was, it was cool to, you know, work on the story.
And Mark has such a great team.
I mean, we don't really, maybe the office in Los Angeles is a piece of shit, shack and Venice Beach.
I don't know.
I don't even know what kind of, we say studio.
I have a feeling.
I've got like a microphone and a Mac and Pro tools or something.
But the group of people that that we were able to work with on Shadow Falls is just phenomenal.
These are really good actors.
These are people who are working actors who just saw the fun of this.
And, you know, and of course, they, they got paid.
And they enjoyed it.
They really had a good time.
It was really creative.
You know, and Mark has all kinds of stuff that we got to get to.
These are like, we have clips from table readings.
We turned on some recording while there was writing going on.
I mean, it really, truly, it is the audio version of a spelling entertainment.
It's my time.
But it was so cool that with podcasting, you sort of reinvent this whole thing with old-time radio.
But it came out with something brand new and fresh.
And as genius, I, I am an instant fan of Shadow Falls.
I am so looking forward to the next episode great stuff.
And finally, one more thing.
I know you retired the subject.
I'm a folder.
It's a lot more sanitary than being a scruncher in my humble opinion.
So anyways, Adam, I thought I'd go ahead and ask you questions and pass along some good comments.
Talk to you later.
John Radio Show.pot show now.
There it is.
Okay.
All right, man.
Thank you very much.
Enjoy the pod show plus.
So I don't know.
When is the next episode of Shadow Falls coming out?
Is it, uh, do we do it on Monday?
I'll have to ask Mark.
But, uh, yeah, Kudos for sure.
I mean, Mark is going to take all the credit for this.
And that's okay.
We know who really did all the work.
Don't we, Mark?
You're honored.
I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out.
Please don't bang that gavel.
You can try this cowbell out.
Let's all kiss a night.
To the hardest work.
And long hair.
He's jersey tied.
Hey!
Talk to me.
Let's go to hell.
So you talking to me?
Well, I'm the only one here.
Well, well, well, what's up, Adam?
I'm curious.
Jersey Todd.
And I could not have possibly heard this on yesterday's shot shot.
It's going to be the thank God.
It's Friday edition of the Charlie when we're Northern California.
We got a rocket out.
So send it into me.
And that's yes.
I'm looking at you, Jersey Todd.
The official music colleges of the Charlie.
Get it in early.
Get it in as soon as you can.
Are you looking at me?
You know, you and me, Adam.
We're, we're Jersey guys.
And you know, here in Jersey.
That's considered calling a guy out.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, pot father.
You call me out.
Get out of here.
Forget about it.
You want a Friday song.
You got a Friday song.
Okay.
Fine.
It's summer time.
And you need to go down the shore.
You need to hear one of the most unique voices on the podcast.
Music network.
And that voice is Jendello.
So of the band allowed.
You want passion.
You want rock.
You want to get things going.
Well, then you've got to get a loud.
Hey, got nothing but love for you, baby.
Have a great weekend.
I was born on the beaches.
I am long and to be free.
I have lived.
But the stations will be crossed.
The hands over me.
I will die.
And I must be the only case in a zero.
My belief on our actions.
Ain't no conflict in this world.
You are the world of Washington.
Now we fall on the beach
Oh, yeah, time is up to here
Thank you, Jersey Todd, the official musicologist of the Charlie
You did me just as once again my brother
Aloud and beaches from the Podsafe Music Network
Jiminyd on a Friday, yeah, that sounds good
Ah, he's been looking forward to Friday night
You know the Friday night in San Francisco
where I come home after working
home after work and just collapse and forget to eat and do you have the ability from the weekend
cast really, really loving the new Pod Show stuff. I think it's great. There's one question
are we ever going to merge the Pod State Music Network and the Pod Show stuff so you can have
one login where you can, an option where you can merge your accounts and playlists so that
you're able to put things up on the, on the Pod State Music Network and also on the, on the
Pod Show account. Just wondering if that's ever going to be a possibility if that's ever,
if that's even brought up. So thanks, love and the show keep it up. Yeah, baby. Absolutely. Yeah,
yesterday, emo boy Mark showed from Pod Show HQ showed me what it's going to look like because
yeah, of course we're going to merge that. It makes that doesn't make a lot of sense where you
have one account that also works in the Pod State Music Network and it's also where you
where your songs are that you've purchased absolutely and also the purchasing still has to be
turned on for everybody. So there's, you know, there's a lot of stuff going on. Absolutely.
And it looks really phenomenal. Just look at Pod Show Plus. Look at my page on Pod Show Plus,
look at anybody's page and then imagine what we could do adding music to that and integrating
the Pod cast and integrating listeners. It's yes. So the answer, of course, is yes. Absolutely.
And all the songs that you hear today on the Charlie, can of course be found on the Pod State
Music Network links to those in the show notes. Hey, Adam, it's Bruce Murray from the Zedcast and,
you know, folder, scruncher, roller, muncher. I mean, it doesn't much matter to me, okay? What you do
in the privacy of your own WC is between you and your maker. I mean, people who listen to the
Zedcast know, I don't ran very much. You know, I'm trying to keep it light, but there is just
something that burns my butt if you'll excuse the pun. And that is after the aforementioned fold or
scrunch, people who do not replace the roll. Okay? This is just human kindness. I mean,
sometimes you're in a hurry. You can run in, close the door. Aw, sweet relief. And then you turn to
the roll and there's nothing there. The person before you has used every last square and left you
the empty roll. And then you're hobbling around the bathroom with your pants around your ankles.
It's not a pretty sight. Okay? So, and it does not like it takes that long. Here, here I'll show you.
Okay, I'm here in Pacho Headquarters and somebody has left an empty roll in the stall.
And if Chris Rockwell came in right now, he would be mighty upset. Anyway, I'll show you how quick
this is. Start the timer. Okay? Doesn't gauge? Toss the old core. Hey, three points. Reinsert.
New roll and engage. Oh, yes. What's that? Four, four and a half seconds? I mean, I know
everybody's in a hurry, but come on, people. Before you race, please replace.
For the record, I fold Anne scrunch. That's why I guess that pretty much makes me a funger.
Anyway, Adam, you can check out the Z-cast at Pacho Plus and I was going to do the little
lighter click thing at the end here, but I'm pretty sure it'll be a little unsafe to have an open
flame in here right now. Exactly. Oh, wait. All right, man. Thank you very much, Bruce.
Really appreciate it. By the way, the lady Patricia is often known to leave the core exposed.
More about that when I get back to the hospital.
It's cold, he didn't fall out. Boy meets girl Jimmy, he world was slapping pills to les all out.
Not once, not twice, he was thraced out to lady. Back in all brand new, but I had to.
Bounce over to the Uncle Service Insta. Click up his pills that take care of my nervousness in.
On the way, I saw planes and was stuck up with stars. She played games, but she took them too far.
At the driving, watching soft morning, you can tell by the trail of the tent that there was
something in the popcorn. Popped in my cab, destination, mid-town. Just a kid up with some kids and
like to get down. I made my rounds and that was that. In between the frowns, the scraps, and hard
intact, and I remember. I seen a ass early November, on the Thursday, taking back Sunday for a brief
fun. She shot a wig like no hard feel is that she jell it to Brazil, and the pills had me spun.
How many different band names did you hear in that track?
Music network. It is taxi driver brought you by Jim class heroes on the daily source code for Friday.
If you're listening to this in Australia, how's your Saturday doing? Hello Adam. This is Ron with
zip 71101 podcast here in Louisiana. You mentioned it was hot there in England, 91 degrees.
Well, it's 106 here in the shade in Louisiana. Man, August has not even come and it is already getting hot.
Well, we've just learned to live with it. So I guess that's what you'll have to do as well.
Hey, I heard you play sunny combs in the kitty cat rodeo. What was that Friday?
And I just happened to have a new interview. My latest episode with sunny combs, and then you can find that
at zip.podshow.com. Just click under my shows and I'll take you right to it. Love and pod show.
And it's not a lady Patricia. We said hello from Louisiana. Hi, Adam. This is Whitney Hoffman from
the L.D. podcast. Listening to the Charlie as I was tooling around in the car today. I saw it
of how neat it was when we were in England. I'm the virgin trains run by Richard Branson. They
had channels like radio channels that they have on airplanes where you can plug in your headphones
and listen to all the different music that was kind of pre-selected. And I was wondering,
have pod show looked into doing channels for airlines and trains and things like that?
Just like the channel exists on serious satellite radio, it would be great if there were podcasts
and pod safe music available when you're taking a trip somewhere on a long distance,
you know, and get some more exposure that way to people who might not otherwise actually listen
to pod cast. Just a thought, something you might be interested in. Thank you for everything. I love
pod show plus and love the Charlie. Thanks so much. Bye-bye. Yeah, thank you. Good question, actually.
You're from time to time that does pop up and there'll be, once in a while, there's a company
that does something for airlines and then there is like a brief conversation. But
in general, first of all, that business is very stable. People who do that stuff for
in flight entertainment, those companies, they know their clients and they know how to handle
their clients and they know what to do. So it would have to go through one of those companies and
there's all kinds of stuff going on there that I just don't think we can break into. But really,
it is kind of a dying breed. Sure, I know that there are people who absolutely still listen to
the inflight entertainment, but really with MP3 players. I think that that is pretty short lived.
And maybe we'll see a lot of that capacity that's in those inflight entertainment systems
being swapped out for something else, a little more useful. Like, well, broadband connectivity.
Yeah, I know. I know that airlines are now saying they don't even want to do it because it's
too expensive and the customers don't use it. But believe me, within the next five years,
we'll be connected everywhere and you'll be able to just turn on whatever box that is you
have in your hand and you'll be able to get stuff that doesn't even live on the box.
It'll just come in streaming and it's very clear that's going to happen. Maybe 10 years, who cares?
But yeah, it would be nice. Certainly on the Virgin Trains, that would be cool.
So if anyone's listening and you're curious about how we could hook up, give me a call at the
Charlie. Hi, Adam. This is the French lady.
Ah, it's going to be not dead yet, the life I call you to give you some feedback.
No, I'm not dead, and I'm still podcasting. You can check us at the 2021.com.
It's my little website. And I'm kind of a secret agent, no, and still busy with a lot of this one
and I'm building a theater, explain them that theater in Las Vegas, that's why I
I didn't call the time to see this is what sucks so bad. You heard the quality of that call was bad,
right? And then it cuts out. It was really a shame because he went on for like a whole
other minute, the French lady bastard. Finally checking in, it's just the quality of the call
was so crappy and you couldn't really even follow the conversation. But what he did do is he did send
me a song that he thought would be perfect for playing on the Friday. Chacha, so I want to roll
that one out for you. Jazz breakfast on the Charlie. Feel that. Make your feet want to move.
So I want to say music makes me groove. Gekko 3.
Yo, we're coming back late from the show. There's only one place to go because it's open till three
in the end or entry fee. We're just in the queue and it's high time for me to wear
but hold them back up and to let the moves come out nice and clear. Seven ovals. He been drank it all night long.
But bother read is not the favorite place to go with night. You know we told the many times
that we just don't like the light. The sabers ain't facts, but a maiden meets with a wattage yet.
It's open and free and represent the fucking cottage. Spirits are high, what a bunch.
From all the cool, the moment we take out already we could do. Without the movement of the
getting and going around the shift, yeah man, that ain't no uma bad yet could it get eight points
to step on do. You want to do, you wanna do, you wanna do, you wanna do, you wanna do, you wanna do,
you wanna do a jazz breakfast. It's the question not everybody who laughs. From do, you wanna do,
do, you wanna do, you wanna do, you wanna do, you wanna do, you wanna do, you wanna dudo, you want to do it,
It's gone 2202, it's so beneath to make a move
I've the neck and back the OJ, well through sticks
It's in the foam, smooth, try it out
It's a lot of pausing for the body in the afternoon
Now we're singing our hangover tune
We're almost been standing in the shower for an hour
Fuck him, we're making our way
To the city, can't think we got a table at the back
So we don't take no flag
When we try and play pool and end up looking like so cool
Slow the true hiccup and rest of the crew
That's the smooth, smooth, smooth, smooth tip
And we're falling too
We got the love of me, shoot mama, don't be wild
I'm the late everybody
I know the table you say yeah
When we say here you want to do
Do you want to do? Do you want to do?
Do you want to do?
The jazz breakfast
I'm a hip-hop to wait just
I do you want to do? Do you want to do?
Do you want to do? Do you want to do?
Do you want to do?
The jazz breakfast
Lips the king, once she knocked off paper
And yeah, could I get tea for three or five more for coffee
The girls are still the side, so we start here with me
Now I know it's not an event
Because you can't miss the slack
Because we all want chicken burgers
I'll be nursing jack
Shit, I need some pickle chili
I'm a Monterey snack
Lips the side, you got the arby breakfast
No shit, hold the funk, I said
It's your little beans, I think they've touched you
They got it, love is hungry
But what, fuck's he's making?
He wants the arby breakfast
Vegetarian, we have a bacon
The spirits in the beef are all fun
But I mean they never get the order right
No shit, wait so patiently
Now we can't see the table for the lady's time
They made the fun, we know where we'll return
Because the mousse is going to make us
Do you want to do? Do you want to do?
The jazz breakfast
Do you want to square?
Yes
Do you want to do? Do you want to do?
Do you want to do?
In jazz breakfast
Guys, guys, can we get some more jazz
without?
Thank you, this is plenty
Do you want to do? Do you want to do?
Do you want to do?
do you want to do? Do you want to do?
Do you want to do a jazz breakfast?
Uh, uh, do you want to do?
Do you want a dude, do you want a dude
Do you want a dude, do you want a do
A Jack Sommerckfriend, who steaks down the photosket with the check?
Yeah
You know we'll remember all this cool music coming from us from the pod save music network
Ah... Friday Show as always compiled by listeners of Charlie
Thank you so much laxi french bastards
Next time dude, don't pick up the phone
If you're gonna really run on with something cool like that
Send me a video comment
Which you can still do, of course, adamaccurry.com, DailySourceCode.com as where you can find this show.
You can play it right there, you can get the show so you can always be alerted when there's something new there.
Yes, we even have old-fashioned XML links, so you can copy and paste it into the favorite pod catcher of your choice.
The following is a paid political announcement from the Troy Needs and iPod Foundation.
Always true, there are a podcaster and an iPod.
Master Yoda, is adamcurry the pod father?
Told you today, how?
For Trinit, pod show plus, go there you will.
iPods run heavily in pod casting.
Adam has one.
Alan has one.
I don't have one.
You must bring balance to the pod cast.
For once you start down the pod casting journey, forever with the dominate sure does.
I won't fill you master.
I'm not afraid.
You can help bring balance to the pod us here.
This is www.troyneeds and iPod.com today.
I shouldn't say it.
I played that because Troy has a domain name, Troy Needs and iPod.com.
This thing is now escalating.
It's his other guy who has a domain name, which is I need to add more than Troy.com.
I was thinking, what a perfect opportunity to go to godaddy.com.
And register, screw those guys.
I should have the iPod.com.
In fact, here's a new contest for you.
The most original domain name registered through GoDaddy, which will be judged by me,
and by me only, of course.
We'll receive an actual iPod.
It only costs $6.95 to enter the contest.
Go to godaddy.com.
Choose that Waktas domain name that pertains to the Troy Needs and iPod.com contest.
Use code DS3, DSC3.
Upon checkout, you get the domain name for a whole year for $6.95.
Think about the entertainment value.
And, of course, a chance that an actual video, it's not just an iPod.
I just heard from the judges, it's a video iPod.
I don't want to be infinity cause it goes to midnight.
I don't want to be in Berlin green because it's plastered all the time.
I don't want to be in line with my cause.
There's nothing there to do.
I just want to spend some time with you.
I don't want to be in sincey cause.
It smells like burnt tires.
I don't want to be in Cleveland cause.
The vehicle catch on fire.
I don't want to be in date.
Not without a 22.
I just want to spend some time with you.
Will it solve them hard to find the reason?
To stay in this and carry in place.
But it's hard to find the reason to be.
I don't want to be in New York cause it's buried under the slime.
I don't want to be in Portland where it's raining all the time.
I don't want to be in San Francisco in the early morning too.
I just want to spend some time with you.
I don't want to be in London cause.
The skies are always grey.
I don't want to be in Paris because I don't powerly know from saying,
I don't want to be in China with a horrifying flu.
I just want to spend some time with you.
Oh!
It's a reason that morning in Vancouver.
The highest folks are scaring the church.
We watch that church from Earth's sludge.
I guess this place could be a horse.
They say the grass is always greener.
On the other side of the car in life.
But I just stay.
The grass is pretty anyway.
Because I just want to spend some time with you.
I don't spend some time with you.
Josh Woodward won then up the Charlie for his Friday.
Thank God it's Friday.
I'm ready for the weekend.
Thank you again for everybody who sent in songs.
I think it's titled Innership.
Because that's what shows up in the ID3 tags.
Although on the Podsate Music Network, if you follow the link, you'll see that it's listed
as in Teria.
I don't think that's right.
And I sure hope it's Innership because that's the stuff that keeps helicopter pilots alive.
Alright everybody, next week's going to be a really big week.
We'll be rolling out campaigns, features, new episodes of amazing new podcasts.
So including I would hope a brand new shadow falls, bone design the way.
And I'll be here in Northern California to take you through it a haul.
Hey, take it easy this weekend.
What are you going to do?
Do it safely.
And I'll see you on Monday.
Boy, I'm slow.
Another Pod Show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it.
On the high performance Podcast, a delivery network from Podshow and line-white networks.
I love it.