This podcast is brought to you by Potcho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 403.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Transmittance?
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this show.
Yo, Adam.
This is Chris from Dallas.
Hello, right now.
I'm taking a nice drive.
It's 150 mile drive.
Got my DMV for the Charlie.
On the iPod and that got to tell you a love it.
Just calling it for the legitimate man.
She has seen what you don't know.
Let it brought her here to this place.
It's amazing what this life can put you through.
Yes, it is.
There's a choice to make in all the things you do.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
I wish that there was something I could see
I could feel her
And I'm like, yeah, can't remember
He's gone, I'm like, yeah, yeah
So she lost in time and stay
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I wonder what brothers do this place
He's goin' in a dream
He's supposed to lost in time
And stay
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I wonder what brothers do
This place and there's preparation
For Mom and Mary's command
And I want to chase Fist
He's supposed to lost in time and stay
I wonder what are them
I wonder what promise you this place is in my voice
I'm not eating, she's lost in time and space
I'm not taking this place, she's lost in time and space
I'm not eating, she's lost in time
I wonder what promise you this place is in my voice
I'm not eating, you're lost in time and space
Hey wait, are you using one, stick that in your crackby, bud.
Natalie Brown, I wonder kicking off two days
Daily source code coming to you from the curry condo in an overcast and kind of dark
Northern California the 24th floor. I'm looking out over the bay. I'm seeing clouds
I'm looking out towards the mountains. I'm seeing clouds coming rolling in. It's okay after
After all the hot weather we've had in the UK. It's all right. Hey everybody, how you doing?
This is the Daily Source code episode number
four hundred and three. Wow. So apologies for yesterday that we didn't get to share a show
together. But at the very last minute, actually Saturday is Patricia and I were on a way to
to visit my mom which we did flying of course and Patricia loved it.
Ron and I had a conversation. It's just so much stuff going on that it made a lot of sense for
me to come in a day early. Which of course means it? Which of course means that I don't have
my shirts from the dry cleaners. I forgot to bring half the stuff and normally bring it
when I get out of my rhythm man then it all seems to go to shit. But gonna be here for the next
couple weeks and we'll be bringing you the Charlie direct from the condo. Today of course the first time
I've actually set up with everything on the on the windows laptop. So my outline of the show notes
including cast blasts are all in this tiny teeny little screen which tells me I really got to get a
studio set up here. I'm gonna have time for this trip around and I think when yeah tomorrow
some furniture rise which Patricia and I ordered last time we were here. So I finally get my
dining room table and some chairs. I mean nice to have chairs in the condo. That would be novel
and the studio set up which isn't really a custom job. Like I have at home the my father
and law made for me but we found a baker's rack and it fits perfectly against this one wall that
really is wasted space in the condo. So everything will be up on racks. I'm gonna get a dedicated
machine here. I really should get a dedicated mixer and all that stuff as well. But everything seems
to be working fine for just now. Hey I've been missing them for a couple days. No not just days.
Maybe even a week and a half and all kinds of crap going on with him and comments their
blogger and thank goodness the man is back.
Hey I've been Roger Heyer. I had you mentioned that you're looking for new house and
gun fire and I want to let you know that I found a nice one bedroom to sell this.
Probably just a few doors away from my house. I think it would be splendid if you moved
at the road as you'd be able to come over to my house so nice could have teed
maybe some drugs I've got some more seen. It would save me having to walk all that
way to the usual wifi just to download some podcasts. Anyway I had to send my blog off this weekend
because coming to the blog goes report me to the police and I don't actually want to get into
any trouble. I know I sued a lot of people in the past to argue with him and I don't
want to be another one. I certainly don't want to make you liable for podcasts and
these ghost Hitler because we might end up in prison together and unfortunately a
beautiful man like you wouldn't last two minutes in the shower block. And what
worries me is that I didn't think podcasting has any rules or regulations but
it just looks like anyone with enough money and guilty secrets can control what
the other people say just like traditional media can explain what these rules are
so I can start blocking again and right now though it's quite a half to be
angry on a lovely day like today and being in the garden in my end to pants
listening to your voice we might move so soon. It's a very sweaty and content though
just wish you were here to share this right being with me. Thank you.
All right Roger. Actually at the mix we did and it's going to put in can I
be your B&H? You can be my B&H any time Roger? Yeah this thing has got to
be. But I think I have to jump in mediate if you've ever looked at curried.com
look at the comments underneath because I cross post daily source code there as well as
on daily source code dot com which is the official site and where you get the official
feed please that's where you need to get the podcast feed. There's such a stupid
stupid infantile thing going on between comic strip blogger some of Roger
is a jacic watcher dot it's it's annoying. Now I'm not a guy who moderates comments.
I have no time for it. I can't even moderate my email which means you know
way through the crap on email so not to do that for comments I don't I don't
think so. So with me it's either comments or no comments and if we can't stop all this
crap I'm just going to turn the comments off you know it it'll be a shame but it's just
it's not worth it so I've sent out to request to to all parties involved and
such a stop it stop already ruining the the comments. Oh ruination. By the way
interesting news it seems that Roger Smalls now has a gig with a BBC on what is
it called one click BBC. Now wasn't able to actually download the file I'm not quite sure
if if that's a podcast or not they have some kind of player that pops up when you access
the link and loan behold there was Roger doing an overview of the latest news on the net and
podcast and huge disclaimers from the BBC by the way saying that nothing Roger Smalls says
is represents the view point of the BBC or the general counsel of the BBC but
congratulations Roger I couldn't be happier and you know that whether we live next door
or not you're always welcome to come and filter my Wi-Fi and it's totally my pleasure.
More news from around the from around the weekend Robert Scobel has left Microsoft
is joining pod tech the technical the technology podcast network he'll be vice president
in charge of media which I guess he means that that means that he chooses shows the
join the network and works on the on the overall strategy congratulations to Robert
if you've never read his scobelizer weblog definitely check it out it was all
you know I even though this is this is great for Robert and I had quite a conversation with
Steve Gilmore about this I think it'll be on the Gilmore daily this week you know
I think it's a loss for certainly for blogging when it comes to well not not for
blood it's not a loss for blogging is it's a loss for people who want to know
what's going on inside Microsoft for some reason scobel just kind of you know
made the made the company more a bunch of nerds and geeks and he was like our port
through the firewall and I really enjoyed excuse me since sale this since sale
moment brought to you by the rock and roll geek show
for some reason it just felt like I was getting more information out of Microsoft
with having Robert there I think Microsoft messed up I think they made a huge mistake
by not keeping him on but congratulations to Robert can't wait to see what you're going to do
and of course I'll be moving to the bay area so that's my neck of the woods
50% of the time so look forward to hanging out with you once in a while Robert
this is a question I received from a lot of people
this particular one came from oh this is actually a comment from Jonathan
Adam sorry to hear about your mac issues for those you don't know after three
fried power books in a year I'm now working on the windows platform using the
notebook since most of your life is now online I'm curious to know if you have an
online solution for your on the outline or no dude I wish I did I wish
you know and I have a very simple so right now I'm using something called
whizz folders as an outline because on the outline if you have to use a
mac I think it comes pretty bundled like the light version comes pretty
bundled these days I love I love working without liners I love the
on the outline because you could easily drag a file right into it and it
would just be in the outline and it would know where it lived on your
hard drive and everything and this whizz folders kind of has that
capability but it's still not really the interface doesn't really work
for me that well yet if there were an online version where I could just
drag and drop files and clips and stuff into it gosh I would use that
no hard beat I'm now using you know just to let you know how
how little I actually use the operating system itself I live within
the entire box I'm using gmail google calendar what else does
let me just check my bookmark bar I know missing something
google calendar rightly I've been using rightly for word documents
and now the new google spreadsheets and it works fantastic I'm not a
power user you know this stuff is great for me and I can access it from
any computer anywhere love it so if there is an online word
processor not just an outlineer and not just an outlineer that just
has you know text outlines I have to be able to link stuff into it
please let me know I'd really appreciate it little behind on
comments and stuff that I'm coming in and of course our voice
mail lines are wide open and available for you to call in
we have a new jersey number two zero one six two five six three five
seven and I have a London number oh two oh seven six eight one three
seven five three a bit behind as I said so even though we already
know all about the Tony Awards I'll play this for you anyway I
had him this is Jim Farley with the musical world podcast the podcast
for all things musical theater I'd like to invite you in the lovely
lady Patricia and all of your listeners over to www.musicalworld.us
to give a listen to our special Tony Awards preview show I know you and your
lady Patricia are fond of musical theater and I think you'll enjoy the
we have theater critic Russell Florence Jr. as our guest and he's going to tell
us who he thinks all the winners will be on Sunday night so on Saturday
June 10th come on over to musical world and join us for some Tony Awards
revisions and they add them congrats on 400 plus I'm so sorry I fucked that up
I should have played that obviously I should have played that Friday I really
messed it up dude but two things I wanted to say first of all I'd like the fact that you're
doing that show the other thing is we hate musicals we do not like the musical
theater know we like theater we like shows but real musicals all men you got
to have a real good one for us to particularly for Patricia to like it and boy I'm
going to miss her while I'm here these you know the next few days or two weeks
because and yet the only thing I can think of is we maybe I get her on Skype
and we do something together but I don't know if it's going to be the same
and of course there's also Christina's pod save the queen like how am I going to do
that now I hadn't actually showed her cast blaster and half the studio is with me
and I don't want her to create it on a Skype headset or something although
I did say why don't you get one of those sexy boy friends of yours to hook up
a really good Skype headset mom will pay for it and then we'll try and record
the show that way because I really do want to keep the the consistency in
there's funny and what the office saying oh man you know how's Christina doing
as she enjoying the show and all I can say is well yes she loves the show you know
she loves doing it and she's just waiting for that pod show contract because
I don't know there's folks over at other networks that are getting pretty interested
on clever little pub 16 this week we explore Anglo American differences
throw away that British reserve god dammit we're American there a famous
outlaw terrorizes nottingham a hooded robbing person going around
robbing in a board you know what this means
week 10 as we turn plus music from the Scottish band dropkick
and bloopers from the show it's just begging to be downloaded
on i choose brickaster and a clever little pod.com clever little pod
it's good to be playing promos again even though I love talking to Patricia we
never seem to get around to them and uh there's even some that are now new
on the pod show podcast network.
Hollywood based video podcast rock and roll TV brings you regular doses
of rock punk and garage bands film live along with independent music video
clips interviews bridge pop culture and more hosted by me share
us.
We're happy to join the pod show family always under the radar always loud
and always un-sensored.
She's cute too welcome and I got it inside the satellite window.
I'm doing really good today this is groovy even though it's what is it?
715 a.m. you know I uh so I arrived yesterday Monday.
Uh oh wow this was pretty interesting so after a pretty un-eventful fight
you know it was 10 hours although actually we went so far up into the north
uh into the northern hemisphere up into the Arctic circle that the pilot actually
made mention of it that he never been routed that far up north and was beautiful
oh I mean just looking down onto uh ice caps and as we came down over uh
over the northwestern territories you know the volcanic uh land scape
the rocky mountains it was just a beautiful flight and I'm so glad I I slept for
probably about four four hours or something like that see I also saw some movies
what I see today you go can you remember oh uh E on flux which I think
I'd seen before but it was just it was at Charlize Theron.
I'll watch any movie that she's in.
What else did I see?
Uh oh man.
I'm a little fuzzy I'll see if I can come up with it later.
So I got in around uh 130 and uh interesting I got completely opened up
at customs that was new um and there was a lot of activity yesterday at San Francisco
at the airport you know customs activity lots of people there you know their suit
cases were being opened up and I got a pretty thorough drilling I have to say
uh even was asked to take off my jacket which has lots of zippered pockets
but they didn't look in that one that was already practicing.
Hey Ron I'm at the airport so to work out fine when straight to the office actually
after I dropped off my stuff and we had a couple meetings up until seven o'clock
so it was completely wiped out by the time I got home or my favorite sweet and sour
chicken from the Chinese guys around the corner built the studio got it ready
for this morning and went to bed straight away so I got a good seven hours
of sleep was up at five this morning going through all the backlog email.
Of course that's why I got a lot of these voicemails and promos I just way too
laid on and I also checked out the ad challenge this is the earthlink ad
challenge campaign that we're running where we actually are going to pay you
valuable cash prizes and your commercial will be used for earthlink
across the board you know as uh as as their commercial and we'll have a couple
of different categories you can check out all the information at uh ad
challenge.podshow.com if you want to enter um and uh I was just skimming
through when I found a lot of really good ones I want to share with you
because this is advertising and it's best when when the when the customer
really conveys the message
big news today earthlink ice beat it in an access and ounces there are
liberating spam no spam what you mean you spam what you mean you spam what
you have to break this all of these
thumbs up
this is great testimonial by a 14 year old uh 14 year old i i would say
kid but he's a 14 year old you're not really a kid and he talks about how
as dad uh uh how he convinces dad to get earthlink when he was 11
3 years ago I'll play that one tomorrow uh cash prizes and lots of
social reward it can all be yours ad challenge.podshow dot com
been following the world cup looking for another update from from my
from my guys they're gonna be sending me one soon this week I presume. So even though I didn't see
oh I didn't see the Netherlands play on Sunday. Wow Robin was great and I must say I'm kind of
getting into it I got a little bit of World Cup fever and it was so cool to go Saturday morning
I had to fill up the car before we drove to the airport. So it was really early it was you know
730 and the the the gas station was just filled with cars and people buying big
crates of beer and crisps and you name it and flags everywhere everywhere England flags people wearing
England flag T shirts and tattoos and paint and the other pride is just unreal and then we flew to
the Netherlands and everything was orange and there were orange shirts and orange flags and
different money it was like going to a whole other country in just an hour and 15 minutes.
Unfortunately the US lost their first game three zip I still you know they have a chance still
and they are ranked I think fourth in the world so I'm really hoping that they do better it's hard
now I've got like three teams that I'm following and I really like them all for different reasons
and I'm affiliated with all three so any one of those three that wins will be great and
I'm not quite sure if it's if the world cup has any life to it in the States I'll figure that out in
the next couple of days and I have no idea who's playing today or what's going on but
definitely enjoying it the only real sporting event I can totally yeah and the Super Bowl I guess
it may be the world and maybe I guess any final game I like so lots of talk around the office
about me being on windows particularly because a lot of people have now purchased a
MacBook Pro and
they're running side-by-side windows and Mac applications very cool he in fact here's the listeners doing
exactly the same. Hey Adam this is York from Berlin Germany and I just wanted to tell you that I'm
actually recording this bit in Casplaster on parals on my iMac since you wanted to know
yeah and winners look like shit okay bye love you show don't go yeah it does look like shit doesn't it
but it works you're right the only game the village is not well should all it's English but it's
supposed to be said with a Welsh accent says Jamie Garner through Gmail Welsh is quite a hard
language to master and does slightly sound like cling on yes no kidding second thing
oh that's about taking the Jubilee line to Canary War. I'm getting so many comments about that
I'm the only game the village I wasn't it doesn't sound Welsh at all to me I watch those big brother guys
the housemates and they were speaking Welsh and it didn't sound at all like the only game the village
but I find it a fascinating language and there are Welsh podcasts and you know when we get
kicking with the show in the UK we'll definitely have a place for Welsh podcasting and for Irish as
well interesting love I was we're just trying to build it up we're just trying to make the show the show
something else I received oh I wish I had find uh oh now I gotta go back and look who sent this to me I'm
sorry uh how it's turned who of course is only uh one channel up from us on serious satellite radio
is definitely definitely listening to this show let me see if I can make this just before the
satellite window closed you know but I like the classic rewind and a classic vinyl I'm I'm on all the
time I'm on uh channel 9 that's the pulse I listen to the heavy metal thing I don't even
wish one when I work out sometimes I listen to Jay Thomas on um stars and sometimes I listen to that
iPod show with uh oh god that drives me crazy what's that guys name um curry yeah I like that
guy Adam Curry I like that guy an iPod expert I imagine somebody's sitting in I like a little room
you know broadcasting to nobody I don't know I just listen to that so I don't know what they're talking
about I'm trying to listen to the figs but then I can't I don't listen out here I listen to
serious left all right those of you listen to us on stars 102 Pacific Coast Hellway is next
that you know that really chaps me I have to say I really dig that you're having been a
stern junkie for years for years and still listen to him on serious I love that that's cool
he said I love that guy thank you that that is a huge compliment to me oh let's see what are we
doing here yeah people in their living room kind of in the kitchen on the bar in the kitchen
does it really matter I don't think so I really don't you know stern is he's smart man he's
he's just listening he's listening to everything that's going on he knows he knows what's what
people are doing and uh he knows that this really is the future of audio entertainment that's why
he's listening to it Steven Dawn said hey Adam I have a daughter who's turning 14 curious to know
what age do you let your daughter begin wearing makeup and perfume thanks Steve wow I think
Christina already had lipstick in her hands and all over face at the age of three and you know it's
so hard because what is what does a kid do a kid replicates what mom and dad are doing but going out
out of the I mean it all depends you know if I think it started very slowly Patricia being a
makeup expert hands down having her own cosmetics company of course it went very gradually I think
maybe she was you know a little bit of I shadow or maybe a little bit of mascara or something like
that and it really depends on what shades of stuff and how heavy the makeup is applied but
I think that she really eased into it but it's not like you flip the lights twitch and say okay
do whatever you want go out with you know with bright red lipstick I wouldn't let my wife go out
with bright red lipstick if it was too bright too red or not coordinated with her dress and she was
in handbag so it's all about you know what's the balance there but it's going to be very hard
you know to to set a particularly when kids or teenagers look around you pick up any magazine any
magazine and you'll see that there's not just makeup there's also a shitload of a photo shop and
go on on everybody looks so thin and pretty yeah I'm just a little flat think again listen to
you're not supposed to talk into the microphone so I this guy sent me a couple of voice comments
about about three nine or five where I got so pissed off about the plopping sounds etc and so
now he's telling me how and by the way this is you know you can this is a real shit quality
coming through on the voice mail line but he's telling me I'm not supposed to talk directly into
the microphone okay I know you've been doing an radio and broadcast and shit for a long time but
let me tell you what I've been working at a radio station for often on OPEC in years and I've seen
all kinds of different microphones and people all the time all the time when they go in and they
sit down they talk directly into the microphone well of course it's this big phallic thing that's
staring you're right in the face you know you don't approach those things at a 45 degree angle
ever but once we're using the right now or the electric voice something 20 looks like a giant
trojan kind of or something you probably know what I'm talking about yeah I do well hold on a
second that's not entirely true because and this is just geeky for for people who are interested
but the the shoe or microphone that you that you speak of is pretty much the same model as the
high PR 40 that I'm using originally it was developed for a to record drum kicks the the
kick drum the bass drum so they put it into that hole that you see often in or on the other side
of course but they would put it into the into the bass drum so it gets the actual force of the drum
the wind straight into it so you know it wasn't even developed for for use in for voice it was
did not have to for drum kicks the 45 degree angle to your face if you talk into the mic not only
are you gonna pop it unless you got this thing perfect that's it you're also gonna get the sound
of you breathing into it yeah exactly I like that you gotta understand one thing and I do appreciate
what you're saying but my show has a sound and I think if you go back to 395 and listen you'll
understand that I take my sound very seriously I like it I like being able to I like being able to
hear myself breathe I like a little bit of a little bit of a reverb on it I like a lot of compression
I like the music to be compressed it's my art you know it's almost like saying to the Rolling Stone
you know hey your guitar is distorting hey Jimmy Hendrix man can you hear that the guitars distorting
turn it down don't turn it past eleven something that I didn't leave on the last message that I'll
leave on this one just been popping on and off probably about three or four times first show
for about the last ten or fifteen shows I've noticed I'll be driving along I'm feeding my NB3
player through my car stereo and I'll get a pop just coming out of nowhere so you're either pop in the
mic or you're over modulating cash last or one of the other so dude for the other the
content oh okay right it's about the content it's my sound man I like it that way I want you
to hear the the flem in my throat if at all possible we discussed during a Trinity segment
where was that there was three hundred seven maybe I think about this new hydrogen power
that this guy developed and he's making hummers for the US government that run on water
or it's like hydrogen and so the the person the only person I know who really knows about this
stuff and his up on it is Ray Lane one of our board members and investors from
Clienter Perkins because they do a lot with this green tech fund they have like 200 million
dollars they're investing an alternative energy and fuels and research and all kinds of stuff and
so I sent him that and he said yeah well first of all he says that he had like he really
laughed about Patricia talking about you know the conversation she had with him where he was
offhandedly talking about the forty million dollar house he almost bought and of course he'd already
seen the YouTube video and I did but I think I put a link to that in the show notes he said
he looked into it and let me just grab a couple pieces from his response here
the first question from the water fuel video is can you get more energy from hydrogen enhanced
gasoline combustion then it took to make it and I guess that is really what it comes down to the
answer is a very cautious yes what's very poorly understood is the characterization of that
enhancement effect the thinking is that the combustion of a relatively much larger mass of fuel
in a process that is quite inefficient to begin with can have big swings and efficiency from
small changes in combustion okay so the one-out bought a number of onboard H2 generation systems
advertised around the web installed them and put the results on the dyno what's the dyno no
statistically significant results however the characterization of the impact of hydrogen addition
to natural gas is very complete and there is a threshold is 10% for an observable effect
so I guess what what he's saying here is that maybe there's even more yeah the carrot is that
using primary ice energy man there's too many acronyms here ray ice energy to make sufficient
hydrogen might not have a net positive impact on power output so it actually takes more energy
and people said this about biodiesel in the beginning as well but it's not entirely true at least
biofuel maybe with ethanol but not biodiesel but when it comes to the hydrogen stuff it apparently
takes more energy to actually create it than it delivers however using waste energy in the exhaust
heat and pressure might very well tip the balance and of course it also the result of a hydrogen
hybrid engine is water so you can reuse that but the jury still seems to be a little bit out
lots of comments still about episode number 400 that we had recently and here's an interesting
feedback about a future milestone what about um this is Buck Thompson a listener i don't have a podcast
at least not yet um so i'm just listening here to uh to the charlie number 400
congrats on that milestone but i was thinking it was like you know what's the next milestone
and it like it hit me like a ton of bricks i'm driving from work i'm like holy shit it's 420
and like i gotta do something i gotta i gotta start a podcast or i gotta i gotta do something this is like
monumental jeez so i decided to share uh my excitement unfortunately that's all i have to share right now
like hard and uh i can't do much about it but uh i don't know maybe you'll hear from me um but that's
it no plugs uh love the show keep going um i'm having a lot of fun listening to it thanks right
on man and uh 420's back at you make sure you get all your stuff in for episode 420 get your
light clicks get your pod save songs that you think are relative send them on in lots of people
suggested stuff i should do for tomorrow's show which actually i was planning to be the show while
i was in the air i wanted 404 to be very simple the podcast you requested is no longer a bit
it's always difficult to see a loved one struggle with cancer and there are many
worthy organizations working to find a cure there is another approach prevention
located in the San Francisco Bay area the breast cancer fund submission is to identify and eliminate
the environmental causes of the disease for example some plastic water bottles contain chemicals
linked to breast cancer the breast cancer fund is working to eliminate these and other dangerous
chemicals from consumer products i'm inviting you to participate in the fourth annual bike
against the odds a fundraising ride for the breast cancer fund on Sunday September 10
you can either ride or sponsor a cyclist or team there are five beautiful roots winding
through the picture-esque espae hills ranging from 12 miles to a challenging full century
the local yellow jacket cycling club members will keep the bike riders safe and on track
at the finish line a delicious organic lunch live music and an expo await you
for donations or sign-ups please go to www breast cancerfund.org spelled f-u-n-d and click on the
bike against the odds link you'll be glad you did thanks and tailwinds to all the cyclists out there
in the background you've been listening to scanlin on the pod safe music network
good initiative man anything i can do to help so let me know
even though we've got the earthling ad challenge running right now we still have plenty of
domain name available for you to go to go daddy any domain name that you register you can get for
695 six dollars 95 cents very i'm still a network solutions customer and man i'm
paying so much money's like 30 bucks a year just use promo code dsc3 that's all four characters
together dsc3 upon check out and you'll get that domain name for only six dollars 95 cents christian
from from Germany says hey Adam think you already know this maybe you don't care Angela Merkel
the German federal chancellor which is comparable to a prime minister is just started a weekly video
podcast and it gives me the feed christian thank you very much i've said i'm subscribed to that
and i'll put a link into the show notes it's always good i love seeing politicians getting into
podcasting and using new media and i love even more if they keep it up very few do you know usually
it's like maybe one or maybe even a second episode and that's it you know almost second what's
flashing here for some reason oh what is this still still so getting used to some of the
quirks of windows oh man this is sheba is not very nice when you run on a battery power though
it kind of tells you and then closes down within seconds okay just a couple more g-mails here
Adam Doug from Doug and Boulder oh Doug and Boulder right had a quick request can we stop using
the term wife beater to refer to tank top undershirts hoping not being too thin skinned here but
I gotta tell you every time i hear you or someone else use that term well it makes me cringe
it has a real negative connotation for me kind of like child pornography whoa dude i mean
no it's a wife beater it's just a figure of speech come on it'll be so sensitive
okay and thanks so much to everybody who sent me invites to rightly i'm now using it man
is that stuff amazing you really is fantastic this is the online word processor so you can
create an open and and edit Microsoft Word documents you can collaborate with people on documents
you can actually use it as a chat system it's it's really it's a very smart thing
and i discovered that there's another feature if you receive an email and of course i'm sure this
is all going to be tied together you know soon when there's an h with there's a Microsoft Word
document that comes into Gmail it'll say open and rightly or open and open and google word or
whatever they call it but now you can you can actually forward anything that came in and it'll
forward the attachments into your rightly account and you can just open them up from there i mean
this stuff is so phenomenal i love it uh gone of the days it's spending 400 bucks i'm like
your soft office all right time to wrap this up a song from the pod safe music network which
comes with it's very own listener intro hey Adam this is Jeff just south of Nashville
one of your listeners calling in again uh friend of mine is in a band called salient
and i told them all about pod safe music network and i actually convinced them to sign up on
there so i was thinking maybe you could check out one of their tracks again the band the name salient
at the l i e and t and the track that i recommend is called immortal ice so check it out
but i want to take in all the play i've got to come true when i sacrifice for love and money
pity ultimate price there's no refund for the gun but a state of grace now i don't recover
my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my
my my my my my
my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my mad boot.
Selient from the potsy music network, thank you very much for getting your frames up on the network keeping
We've got tons of new songs every single day. You're welcome to go over there and check them out as a listener
But more importantly, look at the the podcasts that are playing these songs check them out
Listen what other songs they're playing see what other shows are playing that song
It really becomes into a whole network of recommend if we screw this
Recommendation engine stuff like if you like this song you'll probably look that song
Now you write a little emailing you send the to your local DJ. You know what I'm saying? That's how it works
All right, everybody I'm out of here got to get to the office. If you're wondering
What the whole point of this trip is for me? By the time I leave
We will only be days away and this is no joke
This is the real deal. We're finally close enough to releasing pod show plus which is for you the listener to help you
Listen to podcast to find the podcast you want to communicate with other listeners with other fans with podcasters with pod save artists
We're really trying to tie it all together, but the time I leave will be ready to go public beta with that
That's going to be fun
for 20 everybody tailwinds and I'll see you tomorrow. Bye bye
Yet this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from podshow and line-white networks