This podcast is brought to you by Potio and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 467.
This is control.
Can you identify yourself, sir?
Please.
This is control.
Can you identify yourself, please, sir?
Roger, I hate you faintly in the background.
It sounds something like Delta Sierra Charlie.
Hang on.
What's it?
All right.
It's Adam Curry, everybody.
Adam's here.
A $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
It's Adam Curry.
Everybody in the house is ready to party.
Let me hear your signal.
Let's go.
Stop.
I take you get yourself pumped up.
I turn a little brush into you got to jump up.
Sometimes I gotta put the tape on my back.
Make sure that we win and break it back.
Stop.
I let him know you in the building.
Everybody may win and the children.
We ain't gonna do the way.
No more.
We gon' stop.
We ain't gonna fight him out of the floor.
To the reader.
We gon' make one thing real clear.
To all my people getting down right here.
We gon' party like this.
All these.
We gon' go crazy.
Everybody in the house is ready to party.
Let me hear your signal.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Stop.
Let's go to the reader.
The blood's just here.
They're making it clear.
A brand new sound getting dawn up in the air.
Yeah.
We see her.
This is something different.
Make it a grapple brow.
What an issue is.
Raise your body.
Come in.
Some with the watch.
And make it clear.
We gon' do the way.
We gon' like it just don't break.
Everybody in the house is ready to party.
One, two, three, four.
Yeah.
For the reader.
Stop.
Let's go.
The reader.
Stop.
Let's go to the reader.
Turn down the truck.
They're going to.
We can't join a wireless ticket.
The band plays the tool, so then I know you
Stop the pictures in your new and old suits
You are your whole soul, you know we're taking it hard
The boys picking their back up in the rookie car
It's not the 20 yards, they call their grandson
Give it up for the team, so we're getting it hard
To the reader, we don't make one thing real clear
To all my people can down right here
We don't party like this all these
So don't know how to say that we are
I know the way you are like it's a stone trader
Everybody in a mess, you ready to applaud
Let me hear your signal
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Well bunch yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Stop the bleachers, hey everybody, how you doing?
Welcome to the Daily Source Code
Wow, come on!
Coming to you via podcast and serious
Satellite stars 102, it's a start of a new weekend, man
It's been a busy one, of course, when the midst of getting the house shit together, and this morning I had a nice visit from
A gentleman from his royal majesty, royal majesty's
Revenue and custom service
Regarding ex-ice, duty drawback on ships and aircrafts
This is something Captain Dan found out for me, that
You actually can get money back if you fly and use fuel for aviation
I'm not quite sure what the percentage is, but it's enough that Captain Dan got all the numbers out
When you're flying around as much as we do, it does kind of add up, it could be easily a thousand pounds
I'm going to get back, I love this
It's a very little known thing that you can get ex-ice duty back
Anyway, that song from the wild bunch
That's what Jersey Todd turned to song to on Friday
It's, I don't think it's up on the podcast music network yet
Both he and I have been in touch with the record company
They've given me permission to play it in Jersey Todd and actually Todd
Completed on any show that he can get it on to
I just hope we can get them on the podcast music network
Because gosh, that song is so incredibly good
Patricia was even talking about it over the weekend, said that song
That's a major smash
Please put it on the podcast music network, so we can all get behind it and show something
It'd be so cool and there's more happening with podcast music
It really is spinning around the globe, proving that we're all part of one kind of thing
All the winds blow and all the winds are one
It's working all over the world, listen to this piece of feedback I got
Hi Adam, this is Dean, I'm a software engineer down here in Houston, Texas
NASA and an aspiring musician, and I just wanted to call him
Where are the tapes? That's what I want to hear about, where are the tapes?
Let you know how much the daily source code is wrapping around my real life
I was listening to our local community radio station about a month ago
And I had a local duo on called Smife and Taylor, who we're talking about
Going and touring England and playing at a deal fast in Guilford England
The light just went on in my brain, and then today I go to
Plug in my headphones, fire up the daily source code, sip in my diet coke, logging into my email
And what comes on, but me and Jean Kelpton and the die hards who are a local
Blues band down here in Houston, that I've heard on the radio, I've seen them in clubs
And now they're on the daily source code, this world is just getting too crazy
Anyway, have a great weekend and enjoy the source code, and the guy was right
By David Epilitos, almost Bob Dylan, but nobody can be Bob Dylan, come on now
That's what I was sitting at this morning going full to scruncher
Then I checked the next voice mail
Adam, this is Dean, and Houston, Texas again, I forgot the most important part
I love that, I love it, it truly is one big world that we're all in, fantastic
And then the voice mail right after that, when after he called back and said he was a folder, was this
I had a my name is buddy, bro, I am the national motion structure, jam bone records
I love that, hi, I'm buddy, the national promotion director, jam bone records
Let me just stick you to bone bone
Thank you for playing one of our hardest on your podcast, me and Jean Kelpton and the die horse playing my baby
Don't wear no things, I know your listeners enjoyed listening to that, and we hope that you use our music in the future
Again, if I can do anything, you can email me at buddy at jam bone records.com
And then he gives us his phone number, you know, buddy, let me just tell you something
Thank you, dude, thank you and the band and all of the forward thinking, forward looking, innovative
Record companies, independent labels, artists, promoters, managers, whatever it is
Putting your music up on the podcast music network really does bring results
It's fantastic for podcasting because it's a very simple resource, anyone who's a podcast or can sign up
And you can play all this great music and it just doesn't stop every day, there's tons of new songs coming in
And you can see it's being recognized around the world and people are really digging it, so thank you
For putting all of your stuff up on the podcast music network and sharing in that regard
And hopefully we're sending enough love back to you guys and people who are interested in buying stuff from you
And I hope our own purchasing system will go full, I still haven't heard from Chris Beshear
He was going to tell me when he's going to go full blown, but I think it's when we
I can't tell you too much, we're integrating, you know, pod save music network, of course with pod show plus
And I think that's when we're going to blow the sales wide open as well
I don't see any other thing that we could be waiting on, I will double check today for sure
Greetings Adam, so the doctor here from the blood cast, blood cast, dot com slash cast
I just wondered if you'd written these about
MTV and what it's been up to in its total date itself and now you haven't been in second life for a while, I think it's a bit of a shame
But there was news yet a day of MTV doing a deal with their dot com, which is another virtual world as you knew
Wait, is it called their dot com? I couldn't quite hear that home, just roll it back a second
The virtual world as it has MTV doing a deal with their dot com, it's another virtual world
I think I have heard of this, there's a couple of virtual worlds that worlds out there
So they're doing a deal with them, huh?
Johnny come lately
After months of whispers and speculation apparently
And it's basically MTV's creating a virtual degree in a beach to go to TV show
A virtual lagoon a beach
And I quote
Lough and the shows create avatar socialize the friends partaking and brood up and prowl around a fluid digital version of the orange county California city
It gave a show its name
And then today I throw another piece in New York Times
MTV is now acquiring maker of music oriented games and now they've gone and bought harmonics, which
His main product, they make sort of music oriented video games that their main product is guitar hero, which is a PS2 game
And you get a little simulated that looks like a guitar
And so makes you feel like a rock star
Without knowing how to play music or even leaving your bedroom according to the New York Times
Anyway, I just was quite interesting moves that your old employers are making sort of themselves into virtual worlds and two games
Wonder what you thought about it, anyway, you know I'm a scruncher, bye
Thank you, Dr.
And despite the fact that you're a scruncher, I love you to bits and you know that
Don't tell blog, okay
Yeah, I think MTV is really lost its way
I have to give some to Redstone the chairman of Viacom
I got to give him props, you know, he was right to get rid of Frustan
I don't know if this stuff is, if this stuff is still leftovers from from the Tom Frustan days
Tom Frustan, of course the CEO of MTV Networks
It was recently removed from his post
And now there's two other guys who are in there running the show
This is, oh man, give me a year, give me MTV for a year
It is so obvious what you should be doing in this new world
It is so obvious, the whole that is there is so big I could, I could do a 360 with my airplane in it
So we're going to fill that gap, I'm sure pod shell is just going to do that
I'm pod casting independent producers, this makes no sense
No sense whatsoever
Yeah, you know what, it's a shame, it really is a shame
I was telling him what to do in 1993
What I registered MTV dot com, it's got to be doing something different
I don't think acquiring game companies is going to do it
And I don't think any virtual world, it's ancillary stuff
You can't get more than 100 people into one simulator at the same time
That would be, you can only see that it's an expansion of your brand
That is anything, you know, large quantities of audience can jump onto this
It's so simple, so easy
That's a corporate America, I guess
MTV not the only one doing funky things, I'm sure you've read about this
Hi Adam, this is Pana Yotis from Greece
I was reading today that Apple is taking legal action against the sites that use the term pod casting
And pod cast, because they think that the term pod cast is a copyright infringement of the ripod trademark
Well, I think this is stupid, and they should stop acting like they have a stick up their ass
But would it be a nice idea to start calling it zoom cast, would they prefer that?
Folder
Yeah, Pana Yotis are buddy from Greece, check it in
Okay, so this is what's happening, apparently pod cast ready
Who make a kind of like, I think it's, it may even be based on on juice or iPod or lemon
They make a ready to go download thing that you can pop on
I think it comes on a memory stick and they're trying to get it embedded in players
And it's definitely a very good idea
And they, so here's the report that came out sometime last week, late last week
That they received a cease and desist letter from Apple
Regarding the use of pod cast ready and my potter
Now this is, I have not seen an actual blog post report or the cease and desist letter
Which, it makes me cautious, very, very cautious
Yeah, it's things on the internet just grab, catch fire
It runs around like wildfire, everyone's saying they hate Apple and it's stupid
And they're trying to now grab the pod cast name
I'm not too sure about that, I really am not
Let me just go back to, when before Apple announced iTunes was at 4.9
Where they had pod casting built into it
I had a meeting with Steve Jobs and we went through like two hours
Went through a whole bunch of things and then at the end of the meeting he said
He went through his whole, he was very kind
He went through a whole wrap about trademark and how you have to protect your trademark
And he said, we're going to have an issue protecting our trademark with iPodter.org
And I can understand because it's a derivative of the word iPod
And he said, can you, can you do something about that?
So you know what, we'll change it to indiepotter.org
You know iPodter.org, the links will remain
You don't want to break the internet, there's a million fucking links to go from iPodter to now indiepotter.org
But there was no problem, I didn't see a real issue and I understand how trademarking works
Now if it's really true that Apple is trying to go after the use of the word pod cast
And any service or product, then I think there is a major problem
But I'm not sure, I'm really not my potter, I understand that
It's also, you know, the my, the derivative of iPod
When lawyers get together, I've been through this exact
Type of legal procedure with mtv.com where it can become confusing for consumers
So iPod, my pod, iPodter, my potter, I can understand that
But is it also about podcast ready?
I've seen no proof of that and I'm going to be, I'm going to be very cautious
about taking real stake until I've seen exactly what the letter is. Now here's what I think is going on
There's a great article on zdnet
Excuse me, which really extrapolates all of the trademarks that Apple is trying to
Has filed and is trying to acquire one of them actually is the iPod trademark itself
And it's a lot of legalese and a lot of explanation so you'll have to go to
Theysourceco.com and click on the link in the show notes if you want to read it all
But it does seem that Apple has been trying to
Trying to trademark iPod cast
And that's been rejected several times to keep coming back at him and the US patent trademark office
As slapped them a couple times and it feels like the lawyers are kind of on the
Loosing edge of trying to get this trademark for iPod cast and perhaps and that may be the case
Maybe they're trying to strengthen their own position by going out and protecting
The iPod cast future trademark by going after anyone who's using podcast in their name
And I think that if if podcast read it really did receive a cease and desist for using the podcast
The podcast nomenclature in podcast ready
Then I think it's just lawyers who are just not understanding the marketplace
Not understanding what is happening not understanding how closely bound Apple is to podcasting in this huge community
Of people who will turn around and revolt and rebel against Apple if they try to grab the name podcast
I think it's almost impossible for them
I think that there's just no way and and look at how stupid it is from a business perspective indeed as ponayota said
You know, do we want to call it zoom casting would you rather have that it's like you know how dumb can you be do not alienate your customers that way
Again, I'm I'm being cautious because I don't know if that's really what they're going after but I can see if they're trying to register iPod cast where
Sending out these letters regarding pod the use of podcast would make sense from a legal perspective
But certainly not from a company perspective Steve jobs. I know you're listening or someone who will pass this on to you is listening that just makes no sense because what happens
First of all, who cares podcast it's already the word pod is in there you have the iPod
You know there it's it's it's probably not even good for podcasting and for independently produced audio to use the word podcast because so many people believe that they can only receive it if they have an iPod
Which is not true you can listen to it online in a web browser. You can download it. You can play it on anything you can burn it to CDs
But if you go that route and you try to capture the name podcast, you're going to get some extremely pissed off
Not just customers fans, but also other types of people
Hello Adam Kerry who abuses sexually blackberry. I wanted to tell you that this fucking bastards hit people scum
Apple Corporation are suing people because some people are using podcast in the name for example
They're suing now www.podcastready.com
Fuck them fuck you Apple Corporation
I wanted to say that I never in my life owned an iPod
And I thought that the name podcasting is coming from pots coffee pots for the sensor machine that you are mentioning on your podcast on your audio recording
And the coffee pots for sensor are actually the inspiration of the name podcast and podcasting
If there's nothing to do with Apple I never had an Apple iPod
I don't know what iPod is. I was convinced that it is about a pot for coffee machine
The cell this batch was dedicated to coffee pots for sensor
Yeah, and case you're wondering
Comic strip
You do not want people like comic strip blogger to be your adversaries
So let's find out if this really is the case where the cease and the cease letter which not one single fucking journalist has questioned
Not one not a single one everyone just reprinting
Please if it really is a cease and the cease against podcast ready
And it says because of the use of the word podcast then I will
Trash every single Mac I have every single last one
And I'll put it on video and we'll put it on perversion for profit
And you're going to do the same
Hey there, I'm Christina Curry, one of the hosts of the BJ blast
Be sure to tune into this week's episode where I showcase new music by mellow bright band
Sean J and more. Listen to hear about the exciting how low-screen promotion
Where one lucky listener will get a free trip to Bush Gardens
We even learn about hippo camps
And I share the star of my most recent drama and the dressing room of London's top shop clothing store
Toon in this week and check it out
Yeah, there you go. We're teaching teens the fine art of economics and having a job
It's BJ blastbgblast.podshow.com, Christina
My daughter of course, one of the hosts, Martina Butler
And Shme the other host and you could be a host too
It's it's it's it's great project
You got to listen to it. It's very different from pod save the queen which by the way
Christina is getting ready to do a new one. It's just been busy with starting school and everything
Yeah, it's on its way
But check it out bgblast.podshow.com
I think you'll I think you'll like it. It's a
Little different. It's a highly produced. It's fast. It's a full of prizes and fun
And and I just love hearing Christina Martinez. I haven't I've only heard two episodes
So far. I think third one is now yet, but you like it as well
And this this is what I call what do I have a promo?
I had him curry. This is Walter Flange. Really really big fan from the Walter Flange show
I'm sending you this promo for my show and I've written a song
Sorry strange things have been happening around the home studio lately
I think it's possessed
Let me try this again
Walter Flange dot com
Roo check it out
I have to tell you fruit roll looks can't go down the garbage
Mom you've interrupted my promo
I'll play blue oyster cult for me. I'm not playing blue oyster cult
Do you hear that? Okay, seriously
There's something paranormal going on in this space
Since you know you were conceived in the parking lot at a blue oyster cult concert
Yes, and that information is haunted my days
Now, would you get kind of here and let me finish
Walter, all I want is to see you do your little show
Okay mom, you can say
Walter Flange dot com
Give me five
Put me next to Adam Curry on your whole drive
Don't fear the reaper on baby
I'm your man
Mom
Christ, what was that?
Oh my goodness, our new neighbor is upstairs
Sweet little lady probably walked into one of your heights
She walked into the light
Any chance is this house built on?
An Indian burial ground
Mom
Walter Flange dot com
Check it out
Alright, like it, like it very much
We're talking
Talking a David Epilito about getting Sid Bernstein to do a podcast
And you know, Sid Bernstein the guy who brought the Beatles to America
And he's still so incredibly interested and involved in new music
I like this would be great
Let's get this guy to do something with pod save music
I put the question to David
Here's part of the answer
Adam, you know, first of all, I got to say thanks so much for all the cool things
Just say about my stuff and the way I write and what I write and why
But I really don't have a choice in the matters
Just who I am
But I wanted to talk to you
I wanted to send you a sound file about your idea that you had about my buddy Sid
Doing a possibly a serious satellite radio show or a pod show
It would be really cool thing
And I floated a pest said because for years
I've been trying, I'm a nobody
But I've been trying to think of a way
To get Sid
He's still just passionate about young artists
He was the day that he brought the Beatles here
He managed the rascals and put the stones in Carnegie Hall
He's the same guy
He's just been around a little while longer
And he loves music and he loves young artists
So I asked him, I said, Sid, would you be interested in doing something on the pod show network
Would you be interested in doing a show that promoted new music and new ideas?
This is what he had to say
Yes, I would, I had learned from my good friend David and Toledo
What you're doing and it sounds like a great idea
And this is your show is giving circulation to no ideas to what matters today
And thank God for the internet
To express views that have to be expressed
You know, not getting the circulation that should be getting
But by daily press and from our commercial radio stations
I should do it as a heck of an idea
I'm an advocate of the idea
I've spent a lot of my musical life
And as a musician, I enjoy my musician
But I'm one who works with musicians
And part of my life has been doing courage
In the classroom life
I have been teaching at the New School for number of years
To encourage and to try to give publicity
In any way I can by voice to new people
Who need attention and who do not get it
Don't get the recognition
To writing in and a vocal talent
I like the idea so much
And I want to let my voice to it wherever I tap
Yeah, that is effing
Cool
So I'm going to talk with David E. Toledo tomorrow
You know, we've got some time zone differences, you know
And we're going to set this up
This is going to be, I mean, I'm thinking of maybe Sid says or something like that
Can you imagine if you put a microphone in front of that guy
I think it's a great, very mature, you know, very authoritative voice
And he's, and he can relate stories
But he can also, I think he can do a lot for pod save music
So David, I'm going to brainstorm a bit on that tomorrow
And then we'll get something going for sure
And then we have Sid Sid
Shows what we hear and see
On radio and on TV
And Sid Sid have you
What makes your last so tight
Does the religious rights rule over you
Those two fanatic fools
And you are outraged
Just rules kick
Freedom in my family
Just let Sid see
Have you
Are we also
Repressed
What's more
It's a press must be taboo
One journalist
Trots and boom
Watched up what's on
That's, I love that
If you want to hear, if you want to know exactly what the lyrics are
It's a little hard to understand, I think
Just like a lot of religious songs
Go to FCCFU.com
And you'll be able to see a video with a little bouncing ball that helps you
Join the fight to tell the FCC to FU
I've got to put that up a version for profit
FCCFU
Don't
I'm the next test drive girl
We're going to be test driving the Hummer H3
Hey Adam, it's all the test drive girl
Next time you're in San Francisco, we'll have to test drive Trinity
Oh, and by the way, folder
Why are you saying folder?
So much for tore the paper
This is a bunch of shit
Check out the test drive girl
Excellent
That's on that Pa choe
Plus great video of the test drive girl
Testing out any car she can get her hands on
I think the next one is the Hummer
It's just great to go with a camera
A Holly and Jay Donnelly
And they say hey, we just like the test drive this car
And they film it all
I'd love it
I've always dreamed of a show like that
Oh, oh my god
You know what happens with a satellite with camera, but Jesse stops by a satellite repair man coming after you
Satellite repair man, watching all of you
Can't fix your misconceptions and answer questions too
Turn nothing in the universe and you can't do for you
Satellite repair man
Well now here he comes, he's got something to report
Listen here, it's the best that you could hope to get from good old Uncle Jesse shorts
Is the biggest find is mess you've ever seen
Or it's the best from this week's pot of sphere
That might be what we really mean
Well it won't take long, but that's okay
It'll make you want to stand up and say I can't get enough
Out of Uncle Jesse shorts
No sir, so let's get right into Uncle Jesse's value packed
And very important, super sized
His Uncle Jesse shorts
That's right
Hello, Daly source code listeners
This is P-Dub, also known as Uncle Jesse
And I need some help
I'm working on our new show called Uncle Jesse shorts
And despite what my wife fries might tell you
It has nothing to do with me walking around the house
And boxers and black socks
Or favorite outfit
No, it'll be a show promoting all those great short podcasts out there
The ones that are usually 10 minutes or less
Well I've been trying to find as many as I can
And I've discovered that nobody has a directory
That can be sorted by average show length
Not even pod show
So while I have plenty of short podcasts that I'm aware of
It's going to be hard to track down the ones I don't know anything about
So if you do a short podcast that you would like to have featured on this new show
Drop me a link at playmy shorts at gmail.com
Playmy shorts at gmail.com
I have been a love short podcast
And they don't get the exposure they deserve
So send them to me and I'll try to get them up there on the satellite
And get you some new listeners
Thanks for the time Adam
Keep an eye on that satellite window
One, two, one, six, two, five
Six, three, five, seven
Hello Adam
It's my turn I have from the gentleman
We've been about on GSE465
About shadow falls
And doing a setup on it on pod show island
We're in the corner
I have to show out under it as a shadow falls
But I'd like to see if that's the thing expand a little bit
Wouldn't like to know how long I'll take it away
Because I do like the past
And I do love the palace and hang out there
So I'd like to see the shadow falls
thing a bit more in handstander
Expand a little bit
And I'll bring it to the waist out of ecstatics
Anyway, check out me get a show with a good name
She'll go and then.co.com
Scrunch out
Alright, dude, yeah, absolutely
And by the way apologies for the full paw
Last week when I was talking about this
So Brittany, I think it's you slam me
So you don't know we've had a shadow falls
Woods there for the longest time
And I'm talking about changing everything
You know, really changing everything
Having people whose avatars are
And our characters from the series
If you don't know what I'm talking about
Go to shadow falls.podshow.com
And you'll get quite an education
Audio drama is back
Theatre of the mind rules
And I think it's a great idea
But I do have to leave that up to my SLGF
Brittany Mason
She'll have to make the final call
And that because people do love the palace as well, you know
So hey, drop this number into your cell phone
And put the first get a plus in there
Because then that way if you travel outside the country
You won't have to reprogram the number
One
Two zero one
Six two five six three five seven
Notice I found the jingle again
Yeah, so whenever you have a question
That we can answer or address here on the Charlie
You just grab the phone and dial
Don't have to go to the show notes
Where the number of course is always listed
But it's handy to have around
I am and from my no body cast
I would like to thank you for playing
That palm line you show you me this is very popular
And I do
Oh yes, so are the ways of the pod father
Question
How does the plane get all of its power
Like all lightens
I'm like a
Get out of mind is it like an alternator
Because all I know is that it's a jet field
Which power is the engines
It's like an alternator
How does it get us power?
Because I don't think it could be
I find it at last that long
So play on the show
And all we have to hear the answer
You write by
That way
And I am in full of it
It's an interesting question
I don't know if it's an alternator
But if you're throwing jet fuel into something
That'll into a turbine that turns
Of course it can propel you
Also do a lot more with just a little bit of extra energy
So yeah
That's the same way it works
In piston powered planes
You've got gyros
And all kinds of stuff rolling around
Creating spark and creating electricity
It's pretty easy to tap into that
And use it
But of course you could be an airline pilot
And only use battery power
But you get some interesting results
Hello
I'm Mr. Robin with another cup that's called
On my way to St. Thomas today
That's last time
Kind of
Wonder and folder
Scruncher or cruncher
Instead I'm a folder
And a one time cruncher
So here's the scenario
Just imagine survival training
Out of the woods
Colorado
You've got to go
Do the paperwork
There is no paperwork
So
Got to use leaves
Pines straw
Whatever you can find
And that
Is crunching
It's long tailwind
Yeah tailwinds back at your Robin
Of course, inside works
And the diva cast
Up there
I think it's a
Fly 747's
So if you ever wonder
When you sit in there
Scrunched up
In your seat
Probably next to someone who
Does not belong in just one seat
And the guy in front of you
Was pushed to seat back
And crunched your laptop
Screen for the 20th time
You're wondering what the flight crew
What your flight crew is doing up there
Up at the front of the plane
They're worrying about important things
About what the rest
With branches and leaves
Yes, yes
This is podcasting
Exposing the true nature of the flyboys
Hi Adam
Hi
I'm Sam Idol
I'm really looking forward to seeing
Beatly caught ship being unleashed in the UK
Um
I was wondering whether you'd heard
About the floor
We just been around
Put cast
Paul
At the third number
The nice
Um
So we say
I'm too Islamic
Comment
And I've been quite a lot of
Comment friends
On his podcast website about that
I wonder if you'd heard about that
And what your opinion was
Um
Yeah
Very differently worth listening
There we go
With all your podcast
Paul dot com
And so that's it
Thank you so much for playing this comment
If you do
And
Um
I've become a folder
But I don't need quite no difference
Uh
If you give any website
They can tell me whether on the folders
Or scruncher please let me know
Okay
Thanks Adam
Uh
I think it's scruncher or folder dot com
This way you can find out if you are
And doubt is to
What the part of the population you belong to
The folders or the scrunchers
Regarding podcast Paul
Interesting
I haven't heard it yet
I am subscribed to podcast Paul
So I'll go and have a listen
And see what he said
And then maybe we can start a conversation
Sounds like someone tripped up
So it's going to be interesting
Controversy here in the UK
Keep your submissions coming
To btpodshow.com
Um
We've got this amazing amount of stuff
That's coming in a lot of videos
Stuff too
Just so much talent here
Just so much with no place to go
Can't wait
I think November is when we kick into high gear
Also next week
The digital music awards
Which pod show it's co-sponsoring
And
Of course
BT
British telecom is a sponsoring the show
I think we're going to be on the show
Which airs on channel for
I'll get all the details for you
I think that's Tuesday
Maybe October 4th
DMA06.com
All right
Why would you want more song here
Um
I saw this song
I hope that I find out about this
I'm just a sucker for a country song
Trendy Lane
When Angel's cry
I'm your daddy source code
Everybody
I'm all the directions
Right from the start
As you handed me your lines
I held back the tears
Until they had to fall
And I just watched you
While right at that door
You know I'm not that strong
And I don't want to cry
And any more
Now I'll be
Every beat of my heart
I knew I would lose you
Right from the start
But I came to realize
There's a power in disguise
In my life
With love dines
His God with the angels cry
When you close my door
I close one two
But there's still a window
You're waiting for you
If you say you're sorry
I don't want to
But there's still a window
You're waiting for you
If you say you're sorry
I will forgive you
Yes, I will
But there's still a thing
Now I just want to
I can love you
My whole life through
But I don't want to cry
Any more
This is a power
In disguise
You angels cry
Sorry
It's the yank in me
Trinity Lane
When angels cry
From the pod save music
Now work at music.podshow.com
That's it for today's show everybody
Be back tomorrow
Plenty busy week
We've got parts of the pod show
San Francisco crew coming in
Midweek
Wednesday or Thursday
Gearing up for the digital musical words
I said dma06.com
Porsons of today's podcast brought to you
By the accurate target cast for the
Architects SUV
Find that at accurate.podshow.com
And of course go daddy
If you want a great deal
A domain name
For 95
All you have to do is use the checkout code
dsc for Delta Sierra Charlie
Three
dsc three
And you'll get a great deal
And yeah
Whatever
All right
I got to get out of here
I got to help Patricia with some stuff
Got to call the reload
Got to do all kinds of things
I'll be back tomorrow
DailySourceco.com
Adam and podshow.com
Thank you
Thank you very much for listening
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
Get this podcast
And we're great ones like it
On the high performance podcast
Delivery network from podshow
And line-white networks
I love it