Already a hit state side. Now you can check out the following podcast and good old
blightybtpodshot.com single-handedly making a mens for giving you Madonna.
One show at a time.
The DSC 499, the big one, before the big one. Congratulations Adam.
And on Fubar Friday, nonetheless.
I'll tell you some people say you have to be crazy to do this many shows. I mean, 499 shows.
And I don't know, what do you think Adam?
Yeah. I was wondering if you can always understand
because sometimes it sounds a little rough. But anyway, as far as I know,
I'm in pocket. We're going to finalize plans. I think I just might go,
um, I don't know if I should go next week because next week is kind of like, you know,
I'm just not sure. I have half a mind. I have no idea why I said that. I'm spacing out a little bit today.
Okay, Lady Patricia, can you come help Adam and Q-the-music?
This is Delta, Sierra Charlie for online.
And after the song, Adam Kerry, who is a gay, um, blonde, is coming.
But first, Latin Italian secret, to speed up via girl absorption from 7 to 5 minutes,
it's enough to add splendors with enough of your key or coffee,
which you bring after my agrarian time.
We will be with the same vibe, so I'm feeling really right.
We're all in the moonlight, down at the healing ground, now I'm at the healing ground.
I've already done this wrong.
I've already done this wrong, now I've already done this wrong, now I've already done this wrong.
I've already done this wrong, now I've already done this wrong, now I've already done this wrong, now I've already done this wrong, now I've already done this wrong, now I've already done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong
now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now I've done this wrong, now traveled
I've already gone this wrong
Do I really miss y'all this wrong?
Can someone be found?
Now that I'm here around
It's only me if I have to leave
Don't worry about me
It's a must-bearing dream I'll go like I'm in this wrong
Right now that I hear it right now
Do I really miss y'all this wrong?
You got to be like me to recognize the name
But the music speaks for itself
Wishbone Ash on the pod save music network
How did we miss them coming aboard?
Fantastic
Of course they've been hugely successful all over the world
35 years I think their career
12 UK top 40 albums and still under leadership
Of guitarist and singer Andy Powell
They got a brand new album out planned destiny
Wishbone Ash
Kickin' off our footballer Friday
Everybody coming to you from a shopping wetsuri
The affluent suburb that is known as Gilford
And the curry cottage is really nasty outside
It is the daily source code episode 499 or 9 or 9 or
Moving up on that
I have no plans to celebrate it
But people are sending me so much stuff
There's no doubt I'm gonna have to do something cool with it
And I send you shit in I'm happy to play it all
And of course it's great because the lady Patricia is back
I know you're waiting for it to pipe in but she's not on the microphone
Now you know what this is what happens every single time
She goes away for two days and she comes home
And I've really done my best
I even prepped Christina I said look dude
You know I really went all out for you
You know I was supposed to be in London
And doing all the stuff through phones and taking you to the hospital
And just tell Mama was great and then I did a good job
Yeah
And the first thing Christina says is oh well you know I was a bit hungry
That's what she tells Patricia
And Patricia has to go around the house and has to inspect every single corner
And every inch and make sure everything's been done properly
And so she's still doing that
So maybe she'll maybe she'll walk in later on in the show
In the meantime we've got a lot of stuff to take care of
Because it is time once again
From my girlfriend Amy Mack
To help me slim my ass down
It's Amy Mack how are you?
Hey baby I'm good
I'm ready for some exercise
Today we're going to take the plane squats from a few weeks ago
And take them up and up
I'm going to get the other mic running
Why?
Because you're getting that good
Yeah right
All right switch my escape situated
Okay more over here now
That's right
I'm set
Are you ready?
Yeah what am I doing?
Okay
Feed a little wider than shoulder with a part
Okay got it
Toes pointing straight forwards
Straight forward
Now you're going to squat with your weight and the heels of your feet
And swing your arms down towards your knees
And then as you come back up
Jump
You're going to use your arms as well
I'm going to move all the way up
And then you come back down
I've got to watch Chandler
Slow controlled squat
Let me try it ready
And also when you land you want to make sure your knees are bent
And don't know the length
Okay
I think you have the idea
Oh I'm already started
Do eight
Ready go
And squat in
Jump
Eight
And squat in
Jump
Seven
And squat in
All your muscles to try to land squat
And jump
Six
Make sure those knees don't come off your toes
Even on the jump
Five
Use your arms as guidance and momentum
Jump
Four
And jump
Squat
Are you squeezing that booty?
Yes
Squat
Two
Last one
And jump
Great
All right
Okay that was an adventure
Oh man
That was your first day of super advanced squat
It sucks
See it doesn't necessarily get any easier
The more you work out
But it doesn't get boring either
No
All right
This is Amy Mac from Fitness Attack
And until next time
That's just
Amy
I wasn't prepared for that
Oh yeah
Holy crap
Yeah
Remember what football stands for my friends
Fucked up beyond all repair
Adam Paul here
Just a bit about your comment on Apple's deal
To install iPod Docs on the seats of a bunch of major airlines
So you said
So in essence what is being said is
If I understand the release correctly from Apple
Is that you'll be able to plug your iPod into your seat
And yes I find that interesting too
Especially when you say
Oh this is kind of interesting
Apple announced
That a whole bunch of airlines are going to support
Purchasing music
With your iPod on the plane
Because I couldn't find that
And any of the coverage about the proposed deals
What the articles are saying
Is that you'll be able to plug your iPod into the seat
And
Charge it
Play your own content on the larger screen
On the seat in front of you
And play your music through their noise canceling headphones
I agree with you
That the KLM spoke when this comment
Was funny and puts Apple in its place
Regarding KLM
But there are four other airlines mentioned
Besides KLM and air France
UAL corpse United Airlines seems to be quite keen on the idea in an article in the press room
On their site saying
From Chicago on November 14th
As part of United's plan to upgrade its international first and business class travel experience for customers
United and Apple have teamed up to add iPod connectivity to United's flights
Entertainment service
This connectivity will enable customers to plug in and charge their iPod
Watch movies and TV shows on their iPod using United's big screen monitors
Ooh
As well as listen to their entire music library on United's noise canceling headsets
That's all well and good
But your little mix of badmout
The airlines installing download capability is most interesting to me
This is where the real benefits are
This is huge dude
We have to talk about this
I'm in San Francisco
So when some guy you don't know tries to contact you next week
When you're here in town
Please try and remember me
Love the show
I hope Christina's knee gets better soon
Thanks from Paul at pdvd.wordpress.com
And oh
Find a scrunching
Oh scrunching roll
Paul, thank you very much
Yeah, and I went back and I read that release in your right
I made a mistake
But I tried to look for it
I have read another report that song purchasing would be possible
I guess the whole point was really is that Apple announced the KLM Air France F-Rolls
And it wasn't true
That's really what that was about
Personally, I don't know it's such a good idea
I mean the idea of being able to connect an external device
I mean what is the benefit really
You know
Are my headphones going to be less?
Let's put it the other way around
Well the headphones on an airline that they give me to use
Their noise canceling headsets
Will it be better than what I have myself?
Will it be better than earbuds?
Hmm
Okay, so maybe jacking your video into the screen
I don't know
It sounds like it's the marketing thing that no one really cares about
I just smite
Yeah, whatever
But
Can you tell I'm still a lot of breath
Hey, so yesterday
I've tried, you know, you know, I took
Pretend Christina to the doctor
And then we indeed had to go get an MRI
Which was a pretty interesting
Never seen an MRI machine before
It's basically a one huge unbelievably
Powerful magnet
That has a waiting room attached to it
And a cashier
It's a complete commercial business
Obviously
So we'll know in
Sometime next week
But I gotta tell you
I am a bit fearful
Then operation is going to be needed
To fish out some of the broken cartilage
By the way
I spoke to another
Another specialist
And this kind of stuff apparently happens with adolescent women
Quite a lot
That they throw the knee caps out and stuff
And apparently it's because their hips broadened out
And the weight distribution
Is all off and you have to get used to that
And it just seems to happen quite frequently with
Adolescent women as what I said
But I'll just say my teenage daughter
I'm a school friend and I'm a new kid
I'm just been listening to doctor
If you were a theory
Or is it going to be for the night
Yeah
I don't know what the NHS
I don't know if it's going to be for the health service
It's basically going to be the base
Or for that look service
I don't know if brands are going to be in play
And then the whole price comes
And it runs if you're over 16
And you're nursing full time education
If you're over 16
And you're in full time education
It's a lot of work to do
But the official fee may be gonna run right
No money or not
All the money is left
And I don't know the price and
The message and the micro
And WWWWBWBBBBBBBBBBBBBBBBBBBBBBBBBBB
I was right national health care service and pretty good though, you know, of course yesterday was a private visit.
Oh, 500 pounds for the MRI and it was a special deal.
They said, well, you know, since it really isn't busy, special deal, 500 pounds just for you sir.
I got a nice cup of tea and Christina got a nice cup of hot chocolate to go with that.
But it's interesting, I think, you know, our new Congress should...
Have you ever noticed how the Brits say Congress?
States we say Congress.
And here they say Congress.
Suttled differences, differences, but they're there.
When looking at a national health care system, look at what's happening here in the UK.
Very interesting.
Of course, the system is always bankrupt and lots of people complain and lots of people die
unnecessarily.
But I think if you really evaluated it and you look at all the waiting times that people, you know, have to endure.
But still get treatment.
I think it's probably a really good system.
I think the US could learn something from it.
You know, it's basic health care.
It really is.
And I don't know.
I guess the grass is always greener on the other side.
And it's funny how people here in Britain are always complaining about the national health care
system, about the health care service.
I just hear it everywhere.
I read it everywhere.
I see it on the news.
I think if you guys are so fucking lucky.
You know, at least you have some kind of health care system.
If you want to chime in, all you have to do is call our phone number.
Plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 16, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3, plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3.
That's so nice to hear all the Brits Calling.
Especially on that we've launched BTPodShow.com.
It seems like a lot of people are calling in and getting involved and paying attention.
Thank you very much for everyone who sent in comments that I had yesterday.
The question I had about the dialogue box folder settings in Windows.
Chris Murray told me what to do.
And essentially, see, I was thinking if you want to change something in the view of dialogue
box when you're trying to open a file from another application that you would change setting
in there, which you can do.
But apparently the way to do it is to open up a folder.
Let me see how I do that now.
You open up the folder and then you go to folder options and then you go to view.
And of course, you want to set the folder options the way you want to set it the way you want it.
And then you say, apply to all folders and then it works.
I have no idea how it got reset, but it did.
And thank you very much, Chris and others who sent that in to me because I was really lost.
It was taken me three extra clicks per edition to the playlist and cast blaster and really sucked.
Hi Adam, it's Archie.
I'm on the way home from work and I'm just catching up.
I've been around business and just catching up with some of the podcasts I've missed.
I've listened to two of yours on the back.
Back to back.
And I've just listened to three of Paul Nichols' podcasts.
136137 and 138.
There's one guy in the podcasting mode of the moment who deserves more credit to what he's doing.
It's Paul Nichols.
The Slavic Land Podcasts he's done this year and the Slavic Land Podcasts he did last year deserve an award.
This guy is amazing and I would encourage anybody out there who have listened to 136137
and 138 from Paul Nichols at www.podcastpod.com to go out and listen to them.
They are just incredible.
Thanks mate.
Have you had a good weekend?
Hopefully I'll see you on Saturday.
Yeah.
And yeah, no dude.
We'll definitely catch each other on Saturday for the podcast con UK podcast con.co.uk.
If you want to find out more about it, it's non-profit organization.
It should be a really good time.
And I'm definitely going to be stopping by.
And of course Roger Smalls tickets are at the wheel call office.
Just like Elvis at any rock show.
Oh, yeah.
Marcus couch checks in.
Cool.
Marcus couch from pod show music rewind and the scenes scene.
And I've got something pretty cool happened in this weekend on the west coast.
I'll be in San Francisco at Pod Camp West speaking on a panel this Saturday.
And boy, what a great panel.
This is going to be is the veteran podcasters share the tips and tricks.
We've got Michael Gohagan, J.A. Donnelly, Vic podcaster, yours truly Marcus couch
and Michael Butler.
We've also got Joe Klein, the broadcast legend and podcast voice guide doing the moderation.
It's going to be a fun time.
So come on out to San Francisco.
You can find out more information at podcampwest.com.
Hope to see you all out there.
Hey, since it's full bar Friday, I wanted to bring a little music to the party here.
Here's a band that I'm really stoked on.
This is live and trust with weighted.
We've got a lot of music.
We've got our songs.
We've got our songs, and our songs.
We've already have our songs.
Uh oh.
Oh, really yay!
Yeah oh, we're like,
you played as well too,
Yeah yeah, ya.
Oh, hey.
It's me, myself, you know I'm way too long to hold
I hold it my own and I can still feel all dancing with you
You know I'm way too long
You know I'm way too long to hold it my own and I can still feel all dancing
I can still take this mask off and let my guard down
With all our storm on the prone will fade
So now I've become so jaded and I'm tired of it
You know I'm way too long to hold out no more light
And I'm feeling it now
I've waited so long to find a place inside and I can finally be myself
You know I'm way too long to hold
I hold it my own and I can still feel all dancing with you
You know I'm way too long to hold I'm way too long to hold it my own and I can still feel all dancing with you
You know I'm way too long to hold it my own and I can still feel all dancing with you
You know I'm way too long to hold
And I'll think I'll be in love with this body
With this crazy sun I know I can finally be myself
You know what I'm waiting for long to hold
Oh world of my own, I know I'm so good
All that I'll see You know I'm waiting for long to find
This crazy sun I know I can finally be myself
You know I'm waiting for long to hold
These walls are my fault
And I can show you just what I'm waiting for
You know I'm waiting for long to hold
Marcus really knows how to crank up a food bar Friday
Thank you very much my friend. I was looking for that song in the podcast and music network for the show
No today the source code could not find it
So I just got a presumed that that's something special Marcus sent in for us
There you go pod show in London pod show in San Francisco
Lots of stuff going on
Oh, you know, I played the enormous penis song earlier in the week
And Antoine Adams, who I believe is from the Netherlands
Found a clip on YouTube. Here's something I got to remember to put in the show notes
It is the Da Vinci's notebook the guy who put the song up on the podcast and music network
And this time it's the entire song. I've never actually heard the whole song
And in this case they do it a capella
On a live radio show
Let me see if there's any information about where this was done
Of course not you know when people just upload shit to YouTube
But they never actually put any information in there. It says a live radio show
So I'm by Da Vinci's notebook
Let me just let you listen to this because it is so good not only the lyrics fantastic
You probably only heard just a portion of them
But also the arrangement and the way these guys sing this accapella just blew me away
I have in the studio very very excited to say hello to people listening all over the world
I don't want you guys to feel any pressure but people listening in the internet
Literally in every continent ships it's sea tuned in
That's fine as long as my mother doesn't listen
And all the rest of the Chinese people won't understand what I'm saying
Here we go
You don't know which way to go
Come on and take a walk in my shoes
Never worry about a thing
Got the world on a string because I've got the cure for all of my
All of his blues
I take a look at my enormous penis
And my troubles start to melt away
And the happy times are coming to stay
I gotta sing it on dance when I glance in my pants
And the time is like a sunshiney day
I take a look at my enormous penis
And everything is going my way
Salvation
And maybe thank you
Have a bit of chat
Send email to the youtube and I'll leave now
Help me
Just Bob and Tom, I'll take a look at my enormous penis and every time I come to see
Yeah, I got great big amounts in the place where it comes and the feeling like a sunshine
I take a look at my enormous penis and everything is going my way
I'm Bob and Tom now everything is going my way
Hey look at these coobers
I do I want
I guess it was the Bob and Tom show that
Those guys are so awesome. They should do more. They should do a whole album of stuff like that man
That's just awesome. Food bar Friday on the daily source code
Of course, so lots of Brits calling and don't forget you yanks are welcome to
One, two, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven
Ah, hey Adam, this is Paul Smith, though. There it is. We'll forward a
Hey, I got just a quick comment about the feeds for Pod Show
It seems like that's all that I've got mostly in my juice pod catcher
And it seems like all day long while I'm at work my little computer has been downloading all of your
All the pod show feeds and I'm not sure I guess something's happening on that side
Anyway, it came to my attention by my wife saying that
Gosh, the bandwidth is too slow. It's much lag
She was trying to download porn, dude. Anyway, we wouldn't want to interfere with that
Anyway, let us know what's going on with the feeds for Pod Show.
Thanks, love the show.
You know, I don't know. This is the kind of crap that can always happen.
We do an upgrade of something. The URLs that you're reaching should not have changed
It should be exactly the same. So it could be a pub date or something
Of course, juice is a very sophisticated pod catcher
Andrew Grummet, who works at Pod Show, was one of the original architects of the pod catcher
Normally known as iPodder, iPodder Lemon, now known as juice
I did receive, I think one or two other reports of this happening
Of course, it sucks tremendous ass. If all of a sudden it starts to download,
It shows that you've already had and slurp up your bandwidth
So we'll see if we can figure out exactly what happened
It must be something in the feed itself that has changed
Perhaps a pub date. I don't know. I'm sorry, I really am
Because I know how much of a pain in the ass that is
Particularly when you're trying to download porn, man, and your pipe gets all filled up
The series of tubes with truck stuck in the middle
Time for a new a new feature on our food bar Friday
They already threatened they would do it
Speaking of enormous penises, here is Chef Mark and Jennifer General
Adam, sweetie
You didn't really think Chef Mark was going to stay in your kitchen, did you?
Hey, I know which side my bread is buttered on
He's decided to return to mine instead
After all, I have better pots and pans
Oh, oh
Yeah, maybe
So Adam, we've cooked up something hot for your Friday
Welcome to finger-looking Friday with Jennifer
You know, and the talented kitchen virtuoso, Chef Mark
Since the weather's getting chilly here in New York
We thought we'd give you a hot little taste of Nolan's
With a special recipe for cafe brulo
It's a spicy fiery twist on coffee that's just perfect for a winter's night
You're going to need one quarter cup of cognac, a couple dashes of triple sack
Two cups of very strong hot coffee
By the way, I recommend folders gourmet selections espresso flavor for that
One teaspoon of lemon zest, one teaspoon orange zest
Two cloves, one cinnamon stick, a teaspoon of sugar
And of course some whipped cream to garnish
Brewed two cups of very strong coffee and keep it piping hot
Meanwhile, in a copper saucepan, mix the cognac, the triple sec
Citrus zest, cloves, cinnamon stick and the sugar
Gently heat the mixture on the stove to release the flavors of the spices and the citrus zest
Then you're going to flambay the liquor mixture and stir it gently
Meanwhile, prepare the two cups of hot coffee
Filter the cognac mixture, pour it over the coffee and decorate with whipped cream
And an additional lemon or orange twist if you like
Yes, you have to have whipped cream, or it's just not fun
You know, they might want to add some flavored splendor to it
Only if there are a scruncher, anyway
Check out chefmark at RemarkablePallet.podshow.com
And Jennifer is the mistress of foodfullossafee.podshow.com
Talk to you next week Adam
Have a great weekend, ladies
Happy cooking
Oh, Jennifer Jennifer with your pots and pans
You know, I kind of like doing this
Because it's something that when you're on your way home
Friday or maybe if you're on your way to do some weekend shopping on Saturday
You just take the podcast along with you and you don't even really have to write anything down or copy anything or print anything out
Which of course would also be nice if we had some show notes to go with the finger-looking Friday
Jennifer's pots and pans and marks enormous penis
You can just take it with you to the supermarket and just hit
Pause every single time you get an ingredient
Same thing goes for the actual
Creation of whatever it is they're talking about
Sound I could almost smell it really
Hey, uh, speaking of pots and pans Jennifer, do you think that I could grab your copper sauce pan one of these days?
What have we forgotten today? Oh, yes, of course
There's one very important thing we haven't done
Let's all give a dive
To the heart and for real
Surgery
Yeah
Yeah, what's up ACS just a time
The official night at musicologist of the Chacha
Hey, I figure if I'm a night that means that you're the king
I'm from what I understand the nights every once in a while had to go and pay tribute to the king
Or maybe hey, that's just a New Jersey mob in the bosses
But either way, I understand my place
And I was looking through the pot safe music network for this football Friday
And I realized it that you probably haven't played this artist yet
Her name is Louise Satara
She's 18 years old out of the United Kingdom
And she's just unbelievable and awesome
She's great. She's collaborated with ladiesmith Blackman Banzo
She's collaborated with Stains guitarists
And I'm just blown away by her
So from the pot safe music network, this is something a little different for football Friday
This is Louise Satara and her song, Wrong Again
Have a great weekend everybody, I'll check you later
You're going to really enjoy this song and check out her voice
I thought that in a sense would be it's own very well
In so powerless, I'm feeling my strength restored
I'm full and far enough to see which way to go
And I know I know I made it closer
This life won't lay me low
You thought I was broken
You thought that my time now ran out
Don't think for a moment
But my spirit's gone, you're wrong again
My spirit's gone, you're wrong again
But I found the will to carry on
And if you let us know, don't you be that strong
From the dead, oh, you're wrong again
Just when the darkness fell, my light began to shine
I could start to tell the dream that I caught mine
And I thought you feel myself, I'm losing my desire
And you understand, I need to take that
If you think that I'm alive, you thought I would love it
You thought that my time now ran out
Don't think for a moment, I spirit's gone, you're wrong again
My spirit's gone, you're wrong again
But I found the will to carry on
And if you let us know, don't you be that strong
From the dead, oh, you're wrong again
Just when the darkness fell, my light began to shine
Don't think for a moment, I spirit's gone, you're wrong again
Don't think that you know, don't you be that strong
I found the will to carry on
And if you let us know, don't you be that strong
From the dead, oh, you're wrong again
Oh, yeah, only 18 from the UK, her name is Luis Satara
She's actually beautiful, I'm looking at a picture in the positive music network
Iris Brazilian and English descent
Her brain, her debut album, still waters, very nice
Influences, Arita Franklin, Alicia Keys, Jostone, Jostone
Last night there was, and it really sucked because of course I was watching
I'm a celebrity get me out of here, so I missed the first, almost the first half of the UK Music Award
UK Music Hall of Fame
I think it was a live broadcast, oh, this was so good
And it was a lifetime achievement award for Dusty Springfield
who I'm a huge fan of
And Jostone came out and did a son of a preacher man
And she did it on, you know, just a short kind of like blue dress,
a bare feet and she walked throughout the entire audience
And just sang her ass off, it gives me goosebumps just think about it again
It was so incredibly good
And then, and this just blew me away
And remember, yesterday I was talking about production about music production
Sir George Martin, who of course is responsible for the entire Mercy Beat Sound
Very famous obviously for the work he did on the Beatles
He produced so many different artists throughout his career
And he received a lifetime achievement award
And I wish Patricia were here because she's a hung out with him in Malta
In the song contest days
So I'll have to get that dirt from her next time, I guess
But then he did three Beatles songs
And they had an all-star band, they had a huge orchestra
I see who was on drums
On drums was the name Roger Taylor from Queen
I don't remember who was in there
But it was clearly and Sir George Martin was conducting this orchestra
And when you listen to that and you heard the sound
This unbelievable every single piece filled to the right amount
Every just close your eyes even and it sounded so incredibly good
This guy really was the Beatles sound
No kidding, no fool and it was so good
It just has like, oh man, I do miss, I do miss that
And of course it's tremendously expensive to do that with live instruments
But just wanted to say it was a beautiful, beautiful thing
Really, really wrapped up the week just perfectly for me
What the hell is it today?
It's Friday
Well, you can almost know what's coming
If you live with someone in sin or if you're living in holy matrimony
Or if you just have some kind of social agreement
Think about your spouse because when you really evaluate your living situation
And you see what your spouse does to keep the house running
You should really appreciate that stuff
You don't think about it a lot because life just goes on
But just two days, you know Patricia went off, she did her own thing
Which I'm real happy about
Really glad that she's enjoying
Her strictly come dancing, a competition dancing with the stars
But boy, once again greater appreciation for all the shit she does to keep this place running
Because of course it was up to me and I had to do it
So, um, living together, living in sin, social agreement
Think about the stuff your spouse does and appreciate them
And give them a lick from me this evening
Will you?
That's it everybody
I guess Monday will be episode number five hundred
Get your crap in now, get it in early
If I
If I don't see a podcast con UK, that means you didn't come or you don't live in the UK
And of course, we'll be back here on Monday
Have a fantastic weekend
Take care everybody, bye-bye
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear