Delta Sierra Charley, 34-2.
Let us pray. Our pod father who art in England, Adam B. Ly name, thy pod cast will come,
as thy download will be done on serious, as it is on iTunes. And give us this day, our
daily Charlie, our metro-sexual moment, and a glimpse of our dear Trinity, and lead us not
into temptation, but deliver us from unsubscription. For thine is the pod cast and the pod safe
music, forever and ever, tailwinds.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I never think everything will be, I never think all I saw was me.
But while making beds a new kitchen stand, just be in the future, God rush.
Let's see how new we'll match and let the chill easy came out of the dark.
Is that another look and did you mean what you meant when I thought that you meant
you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you
You don't know what that kind of thing is you meant this means that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant about the you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant what you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you because that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant because you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant that you meant
Oh, the future misses me!
Thanks for the drink.
But my boyfriend is right over there.
Imagine any man's magic went to town.
He's even in town with eyes.
Yeah.
I'm feeling nervous.
I'm in a hard drive.
Cool water's ban.
Two car garage.
Comes to you from the pod safe music network.
On your Charlie.
A daily source code.
Hey everybody.
How you doing?
Welcome.
Back here in the cottage.
At the wonderful podcast complex.
Always so happy to stand in front of this thing.
It is so the perfect height.
It makes such a big difference.
Well, I'm back.
But only for a couple hours.
It is Monday morning here in the United Kingdom.
So for the affluent suburb of Surrey in the UK.
I am off around.
See what my flight is around.
Two o'clock this afternoon going to Amsterdam.
No, no flying myself.
Unfortunately, seeing as the assessment of the Delta Sierra is almost done.
In fact, the wind commander called me up on for was it Saturday morning.
As I was said, before I left from San Francisco and he said, dude, I've flown it.
It's like a sewing machine.
So quiet, no vibrations.
Which is apparently a big thing after you take an engine out and put it back.
And now we're just waiting for the for the new chairs which have been re-opholstered.
But the seats, I should say.
And then I'll be able to fly myself.
So I was just going to be with Stelios today with the easy jets.
Because tomorrow is the big lawsuit.
This is the one that that I've been preparing.
Well, I guess my lawyers have been preparing for.
Although most of folks who listen to the show know what I'm talking about.
Just a quick recap of that.
A few weeks ago, a gossip magazine published
Pictures.
A huge front front cover, which was one of their own pictures.
They took a Patricia as they followed her around the UK.
How disgusting is that.
And they got her pushing a cart of groceries, which of course always looks so lame.
According to at least the picture they took.
So life is horrible here for the for the ladies.
Well, Adams often San Francisco was the whole gist of it.
And they followed my daughter and of course published the name of her school.
And how how she gets there every single day that was really nice when it comes in
Dangerment of a child.
But probably the thing that is most provable and most offensive according to the law is the the theft of
Pictures that I'd posted on flicker.
Which, of course, is all under creative commons.
You can select that.
It's self-selectable.
And I use the share like non commercial attribution license.
And they felt that just because it's said this picture is public.
If you look at how flicker works, it's pretty evident that public means something very different
than go ahead and copy this and use this for profit in your magazine.
And they did about three, three pages of my own pictures.
So we're off to go improve that the creative commons license does hold value.
And by the way, my life in the Netherlands with my wife and daughter is very valuable.
We've proven that in the past.
We've made millions of dollars on our own reality show.
Which, of course, we also entirely did ourselves.
And you just can't be doing that.
And this is all about the arrogance of mainstream media.
You know, thinking that if you publish something on your own weblog or on your side or on flicker,
or wherever you publish it, that it therefore automatically becomes public domain.
Well, I guess we shouldn't be trying that with your shite.
Now, should we?
Funny enough.
So literally they, they entered their documents.
I guess, you know, their defense documents, which, of course, we get a copy of.
And literally what they're saying is, well, look, you know, they circle this little thing on a little copy,
print out of a page of flicker and says, it says this picture is public.
Which means we could take it.
That's going to be interesting to see them prove that.
And then there was a whole transcript.
I mean, an entire long form written out transcript of Delta Sierra Charlie of the source code.
We talked about this and what my lawyers were going to do with them.
So they're going to enter that is saying, Curries are really not a nice guy.
And he doesn't deserve any retribution.
It's just crazy.
And let me, let me tell you, I really despise this shit.
I really do not like going to court.
I'm a guy who likes to settle and get things over and done with.
Because the only people who win at this game at the end of the day are the lawyers.
And I do like them very much.
I got nice lawyers, but, you know, they're always winning in all these things.
So anyway, so getting the bump in this show out as quick as I can, then hopping on the plane.
So don't really actually get into Amsterdam until like five or five thirty.
And then I'm just going to chill.
I'll be able to hook up with everyone at the office in San Francisco since we're getting so close to.
I think another hundred or a hundred people in to try and, you know, start test out the stuff that we've been working on for the past,
I don't know, six months, more than half a year at this point.
And then Tuesday morning, I'll get up really early before the case and I'll do the show for Tuesday.
So you won't, I'll probably post something on the weblog, depending on, well, I believe I'm getting an answer or a result or some kind of judgment on Tuesday itself.
So I'll post that and then, of course, Wednesday will actually have all the details in the show.
And along with that, we'll have Metro sexual moment because I've got just tons and tons of stuff to do in the, in the moment.
Trinity stuff as well. It's going to be a pretty busy week and they'll be nice because I'll be home for for a few days.
Something really exciting coming up on March 12th, Christina is doing her first runway appearance.
She'll be in a fashion show with another young lady who's the daughter of, I think, a famous model who used to be a famous model.
Well, I'll get all the details from Patricia. We'll have her on later in the week and she'll, she'll talk about stuff and it's going to be fun. I'm happy to be back home.
It's good to be here with the girls hanging out.
Whether's not too spectacular. It's typical, you know, England weather kind of gray overcast.
It's chilly, definitely a lot cold in San Francisco, but the sun does peep through once in a while.
Regarding Podsake Music Network, music.podshow.com. That's where the cool waters band came from.
Later on in the show, we'll roll out a Matthew Ebal song.
Matthew Ebal is joined the beta test along with American Heartbreak, Michael Butler's Band.
And you can actually purchase those tracks online. Lots of feedback. Really appreciate it.
Again, this is not, you know, this is not like we've launched some store and come on and check it out. We're going very slowly.
Trying as best as possible to integrate the, the, how the whole experience of signing up for.
For our partner, clicking by who, you know, a lot of people have some comments. They do things in a different way.
Addresses are entered in a somewhat stranger way, but they're very open to working with us so we can really streamline this whole process.
I'll tell you, these guys, clicking by really are the best we found when it comes to the processing fee.
And also the type of data that we could pass off back and forth between them and us, which, of course, doesn't include any, any credit card information or anything like that.
But so far, we've, we've sold, I know more than 100 tracks combined of Podsake for peace.
And people, I guess, are already found Butler stuff and Matthew Ebal stuff. And so, I would think that once we get the reporting structure in place.
For every single sale for this entire beta period, which I'm just pegging it about three months, 100% of everything minus the transaction fee, which is nine cents goes to the artist.
So, you really helping out by participating in the beta test and just give us the feedback. You know, a lot of us know how we can improve it.
What we can do to make it better and we're on it.
Got an email from Martin Hendrix. Adam, I'm 28 year old teacher from Belgium. I do a regular podcast with the kids in my class at www.mace.
Mike echo, echo, Sierra dot, W.S. Whiskey, Sierra.
We do a weekly show in which the kids recite poems, tell jokes, read stuff from newspapers, the kids are between the ages of 10 and 12.
A few weeks ago, I started to, Andy, show with the Podsake tune.
And since yesterday, the kids and every other listener are able to rate a Podsake tune, but clicking on little flame icon next to the title in the show notes.
They really did this feature. And a few more weeks, I'll be putting out a top 10 of Podsake tunes on the sites as rated by the kids.
This could be really interesting getting a kids perspective on the Podsake music. I completely agree, of course.
And he was the interesting question. Are you planning an API on the Podsake music network?
This could be really useful because my kids who speak Dutch can't interact with the PMN now.
Is that because there's no API and what would the API be for?
Or is that a language thing? I mean, just reading your email, Martin, first of all, I think it's fantastic that you're doing this.
Let's get, let's educate kids very soon, very early on about music.
And that it's more than about buying a CD or downloading a track from iTunes because you've heard it on the radio and the videos have been jammed up your ass.
Thanks to many music channels.
Perhaps what you should do is put together a Podsake top 10 that your kids put together.
And maybe that you have each intro their favorite one or maybe you act as a conduit in that.
And let's highlight a show like that. I'd love to have.
And this is the great thing about the PMN is that we have, I don't know, we have at least four or five different top 10s.
That's great. It can be the top 10 of what the Dutch kids in your class think it is. There's nothing wrong with that at all.
And I tell you, you can't just take billboards list and make a top 10 because you'll get sued.
So we have our own list and the nice thing about it is there's all kinds of ways to look at what's a top 10 about.
So looking forward to it.
Big news in the UK today.
George Michael was a, this is so sad.
George Michael was apparently found in his car, slumped over his steering wheel.
And I guess someone who saw him around four in the morning, this was in London.
You know, said, oh man, this guy's probably been taken ill.
So called the cops and the turned out it was George.
And he, I guess he just kind of passed out and they found marijuana in his car.
And what they believe on this is just what the newspapers report would be ecstasy.
And I think they, they specifically said liquid ecstasy. So that would be what MDMA.
But all the newspapers this morning.
They're so creative and so clever.
So big headlines front page, the careless spliffer.
And then there was another newspaper had skinned me up before you go go.
So he got arrested and he was released and I'm sure it'll be okay.
But let it go.
Please let the poor man go.
Boy, oh boy.
Okay. I got some promos for you.
A couple more things.
One chat about us as I said, some pod safe music.
And I'm just barreling to get out of here because there's so much.
I mean, my head is just boggling with all the stuff that's got to happen this week.
But I'm very happy you tuned in once again for the ride.
The disease is lethal.
It is contagious.
But this disease spreads by sound.
When you hear the voices, it's already too late.
You listen to birth core and you were exposed.
You listen to ancestor and the disease germinated.
It's already too late for you in five weeks.
You will be another victim of the infection.
Infection.
It's the horrifying new podcast novel by Scott Siggler,
All the revenge, sister and earth core.
Sign up now at ScottSiggler.photshow.com
Or subscribe directly at
Thanks.phiburner.com
For slash Scott Siggler.
The infection kills you slowly.
If the cure doesn't kill you first.
Hey there, this is Michael Odee from Most People Our DJs.
A weekly music interview is podcast.
When I let you know, the month of March will be a special one for Most People Our DJs.
As I'll be playing with permission, my music heroes like Gary Newman,
President Lloyd Cole and Stan Ridge Way.
And also talking about other artist writers that influenced my outlook on life.
So join me in reviewing the latest comics, magazines, TV and most anything else,
while playing great in the alternative music.
Everyone's a critic and most people are DJs.
Especially me, Michael Odee.
You can find my show it www.MostPeopleourDJs.com
Hi Adam.
It's Derek Kay Miller from the pen machine podcast at podcast.penn machine.com again.
And first I have to apologize.
Back on DSC 339.
I tried to tell you how to run your show.
I'm sorry, man.
I really am.
I shouldn't have done that.
I mean, I'm sorry.
Nevermind.
On that show, you played a promo for my wife's new podcast at
lipglossanlaptops.com.
And she and her co-host Karyan have since recorded their first episode,
which they're putting up on March 1st Wednesday.
And in it, they asked a question that I think DSC listeners
might want to hear.
They may call these kissing potions and kissing glasses and etc.
And what I was doing my research for the show,
I actually put on one that was called Kiss Gloss.
And I kissed my husband to see what sort of reaction he would have.
And he thought it was horrible.
But I thought maybe if I was wearing a meat-flavored lip gloss,
you know, like bacon or sausage or beef,
it might be more appealing to him.
Because they say the way to a man's heart is through his stomach.
So I don't know.
Maybe that's another marketing angle that no one thought of yet.
And well, perhaps you need to do some market research on that for our next podcast.
You know, like a lip gloss shaped like a fun burger or a fun hot dog.
And we're just stuck on some sausage.
Then kiss your husband.
He sounds so disgusting.
So, well, I'll have to listen to the rest of the episode to see how that went.
But I'm just wondering,
what listeners of the Charlie think of that woman,
man, would a meat-flavored lip gloss be appealing?
Because, you know, at first I thought, no.
And then I thought, you know, thought of myself as a man,
and I thought, hmm, I like bacon.
So anyway, their podcast is lipglossonlaptops.com.
You can listen to it March 1st,
maybe leave a comment there.
And I'll talk to you later.
Lipstick and laptops.
Was it lipstick and laptops.com?
Dude, I'm totally, I'm totally, this is a,
it's really nice, actually,
that I'm getting so much feedback on the Metro sexual moment.
But you can call the Metro moment for sure, if you so, please.
And I'm getting a lot of feedback from women who realize that now,
we've created this little corner, little area,
a little virtual place where we guys hang out.
And we talk about all the stuff that we're embarrassed to talk about in public
or at the office or at school or.
Certainly in the locker room.
And I like it because I guess what women are catching onto is that,
you know, there is an interest as to what women want from us.
And there's obviously quite an interest of what women want.
I just said that.
Hold on a second.
Let me get my careless spliffer going.
That should help.
So, I don't know about about meat flavored lipgloss.
Lipgloss.
I agree.
I too like bacon very much.
But I don't know if the bacon lipgloss would do it for me.
And by the way, this is how we work at Pod Show.
So, you know, you sent in this probe.
I actually thought the podcast was already on.
You sent in a promo.
Or no, when you told me that this would be great to play in front of the Metro sexual moment.
I went looking for the podcast.
And of course, the promo was there.
That's what you sent in.
But immediately, I had an idea because I know that there's a sponsor.
A sponsor looking for that type of audience, which I think the show will have.
We need to get a couple shows under our belt to find out what your audience is and we need some feedback on it.
But we're in motion, dude.
And you probably will get a call from Richard over at Pod Show.
I told him to get in touch with you.
He was off of the podcast hotel this weekend in Seattle, which I here went really well.
So, we can see if we can hook that up.
That would be very cool.
One more, here we go.
Yeah, I'm Curry.
This is Andrew from the DJJ podcast.
Well, I thought I'd leave you coming, much you know, you know?
Your shows.
It's not half bad, not half bad whatsoever.
So, I subscribed.
You're on iTunes.
You get play on my iPod and cool stuff like that.
And well, I thought it was a new comment and I might be coming over to my side at
AJForkstiles and dot com.
Tell you to check it out.
Just tell you, you know, it's all good.
Love the show.
Keep it going.
It's all good.
All right.
Nice.
Oh, he's good.
Here's something really interesting I learned.
We had a meeting last week.
And I was probably on Thursday since that's why I didn't do a show on Friday.
So, I didn't have time to tell you about it.
I've learned something very interesting about email when it comes to large services or services in general.
Something I really didn't know is that you essentially, if you want to have any type of verification service,
meaning you sign up for something and then an email gets shot out to you.
You click on the link or you know, or even if you just request a password or any of that stuff.
The more you send, the more likely you are to be finagled into this trap of the white lists on ISPs.
And I had no idea that this was, this was really such an issue,
but apparently, lots of ISPs in particular hotmail and MSN mail.
Of course, under the guise of combating spam, they blacklist a whole bunch of,
you know, and I guess it depends on the content, which would make sense.
You know, if you have a registration email, of course, it's pretty easy to figure out that it's a registration email.
So, you know, they're scanning that for spam.
And then they put you on a blacklist.
Currently, and I think it is with hotmail. I'm not sure about MSN.
If I send you an email to, you know, to your hotmail address, it won't arrive.
Because that is, if I'm sending it from adamatpodshow.com.
Now, we certainly have not done any email marketing whatsoever.
We've only done signups for the pod save music network of which Chris Rockwell usually has to,
manually approve what is it like 40 a day?
Because these emails go out and they bounce back because they get trapped in all these ISP email boxes.
Well, guess what? There's a way around it.
And there's about three or four companies with names like Suremail or Sure Delivery or whatever.
And they charge you a fee to make sure that you're on the white list of all of these ISPs.
Everyone has to do it.
Anyone who has any type of registration service that has any type of volume has to go through this.
And, you know, I was just blown away when I heard what the fee was.
Now, of course, you can do this yourself, right? You can, you can put it all together.
And, and call the ISPs yourself, but, you know, just take the service it'll cost you less.
And if you're listening to serious right now, you won't hear how much money that was because the satellite window just closed.
80,000 dollars. Can you believe that 80 grand?
80 fucking grand.
You know, to be able to just send registration emails, what?
I mean, I don't know if it's a setup, per se, although I must say,
a Microsoft through Hotmail and MSN only lets you use one particular provider who basically works directly with the ISPs.
You know, and they ensure they say, okay, this is not span, this is a registration email.
So these guys go on the white list.
So you have to get the 80,000 dollar service, which I'm sure is negotiable at some point.
And then you have to get an additional service just for the Microsoft, the Microsoft mail addresses.
Come on, what a fucking scam.
This is just the beginning.
Now, I had no idea this was going on.
Apparently it's really normal, and anyone who has a service with signups is aware of this.
But, you know, next, of course, what is coming.
I'm telling you, it's coming.
You're reading about this stuff already, probably, about SBC, which, of course, is AT&T.
And all the huge telco saying, you know what?
We're going to be able to really fast internet next to the internet as we know it today.
And we're going to charge companies like Google and Yahoo, and I'm Amazon and eBay and pod show.
I'm sure, to use the network.
Oh, my goodness.
That'll kill a whole bunch of innovation if you start changing the, excuse me, since I'm drinking one right now.
So good to be drinking one.
You know, if you change the level of the playing field, that's, that's, oh, it's so wrong in so many ways.
And, you know, and this, this is just another piece of it.
You know, you can, you can't start a little company by yourself, and actually be successful.
If you have email-based registration signups, because you have to wind up being 80 grand.
Something very, very wrong with that.
And I've had an ongoing email combat thread for over a year now with Rohir Rosert.
It was from, uh, pop, pop, pop off from the Netherlands.
And, uh, he said, Adam, congratulations.
I owe you a beer or something else that you might fancy, because he's been tracking how many hits podcast.
The word podcast has on Google.
If you remember at BloggerCon 3, which was, uh, only about not even a year and a half ago,
Google did not recognize the word podcast.
It still doesn't, and it's, uh, Gmail, spell checker.
I just might add, um, in fact, Google at the time would say podcast,
Did you mean broadcast?
Which was funny.
And just recently, just, uh, just last week, we surpassed 100 million hits.
Let me just say that again.
100 million hits for podcasting.
God damn it.
Play.
That was nice.
Oh, shoot. This is, for some reason, what the hell is that?
That's weird.
Came up as the wrong track.
Oh, damn it.
Dammit.
Curses.
Hate it when that happens.
Let's try.
So maybe this one will work.
Green room radio.
Yeah.
Okay.
This came in while I was in New York, but just wanted to play it.
Because it was so nice here.
Check it out.
Hey, Adam, how are you?
This is Eric Bergen from the green room radio podcast that we're at greenroom radio.com.
We're broadcasting live from, uh,
20th and 7th.
That's right.
Chelsea Manhattan, New York City.
Welcome to New York.
Adam, a see on, uh, curry.com that you came in tonight.
I'm glad you made it in safe.
How about that snow?
You know, that's the worst thing about New York.
I hope you brought your, uh, your, uh, uh, boots because the day after we get snowfall,
it's the worst.
You can't walk anywhere in the city.
But you try.
And then you fall down.
Hey, I just wanted to point out a funny thing that happens to me today.
You know, I'm an actor.
So I have to go around to all these places and audition.
So, uh, I'm walking in today.
I'm walking up to Times Square.
And, uh, I hear my name mentioned on your podcast because I was, uh,
finishing Friday's podcast, which I hadn't finished over the weekend.
So I was listening to the rest of it that I hadn't listened to yet.
And, uh, all of a sudden, the list of use biddies came on.
And they mentioned my name.
And they played a piece of their, uh, a podcast.
They did a, uh, I think two weeks ago or a week ago,
where they went to this Monday night hangout called Jim Crusoe's
last party.
And I ran into them there.
And I met them there.
And we started talking about you.
And they recorded it.
And I believe they, uh, you played a little bit of that on the last,
last Friday's show.
Where we talked about if we would sleep with you or not.
Well, I just wanted to say that the biddies in their promo only played the part
where they talk about if they would sleep with you.
They didn't talk about if I would sleep with you.
And I guess you'll just have to tune into, uh,
their podcast to see what my answer is.
Just saying.
Yeah, so that was funny that as I was, uh,
pulling up, uh, to 15 15 Broadway,
that's right.
The MTV building is when I realized that hey,
I'm listening to Adam Curry.
One of the people who started MTV.
Well, you didn't start MTV.
But you had a process.
And you know what I mean?
Never mind.
Anyway, I just thought that was funny.
You know, walking into MTV and you being in,
and empty, the, the, the,
making sense.
No, I don't know.
Something.
Whatever.
Um, so yeah, that's it.
Check out www.greenwareradio.com for all your arts and entertainment.
Needs.
I'm Eric Bergen.
And, uh, I have some gas.
So the bathroom.
All right.
Eric, thank you.
Complete non-secretor.
Very unimportant stuff.
I appreciate it.
Makes me feel real good.
I'll be bringing along the, uh,
the love microphone just to, you know,
for space constraints.
Only taken the, uh,
the portage laptop.
Still running cast blasts or running, uh,
beta 60 now, which, uh,
apparently removes the warball from some of the songs played.
Um,
and actually the interface is a little bit different too.
I'm liking it very much.
Um, that has a bunch of tabs.
And you can do all kinds of stuff that I was already thinking of asking about rewind all clear all.
Ah, it's just, it's really,
it's nice, man.
It's coming together very, very nicely.
And, uh, I actually considered a couple times,
now that the Mac is fixed,
that audio crap that, uh,
that they didn't tell us was broken and didn't really cop to and told us to use one application.
Well, they fixed it with the latest update.
Um, but I, I don't know.
I'm just so digging cast blasts are just kind of going,
it's got it all going on for me.
It's really easy to manage the show.
That's a big part of it.
It's not just being able to produce it.
Um, while you're actually doing it,
but to be able to manage it pre and post is,
is pretty damn cool.
Um,
what's that thing called, um,
as a Mac program that's being,
that someone that some German guys are working on,
Uber Castro, which looks really slick.
I mean, they've integrated every single bit of Mac interface that you can think of.
But I don't know if it's going to work at all for production,
because sometimes you just need a somewhat simpler,
almost dumb or way of doing things.
Um, and, and that simplicity is when I'm digging cast blasts right now.
Without a doubt, past week,
uh, during doing shows from San Francisco,
the absolute highlight of the week when it comes to audio feedback,
was the piece called, I hate Adam.
And just in case you didn't hear it,
I want to play it for you one more time because it makes me smile every time I hear it.
Good evening.
I'm Arthur Sandwich of Strange Brain Radio.
I'm an avid listener of Adam Curry's daily source code,
more recently known as The Charlie.
As of late Mr. Curry has become somewhat perplexed and distressed,
by the growing volume of his detractors,
and the relentless attacks upon him.
Well, Adam,
since you appeared to be clueless in this regard,
I've compiled the list,
of why you are so despised.
I now give you the top 10 reasons why we hate Adam Curry.
Number 10,
he used to work at MTV when MTV was still cool.
And as host of Headbanger's ball,
arguably, he had the coolest job at MTV also.
Number 9,
he is married to a beautiful former pop star,
who drives a lot of fun.
He is married to a beautiful former pop star,
who drives a Jaguar and has her own cosmetics company.
Number 8,
he's gorgeous.
Over six feet tall with roguish,
good looks and a full head of thick blonde.
You know,
fuck the list.
I'll tell you what I hate you, Adam Curry.
You're always prancing about.
Look at me, I'm Adam Curry.
I can speak five languages.
I fly planes and helicopters.
Look at me, I'm Adam Curry.
I've partyed at the MTV Beach House,
and the Playboy Mansion.
I'm Adam Curry.
I commented podcasting.
I was in a movie with Sean Penn,
and Elizabeth Herley.
And I was also in Truth or Dare with Mandala.
I had my own TV series.
I'm so rich and bloody fucking successful in popular.
I've got my own stalker.
And, and if that wasn't enough,
my last house, my last house was a fucking castle.
You've got some sort of magnet of vacuum
that sucks away all the good fortune
that was intended for the rest of us regular guys.
You're taking more than your fair share.
Well, fuck you, Adam.
Fuck you and the plane you flew in on.
Headwinds, headwinds, Adam.
I watched my hair back.
You selfish bastard.
What?
Well, I wouldn't do this.
Check out Strange Brain Radio
if you want to hear me or more of that good stuff.
Oops.
Slip in my dutch in there already.
Thank you very much, Mr. Rusty Bender.
Loved it, loved it, loved it, loved it.
Yesterday when I came home from the airport,
what did I land at like 1030?
I was on your home around 1130, 1145.
I could have sworn I saw a mini Cooper drive.
But we weren't a cul-de-sac here.
So I could have sworn I saw a mini Cooper drive
the other direction.
And I'm not sure.
But you know, just referring back to that,
I've got my own stalker thing.
That could have been, I didn't really see the driver that well.
Because I only really realized it.
I look at the, I mean, a mini Cooper is nothing,
nothing special to think about or you know,
when you notice one.
But it is if it's one of the older models.
So you have the new ones, which are,
I guess, comparable to a Volkswagen Golf,
really just a small version of it.
But the old fashion mini Cooper's,
they do stand out these days because they are definitely
our, you know, it's historic.
You look, I said, oh, there's a goes and old mini Cooper.
And at the very moment, I'm like,
don't tell me that was Roger Smalls.
So I haven't heard from him.
And no emails have shown up with pictures.
So hopefully I'm wrong.
But Roger, just do me a favor.
We're going to have lunch.
I promise you, just give me a couple days
to get turned around, get done with my stuff.
And Amsterdam, you know, then we'll hook up, okay?
I promise you.
And maybe not, you know, maybe not in the next week,
maybe in the next couple.
We're going to hook up, just, you know,
please don't wait for me at home.
Sad news.
Last week, don knots.
Of course,
most people know him as deputy Barney Fife
on the Andy Griffith show.
I'm a, I even I'm a little bit too young
to really witness that, you know,
that show the way, you know, some do,
particularly because we left the United States
when I was seven.
So the reruns kind of already were,
I guess, taking place at that point in time
in the early 70s.
But he passed away.
He was 81 years old died Friday
of respiratory complications in Los Angeles.
And Todd Walktell was nice enough to send me
a little piece of audio that he picked up
from the Pod Safe Music Network,
which is titled The Ballad of Barney Fife.
And I figured, you know,
if we're going to play any,
play any type of homage to Don knots,
we might as well do it in the way that we know how.
This is the Ballad of Barney Fife.
Don't fret, nine girls old Barney
got a wife.
You know,
now this year's the Ballad of Barney Fife.
Don't fret, nine girls old Barney
got a wife.
But he knows how to speak.
One bullet's killing me.
If we look at it,
it's worth her talking.
And my mom picked the ball right.
Well, you've made your papers right hand, man.
And he's the bad at deputy of Babyland.
While you could ask any one right,
you're on my right, but you're in space to learn.
And even what you can do,
down to the dining.
Oh, boys, please.
You don't want me to.
The Ballad of Barney Fife is a bad afternoon.
You're the little bed and I'm giving them a move.
Ooh, the fence here's justice,
and she rules the setters.
Even if she comes in,
and Barney Fife knows you are a man too.
So we got comes the time act,
and all cities,
big, well-barned signs,
up to my sister's.
I ain't no ordinary,
he kept you there.
You better watch your step,
Mister,
because I'm here to uphold the law.
Now it's my job with the law,
and he's talking,
and I'm holding on.
So with the whole load,
this is out on a bench.
The movie Barney and Andrew Empress
spend with their women in the football club.
Will O'Barny, he's always swallowed the bone.
And I like making rules on it.
Barney Fife is a bad day.
Women who's better than I'd give him in the mood.
For dispensing justice,
he's the truth.
He's going to see the people in Barney Fife.
I'm scared.
It's a great time, Barney.
Well, Barney and Andrew did the best job around,
and I guess it was inevitable,
but eventually we're got out.
Folks tried to hire old Barney way
to another town,
close by.
I'll try.
What do you want?
The Barney stuck around,
because he put some roots down,
had his terrific man came up from Raleigh,
that's the capital North Carolina.
And he said,
Barney wanted to come work for me in the big city.
So he did it.
Barney Fife is one bad day.
He used to keep a piece,
but now he's moved off to Raleigh.
Oh, my son is poor,
but he brought me down to New York style.
He's a good man.
It adds a woman.
Good man.
He's a good man.
91 in John's Royal Oak Missouri Basement Missouri Michigan Michigan
Sorry rock trivia buffs will note that the borrowed name the original Hula Poppers
were of course a wildly popular Hawaiian jazz combo whose career ended tragically in
1968 when their plane was shot down while on a USO tour.
Kind of nice though nice nice to play homage to to Don Nost he did a lot more than just
Barney 5 okay but that was nice um last song I talked about sales on the pod safe music network
okay so here's what we have set up if you are registered as a podcaster and you add a song
they're only I think three now for sale actually there's a couple songs all songs by Matthew
all songs by american heartbreak and of course pod safe for peace by slow is for sale now this is
all just in the beta test if you if you add a song to your playlist which is of course also how
you report on the song after you've played it um the link the show notes link is automatically a link
that identifies you as the person who sent that you know anyone who clicked on it over to uh
the podcast page and of course if there's a purchase and these are all MP3s in the clear no DRM
this is just about supporting the music and please you know I know that there's a million ways
to hack into the site you know you can shoot you could actually become a podcaster register as a podcaster
and just download music I mean of course it's very easy to steal the stuff you can buy it and you can
copy it and send it to 100 of your friends but that's not the point the point here is we're trying
to prove that humanity will kind of work and and that we as consumers have never had the
opportunity to show that we're not thieves you know all this DRM stuff no no I think that we can
certainly prove and certainly as we move on uh to CD sales we're working on uh on some stuff with CD
baby uh to integrate into the unlabel as well uh we're working on merchandise all that kind of stuff
all just enabling this uh this particular form of commerce which will just call the new new music
business which of course is the new black so you can go and check out Matthew Ebel's entire collection
that he's uploaded to the pod safe music network uh you'll see that the buy this song is enabled
next his name if you want to sign up and want to give it a whirl it's 99 cents 90 cents of
that goes to Matthew during our beta test nine cents is just the transaction fee which is out of
our control uh and please let us know what the experience was if it worked you know what what
we what could we make better and know that we are working on making it better because it's well
shoot it's the beta how can you love me when you don't know who I am these pictures got a lot more
feeling from the bloodstained dirty hand and all I know is I was blind to the beautiful
bloody friend I've been a white devil a whole year old I'm walking on a stand alone with a
temper and a cold shoulder I just keep wasting the time again I've been accused of the crime
I'm dead
my baby loves me gives me everything I need she'll make a crown out of our plot and I'm happy
just to bleed she knows that I've been trying hard to take my thing she likes guns and she makes
love like a lightness but I like more than the other son has to leave it I'm wasting my time again
oh yeah I've been accused of the crime but it's hard and but it's been
oh yeah I don't want to have a told me they would only like to do down with the pins and needles
instead of the way
everybody told me I'll beat your spine but it's back time to bring that bitter white nobody loves you
She will let us you get in my eye
I won't keep wasting my time again and again
But a minute, a minute, a minute, a minute, a minute, a minute, a minute
I get so used to these crimes, but it wears kind of this
I won't keep wasting my time again and again
I've never been for the crime, I've just been with the Sith
Oh yeah, I just keep living like a dish I got to ask you
Oh, that's your evil
I keep it under my skin
Wasting my time, that's your evil now for sale
Now on sale, I'll 13th of the pot saved music now
Alright everybody, I gotta get out of here, gotta upload the show
The show, Peter, I've just got to throw it up on the bird
And I'm off, I will be talking to you tomorrow morning
As I said, coming from the, I'm not gonna tell you which hotel I'm staying
You probably know my now
No, I'm sorry, I don't have time to come and hang out and Amsterdam
All I'm gonna do is come in, go to my favorite coffee shop, hang out for the while
Go to bed, get out, do the show, have a lawsuit, just do a little quick lawsuit on the side
And then I'll be on my way home, okay
Oh, by the way, before I forget, keep your ideas coming for earthlink
We're gonna be announcing the, it's gonna be so cool
The quit your day job, earthlink challenge
I just wanna tell you the byline, because it's so cool
So the challenge is earthlink is gonna put their money where your mouth is
Stay tuned for that this week on the Charlie
Bye bye
Stay tuned in your rear
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do, we're earthlink
We believe in an internet that's safe from virus hidden scammers
We're earthlink
We believe your personal information should be just that personal
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a fo
We're earthlink
Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you, earthlink
We revolve around you