Delta Sierra Charlie 3-3-2
I keep your eye on podshow.com because pretty soon we're going to help you all back in.
I think once we get our podcasters up and rolling and there's a shit loader that we can
bandwidth all kinds of support and that work support if you will then we're going to go after you.
We're coming to get you 100 million listeners.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strap to my ass.
Do you need us?
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
It's time once again for the Charlie Daily Source Code is on for Wednesday.
How are you doing today?
Payman Paris in 94.
Oh, was it 95?
She was best studying abroad.
He was on tour.
Playing in another dime.
They potted hard and they potted wings.
A little north of the sand.
He dreamed about her in so many ways.
She dreamed about her in French.
Well, she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
That is the one.
He's another son, not like anyone.
Just needs time to heal.
They met in New York a few months later.
He was still living alone.
Hugging the ball and masturbating.
Never answered his phone.
Never's date was a movie together.
Outside it Brian Pock.
And the spirit of St. Louis just went on forever.
So they drank wine until they saw stars.
Oh, she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
That is the one.
He's another son, not like anyone.
Just needs time to heal.
They finally hooked up for the first time.
When night before the Fourth of July.
He fell so awkward saying goodbye to the girl who just changed his life.
Now my friend, they are in separate bars.
She even gets that boy to go to the gym.
Now if you don't think that's love, you must be cynical.
Oh, make a man, you're just dreaming in French.
Yeah, because she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
That is the one.
He's another son, not like anyone.
Just needs time to heal.
Well, she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
That is the one.
He's another son, not like anyone.
Just needs time to heal.
Yeah, he's the one.
He's another son, not like anyone.
Just need time to heal.
Well, that's right.
He just need time to heal.
By requests, candy butchers.
What to do with Michael?
Mike Viola at his best.
He's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who
mounds of feedback and email about the cartoon
um controversy
uh... so we're gonna talk about that in a few minutes and uh...
see pot-saic music uh... Trinity segment today got enough to do one
and uh... feedback from yesterday
and this really gets me when people write this kind of stuff check this out
uh... this is from uh... Paul jberry junior who has a uh... podcast window to the magic
uh... had a question about what happened on uh... dsc three three one when you read people's
name to give you feedback about your timer thing you read a list of people's names in the
name of their podcast but when you got to my email
which gave you really specific info so i recognized it you didn't mention my name or podcast
isn't due to the content of my podcast did you not mention my name or my show due to my podcast
covering Disney sound seeing tours the whole can't play not non-pod safe stuff deal
Paul jberry
from the windows to the magic podcast window to the magic dot com listen dude
every single day i get at least a hundred pieces of the i mean the timer thing
was a hundred by itself and i really appreciate everyone sending uh... the feedback in
don't take anything i say on the show personally if i admit something or
you know or don't play your promo i just look i'm doing this by myself here i've got no
producer you know my content has always been what i'm doing you should be able to do at home
that's why for the longest time we stayed away from uh... outboard gear uh... that's how
cast blaster came to life i'm using cast blaster as we speak yeah i've got a i'm ninety
dollar mixer that have attached to it and fifty dollar microphone uh... and uh... what is it
uh... like a forty dollar uh... preamp for the mic but really you should be able to do all
this stuff at home um... and of course with that comes the knowledge that i don't
as no way i can manage all of that and you know the show i try to keep the show around forty
minutes and even that's really really hard because it's just too much good stuff so don't take
it personally do please yes today i had a uh... uh... community test
listening to uh... what was the song uh... it was brother love uh... and my question was when i
heard brother love
say right uh... right stage right stage left right and you know state center stage
it was reversed on my headphones
yeah i got some good feedback on that one
starting off with window to the magic dot com
Paul jberry says all were correct in my end you must have had your ears on backwards
yeah
possible although doesn't the wire i'm i'm i'm using a pair of what are these oops sorry
jvc noise cancelling stereo headphones and i look to see if there was an r
or an l and there's not so i automatically presume
that the wire goes down the left hand side that may just be a uh... a right-handed person thing
as quansitoli points out
they man the headphone with the r goes on your right-yet
the l goes on the left
i learned this from podcast four on one or was it quit
with the producer from the quansitoli connection quaza totally connection
it's quansit or quaza
even misspelled it okay
uh...
yeah don't know but in in general uh... all the reports i got said that my system was configured
correctly
james chaplain said uh... hey must be a uk thing driving on the wrong side you know
here in Canada
to the left was left to the right was right and center stage was right in the middle
it helps when i listen to delta cia charlie and dobe digital five dot one on my home
pc
could we actually do something with that can i actually create
uh... surround sound and p threes
uh... or do you have to have something special for that i don't know anything about
uh... uh... about five dot one yeah i mean i've witnessed it watching movies and five dot
one is amazing
um... i don't know if you can do that with it with mp threes and with podcasting
and i really don't know if the five dot one gives you any
advantage other than a whole bunch of speakers
exciting day today it is the last day of the rocket boom auction on ebay
if you haven't been up to speed on this rocket boom
at rocket boom dot com which is of course uh... the daily video podcast uh...
uh... it uh... it's produced by Andrew and uh... hosted
by Amanda kongden
uh... they're trying a new model for advertising and they's they put up a
basically an offer uh... four five days a week long of a commercial running at the
end of rocket boom uh... with uh... i don't
the kind of guarantee uh...
one was it was a one million or two million i think two million impressions
let me just double check for a second yeah
uh... no one million one million views
over the course of a week
and you can bid on that now they have a reserve
which means you know there's a number they have in their head which at least has to
be reached before anyone gets anything
current bid fourteen thousand nine hundred ninety nine dollars and ninety nine
cents just under the fifteen grand
which would essentially mean in uh... advertiser terms a fifteen dollar cpm if it
were actually to go for that but of course
there's the creation of the spot you know the production of that is all included in uh...
in the price so i think the price would be a little bit a little bit lower
uh... let's see who the last bitters are eighty nine bid
so far highest bidder is dave taxes these are these are real e-bayers there's no
doubt about it five percent card dot com
uh... oh wow this is kind of exciting five percent card dot com had the the bid
uh... just before the the latest bid and bid fourteen thousand nine nine nine
nine then day from texas came in with ninety nine cents above that i wonder
if the reserve is fifteen thousand
personally i think it's higher i think they're probably more on
twenty or twenty five thousand
dollars
for the highest bid
uh... but it's the sea one day uh... where i am at right now
recording this podcast time left on the auction one day four hours fifty six minutes
and ten seconds so tomorrow
uh...
i don't know tomorrow on this time at least we'll have we'll be at just hours away from the
closing bid so
and see if uh... if this actually gets sold or not it's exciting stuff i'm really curious
and of course the thing that i like most about all this is
that it is not traditional advertiser bidding on this stuff it's uh...
it's internet companies and and ebay people who of course have our you know by
themselves great entrepreneurs lot of these power sellers
right now
now let's talk about the card the cartoon controversy
one second my uh... i set up a screen saver on my uh... on my laptop that's running
cast blaster
and it's kicking into façade
having to log in again okay there we go
um...
yesterday i i started uh... i'll just call out a conversation amongst ourselves here
listening to the source code about
these cartoons that were published and the outrage that ensued and the violence that
came from that
and uh... i'm not seeing a lot of newspapers respond to this i think that they're
well but actually let's talk about all of that let's take it in order though
since i started the conversation yesterday i received just a ton of amazing
comments feedback most of them written most of them very very lengthy pointers to
websites of uh...
Muslim community leaders uh... i really learned an incredible amount
and you know and it's so hard you know because religion is something that is so easy
to interpret and of course throughout history has been misused for many many evil
causes
but in general i of course believe that any religion is based in uh... in love and understanding
and togetherness and uh... and saying otherwise just doesn't make sense because that
goes against i think human nature you want people to believe in something
good and positive and i believe that the founders of these religions of all religions
basically have that had that in mind with some lessons to
to live live a healthier life by
uh... i'd like to take
uh... religion out of this equation though because i think that's where we're messing up
and this audio comment that came from a 14-year-old listener to the source code
really put a lot of things into perspective when i'm talking about uh... islam
uh... the faith of islam uh... Muslims
so we can take this part of the story out and really talk about what i feel is going on
so i want to play this comment first
and this is mkp from the mkp show and pseudon use at mkp media dot net and i wanted to
comment on the Denmark editorial cartoons
i'm pressing one to clear up is that there is no law that says that uh... insulting the
proper moment based upon him uh...
anybody doing that should be killed there's no law that says that still shouldn't be done
but uh... killing is nowhere in there
but second is that uh... what it is that there's so angry about
is not only uh... religion being insulted uh... want to say they uh... i mean these people who
who are uh... hearing of these about that uh... what to say about is that there's a lot
of the basic says that any profits or uh... so any profits would be like including a
home mother Jesus or Moses or Abraham or whoever uh... you're not allowed to have
pictures of them
now
the problem with these people is
they they they're getting mad because uh...
of something that's going to stop
but they're not going about it
islamically so they're being kind of hypocritical
in the summer the wouldn't
a more one violent
is not part of the religion at all uh...
in fact the these you know the way of screaming people in the summer is a salamolica
which means peace be upon you
and there's no violence uh... anywhere in the prudon
so they're not going about it is something they at all i mean people in Denmark
they the cartoonists didn't know about this rule
besides the fact that he still did something they shouldn't have done regardless of
the rule or not
uh... being there but
he didn't know about it so the salamolica doing it would be
no writing a letter or even publicly doing it you know telling him and telling
everyone
straight out that that's not allowed and just asked for an apology i'm sure they would
in a realizing what they did
and so all this violence that kind of breaking a hundred
is some rules uh... because of one
which doesn't make sense at all
now the problem
with uh...
i think it's a word west but
the west is uh... doing
is that the whole comic was just
not it has nothing to do with freedom of speech was just
and it's kind of like if you started being racist on your show right now it doesn't
make sense it's not allowed doesn't matter whether freedom of speech or not
thinks something like a blank
that skin color people are stupid or something so
before bashing
uh... any religion
you should try and learn about a verse now another thing that i just want to come
down is
a lot of people are stuck on the whole seventy two versions thing
that's taken out of context and if you're going to look going to the
Quran
just read more than one sentence is all i have to say
uh... i'm sure that there's this online search engine thing where you can search
inside the Quran go ahead and search for that
the absurd it's in some other context because i've read it before but i'm
feeling it right now
most of the suicide bombers aren't considered martyrs in the song
uh... they're not considered to be people dying for their religion
oh yeah and one more thing i've never heard you say the word
fundamentalist or extremist on your show
but uh... just for your listeners uh... the term
fundamentalist uh... most of them
in the world in a mainstream media is
considered to be a violent person who you know is a terrorist or something
and uh... that doesn't actually make any sense there's no
violence anywhere in the religion the fundamentals of his uh... or actually
a prayer charity the book of rich to record once in your lifetime
fasting
in uh... the month of the month and uh... fame that's nothing
so no one there's violence
and uh... you know just i don't know that because i kind of hate it when i'm watching
news and something they say
extremist or fundamentalists is that makes no sense
that's like calling hill or an extreme catholic or something it's uh...
anyway so this comes getting really long i hope you can play this on your show
to clear up some confusion with people and uh...
took my podcasts and empty media dot net uh...
i don't do religious podcasts but they're on a gaming attack and check
them out to good podcasts and uh... if you ever have any questions about
this time just uh... just email me at mkp show at gmail dot com
uh... to the police will be guaranteed no burn absentees
and uh... by the way your camera was off by around five seconds yesterday i think
anyway uh... good luck with our show
and by
right on okay
so that is the the youth the youthful voice of his long and i think it's very clear
so
obviously the demonstration to we saw the violence we saw
was not burned down by hundreds of millions of muslims all around the world it was a
a relatively and i'm just gonna say relatively small group of thousands
maybe ten thousand in total maybe twenty thousand total but it was not millions of
millions so you can't say
and i agree with that you know that saying islam fundamentalists that's all
crap these are just trouble makers is what it is led by trouble makers
some other facts i learned from uh... email that came in
and this is something that uh... and i read three newspapers a day i watch uh... the
BBC news
um... there's so much that i want you know the background of this has never been
clearly explained to me
these cartoons apparently appeared
in september of two thousand five and it's taken all this time
uh... and from what i have read and this is from people on the street in
denmark and i appreciate people from denmark getting into the conversation
audio feedback would be even better obviously
but you know this was something that was uh... i think there were a few cartoons that were
published uh...
several people took this back to their country
uh... excuse me i'll give you download dot i give you dot com
uh... taken back to uh... their countries and their communities and start up
shit with it and apparently allegedly also using other cartoons that were
may not even have been published by any publication whatsoever
now i'm just gonna make a presumption here uh... i have been to scandinavia i've
not been to denmark uh... but i i've always uh...
thought that the Netherlands Holland is kind of uh... you know like a backup scandinavia
if you will it's it's they're they're not they're not that far apart really uh... in
geographic distance and i think the makeup of the countries may be very similar as
well you know you of course you have a
a language which is a pretty isolated you know where in the world do we speak
Danish you know we speak it in denmark uh... Dutch is the same way where do you speak
Dutch well maybe uh... a little bit of south african because it kind of is derived from it
but it's really in the Netherlands so you know with the media explosion that we've seen
in the past years uh... in the Netherlands there are like 15 commercial television stations
you know there's uh... an equal amount of commercial radio stations there's newspapers
everyone's fighting and jockeying for position and i'm and please in denmark let me know
i'm just gonna make a guess that most newspaper publications uh... our sensationalist
and uh... they love to publish it that gets shit stirred up uh... because that's that's and
it's not you know it's it's not that this is politically motivated it's in their DNA it's part
of their survival this is you know this is what the news media have discovered
is if they want to survive they need ratings ratings are based upon uh... people watching
people watching is based upon emotions the easiest emotion that is you pretty much the
same uniform reaction in just about every human being is fear joy is different uh...
love can be experienced differently but fear i think is pretty universal and that's what they
and you can't even blame them for it you know this just it's stupidity and
has nothing to do with journalism anymore so let me know if that's true i'm just going to
going to presume that now you probably also are a very
peaceful loving nation which the Dutch are as well and i'm just drawing these analogies you know
by the way people get uh... the Netherlands and and denmark infused all the time particularly
people in the u.s. hey you speak Dutch you're from Denmark um i'm i'm i'm going to also think
that because of uh you know i don't know what the history of the recent history is of your government
but you probably have had a version of what in the united states we'd call affirmative action
this is what i saw uh what i realized in the Netherlands after having been gone for 15 years and we
move back five years ago and stayed for a couple years is that uh immigration policy was completely
mishandled uh people came in from the east i'm just gonna say from the east because it doesn't
matter what their religion is they came in from the east with their own culture and we're not
asked to adapt to and to integrate into the Dutch culture on any level not even uh learning to
speak the language now if you're in the u.s you know and my wife had to go through this
too Patricia uh when you when you want to come to united states you want to live there you have to
pass a test and it sounds really stupid and trivial but you know what it does work and you know
you just learn a little bit of history national history um you have to be able to conduct that
i believe you have to be able to conduct that uh the test in English um and you have to prove you know
you just have to prove that you're uh uh a contributing citizen to society and then you're more
than welcome which of course is the entire you know the entire foundation of the united states
and their immigration policy and many of the countries that are now overrun by uh i think i
truly believe people running from the hills in uh in the middle east where uh their life is just you
know nowhere compared to what they think life could be look if you don't think they don't see
television or see pictures or there's no underground stream of information then of course your
mistaken you know go to Baghdad dude that's a western city people walking around with mobiles you know
it's this is not you know this is not all sticks and cave stuff oh man people on serious satellite
stars 103 i'm so sorry you can't listen to the rest of this conversation at least not now
go to dailysourceco.com when you get to the officer home and listen to the rest of it because our
satellite window is closed there you go now let us continue here so i think there's probably some
kind of version of affirmative action i saw this happening in the Netherlands and when people start to
not even test their rights but just express their opinions and and i'm not getting into a legal
freedom of expression freedom of speech thing just a human thing people like to express their
emotions their anger their outrage whatever the best example in the Netherlands is i can't really
call in my friend but i was an active colleague of his up until just weeks before he was he was murder
tail fanghoh Dutch filmmaker descendant of Vincent fanghoh who created with money from the Dutch
state by the way co-funded created a piece of expressionistic art in the form of film
about how the islam treats i'm sorry i shouldn't have said that how how women are treated
often in name of the coroner islam maybe that's a better way to put it because it it you know it was
totally an expressionist piece and what happened to tail is he was gunned down from his bicycle
in the middle of Amsterdam after just having done some shopping and then a note with the other
people who would be killed was stabbed into his chest with the notes the note was stabbed
into his chest right in his heart and they got the guy and he's currently going through the
legal system there's no death penalty in the Netherlands and no one's calling for it either
but the uh the way that this has been handled publicly i think is is quite poor
and that comes back to the you know this whole idea of almost affirmative action you know and
and tiptoeing around stuff because oh my god and maybe this is it oh my god we don't want to
piss off the entire nation of Islam we don't want to piss off all Muslims guess what guys you
want this is what i've come to realize you know there are people misusing religion i've done
so with christian gym with Judaism you name it for their own good for their own preservation for their
own advancement and and cracking down really hard on people who do this kind of stuff who
who use violence in any manner in any manner doesn't matter who you are or what you believe
and or the color of your skin it's unacceptable in our society and we need to stand up for that
and make it known embassies which were attacked as far as i know our sovereign territory
of the countries they represent so if you go to a US embassy or if you go to a Danish embassy
you were actually standing on Danish territory attacks against these buildings are of course
an attack against the country now i'm not too worried about you know a couple people shooting
AK-47s into the air and pelting buildings with eggs but when you start to burn it down you've
got to come out you got to come out and force you got to kick these guys ass and don't be afraid
because the entire nation of Islam and the entire population that is Muslim will not come and say
oh you can't do that you have to crack down on that stuff where's NATO in this is is then
mark a member of NATO aren't they mean come on what's going on with these leaders it's not
it's only a few thousand people it really isn't millions and hundreds of millions and i think we
just have to realize it you know look at cops you know there's no discrimination
between who's being picked up yeah you can say oh it's cops and black people it's cops and white
trash it's cops and this and it doesn't matter it's people who are doing bad things who need
it serious attitude adjustment now what is what is the the thickest to all this of course i don't
know i can only look back to history to see what has been done in the past and it could very well
mean that the multicultural society will just have to become a reality whether we like it or not
because we only have really two ways to go i think that there's just millions of people who want
to leave the east and come west this is not the first time this happened this happened in the
Roman Empire too and they overran the the Roman Empire and not that they over overran and pillaged
and plundered it was too many people for the infrastructure to support it you know and now
where we have great social security and not everywhere but in many places there's great social
security there's facilities there's just no way you know you can't have 10% of the population
paying taxes to support the other 90% so there has to be a balance there so i think we can go with
complete lockdown nationalism close off every borders no way you're not coming in i think that is
probably not going to work then of course you could open it all up and let anybody come in
under certain rules and right now we're somewhere in the middle and it's and it's kind of not
clear and and i really don't know myself which which way i i think we should we should play it
everyone i'd speak to in the UK and in other countries in europe just say hey you know we don't want
any immigrants doesn't matter where they're coming from which of course is not true because they let
me in so let that be some food for thought for today and let's try and just take the
religious part out of the equation let's take the freedom of speech freedom of expression let's take
that all out of the equation this is just about people communicating and dealing with other people
i don't speak Arabic by the way i have no idea what people are saying half the time and what they're
all pissed off about so it's very hard to take things in context i just cannot i can no longer
trust newspapers or news media to tell me really what's going on i've learned so much directly from
people direct contact and if you want a yelling shout let's do that let's yell on shout if you want
a right nasty things if you want to create video shows where you say horrible things i'm really i'm
really okay with that because you know that's a level playing field that everyone can work with
oh boy you know we sometimes i think it's like what are we living in in some kind of special
time but if you see what's happened in history this is this is so not new this is just so not new
and i really hope we can get over this and just move on it would be nice but uh you know if
someone's gonna burn your house down you gotta go kick their ass it's just that simple and that's the
only way someone will learn but let's not do it with words of my laptop just go to sleep let's just
you know let's not be pussy footing around with stuff okay let's let's really let's really make a plan
and let people know in each individual country what is and what is not acceptable and just take
the religious part out of the equation please i'm tired of it oh my goodness okay hope that
made some sense it's it's it's it's such a tough topic to approach and just kind of doing a
brain dump on you hope you don't mind i'd love to hear back from you because of course it's just my
opinion i could be completely wrong wow that's pretty interesting i thought that promo was a little
bit slow to play let me see if i can do this again hold on a second what the hell happened there that
was kind of weird see if it works now hey adam this is envy with bedtime stories my kids love
you cause quite a stir with the bedtime story gofers because of some of the changes that were made
on daily source code 331 oh excuse me that was nasty uh download dot ikeview.com yeah that's my new
uh Vulcan mind trick i'm trying i'm gonna try and deep program everybody from the sen sail
link to the burp so i'll just mention different sponsors each time i do that and i'll do a different
one each time so that uh we can deep program yeah first link hey happy what's up download dot
give you dot com no you mean sen sail no things have changed earthlink what are you doing
daily source code stop let's say music network stop let me get this hey Roger
Roger hey can i call you back okay see yeah on the phone happy you burped on the phone
try to stop it not bottom well at him as you can see you cause quite a stir here at bedtime
stories my kids love nothing like the stir however that will be caused by bedtime stories becoming
a beta tester for the pdn thanks for the opportunity adam you thought the trip to walmart was
may him you just wait thanks again adam thanks Adam do you believe anything is possible we do
wear our flink we believe in an internet that's safe from virus hidden scammers we're earthlink
we believe your personal information should be just that personal and we believe your internet should
be a friend not a faux we're earthlink make this smart choice visit earthlink dot net and discover
what our internet experts can do for you earthlink we revolve around you
man something's funky with cast blaster today let me try that again two stay January 28
1986 11-8 a-o ở east mist Andrew two
day
a thick coating of ice coverage trees ever greens in four to high grass
three two one
Roger. Go with throttle up.
Shuttle commander Dicks go be radioed on a freezing January morning 20 years ago.
He's daughter Kathy, 25.
Huddled with her mother, brother and infant son on a roof to keep canaveral.
Along with the assembled families of the six other challenger astronauts about to blast off in the space,
she thought the rumble of lift off and huddled baby closer in the cold.
Wow. Look how pretty she said 74 seconds later.
Is that normal someone else in the crowd asked?
Their gons said Jane, wife of pilot Michael Smith.
What do you mean, mom? Ask her son. They're lost, she replied.
I know they are. The from framing him Massachusetts, a rare child with Grace Corrigan.
Mother of the late christmas call off.
They had a hunger to explore the universe and discover its truths.
They wished to serve and they did it. They served all of us, the guests, Glenn Loney.
Jones, go be Rogers.
Lorna, onizuka.
The crap they're even seen is a major malfunction.
Totally years after Challenger, we shall see you.
Mad Dog, don't kill him.
Holy, holy, holy garbage heap, man.
That's madpod.com.
New member of the pod show podcast network, man.
It sounds really produced. This whole Challenger special.
Definitely going to check that out.
I don't know what's going on with Castblast. It's kind of weird.
Normally, I'll start up the program fresh each day and of course,
it remembers what I had the previous day.
But now I didn't do that today and I think I made a mistake.
It sounds like the sample rates are getting kind of mixed up.
Let me try one more promo here.
See if it works.
Hey Adam.
Chef Tom here in Chicago.
I'm a chef teacher chef and teacher who teaches cooking and specifically
baking at the cooking and hospitality institute of Chicago.
I've been providing baking information on the web for about the last eight years
through my website Let's Bake with Chef Tom.
I've recently added podcasting.
The chic podcast.
See HIC.
What I really love to do is bake bread.
You love bread.
I don't just love the crunch of fresh crusty bread.
I thought so.
We talk about sweet, sweet, but savory food every episode.
Don't you want to know how to bake?
Do you want to know why stuff works?
Or in some case cases doesn't.
I talk food science with some of the other instructors to our school.
We have episodes coming up about ice cream, cookies, and chocolate breads.
Mmm.
Check us out at Let's Bake. Frostbitten.org for the chic podcast.
Thanks for checking us out.
You're on.
Another chef hits the pod waves.
Groovy.
I like cooking podcasts.
Of course, I like to pretend I can cook.
And Patricia's really good at it.
Chef Tom, thank you very much.
So I think I've found a momentary solution around this cast blaster thing that's going on.
I basically reloaded all the clips that I'm going to play and they seem to be working fine now.
That's kind of a message for cast blaster mic because he needs to know what I'm doing when shit goes wrong.
Just a couple of brief things here.
First of all, there's a new geek brief out.
geek brief.podshow.com.
Callie, bringing you all the latest gadgets.
Dude.
Callie, looking good.
She changes wardrobe in the latest show.
And I like it.
Very, very cool.
And I got a cool email from podshow headquarters yesterday at him.
I was going to mention something about this the other day, but thought otherwise.
But as you brought it up again today, I had to warn you.
You may or may not know me.
But I'm working at the San Francisco office, and if just about completed a player for the podcast,
I think music network.
By the way, I think we're going to throw that into beta on Thursday.
No damn announcements.
Of course I know who you are Kevin.
Aren't you the guy they call Kevin Oz?
Unfortunately, we haven't met in person, but I will.
And we can have from now.
The reason for my emails this, I have many relatives and friends in the UK.
And one of them known for driving like a maniac has been driving like a little
lady for three years there now.
The reason there are many cameras all around the motorways that snap photos of
speeders.
In the Netherlands, there are quite a few.
And I've been tagged there, but in the UK, they are ubiquitous.
So forget about 90.
Don't even think about 80.
Once you're aware of them, you'll notice them everywhere.
I do have that built in warning system.
I have to admit.
And I think they all are kind of painted orange.
So you can see them.
But yeah, they're not, of course.
These are speed traps.
And you know what you guys are right.
And by the way, I'm not a speed freak at all.
I've never been a speed freak.
I've never given a shit about cars.
Really.
And I've had all kinds of cars.
Every stupid car you can imagine, I've had it.
I'm just as happy, tooling around San Francisco and Trinity as I am in the Super V8
Jag here in the UK.
And you're right.
It's ludicrous.
I'm going to keep to the 70.
Yeah, I mean, within 70, 75.
By the way, when I was cruising 90, there were people passing me.
So I was just kind of going along with flow in the right hand lane, which, of course, is the passing lane in the UK.
Very, very frightening.
And if I want to get somewhere fast, hey, the solution is there for me.
Delta's share.
I'll just grab the plane.
There's enough airports here in the UK.
So I appreciate all of you concerned for my safety and that of my family.
Okay, some pod safe music coming up.
A brand new one.
At least brand new to me.
It's been on the network for a while.
But first something very important.
If you create a music show that uses pod safe music, we're a looking for you.
Yes, we are.
In September of 05, we made landfall with the seven headed monster known as pod show music rewind.
The weekly compilation featuring the best independent music from the best independent music podcasts.
If you've got a music podcast, it's time to unleash the monster within you.
Now on pod show music rewind, we'll be presenting guest podcaster personalities.
Right alongside pod show music podcasts, like the rock and roll geek show, accident hash,
the scenes in the roadhouse, and the rest of the pod show music game.
And as always, the show is broadcast every week on Sarah Stars channel 1003, part of Adam Curry's pod show.
Just submit a podcast clip featuring pod safe music of any style or genre to pod show music rewind at gmail.com.
All clips should feature songs from the pod safe music network and be no greater than five minutes in length.
Submit your clip today and you could be included on the next episode of pod show music rewind.
Check us out online at rewind.podshow.com.
Now that's exactly how a network is supposed to work and is supposed to come together.
I love it, so you're shot at promoting your show through the pod show music rewind.
Here's my shot that I guess coming around, poddle of dreams on the source code.
I love my shot, my house in my wife, this place my edge, my keys in my life.
I can't breathe yet, to make it again I have to find out just wherever I've been.
But I'm happy, and seeing the blue's got the clothes on my back, and got nothing to lose.
Still got my friends, for sharing some food, just a little bit.
And seeing the blue's got the blue's got the blue's.
Ain't got no more.
No hope on no gas, just one wetting ring.
And I can't get my nails out of the floor.
No I don't need anything, just some good friends, and this bottle of dreams.
And I'm happy, and seeing the blue's got the clothes on my back, and got nothing to lose.
Still got my friends, for sharing some food, just a little bit.
And seeing the blue's got the clothes on my back, and got nothing to lose.
I believe tomorrow we will finally be able to open up the beta test of purchasing free and clear MP3s through the pod save music network.
You'll be able to do it with a credit card from anywhere in the world, as far as I'm aware, of course if that turns out to be different, I'm sure you'll let me know.
I think we'll have one song to test with, and the idea here was to make pod save for peace with every day we're Christmas, to make that the test song.
The reason being, obviously, is that all the proceeds of that song go to UNICEF.
So you can help beta test and all the proceeds go to UNICEF except for nine cents, which is paid for the transaction, which is out of our hands.
We're not going to take any money during this beta period, and obviously nothing is going to anyone else except for UNICEF.
And SLOW is managing all that. So we're going to use that as the test song, and you'll be able to basically try it out.
And then I think it'll be as simple as artists just checking a box saying, make this song available and you'll be able to buy it for download MP3 free and clear.
It's a concept here. This is not a store people. This is a part of the unlabel. This is a part of, well, this is a part of something new.
That what comes into account here is trust and support of independent artists. That's really what this is all about. And hopefully it'll be successful test.
Also tomorrow, and I'm just going to start warning you now. I believe I'm going to try out the DGAP system of the PDN. Now DGAP, another fine acronym stands for dynamically generated audio placement,
which enables insertion of tags, promos, and, of course, advertisements in Earthlink.
How's the D program going, by the way? Is it working with you guys? Are we messing up enough? No more anchors to send CO?
So the reason I'm warning you is that files may come in name differently. There could be different date structures. It may not work at all.
You know, any type of things you notice, I'd be very happy to hear from you regarding that, and obviously bear with us.
Well, this is what Daley's source code has always been about it. This is where we test it all. This is where we break stuff. And that's why it's every day.
Because if it's broken today, well, we'll probably have it fixed by tomorrow. And I'll see you tomorrow.
Daley's source code.com for the latest podcast and the podcast feed.
Adamacrate.com for your feedback, love that audio feedback, and please throw it on the server and just send me a link if you don't mind.
Bye-bye.