This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want to hear our content with that ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta's share at Charlie 3-8-3.
Ladies and gentlemen, Mr. Vincent Price.
If I am feeling particularly ambitious,
I make a real curry plus all the side dishes.
Many currys are made with meats on the bone.
But for my guess, I only want to serve small boys.
I like to look around for some really exotic and very hot ones.
That's the way my wife likes them.
I then skin the boys and take all of the meat from the bone.
The easy way is to stab them one at a time with a fork and heat them over a gas flame
on the stove until the skin bursts.
It then peels right off.
What fun?
To make the curry itself is child's play.
A very simple but a very elegant dish.
Nothing makes a more exotic party.
I generally lower all the lights and burn a little child to help create a mood.
I bet I have citar records and put them on the stereo and that helps tremendously.
Candles winking everywhere are very romantic.
The visual display of the curry, all the condiments and the boys is really spectacular.
This meal depends on you to create a mood.
So be daring.
Use a different table cross or a brilliant remnant of material.
Pull out all the brass and copper you can find.
We're dangling eerie and a drape sorry if you have it and every bracelet you can find.
You'll guess we'll talk about this in a party for weeks.
Hello.
Hey baby, it's me.
I told you not to call me.
I know baby, but I've got this idea and see.
I thank you, man.
She'll make a Poon on the field.
Poon on the field.
Because I thank you, I agree.
Everybody wants to look like they look at a Poon on the field.
Everybody wants to smile at this moment.
Poon on the field.
Nobody wants to cry, no cries in the Poon on the field.
Nobody wants to cry, no one does any Poon on the field.
Poon on the field.
Big adjusting in.
You'll be the star of the show.
Get a Poon on the field.
Everybody wants to talk about the Poon on the field.
Everybody wants to walk like they walk in Poon on the field.
Nobody needs to show the machine in the Poon on the field.
Nobody needs to play in the Poon on the field.
Everybody wants to talk about the Poon on the field.
You'll be the star of the show.
When you cry, what do they get they come out to you?
Let's see, I didn't know what to do
You'll be the way
I think yes, I really didn't give up
You would come to this
I really didn't give up
You're unbelievable
You're 16 million dollars worth of airplane
Strap to my ass
Than the next generation radio content in my ears
We don't need no stick in prison
I like to think I'm flying into this genre
Fantastic, it's Adam Curry
And Lady Patricia
Hello, good morning
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
How about that for a different start?
Different opener today
I was just thinking you always say that to me
Who are a boy now movie?
No, I don't say that
You're not a boy now movie, I say
We live in a boy now movie
No, I don't say that
I say we have sex like a boy now movie
Okay
So
That's it
Right, only you know that if you actually film that shit
It doesn't look that good
Of course, no
Just let us think it looks like that
But I like that song
I came across on the podcast music
It's very funny, I like that
Ampsix, AMP, SCX, AMpsix
Very nice
From California
It's something else when people
Because normally it is
I think I love you
Yeah
I think we should be in a, we should make a porn movie
I like that
I like that, I like that
Very much, that was funny
Very funny
I could have done it some more
It could be open now
Yeah
A little bit earlier
Excuse me
I understand the groove
I should tell people about what happened at the tower
Oh yeah
It's Joey
At the tower
Yeah
It's a fair oaks
I wasn't here, but I have this on
Reliable information
So when you're, when you're landing your plane
You do a circuit
So you go first you fly perpendicular to the
To the landing strip
Downwind then you turn left or right base
And then you turn finals
Which is just the last leg before you land
And the person in front of you
Determines the circuit
So you're supposed to fly
You know the corners that that person flies
You're not supposed to cut in front
Even though you may be faster
No
Now it was really busy
At fair oaks
And Joey
I mean the only, one of the only women on the entire airfield
Top girl
Top girl definitely
Chopper pilot
And wants to be a cop
Once, once to be to Bill
Okay
Um
So it was, you know like end of the day
Close to six people are trying to get in
And just a lot going on
And then someone cuts right in front of a slower aircraft
And then Joey utters the infamous words on the radio
Golf Golf Alpharomio Delta
Did you just come inside
And it was quiet for like
10 seconds
Everybody heard that
Yeah, I think Captain Dan went back
I don't think there was an official response
For that in the radio call book
I didn't say that
Yeah
You gotta get, you gotta get to know Dan
Okay, this was funny
Presuming he said that
It's one of these folklore things
In aviation and of course could have happened anywhere
Coming to you from Curry Cottage
This is the daily source code
We're sure kind enough to join us today
And there's only been really one topic
Since yesterday afternoon
We've discussed nothing else in the house
At all
Besides
The new Patricia Project
You've heard of the Evan Parsons project
This is the Patricia Project
Yeah
Do you want to hit it?
Well
You know, we actually set to each other
Let's start
Let's fall in love
Love
We're looking for houses
You know
Because we're renting this piece of shit
That an astronomical amount of money
It's not a piece of shit
But it's not a house
But you can't fix anything
Because you're pouring it into someone else's pocket
Now all the things that we think is shit
We can't do anything
Which is most of it
Whichless face it
It's the doors are too narrow too low
Now we bump into you
Keep bumping into your ribcage
The door handles
Yeah, we go into you sleep
Our bathroom is crap
And leaking downstairs into the living room
There's no double glazing
There's no insulation
Yeah
But the atmosphere is good
And the location is empty
The location is empty
Yeah
Very good
It's a nice house
So you know
Yeah
It's handy
So I was starting
And so I went to a couple of real estate agents
And one of them
Oh no, actually a couple of them
Step back a second
Because producer keeps looking
And looking at all these great houses
And then you look at the
You show me things like
13 million pounds
Like $25 million
On daynice
Right
And then I say, well, just call them up
And just say, hey
You know, I want to come take a look
You know, you're a lady
But even if you can't afford it
Oh, it's good
Oh, yeah
You know, you need a good example
Yeah
And that's actually the way I shop too
I go to very expensive stores
Look at it
And I don't buy it
Then I go to the high street
And buy the same thing
That looks like it
Baby
If I ever really introduce you
The second life
You would be so into the shopping there
You have
It's all about shopping
Well, let me do it in real life
Okay
All right
So I went to a couple of real estate agents
And they gave me some brochures
To make brochures
And one of them
Was a house
That we actually seen
In something that we got
Remember that
By mail or
Well, that was a while ago
Sometimes you get those brochures in the mail
And we saw it
And we set immediately
The looks nice from the outside
And you set to me
Why don't you phone them up
And just take a look at it
And see what it is
Yeah
But we never did
I don't know what happened
We never did
So one of the brochures that I got
Last week
It was the same house again
Better known as horn castle
Yeah, so we called it horn castle
Right
And because it's a castle
I mean, it doesn't look like a castle
But it looks like a little palace
It's more like something
Yeah
It's got something
So staying in my
In my alliterations of curry castle
Curry curry cottage
It could be Patricia's palace
So we thought
Maybe that's a sign
Patricia's palace
Pat's palace
Sorry
Or anything
So we went there yesterday
To check it out in the end
Outside is nice
First and evening
We went together
Just check out where it was
And what kind of neighborhood
You know, just, you know
Before you say anything
Let's just check it out
Because sometimes it's no need to go
You know, if you see where it is
So we checked it out
And it was actually very
And shunting
And chanting
On shunting
Shunting
Very
Yeah, I have to say
It's about the same size
As the cottage
It's not huge
But it's
It is very charming
It's very charming
Very charming
And when I'm done with
A great place for entertaining
Oh yeah
So
I
We probably think
That it used to be one huge
That's why
Yeah, it's been
It's a palace
A palace
A castle
It was a castle
It was chopped into the throats
Probably
I only have like 40 minutes on
So I don't get to the good stuff
So you know
No
And if I don't board this
In English
It has a real
Boardess
A board
A queen waves
Yeah, a little about
It's not a balcony
But it's more
The entire length of the house
Very brilliant
Yeah, yeah
You can wave to your peeps from there
So from the outside
We really liked it
Now we had a peak
In the inside
With the real estate
He's a lot of work
Yep
I mean this is like
Serious ass
Rebuilding
Re-changing the inside
Yeah
Can you not stick that in your ear?
Why not?
Well, I'm asking you, keep falling out
Yeah, my ears are too small
Do you need me to help you?
No, it's okay
I can do it
It's just annoying
No, you know why
I have warm ears
Because I just had my walk on the down
Oh, that is a big spanned
Yeah, they pop out of you
Yeah
You know why
It goes to 11
And it's exploding
I wasn't a funny to see this
It's my laptop
Yeah, it was on over there
Just watch it over and over and over
Well, at a certain point it's like, okay
I remember it again
And I do recognize
All the situers
That was on sky
Over the weekend
But anyway
I made a little mood board
How
The house
I was already in the mood
But I do
Is it
I'd you've got to see the mood board that I've made
Yeah, you know
You're right on
And see what you can do with it
And what the colors
Could have been
And you know
So it's just fantasizing about it
We have a lot of questions
And also
Very interesting
And that's why I went a bit slow with a house
Because what's going on
In the back
Is
Sort of a garden
Yeah, you have to understand
It's built on a hill
So it's built up
Like just
You know, if we actually go through this
I'll put some pictures on that
Yeah, it comes down
I mean
It's just ridiculous
From your kitchen window
You just look at a mole
So anyway, so the best laid plans
Where I said the next house
We have we both have individual bedrooms
Because I definitely want to have my own bedroom
But I want to be able to visit you
I frequently
As much as you can on
People think that's really strange
We say that that that we wouldn't mind
Separate beds
People think that's really
But
Didn't we explain
The way we have my habits and your habits
Yeah, I'm a big sweaty man
Although we love each other so much
I mean, you don't want to go to bed
And you have of course
But anyway
It's all a mood point now
Because my bedroom now is now changed into the bathroom
So it doesn't matter anymore
I guess you're stuck with me
No, but we have a plenty of rooms upstairs
No problem at all
But I want my own room
I don't want to be in the guest room
Go to the attic
Sit that thing in your room
I want laughing and pop that
You know, Roger Smalls is
Actually, I was going to say
I noticed yesterday when looking through that
That I had a much
Clear vision of what we could do
With the house
Then
Previously
Because
And you're going to laugh at me
When I say this
Oh, not again
It's true
Because we're building stuff in second life
But isn't it the way they actually
The architex and everything work
When they build houses
Well, yeah
You can walk around like that
Yeah, so this is very, very similar
And so I'm looking down like
Hmm, we could just chop this wall in half
And round it off like that
And I find myself
Almost wanting to move my mouse finger
To click and you know
And to move the wall
Oh, yeah
You do it in second life
Oh, that's what they do
When they make a
And design or something
They do that
You can walk through the house
Before it's done
But it's really affected me
I'm not making
I'm not making it
I believe you
It's really affected me
Or maybe if we find somebody who can do that
In second life
In real life
We can see what you can do with the house
So that's what we're going to try
We're thinking about and see what the
The
Very cool
Yeah
I'm building things with two different women at the same time
Oh
Yeah
I'm building the
Potio Palace with Brittany
Remember
Oh, yeah, Brittany
No, not Brittany
Brittany
I say that
But that's incorrect
Yeah, I know a Brittany
But just Brittany
There's no A.N.
No Brittany
It's Brittany
Oh, okay
Brittany
Yeah
I know
What is that
A lot of time with Brittany
No, that's
Yes, you do
Some
But it's going to be very cool
As long as you have fun
Oh, God, I love you so much
Do you know how many guys are listening to this now going like
Like
Listen
Why don't I give me one of those
You know
It's nice to see that your husband is busy
That's true
Not sitting around
So he can't
He can't nag
Or
Do I ever nag you in the way?
Oh, okay, yes, I'm often often in the way
So but anyway
Roger Smalls, I think he's pissed off at me
Oh, we haven't heard from him for like three weeks now
True
And he put this whole thing on his on his weblog
That he can't well he can't get on this
He just he hates second life
Everything about it
He doesn't want to be a part of it
And he feels left out
And it's like I don't know what to do
But he's not sending in any more stuff
Well, there you go
Yeah, but a couple people
You're losing friends, huh?
Oh, Roger come back
I'll do anything
Yeah, please
Gaining of gaining friends in the air
And in your second life
Losing them in RL
In real life
How you doing?
Didn't I warn you about that
I haven't this is Simon James, a listener and pod say fart is from the UK
I've been listening to the Charlie for about again
I love it
I'm a little miss an episode
I was listening to your comments
It's a day on hypnotizing your listeners
And I was wondering
Why you wanted to do that
I understand from another closing point of view
It might be quite a nice trick to have it
You sleep
But it sounds a little bit too much like
A plot from an often empowered film to me
Look at you, man
See you on the next one
It's a little genius
Don't worry
Anyway
And Simon, I did check out your tunes
Thank you very much
And definitely going to play them on a future
A future Charlie
But I was already stacked up for today
So I started this conversation
I don't know last week or whatever
I said
You know we did this in Saio thing
And let's be honest
If someone burps in this house
Don't you automatically think Saio?
Oh yeah
And I hear
Christina has doing it
Yeah, because you never burp a problem
You never do it in school, man
You never burp do you?
Oh
Like a truck driver
Yeah
And then I say
I'm sorry but I need to
They're not okay
I'm not going to hold in the air
The only thing you have to say is
Saio
You don't have to even say
I'm sorry
No, I say these things
Only if I get paid for it
Unlike me
Full not getting paid for this in Saio
You remember when I met you
You were drinking milk
You didn't notice
You were actually
Yeah, the TV show
The producers made me drink milk
Yeah, but you didn't
I didn't know it was sponsored by
They said don't drink a beer
I'm going to ride away
But I got a car out of that later
Because I told you
I got a car out of there
Got my back, baby
I was young
And defenseless
Like a little deer stuck in the headlights
And that's what you saw
And went
I saw my pulse
I was fresh boy
Mead
Yeah
So we were talking about this
And so the Saio thing is
Neurolinguistic Programming
You know I've messed around with that
You're trying to link stuff
And it worked
I've helped Christina over a lot of fears
And things by anchoring
Good thoughts to
Or good thoughts to good images, etc
But apparently there's this
Your body's made up of protons
And electricity and stuff
It's not like your
What made a wood
So you're all even wood
It's all made up of stuff
Electric bits and pieces
Yeah, that's why I'm disturbing you
Every time
Whenever Patricia comes near a computer
Garanty people freeze up
I don't think it could be
It could be a super company
I don't know
It would freeze up
It's true
Yeah
So
There's some theories out there
That if you get the right frequency
Sound
And you have that in your ears
You can also
Not well, maybe not hypnotized
But you can program your
Body, your mood
Levitate
No
Let me see if that's in the program
Yeah
Do we have a levitate
No
But you understand what I'm saying
Yeah
So basically
If you
You know, some people do it
With those
Headphones
And sunglasses
And these flashes of light
In the sunglasses
So
There's this thing called
The Brainwave Generator
And I'll put a link to it in the show notes, of course
It's only for windows
But what the hell
I took the time to install it
So we have all these different tone
Settings
And so we have one that can
Attention
Focus your attention
Increase your creativity
Three for headache treatment
One for learning
Meditation
What else is there
Quick mental refresher
Relaxation
Or self hypnosis
Sleep induction
And the awakened mind
Okay
Which one would you like to try
Hard repair
Let me see
Hmm
No
No, but maybe if we use
The self hypnosis
Yeah
Maybe you can tell yourself
Repair your heart
Okay
Ready to try
Yeah, look at my eyes
Look at my eyes
Listen to this
Crap
Not working all of a sudden
Right?
Tested that 15 times all of it
I know what that is
You lost it
No, no, no
Feel anything yet
What does it do?
That's a
I can't remember
Now relaxation
Now that's that's self hypnosis
You want to relax?
It sounds a bit like you can hear your blood gush
Well here's this is relaxation while staying focused
So I think this is good
Because even if you're driving the car right now
It's okay to listen to this sound
You relaxed
No, I don't like
You're not relaxed
None of the drives me crazy
That shit really worked
Yeah
How about a mental refresher
Maybe that'll help
Almost as I remember
I have to pay the bills
I can imagine
It's irritating
So it will probably
warn you or something
It's place in promos
We'll be right back
So what is the MAC attack podcast
Tips, tricks, and hints
Apple and MAC centric tech news
Reviews
Must have shareware, freeware, and commercial software
Creating music on your Mac
File, backup, file, share
Utilities, optimizing, maintenance, questions
Answers, font management, wireless routers
Networking, special guests from around the Mac universe
Safe surfing
Everything you ever wanted to know about
Search protectors and UPS
I live graphic design
How memory works in Mac OS 10
Gifts for the Mac user in your life
Troubles shooting
Getting up close and personal with hard drives
Which are stories
Securing Mac OS 10
OK, you get the idea
Join me, Steve Stanger
Every week for the MAC attack podcast
Give it a listen on iTunes
Or visit the show blog
at www.TheMacAttack.us
And for those of you
Checking this out on a series
Stars 102
Our satellite window is
Closing
Pacific Coast Railway
Up next
East Radio after that
Then Dawn and Drew
And of course, Steve Gilmore
With a Gilmore Daily
Frank Truth Tonight
That's Brian Know
Who sent in all the things about Frank's
Not True
Yeah, thank you so much
Very interesting
And after that
Michael Butler
And also you guys back here
Tomorrow on 102
And for those of you still here
Check this one out
Story
Opinions
Possibilities
And Music
Every installment of
Killer Fiction is stuffed with stories
Short stories
Stories told in song
Stories recorded in real world audio
Odyssey's
Stories told from memories
From possibilities
Stories born of wonder
And anger and awe
And everything that powers our human imaginations
This is Todd McKinney
And I'm inviting you to listen to Killer Fiction
Find us at killerfiction.com
And wherever else quality podcasting is delivered
Tell the truth
Tell a story
It's Killer Fiction
From Todd McKinney
And Curie's Metro sexual moment
Oh harmonious
Cool
So I think I have you here
You might as well do a Metro sexual moment
Because you are the authority when it comes to men
Oh yeah
Okay, so sleeping with your man
I thought it would be the topic for today's Metro sexual moment
Because let's be honest
It's not
It never is a really good idea
I mean men and women are so fundamentally different
Very different
When it comes to sleeping and you and I
I think we definitely
Yeah
Yeah, but I don't think everybody has that problem
That you have
So let's just say hypothetically speaking
You have a very long husband
Yeah
Very long
Everybody's too short
He continuously
Let's when I'm just start with the covers
He rolls self in a pancake
Yeah
You don't like DuVase
DuVase
Yeah, you hate that
Yeah
So you want sheets
Yes
Which they are very hard to find
But I found them
So women, so for first of all
And this of course is for guys right
We're giving guys a very son
Yeah, so you want sheets
So the DuVase has to go
Plankage
Yeah
And then on top of that sort of a very nice light
Wait, come for dinner
Come for dinner
That's what you like
But is that what women would like to
Is that too?
I like to feel something on top of me
Oh yeah
It's not exactly the problem
I like to feel my blankets
I like you know
You could be very fluffy and very easy
But you're not a guy
So we don't care about you
And this is the Metro
Because we are always cold
I've cold feet
Yeah
You know, I'm always cold
So what if your guy has like horrible night sweats
Yeah
What do you do with it?
And I don't know why I don't have them all the time
Maybe
Could be a couple of things
Could be the splits
I
I don't get to play
Yeah
So could be that
Possibility
Yeah
Could be that your brains
Never stop
They're working
Yeah
No, no, that's not true
Because the split definitely combats
That's showed up repeat the day
You know?
That's the thing that you did
That's supposedly
Yeah, your brains aren't going to be
Because I'm here
I'm in San Francisco
Thousands miles
I'm all over the place
No, but I mean
Yeah, that's true
But the hell am I?
What the?
I can't say
Oh, I must be the codi
And sometimes
You have those sweat attacks
Yeah, but let us call it that
There's anything that guys who might suffer from this
Yeah
There's nothing more embarrassing than that
We tried everything. We tried shower in the morning, so you don't
shower in the morning, shower in the evening, shower in the sound time. So we tried
shower in the night that evening doesn't help. Because if you come out out of the
shower, you're still very warm. You're going your bed and you start to sweat. You
not make it. But it's really embarrassing. I'm sure other people have that. Yeah,
so sometimes I want to just, you know, cover which you're a
ejaculator than a sweater. That is a problem, too. Not with me. I sometimes I want to
spoon spoon. I want to spoon. And then I want to feel you tiny little
bots. Yeah. And here, no. And have you on my lap? The other way around doesn't
matter and spoon it a bit. But then, but then suddenly, it gets so wet. It's you. You
know, you make it. That's what it is. You're making me blow up. And then I wake up
and I think, holy shit, what is this? And then my whole knees are wet. We have
actually, we have actually considered the fact that I just might be one of those
people who can spontaneously combust. Yeah. You know, I'll be sitting in the chair
and then I'll just explode and my legs will burn up and have my body all
being on. Absolutely. I think so we have no cure for this currently. This is
still something. And I think that this is something that we love to sleep with each other,
but you know. Okay. And let me play this Metro about one of our pet peeves.
The Metro Sweaty moment. Thank you.
Well, I hope I'm leaving him to have him carry his other way. This is not going to make
much sense. I don't really get to travel around the world much. I don't get to
13 people. But I think. But I think.
Not all on a second. He can't fucking hear what he's saying. I got to on the music
up.
Two floors for a conference this week. And I'm staying at the Rhett's Colton in
Orlando. Absolutely smashing hotel. Yeah. And I just thought that I have a look
around and sure enough we have the marble lined bathroom. We have the
huge flat screen TV with built-in PlayStation. We have the internet
connectivity. But the one thing that really made me smile and made me think of
you, Mr. Curry, whether we have plug-in and drives and they got extendable
cords and my deals are that Metro sexual man. I thought he was starting to talk
about that because you missed that. That toilet is a bit particular toilet.
The one that shoots water in the ass.
I love that you do that. I feel so clean and fresh. And it's made for women.
No, it's not made for women. Where is that? It's like a bathroom and a
be-day and one. No, no, no, no, no.
It's okay. I use the be-day, too. You got it for you.
I love the be-day.
Are you going to go that? You're nice.
Yeah. Well, I think that that is probably a topic for another Metro sexual moment.
Good news, baby. When we go to San Francisco, you didn't hear it yesterday because we
know you never listened to the show. But a Ranger Craig-
I hear you the whole day.
Yeah, but you didn't hear it. You don't hear what's being played on the show.
Yes. You don't care about the show.
I'm getting an overdose at him curry at home.
20 years long, babe. Well, you know what? I was just saying to myself the other day,
I can't wait to be in San Francisco alone pretty soon.
Really, you mean that? No, but just trying to be mean.
Oh, you don't mean that because then you call me.
The moment I sit down, you call me.
It's the time you say. I want to see you put the camera on your face.
Yeah, no, not on your face, but on your face.
What are you wearing on? Oh, what are you wearing on?
Go a little bit back. Oh, okay.
Oh, yes. Show me that one again.
Yeah, right. Oh, yeah. And then amazing.
It's unbelievable. See you next time.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
So, yeah.
Okay, well, no. But because the question in the phone rings.
And I said to see that, oh, it's dead again.
You guys like, you know, you don't give a shit.
See, you don't care about my show.
It's one of my sentences.
Just give a Christ. It's dead again. He's calling.
Exactly the wrong moment because America's next top model is on or something.
No, no, no, no, no. It's endless.
Dude, I do, I totally, totally, totally coordinate with the East Ender schedule.
That's not true. Oh, I'm sorry, Nick Tucker's on.
I can't. Yeah. Oh, I wish, no, they're gone.
But East End is, it's very relaxing. It's simple.
I love it. It's simple. And it just clears your brain.
Tonight, I'll be Grant and you be Jane.
Anyway, I'm back to Ranger Craig.
So he works at Alcatraz. And so he has this whole thing about Baghdad.
The San Francisco used to be called Baghdad by the Bay,
which I thought was funny, but there's a whole history behind it.
Oh, hi.
Herb Cain referred to it as the city Baghdad by the Bay.
As for your trip to Baghdad by the day, I'm on Alcatraz on Sundays,
but not on Saturdays, which dates will you be there.
We're going to get a special tour dude.
Hmm. Ranger Craig will take us around.
How cool is that?
Hi, that's cool.
Could you really want to see it?
Yeah. All right. So we'll make it Saturday, Ranger Craig.
Feedback was great. I just love people.
You know, people just calling up listeners calling up.
So much fun to hear him. In Jersey 201-625-6357,
or in London, 020-768-1375-3,
just saying Jersey reminds me to thank Jersey Todd for the opening of today's
daily source code. He totally hooked me up with that Vincent Price thing.
I had no idea where he got it.
It's so scary.
Only a Jersey guy could understand that.
It was send it to me, right?
He boy.
So someone called the listener called the other day about,
I thought it was on KLA radio in Los Angeles,
but it turned out to be a podcast, which actually pretty funny,
and she called back, listening to this.
Hi, Adam. I have to talk for a little bit because I'm at work,
but I want to say that I suit my voicemail on Friday,
and one of the clear-up is actually KLA radio.
It's a podcast, and I think I figured out that,
I think the guy just used some clips of your voice,
but was pretty funny though.
So I just wanted to clear it out, but you're doing great.
Okay, let's go. Bye.
Okay. Now, what I liked about this phone call,
here's what I liked about it. I mean, not too much what she was saying,
but she was at work.
She's at work. She's doing it secretly,
and it sounded really...
On table, on the other day.
Yeah, so what I want is I want people to call up,
yeah, I want people to call up more,
but you have to be, you have to speak clearly,
and you have to have a good phone connection.
But that's clear.
Listen to listen, I can't talk, it's really sexy.
Listen to it, listen to it, listen to it.
Hi Adam, I have to talk very little because I'm at work,
but I want to say that I suit my voice.
And tell me what you're doing at work.
Yeah.
Yeah. And then call me.
So I can play it on the show, right?
Yeah.
I think they'll do it.
Of course.
Yeah, I love that secret stuff.
Okay.
I can see her sitting on her deck.
Exactly, that's it.
Did you get a visual order?
Had in her bag or something, her hand bag.
I'm inside the Gucci.
I'm in my hand bag.
Alrighty.
What else happened this week?
On Thursday, we're going to go back to the pet's palace.
Pat's palace.
Do you hear your pet project?
We're going to go with taking a professional
to look at the house and the inside and the walls
and everything is in check it out,
because it's very old.
I'll bring X-Dar and it's possible.
The thing that we actually would like to do to the house.
And ask for, oh, and I talk to the lady from the
real estate agent, and she asked Helen, and she asked the vendors.
That's what they call her, right?
Venders.
You mean the old dudes were selling it?
People were selling it.
Yeah, the vendors.
That's what we say.
The people are selling it.
And they're going to provide us with papers and
very interesting stories about the house.
Oh, the back also, we can tell people about the house stories.
Yeah, so that.
And we can change the name, right?
And I already checked, is there anything in that ski slope in the bag
that you know, Indian burial ground?
If you want to do something with the garden, we need a good garden designer.
And do something with that.
Can we get one of those to top?
Can we get the flying gardener?
One of those TV shows to do it for us?
We'll disguise ourselves.
See, somebody like that, because you see it on TV.
And somebody comes in in a couple of days.
You have a nice garden.
I would have to say, I want to dusk it all.
All things all things aside, we would be perfect for one of those.
You know, we're one of these, we bought a piece of shit.
We're building a great house project TV show.
We'll be, I mean, we're dynamic.
Yeah, we'll be perfect.
It would be good.
It would be funny on TV.
Yeah, it would be good.
Not in Holland.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
No, but I think just the two of us would be pretty funny.
Because we need an Architech to do the inside and
an architect for the outside.
Yeah, it's quite in, um, uh, wasn't out there.
Big deal.
Oh, you need a challenge.
A challenge.
Yeah, the whole thing is a challenge.
Yeah, very much, especially the backyard.
You have no idea.
Yeah.
But when it's done, then we can have the ideas.
Yeah, and then we'll have a garden house with a hot tub up on top.
And it's Jacuzzi on top of the floor.
Overlooking the mountain, overlooking the mountain.
The city of Gilford.
And you ever saw, are you kidding me?
Simple.
Got to put some postballs down there and take advantage of you.
So let's see.
Let's see what happens and let's see what the professionals are saying.
Okay.
That's so funny.
Finally, that ear plug fell in into your cleavage.
Yeah, finally.
Finally, to my cleavage.
Hello, hello, boys.
Can you hear me?
Hello, hello, all right.
I'm going to play one more song on.
This is the song that everyone's playing.
And I've played it a couple weeks ago.
I think when Kevin gave me his new album.
You saw the video last night, which I think I should post up as well.
Oh, yeah, I know what you mean about mom.
Yeah, isn't that sweet?
And I remember playing this.
There are a lot of songs about mom.
But they cannot be enough songs about moms.
I think so.
You're so right.
Well, people are just going to ape shit over this song.
And the timing.
I mean, this is mothers.
Do you know how hard it is to get a record company to cooperate,
to release a song in conjunction with mother's day?
Yeah, but it's not mother's day in England.
The biggest mother's day.
Give it Kevin Reeves lives in Nashville.
Yeah, maybe mother's day over there too.
It is no mother.
It's the second May in a second Sunday in May,
is mother's day in the United States.
So that's next week.
All right.
Yep.
And so don't harsh the guys, Melo.
Oh, all right.
I mean, what I was saying is it's so cool that he can time this release himself.
Yeah.
And podcasts are sitting around going like, gee,
you know, mothers days coming up.
Oh, yes, one mother's day.
So for mother's day.
Every day.
Yep.
So without further ado, Kevin Reeves and mother.
I have been down.
I have been out.
And I feel like my life's killing him.
And I can't seem to find your life's about.
And I've lost my direction again.
But I'm feeling lonely at the end of the day.
I know that my son is phone call the way.
Because he's here.
Oh, mother.
Oh, the wings smile.
We're so wet and spent sleeping.
And he's here.
Mother, mother, take my broken heart in your safe and leave.
We're now stripped away.
Nothing more can I say than I love you.
Here I go.
I am making a sound that came for me.
But I know what I know that I can tell.
Because you're sharing me on all the day.
I'm feeling lost in the dead of the night.
And tell me that I can't don't give up the fight of this year.
Oh, mother.
Oh, the wings smile.
We're so wet and spent sleeping.
And he's here.
Mother, mother, take my broken heart in your safe and leave.
We're now stripped away.
Nothing more can I say than I love you.
Oh, mother, take my broken heart.
I'm feeling my broken heart in your safe and leave.
We're so wet and spent sleeping.
Oh, mother, take my broken heart in your safe and leave.
Oh, I love the harmonies.
Isn't that great?
You want to glide with them?
Yeah.
Even if you don't know how to do it, you just want to go.
It's great.
So I just...
Beautiful courts.
Kevin Reeves from the Podsake Music Network, music.podshow.com.
I just popped off an email to Chris Bershiers.
Whoopcaster guy?
Oh, yeah.
Because he, of course, runs that.
Even though we're opening up all sales when Podshow plus launches, I'm going to ask him
to enable Kevin Reeves.
So people can buy that for the mom from Mother's Day.
Would that be nice?
Yeah.
Okay.
All right, baby.
Good idea.
Yeah.
Well, we aim to please here at Podshow.
I know.
And on that note, huh?
If you wanted to get Pat'sPalest.com, you just go to godaddy.com.
And if you use...
Promotional Code, DSC, three upon checkout.
You'll get that for only $6.95, $6.95.
Yes.
Pat'sPalest.com.
Sounds like a porn place, doesn't it?
It does.
Yeah.
Oh, there goes the neighborhood.
Pat'sPalest isn't it?
Thank you.
Everybody wants to know what to like and look at it.
For an all-movie.
Okay.
And of course, also, I'll keep you contact lenses.
Check out her at download.acu.com.
And by Earthlink.
Earthlink coming soon with the ad challenge.
Would you participate in the challenge?
I don't know if you...
Would you do some for Earthlink?
I don't know.
Depends on what.
It pays.
If you win it pays.
Valible cash prizes.
Yes indeed.
Do you know how many people send me email every single day.
it positive. Do you have any idea how many people ask that? It's unbelievable. You never do that.
I got like a million song writers, a million producers, musicians, and they'll make the whole
track for you anything you just don't, you're not at all. I don't feel like it. If I had a voice
like you. I did it all. Don't forget, I've starred when I was 15 years old, so I've been
playing my instrument. I'm a professional. I think it's not, it's not a hobby. Really?
Yeah, for me, it's not a hobby. You know, I'll pay you that. How much sounds? No, no, no.
I'm going to take note about that. What's it going to take? No, no. Leave me alone.
Do you understand why people ask? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because people in your art want to hear how new generation and they are so good these days.
You know, they are so good. I'm from old school. That's why if you put the two together,
it would be so wonderful. No, I don't need to. Let them. I know you don't need to, but people
have no need. I have no need at all. Not at all. I do it sometimes just, you know, for fun in
the bathroom more. Some are screaming through the house. I do it sometimes. It's fun in the bathroom
too. But if you say every time you sing, I say, hello, you all right? I know. This is my
frustration. I mean, yes, thank you. We know that I'm not the singer in the, at the cottage.
Something's going on. He's in pain. It's a no, I'm singing. So that's why I, well,
guys, I gave it a shot, okay? I can't convince her. I know, but maybe if I love music,
listen, if I, if I leave it to the young, if I gave you the right song, if I, if I, if I
played you the right song and had the right lyrics and all you had to do and all you had
the, what, you can't get in passion by a song? No, no, no, I leave it to the new talents.
Really, they're so good these days. Are you afraid? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
I think sometimes it's so pathetic when you're old and you're older or you're going to do your
act again. It is so, okay, but that's where I'd like to correct you. This is not about an act. This
is about a movement. This is about you. It's not necessary for me. It's not necessarily for me.
It's not necessary. I know, but would you do it if I asked you? Well, sometimes we, you know,
we did something together and did some music and sang it a bit. And we have our, we have my,
I have my machine downstairs. You can't really open. Okay. What is fun? But I can't, you know,
you can't play those songs. When my daughter is next to me and I sing with her and I think,
oh my god, I'm singing with my daughter. And you know what, whenever you're, whenever you're
listening to things, you know what I think? Oh, she's in pain. No, she's no, she's very musical.
She's good. She's good. She doesn't care about it, but, but it's not her. But we can't play
those songs on the show because they're not pot safe. I know, I know. I hate that shit. Yeah,
hate is a shit. Now, and you know what, there are, you know that I always say there are so many
other things that I would like to try. I've, I've tried it. I did it. I've done it. I've been in
every studio. And now, I think, you know, I'm also very, um, artistic. So I love to design. I love to,
you know, be busy. Let's try another woman in the bedroom. Why? I don't know. You said
their things you wanted to try? No, that's not what I mean. I don't know that. We talked about that
enough, didn't we? If we did, just give me a refresher. No. Yeah, it's okay if I bring another guy.
I'm sorry. I'm from the 60s. Did it all. Yeah. Sorry, grew up in the air, grew up in the
cities. Yeah, you're fine. We had AIDS. That was fun. That's right. You guys had free love and sex
and we had AIDS. Gee, it was not fun. We just did everything. That sucks. Yeah, flower people,
the flower people did it all. Put your dick in, explode. Go to 11. All right, baby. All right.
Okay. So I thank you for having me. No, it's wonderful to have you. Okay. And I'll make sure you
have something nice and warm on top of you tonight. Thank you for first. All right, but thanks for listening.
DataSourceCoat.com, out of recovery.com. Love you on. Love you, too.
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it. On the high performance podcast,
delivery network from Podjo and limelight networks. I love it.