Delta Shira Charlie 313
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass
In the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk
I'm testing this battle curry
Coming here once again, something happened
Nor the California from the Curry condo
Your daily source code, for Tuesday's on
You're staying right in one, four, three
Right on, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Making plans, more than the care, and people go
Ten happy faces, ten as lonely as yet
House, number one for three
That's where we're the way we live, all of y'all
Everybody can be our one by four, yeah, all of y'all
One from the corner we've been by a drive
Take all right and mark for we got nothing to hide
Take a start just one bite to our ride
Never say that good boy with your heart
What do they want to do, what do they want to do?
Five, number one for three, that plan went
Let it all go, let it all go, let it all go, let it go, let it go, let it go, let it all go, let it all go
Come on, over with three, count it up till you've got a filme
Come on, go, let it all go
Let it all go, let it go, let it all go, let it all go
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
oh come that one or come yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah shit, you
You know, it just doesn't get any better than to kick off a show with some cowbell from the
Pods eight music network.
I caught that one on the ultimate mix podcast.
That was, oh no, you hear that?
That's my new blackberry is going off on the second stingray, one, four, three, it's from
music.podshow.com, and it's from their CD Ghost in the attic.
Yeah, indeed.
Got a new blackberry, everyone got an upgrade in the office.
I have the 8700 model, the 8700 Charlie C for singular, I guess.
And I got to say pretty impressed.
This is the one with the new screen, it's got a faster processor inside, it utilizes
the edge network, actually quite nice I have to say, it has a full-fledged internet browser
in it, not just like the singular web browser, you can choose between which one you want
to use.
Yeah, I like it.
I really do.
And it was real simple reconfiguring everything, you just had to enter the IMEI number or something
like that, and then re-sinked it up to my Mac with Pocket Mac.
Voila, Presto, it was completely ready and beautiful.
Let me just put it over there.
So it doesn't bother us too much.
Let me see, so I did spend some time configuring a couple new applications.
The coolest thing is Google Maps, it's basically it's a hybrid between Google Maps and
Google Local.
It's an application that you actually load onto your device, you can download it over
the air.
And you just type in an address or a zip code or if you want directions and it gives
you the map and it gives you the satellite images too and it's really, really fast.
It's unbelievable.
You can even put an, not IKO, but like the consumer airport codes and it'll, it'll
show, it'll take you right there, it's amazing, I was able to find the cottage, although
interestingly enough, and I think this is still the same in Google Earth and any Google,
was it Google Maps.
If you look at the address of the condo, it basically shows one big construction site because
the pictures are that old apparently.
And then I installed this IM plus, and it's a trial version, but IM plus basically gives
you instant messaging clients for, what is it?
Yahoo, MSN, AOL and Jabber and Google Talk, and so I've configured all that, and that's
actually pretty cool.
I haven't had enough, I am traffic to really be able to give you good report, but the
speed of it all is certainly getting there.
That was really the problem on previous Blackberry devices.
This new one is just fast and it's nice and, like, I really like it.
And you can find that, of course, I'll put a link in the show notes, but I think it's
a Google.com slash GLM Gulf Lima, Mike.
And the ongoing conversation about the mysterious Apple Powerbook audio echo issue.
Hey Adam, this is some feedback from DSC 311, where you were talking about the audio echo
with your power book.
And as I was sitting here listening to your podcast, I was having a conversation with
you while you were talking about the problems that you were having, and it went something
like this.
Hey, you know, this is very, very freaky.
Now I know that certainly some people at Apple listen to this podcast, so let's find out
about it.
Is it something that can be fixed?
Is it a hardware problem?
Yeah, it can be fixed.
Now, and it's definitely not a hardware problem.
Or is it a software problem?
It certainly seems to be very intermittent.
I actually rebooted my computer before doing the show.
That's not going to fix it Adam.
Just to make sure that I'd be kind of fresh with a clean boot up and amazing.
You don't hear it happen very often.
It usually happens when I'm using, you know what?
It could be a quick time thing.
No, that's not a quick time Adam, because I think that it only happens when I'm using
iTunes, what I'm using a quick time.
I'm trying to think if it's ever happened while I was watching like a Windows media maybe
clip or something.
That could be, but certainly gosh.
Okay, well, we have to start tracking this and start paying attention to when exactly
it happens.
Obviously, a culprit that comes to mind right off the top of my head is a quick time.
But it certainly is not very good if you're using your machine for podcasting.
No, you're right Adam, and it's not a good thing at all if you're trying to record.
But thankfully, there are a lot of people out there that are having this problem and there
is a documented fix.
The thing that people are finding out there right now that seems to fix this problem,
although people aren't sure yet if this fixes it 100% of the time is if you go to the
library preferences file that's at the root level of your hard drive, not your user library,
but the OS library.
So go to the root level of your hard drive, go to library and preferences and look for
the audio device settings preference file.
The name of that pile is com.appel.audio.device settings.pless.
And if you delete that, then that seems to fix the trouble that a lot of people are experiencing
with the echo issue.
So give that a try.
I haven't tried that myself, but I've got an older 15 inch power book, so I'm not experiencing
the trouble.
But give that a try.
Let's see if that works.
And if that works, then maybe we've got it fixed.
And as always, I'll go ahead and get my plug in here.
People can check me out at nulmyster.com, and I've got the nulmyster podcast there, and
it's just kind of the, I call it the ramblings of an everyday kind of guy.
So it's just, I've put it together for friends and family to keep track of of what I'm
up to.
So it's not the world's greatest podcast, but it seems to work for all my friends and
family to keep track of what I'm up to.
And we love the daily source code.
So keep up the great work at them and take it easy.
Right on Robert, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much everybody.
Well, let me just get my levels all straight here.
This is, if you listen to this on serious satellite stars 103, this is the daily source
code, start of the pod show line up four hours of pod cast on channel 103.
The problem with the audio last night, after I'd kind of wound everything down, I turned
on actually with the ultimate mixed podcast, that's how I heard, I actually got another
song from that show, which I'm going to play at the end of today's source code.
So I had a nice bubble bath, you know, and I had the sound system hooked up to the
logic tech MM50, so I got some boom and sound, and if it didn't happen again, it did.
It started echoing, it went away all by itself, so I didn't have to actually get out
of the bathtub.
And let's, you know, it's not an echo for those of you who haven't heard it, it's like
a CD that gets stuck, just keeps on repeating at consistent intervals.
So it came back, after I did the P-list deletion thing, there's also reports of this happening
on other Mac hardware, on-board snare, I think, and that's how you are on-board, no,
on-board.
I think it's probably on-board, Gmail messed up, the, uh, some characters here.
Happens as well on my Mac mini and my iMac G5.
Haven't had it happen on either on my G5, not the one here at the condo nor the one at
the cottage.
So now wondering, is it, is it related to specific hardware, or, um, is that just a fluke?
I mean, if it happened on different hardware, then it has to be, um, something OS related,
or maybe some new components that got put into these new machines.
I don't know, but, uh, it definitely is, uh, it's not cool, you know, it's, it's got to
get fixed because this is why I got this computer and, uh, although it hasn't happened
a lot during recording, it is extremely annoying.
Ah, let me see, what happened here, I thought I had, uh, I think you'd, uh, was this,
I had, uh, was this, oh, man, I hate it when this happens, okay, I'll just
play it off a quick time here.
This was, uh, a comment that came in about, um, language, specifically the language
used on this podcast.
Hello, Adam, this is Stephen Pender from karate cast.
You know, while back I was listening to one of your shows and I believe a person had left
you a comment, uh, saying that he had reported you for not having an explicit tag on your
show and I thought about this and I know that, uh, some people may think that you use
some harsh language on your show and that it may require this explicit tag, but you
know something, I'm thinking to myself here that it really after watching most of the shows
and the ratings, I'm thinking it probably wouldn't be a half bad idea to throw an explicit
tag on your show.
Your ratings would go up because it seems to work for everyone else and believe me,
I thought about it for myself, I'm, I have a family show, it's rated G, but I thought,
you know, something, I mean, my ratings are going up right now and they're very high.
I'm featured on quite a few sites and I'm in the top 50, I guess, for most of them in sports.
And I thought, you know, I could go even higher if I was to put an explicit tag on my show.
So what I thought actually is that I would test this theory.
And now for the explicit portion of our show, I'm sure all of you that this is an honest,
but this tastes, so he goes into this whole thing, uh, it lasts for like another two minutes,
so I'm not going to play the whole thing, but, you know, I was thinking a lot about this,
particularly listening to Howard Stern's first show on, um, on serious.
And already you can see the presses is, I have to say, I'm so disappointed yet again by the press.
Man, you guys are so fucking lame and stupid.
It was like, oh, well, it was, uh, it was pretty tame and Howard didn't really, uh,
you know, get her to any bad, fall, language, or obscene, or indesian, but, uh,
like, you're missing the whole point.
It's, um, that stuff is an exception, not a rule.
It's just so you can remove the filters.
That is where the brilliance is going to come from.
It's not going to be from being able to say everything, uh, but, uh, not having restrictions.
That's really what it's about.
And, and I could really tell, listen, I've listened to Howard Stern for many, many years, um,
a lot of them while commuting into New York on a daily basis.
And that's really, I would have to say the best way to listen to him.
You know, we're going, particularly when, uh, before he had really hit big incindication,
and it was still, um, very much a New York show.
And, um, you know, it's, you can tell that he's so relaxed now because he's just able to drop all the filters.
He's still, he's, his mind is so trained.
And by the way, we don't all use, uh, uh, uh, explosives, uh, in, in all of our speech all the time,
you know, that just doesn't happen that way.
Um, and so it would make no sense for him to all of a sudden start swearing and, uh,
it makes no sense.
I don't understand why the press thought that that was going to happen for some reason, um,
but he'll be able to explore new boundaries.
And that, of course, is, is what we've discovered in podcasting, um, and what we've known for quite a long time,
how wonderful that is not to have to have these filters that are, uh, are always, uh,
consistently present and, uh, and you're always aware of them.
It really slows you down.
So, um, um, I, I was just, you know, kind of flabbergasted by what I was hearing and reading everywhere,
because I actually thought those show was great.
It was just a typical Howard show.
You know, only some of the bits were better, um, because, and just some of the stuff he was saying,
just what the crew was saying was just good because, uh, all the filters have been removed.
Uh, anyway, uh, good day, uh, at the office yesterday, uh, just kind of caught up with everybody,
uh, uh, today we get the big demo, and, uh, that do we is, uh, Ron and I are getting the big
demo of all the stuff that everyone's been working so hard on for the past, um, and just months
and months, but really, uh, the hardest between, uh, Christmas and New Years.
By the way, the company grew with five employees, uh, uh, over the holiday month.
And so I had a lot of new people to meet today, um, extremely smart people, uh, doing all kinds of
just amazing stuff.
And, um, I'm, um, I'm really proud of the stuff that I'm seeing.
So, look for, uh, for more comments about that in, uh, in the, in the coming week, and hopefully
we'll be opening some stuff up at the end of this week or next week, whatever.
Uh, coming up, uh, we've got some more, uh, music from the podcast, music network, um,
got a cool audio comment about the flight simulators.
And for the first time today, Yadsey coming up, yet another drum cadence.
Hi, I don't walk on here.
And if you're wondering what it's like to live in Ohio, what there is to do in Ohio,
what bands are from Ohio, and whatever else I decide to put in the show.
Please tune in to the Life in Ohio podcast at hdp.
Go on slash slash life in Ohio, dot libson.com slash RSS.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do. We're our flank. We believe in an internet that's safe from virus,
hidden scammers. We're earthlink. We believe your personal information should be just that,
personal. And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe. We're earthlink.
Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you,
earthlink. We revolve around you.
This week on the squad cast walked out of the, you know, restroom and who is standing right outside the restroom,
Richard Simmons. And he turns around, looks at me, grabs my hand, he's like, oh, you know,
what's your name? And I'm like, and you said, my name's Anthony.
I think that's your question while you're doing that. What?
I'm on podcast pickle. By the way, voter first three times. Awesome. So, that's why you weren't finding
tonight, you're over to vote. Thank you.
So, Charlie, then you get the June gloom coming in and the June gloom?
Yeah. Do people actually call it that or is that real? Don't do, do they not call it that?
Uh, not bloody familiar with that. What a pleasant way to call Brian a fucking asshole.
It's like 530 out there right now and he's like, oh, these guys. By the way, he was looking
at all kinds of fun. Oh, hell yeah. You think he was? I think I actually heard him yell out, give me
to say it for it. But that's squad cast squad cast at gmail.com squad cast squad cast dot com.
You know, I've got so much feedback coming in over the earthling promotion that we're running in
the 32nd commercials that we're playing. And why know, earthling is a big client for us,
big customer. And we're working very closely with them and with their agency on, you know,
this whole conversation that we've been having about user generated advertising. But Steve
Gilmore opened up the Gilmore gang. I guess the show was posted on Monday. Yeah, yesterday.
And he just, he had this, this, not a rant because he's had, he's had the flu for like a
month or something. But just listen to what he said about about earthling and sponsoring the Gilmore
gang. It was said, I thought it was pretty cool. Oh, a second. I got to get it from, uh,
see, here we go. I think it's, you know, it's a good story. I don't know what to hear that.
So, yeah, Steve Gilmore, welcome to another edition of the Gilmore gang. Today we're going to
have a conversation about CES and the after effects of that conference and some of the announcements
excluding, of course, the Google announcements, which came after the recording of the show on Friday.
So before we get started, I want to say a couple of words about our sponsor earthling. I got
some email from somebody who was talking about how they weren't particularly excited about having
a mainstream advertiser on the podcast. And I just want to say what I said last week and I want to
put it in spades again. There is nothing more valuable than having, excuse me, somebody from the
mainstream world of advertising for my perspective, validate the podcast space and contribute their
support, time money and encouragement to what we're doing here. So, uh, if the person who's listening
to the show is put off by this kind of an ad, although I did notice that they indicated strong
with that this wasn't enough to defer them from listening to the Gilmore gang. The proofs and the
pudding, uh, if you think that the show and that the thought leaders who are on the show, John Udell,
Doc Seroles, Dana Gardner, Dan Farber, Mike Fizzard, and all the guests that we have,
the come on the show from time to time, if you think that those people are important to listen to
and important to support, then you should be supporting the people like Earthlink who are supporting
us, uh, give them the respect that they're giving us. Thanks. Uh, here's a message from Earthlink
and then we'll get on with the show. Right on Steve, way to go. Exactly. Exactly. Hey,
and the advertising community is going to have to learn too. We're all going to have to figure this
out. And that, by the way, was a fantastic example of user generated advertising. Hey,
congratulations to Brian No, um, I've played a lot of his stuff on the source code, uh, certainly
uh, pre the, the switch to all pod save music on DSC. Um, Nancy Sinatra. Now, by the way, if you've never heard
the show, it's called the Frank Truth. Um, and it's on the serious, uh, 103 on the stars. Uh,
I think we do it on Wednesdays. I believe it is. And, uh, because we can play RIA, music, if we
so wish. And the podcast was so good. It was, you know, it was very, very difficult for him. Um,
he's, uh, you know, he's kind of skating the edge there. But Nancy Sinatra posted a link to
his, uh, to his site from there from the Sinatra main website over the weekend. Um, that he is, uh,
Brian has reached out to the Sinatra dynasty many times. Never really heard much from him. But, uh,
this was the first time he kind of got a positive sign from some very happy form. Extremely cool.
It's a great show. Uh, and the, uh, the Sinatra clan is actually the Sinatra family.com.
That's fine. I, um, you know, that when, um, when, when I first learned about registering
domain names, I'm talking 1993, uh, and I'd already registered MTV.com and curry.com. I actually
for quite a while had Elvis.com. And I'd set up an email address, uh, which was king at Elvis.com.
And there was a one page website and it just said, you know, email the king. And somewhere, uh, in my
archive, uh, on some hard drive, in some place, I have thousands of emails of people who would
send, um, a message to Elvis. And they were really amazing. And you could tell that a lot of people,
you know, really were like kind of, you know, believing that he, uh, but he had an email address.
Uh, you could just tell from what they, uh, what they sent to him, uh, but then eventually, um,
the, uh, the presently dynasty got in touch with me. And I sent a nice little little letter that said,
uh, give it back. God damn it. And we'll sue your ass. But it was, it was said in a nice way. I guess,
kind of, um, get out of the drum cadence on the way. The folks on the serious satellite who are
listening to the show right now have to miss out on that. Uh, so we'll, uh, put the yachts see
early run in the show the next time we do it. Uh, we'll see you guys tomorrow Pacific Coast,
Hellway is up next for you on serious. And for us here, I got a very cool email, particularly if you're
into aviation or if you, um, you know, if you've ever used a flight simulator, um, I asked the question
if you could use the OSX X plane flight sim, uh, to do, um, instrument training.
I had him in its Andy last week in DSC three or six. You were asking about X plane and could
it be used in a professional way to learn instrument flying rules. I think it can, but then I'm not
a pilot. I'm just a user of the program. And since I haven't had anybody come back to you to confirm
that you could use it. I'd like to tell you a little bit about it, which might prompt you to take
to the east of the east of the east of the east of the east of the east of the east. There it is.
My, my, my is the best flight simulator. That was the, uh, the infamous Apple playback bug.
There is. It's got realistic aircraft, cockpit with working instruments. You can fly to any airport in
the world using VFR or IFR. And if you file a flight plan, the air traffic controller will
recognize you, uh, direct you safely past other traffic, uh, land you. And, uh, it does this using
the built-in speech of the size of it in the Mac. It does have working navigational aids, uh,
VFR, DME, nav and calm radios, and you have a transponder. Even without the scenery,
explain is the most useful flights them you can get. You can fly in any weather situation,
which you can dial in in the menu system. You can set the level of precipitation, whether the
weather is getting better or worse. You can even download meter information and load that into
explain so you can fly in real weather. You can also simulate failures of any part of the aircraft
and the probability of that happening over a random time. So you could practice, for example,
an engine failure happening at a random time. Good practice. It even simulates ice on the
comparator if the weather gets too frosty. The level of detail in this program is just amazing,
and I only told you a little of what it does. There are also lots of interest groups,
which are linked from the X-plane homepage, covering everything from aircraft to scenery to virtually
your lines. X-hifinplane.com. If you go there now, you'll see that the latest news is that
a customer of theirs who uses their software in a professional flight simulator to train pilots
has just got FAA certification. And if their story is true, they are the first software company
who produce a consumer grade flight simulator to ever do so. In summary, you just got to get this
program. If you're going to be a serious pilot and you want to practice those skills in the most
realistic situation, explain is the owner program that will do it. With it, you can practice skills
that you will use as a pilot in the real world. Buy it now. Buy it now. Yeah, okay. Well,
it's only 50 bucks or something. Thanks Andy, I appreciate it. So I've made a decision besides
the desperate desire for a biodiesel refinery plant here in the Bay Area. So actually,
Sue at Podshow headquarters, you said that if I could somehow get big mics and drums out of the
garage, so she could park there. I could certainly have a corner for my refinery. So that's
one project that I want to set up here. Another one, this place is so perfect for a flight simulator.
I'm really considering, and I've seen some pre-built stuff that is just amazing. And I could
put it right up against the windows. I've got that 180 degree view. I could put it facing the
window, so at night it could be like, you know, it would be kind of dark. The ambient lighting
would be dark. I could be just flying. Oh, man. I'm sick. I can't wait to do that. So much to do. So
little time. Goddamn. Another idea I had. This is something that I will do. I'd like to do it myself,
but if not, I'm going to have to recruit somebody to do a car podcast. And the car podcast is
actually it's pretty simple. And I think it could also be very commercially viable to go to different
dealers. Yeah, so let's say today we grab Volkswagen. And I do a sound seeing tour of driving in the
Volkswagen and give a description. And you could really, I think we could give you quite an experience
just by hearing it just listening to it. The narrative of course would be very important. And we
just go from dealership to dealership and rent any on that rent and test drive cars. You know,
like we actually want to buy it. And anyone who could dress up, you know, kind of nice. If you clean
up a little bit, then you can probably pull this off. So we could do it that way, but even more
exciting, I thought, would to be have a collaborative effort and have, you know, just members of
this car cast, you know, to select a brand and we'd split it up and then, you know, send it in.
And we'd put it up and we'd, uh, we'd make a show out of it. I'm telling you, this thing will really
sell cars again.
Yes, it is yet another drum kit. Thank you very much, Jeff Smith. Since I didn't have any material
for the yet another drum cadence, Jeff was nice enough to send something in that he did himself.
And I didn't realize this. I guess he's Dutch, or at least he lives in the Netherlands,
because it acts in his perfect. And he created a drum cadence, which he did entirely with, um,
things you find in the kitchen. It is appropriately titled, no can in the coconut. Hey Adam, Jeff Smith
here. I got a little drum cadence for you. I've been working on a kitchen, like to call it,
no can in the coconut, like it.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Thank you Steve Jobs for giving us garage bands
See? That's all you need. You don't even know Steak and Studio. You know the damn instruments. Just get yourself a power book.
Watch band and hammer away in the kitchen. It works perfectly.
You've got a drum cadence you want to share.
With the source code on podcast and ultimate mix.
Yeah, the blog spot.com.
On door.
Hey.
The valley up there.
I am under free.
Even though I want to the valley up there.
When they tried to pull me down.
But I am under free.
Just enjoy over guys.
All my tea, I don't.
Just come by my guide.
She's over my guide.
All my tea, I don't.
But she's a spider.
I am under free.
Even though I want to the valley up there.
When they tried to pull me down.
I am under free.
When they tried to come by my guide.
She's over my guide.
All my tea, I don't.
Just come by my guide.
She's a spider.
All my tea, I don't.
Just come by my guide.
She's over my guide.
All my tea, I don't.
I am under free.
Even though I want to the valley up there.
When they tried to come by my guide.
She's over my guide.
She's over my guides.
She's over your guide.
Of course, I don't listen to the radio that much anymore.
When's the last time you've heard a new reggae song?
Oh, yes.
My Jack Fashick.
I am not afraid.
You can find on the Podsafe Music Network music.bodshow.com.
And we're going to leave it for that.
I'm sorry, I'm not completely together today.
It's still a bit of the jet lag.
And just so much to do.
Hey, tomorrow I'll be back.
I'll tell you all about the demo.
Tell you about maybe we'll have a release schedule to let you know about that.
You know, we've got new podcasters coming into the network.
Lots of shit to talk about all that tomorrow.
On the midweek Home Day Edition of the Daily Source Code.
Hold on, let me get my...
Oh, by the way, for those of you who are in the comments.
This has nothing to do with cigarettes, okay?
Pot show.
The other white meat.