Delta Shara Charli, 3-1, 9.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Transmiddles?
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky and crispy.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Oh, fantastic! It's a battle curry.
I gotta tell you, I really despise it when I'm just late to rise,
but need a little bit of sleep.
So, daily source code is on the late side today.
Coming to you from a very sunny Northern California from the Curry condo.
Let me get some coffee and everybody.
I'm sad, jealous to me.
I love his wonders, and all the trips we have to take.
Where's the scrollfinder?
We have to take.
Where's scrollfinder?
We know these stars the way.
We saw a light stay straight through the day.
We're on a side.
We come and go and never let it.
You know it's time.
As for holidays, we'll dream about them.
And those will shine.
We know these stars the way.
We saw a light stay straight through the day.
We say through the day.
We go and let it go and let it go.
Okay, that would be haunting, I guess.
That's how I could just envision a rolling stone magazine critic categorizing that song.
Thank you so much.
I like it a lot actually.
I like it more than the blur track.
I like it a lot.
The first time I was able to demo the whole system or at least what we have of the system that's working now for the podcasters but more importantly for listeners that's really the stuff that I'm so incredibly excited about what we've put together.
I think I can't remember when I actually had dinner at a dinner time.
This thing is so easy, I could actually do my nails while producing the entire show, it's so fine.
We'll talk a bit about some feedback you guys sent me regarding using cast blaster and yesterday's sound.
Something else I tested yesterday and demoed which I'm just so happy about because it's working is purchasing music on the podsafe music network.
And I think that we are just about ready to open this up and see what everybody thinks and see how it works and get some feedback from well from you guys the listeners.
Yeah, some people like this.
I'm the DSC and you're talking about pricing for music on the PMN when you get your credit card system up and running for the public.
Personally myself, I think 99 cents for a free and clear MP3 is an excellent value and I would pay that for almost any song on the PMN right now.
And I would buy their music at the drop if I had free and clear.
Let's keep up the good work out. I'll be one of your first cast version when you get that up and run and thanks a lot.
Right on my brother.
Okay, so here's the steps we've got to take. So first of all, for those of you who don't know or maybe you're just tuning in or never listen to the source code or maybe you're listening on.
And serious satellite stars 103, pod safe music is a concept that brings together podcasters and independent artists or basically any artists who owns their own material and the copyrights and hasn't.
Given them well, I don't think anyone gives them way or as a sold them to a to a record company or traded them in some fashion.
And it's really simple, you know, when you sign up when you register at the pod safe music network artists agree that podcasters who are also registered it's a very simple licensing term which is essentially agreed to when you sign up you can read all the terms online.
When when you sign up podcasters can use your music download it use it in their podcast as long as they report it back into the network.
It's really simple so it's a great promotional tool.
The concept has been to actually turn on sales so that anyone because we get so much feedback from listeners who really want to get a hold of these tracks they want to buy CDs.
They it's a lot of the pod safe music artists by the way are also available on iTunes.
So the concept is is to make available individual tracks for sale on through the pod safe music network.
Through a one click actually is what we've been implementing and I really wanted to be the things I like about the iTunes music store is that they have my credit card.
So whenever I want something I just go in just click buy it's all you know I'm already logged in so I don't have to pull out a credit card ever again for you know for this relatively small purchase of 99 cents.
So we want so we replicated that functionality which is logical I guess or any any store that you're going to visit a lot of it just makes so much sense if if we know who you are.
And the the big thing here I think the big oh wow factors that we want to sell free and clear MP3s now we're ready to go the system is in place.
I've already purchased two songs in a test you know testing obviously but actually did have to pull the credit card and actually did have to pay my 99 cents.
Oh here's something that's very cool worldwide okay so there's no restrictions by market anywhere in the world and currently we're looking at just to get things going at the same pricing 99 cents.
And what I'd like to do is okay let me just back up one second so this will obviously not be compulsory for all artists because particularly the artists that came in you know this is a new deal so we want to give people an option.
The way it's going to work is if you're an artist and you've uploaded music to the pod save music network all you have to do is well when it's available it's not enabled yet all you'll have to do is just go into your account and any song that you want to make available for sale you just click a checkbox or I guess you'll be able to click one checkbox to make all your songs that you have uploaded.
Available and of course that'll only work if we have all of your information because we need to be able to send you money makes sense doesn't it.
And there's a whole whole bunch of other pieces that are going to be coming and strapped on to that as we move along but that's the start so what I want to do today isn't going to reach out to.
One or two artists I'm not going to tell you who now but I think you'll agree that it's the right choice for the test one or two artists.
And going to ask them if it's okay if we test with their song just to make sure that everything works I'd like to have some global reports and global feedback I already tested my UK credit card and of course my US credit card and they both work fine but we wanted to work all over the world.
So hopefully by tomorrow you will be able to participate in this test and now the test is going to cost you money if you actually purchase something will cost 99 cents but it will be great if we can if we can get the if we just make sure everything is working globally and then.
I guess it'll be turn time to invite the artist to turn on the the sales mechanism for the individual track so.
It's going to be it's going to be pretty exciting.
Let's see what else we got going on here a lot of response to to Rogers not necessarily Roger Smalls who sent me of course that wonderful.
Did he the other day asking or actually wondering what I smell like but people like Devon of some dwarf said okay I just had to write you that Roger Smalls jingle is just fucking hilarious it was all like I do to keep swearing off the road this morning when I heard it.
So we play it just one more time then yeah why not here we go.
Jeff Smith man you too much okay I hope you didn't drive off the road we don't have anything from Roger although I did see that he posted a whole bunch of stuff on his weblog again about how I see it was a bit disappointed that I smell of.
What do you say Asian women hairs or something like that oh man it's too much.
I'm going to do something it's here's what happened yesterday went to our board of directors meeting and.
What's really cool is and you know some of these guys who are on our board.
Control significant portions of the universe as far as I'm concerned you know they they're really involved in a lot of things and extremely well connected which is of course exactly why one of them is our investors.
And just get rid of the tea here this is I need a microphone stand here because I'm always hunched over when I'm in in the condo.
So so we show up for the board meeting I was like 10 o'clock or something and it's so cool when you get someone like a Ray Lane who basically ran Oracle corporation for a number of years.
Really you know as a guy who's involved a lot of things extremely busy and you know I hadn't seen him for a while since the last board meeting couple a couple weeks and.
And he says hey man where's Trinity.
It makes me and you know and it's not a business thing is purely a creative thing when when someone turns around and basically you know is saying hey I listen.
I don't just listen but I'm involved and I'm listening it was really it was nice.
And of course we didn't take Trinity because no one would let Ron and I drive in the same car.
At least not that car for for fear for fear that she wouldn't make it by the way the brake light is not coming on anymore so I guess that was just a momentary momentary thing maybe because of the rain.
But Ray also said that he hates it when I talk about my microphone he doesn't give a shit.
And I'm sure a lot of you don't care about it but since I did ask yesterday specifically about the sound of cast blaster.
And actually of course I record the show then I hit the button to make it go up to the to the podcast delivery network and you know so I didn't really so I already put it up and posted it before I actually heard what it sounded like and I heard some of the problems that you guys sent back.
Michael Berg just a quick comment congrats on the new laptop and cast blaster set up I'm guessing you'll be very happy with that yeah I am actually quite happy I didn't notice one thing during Roger Smalls intro the volume was going noticeably up and down especially during that yeah.
Don't know what could be causing it I think I found it because I had so essentially there's a way to set up cast blaster to use an external mixer and you disable the internal mixer but you're still kind of running everything through.
The channel that is labeled microphone and there's a limiter that you can turn on or off and I had that on and I think that that really just you know because it wasn't just my voice going through it was everything the music the whole deal.
So I think that's probably what would messed up the sound annoying is the title of this one from Chestnut Bay podcast Bob Robinson somewhere in Vermont cast blaster pumping.
During your really annoying Roger Smalls jingle oh come on it's not annoying.
There was definitely some pumping of the audio system when the jingle played the audio levels cycled several times so annoying or not it's a great test case.
See if you can isolate it to cast blaster not pretty sure it was cast blaster we're going to wait we know we're going to try this in a second so I got one more pumping here from.
Was it Mike Scott.
Yep just listen to three 18 yep the limiter is pumping especially on the music drop in your smart to use an external board and compressor limiter.
It's easier to avoid pumping digitally okay so I think that that was the problem let's just do this Roger Smalls thing one more time just to make sure that it's not anything other than.
Roger ready.
It's another message from Roger Smalls.
Roger Smalls.
Man.
Joes.
It's.
Man.
Joes.
Yeah.
So I'll have you know that yesterday I I presented all of our ways to our board of directors in my Metro sexual outfit.
I was so proud, I had my black Dolchukabana pants on, and my ugly boots, my black ugly boots.
And I was wearing a pink sweater, it was fantastic. I could see him all looking.
That hell was out of where? Where's the suit in the tie that we're supposed to have when we do board meetings?
Anyway, so that was my minor metro sexual moment for yesterday.
A couple of things for today. Let me see Leo Vagoda sends in.
Do you let in the UK have a promotion going? We can get a free mock three razor.
And you actually post a link to it. Who can argue with free?
Absolutely.
What does that say? He posts his own site.
Leo Vagoda, toothpaste.bind.org.
Wow, okay.
So, looks like the, the Gillette folks are gearing up in the UK.
Hey, it's not like we wouldn't take any free razors over here for registered listeners of the source code.
You know, we're raising our hands.
Giles says, as a follow to my previous email on the mock three and it's alternative use that my wife and I found.
I have a more conventional shaving tip.
Basically, you should always try and wait 30 minutes after waking up before shaving.
This gives the skin time to recover its normal level of topness.
After having been relaxed overnight, thereby hopefully helping to reduce cuts and providing a closer shave.
That's pretty, that's actually a good tip.
I mean, there's a couple of the, I think the first thing you really should do in the morning when you wake up is probably splash cold water on your face.
And then before you get ready to shave, then you kind of warm it up with a nice relaxing bit of warm water.
Giles goes on to say, I was also wondering if Roger Smalls has got any mail grooming tips that he could pass on.
I'm sure that if he has any, there would be of interest to many.
Now, that's a good idea.
Let's see if we can get Roger into the Metro sexual moment.
I somehow agree with you, Giles.
I think he probably does have some interesting tips that we would enjoy.
Quick note from Steve Harlow about stubble.
The way to do it is to not shave, but to use barber clippers.
Wall, that's Whiskey Alpha Hotel Lima, are the best.
The small salon type.
Use them like Swadeheads, use them on their heads. Swadeheads.
What the hell is a Swade? Is that someone who's bald? Is that what you call all across a Swadehead?
Experiment with the settings to get stubble long enough to be soft, so the girlfriend is tickled, not abraded.
But sure enough, to not be a beard.
I did this throughout the 90s until my whiskers turned gray and the look became less sexy and more like mold.
I'm back to shaving again.
I'm the one who used the single blade at big for 10, for a year.
I also use regular bath soap and lather up with my hands.
That makes me more caveman, but I can watch more figure skating and scrub my own toilets.
So maybe I'm not a complete jerk. Steve Harlow.
Thank you very much.
I've actually gotten some calls from people who have admitted that they too are, well, they're completely into the skating championships.
And it's even worse, yesterday I watched skating with celebrities.
Okay, and I don't know if I feel good about that at all.
Do you believe anything is possible? We do. We are a flank.
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers. We're a Earthlink.
We believe your personal information should be just that, personal.
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe.
We're a flank.
Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net, and discover what our internet experts can do for you, Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
Hey Adam, this is Nick Carver from the Wildle Fritz, jazz guitar podcast.
You know, so often at the end of the work day, I've got so many committee meetings.
I've got internal problems and I've got clients calling me and I'm thinking if only I could quit my day job.
Well, hey, I'm glad to be joining the pod shown network and who knows.
Maybe I'll be able to quit my day job.
But for now, I'm just going to keep broadcasting great jazz guitar music.
That's no little frets.
The jazz guitar podcast at podshow.com.
Right on my welcome Nick.
No, I don't fret spotcast.
New member of the podshow podcast network fantastic.
Look forward to hearing how you do with cast blaster.
Got a note from cast blaster Mike, by the way.
He was often the wood somewhere programming stuff.
He had to get away, you know.
That's developers like to do that.
I like to do that shit.
You know, just get away and have total silence and be one with nature in your laptop.
I got this email for to to me from who's it's from Shayna.
The email from from sharedmarryk.com.
Interesting.
And it's one of these lists, which I thought was pretty funny.
It's 15 things to do at a Walmart while your spouse or partner is taking their sweet time.
And so there's list of 15 things, which I think are pretty funny.
They would be even funnier if someone actually recorded doing these any one of these 15 things at Walmart.
And shit, if you send me any one of these, will you actually do it like a sound seeing tour set up.
I'll send you a t-shirt.
So let's just run down the list.
Get 24 boxes of condoms and randomly put them in people's cards when they aren't looking.
Okay, that won't work with sound.
Set all the alarm clocks in housewares to go off at five minute intervals.
That's a good one.
Make a trail of tomato juice or should I say tomato juice on the floor leading to the rest rooms.
Walk up to an employee and tell him or her in an office tone.
Code three in housewares and see what happens.
I'll be a good one.
Put a bag of M&Ms on layaway.
Move a caution wet floor sign to a carpeted area.
Set up a tent in the camping department.
Tell other shoppers you'll invite them in if they bring pillows from the vetting department.
Ask a when a clerk asks as they can help you begin to cry and ask,
Why can't you people just leave me alone?
Look right into a security camera.
Use it as a mirror and pick your nose.
While handling guns in the hunting department.
Ask the clerk if he knows where the antidepressants are.
Dart around the store suspiciously while loudly humming the theme from mission impossible.
In the auto department practice your Madonna look using different size funnels.
Hide a clothing rack and hide in a clothing rack.
This is a good one.
This is this would work great.
Hide in a clothing rack.
When people browse through say pick me pick me.
When an announcement comes over the loudspeaker assume the fetal position and scream
No no it's those voices again.
And last but not least.
Going to a fitting room shut the door and wait a while and then yell loudly.
Hey there's no toilet paper in here.
So this was for oh here it is for to from Ask Shayna.
Shayna is with a Y dot com.
Okay I like the last one.
They did cross Chris Rockwell do another a daily download yet.
Man he better.
He better hurry up.
I didn't do my dump for nothing.
Hey folks on the serious satellite Pacific Coast.
Hellway is up next followed by a Madge Weinstein Dawn and Drew and all of the pod show.
I'll talk to you guys tomorrow on our Friday.
It's running through the wrong speaker.
I got to put that through the different sound card.
Okay while it's just us here a couple things.
Oh yeah I got several emails about going to Australia.
Doug Mooney who I've known for a long time.
Who actually in his own way was quite instrumental in getting pod casting on the map.
He wrote a great story about pod casting.
I think before even slash dot caught on to it and certainly before the BBC showed up.
At the what is it?
What is he right for register dot com?
I'll have to look that up.
Anyway Doug Mooney I know from back in the digigic that digics days.
Those are the guys who are hosting MTV dot com when I own the domain name.
Let's see.
I've been to Australia three times Sydney twice Melbourne once as Doug Karen's twice.
Sydney is like San Francisco except this cheaper less hilly.
The people are more friendly and the food is most excellent.
It's also more water oriented with one of the largest ferry services in the world.
It's worth the trip especially if you can manage the depart rainy cold England in December to go down during the warm sunny beautiful season down under that's right because of course.
Summer and winter are perpendicular to each other down under.
Commence the family and he says shave closely first of course to take two weeks down under spend a couple days.
Quote working and the rest of the time taking in the beauty of the country and the hospitality of the country if you want to be a real or entrepreneur.
Maybe you could con submit a proposal to the Australian Ministry of Tourism to sponsor your trip and exchange for a daily podcast down under.
Well first of all Doug I've been to Australia I've been there for for two weeks and and I do love it and I just want to go back and I want to meet some of these podcasting.
Podcasts there seems like such as seen is going on and it is a beautiful country.
I don't know if it's if Sydney's better than San Francisco I think they you know each one has stuff that it excels in.
Michael Collins says business reasons to come to Australia.
Hey Adam I heard on the Delta share Charlie three one eight you're looking for business reasons to come to Australia.
Well if you come to Sydney I'd be happy to buy a Logitech MM 50 from you.
Hell I'll even buy you a cup of coffee.
There you go two business transactions.
I'm sure if you encourage us Australian listeners for some business you'll have enough business reasons to come to Australia in no time.
You know what you want to here's what I should do.
I should figure out when when of one of our board of directors is taking their private airplanes that direction and hop on board that would be business to be to go talk business for 20 hours.
That's not those kinds of business reasons I need obviously but appreciate the thought.
And one thing I just wanted to mention that was it really really surprised me.
It was either yesterday or the day before I saw some news that was reported by.
Let me see I have here from clicks dot com that's probably I don't know if that comes from news dot com where that's from but I know that I saw it on CBS market watch.
And it was it you know there's there's announcements about podcasting advertising networks and people doing add insursions and aggregation and networks and there's stuff all the time.
Which of course is good which means we are forming an industry but what surprised me is that pod track announced as reported by.
CBS market watch that let me see I want to I don't want to miss quoted here.
So they basically announced some of the podcasts that they're working for and what they're doing.
They've signed hundreds of top rank podcasts where's the one I'm looking for this was.
Oh man okay well while I'm looking for what I'm scanning this page to try and find exactly the exact wording what they said.
Is hold on I don't want to miss quote this shoot where's this thing.
Well maybe we should go back to CBS to marketwatch dot com to find it.
Okay so anyway what they said is that they are holding an auction.
So basically the advertisers are bidding in an auction for I guess the rate for a number of podcasts including.
To it.
This week in tech this week in technology which of course is the the extremely popular.
Technology gab fest produced and hosted by Leola port and of course he has the tweet crew on there including John C. Dvorak.
And here this it really caught my eye because I'm like.
Leola port is like the number one.
Well let me just say at his keynote at the portable media expo he said he would never ever take advertising.
Yeah he has a deal with I think AOL or something for bandwidth but he said he would never take advertising.
And here I'm reading that pod track is saying that they were actually holding an auction for advertisers.
To advertise on Twitter and I couldn't believe it so I fired off an email to Frank Barnico who.
Who writes those who actually wrote that article for marketwatch I said dude you know how can this be true.
It was pretty funny Frank said well I did ask the the PR lady twice like okay maybe you should ask Leo if it actually is taking place.
So he said he was going to get in touch with Leola port but.
I have a hard time believing that if it's true then I think that that is bigger news the fact that Twitter is taking advertising than anything else.
And and it's extremely exciting actually so.
Let's let's find out anyway I haven't heard back if if Leo has said this is indeed happening or not and I apologize I just can't seem to find.
This one particular this one particular quote.
But if you go to marketwatch.com you'll be able to find oh here it is.
Thank goodness it also launched an auction for three top podcasts including technology focused this week in technology and entertainment oriented muggle cast and Josh and Japan quote.
Advertisers.
And that's not the quote I wanted.
Yeah this week pod track began selling ad space on individual podcast and it's network and across multiple podcasts in the category.
Okay there it says this week in tech interesting interesting to see what comes out and what kind of what kind of advertisers are they going to be this is extremely exciting.
All righty let me see I got to get I got to get out of here. I got to get to the office where you got all kinds of stuff going on.
Let me play another song from the pod safe music network all read this girl's bio to you after you hear it.
But it was basically another recommendation from a listeners.
I was really keen to meet.
I thought was right on the make the leave.
Said he showed me how to breathe.
Said he can't get up to sleep.
Got no wakily from my sleep.
Only I'm my soul to keep.
See the words been never speak.
Make the strong but keep me awake.
Want to touch the stars we go.
See the art show with this bone.
Watch the lion flying free.
And the scale that took from me.
And he's got to take me here.
One of the stars they are going to use tonight.
There are no words to make it right.
But one has been to what has begun.
Many business.
I've been to these empty hopes of mine.
I'll reach all the words between the lies.
And draw some strength on what we've done.
Then eat this setting sun.
And I'll reach all the words between the lies.
And then I'll reach all the words between the lies.
And I'll reach all those words between the lies.
And I'll reach all the words between the lies.
And many of this setting sun
I've been through these empty hopes of light
I'll reach your words between the lights
And draw some strength on what we've done
And many of this setting sun
You said you'd walk with me again
Like a brilliant voice, my turn
Once sharp as anyone
Now the scorpion has stuck
I'm like a virgin all the time
I don't think he's coming
What else do I say on these tonight
There are no words to make it right
But what has given to us has begun
Many of this setting sun
I've been through these empty hopes of light
I'll reach your words between the lights
And many of this setting sun
This is Shuman
And the setting sun from the pod safe music network
A little bit of Laurie Anderson there at the end almost
As a former member of Dream
As it says on her bio on the PMN
Melissa Honderscills, opening for the likes of Britney Spears
In sync, the backstreet boys
98 degrees in Destiny's Child
Currently she's working on a new solo album
Which she hopes to release independently in 2006
Melissa, we look forward to your independently released music
And we want to help you
Just want to help you
And thanks to Brent Bradley who sent me the link to Melissa
On the pod safe music network
She said, great song and she's very hot
Thanks
That always gets my attention
Immediately clicked on it to see what was going on
Alrighty
Tomorrow we'll have the thank god it's Friday edition of the show
And then Saturday it's back home
I can't wait to see the girls
I really miss them
And I think they kind of miss me too
They've hinted at it
And it's going to be busy because I'm definitely going to have to go to Holland
In the next couple of weeks my mom isn't feeling too hot
She started with her chemo treatments
And the first one hit her like a fucking atom bomb
You know like three four days into it
So she's actually a
Admitted to the hospital because she couldn't eat
And she was completely dehydrated
So my poor sister man
She's the only one of the siblings
That actually lives in the Netherlands still
She's taken the brunt of all the stuff
And my dad is still a rehabilitation
And the dog is sick and all that shit
Anyway
We all got shit going on right
It's all what life is
It's all that the stuff that life brings us
And
But we'll be back tomorrow
And we'll party
We'll just continue to party
You know?
Because it's Friday
That's why
Take care everybody
Bye bye
Another pod show pod guest
Stick it in your ear