Delta Sierra Charlie, 3-2-2.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped my ass.
3-2s?
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need lost, thinking crazy.
I like to think I'm flying into this journey.
Oh, fantastic.
It's so curry.
I don't know if it's the resurrection of Jimmy.
But it will definitely put you in the mood for today.
It's Tuesday, Daily Source Co.
From the curry cottage.
Set the next on fire then.
Mother, dream, destiny.
Life's so bright, you can't see.
You go to the window, I'll see the students and we'll all go.
So good, can't be real, terrible.
You can't be real, you can't be real, you can't be real.
You stop so knowledge.
And say no to me.
Could I clean the rest of this?
I don't see.
So God knows it all.
From your faith, we've got a sunshine with God.
He's cooking.
We've got his cooking.
We've been running to live the madness, stay blessed.
I said this, always be so much to see.
And give me the talent to feel good,
stay blessed.
And give me the confidence to be worthy.
So good, can't be real, you can't be real.
You go to the window, I'll see the students and we'll follow.
I don't say hope, but I don't think we've got a sunshine
Well done, it's good to hear you, it's awesome to hear you
It's awesome to hear you, it's awesome to hear you
Cool to hear you,OS, feel so deaf
Girl tell me, that's awesome
Girl tell me, we're gonna sunshine
Well done, we're gonna attend
Oh man, the substitutes got his cocaine, not an endorsement of the drug, which by the way
I've never done in my entire life, can you believe that?
All the rock and roll showbiz I've been a part of, it's never even been offered to me.
That's right, that's actually something that when you think about it, maybe it's interesting,
maybe it's strange to you, but I've never swallowed anything, never snorted anything, never
injected anything, and it really never had any, any, any need to, but honestly, I don't drink
either, but we all know what I do do in my spare time.
Hey, everybody, how are you doing? It's Tuesday. Come to you from Curry Cottage. This is the
Daily Source Code. It's a big audio feedback today on the show, plenty of cool comments that
came in, including one from our friend, comic strip blogger. If you've never, or if you'd like
to put a voice to the interesting and varied postings that he puts on my Curry.com web
blog, then stay tuned for that update. Well, first of all, I want to thank everybody for all the
beautiful thoughts and prayers and poems, and just words of inspiration about the passing of
Jessie are beautiful, beautiful. By the way, I don't think I told you she's a mixed breed,
she was a mixed breed of golden retriever and German shepherd, just beautiful.
And today, this glossy magazine, this beautiful photo shoot, this series that Patricia did for
a magazine called Beaumont, which, of course, is like a fashion magazine. One of the pictures
is Patricia on the downs, just looking fabulous with a, you know, with a white like Russian hat and
a faux fur coat, and that she has a swubber, who's our little Yorkie, who
barks for three, as you heard yesterday on the show, and Jessie, the last picture of her alive.
As just kind of heart-wrenching, but thank you very much. It's, it's much appreciated and I've
been sharing all of those with Patricia and Christina as well. Thanks. Legal update. Um,
yesterday, of course, after I'd already done the show, the publisher of the magazine that
published the stolen pictures stolen because they were taken from Flickr from my account on Flickr,
which clearly states they're available there under the, uh, attribution, non-commercial share,
or like license. Uh, so these guys, apparently, are a little worried about taking this to court.
So they said, oh, well, let's try and settle out of court. Uh, we'll do is we'll place a
retraction and an apology on page four, and we'll pay you 1,500 euros. Which is about, uh,
what was that? That's like, uh, 1750 bucks or something like that. It's not about the money you
you guys. Um, what is very interesting, though, the, the apology that they said that they would publish
along with the, you know, if we accepted their, um, their settlement basically says, and I'm just
paraphrasing the translation here. Uh, we published pictures that we had no rights to publish. We
apologize to the curry family. Hold on, that's my blackberry still. Which, of course, is, uh,
is true. Uh, but, you know, that, that is not going to get you out of this. I mean, no way. No way.
What's interesting, though, is that they said, well, um, even though, um, you, you might have
to consider our offer. We're still going to publish the apology. So they're basically already
admitting guilt, which is really smart guys. But I'm holding out, not from money. I'm not holding
out from money. I'm holding out so that we have proof that you did something wrong and that we have
your spruedance and we can use that moving forward. And then, of course, there's a whole child
endangerment thing, which is when I'm really, really emotional about, um, although I, uh, knowing the
Dutch court system, again, this is a court system that does not have a jury. They have a professional
judge system. And judges will decide the case. And what's interesting is because the court
system is so overloaded when they run out of judges, they hire lawyers to become back of judges.
It's a fucked up stupid system. It really is. But this time, I do have the law on my side.
Certainly, when it comes to the pictures, the endangerment of a child piece, I think that's open to
interpretation by a by a judge. Because, you know, obviously, when you're a celebrity, then,
different rules adhere. And if you don't think it's true, do you just have to take my word for it?
Actually, there's an audio comment that came in that talks about just as very topic
from a podcasting perspective. And I wanted to start off with that today. Because it's something,
uh, it's a topic that is, uh, of interest to me. And I think that you'll find it interesting as well.
Listen to the comment first. Hey, Adam, this is Cory from sportshawks.com. That's SPORTS HAAWKS.com.
I wanted to comment about something that I've noticed in the podcasting community to start off.
And I've heard a lot of this over the last couple of weeks. People have been talking about podcast
there's a celebrities. And I can understand that. And I, to, I agree with them to a certain extent.
But I think that we are a better kind of celebrity than a Tom Cruise or someone of that nature is.
You know, we have this movement that's revolutionizing the media industry. If not the world,
we're getting all this exposure, even if the BBC still thinks it's recently or suddenly.
We have thousands of listeners subscribe to our shows going to the websites and downloading the MP3s.
But we're still ordinary people. And I really think that there's more to that.
You know, while we enjoy the success, we shouldn't forget where we started out. Us podcasters,
checking out the latest software, trying to, you know, scratch together some kind of show,
figuring out how to upload your audio files and host them, having all these problems with RSS feeds and XML.
And you know, it was very humble beginnings. So I think that the podcast is really
need to remember that we are not better than anyone else. We're still regular people.
And we should try to stay in glove with our listeners as much as possible by playing audio
comments or responding to emails, something, right? But staying connected and in touch with our fans
is probably one of the most important parts of podcasting. One quick thing before I go,
I've also noticed the camaraderie, if you will, within the podcast and community.
Really what it is, just everyone willing to help each other out. Pods say for pieces,
an example. Another one is something that I'm currently in the middle of.
You know, Kevin Reeves, the recording artist, two things, the song shine. Believe you played him about
a month ago. Kevin and I started talking, right? And now both of us,
okay, so mostly Kevin really, working on a theme song for Sports Hawks Radio. That's the show
produced by SportsHawks.com. And I just wanted to say that I think it's awesome how this community
of podcasters works together to, you know, to do any kind of projects. And just it's great. I love it.
I'll send you a promo in about a week or so. Peace.
All right, man, looking forward to the promo. And thank you very much for opening this
conversation, this topic of discussion. Because, and I'm obviously speaking from my own personal
experience here, I've been a, and I'll just say, quote, celebrity in Europe, have been a celebrity
in the United States. And I would venture to say, I'm a celebrity in podcasting. What's interesting
is that the, and this, I've witnessed this all throughout my life. What people always will say
is that it is the celebrity that has changed and doesn't care about their audience anymore.
This is just not true. What happens is exactly the opposite. The people around you change that
attitude towards you. By the way, celebrity from the dictionary.com, a famous person or
renowned fame, celebrity hood, synonym celebrity hero, luminary, name, notable, personage.
These nouns refer to a widely known person, the social celebrity heroes of science,
the theatrical luminary, big name and sports, notable of the constant stage of personage in the
field of philosophy. And so, well, let's take Tom Cruise as an example.
I can only imagine what this guy goes through. I don't know him personally. I can only imagine
what he goes through. If you just open up any magazine, open up any newspaper,
listen to anyone who talks about movies or actors, and they piss on him. Nine times out of ten,
because when you get really big and you get quote fame or celebrity, which I guess is because
you are celebrated for doing something interesting or good or being a hero, as they say here,
or social celebrity, that's when it all starts. At first, it's like, hey, go, man, that's great.
And then you are over-analyzed in anything you do. And what happens is people start to project.
And this is actually something that I learned from the podcast InsightWorks, where people start
to cast their own shadow over you. And if you go ahead and look at podcast alley or any other
forum or lots of postings around the internet about podcasting, there's a lot of negativity,
a lot of bad vibes, particularly directed towards me. And although I understand why people do this,
I think I understand the philosophy, it is not the celebrities who lose touch with their fanbase.
The fanbase usually grows so big that you can't just handle it anymore.
You know, and so what some people do is they get a secretary to read through the email.
And people actually suppose that. You know, say, oh, well, he probably doesn't read his own email,
and someone else is doing that for doesn't care about the fans. It's, it's, you have no idea
what goes on. You really don't. And a lot of this stuff is really hurtful. Particularly if you're
still trying to do the same thing that you set out to do when you started your career, whether it's
in writing or acting or movies or podcasting or music or whatever it is. You know, look at Madonna,
do you think it's nice to read what they write about her, about her body, about her family, about her life?
You know, what happens actually, I think is that the fanbase usually just starts to alienate
the celebrity. Now, of course, this is something that I believe is embedded in human nature.
So I can't take, I don't take it personally. I can't hold any responsible, and anybody
responsible for for what happens. But it really is something that just happens over and over and
over and again, and I've had multiple careers in different forms of entertainment, different forms of
business, and it is just unbelievable what people will write, what they'll, you know, the conspiracy
theories, it's, you know, and you actually set this up very interestingly with your comment,
you know, like we've got a nice little community. And then what happens is when someone
rises up above that community, could chunk, it's time the chopper's head off. And
oh, man. Oh, wait, like Barry, don't do that. Wow, these new, so I got the new
bottle model blackberry, which is the, what is it? This 7900 something. It seems to be even worse
with disturbance on equipment than the previous one. And this stuff is very difficult to explain
if you haven't witnessed it firsthand. You really, you really don't know what it's like.
So I think that you might want to take a look inside yourself. And sure, people do wacky shit.
You know, Tom Cruise jumping up and down on the couch in front of Oprah is pretty fucking wacky,
but you know what, it was frustration. Here's a guy who has just been beaten to a pulp.
People are rude to him and look, and again, I don't know him, but I see what happens. And I do
feel bad for him. And just open up any gossip magazine. Yeah, it's really funny. It's very funny.
It's funny to make little puns and make jokes or come up with conspiracy theories about what they're
doing. But when it's you, it's not so funny. Particularly when you're like, hey, dude, I didn't
change anything. This is just how I am. And you know, people start to microanalyze and scrutinize
everything you do. So look at yourself first before you start to say that a celebrity has
gone off the scale or jump the shark or off his rocker. Dude, I'm still the same guy,
sitting the same freaking cottage. In fact, I downgraded from a castle to a cottage. Just trying
to make things happen. Just trying to make things work. And we're getting pretty close to sharing
a lot of that love with the podcasting community. Um, to anyway, take a look inside yourself
before you start to project onto celebrities in any field of expertise. Let's move on. Shall we?
Don't want to get depressed or anything. What's this from the School of Podcasting?
Hey, Adam. This is Dave Jackson from the School of Podcasting.com and the Musicians Cooler.
Got a quick creative commons question for you. Realize that you're going to probably turn into
the creative commons genius here in the near future. And if with all the different options available
to podcasts, just now to have advertising in their podcast, is that then officially make them a
commercial podcast. And if so, does that then stop them from playing music from the podcast
safe music network, realizing that some of that creative commons licensing may have some issues
with commercial podcasts. So as we all plan for the future, and we all started thinking about
adding advertising to our podcast, is that something that's going to kind of screw things up
with playing podcast safe music. Love the daily source code. And I wish you all the best of luck
with your court case, and I really hope you stick it to those bastards. See you later, Adam.
Thank you. Okay. So just to reiterate, the term pod safe music, which was coined during a,
as far as I can recall, I got to be so careful about saying this stuff. As far as I can recall,
during a trade secrets with Dave Winner, myself, we came up with the concept of pod safe music.
That's, it's a pretty broad concept. Essentially, it means that you've received permission to
play this and all fees associated with broadcast or performance rights or synchronization rights,
or what have you have been waived. So whether you have creative commons, whether,
well, I can only really speak for the, for the situation in the United States, because the
ASCAD BMI definitely works differently than in other countries, particularly in Europe.
But as a copyright owner, if you own the copyrights to your work, you can determine whatever you want.
You can write a license to the daily source code that says you have to pay a thousand dollars per
each time you, you play a song and you can give it away free for someone else. It's up to you.
It's your property. You know, that's what it's about. Copyright is your property.
Now, you can license a piece of work under different licenses for different people. That's very,
very normal. So if you have a creative commons license, and that would conflict with being played
in a podcast that is commercial by nature or has a commercial zenith, then the creative
commons license that you choose, if you had for instance a non-commercial creative license,
well, then it could not be used. Now, the difference here is on the podcast music network,
music.podshow.com. When you sign up as an artist, you are basically creating a new specific
license for other podcasts that are registered on the system. And it makes no difference whether
they're commercial or not, the license means they can play your stuff as long as they
report it back into the network. And by the way, as we're moving forward on development,
that reporting process is going to become automatic. So you won't have to think about it anymore.
You can just play it. You can actually mix it, mash it. If all goes according to plan,
it'll still show up as played in the podcast music network, which also means, and I'm hoping,
and we've got the George the Russian scientist working on this stuff, that if you were to use a
little piece of music to mix it into a promo or something, that it would also would be
accredited at the podcast music network. That's some of the technology behind it all that we hope
to be coming out with soon. And we will be talking more about the podcast music network and pricing,
since I didn't get to that yesterday when Patricia walked in. But you know what, I don't mind,
she walked in, you know, came on the show, it's cool. Aloha from Mikey Key Adam. This is Kurt
from the digital slot pod at digitalslob.com. Look, I know you've got to be busy right now,
but I just wanted to bring up something that's surely occurred to you, but maybe not all of your listeners.
And that is that there is a large fraction of people out there who don't listen to podcasts with an iPod,
or even an MP3 player, like me, for example. Sure, I mean, I give my iPod some fresh air every now and then,
but probably 50 to 60% of the time I'm listening on my I'm hacking my comfy chair.
As a digital slot, I've really got to have a good reason to leave my comfy chair. Anyway,
I've got this my space page and many of my friends email me saying, hey, Kurt, I'd listen to your show,
but I don't have an iPod yet. So it seems like dozens of times I've had to email them,
telling them that their computer isn't MP3 player. I think there's still a big education task out there ahead of us.
I know Rob over at podcast 411 has been doing a lot to educate the potential
podcasting, listening populace out there. And no matter how many listeners you've got now,
you're kidding yourself if you think everybody out there knows what the hell is going on in the podcasting world.
But I just wanted it to suggest, I know I'm preaching to the converted here,
but I just wanted it to suggest that all podcasters and podcasting listeners for that matter,
spread the word that basically, you know, you don't need a fly to kill a fly swatter.
You don't need a sponge to make a sponge cake, and you don't need an iPod to hear a podcast.
Just a kind public service suggestion from your friendly neighborhood digital slot.
Mahalo Adam and Aloha.
Aloha, my friend. Aloha to you too.
Absolutely right. And we do need to do a lot of work on that.
I have heard so many times. I don't have an iPod, so I don't think I can get podcast.
Yes, you're very right about that. That is, of course, the drawback to the name,
which on the other hand got us a lot of traction. And we definitely, you know,
lead stuff of the iPod to get that traction. So, and let's be honest, the majority of portable
players that are marketed as portable players, I'm talking about cell phones, are of course iPods.
But yes, this is a big part of what we're doing with at pod show.
When we start our campaign, which as soon as the PDN is launched and we're getting people into
the network, then we're going to go on our 100 million listener march. And a big part of it is
saying, come over here, enjoy podcasts. We're not going to put the RSS, you know, stuff up at the top.
In fact, if you look at what's going on in podcasting online, a lot of what you're seeing
is geared specifically towards the podcast community. And I think there's a very different way to
look at a show site. It shouldn't necessarily have to be a weblog. It is by default from
many people because it easily creates the required RSS feed. But we're going to, we've actually
done quite a lot of work on trying to make this as easy as possible. And really to get the
listeners involved, give them tools so that they can get involved with their podcasts, promote their
favorite podcasts. And also, talk amongst themselves. And that will be a part of what we're launching
a couple of products. Of course, we have the pod show delivery network. We have pod show plus,
and we have my pod show. Ah, is there enough pod show in there? I think so. So be on the look out
for that. And indeed, make sure, if you just tell one person, they're going to tell someone else.
If you turn one person on a podcasting, and you'd be amazed how many really smart people just
don't understand it and can't parse the information of what a podcast is. How do I listen to it?
And that definitely is up to us. So if you're listening to this before, um, you hear that my
Dutch slept in. Eccrepted. I was going to say, if you are, for instance, listening to this show
on serious satellite stars 103, and you want to know more about podcasting, and you don't have
an iPod, no worries, because you can just go to any computer, or you can go to podshow.com.
If you want to go to this show, go to dailysourcecode.com. You can click on the link where it actually
says direct link to the show, and you can listen to it right there on your computer. You can download
that. You can burn it onto a CD. Um, you could email that to someone. You could file share it. I mean,
all of that is completely cool. And that is what podcasting offers in its consumption mechanisms.
Speaking of those very same people who are checking us out on the serious satellite stars 103,
one channel over from Howard Stern these days. Um, the satellite windows closing up next will be
Pacific Coast Hillway followed by Madge Weinstein, and of course followed by Donor Drew. And I'll
talk to you guys tomorrow for the hump day edition of your Delta Sierra Charlie.
I got this great countdown timer called Countdown Clock. I'm running it on the, uh, on the
PC, where I use cast blaster these days. And that's the default sound when your timer is up. I thought
it was just now. I hope it's part safe, by the way. Hi, I don't carry. Here is comics trip
blogger, and I would like to ask you two questions. First, uh, when approximately this podcast
delivery network will be starting, I'm interested in it, and I presumed that a lot of other people
are interested. Second question, what does Shiba model have you purchased? I also have Toshiba
not book. I have tablet PC, but probably you don't have tablet PC. So what Toshiba model
have you purchased? I am just interested. Thank you. Bye. There he is, ladies and gentlemen.
The illustrious comic strip blogger, who, um, depending on his mood, has something interesting to
say, or something interesting to say in a very fall way. Comics strip blogger, uh, the podcast delivery
network. Um, well, it's going into beta. Uh, I believe this week, as we signed up a whole bunch
of podcasters. Uh, well, actually, we, we made an offer, uh, and most of them signed up, which, uh,
I met with just as many people as I could at the portable media expo. And, uh, internally, we call
these people the super 30 or the data 30 or whatever you want to call them, but they know that they're
coming in to try out this new system. Of course, the delivery network part, um, uh, is crucial.
And we spent months and months working on, uh, on getting the right partner in for that, um,
to, you know, so we just don't want to go through any of the, you know, if you get successful
and this, this stuff really works and we got a hundred million listeners coming in and we got
stuff rocking and rolling. We don't want bandwidth and scalability issues to be a problem. Um,
so that part we saw. That's, that really took the longest and, uh, these first podcasters who
were joining the network will come in and they're going to help us figure it out. I don't think
it'll take very long, uh, after that before we start letting more podcasters come in, um, and,
you know, of course, with that comes, uh, comes the offering. Um, and it will be free.
I just want to reiterate that free. They'll be the different levels of what you can do with, uh,
with podshow. Because we've noted me, you know, we've never made any, uh, any secret that we're about
helping you make money, helping us make money, and actually helping your listeners make money as well.
So look for that, uh, look for some beta reports to be out in the next week or so. And, uh,
you know, we're not going to probably open the door wide open for everyone to come rushing in.
We, we still want to scale this up, uh, carefully. Um, so there will be, uh, I don't know if we're
going to do, um, you know, like open the door for 100 people at our time, or the invite system is
one way, but that's not, that really doesn't help you with scalability. That's just kind of like the
hype it up. I don't think we need to do that. Um, and the second question, come extra blogger,
I have the, uh, podj, what is this? R205-s209? Is that it? No, this is making me sense. Let me see,
is that I'm marking on it? It is the 205 series. It's the one that comes with an external, uh,
CD DVD, uh, reader and burner. The thing weighs nothing, it weighs like, you know, less than a pound.
It's the thinnest notebook I've ever had in my hands. Um, but I really enjoyed, has super long
battery life. So if I needed to do something in a pinch on the road, I could even with the internal
microphone, uh, using cast blaster. Um, and, uh, yeah, it's, uh, it's a nice machine. I'm liking it.
I still do not like the windows experience, but hey, at least I can, uh, use it without the audio
stuttering. It's funny. You know, Apple, of course, recommends to get rid of this audio stutter, which is,
you know, incorrect that that's happening on a very expensive laptop. You know, their fix for now
is only use one audio application at a time. And of course, that doesn't work because you need to
have more audio applications open on the Mac in order to make it work. Interesting enough with
cast blaster, I only have one audio application open at a time, but it does work and it does get me where
I want to be. Hello Adam. I have a pretty big announcement to make to do a podcasting community,
but first of all, for those who don't know, uh, what my show looks like. Let's, uh, give a little
preview of it. 1984 won't be like 1984. Good your iPod, iPod tier, you like your Mac and I like your
Mac and I don't like the past. Apple, Apple, and the Mac and Has, of all of the scenes I've ever
seen is the only one that meets up here in the iPod, a thousand songs in the past. If today were the last
day of my life, what I want to do, what I'm about to do today. So I'm back on the microphone and
if today was the last day of my life, would I want to do what I'm going to do today? That's the
question I asked myself. And I answered the question by taking a pretty important decision.
I actually currently am a freelance IT man, so a freelance developer, so to be honest, I can
make a shit lot of money. But I'm going to stop this in three weeks and I'm going to start
earning almost no money because I'm going to turn to be a 100% podcaster. Actually, I'm going to be
kind of 50% podcaster and 50% feather because I will be getting something really nice with
my girlfriend to get her in a few weeks. And that's one of the reasons why I hit this opportunity.
So I will go ahead and I kind of quit my day job, but my day job was paying really well. And I
stopped this whole thing just for the last of the forthcoming baby and also for the last
of my show, which is called Pampampampampampampampampampampamp. As you know, and which is a show about
all Mac things, all Mac and iPad things. And it's in French, as you may know, but it's also
in English. And the third show is online with the Eddie Kim, the guy from Potion Factory,
that come the makers of Potcast Maker. And we also have the show in German and who knows
in which language we might do it in the future. So Adam, thank you for what all the things
you have done. And thank you for the PMM and thank you for the forthcoming PDM that I expect to use.
Soon. And by the way, I also, I would like, I don't know what I have to do to that. Maybe I have to
secure. As the first multi-speaking membrer of it. So whatever, I
would have to do. I'm kind of ready for everything, just for the importance of podcasting.
So, you'll soon owe everybody and return to pampampampampampampampampampampampampampampampampampampampampampamp
Yeah, this is also a message to my listeners that's still going to know that three weeks from now I will be in trial
You're doing your do fantastic congratulations on both counts by the way on quitting your day job doing a full-time and on the pending
release on the fatherhood
You know, let's quit. I think I mentioned this. I don't know if I did it last week, but in like two days in succession
Three people found out they were pregnant in a pod show
Actually, it was three guys to find out the girlfriends or wives were pregnant, but you know basically we say you're pregnant
And it's just wow, what a boom, you know
Fantastic and of course you will be more than welcome palm cast to join the
Potchow Plus podcast delivery network. You will more than welcome and we intend to help you fulfill your dream
Importions of today's show are brought to you by acu view who are underwriting the Heather and Janelle show
You can download that and check it out. No iPod necessary at download.acu view.com
Acu view is ACU VUE and other portions brought to you by earth link
Do you believe anything is possible? We do where are flink?
We believe in an internet that's safe from virus hidden scammers. We're earth link
We believe your personal information should be just that personal and we believe your internet should be a friend
Not a fo
We're earth link
Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you earth link
We revolve around you
Now
It's too loud, but we weren't on the set.
There's music right here, go ahead, go with that.
People from is it, all in the mind is that the results
might hopefully happen in the imaginations design and see it.
So you have a mind that sounds like to my activities and it was.
Then the breeze that I've heard is,
our knees open, knees in my life.
Singing this song, and you can't hope one's sing alone.
No, it's just, it's my most giving,
but let you know, you belong, yes it's on.
A stand-in room that's kept on,
keep on, keep on, keep on, keep on.
Everybody's in the stars, we live in Chocolatini,
and soon my people will be born.
I will keep learning music in your head.
There's music playing in your head.
So listen, listen, listen,
do what we do for the same.
There's music playing in your head.
There's tension,
so you can't do it.
You should have the time to keep that music.
Say, I don't keep that music playing.
So listen, listen,
do what we do for the same.
There's music playing in your head.
I've got you to say,
I don't have to do it.
All I can do, I don't have to do it.
Check the hornets,
I draw the line to the left,
I've got everything,
I've got all the stations,
and it made a bad expectation,
except for casual sacred holds and cubby old salvation.
It's a fun room that's kept on,
keep on, all too mood.
It's a soul-reaching meal,
this shit is fake,
I can still find people.
Too long, too, too,
but all right with this proof.
Too long, too,
For the boys, what had it on you who live a time,
you have to keep on,
have to keep my life new year in your head.
There's music playing in your head,
so listen,
do what we do for the same.
There's music playing in your head.
There's tension,
why you've got to use your attention,
I don't keep them used to think
We're gotta keep them used to think
So listen, all the time
And while we're here, we're gonna say
There's music playing in your room
Here we go
People there is nothing
There's music playing in your head
So listen, all of this out of life
I'll be burned, I see
There's music playing in your head
There's no tension
When you can't do it, you're not getting out
You can't do it, you can't do it
So listen, all of this out
You're not being burned, I see
You play in your head
There's music playing in your head
There's music play in your head
Armhand still love that song
Oh, you can find that at the PodsA music network music dot pod show dot com lots of talk about the PodsA music network in the next couple minutes, but first I want to welcome a new podcast to the pod show network
If you have kids who can or in within earshot, you may want to turn the volume down. It's not entirely family safe this promo, but welcome squad cast.
Hello, we have to cut a promo. Yes, we do. Yes, you do. He's got to do it. Can he just put them on hold?
I got the nod
May which means fuck you
I've known you guys for 15 years, and this is the way out here about who get together. We watch videos. We'd exchange gifts and shit
Fuck you
Wait a minute, the kid with cystic fibrosis is roll and drunks
Yeah, they're hot. I told you I dated ones that I didn't know with the whole boot. No, we're talking about not calling them orientation
Hard on with a person attached to it
So you've installed iTunes and you're listening to music on your computer. No, no, no, so she's just called me
It's not what I said. You didn't let him finish Larry. He was listening on his computer. No, go ahead. No, still no
You know what okay, go ahead
Get him my kind of call. Hey Adam. Hey
Daily source code listeners. I'm Scott. I'm here with my friend Anthony. Hello. We are from the squad cast
squad cast is a weekly show of actually four idiots is just kind of hang around and talk shit and be stupid in whatever and
For some unknown reason Adam wants us to join the pod show there. Yeah. Yeah. I mean maybe he had us head on something
Maybe we could have a week moment. I don't he is a fan of this and say I'm guessing somebody swapped it out with I'm gonna go with our snick and
Here we are
Really happy to be here. Uh, hopefully you just those of you haven't checked out the shows swing by and take peek-a-boo yarn
What we do you like to say we're you know, it's a sponge four guys Gavin about nothing and
Okay, she will hook up with some other shows and I have them do stick to shit. There's some fun things right right
So if you get some time come and check us out and add them thanks for inviting us
And I didn't hit my head
I don't know
The only criteria is if you want to join the networkers
You want to help make them that work grow and you want to grow your audience and you want to work towards quitting your day job. That's all
That's all that it takes you know
I'm not gonna judge what you do in your show. Although I did laugh a couple of times
I'm not listening to it
Okay, let me see what do we have to do? I got a couple things still schedule. Let's see first the promo
Regarding pod safe music
Matthew Eble is working on a series of
What is calling pod safe showcases and
He's gonna get back to me with a better lineup of the venues as he starts to figure that out. Let me just read the email
Okay, we're playing a one hour round of original pod safe tunes at the French Quarter Cafe and Nashville 10 to see French Quarter Cafe.com
That's Tuesday January 31st at 9 p.m. During Jack Scott's writers night
No, that's interesting. Venue is all ages no cover full menu with great gumbo
If we ever get a real supported pod safe showcase going on and can't get a whole high profile
Then you like third and Lindsey or the exit. I don't even know these venues
This place has a huge stage full-back line drums. Well, you know what? I think that this will be able to happen
I think we will be able to do pod safe music showcase as I think that
It's something that we really haven't worked on yet
That's why I played big mics two or dates yesterday
That's another way that podcasters can really help with the with the artist by the way
This is what traditional radio really has cornered pretty well, and you know the reason why clear channel has a huge concert promotion business is
Airplay really promotes
Live venues and so I believe the same can work with with pod casting and it could work very much on a meet-up like scale
You know where we have local chapters of pod safe showcases and
They put together promos that Daniel can run throughout the network or individuals can oh my god
I have a heartburn you won't believe
Oh
Oh, man, hold on let me take something for that. So they with me. Okay. Lay it open up the other mics so you can hear me actually travel over here
Now I've got to get something for this out of my coat pocket
You know what that is. It's too much freaking senseo hold on
Where's my emergency stash?
Here we go. Oh, yes
Sorry, I'm desperate need of a
Calcium product here. Okay, let me go excuse me while I put pop this in my mouth. Oh
Okay
Anyway, so I think that can really work check out
Matthew ebel.com for more information and of course for beer and coffee
Which is the name of his lifestyle?
yesterday
I didn't quite get to the pricing. I've gotten so many requests in your information about okay
So you guys are going to start selling tracks on pod safe music network
Which is really just that. I mean all we're doing is enabling the commerce portion now to make this the whole
Unlabel concept we have to be able to enable podcasters and listeners to help promote
And the easiest way it seems to me is through a kind of affiliate network so you just you know post a
Logo link a button whatever it is to to the artist page when the pod safe music network and right there
Any tracks that they have enabled. It's not obligatory or compulsory that they've enabled for
Purchase can be purchased right there
What surprises me is that
Just a ton of people are saying what's the split's going to be now? I
Let me just talk about this for a second. I'm not a big believer in
Let me back up laying back up. I'll tell you what I'm a I am a big believer in is is making this work
I'm not a big believer when it let's just take an example of these these ad sharing networks now
You know for Google to do ad cents. I know I'm confusing topics here, but it's just want to get it all out
When Google does ad cents the volume the sheer scale of this is so incredibly large
That it it works with podcasting. I don't know about
Advertisers showing up with their credit card and saying you know give me a couple spots here a couple spots there
I think that that's going to be very disappointing. I believe much more in taking the risk and guarantee
Payment based upon performance where the we sell advertising or not and that is and by the way
Advertising is not just inserts before after a podcast. Yeah, of course. It's a part of that
But that's not the end all the be all that we believe in valuing the relationship between the podcaster
And their audience whether you have a hundred thousand or a hundred listeners makes no difference you will be able to participate
In sponsorship opportunities at pod show
So we don't talk about splits. You know we guarantee money. That's what we do and we go off and we bust our ass and go make the money for you
So you have no risk that you put on yourself. We take the risk. Okay
Now about the pod safe music network
I really don't know. I mean we have all kinds of thoughts and ideas and no one can really tell me exactly what it cost
99 cents song what you wind up having or what you wind up getting as an artist as an independent artist that is
It kind of it's all over the map and it depends of course in how much you sell
I think this is something that we have to figure out and I think that the beta part of this
Of this program we're just going to roll it out see if it works get make sure people are happy with the entire purchasing experience
And we should figure out you know what the actual cost is going to be what the split should be and really
I'd like to turn around and say I'd like to hear from pod safe artists how much they're willing to split
with people who help themselves. So what do you think is fair?
And let's just take our 99 cent model. Let's not talk about percentages. Let's talk about cents. You know real pennies here
What do you think is a fair amount if if someone sends a buyer from a podcast show side or a
listener a fan who has promoted your music or maybe someone who created a music video using your music
You know if if a sale results of that what would you like to give away to the the promoters of the music
Tell me that and then make it a lot simpler to start and break it down
One things for sure as we enter this beta period and I'm just going to say this will be three months this beta period
Isn't we need three months to get through it
We're going to take no money from this everything will go to the artist except for the actual credit card transaction fee
Which I think is like nine or ten cents
off of the
You know off of your theoretical dollar
You're 99 cents because that's a hard cost us everything else. You know I don't even want to get into it if we start
Talking about splits first before we actually get anything going
I think it could it could really bring down the whole concept so pod show will take
Nothing while we roll this out and beta and we're going to work on this together
And we're going to come to something that's fair and we'll lay out our costs on the line and we'll see what we can come up with
I've never considered this to be a huge money making opportunity for for pod show
In fact we've never even put the pod save music network
I don't think it's even in any of our projections. It may be in the back of our mind, but dude
We have to have so much success before something like this you know it starts to pay off
Even pay off the cost of the people working on the pod save music network, but that's not the point
I'm looking at the overall
The bigger picture of what this can really mean and how we can undermine
Well, I'm not out to undermine the music industry, but let's make some stuff right let's create our own industry
And let's not go straight into the split's conversation so we're just going to say hey, fine
We'll take nothing while we figure it all out for the first three months and it's going to be up to the artists
Primarily to feed that back to us and remember
The unlabeled consists of the infrastructure the consists of the network
podcast a consist of the pod save music network, but really consists of listeners
fans
Who can also be podcasters at the same time, of course, and just podcasters who who love to play the music who are going to help promote this
That's what's working
Okay, so
Let me know what you think
That split should be and we'll work on that, you know, and we'll we'll come up with something in the next couple of months that everyone will be happy with
It's the same way we
We start the pod save music network to start with, you know, we had terms and conditions we got some feedback
We changed them no big deal and everyone was cool with the changes all they must say Cory
Doctor was never reported on that change after he wrote that
That article I'm boying, but that's okay. That's very typical of him, I guess
Hey, low strawberry barking for three again
Okay, so we've gone through that
Oh, had another comment here
Brendan Bulger Adam or Bulger, or maybe I enjoy this so each day and have been listening for the past few months
And this is based on Patricia's comment from yesterday the gaelic language is alive and well
There's some podcast in the language google podcast and gaeli
Patricia said who wants to hear gaelic? I said no baby. That's not the point anyone who wants to should be able to and in fact
In Ireland the European Union will recognize Irish is one of the national languages next year
I guess that's gaelic then a gaelic derivative and check this Microsoft release windows XP in office
2003 in ilish Irish gaelic just last year so
Wow, I wonder if I could learn gaelic that might be kind of cool
Just be able to throw some gaelic out there
This heartburn is killing me
Okay, a couple more pieces of the audio feedback this one really tickled me. I didn't think anyone would actually take the Walmart challenge, but yep, somebody has
Ladies and gentlemen, at times, there is my kids
Welcome to Walmart. That's right. I'm hurry to you remember this
And it's said one of these lists which I thought was pretty funny. It's 15 things to do at a Walmart while your
Spouser partner is taking their sweet time and
So this list of 15 things which I think are pretty funny. They would be even funnier if someone actually recorded doing these any one of these 15 things at Walmart
And if you send me if you send me any one of these will you actually do it like a sound seeing tour setup?
I'll send you a t-shirt
Make a trail of tomato juice or should I say tomato juice on the floor leading to the rest rooms
I'm pushing my cart and hopefully this works. What I've got in my pocket. I've got a small
Sunni deep bottle of the kind of plastic one the kind of fine
I can your lunch bag
And two in and why does I have to the bottom and I drill the small hole and in that hole I stuck a
A piece of tubing from the fish deck
And I've got this thing in my coat pocket. I've got a little hole on the inside of my coat pocket
And then running inside my pants down my pants ladies this too and it this works that I can reach in my pocket
And undo the clamp on the fish
hose and the tomato juice that is now in the Sunni deep bottle will run down the tube and onto the floor
And it will be very discreet. Let's see how this works
All right, have I done the clamp? I'm going to try to keep moving while I did this so I'm very
Inconpicuous
All right, it's dribbling out
Okay, it's really stuck into
Flow well
Okay, now I'm here
I'm afraid to pull that look at it
And that's gross, is that not cool?
I'm going to keep going. I'm going to grab and go on in the bathroom
While handling guns in the hunting department, ask the clerk if he knows where the antidepressants are
Hey, could I look at that one chest or anything over there
This one is this one right here. Okay, I'm going to start
You go sir
It's really nice
How about how about how much is this thing? I'll talk to you since you're not
All right cool. How about can you go? How about that limit to right next up?
Let's see what I'll try to do
You go sir
Does this shoot pretty?
Straighten them to go and pull my stuff
Have you ever shot it?
No sir, but
The way the staffs
Otherwise it returns, I'm guessing it's a pretty good
Okay, great. Can you go? Hey, you got a question
Um
Where do they sell the antidepressants?
Excuse me sir
Hey, yeah, antidepressants. Where can I find the antidepressants?
The antidepressants
The pharmacy
I can't break them out. Great great. Well, I appreciate your help
Yeah, that's me
Well, I wonder if you want to get the entire trip filled with me in a Walmart with a bedtime story's
My kids love it. Don't be dumb. You got me at mkl.com
Oh, yeah, mb was an extra large. Bye, antidepressants
Oh
Extra large antidepressants away my friend
I only heard the promo. I haven't listened to them
I hope you did all 15 of them
That's so mean
We got to get your better recording system though because the quality was
Unfortunately it would be so much nicer. We had nice
Broad stereo phonic binorals sound nice and clear, but
Very cool
Man, that's excellent. I have like 20 more things I would want to do but we're already at 53 minutes
So I'm gonna leave it at that for now tomorrow be back of course with the
With the hum day and mid week edition of the daily source code and enjoy the rest of your day
Thank you very much for subscribing if you are subscribed to just listening
Which could be just on your computer or you could be burning it to CDs?
Doesn't have to be on an iPod
DailySource code dot com for the latest episodes in the podcast feed out. I'm a curie dot com for your feedback take care everybody
Oh podcast stick it in your ear