It's Cali Lewis from Geek Brief TV.
I just listened to episode 1 of Shadow Falls and it scared me.
I know I'm the fearless leader and all, but there are things that get to me in this dinner.
I'm not sure I'll be able to sleep tonight.
Maybe never again.
This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Here's some.
Go ahead, Moonlander. This is Houston.
I'm stepping down the ladder now, Houston.
I am on the ground.
This is one small step for men.
One giant leap for Fubar Friday on the DSC 449.
Roger that, Moonlander.
Alright, boys, let's lose this tape and we can start the weekend.
I've got it.
Not like it matters.
I'm on the mountain.
Coming back with the records.
The orange circle actors.
Time to hold in.
Check it off while you sit.
Yeah, yeah.
Push it off while you sit.
Once in a cell, it's in my face.
Come to know your way through.
Make way for the jet set.
Because they're taking you off.
To start a new evolution.
The grass elastic confusion.
Gonna kill her.
Shut up while you sit.
Push it off while you sit.
Once in a cell, it's in my face.
Come to know your way through.
Start.
That's in trees.
Static or words.
If you fast forward through the song, welcome to the daily source.
It's a football Friday coming to you from the curry cottage in the
affluent suburb of Suri known as Gilford and how you doing.
It's a beautiful day here where I am.
I'd love to know is Saturday great.
Of course, it's winter down there today show.
As often happens, completely driven to you guys.
This is the stuff that's on your mind.
It's what you're calling in a bounce.
So if you want to change the course of the Charlie to a new heading,
all you got to do is call in and give me some feedback.
This is a question I received so often.
It's got you to hear.
This summer, I went tree planting and started listening to your back catalog.
Last summer with the SC198.
And I have one huge question that has been bugging me for three months now.
As I listened to maybe three or four episodes of the day along with some other podcast.
Where the heck does the $16 million worth of airplane scrap to my ass quote come from?
I've heard of just about every day, like most people who listen to it,
listening to it many times a day.
I have no idea where that would have come from or the context.
I've tried thinking about it and I've gotten nowhere.
If you could help me, you would make my brain stress level a lot lower.
Also, check out the band The Deep Dark Woods on the part of the music network.
I met these guys at a party, mentioned the PMN to them.
The next morning before I could send them an email with the link to it.
But it was already on it.
These guys are pretty on the ball.
Thanks. Have a good day and.
Folder.
Okay.
It doesn't matter as long as it gets clean.
Alright, thanks buddy.
Yeah, a lot of people asked me that.
The opening for the show is one of the most difficult things.
I used to have this rock money off kind of remix music that I would use.
And I always want to have something that is recognizable, just the way I like it.
But it's very hard to make that yourself.
I find because, you know, there's no one else to bounce off of.
There's no other voice talent. And in this case, this was made for me.
It was me reading an email from a pilot who actually said that he was flying with the $16 million worth of airplane
strap to his ass with the next generation radio content in his ear, which was the daily source code at the time.
He was listening to that while flying.
And so I just read that kind of dramatically on the show one day and it got turned into an opener for the show.
Another one, send it to me. If you got another opener, I'd love to have something different.
It's just no time, no inspiration, I guess.
Now, I've been reading a couple things around the blogosphere and finally someone sent in a comment about this.
And I'm glad too, because it's something I've been, you know, there's this.
Have you ever seen podcastingnews.com?
You know, this is supposed to be a news site.
Now, when we sign up shows to the network, we send out a press release.
And sometimes press releases get, well, get used as a source of information, but then extrapolate it into a opinion.
Listen to the audio comment, then I'll see if I can make it.
Hello, I'm this is Stephen Lewis from the rules podcast and in Larte Veritas.
You can see what I look like and what my co-host looked like by going to our websites, the rulespodcast.com and in Larte Veritas.com.
But I don't think it's really important what we look like, which is why I was disgusted to go to podcasting news today to find
What I assume was a rehash of a media release that you sent out under the headline podshow add seven hot women.
Podshow co-founded by Adam Curry announced another set of podcasting partnerships today.
This group focusing on hot women according to the company.
Now, among those women, for instance, is Calli Lewis of Geek Brief TV.
Is that really the best way of promoting her and what she and Neil do with the show that she's a hot woman?
Speaking as a listener, promotion like this is much more likely to make me unsubscribed.
It makes me queasy to think that I'm subscribed to a show that's being promoted on the merit that its host is hot.
And that's for whether I'm a folder or a scruncher. Do you really want to know? Why?
No, I don't want to know. People just seem to tell me.
So this obviously, it didn't sit right with me either.
So I went over to podcasting news.com and their headline reads podshow adds seven in quotes hot women.
And indeed, you know, the piece that that you just read there.
And that even says down below, show descriptions provided by podshow.
So this is what we call editorializing because I'm going to go to the original release that we sent out.
Which, of course, I saw before one out and I was absolutely happy with it.
Here we go.
Podshow becomes home for seven of the hottest women in podcasting.
Top women hosts and producers rock the house at Podshow plus with new shows, formats and direct connection to their audiences.
Now, I can see there's a big difference between saying seven of the hottest women in podcasting, which really refers to their popularity.
I would say mainly the popularity.
There is a slight nuance in difference, though, is to saying hot women.
Because that has, it has a totally different, well, it's different words. First of all, it's not what we said.
But here's the context on the first line.
It makes it very clear.
Podshow ain't the premier brand in podcasting.
And now, today, that seven of the hottest shows featuring women hosts and produce hosts.
Sorry, I butcher that.
And now, today, that seven of the hottest shows featuring women hosts and producers have joined the Podshow podcast network.
And that these shows are already lighting up the Podshow charts.
And then it goes into, which shows are in the lineup.
So, you see that there's a little bit of context that podcasting news could have added to their, quote, news.
In fact, the second paragraph, right after that opening, which gives you the context that we're saying that this is hot shows,
not hot women who are doing shows.
As a quote from me, these ladies have great talent.
And all they've needed was the proper promotion and distributions that Adam Curry blah, blah, blah.
Within weeks of joining Podshow, their ratings have exploded.
Now, with the launch of Podshow plus, they're inventing new formats for interacting directly with their audiences.
And I expect them to take their amazing skills to the next level.
Now, of course, I could have added, and they all sent me naked pictures, but I didn't because that's not what this press release is about.
So, I'm, uh, I hopefully that answers your question.
I can see where, you know, we have to be more careful using words like that because so-called news outlets, like podcasting news, totally turn that around, unnecessary.
And they didn't even read the first paragraph, because in the first paragraph, all the context has given.
If you believed any kind of news based upon a headline, and you're an idiot.
So, cleared.
Now, let's get back to the naked picture, shall we?
Man, you guys were talking about that one on the voice mail, that's for sure.
Hello, Adam. This is Kevin C. Mason from the Coloring Outside of the Lines podcast.
I'm sorry about the audio quality. I would like to address this whole naked picture thing.
Well, I just happen to be an expert on this. My day job is the fact that I am a professional body painter.
That's right. I paint on naked women for money. They take off their clothes.
I paint all over their body. I take their picture. I get paid. That's how it works.
Occasionally, I put their picture in a conservative art gallery somewhere.
So, what is it? Great job.
This is that I've noticed that 90% of my clients are Christian and ethical at the same time.
So, why do we just assume that just because someone is Christian that they wouldn't want to have their picture taken?
I can't stand the audio dude. I got to cut you off there.
In case you just dropped into this, into this threat of shows.
I asked Carmen Tyler for a naked picture a couple of times. Carmen Tyler is beautiful woman, former Miss Louisiana.
She's a singer. She has solitary pictures on her webpage. Do I really care if she sends him? I'll live.
But, you know, I'm going to be 42 in a couple days. You send me some naked pictures.
Everyone's coming down on me. It's like I shouldn't be asking this sweet, pristine girl these types of questions.
Adam, just listening to DSC number four, four, eight.
And you always say, call in. And, you know, quickly, when you have someone on your mind, the middle of a show.
And I do, because this guy, calling in, defending the girl who you asked for naked pictures from, sorry if I'm horrible with the names.
I agree with you totally, man. I mean, she's a big girl. She can take care of herself.
And it's not completely irrational to ask for naked pictures like that. She could defend herself, man.
Even if she was slightly offended by it, she's in the business, Miss USA. You know, Miss Louisiana, whatever she was, that's not a personality contest.
And it's not exactly about who's the sweetest person. It fits an ass.
And, you know, we don't need to have that conversation about who anybody's fooling, acting like it's not.
You know, swimsuit competitions. I mean, you're, you're not watching that with the pure thoughts on your mind.
And it jumps out of the career. I'm not talking about the talent, you know, for sale.
There's obviously some aspect to see realize that's going on.
And the guy said, you know, he's there right there that he's assuming.
You know, it happens when you make an assumption, right?
You make an ass out of your arms.
So, I'm not going to promote any, I have a podcast, but I do listen to and sponsor the sound of young America at maximumfund.org.
So check that guy out. And I got to say, I tried it after your suggestions, I respect your opinion, but have always been, will always be.
Thanks.
Exactly. I'm so glad someone said that. Finally.
If you're in a missed Louisiana competition exactly, is this about, is this with God intended to be judged on exterior?
Give me a break.
Now you got to do is go to the experts.
Hey, it's one of those hot women in podcasting.
Hey, Adam, it's Callie. The last couple of days you've played two comments.
One from a guy who is on a Christian and one from a guy who used to be a Christian.
Both can tend you for asking for naked pictures.
This was after you played the song, Amazing Grace. Amazing Grace.
Well, I'm as much of a Christian as I ever have been, and I just have to say that's what Grace is all about.
God made us naked since separated us from God. Adam and Eve covered up, but if you believe in Jesus, then it takes away that shame.
For people to tell you you have to do something in a certain way.
Well, they've never experienced amazing grace.
You can ask for my naked picture anytime. I may give it to you or I may not.
But if asking for naked picture will send you to health, then I just have to say, God's Grace isn't as amazing as I thought.
Oh, Callie, I can give you a couple of amazing grace. There's no problem. That's Callie Lewis from Geek Brief TV.
Who I respect for a talent. Okay?
Alright, I'm off the Carmentiler trip now. Now it's all about naked pictures of Callie.
Hey, hey, check it out everybody.
He must have something very wise as that.
Yep, you know a topic is really closed when Uncle Jesse checks in.
As you could imagine what would be being in the satellite repair business and all, I'm quite a space buff.
So I'd like to share with you in your list. There's something interesting about those missing Apollo 11 materials.
It's a little techy, but hopefully I can make it clear and not too boring.
Back in the early days of TV, when we were deciding on a national standard for Caller TV broadcast signals, there were two competing systems. Actually there was three.
A lot like the VHS versus Beta Max days, except that the decision got made before people started buying Caller TVs.
One system developed by RCA, involved using three image sensor tubes for the red, blue and green portions of the picture.
It was pretty tricky because the three images had to be precisely aligned physically to look decent.
And by today's standards, the pictures were pretty sorry looking.
The main competing system created by CBS used only one image tube and a synchronized spinning wheel with three colored filters on it.
Since the three colored pictures came from the same tube, the result was perfect alignment and way better pictures.
And even though the CBS color wheel system made far better pictures, it wound up losing.
Mostly because the RCA system was more compatible with existing black and white TV sets.
Something nobody would care about today, today they just ran a cell you knew things.
But the losing CBS system didn't go away.
It was reborn many years later in modified form for the Apollo missions.
NASA needed smaller, lighter and foolproof cameras to document the moon missions and the color wheel was reborn.
So the problem is that those original video tapes recorded in this unique format are the ones that are missing.
In this age of digital video, if we had them, we could probably convert all of the frames to digital and make extremely good copies.
Better than anything the public has ever seen.
I sure hope they get found.
Well that's it Adam. I got to go back to keeping this window open as long as I can.
See you.
Hey, what's up?
Today needs to eat in the Atlantic Ocean down at the beautiful Jersey Shore.
Hey, for all of you people sitting in front of your computer for listening to your cars.
I'm standing at a power cell now, and I'm need to eat in some beautiful New Jersey water.
So Adam, the song of the week, Ocean City, say my name.
So see what I have great weekend everybody. Bye-bye.
Let's be on again.
Something strange about the notion that I'm lying here alone.
I guess I just love the sound when you say no.
So I try to count the train cars, but it's dark and they're all fast.
Then I know a good example of how I'm not thinking about it.
Then I don't know where they go, but they're cut down to my soul.
I guess I just love the sound when you say no.
Then I try to climb the mountain, but I stop the long way.
Because I saw the sky was falling, and I knew that sound was the same.
Just a brave interpretation of an old familiar play.
I guess I just loved the way you say my name.
There's something crazy and we're going through the trees and green.
And it's trying to tell me something I might never hear again.
Then I don't know what it's saying, but at least I'm not alone.
I guess I just love the way you say my songs.
Then I try to climb the mountain, but I stop the long way.
Because I saw the sky was falling, and I knew that sound was the same.
Just a brave interpretation of an old familiar play.
I guess I just loved the way you scream my name.
I just love the way you say my name.
Every thing is everything is everything is everything is everything is everything.
Then everything is everything is everything is everything is everything is everything is everything is everything is everything
Nothing I don't know.
Ocean Street from the Podsight Music Network,
same my name that from Georgia.
Thank you very much, Jersey Todd, for suggesting that.
From your vacation spot, no less.
Oh, so jealous.
You got your feet in some good,
good, clean, new Jersey Ocean water.
If you're checking us out on a serious stars 102,
it's our Friday lineup, which means Pacific Coast.
Hellway is coming out followed by Don and Drew.
And Julie and Jackson, within over your head,
which is our brotherford, will be on at 8 o'clock.
830, the Seen Zine, Marcus.
Couch and East Radio at 9 o'clock,
and from 930 to 10 o'clock, Scott,
Siggler and I believe we're still rolling out ancestors.
So PCH is next.
Have a great weekend, everybody.
See you back here on Monday on serious stars 102.
portions of this podcast brought to you by Akira.
Check out their target cast about the new Akira RDX at akira.podshow.com.
Hey, that Northwest Flight 42,
that I played you the audio from yesterday.
Well, of course, no terrorist.
It was just a bunch of rowdy guys who were, of course,
the flight was on its way to India.
These guys live in India.
So they look like terrorists.
There you go.
Of course.
And if they're just being guys, you know,
laughing, joking, passing cell phones around,
probably showing naked pictures.
Then that's a big reason for concern.
So I've not heard any official word yet.
This is all from the Hindu Times.
I think is where I got most of the info.
This is from NDTV, New Delhi TV.
Let me just take a look there for you.
I was scouting around for this.
Nothing in the Dutch reports typical.
But the families of those men detained in Amsterdam are pretty angry.
They say they've been victimized because of their race and their religion.
I was talking to Patricia about this last night.
And you know, it's like,
so you look a certain way.
And by the way, over a billion people look like a terrorist.
Now, if you just look at the pictures that are published,
over a billion, I'm sure.
You're getting profiled.
Now, when you get profiled in that manner,
I don't know, if it were me,
if I had kind of a dark skin,
which easily depending on whatever I'm wearing or whatever,
however, the light falls on me,
could make me look like a terrorist.
And I see people looking at me,
you know, you're going to do like,
one of those things, you know,
trying to freak them out.
It's almost human nature.
So this crap has got to stop.
It's really, really got to stop.
And now, airlines are threatening to sue the government.
I guess it'd be the UK and the US government
because they're losing so much money.
I told you yesterday, my buddy,
Yop is, he's never been as busy,
you know, business manager saying,
fuck, and I'm not going to fly.
You know, and as I think do business class,
or economy class,
they're probably all flying right in air and easy jet,
which is the fantastic service,
but not if you have to be there three hours ahead of time,
just to get through security.
It's not worth it.
You know, they have to stay in overnight.
Hotel rooms are occupancy rates.
Meteoric rise since the,
since the terror threats.
Well, of course,
people are not going back and forth in one day.
You can't do it.
So you got to stay in a hotel.
So that may be good for the hotels,
but it's not good for the airlines,
therefore not good for the economy.
And I read somewhere,
I don't know if you read it,
or someone email the to me.
Ah, drawing a blank on this one.
Well,
the real answer to stopping all this nonsense
is to be quiet about it.
So, you know,
look at all the sensationalism
that the news media have,
have created out of this,
out of this just this recent event.
Forget all the rest.
And you can see how it affects people
on all sides of the equation.
Wouldn't it be so much better
if the secret service,
not secret service.
I guess,
would be CIA or the FBI,
SASMI5,
all these guys,
you know,
if they're on to,
if they're on to guys that are planning
to blow up airplanes with liquid explosives,
I say,
you go get those fuckers,
you prove it,
and you cut their nuts off.
And you just be quiet about it.
You don't have to make this big thing about it.
Just go in,
get them,
excuse me,
man,
we just have to talk to this person here.
Just quietly remove him.
And if they turn out to be guilty,
kill him.
Now,
maybe not kill him.
And I think cut their nuts off.
Do something so that,
you know,
that's not even relevant.
It's not.
The point is,
don't make such a big deal out of everything
and frightening people.
It was FDR that said the only thing
we have to fear is fear itself.
It is so true.
It really is.
This is just going out of control.
We've got to stop the stop this insanity,
making each other crazy.
And the only way,
why we can't control the mainstream news mute.
We can't control anyone from talking about it.
But why don't we just clean up business
and then a nice tidy report at the end.
Here's what happened.
These guys were trying to blow up something
with liquid explosive security.
It's still tight,
which of course it is.
You know,
we've changed a few things,
which they may or may not.
It doesn't really matter.
You know,
they foiled this before someone tried to get
through security.
They were tracking these guys.
That's the good news.
Highlight that.
You know, our intelligence is so good.
You can't even get to the security
and we've already got your ass.
But then don't blow it all out of proportion.
What's this?
A cast master.
All right.
Where are we?
What do we got going on?
Oh, yeah.
Promost.podshow.com.
I've been picking up on that again.
That's still as a great place to put your promo in.
If you've got one,
lots of people subscribe to the podcast feed.
Promost.podshow.com.
I started looking at it again.
Some good stuff in there.
So if you got something you want to
disperse to to a whole bunch of people,
just upload your promo there.
Promost.podshow.com.
Adam,
This is Brian No coming to you today
from beautiful East Central Illinois.
Hope you can hear the cicadas chirping in the background.
Adam.
Dude.
I am desperate.
I really, truly appreciate you including my
Senatra show.
The Frank Truth in the Podshow lineup on serious.
It's really a blast to do the show.
And also of course,
an added bonus to work with PW every week.
And I also appreciate all of the second bonus.
Second prize.
Two weeks working with PW.
The help that you've been to me getting the word out on other podcasts
like Studio C and World News mashup and the No Zone.
Sincerely.
I can't tell you how grateful I am.
But every Wednesday when you say what's coming next on the satellite,
you say that the Frank Truth is only available on serious.
Dude.
Stop saying that.
Stop.
Please.
It's a podcast.
It's all has been a podcast.
It will continue to be a podcast.
Now it's true that the podcast version is a little different from the version on serious.
Since Senatra's music isn't pod save.
So obviously I have to admit or abbreviate the song clips.
But the Frank Truth is indeed a podcast.
In fact, a lot of listener reviews of the show have said things like this
shouldn't work.
A podcast about Senatra without Senatra music,
but somehow it works anyway.
I will be migrating the show to pod show class at some point as I have with my other projects.
But in the meantime people can find the podcast version of the Frank Truth on my website
at nobe.com.
Or at the domain I just registered at GoDaddy for 695 using Code DSC3,
which is Adam.
The Frank Truth is a podcast too.com.
Thanks again for all your help, pal.
Oh and scruncher.
With an attitude like that you think I'm surprised you're a scruncher.
Brian I'm sorry Matt.
I got confused.
I did.
Okay.
So I'll put that link into the show notes.
The GoDaddy link of course.
I'm sorry.
And I will never say that again.
You called me out and I'm there for you my brother.
Hi Adam.
This is Jay Jay from Finland.
Yes, you have listeners all the way up to the north as well.
Adam.
Have you ever been to Finland?
Welcome.
If you haven't.
So something about myself.
I'm 31 years old.
Married.
Two kids.
And I guess compared to many of your listeners.
I'm probably one of the newest ones.
I'll make from a few months back.
I used to listen to your soul slate in the evenings when I'm taking my dog out for a walk.
And I found your show's very, very funny.
And I listen to your shows using this quite new Nokia 91 device.
I remember you sometimes go, you had received one of these and he gave a short review of it in your show.
You had some problems with it like using your files and stuff.
Yeah.
All right.
First of all, thanks for calling in from Finland.
That's very cool.
I like that.
I've never been to Finland.
I've been to Sweden.
But Finland, no.
Of course, comic strip blogger has been to Finland.
Isn't that where Nokia is located?
Hey, the N91.
My problem with it is I need a phone.
And if you look at that thing, you slide it open.
It has the smallest keypad in the world.
And that's why I love my blackberries because it's laid out so that I can, you know,
that's that patented fan layout of the keys.
So you can easily hit all the keys with two thumbs,
or even with one thumb.
Left or right handed, the device works beautifully.
And if you look at the Nokia N91,
although it has built in Wi-Fi and has, you know,
that the podcasting stuff, all that works great.
And the sound is good and the storage is there.
It's a little clunky to carry around.
I felt personally, but I could get over that.
And the keys are just so small.
I mean, I have to be able to do email with it and make phone,
really email is the, because who punches in phone numbers anymore, huh?
I mean, of course, we all have the voicemail number for the source code,
stored in our phone,
plus 1, 2, 0, 1, 6, 2, 5, 6, 3, 5, 7,
or in the UK in London, 0, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3.
But when you can do email with those,
you can't even read the letters on the keys.
That was my problem with the N91.
And I'm very sorry to hear that.
And that has never happened to me, actually.
But I think this N91 is an ultimate podcasting device.
I can browse the feeds with the podcasting application,
download episodes using the Wi-Fi connection,
store them on the four gig memory.
And then with the same device,
call you and leave your voicemail.
Think about that.
Usually you have to have at least three devices.
I think you were all in a queue.
Okay.
And lastly, Adam, about your sincere interest
to watch people's toilet behaviors.
I must admit that it is very interesting to hear different stories.
No, it is interesting, isn't it?
And I wonder how long that you take before someone makes a college,
so you reverse the level of fees, he's above you.
Yeah, I'll follow the structure of the scenario.
Well, anyway, while waiting that course to happen,
you could maybe extend your research with some new areas.
It seems that you have been focused more on the bottom side
of Wi-Fi behaviors.
One interesting question.
No, I'm not interested in that.
Once you've folded or scrunched,
I'm not interested in what happens after that.
Okay?
I'd never have been.
The earthlink ad challenges coming to you close.
We have three finalists.
And I'm going to play one of them today
and Monday and Tuesday have played the two other finalists.
And we're going to be announcing the winner.
I think next week, $2,000 in prizes.
And of course, their commercials become the commercial.
Let's listen to this one.
This is a celebrity endorsement from someone that you don't know.
Of course, you don't know me.
The New York Times once called me the most famous person
in New York that nobody knows.
That's true, go ahead, search it.
But you know, to $700,000 people,
I am known as that guitar man from Central Park.
And I'm here to tell you that earthlink is just about
the best thing you can get on the internet these days.
I mean, if you're anything like me,
and you hate junk mail, earthlink spam blocker alone
is worth a high-speed connection.
It starts at 1295 a month.
It comes with free anti-virus software,
a firewall and spyware blocker.
But take the word of somebody that you don't know.
And you have no reason to trust.
Get earthlink.
You know, I hadn't even heard that one yet.
That's David Epilito, that guitar man.
The guy who sings in Central Park,
and that's the Tom Cruise scares me so long.
I love it.
One of the three final contenders, congratulations, David.
Can't wait to get to New York and hook up with him.
He is so keyed into the music scene in New York.
I'll be cool to hang out with him.
Go to adchallenge.podshow.com
if you want to hear the other two finalists
and to keep a close eye on that
because we'll be announcing the winner very, very soon.
Get out of here.
Fill Walker, Colleen from Canberra, Australia.
My profile.
48 years old.
Married.
Three boys.
Long time Charlie Listener.
Start a listening around about number two, three, zero.
I think.
And I try and catch your show most days if I possibly can.
One is to make a couple of comments.
Firstly, about your description of Australians.
I have to agree with most aspects of what you said.
But one thing I just kind of agree with is
you described us as being proper, like the...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on a second. Hold on a second.
First of all, dude.
I did not describe Australians as proper.
I said, Australia.
Australia has a unique combination of British properties,
Dutch coziness, and American crash commercialism.
It was about Australian general.
Not about Australians.
And I'll tell you in a moment why I made that.
Why I came up with that description.
I used it for Patricia.
It's.
Well, I'd have to say that we Australians,
and being anything but proper like the Brits.
I guess it's kind of a colonial convict thing.
We do love the Brits.
But we are very different.
I'll have to say.
And by the sounds of things,
it's easier to buy a house here than it is to buy a house in the UK.
On to the next point,
the interesting discussion about the naked pictures
and the political correctness of some of your callers.
I do find it amazing that in a country like the US
where violence is so commonplace,
and frequently shown in very graphic ways on the media,
that people all of a sudden become sensitive and caring
when it comes to something as natural as the human body.
Are they men, my brother?
By the way, where is the best porn come from?
With the hottest people.
I rest my case.
America in the mid-80s.
And I've got to say I witnessed a lot of very graphic
and violent acts play out on Primetime TV.
And in contrast to that,
so many references to mild swear words,
or glimpses of nipples or backsides are so carefully
at it out of our TV screens over there.
I guess I just see it as a hypocrisy.
Do they promote death before nudity?
Come on, get real.
At the end of the day,
I think we should all just loosen up a bit about this
and just look upon things as they really are.
I mean, if the lady in question doesn't want to provide you with a photo,
she doesn't have to.
The end of story.
And she's probably flattered that you asked.
So, getting back to you in Australia,
make we've got little cottage down the coast,
miles from anywhere.
Quite where you can sit and have a few beers
and look out over the ocean.
You're more than welcome to use it any time you like.
And I hope we'll see you in the girls down here one day.
So, I'll catch you later.
Have a great day and keep up the good work mate.
Bye-bye.
Oh.
Fold up.
Of course.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for the invitation.
That's very, very nice of you.
Look, the reason I said I gave Patricia that description is because,
you know, I actually wanted to go.
You know, if I say, it's fucking wild down there.
If I say, the people are, you know, they work hard,
but they play hard.
I went to a spinsters and bachelor's ball.
You guys know what that is.
It was three days.
You get like a cup tied to your collar.
You know, so you can't lose the cup.
And then you buck the you and the mud.
And then you shoot carbide.
You know, milk can bombs.
And you build bonfires.
And just shagging away mate.
In your swag.
I loved it.
I had such a good time.
And really did.
You know, I should dig up that documentary.
It was so much fun.
Did some amazing things.
Oh, Australian people are out of their mind.
They love having fun.
I'm not too big on the drinking thing.
That's just not for me.
But, you know, I'll have a beer.
No problem.
It's just the great fun.
Really, really open honest.
I just, you know, I need to convince Patricia to come on down.
You know, so you got to start easy telling her about, you know,
Hey, look, there's crash American commercialism.
In case she needs to buy something.
That's the proper English thing.
Obviously she's into that.
That's why we're here.
And then there's the Dutch coziness.
Dude, I'm totally trying to appeal to everything I can here.
So help me out.
That cottage?
That sounds really good.
Send more information like that and maybe.
Maybe.
I can get her to go.
And now in the interest of equal airtime.
Comic strip.
Like it.
And I knew formally lived.
Or in the Finland or at least worked for the company.
Best known there.
Nokia.
Hi, Adam Kerry.
Here's your European Union correspondents.
So you mentioned lately on this.
See about the new countries that join European Union on January 2007.
And UK wants to block free movement from these two countries.
What countries are these?
Well, there are three biggest ethnic groups in Europe.
Romani countries.
Germany countries.
And the biggest slavic countries.
Romani countries.
Spain, France, Portugal and Romania.
The Jones EU in 2007.
So you see that Romani is a country where people speak language very similar to Italian and
Bulgaria uses Russian alphabet.
And that even inventors it is alphabet.
That's it.
My opinion is that UK should stay open on these two new countries.
Also, batteryistically speaking politicians will be forced to close down.
And they will be forced to close down.
You.
Hey, man, you spun it down to slow a commester blogger.
I've always suspected this not being your real voice.
But now it's really noticeable.
You need to spin it up just a little bit.
Or tell us who you are really are.
Okay.
Hey, man.
I'm there with you.
They joined the European Union.
The United Kingdom.
That is.
And now, somehow, just like, Sweden, they got away with keeping their own currency.
which, of course, is great because the pound is, well, it sucks for me because I get paid in
dollars.
Like anything I have in America, just chop it and have to start with before you even get
to the tax man.
So, it's a very, very rich country, but it's an island, man.
That's the problem.
That's what everyone's talking about now.
It's like, you know, there's already too many people on the island.
So, that's why house prices are out of control and cost of living is out of control.
And it's, of course, very attractive for people to come here for half a year or a year,
work, get lots of dough, send stuff back home, and then go back.
So they can't have it both ways.
It'll be very interesting to see, but you are so right on, man.
I'm here and everyone talking about this here now in the United Kingdom.
Everyone's talking about what happens in 2007 when these borders open up and all these people
are going to come in and how are we going to do it with them?
Yeah, it's a very, very different world.
God, darn, I sound old when I say that.
Hello Adam, this is Jim Farley and several weeks ago you were kind enough to play my
song Katrina on your show as well as put it up for sale on the PMN.
You asked me to stay in touch and let you know how it's going, so I thought I'd give
you an update, especially since we're so close to the anniversary of her king Katrina.
Sales of the song of late have been lackluster, so to help boost donations, I've decided
that not only Katrina, but all of my music on the pop-safe music network will be donated
to her king relief.
I know it's been a year already, but I also know that there are still many people in that
area that can use a bit of assistance.
So please, once again, remind your listeners to download Katrina.
And while they're there, listen and maybe download more music like a call to glory, that's
a 9-11 tribute song written by myself and David Brush just days after September 11th.
I really appreciate everything you've done and poem, yeah, folder.
And then, thank you, don't thank me, check that out and donating proceeds from all of
his music to victims of Hurricane Katrina.
You haven't been thinking about that, that yesterday the window washer, not to the door,
normally Patricia deals with the deals with all that stuff, so he's there, he's like, obviously
he wanted to be paid to figure that out within seconds.
But then, you know, he started talking about, hey, we're going to America and I've done
it three years in a row now and did the West Coast, did the East Coast, now they're going
to go through, they're going to go to Memphis, I said, too, you should totally go to New
Orleans.
And he's like, well, yeah, we thought it might still be a mess if you want to support
these people, go there, really go down there, go check it out.
You know, it may not look like a holiday destination, but you're going to, it's going
to enrich your life, I promise you that.
And I actually convinced him, he said, you know what, you're right, we should go, we should
go see what's going on.
And everybody should do that if you have, if you have the possibility and remember, we
have to keep supporting these folks.
We really do, it doesn't end, you know, just because the news isn't covering it anymore,
doesn't mean that it's over.
And I have to say, there are days that go by and I don't think about it either.
So it's good to have a reminder like that, I really appreciate it.
And of course, I'll put all the links into the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
All right, everybody, time for me to do, uh, get out of here one last song, this is, uh,
seven standard and slow burn.
Like it's a cowbell.
In this time, it's over, I'm not quite sure just how I feel.
Should I be said, just let me go, maybe both of us don't know.
Play your skies over my head, drifting over my head, I feel something, building, building
all up.
I run to see how I play whatever you want, this is conversation over, I never know
what you want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this
this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I  experience, otherwise, this will be what I'm doing, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want , this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want now, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want, watch this, this is what I want, this is what I want, this is what I want,
There's over my head
Truth ain't over my head
I feel something
Building, building on
I don't have to say I've been
Whatever you don't want
In this conversation of me
I never know they'd try
I knew what you were like
I knew what you were
We can't come together
But it's over
I know, I know
What should I tell them to be
What should I tell them to
Be like this, you're the only one
If it's a conversation of me
I never know they'd try
I knew what you were like
But we can't come together
But it's over
Which has happened to me
Life has happened to me
7th standard
Slow burn
Soon to be available on the pond safe and using network
Alright everybody, that's it
Have yourself a great weekend
I'm going flying
Take care
I'll see you on Monday
DailySourceco.com
Add them at pondshow.com
Bye bye
I'll show podcast
Stick it in your ear