Already a hit state side. Now you can check out the following podcast and good old
blightybtpodshot.com. Single-handedly making a mens for giving you Madonna.
One show at a time.
And of course, your host, Adam Curry.
Delta Sierra Charlie 5-0-4.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Sing it back, bring it back, sing it back to me.
And you are ready to ask someone,
take me and do that you will.
Ever do you want to raise your wings,
but there's one way, one, one, one, one, one.
And if you're succumb to this processation,
things will be fun if you're alone.
And the sun is your wish, we'll come and make
a better body of money.
And you are ready to ask someone,
take me and do that you will.
and I can do that you will.
And you are ready to ask someone,
take me and do that you will.
and you are ready to ask someone,
take me and help you.
take me and do that you will.
and you are ready to ask someone,
take me andarcate me and do that you will.
take me and do that you will.
Bring it back, and shake it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it
, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it, bring it back, bring it back, bring back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bringing it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it back, bring it
I'm taking their own words to hard, bring it back, sing it back, Malico, on the Pod Save Music Network.
It's really nice.
I think what happened is the rights to the masters, either were sold or reverted, but apparently owned by an entity called Maloco catalog.
There you go.
This is what you can do with you.
Put it on the Pod Save Music Network, get some pod play, sell some tracks.
Of course, we're open for business now.
Anyone who any artist or band or whatever, anyone who puts up stuff on the Pod Save Music Network,
you can select which tracks you want to be for sale from 99 cents.
9 cents of that goes to the transaction company, the rest goes to the artist.
So it's a good deal all around.
Everybody, how you doing?
It's episode 504 of the Daily Source Code coming to you from Curry Cottage.
The current Curry Cottage, of course.
In just weeks from now, about seven weeks, we will be...
Is it even seven weeks?
Less than that.
Six weeks.
We'll be moving to the new Curry Cottage on the other side of the tracks here in Guilford.
I feel like shit today.
I gotta tell you.
God didn't yesterday morning from San Francisco.
I think I did sleep about four hours on the flight.
The flight was actually was nice.
We had a tailwind.
So nine hours and 20 minutes.
And we landed it.
Actually, we were above Heathrow at 10 past 10.
So a full 40 minute ahead of schedule.
And of course, we had to stay in the holding pattern for about 10 minutes.
And then we landed.
And then all you knew was going to happen.
Well, the gate, of course, isn't ready.
So you never win anything on that.
So we still de-plained around 11 a.m.
Came back.
I did, I caulked out for a couple hours on the couch yesterday afternoon.
It's just, it's hard.
I'm not complaining or anything.
But this morning, my stomach is a little upset.
I'm running a little bit of a fever.
I know it's just my body.
It's just winging out.
Anyway, plenty to do this week.
I think there's a whole bunch of yanks in town for the digital Hollywood London,
which sounds like a mistake.
Digital Hollywood London.
Anyway, and I believe I'm on a panel on Wednesday.
So I'm not quite sure what it's all about.
I think this is the thing that I was held earlier in the year in Hollywood.
Los Angeles, at least surprise surprise.
So I've got to find out what's going on there.
I know that there's lots of people in the UK.
We're going to be attending this.
So it should be very interesting.
Unless you forget what the Daily Source Code is all about.
Please, feast your ears on this movie style promo.
In a world where corporate monstrosities control the airways.
A new media has a risen.
One man leads the internet rebellion that will change the world forever.
Potua Productions presents Adam Curry as the podfather in the Daily Source Code.
Witness the pain.
Fuck me.
I didn't work or I wanted to.
Brahman that used to suck so bad and the pleasure.
And I went into the bathroom and got myself off.
Biting my lips the whole time so that nobody would hear me.
As the podfather saves the world,
as only a former MTVVJ can with extreme prejudice.
You are such a dick weed.
Get the fuck out of my office.
Deep in the bowels of the curry cottage.
Lands are set.
Splendid consumed.
And soon humanity will experience a reckoning.
That usually fucks companies up.
For the next year there's going to be a lot of turmoil and radio.
Trim everything down get rid of the quote excess fat.
Which usually comes in the home.
You know chop people up into bits.
So I think this is the time we need to strike, strike, strike, strike.
Don't miss this daily event because if you do.
Fuck you.
Adam Curry and the Daily Source Code.
This show is fucking awesome.
This podcast is free to get gas.
Thank you Wayne from the worlds of Wayne podcast worlds of Wayne.com.
That's his voice.
Awesome dude.
Now you heard me talking about Mark Yoshimotanemkov using the real movie guy voice.
And as I said, all I want is I just want one of those from my own that starts with in the world
where women wear comfortable shoes or something like that.
And he started off with in a world.
Thanks buddy.
That really made me smile.
And you heard the giselle in there.
I'm not sure if there was an email problem because you know I get all these voice
emails.
I get emailed to me as.
I'm not even as way files as like G at the GSM protocol or something.
You can open it in quick time and then I can export them as AIFF and then re-import
them as MP3s etc.
But I only had one message from giselle which I played for you on Thursday the day after
Thanksgiving because she was coming up from San Diego to meet me.
And so now all of a sudden I got like three messages from her.
Let's just play them and then enjoy together.
Hey Adam, it's me just now.
So I went into the little store and I was able to find a prepaid phone.
So here's my number for one five.
And it cuts off right there.
So now I couldn't have called her anyway because I didn't get these until yesterday.
But you can almost almost see the saga that she went.
I guess she really did come up to San Francisco.
I'm feeling pretty bad about this right now.
Hey Adam.
So I went into an internet cafe today and I wanted to listen to some of the shows that I missed.
And I heard you talking about me and how all of a sudden you didn't want me to come up to San Francisco.
I thought you wanted me to come up.
Anyway, I'm a little bit pissed off and I really need to think about things.
So I'll just call you later.
Bye.
Okay.
So now I'm feeling bad.
But you know, you have to understand Gizelle after getting a call like this.
I don't know who this is but stop fucking calling Gizelle at all.
You know, I got a little bit worried.
And then after that I got calls like this.
I don't know who the fuck you are, but stop putting what you're also.
And and it gets worse.
Hey.
I don't know who this is.
But stop calling me specifically.
I know.
Sorry.
Hey Adam.
Okay.
I feel like a total dumb ass jerk for coming all the way up here to San Francisco.
Thinking that you wanted to see me.
So I'm just going to go back to San Diego now.
I don't want to bug you anymore.
Bye.
No, Gizelle.
I feel pretty stupid about this.
Listen.
I think we can still carry on our our long distance voice mail relationship.
And I love the pictures you've been sending me.
You know, you come and I'm just freaking me out.
Again, it was certainly after this call that I got to break.
I don't know who this is, but stop fucking calling Gizelle at all.
I am in so much trouble.
Hi.
This is Jim Farley of the Musical World podcast.
And I'd like to invite you and all of your listeners over to musicalworld.us to listen to the interview.
I had with the beautiful.
And the charming.
Carmen Tyler.
I hate it because I'm so Gary.
I know you'll find her as sweet as you can ever imagine.
So when you're done with the Charlie,
swing on over to musical world and download episode 21.
I know you'll love it.
Hey, this is Carmen Tyler.
Check out my interview and a whole bunch more on musical world podcast.
That's really, I'm like, give this a clear area.
And we had a couple.
I mean, I just don't want to be offensive.
Oh, yes.
The lovely and talented Carmen Tyler.
Still waiting for those naked pictures.
Other cool things on the network that I wanted to bring to your attention.
The high fee show.
If you're never seeing the high fee show, you've got to check this out.
Kevin App's legendary in the Bay Area as a movie producer.
Creating a show.
It's called the high fee show.
H-Y-P-H-Y dot pod show dot com.
High fee.
And the host on the show is Malica, who's also done stuff on MTV.
And she has a brief but very interesting interview with Snoop Dogg.
When he came, I guess he came to the Bay Area and they've got all kinds of live footage of him performing.
See, might want to take a look at that.
Had some other stuff that I wanted to bring your attention to.
Oh, did you see, I don't know if you if you've looked at the feed or at the site for a
podcast con uk, which is podcast con uk dot pod show dot com.
That's the one I'm going to point you to because there's a whole wrap up there that I think
I told you this of Jill Mills and Robert Dolby did a video show.
It's really good.
You should take a look at it.
But there's something you'll see in the video as I was looking at it on the plane right home.
There's lots of people.
I forget it was a podcast Paul who was selling those t-shirts.
He had some awesome t-shirts.
Which looked very much like the old t-shirt home taping is killing the music.
We had a cassette with a cross through it.
So now that the cassette is kind of turned into a skull and cross bones.
And the actual t-shirt says podcasting is selling music.
I really like it.
Unfortunately, I think they were all sold out by the time I got there.
But maybe someone could put one up on eBay or something.
And I'd be happy to take off your hands because I just love the concept of that podcasting is selling music.
And you know it.
Every year on a special winter day,
Little podcaster girls and boys wake up early to find something special in their iPods.
Little do they know how close they came to losing it all.
Ah, humbug.
The podcast community presents a podcast Christmas Carol.
A special adaptation of Charles Dickens classic tale of broadcast mobile Ebony's or Scrooge.
And the visitation of three ghosts on Christmas Eve.
And I suppose you'll expect me to just play this little promo for free.
Visit a podcast Christmas Carol.com.
And listen, as Scrooge has shown his tragic feature and learns to share the spirit of the Christmas season.
Go stop your own radio station.
A podcast Christmas Carol.
Featuring talents from the podcasting community, including Adam Curry.
And say yo.
Leo Leport.
And starring David Lawrence as Ebony's or Scrooge.
Visit a podcast Christmas Carol.com.
The future is just around the corner.
Seems like so long ago yet really just short short time ago really if you think about it.
Last year we were doing all that stuff.
The podcast Christmas Carol.
If you've never heard it, definitely go and check that out.
It's awesome.
Very well produced.
I think the 30 or 40 different podcasts participated in that, of course.
Around the same time we had podcasts for peace, which I'll be playing all the way up through Christmas.
Obviously.
Not today though.
I got a different Christmas tune queueed up for you, which I think you like.
Lots of comments about the accessibility of the upgraded pod show plus.
Some people saying that it's completely unusable.
Then I got an email from Tino, Tino Fella.
Or what?
Let's see.
I'm almost blind myself.
I appreciate the way you reacted.
Right now I have no opportunity to do an audio comment.
Okay.
Speaking for myself, pod show.com is still pretty well accessible.
Even the new embedded player on the music segment works easy because the buttons can also be activated with the
Interkeys.
Sometimes I have to hit it twice.
But I don't care.
It works.
The only problem is the dashboard.
Here's if you click play it.
To play a show, of course.
A few weeks ago you said there would be a download link on the board.
My screen reader, which Tino uses jaws, doesn't show any links.
Maybe it's not a text-based link.
Of course, the show starts playing normally for me, but the most important thing.
By the way.
Okay.
Yeah.
I think the big problem here is with flash.
That's when I'm understanding.
The dashboard has gone from a straight Ajax.
Actually, kind of a combination of Ajax.
Javascript.
Of course, that would be a part of Ajax.
What's a specific JavaScript call.
There was even some flash-based stuff in there.
We've changed that to all flash.
There is a download link there, but I can understand.
I think it's baked into the flash.
So what we have to do is we have to pull that out of the flash.
So that the screen readers can access.
Obviously, yeah, if you're able to tab to the play it link, and you hit enter,
and then that works.
And it's playing that's fantastic.
But if you want to take it with you, I guess, on a mobile device,
we have to expose the download link differently.
So I will get on that.
I've also received some other messages, people saying that actually the code isn't all that bad.
There's only a few things that have to be changed in order for some of the screen readers to work.
Oh.
Hi, Adam.
Nice to see you.
I didn't want to play that right now.
I'm sorry.
Here's the one I want to play.
Hi, Adam.
This is Bob Netherway in Bristol, South West England.
I'm a freedom box user, and I'm having problems downloading and listening to your shows
since the new home page came in.
My email is Bob Netherway.
It's the NETH, the RWAY, at myfreedombox.com.
I look forward to hearing from you.
Goodbye.
Yeah, freedom box.
But it sounds like that's an online application.
I'm going to have to look into that.
But as I said, we've got plenty of people pitching in the house,
so we'll get it fixed with us soon.
Let's do it for the U.S. folks as well.
So there's this whole long, uh, I just noticed that it's six and a half minutes long.
This reply about Chris Moiles from David Graham here in the UK.
Let me just give you a little bit of it, okay?
Hi, Adam.
Listen to the feedback you receive from your listeners about the mention you've got from
Radio 1 DJ Chris Moiles.
I have to reply and make some corrections.
A response from one of your listeners called James made out the Chris Moiles was a game's podcasting
and so no future in it.
This is incorrect.
Chris actively promotes his podcast, which in turn educates the public about podcasting.
You know, so then he plays all these clips of Chris Moiles.
It really is interesting if you really are interested in the topic, which I am.
But six and a half minutes is just too long for me to do it, but I do appreciate it.
Give me a pointer, put this thing up on the online somewhere, so people can go access it.
I don't just want to put it up without your permission.
But apparently, and this is something I didn't know.
And that's the clip that would have rolled for the next two minutes, two and a half minutes.
Chris, as a employee of the BBC, is not allowed to make any content specifically for the podcast.
It has to be content that is aired on the BBC.
I find this very entertaining and interesting.
Now, what a missed opportunity.
Here's a whole extra channel, a whole distribution channel.
They can take advantage of, but they're just not allowed to do it.
And there's other stuff in there, but I thought that was the most relevant piece of what
was his name again.
Sorry about that.
David, what David sent in, sent in to me.
So I wonder, I wonder what the BBC's plans are.
I mean, you would think that if these guys are brimming with creativity,
they should be allowed to put that out there, don't you?
Hey, Adam Chris, daily hear from a many, many podcasts that you name it,
writing with the window down the PMC top there and Lone Star Grid,
I heard the list goes on and on.
I wanted to mention, I just put the wraps on show number 429.
And here you are approaching 510.
My hats off to you.
I know what it takes to put together 429.
And I started, gosh, a few months after you.
So kudos to you on halfway to a thousand.
Can you believe it?
And one of those shows, you'll remember from a year ago,
because you were one of the stars.
That's right.
You were a rostophariant Jacob Marley in a podcast Christmas carol.
I think it would be a great time for you to spend that promo out.
And hey, when you're sitting down with Leo Leport,
remind him that you two were virtually in a show together already,
a podcast Christmas carol.
Thanks, Adam, and as always, keep it real.
Yeah, so much for scheduling.
Oh, my audio is today.
Sorry.
Screw that one up.
Yeah, I'll be on the Twitter next week, everybody.
Let's put these dropping in again.
I'm all alone out of work tonight.
I used to have a spring in my step,
but now something is missing.
And I know it's not right.
Last year, I was good and oh,
Charlie St. Nick was too to his word.
I was the top of the list of all those who were blessed.
But this year, I don't know.
I give back those toys and gadgetagnic,
nags that he left under the tree.
Don't need the sweater and the jacket and the egg.
No, I've had it and it's no good for me.
If this year, I've been thinking that I don't need a thing.
You get hiding a box, it's true.
There's all I want for Christmas is some hugging,
and it's kissing from you.
I give up my life.
I watch a flow of blackberry.
I don't need to make any calls.
No, don't need my sling box.
Maybe you could call me crazy.
I don't watch it at all.
The magic bullet, the toaster,
or the thing that makes the roast beef,
that's not on TV.
Oh, my brand new vendor, tell a castor.
It don't mean nothing to me.
No, I give back those toys and gadgetagnic,
nags that he left under the tree.
Don't need the sweater and the jacket and the egg.
No, I've had it and it's no good for me.
Oh, this year, I've been thinking that I don't need a thing.
You get hiding a box, it's true.
There's all I want for Christmas is some hugging,
and it's kissing from you.
Yeah, you know what's in it.
It's travel, baby, don't leave me blue and I'll be here.
Let's start something new.
Yeah, I give back those toys and gadgetagnic,
nags that he left under the tree.
Don't need the sweater and the jacket and the egg.
No, I've had it and it's no good for me.
This year, I've been thinking that I don't need a thing.
You get hiding a box, it's true.
There's all I want for Christmas is some hugging,
and it's a kiss, and it's a squeeze, and it's a love,
and it's a sweet turtle, nothing.
I have a wanted on my Christmas, and on it was you.
Oh, yeah.
The Jeff Smith, everybody.
It's the Christmas hugging, as you, baby.
And kiss them from you.
Now available on the Podsate Music Network.
If you want to hear the song again, just go to the GoToDabysourceco.com.
Look at the show notes for today's episode.
Click on the link.
It'll take you to the music network page for Jeff Smith.
You can see all the songs.
It's a nice little player there.
You can embed the player in your web blog or any page you want to.
And of course, many of Jeff's tracks are enabled for sales.
You can buy it and help a brother out.
Patricia walks by when I'm playing that song.
This morning says, hey, that's the guy who did the lady
and the Atom.
Atom's.
All alone.
And he needs his love right there on the microphone.
So here she is, yes, the lady Patricia.
The say to have some better than one.
And with this angel from above,
There's nothing that they both can't do.
I make you while this dream's come true.
It's Adam and Patricia, so that is G Jeff Smith, G-E-O-F-O, that is
Jeff Smith, DJF Smith.com.
And she said something really exciting.
She said, wow, you know, this guy is unbelievable.
He just, he can just shake shit like that right out of his, out of his arms, no problem.
He just does it whenever he wants to, what a talent, and I said, and she said, hey,
do you think that I could do a song with him?
Like, what?
I can't believe it.
It's the first time she said something like this in a long, long time.
And so her concept, I guess, is she wants to do her tracks here.
So, Jeff, if you're listening, I hope you are.
I know you're a little behind on the listening.
She'd love to do some kind of song, like this, like a swing big band type thing with you.
She'd like to record her tracks here.
Wouldn't that be cool?
And it would be a great collaboration, I think, so let's see if we can make that happen.
And I'd say that, you know, I'd get her on the show, but tomorrow morning she leaves
a very early, she'll leave the house around 530.
She's going to the Netherlands, once again, to practice, once again, for the dancing with
the stars, extravaganza, she'll be on at the end of the year.
It's going to be a very interesting show.
She leaves tomorrow, she comes back Thursday, then I leave on Monday or Tuesday, I leave
for San Francisco for good, you know, 10 days or something like that.
And in that meantime, she's going back, oh, hey, it's a true show, bid in the family.
And that's what it takes.
Okay, everybody, I'll be back tomorrow.
Yeah, so keep sending your stuff, love to hear from you.
Talk to you then.
Bye-bye.
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT Pot Show Media Network.
Howard by Pot Show and Limelight Network.
Control your part in the show at btpotshow.com.