With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation
radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
This year at Charlie 3-0-A Tuesday y'all, it's wake up the neighborhood.
Hey, boom, that is completely clear.
Whoa, yeah.
What the hell is nonsense?
Striggling things like innocence, running away to take.
With my mind in it's hands shut, got just me walking away.
Doesn't it get in there?
But to come after the rain.
Whoa, yeah.
Whoa.
Oh.
Sau.
Mmm.
I can't forget you
I don't deserve a castle
I don't blame my own
I'm a thief, I don't deserve a castle
But it's set this morning
Sometimes it's just easy
Walk away from the night
Some people get tired, it's cold
And it's part of your forced life
Woo
I won't forget you
I won't stop
If I had an ounce of musical talent
This is the kind of sound I would make
Man, love that
Scorded on the Pods Abusing Network
Just about 15 minutes ago
It showed up on the homepage
From Ontario, Canada
I won't forget you
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
It's Tuesday, thanks again for
Checking out the show
The big show
It's a weather like today
It's kind of dreary
It's about 7 degrees
Celsius
An Christina started school again today
So it was up early
Crackadon almost
Or at least it felt like that
Neither of the girls
Neither Patricia
Christina slept very well
I slept like a fucking rock
Beautiful
And 730, I was ready to go
So I've been going through email
Didn't do, you know, kind of skipped
Through a few things over the weekend
Just to lighten the load a bit
And of course I had to pay for that today
And hit 99% on the Gmail
My special nerdy
Alotment of four gigs is now officially filled up
So I went in to lead it about a hundred megs
Worth of stuff
Which hurts me so much
But I guess I'm just going to have to
Start
Asking Google again
They can up my Gmail
And I'd gladly pay for it
Let me reiterate
I gladly pay for it
I love it
I love having huge mountains of data
Just stored somewhere
Where I can get to it
With your fabulous searching
Technology
Let's see
On today's show
We're going to do a
Oh, I almost forgot to line up
The Metrosexual moment
Okay, I'll do that in a second
We have a short
We're actually
Enough stuff has come in
For another Metrosexual moment
Item
In the Daily Source code
See what I do
I'm noticing more video podcasts coming online
Which vlogging now seems to be the word of choice
I don't know yet if I want to support that word
Because it's just vlogging
Although I saw a Dutch guy vlogging
And he had a whole bunch of Dutch people
Including his dad who looked about 80
On camera saying
You mother vloggers
I did like that
So the word definitely is
Moldable into something at least entertaining
But there's a lot happening
And I see a lot of talking heads
But I also see a lot of beautifully
Produce stuff
And I think it's actually pretty exciting
I have to say the ratio of vlogs
Vlogs to podcasts
For me right now
I'm probably about
35% vlogs
That I'm
Perusing on a daily basis
So yeah, it's cropping up there
I guess what I'm going to have to do
Is create a channel or something like that
With everything that I watch
The real problem here is just the tools
We're not done with the tools
Yet certainly not for
Routing stuff around
That's the one thing that I loved about
Web-based aggregators
Certainly the one in radio
Userland is you could go through
A list of stories that came in on your RSS aggregator
And then you could literally just click
A button next to a story
And it would take that story
And it would post it onto your weblog
And it would actually open up your weblog
For editing with that story
Already pre-populated it would do like the
Referring link where you got it from
You're the via whatever thing
It really cool
And I think we should have the same
Capability for podcasts
But of course it has to be a lot simpler
Because what people will do now
You've got stuff downloading
You've got megs of stuff all over the place
So somehow just using the original URLs
Which should be able to
Create channels to repost
Which in my mind is very simple
And it's just a matter of implementation
But no to self that we do that
And what is it with the RIA?
And little girls
This is becoming quite concerning
Whole court case that was sent to me by
Hassan Dewan
Hassan said I thought you'd probably like this
This was essentially a court case
Trying to think
I'll have to put a link into the
Show notes page so you can go and look at this whole thing
But basically
I guess a case was dropped because the RIA coerced a witness
And some of the questions
Let me see so that's some cross examination here
Let me just read this to you
Motown versus Nelson
That's the case pending in federal court in court here in Michigan
Eastern division
Defendants Mr. and Mrs. Nelson
I've made a motion for attorneys fees against the RIA attorney
This fees against the RIA attorneys
Pursue and blah blah blah
Law foreign reasonable and
Vexatious litigation and properly interfering
Enduro obtaining false testimony from
Perspective witness
So here's part of the
I guess what is it cross examination
Question what are the areas do you feel that
Mr. Kerch and bomb that would be the RIA lawyer
Put words into your mouth answer
I don't remember any specifically just trying to get me to say that
Angie and Jim or I had rips him
Ripped him music off
Question it wasn't true and so you felt
Mr. Kerch bomb was trying to get you to say something
It wasn't true answer yes
Question did he get you to say something that wasn't true
A from the statement I read yes
And this goes on and on and on
Uh, oh here we go
Did he tell you why he needed you to stick with your original false story
Answer because he said he didn't have a case unless I did
Question so he told you that he didn't have a case unless you stuck to the original
Fall story answer yes
Now this was actually a 15 year old girl
who went through this
This alleged grilling by the RIA which actually
And this and Hassan
Link to whole bunch of information about it
Could actually be seen as illegal
Racketeering even
15 year old girls
You know this whole thing with this settlement centers
They have you know if they if they quote catchy
Sharing music or distributing music online
Then you don't get a call from a lawyer per se
But from the settlement center
And they'll say okay you pay us 30 grand
And then we'll make everything go away
You know they have like whole process for this thing
And
We talked about
Music stores
At least according to the BBC music stores
And therefore I presume it's in the UK
Only for now
Have to pay a royalty
To ask at BMI or equivalent in country of origin
Uh, for
For people actually performing music
Testing out the instruments before purchasing
We have a great audio comment
Uh, that was sent in from
Uh, I was at Darrell
Before I get to that though
Listen to this
You're gonna love this
Oh, I got to open up this link
Uh, this is a Fridrico Avers
Sent this to me
Uh, and this is from 1996
But it turns out
That in the summer of 96
And this is according to this article that I'm reading from
The American Society of Composes authors and publishers ask cap
Has informed girls scout camps
Nationwide
They must pay license fees to use any of the
Formally and copyrighted songs written or published by
Ask cap 68,000 members
Those who sing or play but don't pay
Ask cap warns
Might be violating the law
Like restaurants hotels bar stores and clubs
Which already pay fees to use copyrighted
Music camps including non-profit ones
Such as those run by the girls
Scouts are being told to anti-up
The demand covers not only recorded music
But also songs from around the campfire
Um, here's a quote
They buy paper, twine, and glue for their crafts
They can pay for their music too
Says John Loe Fremento
Ask cap's chief operating officer
If offenders keep singing without paying
He says we will sue them if necessary
Hey Barbara
You're allowed to say something
Okay
I'm sorry
Wait, I'm still drinking that
Thank you
Good day
Okay
My disruption
So if this is a true article
And it's
Apparently by Lisa Bannon from the
Star Tribune, 1996
I guess that happened
Maybe it just probably just passes by
And we weren't paying attention to it
But man, that's, that means so
Coercing 15 year girls into making statements
Girl Scouts, I'm kind of Girl Scouts
Money for singing songs around the campfire
What is the world coming to?
Hey Adam, this is Darrell Fallon at lawschoolpodcast.com
Of course I do my podcast about my tending law school
So first I want to say that I'm not a lawyer
And this is just my opinion
As any individuals opinion would be worth
So you can take it for that
But this is about royalties for playing music
And a business that sells musical instruments
Or a place that sells musical instruments
I don't think they would be charge royalties
And this is why
Under Title 17 in the United States Code
Section 110 limitations on exclusive rights
And the exemptions of certain performances in this place
Subsection for a performance of a non-dramatic literary
A musical work in a transmission to the public
Without any purpose of direct or indirect commercial
And without payment of any fee or other compensation
For the performance to any of its performers, promoters or organizers
If there is no direct or indirect admission charge
I think that covers it
There is kind of a seminal case out there
Which is fourth floor music ink
Versus their place
This basically set out the four things that you need it to establish
And infringement number one
The originality and authorship of the compositions involved
Number two compliance with all formalities
Or required to secure a copyright under Title 17
Of the United States Code
Number three that they are the proprietors of the copyrights
Of the compositions involved in this action
Number four that the compositions perform publicly for profit
And number five that defend and not receive permission
From any of the claimants or the representatives for such performance
So under number four you can see that the compositions perform publicly for profit
In a store that's probably not the case
And I'm trying to go for a minute's this time
But thanks a lot and hey everyone come visit law school podcast.com
Talk to you later
But I'm Darrell
Thank you very much Darrell always checks in
He's not a lawyer yet
But one day he'll be one
So interesting
I think of course that applies to the US as you were reading out US code
So this may only be for the UK
If anyone works in a music store in the UK
Let me know if that's true if you actually do have to pay
For pay for people to play the instruments
And of course you could argue that that playing is for profit
Because if someone actually plays the instruments and they might purchase it
And then there might be a profit and of course there's not the customer paying
Although at least not directly indirectly the customer pays
It's the store that's paying
But wouldn't that be interesting to find out if that's really going on
Every single day there's a little piece of all this licensing business
It's being uncovered that just really blows me away
And I think we should just pay attention to all of it
So that whatever we do with Podsake music
Let's try not to make the same mistakes
I'm commander Scott Leo is the unified defense force
I'm going to so describe information technologies
I dig for old data on ancient reflective radio waves
I've theorized and I may be able to use our contact rise
The pulse wave and more in the people of earth
Of a continuing threat that aren't that
If you're hearing any of this before the year 2009
There may be hope
I don't have time to explain everything
But the important thing is that if you are hearing this
They will be coming back
Point your podcatcher to children of the gods.net
And find out how to reshape this tree
This could mean
That's a donation
No, it's a donation
But that's right
There's a little time, please
Help us with God's podcats
Join the fight for survival today
Hola, soy marina, bienvenido anote in Spanish
31 podcasts in Spanish
Yep 31 podcasts in Spanish
31 days
And here's the deal
31 days we help you learn and enjoy Spanish
And if it helps or if you just enjoy the podcasts
Then please do make a one-off donation
To help you reach my 1,750 pound charity target
Get a barete
For full of the things go to notes from uspain.com
On the next episode of Beyond Science
Richard Cache
Dr. Cache, the country was well
That happened by coincidence
They had the 2600 first frequently met
Phone free game
No, don't take care of you around that machine
And just put your hair in phone numbers
So some people from around the country
Could call such a number for free
And talk to each other for hours
www.phonetricks.com
You can almost, you can almost make that claim
I definitely, I'll give you that
I'll give you that year the first podcast
If I'm aware
Beyond Science podcast.com
Hello and welcome to another episode of TechX
This is Jay Marti
God, I can't even do an honest show
Without getting these help desk issues
Let's see what's going on here
Okay, we got one
My computer slash keyboard motherboard
CPU isn't is beeping at me
Please come and help me
He's another one
My keyboard's not working
There's some liquids stuff on it
I don't know what this is
All I had was coffee this morning
Uh-huh
Here's a third one
My mother CPU board is out of order
Saying something about please insert a disk
All I have is a floppy
Please assist
Let me get on over to their computers
Magicly make it all better
Does this sound like you?
Are you an admin or IT pro in your organization
And this is what you get day in day out
Or maybe you're not an admin
Maybe you're just tech savvy
And this is what your family and friends come to you with day in day out
Do you think you're alone?
My friends, you're not
Come on over to the TechX podcast
at feeds.feberter.com slash techX
And listen to my stories
Point a laugh at me
So if you can
Come on over to feeds.feberter.com slash techX
Like I said
And share in our global computer paid
Because I know I'm not by myself
And I want to let you guys know that you're not alone either
Yeah
Thank you
That's good to know
I'm going to subscribe because I am definitely one of those people
Everybody calls me
Any my house particularly
Now I have a deal with Christina
I told her I'd get her windows machine
But I said that I could not promise that I could support her on it
The way she'd like it or the way she's used to
Because boy, I've had all of those phone calls
Hey, there's something sticking on it
All I have is some juice here
I don't understand
But now Patricia of course has the
Has the eye Mac
The member the old one that I bought just before the new ones came out
I haven't even replaced it yet
I'm doing everything on the new power book
Playback and recording
And so now Patricia has the eye Mac
And so I have some support issues that I have to help her with
But it's really so minimal
Because it's usually just a question of
User not reading
And of course it's you get used to not reading stuff
And you're a little pop up windows and a big flashing
Okay blue ball
Like I get rid of that
What did it say?
Oh, I didn't read it
Okay
But yeah, you do find yourself in that position
If you have anything to do with computers or internet
Then you get the call
And of course you want to help people out
You know, I always say hey I'm going to help you
But just so you know the way it works
And this is actually from the Unix days
If you teach somebody
The person who received that lesson
Is obligated to turn around
And help the health and the next person
That is really the only way to make it work
But then with windows I'm so lost sometimes
I'm just blown away
I see that Intel is gearing up for their core processor
They're dropping the Intel inside
It's becoming I think it's the core or core or something like that
Which is interesting because we have a core acronym that we use
With inside pod show as well which is
Was it a content organization and recommendation engine
So it is actually something that exists
It's nothing that we would brand per se
But that's kind of interesting that Intel now comes out with a core
And I guess their entire mission is to create the next
Version of processor
And DSP chips and all that stuff that you need
To really create great experiences
With that come some things that
And I don't know everything about it
But there's certainly going to be doing a lot with audio
And I think that the
The validity of what audio is going to be played
Is going to be checked at the processor level now
So basically DRM will be embedded very very deep
If you have any information on that
Please let me know please send it an audio comment
I hate reading out emails
I really do I'd much prefer you
Send in an audio
You know what I'm going to do
I'm just going to
I have to figure out a way if you just send it
No actually we have something cool
A show notes module that will be coming up
When we open up the network
As a part of that the podcast delivery network
I'm going to have a really interesting feedback
Which I'll just have to bear until then
Neil Harrington says
Been a long time listening to your podcast
I think I started around episode 10
Oh wow
Dropped an email about mashups in the drum lines
Okay, I recall that I probably didn't reply
I'm sorry because of your product placement of Senseo
I was intrigued by the single serve coffee concept
I didn't research and decided to add Senseo to my Amazon wish list
And my girlfriend bought it for me for Christmas
To my surprise the Senseo has
It was even better than advertised
I love it and have made recommendations to my friends cheers
Says Neil
Yeah, someone outside salesperson
My territory includes Menlo Park
If you ever want a free lunch should be an email
We could meet up. Yeah, free lunch
That's right. No free lunch. You know that
I knew thank you very much
Just to reiterate
I don't get paid
For mentioning the Senseo coffee machine
I just love it
I really do. You heard how defensive I got
When Barbara tried to pull it out of my hands
It was standing here on the
On the podcast complex console
And she's grabbing
I was like at least a third full
I mean come on. It's still a temperature left to it
Let me see
One more while we're still on the satellite
As you know, daily source code is a
Time will cast it on serious satellite
Stars 103
After this show, if you're listening to me now on serious
We've got Pacific Coast Hellway
Followed by Madge Weinstein
We got this in great music for you later on tonight
That's a whole the whole Potsho line up
Let's see
I have this here
Okay, this is highway 61 Romeo Bartlett
Like to thank you for what you're doing with podcasting
It's pretty ironic that I'm into your gig though
I have two sons who used to be really into MTV when they were young
They used to be
I always considered MTV to be the root cause of the end of creative music
Since any ass with a catchy video could become a star
I expressed to my young sons and told them the sanitized version of
Adam Curry is a big-haired fag
Since I've been digging the DSC
I've been trying to get them interested in podcasting
In general on the DSC in particular
They both remembered and reminded what I said about you
All those years ago I told them well
Yeah, okay, he's still the same guy but
Without the big hair in the shitty videos
Just strikes me funny as how life can throw these little ironies at you
Uh-huh
And he also said he wanted smack me because
He found us in sao coffee machine at a local pharmacy chain for 40 bucks
And he's digging it
Right on, thanks Romeo
Okay
Metro sexual moment coming up in just a few seconds
Big response on this
Unbelievable how many people how many guys at least have
You know have something to say about in this case
We're talking about shaving and moisturizing
But first let's wave goodbye to our folks on the satellite
We'll talk to you guys tomorrow
Metro sexual
It's Alan Curry's Metro sexual moment
Yeah
And Curry's Metro sexual moment
All pinfield road sum up on the show notes
Which you can get to from
DailySourceCode.com
Of course, that's the wonderful show notes dot info service
We show notes, you can contribute
And people really do, it's very nice
Um, Paul Beanfield says now that we've moved from shaving to perfume
etc, I have a question of course I moisturize after shaving
Vaseline intensive care
Dermacare
Trust me, it's real good shit
I'm 40 and I make you look like an old hag
My question is am I the only guy who wears women's perfume
I use Calvin Klein obsession
I think that I love the smell of it on a woman
Why should I wear it?
Hair on your palms dude
I love it so much better than the horseshit that is offloaded as after shave
Sure, so women think I'm battling for Lancashire
I guess it's a gay reference
I'm batting for Lancashire
Okay, but they don't bother me because they tend to be ugly and angry
Magic contact you lately
I figured they should have bigger things to worry about
So much of the fragrance market is piss and wind
So what are we all wearing?
I'm out
How many others are there?
Well I have to say
Interesting, I have a myriad
But right now I'm into the Calvin Klein stuff as well
But it's not the the girl fragrance it's the
Shit, I'll have to look it up
So much for the preparation of the show
Charles Ravira says
Regarding your metro sexual moment
You're right on on the blade composition
They use higher carbon steel which can be honed much sharper
The blades are ultimately going to last as long as stainless blades but could
Since they're much sharper right out of the box
They'll do just fine for introducing the products
Hmm, this is about the difference between the introduction blade and the replacement blades
Which apparently are not made from the same higher carbon steel
They can't be honed to the edge
And so they'll need replacing more often since they don't stay as sharp
Wow
But they are cheaper to produce so it's a win-win for blade makers
Which makes the loose loose for the customer
No kidding, that's fantastic
Okay, so apparently there is indeed a difference
As also noted on a visual
Inspection by Andrew Grummit
So
We need to get some engineers or someone to really look into this
We need CSI investigation, you know, we're so ratio
CQ says resistive sending a male for ages
But now I've been down the
Juicer getting loop what the hell was that mean
Anyway, CQ says
But the listeners get razor burn, then try tened skin
Or if they live in Australia they should get stop ingrow
These are alcohol based sprays or lotions that contain aspirin
They're marketed to women but are great on the sensitive necks as well
The alcohol sues after burning the shaved areas and stops razor bumps
The aspirin also makes the hair stubble stand up before reducing the chances of ingrowing
I also nicked my flatmates Mark III greeny thing with vibroaction and tried it
It's bloody excellent better than the Mark III, although I don't buy gelette
Because they still test on animals apparently
Dude
They test on animals, what they trust they test shavers on animals
Okay, hey, here we go. We got an audio comment here
I'll see what to see if I can do this
Oh shit this is so suck
Maybe she's just
See, that's the problem with a two channel mixer
Let's try that again. Here we go. Say it
Hey Adam, what's up?
This is Damon from indiependants.com
You hit on something so very important
The DSC 3.06
Any of the razor that you use in that guarantees a good shave
It's the products that you put on your face
For the longest time I used this thick gelette shaving cream
And it did all right, but it always ended up in like a sore face
Using half way through the day I just had some burning flesh on my face
When my wife's cosmatologist ended
She did a great thing for me. She got me this bio elements for him
Shaving cream and after shaved moisturizer
It was a little awkward at first using this stuff
But the first time I used it
I had my first metro sexual moment
I'm telling you this shaving cream is just smooth
It's butter. You put on thin layers
So you feel like you just actually shave and skin
And just not shave and cream off your face
And the first time I used it after shaved serum
I could not believe it. My skin was tight
My complexion was good
Man, when I use this stuff I walk upstairs
I wake up my wife and it's boring
She loves it too
So in my opinion Adam
It's definitely the products that you put on your face
It's not the razor
I just wanted to hear what you thought about that
Thanks a lot
The shampoo
Products be very important
I think we all agree on that
And then finally for today's metro sexual moment
Paul Muller sent an all thing about
This shaving kitty got from his great uncle
And you know he had the screw down razor blades
He's been using the same one for 8 million years
What I like the most of is he ends up by saying
By the way, I had a very metro Christmas this year
My wife got me a Terry cloth bathrobe from L.O.B.
I'm believable how it feels
Only heathens rub themselves after a shower
Refined folk air dry
Okay guys, it was nice hanging with you
And talking around the water cooler about our personal hygiene
And our shaving habits and the perfumes we wear
Let's keep this up because to me it's very very liberating
Oh yeah, you got to check this out
This came in from the on safe music network
I have something
Sipes their DJ
I want to take you on a little sound scene
To a high have something
Did a Trinity remix by a diesel
Future by a diesel by a diesel me
By a diesel by a diesel
Oh, I am so excited
Will you sell me this car
If you figure it out yet
I actually reached my park that was going to pull it out and start talking
If you figure it out
And ladies and gentlemen
I present you with Trinity Trinity
It is about the on list
The on list car I've ever seen in my entire life
That's about all the luxury you're going to get
By a diesel by a diesel
Oh, I am so excited
She's just like a young cute
What is this set to?
That's me kicking the rear bumper
Oh, she's nice and sail
Hold these different things
Got my coat on
Hello, hello, hello
Coming down at you
Okay, I want to say
Right, and it is all ready
Clean it up with a biop diesel
99.9% vegetable oil
Pressure
Listen to that puppy first
And the runs on the chart
By a diesel by a diesel
Oh, I am so excited
This car was mentioned for me
And it runs like a chart
Okay, you just see me driving down
First straight in San Francisco
With this pumping in the music video
By a diesel by the biodiesel
For some reason I care
Excellent dude, cypster DJ, biodiesel
Available now on the pod save music network
And that's going to sound good in the club, man
I tell you
All right, everybody, thanks for listening
I'll be back tomorrow
We'll have our midweek edition of the daily source code
Preparing for
Departure to San Francisco
Leaving on Sunday with the virgin
We'll be flying away
For a stint on the rig
And it's going to be very busy two weeks
Because we'll be opening up pieces of the network
We'll be finally the strategy cast
We'll get made now
We're kind of all in sync with development
We can actually talk about it on the strategy cast
I know it's been a couple weeks
That I've been promising you this
But I guess in the end it's going to be much better
Because we'll really be able to talk about some things
That are real you can go check out
And
Yeah, we'll do whatever we do
So thanks for checking it out
DailySourceCode.com
Adamaccurry.com for your feedback
And if you are subscribed
Thank you very much