This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts on GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Blog it with your free quick blog from GoDaddy.
May we have your attention please.
Do not cry out to remain calm.
This show is going into motion.
Daily source comes number five hundred and forty eight.
GoDaddy.com.
the curry condo. Hey, it's Friday, everybody. It's Fubar, which stands for fucked up beyond
all repair, at least it does on this show. And I want to welcome you all, but thank you
Brian. No, for pointing that one out. Those guys from Australia literally, it says it's a demo.
Now in their 11th year, they started at 13 years old in 1995. They won many national band
competitions, including the music Oz 2000 signed an international deal with Sony O2 released.
Sony O2 released their EP and oh, and Sony and O2, I got it released their EP in June 2004
gaining national airplay on radio and TV with you're on fire. No, hold on a second.
No, you're on fire isn't. Oh, wait. Is it on the podcast music network? Let me see.
They got a whole bunch and they're all title-like demo. Okay, so they don't have that one up there.
Great. Love it. And they've got an album coming out in early 2007. Can't wait to hear from these guys.
I think that their stuff is absolutely kick-ass. So it's the last show for this trip out to
California to pod show HQ. Because I won't be back for probably about a month, which is
obviously longer than I'd like it to be, but we've got the holidays coming up. And of course,
the first two weeks of January, we are moving house, as they say, in the UK. We're moving from the
What are we moving from the east side of Gilford? No, the west side of Gilford to the east.
Let me just check again. No, from the east side of Gilford to the west side of Gilford.
So that's going to take a couple of days to get settled in, get everything working. And you know
what's going to happen, even though I've already requested all the changes of services, you know that
the bandwidth will be fucked up. The satellite won't work. The telephone won't be connected.
And all of that amidst a celebrity birthday coming up, folks.
You know, we will live soon. Oh, hell, screw that. Hey, Adam, it's Brian. I just want to let you know
that the Jesus interview part one is available right now. And part two will be up in the next couple
days. So if you're interested in what the man has to say, you can find out for yourself,
attitude.podshow.com. Thanks. Can't wait. I see that it's up. So I'll definitely go and check it out.
And we'd love to hear from more you folks out there.
Yeah, it really is quite interesting how I'm getting so many calls from the UK these days. So I want to kick it off with
that U.S. voice number.
It's still easier for me to remember the U.S. one. All right. So we're going to scam the scam.
We're going to scan the voicemail box. You know, I had two beers last night.
That's why I'm all discombobulated. Two whole beers. You know what that does to me, right?
Scott Sigler had a quick little drink with him in between meetings. Literally. We were all in a meeting.
I guess the guys are going to meet up with Scott at 21st Amendment, which is right across from
our office building here at San Francisco. 21st Amendment is a bar, obviously. We then moved down to
Nova since 20 to 21st was filled to the brim. And you know, so we had a drink at like 530.
Then I went back and then we finished some more meetings that we were doing. I got to see Scott. We're
going to do some crazy ass things with him in 2007 with everybody. We're going through this big, huge,
would you go? We're getting our shit together. That's what I want to say. We're finally getting
our shit together. We're going to start figuring some stuff out. I think. Let's make 2007 the year
we get our shit together, shall we? I don't know. It's Andrew Terrylessness from up there Oxford
in the UK. Just listening to the last year, we were mentioning that in the new year,
you're going to kick off flying tools. I really think you need to rethink a title. And I was thinking
AC's high, given just in our so many levels, and AC's high AC's high to get it. I'll get my coat.
Okay. I don't know about that. So this is the show that I want to do in 2007, the video show.
I like flying tools because we're all fools in aviation, mainly because most people burn
all their money in the air when they're in aviation. AC high. I understand when you're coming from
not, you know, AC's high. Got to think about it. Open to more suggestions. Hey, who's that? He's
you're on a black and black emotion to rock this mother out. You're on a piece. Don't bend
that girl. It drives cowbell out. And let's all give a dive to the heart of work in the
room. You're just in time. Yeah. What's up, Adam? It's Jersey Todd. The official music
college of the Chacha. And today, today I've got something very special for you. And that's an
exclusive for the Jersey Todd show in the Daily Source Code. From the album 13 from Surf Dog Records,
I'm bringing you one of the true innovators of the music scene today, Mr. Brian Settler. And when I
love about this song that I'm going to play for you, we are the mortars. It just sums up podcasting.
I mean, check out these lyrics. This is Brian Settler on the DCSC. Talk to you later. But he
happy holidays.
The big television star, we are the Russ.
It's nothing, no one taught us.
The girl of Pennsylvania, man.
The stick of shovel riding your hand.
We've got this music in our soul.
It's nothing to care here on the radio.
If you don't get it, that's your tough luck.
We don't care about making a book.
We're the boys that are here to ride.
We are the Russ.
We'll never obey your orders.
All right, now they think you're a fool.
But next year they'll be following cues.
We'll don't find the official life.
If you don't like the story,
let me one more roll and ride.
I said, five, you want more roll and ride.
Come on, five, you want more roll and ride.
We are the Russ.
Let this one roll and ride.
You got it to what you want to do.
But this roll and ride is way too short.
Feel free to you, well there's a star.
That's all right.
Thank you very much, Jersey Todd.
Happy holidays to you as well, my friend.
Good to hear that.
That's not on the podcast music network yet.
But I hope it will be shown up pretty soon.
By the way, most of the songs you hear on this program,
can be found at podshow.com slash music.
Or in the show notes, a daily source code.com.
Let me see, I wrote down a couple of things.
A couple of notes for today's show.
See, got some feedback here from Luke from the helm.
That's interesting.
I'm going to ask you a question about no keys.
How did you manage to get your podshow on the go channel
into the nokey of podcasting application?
Yes.
Is this something anyone can use?
You could even put it in your iTunes or any other type of podcast
you have created channel at podshow plus.
If you create an account, you automatically have a channel
that's named after yourself.
So you can use that one or create a new one if you want.
So if you're going to use the one that you already have,
first, add a show to it.
There's instructions there.
And so if you already have a channel, go just click on the channel name
and open up a little edit box.
And right there, you can choose how you want to enjoy your channel.
So that could be in the dashboard, which is the default.
Or you could set it to iTunes.
And if you say that, iTunes is going to open.
And it's going to automatically subscribe you to your channel.
Which, of course, will synchronize up
right up to your iPod.
There's also, I don't like the name yet.
It's, we call it what we call raw XML,
which I think is the wrong way to title that.
In fact, we probably should have a whole fucking list of stuff.
Like, you're Nokia phone.
So anyway, if you do raw XML, it'll give you the URL.
And you just copy that and you put that right at,
you use that to subscribe in your Nokia application
just say add podcast under that the top menu.
So that should work.
Maybe we should do a, can someone do a screen, a screen cast of that?
That'll be pretty cool.
Because it really is awesome.
When you can control, see that the Nokia app,
in fact, as Luke said, let me just see where the hell was this.
There, I lose it already.
What the hell was that?
Oh, here it is.
Here we go.
I found the application a bit slow on my Nokia N80.
But I think that's due to I'm writing to the one gig,
a gig memory card.
Hmm.
Now, I mean, all these, the phones, of course, are not as fast as computers
because they just don't have processors that are that fast.
So that's why I like managing just one channel.
Well, I have a couple, but really managing my channels on my Nokia
from any web browser.
You see how that stuff starts to, starts to work, starts to make sense.
So I can, if I don't want to have a certain show on my daily commute,
like I have a daily commute on my daily commute to the office in London.
Then I just remove it from the channel.
There's no bullshit on the phone.
And the phone is automatically synced up, or any other device that I have
subscribed to that channel.
Ah, this is one of those typical ones, Alistair Janks.
Researchers in New Zealand have proven that there is a link between cannabis
and mental illness.
Oh, yes.
Well, let's see what the story says.
I don't know if the bandwidth at the condo is just slow today,
or it seems like things are just going a little slow.
I'll screw it.
I'm not going to wait for that.
That's going to take too long.
Oh, crap.
There's one thing I don't like about that Google notebook.
If you use that at all, is that unlike everything else the Google
does, when you click on a link, instead of opening up a new tab or
a new browser window, you can set that in your browser.
Of course, what it does is it just goes to the page.
So you lose the page that had your notes on it.
And Google doesn't behave this way in Google reader or in Gmail or in
calendar or anything.
Anything with a link and external link pops open on new tabs.
I don't understand why they do that in this.
Anyway, so I guess that's true.
There's some sure there's a link between mental illness and cannabis.
Just in time for the holidays, there's podshow music rewind.
Episode number 50 is out.
I haven't heard it yet, but I saw it come through in my channel today.
The best of rewind.
Look back at 15 of the most memorable podcasters who have appeared on
the show.
Marcus Couds doing his thing, of course, great.
Hi, Adam, it's David Cohen.
One of your YouTube listeners here.
Can you give me a favor?
The whole Giselle thing is getting kind of old now.
Can you on one of the next episodes?
Just ask them to ring in and give you whatever it is they're promoting.
Obviously they're promoting some sort of podcasters or something like that.
The whole thing sounds really fake now and it's getting kind of old.
So can you just get them to tick their hat and just find out what's going on.
So we can all find out and move on from it.
That'll be good.
Thanks very much, bye.
Interesting.
I talked about this with Scott Sigler last night and he said,
Wow, the drama of that shit is unbelievable.
He's like, I don't really know if it's real or not.
We went through that yesterday and there was some analyzing that,
forget it at someone, look at the waveforms and the CSIDSC lab and
determined that the messages we've been getting from Nick,
who says the Giselle has gone missing for four days.
R&D, the same voice that sent in this message.
I don't know who this is but stop fucking calling Giselle at all.
And I don't, I don't know.
I'm going to, I'm still going to take it pretty seriously.
And if there's, if there is indeed some kind of big payoff and there's some,
this is some kind of big joke and I agree,
you should probably get it over with pretty soon.
Although I do appreciate the way all of you are treating it.
First one, two, one, six, five, six, three, five, seven.
But stop fucking calling the Giselle at seven.
And we're reaching across international boundaries.
They need to be events.
My couple of them at Bell and I can chill.
Punna cook.
And this is now for me and R&D.
I have a couple of questions.
What if I happen to be in a metro station?
I really like that segment.
You mean the metro sectional moment?
Yeah, I haven't done one of those in a long time.
I don't know.
I guess I just didn't have the inspiration after I told you guys,
you know, how I remove hair and how I shave.
Yeah, how I smell nice.
I didn't have much left to say.
That's how I had a question.
I was really wondering if anybody has found a really like after surely has like an
SPF, like a 15 or something because I'm really looking for something like that.
Or I hate the punna book.
I think that's a good one.
I don't think you can actually do that.
I think the aftershave part is supposed to like clean out the wounds you've created.
Fuck at home on the second.
Let me see if I can find it.
Here you go.
Okay.
Hello Adam.
This is Mike Moss.
Shit, that's not the one I was looking for.
I can't even find my metro.
It's been so long.
Metro moment.
Maybe that's one.
Is this it?
No.
That's just people calling for a metro sectional moment dude.
Sorry.
Can't find it.
Can't find the music anymore.
It's been that long.
I don't think there is an aftershave.
With an SPF factor.
I think you have to go for a moisturizer.
What the hell am I doing?
First of all, moisturizer.
That's not too much.
I want to have one item.
That's where it's for me.
Everything else.
Whatever happens to it with a sun.
It's certainly when we say the way we know it goes in.
I don't really like that.
That was pretty sweet.
It made me feel special because I was into the podcast.
And I would go to the beach.
Do what you know.
When I was being special.
Thanks a much back.
All right.
Well, you want to feel special then?
Okay.
Sit back.
Put your hands by your side.
No.
You seem like no.
There.
There you go.
Put them by your side.
Okay.
That's right.
It's close.
Everybody.
Because I'm just going the way.
He's here to repair your satellite.
The satellite repair man.
Coming after you.
What's he going to do?
He'll fix your miscene sessions.
And answer questions too.
You're nothing in the universe.
And you can't do for you.
The satellite repair man.
Woo!
Come on.
Hey, Bonnie.
Okay.
I've got a couple more minutes.
Just time enough to play something for you.
This was quite amazing.
You know, we've had.
And when I say, we, I mean, pod show UKBT pod show.
We've had ongoing conversations.
For quite a while.
Because John Cleese does a podcast.
And it's an audio podcast, which I didn't care too much for his audio podcast.
But I'd like the idea of John Cleese.
And I think that's a very marketable media property, obviously.
And we could do something cool with his show.
Certainly get a more attention than what he's been getting over the past 16 episodes.
But we really couldn't get it together with the guy who I guess he's.
I guess he's a, he's a, he has like a production company.
So I guess he records the audio and edits it and puts up the RSS feeds his guy.
Which turns out to be a dick, by the way, Dean Whitbread.
It's just not a nice guy.
I don't like him at all.
You know, he, what we just couldn't get anything together.
We couldn't actually even get to discussing the podcast.
So, you know, off the wall with with what he's thinking about and what he's doing.
And so this morning, and of course, I'm subscribed to the John Cleese podcast.
You can find it in a pod show plus just to use the search.
I'll put a link to it in the show notes.
Search for John Cleese and you'll find it.
And so they finally came out with a video podcast.
And well, you know, I'm going to let you listen to the audio because I was really,
I mean, the, the production is great.
It's called an airline rant and, and it looks great.
But the, the jokes was just like shit.
Okay.
Listen in.
On airplanes, they announced the captain has switched on the seat belt sign.
Are they mad?
The important words here are captains switched on and seat belt sign.
So, these stress, the word has only a reason to say the captain has switched on the seat belt sign.
Is it all the passengers are just shouted out?
Why hasn't the captains switched on the seat belt sign?
In which case was hostess of stewarders?
I'll plate the ten under one.
I mean, she's called this week.
Would be in sighting to say the captain has switched on the seat belt sign because she's contradicting them.
Similarly, the announcement, the plane will be landing in 20 minutes.
The important words here are plane landing and 20 minutes.
So they stress will only, if the passengers are coursing, the plane won't be landing in 20 minutes.
Then the plane will be landing in 20 minutes.
Makes sense.
So, airlines, do something about it.
Will it?
You know, I'm a big John Klee's fan.
I love Monty Python.
And I'm just about anything those guys do.
But the airline jokes?
I mean, this has been done by a thousand comedians.
You know, George Carlin has a great routine about airlines and, you know, you get in the plane and not on the plane and pre-boarding.
So, I just don't understand how this is not funny.
It's not funny and it's old.
Really disappointed.
I don't understand how that happened.
Oh, well.
A serious satellite, one or two listeners, you were about to lose me.
Too bad.
They already lost.
Yeah, so that was, I was really surprised by that.
For all the hoopla, this Dean Guy was making.
I'd expect it a little bit more.
Anyway, I'll put a link in the show notes.
You can go check it out for yourself.
No!
The oldest thing to the daily source, Klee.
Adam Klee.
The guy who is obviously handsome is filthy rich.
As a full head, our gorgeous, long hair has two gorgeous women in his life.
Me, I'm G.D.
I'm old, fat, and bald.
With the perfect face for podcasting.
And if I try really hard, I could probably find two pennies to rub together.
But what I can bring you is 60 minutes of the best independent music five times a week.
That's right.
Mindy food to Friday.
Direct from my home at Typhoid Towers.
I'm a tiny island off the North Wales coast.
I bring you G.D.s bite-sized bonus.
If you like good music, come on over to bite-sized bonus.pogshow.com
and listen to the Greatest Hits you've never heard.
That's bite-sized bonus.pogshow.com.
It's what your ears have been waiting for.
You'd better believe it.
Bite-sized bonus.
Doing it to you.
5 day the week.
www.bite-sized bonus.pogshow.com.
Yeah!
The force is growing in the UK at btpodshow.com.
Welcome to the network.
I think we're supposed to have a holiday party on Friday.
So, obviously not today, but next Friday at the shortage office at the UK crash pad as we call it.
I hope that we'll be seeing some of the network podcasters show up as well.
I have no idea who's been invited.
It's so difficult, man.
Let me tell you.
We've like 125 people coming tonight for the party in San Francisco.
And you know, parties are big word.
I think we're doing the right thing, actually.
You know, from 6 to 9, we're going to have food.
We're going to have some music.
We're going to have some fun.
And then, well, we have to organize the after party.
Who's taking care of that, guys?
Peter Cogel.
Ask Cogel.
Paul with a sea of Cogel.
He's a 16-year-old music freak.
Tract inside the 45-year-old spotty.
Weird and wonderful music.
It's fairly eclectic.
He's only just about anything.
If you like it, I'll play it.
From the latest indie rock, jazz, folk, and bandra.
Twice a week at PC podcast.
Podger.com.
Diversity, musical stars.
Just brightening up someone's day.
Yeah.
I also knew on the network this week as a new Dr. Cogney in West London.
Check that out, International Sex Therapist. podshow.com.
It's the URL you can never remember.
I just kind of beaty podger.com or a few.
I could go search for Dr. Cogney.
It's just a funny shit.
Let's see.
It was a new who's on it.
I don't know if that one's out yet with O.J.
And oh, a new in the attic with Rachel and Pete and the gang.
The fucking great episode.
And I'm really, I got to tell you.
At first, I really was guilty of making jokes about Rachel.
Rachel followers at Pete Townsend's girlfriend.
You know, significantly younger girlfriend.
I might add.
But the more I watch this show in the attic.
So it's in the attic. podshow.com.
The more I watch it, the more I'm really drawn to her.
She is an amazing woman.
She's fun. She's wacky.
I really love the wackiness.
She smokes.
I like that.
And she's sexy.
And she's very talented.
I really like her stuff.
Anyway, so I'm going to try and get her into the.
Into the shortage office.
Maybe do a couple interviews and hang out.
But look at the next episode of in the attic.
At in the attic. podshow.com.
I think you'll agree that this is really some amazing shit.
Okay, Marcus Couch sent me a cage nine song earlier in the week.
Because, of course, I'm sure responsible for getting these guys in the podsafe music network.
You can go to podshow.com slash music and find them.
The names are cage nine.
This is Hollywood Car Crash.
For your food bar Friday on the daily source code.
We'll see you in the next episode.
Oh, yes, that's one talking about it's Friday...
...a.
That's right, we wind up another week at his rhubarb Friday, which means it's time for the final thought of the week.
And really, I've been thinking about a couple of people this week.
I just wanted to stop and thank for all of the work they've been doing, because as is typical with going today's world in general,
people really see what's on the outside. Now, this is kind of a metaphor, but you'll understand what I'm talking about.
They see the pretty pictures, the moving images, they see the things to, you know, to stroke and feel and click and lick.
But there's always something going on underneath under the hood.
Well, that's right, I'm talking about the engineers.
Now, for the past month or so, we've had a new guy in in a pod show.
I think I talked about him before his name is A.L. Shavid.
And together with the engineering team, these guys are really pulled off just such an amazing feat of really organizing this huge ball of the huge tar ball.
Let's call it that we call our platform.
And really when you look at the stuff that has to be done to create the infrastructure to make all of this stuff work, and you know, just take a look at it at podshow.com.
You can see that there's a lot of work that's going on that has been done.
And of course, there's still a lot of work to do.
But these, these ladies and gentlemen, truly are the unsung heroes pretty much of everything cool in our lives.
Everything, you know, whenever you flip on the television, whenever you use the dishwasher, whenever you listen to a podcast or make a podcast,
there's a whole bunch of people that you probably will never know about never will meet, probably will ever even think about who make all that possible.
And let me tell you, writing code, it's like painting.
It's like writing a book.
It's like, you know, any other type of creative activity.
It can be done in a million different ways.
You can get from here to there.
It's just an infinitesimal amount of ways.
So it's creative and I just really wanted to stop and say that I do think about that because, well, I signed your paychecks.
I think fuck what these guys do.
That's, it really is great.
So for this holiday season, I want to toast all the engineers and developers in the world because they just don't get enough props.
I just wanted to play one last song, which is, I don't think it's a gone pod safe or that it's up.
Of course, the song itself is pretty much one of the oldest songs in the book.
If you have not seen the podcast for Bolivian Bolivian Bolivian Bolivian, Bolivian Rapcity, this is a video show you've got to check out.
It's a crew who went to or in Bolivia or went to Bolivia.
I think they might, they just got back from from a trip.
And the whole trip is for, for a good cause, it's for a charity called Sikhism in Bolivia.
It's a charity foundation, and what their goal is is to improve education for children,
obviously, children's education in Bolivia, and the pictures, and it's really focused
around music, and certainly these first things like two episodes up, and the first
of the country, the people, it's so beautiful, and you just, yeah, it's so well done, and
shot in the wide screen. I don't know if it's HD, maybe it's even HD. But they're kind
of mixing and mashing it up, and so there's a very popular song, which I'm going to play
for you. There's a video for it. I don't know if this video is available yet. I hope we
can make it available because I really want you to see the video clip. If it's not in
the episode, I just haven't had time to look at the episode, but I saw the clip and
like I got to share the song with you. So as a Dutch guy on piano, shit was his name. Was it
Mike? I think. And a Bolivian songstress, and just imagine the setting here for a second
if you will. It's a grand piano, there's candles, you know, it's kind of got that nice, soft
glow over it, and I'm sure you'll recognize the song just in time for the holidays, where
in the world children all have equal education and love throughout the land.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let
go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let'm go, let's go,
I don't stick that in your pipe, smoke it, will you?
Damn, that's great.
All played live.
I'll look in the, just before I upload the show,
I'll see if we wish you all the Merry Christmas
Happy Holidays, believe me,
in Rhapsody.podshow.com.
Ah, how nice.
Oh, I wanted to tell you that looks like we're,
we're gonna be doing a concert series in 2007 with Pod Show.
Across all genres, great live music, video,
fantastic performances.
By chance, you actually will recognize it.
All right, everybody.
If you have a holiday party that you're going to,
today or this weekend, have yourselves a great one.
Enjoy the weekend.
I probably will not be doing, yeah, I might have a show on Monday.
I'm leaving Sunday, so arriving Monday morning.
Yeah, what the hell?
What the hell?
Beyond the lookout for our first show on Monday.
And everybody, have a great day.
Bye.
Another Pod Show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best and the brightest served up daily
by the sharpest minds in content delivery,
Pod Show and Limelight.