One at a 420 which is a location.
This is one at a 420.
What do we have?
We have an unlawful episode 490 in progress, copy.
A base.
Could you be more specific on what's unlawful?
There's been a report for some unlawful folding and scrunching at the curry condo you can
check it out.
One at a 420 copy that on my way.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplanes trapped in my ass.
Transmiddles.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding.
It's a matter of theory.
One, two, three.
Got it.
Turn the audits.
With 23 million venture capital behind the organization.
Don't name names.
An international podcasting network second to none.
We don't need no stinking, don't name names.
No one in the office thought to ask.
Hey Adam, is this email from GoDaddy important?
One, two, three, four.
You were listening to the Delta CR Charlie on the million part.
Show delivery at work at hotchro.com.
You were listening to the Delta CRApplause.
You are way better.
Take off the weekend, wind up the week with a little bit of boomers buggy.
Check it out.
When睇 music network, I linked to the show.
the source code dot com actually get ran into them because they've been getting some heat
with this track too much bush blues which is uh...
that's also it's a blues track obviously it's kind of cool but uh...
i don't know i didn't really like the political statement being
uh... but then i uh... i found this boomers boogie is like yeah these guys definitely rock
from Montana in the united states of america hey everybody it is the daily source code
four nine or zero another beautiful day in the affluent suburb of surrey known as
gilford in the united kingdom it's uh... again once uh...
you know really crisp uh... about three degrees above uh... freezing
right now in the uh... on the centigrade scale that is
and the sun is shining uh... no daddy Patricia today
we had words this morning and then either was felt like doing a show together which
of course with the perfect moment to do a show
uh...
but she had to go to sainsbury had to do some shopping so i had to figure i wouldn't press the
point would we get it done next week although i don't know man
next week's gonna be busy again gonna be in the London office staying overnight again
for another uh... you know we're getting so close to the uh... beaty podshow dot com launch
and uh... the uh...
the upgraded version of podshow plus
i just don't know this there's just no time for nothing you know it's crazy
but that's not gonna thwart us from celebrating our food bar friday we're fucked up
beyond all repair that's for sure i'm just looking around the office here and saying
crap
this place is like it's a pigsty it's like uh...
it's a disaster area literally it is
it should be deemed as such by Tony Blair there's just hope just big piles of
wires and
paperwork and stacks and stacks of bills
most of them paid just you know me laboriously going through them god i hate this
i need a secretary so bad it's not funny
i guess i have to get into that uh... when we move i got to change some things around
i just don't have time for it for this crap it's uh... yeah yeah
and i'm also planning this uh... flying fools
flight
on Sunday night uh...
yet to get you some pictures of guy fox day slash
bonfire night and it's just gotten more confusing now we'll get into that in a minute
and it's other thing and this is kind of it's not pissing me off it's the
lack of response that's well it listened to this
uh...
explained the other day
that uh... the podfather logo
which is basically the podfather poster
with me on it and says podfather has been used for a couple years now
and the guardian newspaper is now plugging their three extra boner shows with rickie
jervais which by the way in paragraph or so you know like
in the second minute of each show he's begging for money
i guess that audible thing didn't pay off so well
uh...
he's using they're using the exact same poster and podfather moniker to promote that show
and it's just that's plagiarism
that's all and people are picking up on finally hello at the
they become some sort of contributor long time listen to the dsc
just wants to make you call it that's you on the uh... rich device guardian
podfather thing
just in the sense you're talking about
it seems to me that uh... you know they when they play the arson maybe you should
you know you put you should go off of
when he uh...
it's not the same sort of thing is when the
juts magazine went for a
pictures of
things off your separate half of the shows
and then magazine i know that was more of a personal task in more of a big
years
that's uh... in you know in the court
i think he's basically said we're both they're taking your copyright
over uh... in this case is the device in the garden taking
portrait of the right
just a little
actually later
yeah although i appreciate the thought of course not i've absolutely no rights
i mean i stole the podfather uh... poster myself i actually i didn't do it
i didn't come up with a name podfather
but it just pisses me off that everyone's a fucking self-righteous when they think
pod shows done something a evil or wrong or
we stole and or hijack something and everyone's up and arms but then when it
respected mainstream media
uh... publication
plagiarizes everyone's fucking silent because it's about me
uh... it's just lame
it's just fucking lame
i got all your names and numbers too assholes
i added this is uh... johnson girl can ask us this up the road from here
little bit of the nation that bonfire night
the actual bonfire night is
this from a member which is sunday this year
but for practical reasons bonfire's occur
whatever it's convenient around that time
it's not on the fifth doesn't know it's all happened on a weekend
so there's no reason why we shouldn't be bonfire's on fire night or second night or something
night
and they're influential thinking also if i don't believe this
fog forecast of sunday may make saturday back at that anyway
they like to share an awful lot of times i'd follow this day
if you say to the air on the back of the night for seven nights
that's an out
older
and so we're planning this trip you know to go and uh... get video of uh... of bonfire night
no one gave me a straight answer on this thing
yeah so it's november fifth everybody agrees on that
uh... but apparently it's uh... going to be celebrated on the november fourth
on the uh... saturday night in a lot of places including gilford as far as i can tell
and i get all kinds of conflicting information let's see uh... david graham says
true bonfire night is the fifth
small garden parties will be held out often
will be held but often big fireworks as players are often delayed to
to the closest weekend there's more people will likely to go on that's not even
english man so this year will be saturday
okay uh... let me see do we have more guy fox night from john
go last cock
little research on the what on the web reveals these tidbits yet dude wikipedia is not
research anymore my book seems at the night of the fifth is bonfire night
throughout britain week commemorate the capture of guy fox bonfires and fireworks and
by burning an effigy of guy
uh...
by the way that uh... that nursery rhyme is a lot longer than the uh...
then the bit that we uh... that we're aware of
remember that this is a no-zember
jump out of treason and flocks i seen a reason why gump out of treason should never be
and it continues with guy fox guy fox
twesses intent to blow up the king and the parliament
three score barrels of powder below portled England to overthrow
by god's providence he was cached with a dark lantern and burning match
hola boys hola boys let the bills are it let the bills ring hola boys hola boys
i think that's what it is
god save the king hippy parah hippy parah
a penny loaf to feed all pop a farthing cheese to choke him
a pint of beer to rinse it down a faggot of sticks to burn him
that's interesting burn him in a tub of tar burn him like a blazing star burn his body
from his head then we'll say all pulp is dead
a faggot of sticks no less
and yet go there's some proper use of the english language
one more bob bonfire night
abomin john again how you can
uh... deterred in the death of the show
uh... you're questioning about all fine i guess
traditionally on fire night fifth and a member
would you track his own day
but in those days uh... those people hold their events
and on seven night
and uh... are you fans or in the paper
uh... and then sell a couple weeks ago
but to sell about one by night
uh... yeah definitely the bill for one
open the same three deathly saturday night from seven o'clock
and and there are other ones being held around you for a bit later served
that's it you know seven eight nine window you'll certainly see a fair amount
uh... for now and be down taking it one step further
and there will be strapping fireworks to the actual helicopter and flying the
night and uh... they will happen there that's a hold in front
so i'll let you know that that team uh... can't get a point
crap now that's cool strapping fireworks to your helicopter i'm loving that
all right for those of you who believe
there will be saturday night uh... will there be anything going on sunday night because we
just can't do it saturday night that's the whole problem here so
uh... i really need to know because i got a lot of stuff to reserve i got to talk to
the airfield you know i got to have some guy come out in the middle of the night
and flip the lights on and sit in the tower
so please it will be worth it to go sunday night that's really all that i need to know
but it it's quite important
lots of stuff uh... here in the uh... this is uh... this is a big one
be sure to wish rosanna happy anniversary on friday show
on the fifth which is guy fox day which of course is sunday and there's no daily
source code will be married forty years
wow
that will be p-dub and the lovely ros forty years man
what kind of uh... anniversaries that forty years
is that like teflon
i don't think there's an actual stone associated with it
let me see here i'm still using that google note pad
i guess it's just kind of cool
uh... jadonally
a producer of
mad pod's test drive girl in the dummy cast nominated for two vloggies
at uh... in san francisco to be held this saturday
hold on a second
summer
uh...
dog barks like the fucking same benard
it's just a little yorky
uh... so congratulations uh... to jadonly and crew
is girlfriend
uh... test drive ride love test drive girl that's a great great show
and uh... and dummy cast definitely not to uh...
not to be disregarded there nominated for two vloggies you can check it out
vloggies sf dot com congratulations j
got a nice uh... hook up with uh... an old buddy of mine
through uh... princess
was it princess typo she uh...
pretty much uh... is the online persona of stufia ramus
she's always sending in you know ideas comments uh... bug reports uh... she seems to be
a real wheel in uh... uh... in the in online music community
and she sent an email yesterday and said uh... hey out of my found a little
butt of yours and it was Rudy sarso
and Rudy sarso uh... i think uh... what i feel he's cuban i think he's cuban
Rudy and not sure anymore it doesn't really matter
other than i would have said the fantastic cuban base player uh... who i met when
uh... he was playing with white snake at the time uh... adrian vandenberg uh...
find dutch guitarist it's crazy here i can't concentrate got dogs barking i've got the
phone ringing nobody's here but me go away
go away
uh... so i met him uh... you know when white snake was at the top of their game
as i said adrian vandenberg uh... the long blonde dutchman
uh... play guitar in the band at the time
and uh... so Rudy Patricia uh... and i and uh... Rudy's wife Rebecca we hang out in the
life a little bit uh... never forget we went to some movie the four of us in
Patricia fell asleep within like four minutes
pretty funny uh... so i'm looking forward to hooking up with Rudy uh... when i finally
do get to Los Angeles and i'm sure there will be a Los Angeles trip very very soon
hey let's get this uh... Friday kicked up one notch okay
after all we are all who bar nespas
from the pop safe music network
seven oh and that's so terrible
it's the three-minute classic i don't need to know what i'm supposed to do with
it's right he didn't know so fun i'm about to do it and it's only been three minutes
i really can't finish like this i'm never like this i usually
remember like this i try to set the scene on the wall a little bit of that
i want to steam on the three minutes later i gotta put my jeans on some of your
demon in the sack i don't want it for maybe i go close keep it for
that's right tiktok but i just can't control my
girl i ain't need to put it in yet with the fuck's a deal you gotta keep a ring
you can't be freaking out like janna hit but i feel even though you're
waistline let's take time never waste time it over here one go the
big kind i don't know what's gonna catch that for the poor
but i think it's gonna be too late for the load together
i'm about to leave y'all why cuz i can't believe it
you don't need the fuck's a deal you gotta keep a ring
everybody was boom and see that the lips are misguided
yo union plus all that play i've been my moonly human trying to focus my mind
and let's take a way from the climbing but she's riding up
you didn't find them baby there's no way winding
i'd rather take up a while and cheat over we don't have
none of his feet who's always angry i don't think
it's not only those right now she's melting him out in one one but
baby three seconds in counting and then he's dropping in
beat four from out in five thousand but she won't stop and she won't listen
she's like banging on a mission i'm like hold up wait let me make this great show
let's do it
crazy
Oh no, watch me, and watch me
How do we do your own song and story?
How do we do?
When are things and glory?
We're both on time, all in every moment
something you didn't know you were going to kill him.​
All right darling, big bang bang bang!
Clap bang bang!
Okay, we've got nothing to do of that here.​
They're comp machine!
That's a good like much!
7L AndSO Terric, you can find them in the Podajuian Music Network at music.podshow.com,
they're from Massachusetts,
that's from destiny, album and new dope lots of people,
there you go, which has been out for a couple of months, and I guess doing quite well, I love that.
very cool song. I told you the other day that we'll be launching with a new show in the
attic with Rachel Fuller and Pete Townsend of who fame and just next week actually and I
did want to point out that this is not a coincidence those of you listening to serious
satellite radio and hearing the show. The who who are currently on tour will well they have a
channel on serious right now it's called guess what the who channel it's channel 10 on your
serious receiver and every night at nine o'clock eastern time they play a full recent concert
recording by the who so actually tonight it would be the show from London which was recorded
2004 and let's see they've got another show they got show throughout the weekend as well
with Rachel Fuller's backstage reports as we know her the backstage bitch but that's only on
serious she's a superstar when it comes to pod show to check that out for sure. The comics are
blogger I'm sure will give us a report I think he can receive that at home. Let me just see here
for a second I had some more stuff and what to talk to you about. Hey wow Google released a
an email client for mobile phones the Gmail mobile app I guess it's called hey this thing is
really really good I tried it out on the the Nokia N91 phone damn it's like it's fantastic it
gives you all the functionality plus some of the shortcuts actually because you can use your
your phones keep had as it does on the web it's really good really fast very nice even better than
the mobile web web page that I've been using I'm really really liking it of course it doesn't work
on the blackberry which is well that's a bummer to say at least now I do believe that I have a new
Nokia N93 come in my way so I know it'll work on that and that's really the only thing I'm worried
about you know about giving up the blackberry I'd love to have additional functionality but it's really
the speed with which you can navigate and create and and reply to emails and now it looks like
that problem will be solved you can go to gmail.com slash app and download it now they say it only
works for US networks but I tried it with my UK phone and I have I think a T mobile account works
fine so I don't think that's entirely true but man it's really really really cool totally digging
definitely check that out if you can. Hey Adam this is Chris and I find actually about just
on the road just listening to the October 31st episode of the DSC we're going to explain
that there are a small number of people myself including who are allergic to it what we're specifically
allergic to is the chlorine in it because it's one that's made circular this is made by you're
chlorinating sugar effectively so it's not so we're not life threatening it's just something
caused some discomfort and stuff like that but there are people who are allergic to it so if you
are chances are you should probably just not use it you'll know if you are the easiest way to tell
this obviously take a few days or possibly a week don't have any and then how to expose yourself
to dose of it either in soda or the powder form and see what happens if you have a rash or reaction
then you know splinters not feel it's the chlorine probably so you may be allergic to other chlorine
products may have a hard time for example using bleaching or laundry you may have a similar reaction
so that's the one thing about splinter my dad works for J&J and he's very very pleased with how
well splinters done in the market and glad to see that podcasts are sponsoring it but it's not
for everybody so just be aware that this is good so find actually podcasts trying to avoid
splinter every day that's all right that's cool dude some people got to avoid eggs you know some
people got to avoid me quite frankly so that's all right but appreciate the input there
and say hey to your dad we'll come up and take a factory tour one of these days it's the assembly
line or is he working at some desk job it's a fine product made with sucralose how the heck do you
pay for speeding tickets here in the UK this has this has me completely baffled this is speed
camera on the main drag near our house and you have to be going 30 miles an hour if you go above it
and of course Patricia was a snapped twice doing 40 you go through this series of unbelievable
postal exchanges before you can finally get to the meat and potatoes so the first thing is they
send you a letter saying was this your car and so of course I've had to do this twice because
there were two tickets like one week a week apart was this your car yes this was my car by the
way my name's not Robin Curry my name's Adam Curry and letterback were you the driver yes I was the
driver they got another letterback so do you wish to fight this or do you want to pay for it can
another letterback is 60 pounds fine okay there you go and then I have to send my license
they say you have to send your license I don't have a UK license I have a Dutch license I
got your mind I'm not going to send my license through the mail so I basically sent them 260
pound checks and a copy a color copy of my license but I don't understand why they make it so hard
for me to just pay the fine and move on with my life please Brits can't you help a brother out
understand then how it works can't you
Earthling got some bad press when they announced that they were installing a free
Munny Wi-Fi access in New Orleans do you hear about this or eat it in the news and people started
blogging and saying great now they have free internet but no food or shelter you know as if that
was somehow Earthlings fault okay now if I'm a large company looking to do something to help people
in need okay and I know how to do a thing internet service for example don't you think that's what
I'd bring to the table and offer up hmm maybe why would Earthling offer to rebuild houses are
provide food when they have no expertise in those fields right I for one think it's great that
they're doing something down there but you know who fought them the telcos the cable companies of
course thinking about a new internet provider give her a linkage ride at least they're trying to help
and not get in the way of progress everybody for a great deal on a domain name for an entire year
for six dollars and ninety five cents check out godaddy dot com use check out code dsc three
for this fantastic offer and make it a domain name about me something we can link something messed
up to would you please huh huh you're honored I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother
out you're honored please don't bang that gavel you can try this cowbell out let's all give a
night to the hardest work and lawyers jersey time oh yeah you're honored what do you say
yeah what's up AC it's jersey time the official music artist of the chacha so listen I've
kind of set you up a little bit this week I started off with a little dannable hit you with that
then I hit you with a little a little brown but now now we're we're going to close off the week with
something just absolutely fantastic it's another one of these american idol guys yeah it's Patrick Hall
and I love this song it's got when he's got one of the best voices I've heard in a long time
check this out this is one for the ages by Patrick Hall great great stuff on the daily source code
for a football friday man you got to love it check you next week everybody
we're team off and see I don't know so I'm a good girl we didn't ever think it's
all the same but so they say no the mayor of the sun will shine tomorrow
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh
oh
Oh, no!
Alright.
Jersey Todd, I hear by night you.
Oh, man, that's good.
Who Patrick Hall won for the ages,
brand new on the Podsave Music Network just went up yesterday,
he's from California.
I received from Arkansas and that kicked ass.
I love the classical bit in the middle.
It was fantastic.
I'm telling you that today.
It's Friday.
Monday Tuesday Wednesday Thursday Thursday Thursday.
Friday at a spinal thundering.
Yeah.
Well, I guess the final thought of the week.
I'll put my hand in my own bosom here for a moment.
Yeah, we complain about us rich people,
complain about a lot of things.
And by the way, if you're listening to this show,
you're rich.
Okay, compared to other people in the rest of the world,
you are stinking rich.
You're listening to this thing.
You got a computer.
You got some kind of portable player, something going on there.
Even people in a rock are rich compared to other people in the world.
I'm talking about Africa.
And so the next time you find yourself complaining,
bitching, moaning about rich people like Madonna,
adopting Malawi and children.
Please think about what's really going on in countries like that.
Countries like Somalia.
Countries like Darfur.
Think about the famine, the hunger, the peril that people are in.
And do something about that.
Complain about that, will you please?
Stop complaining about things that are just less important.
And I think a human life stands above all,
particularly on the mass scale.
And we're not seeing it.
Those of you, citizen journalists,
who claim to be citizen journalists,
please find something really important to talk about.
Talk about people dying on mass scale.
Go out and cover that.
Would you please?
A podcast, Paul, of course, excluded from this rat
because he's actually doing something about it.
And I'd have to say that would be it.
Sorry, I've been a little bit out of sorts today.
Ah, there you have it.
I'm ready for the weekend.
How about you?
Don't forget to send in those voice mail comments
plus one, two, one, sixty, five, six, three, five, seven.
Adam at podshow.com.
And of course, daily source code.com
for all the links that you need for today's program
in the show notes.
Have a great weekend, everybody.
I will talk to you on Monday.
Bye now.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.