This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
The show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy!
Delta Sierra Charley, $407.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Transmidders?
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky ingredients, you know?
I like to think I'm flying into this genre.
Fantastic!
Isn't that a curry?
Hey Adam, these days can go and look their line and I just want to bake.
Woo! Woo! Woo!
That's all I got.
For the ever-worked day.
Another day, another show to do.
Another home-to-roofed trash.
Another fist-by-fits-and-guys from the crowd sound.
They're back to the museum.
A quick group is sex.
And they all sound like fun.
But I'm fighting on back there, tears.
Please say me from this rock and roll-off style.
Yeah, rock and roll-off style.
Everybody off the bottom to the sun comes up.
Step on me, I'll go home and jubbs.
Pretty girls tell me why the genius I am.
But they don't even know me.
They only want to blow me out, I let them.
But it's just to be perfect.
Please say me from this rock and roll-off style.
Yeah, rock and roll-off style.
You average people however you live.
I wish I had a mortgage kids ever-wive.
I wish I would from another farm on my pay.
And get some more and just work it too.
Why won't you do?
You kids are an African, don't eat enough.
You don't realize that I'm the one to get it tough.
I'm sure you're dying from famine and disease.
But it's just to be perfect.
I wish I would from another farm on my pay.
Please say me from this rock and roll-off style.
Yeah, rock and roll-off style.
I wish I would from another farm on my pay.
Please say me from this rock and roll-off style.
Yeah, rock and roll-off style.
Yeah, the modern day of the rock and roll-off style.
I need to...
Okay.
Hey, it's...
Where those guys?
They're from Australia, down under.
Man bites God.
Thank you so much Brian from the procrastic cast.
We're turning me on to that.
You can find them at the Podsate Music Network.
Hey, everybody.
How you doing?
Welcome to the Daily Source Code.
You can tell by the crackling of the microphone
that you're receiving the correct podcast.
Another beautiful day in San Francisco.
It's early on Tuesday morning.
And I can see all the way to the hills in front of me
and to the left I can see...
I can even see the other...
Can I see Oakland?
Yeah, I think so.
I can see all across the bay.
It's beautiful.
And it's going to be warm already.
The temperatures cranking up.
I miss my girls.
I want to go.
Yeah, I miss Christina.
Of course.
I don't know if she misses me as much.
You know, 15, 16 year olds.
They got their own thing going on.
I really miss Patricia.
And I'm not just...
Because I miss her.
I miss her on the show, man.
Dang.
You guys got to be a listener by now.
And the time zone stuff is just no way.
It doesn't work out.
We can't...
We can't coordinate it so that we can actually do a show together.
And it probably wouldn't be the same if we can't look at each other while we're talking.
And the delay of Skype or I chat or whatever.
And it had some weird stuff going on.
Oh, you'll love this.
I had...
Well, you know, I have the Toshiba.
You know, I'm still on...
I'm still on Windows.
Although I did take my power book to be a service yesterday.
So hopefully that'll get fixed very soon.
Well, what's flashing at me here?
Google Calendar.
Why are you flashing?
I don't know.
It's incorrect.
It's still set on UK time.
Okay.
So I have the Toshiba.
And I have a great monitor on my desk at the office here in San Francisco.
Pot show HQ.
And so I love...
Hooking it up.
You know, I...
Having an external monitor is fantastic for the extended desktop.
That's really what I love.
You know, so you just move them out to the left and it keeps on going.
And this is something Max do as well.
I know.
But here's something a little...
Some interesting little quirk.
Yesterday, I was showing Ron some stuff.
And doing that on Cas Blaster, showing how...
Because, you know, he...
I think he had a...
He just switched to a new computer.
So he has to reinstall everything.
And Cas Blaster now has this functionality.
Where after you're done recording the show,
you basically just say,
You had to take it away.
And then it uploads everything to the podcast,
delivery networks.
So no more, you know,
saving out FTPing passwords.
You know, everything is all done at one go.
It's just really nice.
One button is done.
But I showed that to him on the secondary monitor.
And then when I fired up Cas Blaster this morning,
I'm like,
I can't see it.
Where's Cas Blaster?
And it was in virtual space.
In the most programs when you set the...
When you set the computer back to...
To singular monitor, it kind of knows.
But Cas Blaster is super dude.
It was hijed up way in space.
And I had to figure out,
I had to set it back to extended desktop.
I know if you've ever gone through this.
This is really funny.
Because I don't have a monitor here.
Otherwise, it would have hooked it up.
And I would have dragged it right over to the laptop monitor.
So I had to start class Blaster,
move the mouse to the left,
into invisible space.
And then just click until I finally hit...
I hit the metro sexual moment,
which I know is F5.
It's the top of the middle row.
So then I just estimated moving up.
And I was able to grab the toolboard.
And drag it back.
It was quite an operation I tell you.
I was like, oh man, don't do it.
Go to the office and hook this thing up to a monitor.
Anyway.
Another thing I miss.
Be real honest with you.
It's the Senseo.
Now, I try not to drink any coffee while I'm here at the condo.
At the office, I drink tons of it.
But I figure it's also kind of good for my system.
Just to be drinkin' tea or something else.
I try to...
You know, mash it up a little bit.
And I saw a comment from...
Who is this from?
How come that's unsigned?
It was funny because it was...
Oh, here it is.
Chris from ChrisGaredMedia.com.
After being compelled to buy myself a Senseo after hearing you talk about it so much,
I've been experimenting a lot recently trying to expand the options.
Now check this out Senseo lovers.
My favorite at the moment is melting white chocolate and mixing it with some freshly
brewed, resulting in a nice white chocolate mocha.
Something else I'd like to do is brew up some senseo.
Let it chill.
Use the blender to mix it with a lot of ice, cocoa and cream.
Which gives you a nice mocha frape.
Just a little something you might want to try.
Seems it's only like four different options for the pods.
Actually, there's a whole bunch of different pods.
And you can get tea pods and pods to make yourself.
And it's just a wonderful, wonderful.
Oh, gosh.
I don't know.
I do miss it.
Oh, I love us.
I don't know if you've been following Roger smalls on his on his web log.
But Roger has gone from my one time stalker.
And I say that would love Roger to...
to, uh, he's a multimedia powerhouse. Uh, so we, I played you a bit, and I didn't play the
bit, but I told you that he, uh, is doing little segments for the BBC. BBC's one click, I think.
And, uh, if I'm not mistaken, Nokia gave him a new phone. Nokia gave him a new phone,
to do all his podcasting with. Hello, I didn't wrote your hair, just because of the
question for your message. So, moment, um, we're feeling very tired at the moment, and I'm just
wondering if it is normal or not. So, I'm going to work every day, uh, coming back, uh, downloading
some podcasting your house, uh, maybe having a meow, listening to your show, have a little
fiddle, uh, but then after that, I feel just like falling asleep, and I was wondering, is this, uh, normal,
I've been unsure if it's the weather or not, but I'm feeling very sleepy and very tired, uh, and
I'm not really getting anything done in anything, then anymore. I probably wasted about two
hours in the evening, uh, asleep on the sofa, and now you mention you got the same sort of problem,
but that's probably due to old age and drugs, uh, I've been matching you, running around the house,
not wearing very much, uh, be like a blonde dog, he was born, shaking away, shouting, uh,
Christina, and then falling asleep on the sofa. So, thank you to your listeners, I've got any
tips about staying awake, maybe in Cogesci, uh, he's quite old, uh, advice is both on half to stay awake,
and that'll be nice. Anyway, that's all I have to say, so bye for now.
Uh, you got, you had to be careful what you call Uncle Jessie there, although of course,
he is the satellite repairman, and he can fix anything, and he, well, you know what, the song says
all, does it? Hopefully he'll be able to help you out there, Roger, with your sleep
deprivation issues with satellite repairman coming after he, well, satellite repairman,
what's he gonna do, he'll fit your misconceptions and answer questions to,
earn nothing in the universe, and he can't be for you, satellite repairman, well,
satellite repairman, here you go, thank you very much, Roger.
Good to hear you again, my friend, and the quality of your phone just sounds fantastic.
For those of you who are brand new to the daily source code, and seems that we're getting more
listeners every single day. I have a Mercedes station wagon, it's a 300 turbo diesel
from the year 1984, it is Eggnog Yellow, currently in the shop because she dropped her
training on a 45 degree incline, but worth the, oh, by the way, it's not 1800 bucks, turns out they
did the bait and switch on me, it's like $3,200, but well worth it, she's being repaired, hopefully,
today or tomorrow will be getting her back up. This is the segment we talk about, the most important
thing, she runs on biodiesel, vegetable oil, kind of, and uh, well, I love her very much,
anyway, so we have this little segment called the Trinity bit, where people send in cool information
about alternative fuels and, and about biodiesel in particular, and of course, anything else that
to kind of fits, I got an email here from, uh, was this problem was really nice,
from Chris, and that wasn't an email, was that it wasn't an email from Chris fame,
finger who heard me crying about Trinity on a daily source code episode 405 and found a whole
bunch of spare parts on eBay, really appreciated. Somehow I get a very, very clouded view of the
ordering parts off of eBay, and then perhaps even implementing those myself in the Trinity,
something I missed though, which I should have played for you on Friday, was really exciting for,
well, not necessarily the biodiesel world, but for the diesel world in general, and I'm telling
you these diesel engines, you're going to see a lot more people drive in deals, because it's going
to be cheaper, and because you can throw biodiesel in there, and when you throw biodiesel in,
it's much cleaner, smells, much nicer, and you can even make this stuff at home. So I want to play
this piece of feedback that fits right here in Trinity, which I should have done on Friday,
but it's very exciting news, check this out. Adam, hi, my name is Chris. I don't have a podcast to
promote for you right now, but I do know of an event that you may find interesting, knowing that
you and some of your listeners are interested in cars and diesel. This weekend is the 24-hour of
Luma endurance race. Now this race is perceived as the most prestigious endurance race of all
motorsport, and particularly of interest this year is Audi. They are fielding two cars that will be
diesel powered, and earlier this year I saw these cars in Seabring, Florida, one of the cars
won that race and became the first diesel powered car to win in international competition. These cars
are amazing, they're incredibly fast, and if they don't break down like other diesel powered
models, if they don't break down, I'm sure they're going to be right at the front of the field.
So in between matches of the World Cup, I recommend looking through your local programs and seeing
if you have coverage. I know in the States the Speed TV channel will be starting coverage at 10 a.m.
on Saturday, Eastern Time, and we'll have coverage going on throughout the day, and yeah, give it a try.
Dude, I really appreciate you sending me that, of course, over the weekend, I was doing anything
but looking at the 24-hour of Lumaan, and I hadn't actually heard your comment until the
this morning in bed while I was prepping for the show, but guess what? The car actually won.
A diesel car won Lumaan, the 24-hour endurance race of Lumaan.
Now I wonder what was the fuel mixture? And those of you out there who know all about it,
could we actually pull the same thing off using biodiesel, would it make a difference? Apparently
the vegetable oil does a lot better in your engine is better for your engine. Could it happen?
Let me know. And we'll talk about it in a future episode of Trinity.
Got voicemail numbers for you to call if you have any feedback while you're driving around or
walk in the dog or whatever you're doing. Just put it in your phone right now. You don't have
to call immediately, put it in the phone. So if you're on a mobile, you want to do the plus.
A lot of people still don't know that, by the way, that on mobile phones, if you travel
outside of the US, or if you travel outside of the country of your choice, you know, we have to
die so in the US you have to dial 011 and then the country code and then the area code and then the
number. If you put a plus in and then the country code, so in the US it would be plus 1 and then you
put in 206256357. No matter where you are, you'll never have to dial the access code again.
And you'll get through to the voicemail box. It's a standard greeting, so it's not like,
hey, it's Adam, leave a message. Could I still haven't figured out how to do that on the
was it J fax, J2 or something like that that I'm using? Excuse me. Oh, senseio. And this senseio
moment brought to you by Geek Brief TV. Kelly Lewis, looking real good. Where was I?
Yeah, that was I saying. I'll get about it. Oh, yes, the London number. That's it.
In London. So you can choose whichever number you want to call. It's the same voice mailbox.
O2O. 760 actually. So it would be plus 4407076813753. Hey, Adam, this is Troy from Rutgers Ramlings.
I just had a question. I actually listened to the Charlie at work, but download it via iTunes on
well, my home computer. And I was wondering if I go back through those shows when you were doing
the golden tickets and find one or two or however many are there are still redeemable. I know
that's wishful thinking, but I was just wondering that because I'm going back through
all the old podcasts and trying to listen to them on the computer. So just wondering if those
were still valid or if they expire or what to deal. Thanks, Adam. Bye. Okay, so a little talk about
the golden tickets and I think you're going to see us doing some more golden tickets very soon with
wonderful cash prizes. The way it works is the ticket is actually inserted when you download the
podcast. So if you were to do it today and you were to download even in an old episode,
you would not get a golden ticket because they've all been issued. However, if you use iTunes,
as you said, and the show has already been downloaded, then you have just as much chances
anyone else. And of course, of course, those tickets are redeemable. You probably subscribe to the
DevCast. It's a DevCast, DEV, Delta Echo, Victor, Charlie, Elvis, Sierra, Tango, dot pod show.com.
That's where I geek out with the boys and girls from the office, talk about actually we got a
developer we had on the show. Andrew and I talked to a DevCast number six. So we handed out I think
two with 300, several hundred golden tickets. We actually talked about it on the most recent episode.
So yeah, if you downloaded it, when the show was released and we said an X number of tickets
and after the all the tickets are issued, every download after that, of course, doesn't contain
a golden ticket. Now we're going to have so much fun with this when everything releases pod show
plus and which is coming soon and to prove it, to prove this my friends, how quick this is coming.
I have made a solemn vow to myself. And the vow was to you as well because you are the listeners
and we're building this for you. Yeah, there's the podcast, the LiBri Network, of course,
which is really what we started out with, but pod show plus when you see how we've put the
my collection together, the channel guide, I know you're going to love it. All the feedback has been
really, really positive. I'm going to keep my facial hair, let it grow until we actually release.
So we can track the progress of how long it takes. Now, actually, I have not shaved in
when did I stop shaving Thursday? Yeah, Thursday. So I'm getting pretty ragged and I guess what
I'll do is I'll, I guess I'll have to take some pictures so you can stay current with the, with the, with the
timeline. You know, I have gray hair on my pierce. It's disgusting. Hey, Adam, greetings from Sunny Florida.
This is Chuck Palm from the website cleverly named the same at Chuck Palm.com. And I got a bone to pick
with you. Last week on the Charlie episode 403, you stole my show, man. You see, I've only just
started podcasting and I teamed up with this commercial studio so we can produce some shows
for clients at ESPpodcasting.com, shameless plug. But now I got a serious credibility problem.
You see, on Chuck Palm.com, my personal audio blog, I had my second show ever, and I spoke about
school full leaving Microsoft and the German Chancellor's new podcast, the Iranians that lost
to Mexico in the World Cup. And then I do this like little tribute to you, the podfather, man.
I did that and the only problem was it was the exact same topics of your show that day.
So now what am I going to do? No one's going to believe me that I posted my show like 8 hours
before you did and you basically stole my content. Seriously, though, man, I was actually kind of
honored that you chose some of the same topics that I did for your show on the same day.
It was cool to hear you talk about it even if it was 8 hours after I posted my content on the
East Coast. Oh, and the thing about the Welsh accent, you did it so well that I couldn't
understand you the first times you did the bit about being the only gay in the village. I've
been to London and we don't get your version of Big Brother here, but I thought you were saying
the only get in the village. Personally, I think that was funny here anyway. But much respect to you,
man. I was old enough to remember you on MTV and you still need a haircut. You need to wash your hands.
Thank you. Keep the Charlie Crank and man. Happy father's day to you.
I buddy, appreciate it. Yeah, like the two and two. That's kind of cool.
Is that pod safe? I'd like to hear the whole song, actually. Don't worry about it, man.
You're not ripping anything off. I don't think. It doesn't, I don't matter.
It's cool. Brilliant minds think alike. Let's just leave it at that show.
What are we doing on time? We can, we have time for this one.
Check this out. Hey Adam. I was just listening to Charlie 403. This is actually the second time
I've spoken with you. I called you a long time ago when you worked for that one TV network
that used to play a lot of music videos. But now all it plays is like reality shows
of kids cranking their high school. Yeah. And you two should wash your hands, my friend.
I think you know what's network I'm talking about. You were thinking video requests.
And I talked about this yesterday. That was dial MTV, the predecessor to total TRL,
total request live. And the original Carson daily. And I requested the song cold blood.
I can't. And I don't know if you remember that. But yeah, I didn't play it. Of course not.
This is so funny. Of course not because it was all programmed. See, you actually think that you had
some influence over that show. No way, dude. It was always the same. The only thing that would
change once and a while would be the number one or number two video, which is probably the
same way it is with TRL these days. We didn't actually take your request into regard. It was just
using it as content. You know? So I felt silly for requesting it. And number two,
I videotaped it. So I actually have a videotaped of you talking to me with it says my name at
the bottom of the screen. So I wonder if you remember that kick skull blood. I do remember. No, I do.
My brush with fame. Because we never play. I want to tell you, I heard of your show on Dom3. So
thanks to them. And I wanted to tell you that a wife eater to be a proper wife eater needs to
have a goody can and your stains on it. But this is the sleeveless T-shirt that I call wife
eater, which some people take incredible offense to. You're right. If it, I don't have spaghetti stains,
but I got like T and I got burn holes does that count. Anyway, I wanted to tell you that
with your current windows, mac and touch problems. I think that you should stick with the PC hardware,
but try not to try it. Just try it. It's Linux. Not big five point 0.1 just came out. And I think
you'll find that the seal is much more of what you're looking for than that cheap windows ceiling.
But try it out. Keep doing what you're doing. I love you. I love you, show.
I love you too. Just wanted to say, what is all this Welsh shape? Do you want to get into
the village? Is obviously to make and not? I'm definitely right. I am the only gain of
it as you see. It's from Little Britain, not from Big Brother, by the way, for the previous caller.
Yeah, not big. So let me talk about that in a second. First of all, our friends listening to us
on serious stars 102. We got some great stuff coming up for you today in our four hour lineup.
We've got the two for Tuesday. P-dub sets up new up, which means our last two shows between
nine and ten this evening will be the squad cast and no idle threats to fantastic podcasts.
Both members of the Podshow podcast network. We're shaken up a bit on this series.
So you'll be hearing new sounds as we move forward. And I'll be back tomorrow for the Wednesday
edition of the Charlie right here on stars 102. Thanks for listening everybody.
Now, about that caller who was talking about topics, I think I spend at least 10 minutes trying
to find topics. Turns out you spell it with a K. K-N-O-P-P-I-X. Very interesting. There's this new
of course, at this point, if I can switch to Windows that easily, I should be able to switch
to almost any operating system and be completely happy. Part for the fact that cast blaster won't
run under Linux, which becomes a huge problem for me. So there's no switch imminent there.
But very interesting topics. This is new. I guess it's live Linux live or something, which means
you can basically load the whole operating system on one CD or excuse me. Oh man, a double shot
of Sensei, a moment brought to you by Donna Drew. And done them yet.
So you can load it onto a USB memory stick. You know, basically take your operating system with you
and it'll load on any machine. Of course, except for any machine like the Shiba Portage
which happens to use a USB connected CD drive. That seems impossible. I like the screen shots,
though, those look pretty cool. And I'm not afraid of trying to try not new stuff. And I'm still
vibing on it. It's okay. It totally is. You know, I think I'm going to get a new PC though because
this one is missing a few bits. It doesn't have the mobile yet. It has the Pentium M. So it's
the mobile processor, which is a little bit weaker. And so Ron recently got a new Sony Vio.
I think I'm going to try out one of those. We're just bumping around trying some stuff out.
You'll be along for the ride as we test more stuff. Give you my experiences.
And I also along with the letting the beard grow, I vow to give you some screenshots of my
desktop. See how I've configured it to kind of give me the best of both worlds. It's almost
like a like a transsexual sound. I've got here. Hey, soccer. Let's talk about that, huh?
Hi Adam. This is Franco, or Castitalia, or Italian minister of podcasting. Yes, not just that, but
my Italian friend. I know I'm a little late for this, but I heard some of the comments of
your listeners about the match between our countries at the soccer world championships. I really don't
think that USA team got spanked so badly. It was a very rough game. It was balanced. Every team had
their opportunities, but at the end, I think the result is fair. So I hope our countries will
meet again along the tournament, maybe in the finals, huh? And it was really a honor playing with
you guys. No. Ciao de l'Italia. Pronto, ciao ciao. It was actually it was totally our pleasure.
And it was, you know, I kind of forgot to mention that, but I have to say that I really enjoyed
both sides. Everyone played a kick-ass game. And what I found kind of interesting is
not the Italian guys. You know, they're all good looking. But we got a lot of US players who
were pretty good. In fact, they look like they could have been on the Italian team. And I do hope
that we meet in the finals. You never know. I think this is a great year for soccer, for football.
Like, what should we have to call it soccer? I guess we have to. I'm just going to keep saying
football. You'll know what I mean. Unless it's the Super Bowl. Because that's the only time
to talk about American football, probably. It'd be great if we would meet up in the finals. I think
well, I'm still, all my teams are still up in the air. England, of course,
will be going on to the next round. US, I guess, they have to be to Ghana. Is it
there to be Ghana? And the Netherlands, of course, still in the game. So I've got three teams
that I'm rooting for. And my boys are keeping me up to speed with what's going on with the rest
of the world cup this week. Hey, Adam, this is Phil. It's Tony. And we are the soccer show
podcast available at soccershout.com. Just a quick wrap up of the end of the second round of group
games. Who was looking good so far? Tony, I reckon our container in Holland are in the
Paul positions in terms of performances so far. Yeah, you can't really look past ours in
Tina's performance in the second round. Six goals. No one else has come close to that.
And Holland is doing really well. They're scrapping out results a bit more, but looking
classy in the process. I think Spain and Portugal to a lesser extent are also
equating themselves quite nicely. I think in the in the part of not playing very well,
but I should get in the results. I will put in their Brazil, England and Germany.
Yeah, Brazil being a bit disappointed so far for me. Yeah, and I noticed that Argentina
actually joined favoring out for the world cup along with Brazil. So Argentina moved up a bit
in Brazil of slipback in the odds. And then we have Italy and France who I think are doing
pretty badly. They did nothing other. Nothing. And just a touch on the USA game. I'm with you on this
one out of. I thought they did phenomenally well on Saturday. I thought they put in a great performance.
And I think the biggest shame is that they would have won the game if they had managed to keep
11 men on the pitch. I reckon they were in a shot if they kept 10. Yeah. So let's look ahead
with a little bit. Tuesday through Friday there's actually four games a day. The times have
changed slightly so you have to look at the website and try and figure out where all the teams
are. But just to avoid collusion between the teams, they play the last games in the group at the
same time. So there's only two time slots and there's two games in each time slot. That's
Tuesday through Friday. And then from Saturday onwards we start with single elimination. The games
if they're tied at the end of regulation, they get extra time and then they get penalties to determine
a winner. And we do that until we get to the final and an ultimate winner. That will wrap it up for
a quick update. Once again, soccer show.com. Thanks Adam. Bye bye.
No dudes. I totally appreciate it since I know nothing about sports. But I am turned on by this whole
world cup thing. I find it exciting. I like the length of the games. You know, it's 90 minutes
and total. And it's good. It's all good. Totally digging it. Thank you.
Hey, this is Scott and Telly. We're actually normal teenagers. Unlike the few people we're
talking about gadgets and crap. So come check us out. And Scott and Telly.com. We have plenty of stories
to share. Trust me on that one. Okay. Certainly we'll trust you on that one.
Here we go. I was looking for this. The submissions are flying in fast and furious for the
Podjo Earthlink ad challenge. Make advertising better. You hear it all over the network. People
are talking about it. Lots of interesting, interesting versions of what people feel are important
to tell about Earthlink. Because you're really making it up. You're making up the advertising.
For me, it's all just content. I love it. It fills up the show. Fantastic. And it's entertaining.
Go to ad challenge.potshow.com. You can enter. Anyway, you like. You can make an endorsement. You
can make a spot, a jingle, a song. And it just be creative. And keep it under six megabytes,
which should be more than enough. And you stand a chance at winning as a $2,000. Here's today's
interview that I really like. Connecting. Sorry. Not connected. Want an ISP that helps people
instead of spying on them. Try Earthlink. They're providing free internet access to hurricane victims.
Thank you, or provider would do that. Earthlink. Plug in. Turn on. Stay connected. See,
now that's a reason for me to switch right there. Do you want an ISP that spies on you or
do you want one that helps people in need? I think that's real easy. Don't you? One more from the
voice mail lines that will play a final song for today. Hey, Adam. This is Alan from Houston.
Swarp. Pass on a Yanks versus the Britswoman. I got into the other day. Actually, yesterday,
I called my colleagues over in Europe over in London, actually. Actually, Henley. Henley.
Henley on terms? Anyway, I was talking to them. Talk to us guy. And there was some girl bugging
him into background. And I asked him whether or not she had been hanging out with a bikey
as we can. Oh, man. Oh, no. That's not good. You know, we've used this word before when
Patricia and I were on the show and Christina's used it. You got to be very careful. We were saying
this too. People do not appreciate this. Um, I'm a bash Italy relayed that message to her.
Almost, I actually, if that then I'm actually hurt. I'm very sharp and taken breath. Oh,
you mean that like one of these? A little bit of quiet as he was chuckling. And then she just kind
of laid it to me. Oh, but it was pretty bad there for a few minutes. And then I managed to
use it by asking her what was a piky? Um, explained to her that I heard it on Christina's show.
And just kind of threw it out there trying to be cheeky with my friend. I didn't exactly
imagine he would start an international incident over. But there you go. Thanks. Bye. Oh,
by the way. Yeah. What is a piky? Okay. So let's open that up. All right. I'm sure our friends in the
UK would be more than happy to help us out. Understanding what a piky is. When I see
one on the street, I can usually recognize one. My daughter certainly can. It's just one more episode.
One more chapter in that big book of two countries divided by a common language.
The yanks versus the bits. Mind the gap. Oh, yeah. One last song is promised Jersey Todd found this
for me. You're going to love this. Daisy caught a feature in the cool key. You might want to crank this
one up. I'm going to make you feel good. Cool Keith. I'm the positive music network. Who would have
fallen kid? You're now good. You're the cooliest. That's the name of a came in the game.
It's not just that it's the chain. It's the same in the team. It's black, black, the race.
Cool. That's me, quite the cat cat to say. Who's the brain? That is the web, that the
thing. You don't want it, but I bet it'll catch the game. I'm the monochin, I'm honestly
bad back again. There's a little bit of riddle and tap tap your vein. It's the six. I'm
maintain it where to gain it better. It's a pain pain. It grinded again. It was said that we
stumbled out of the brutalist man's rights. We're not a combatant. We're doing it again. We're the
men's feet checking the SP. Call Mr. Kurt, you'll know the jet ski. Have you on the
odds yours? Hold the dress, keep the flows and damn it. You'll keep trying to face this
man. You're in a rock and pop and not twist the flexi sexy. Let pick up the phone connect
me. Pick up the taxi. Black and the ball. It's time to step back.
What a beta. I'm great. I'm percolated. The rate I get ready to burn. And the eagle beta.
Get ready to turn. I'm a simulator. The crowd will focus. The down move over. Each
you tell pipes like chocolate mocha. The verb will hurt. The first things that hurt
you. Reality virtue. Maybe so deep, repeat, repeat, repeat. Like breaking and
beat strength. They solve their crease, reap the cannibal cactus practice. Exactly back
this. We enforce and perform the moon. The mouth relaxes. I give you the access to
the waist like endless. They're gonna adjust that bus. A plus, they adjust the combat
a bus. The form on normal global warming.
Bring that feedback, man. Bring that feedback, man. Bring that feedback, man.
I'm a simulator. I'm a simulator.
They fade away. They're my lane for discoveries. They get a paper straight away. They're
medicated. They're brothers. Check his bucket. You bring him the aid or nothing. You
fakers with me. They're brought in here. When you feel the day to cover.
And you wake him up and sleep, man.
You wake him up,...
That's what my personal charm is.
There's no Charlie Music Colleges, Jersey Todd from the Jersey Todd Show.
Jersey Todd Show.com, dude, thank you so much for turning me on to this.
Daisy Cutter featuring Cool Keith Cool Keith, that is a big deal as Jersey Todd said
in his email to me, that Cool Keith is on the PMN.
I'll put a link to Cool Keith's Wikipedia entry, and of course everything you read
in Wikipedia is true.
He's been around, been around for a while, extremely cool.
Hey, you know, when I got to get to the office, we got some stuff to do today.
It's a real busy one because Ron's leaving on a, I think it's his fifth wedding anniversary
that's coming up, so he and Marta are leaving for some undisclosed destination tomorrow.
So we got a lot of stuff to go through today, a lot of work, a lot of meetings, a lot
of stuff.
It may or may not be our last day together for this trip.
It kind of depends.
Besides me missing the girls, I also want to go back and see my mom, because I can pretty
much only do that in a weekend, so it's still be another week.
So as I said, it's going to be a busy day, but that's my life.
I want you to have a good one.
Have a great one.
Remember, every single day you wake up and your eyes open, be happy that they actually
open, be very happy they open by cast last week.
So it's dailysourcecode.com.
That's where you can find the latest podcasts in the podcast feed.
Oh, feedback to adamaccurry.com.
Take care, everybody.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye-bye.
Another pod show podcast, stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery
network from pod show and limelight networks.
I love it.