This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 385.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Yeah dude that was hot.
This guitar rocks man.
It's a dream.
Take your dreams to eat.
The age and both.
Love is so I need them.
Look at me there.
Cloud feels overchanging.
Hope is shining in my eyes.
With a whole biggest deal.
Let's go mama.
Give me a little to a less tattoo man.
And with a whole big queen.
And a fair deal.
With a whole one of me.
Love is so I need them.
Don't get me there.
Cloud feels overchanging.
Hope is shining.
Love is so I need them.
Don't get me there.
Cloud feels overchanging.
Hope is shining in my eyes.
I hope is shining in my eyes.
Yeah, happy birthday.
Happy birthday.
On the show, the new year.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, all this young in my heart.
Oh, crikey.
So, for your Amos, Esperanza sent in by multiple requests, actually, from the Pods
Saben music network.
Oh, me like a direct, yeah.
Definitely, oh, man, she's from New York.
And let me see what's in her bio here.
Ah, Sophia Ramos doesn't just kig that words too puny to describe her concert.
She's tough and smart.
A show stopper who toured with a lot of blues up, performing on the main stage.
Fantastic.
Available now on the Pods' tape music network.
And they're the recycled guys again.
Yeah, right on time.
It's Thursday once again.
I start the show.
They come to pick up the bottles and the papers.
As of today, you'll be able to purchase this song.
Of course, we have to get in touch with Sophia and make sure that she's cool with it.
If you're an Australia, they're available as of yesterday.
However, that works a little bit time differences.
Yeah, liking it.
So, we're slowly opening up the Pods' tape music network to just to start off in the next few weeks.
Every artist that is played on the daily source code purchase will be made available.
And of course, then on in, if the artist decides, hey, I want to put up another song
and make that available for sale as well.
No problem. They can do that without any intervention.
It's the unlabeled coming to fruition in front of your very eyes.
Let me see.
Okay.
Why, I'm not going to get in it.
Any big heavy thing now, because the guys are just pulling up.
What is this like some kind of date we have?
And ladies, I should take a picture of this.
So it's these, actually, I got to say these, these garbage guys, these recycled guys are hunky.
And of course, it's beautiful weather here at the cottage.
So sun is shining.
So once again, they have no shirts on.
I can just see all the ladies in the neighborhood peering from behind.
Peering from behind.
The curtains.
All right. Well, that's going on in the background.
Interesting response to a topic that I didn't expect a lot of response on came into the voice mail numbers.
At the first one from the UK.
I don't know how it's for me.
It's a podcast call.
How you doing?
I think it's okay.
Just a quick message, Adam.
It's a soundly that this is probably a pretty podcastly history, because I'm living a message.
I used this the first day of a message ever from course.
I guess it probably is from a Birmingham County court at the moment.
And this is a writing ring.
Of course, I can't actually get in one of the course.
And finally, I did that.
And I'll get arrested and put in some of the concerns.
But, um, they like.
And I wanted to say as well, just a very quick thing.
Um, we're going on to Patricia's earbuds constantly falling out.
It's been a, uh, a source of humor in my podcast over the last few weeks.
My wife says you have earbuds.
And they were constantly dropping out.
And, uh, she's a dry name notes.
It really did.
Uh, I even put something to put in the blog about how to perform there.
I think, um, in the end, I just went from the board to some decent headphones.
And, uh, can I suggest you do that?
I actually went to, um, test scheduling.
Or has to report some to five quit, which has been to the job.
Anyway, all the best.
Speak the same.
Bye.
So yeah, Paul.
Um, first of all, thank you.
First, uh, calling from court.
Love it.
Are you there, uh, working?
Are you there, uh, being prosecuted is the question.
Yeah.
So these earbuds, they do fall out of Patricia's ears.
She's a hard time like jamming him in there, which is, of course, totally a design
fault on Apple's part.
I wonder how many other people I've problem with the earbuds.
I don't think I'll get away with buying your five dollar test go here.
Headphones, though.
Uh, she's my wife is very particular about sound.
So say, it sounds like crap.
You sound like shit.
I don't sound good.
Yeah.
And so they may not want to do that.
But of course, what was really interesting is that these earbuds,
kept, you know, the right one, or I'll turn to the left one and fall out.
And it would slip right in between their cleavage, which made the whole thing that
much more interesting to watch as it just happened over and over and over again.
And I, I, I mentioned that, uh, or no, I didn't even say that.
I said hi, guys, when, when addressing my wife's breasts and, and boy, that garnered some response.
Hey, Adam, what's going on? Jack, when Nick of the Sick World podcast,
out here in Las Vegas, again.
I am listening to a DSC 384 and, uh,
the guy from a geographic location or whatever the name of that show was,
just called in, talking about Patricia's boobs and how you refer to them as guys.
Well, my girlfriend and I do the same thing.
She actually took a one step further.
She actually gave them names and not only are they names,
but they're male names.
And I, if I remember correctly, uh, one of them is even.
Well, they're dude.
If you remember correctly, your wife named her breasts and you forgot?
Yeah, I hope she's not listening.
Yeah, Hispanic name.
The other one, however, because they're, you know, unlike most women,
one is a little bit smaller than the other.
She calls that one tiny.
What?
Yeah, tiny?
Dude, do not repeat.
Do not let your wife hear this podcast.
Do not.
I know.
I'm thinking the same thing.
Okay, so I'm going to trouble.
Thanks for everything, Anna.
You're so much trouble, man.
You're much trouble.
By the way, Patricia's are perfectly equal, as far as I can tell.
And I've been playing with him for 20 years.
Hey, Adam.
This is, uh, then from Salt Lake.
No.
What page?
Your podcast or anything.
I'm going to crack this plain old banana on me.
I just want to say I love the Bailey source code.
Now, I dig on the Charlie.
Listen to it all the time.
I've been listening for just over a month now.
And absolutely love it.
At first time, I heard the breast stinging referred to in the masculine was in one of my favorite
movies, blazing saddles where Mel Brooks character, the governor, comes over to one of
his assistants and reps of the state.
And her cleavage and says, hello, boys.
Keep up the great work.
Love to show.
Bye.
All right, man.
Thank you very much.
Anyone else who has anything to say about this show?
Mel lines open.
In New Jersey, 201, 625, 635, 7.
Love that number, by the way.
Just flows.
The UK numbers little less flowy.
In London, 020, 7681, 3753.
And we are working on multiple.
Actually, I got a little email exchange with cast blaster.
My, of course, it'll cast blaster.
It's perfect for recording audio comments in combination with the podcast delivery network
because it can upstream them automatically.
I still think we would need an interface change.
I think what people really want to see is, is a record button and a send to podcast.
You know, it's like record your comment, send it off.
Or maybe a review.
So you can listen to it, of course.
And then send off.
And Mike's worry.
And I think he's right.
He says, you know, I hope people don't think that with this pod show plus thing that you'll
be able to actually record comments, you know, like without a microphone.
Hello, Adam, and all the daily source code listeners.
This is Shme from the podcast.
And I am, uh, hold on.
I'm thrilled, exhilarated, animated, and raptured, adrenalineized, and extremely excited
to be the newest member of the pod show family.
Whoo!
That's right.
My wildest dreams are finally coming true.
If you'd like to come check out my podcast,
it's sort of like a cross between an audio blog and a variety show.
You tell stories, jokes.
You talk about stuff that I'm into, like music, theater, and any fails that enters my head.
I'll replay some awesome, positive music.
So come check it out at thenotcast.com.
And before I leave, a huge thank you to Richard, Adam, and everyone at pod show.
You guys are one second.
You're magnificent, impressing, awe-inspiring, majestic, sumptuous, and resplendent.
Once again, the website is thenotcast.com.
And remember, thenotcast is so worrying, you'll not off.
Hey, hey, who wrote this?
That's a kind of promo, I like.
We signed another boring show.
Fantastic.
You'll not write off.
Welcome Shme.
Very happy to have you aboard.
Um, and we got a couple more new additions coming up in the next few weeks here on, uh,
the podcast.
And that worked the pod show podcast network, so you'll be here more of these cool promos.
Also a new pod final.
Hi, Adam, this is Paula.
And this is Alana, and we're a mom writer, talk radio.
Who knew that we would be a part of the seed biggest highest quality pod network on the web?
It's pod show.
This is just so exciting.
I know.
Maybe we should tell them a little about the show.
You think?
I mean, the name, mom writer, talk radio, does kind of tell what we do.
Don't you think?
Well, yeah.
But we want the people out there to know that we aren't just mom to talk about their writing,
though we both could, since we are both publishers.
I guess you're right.
So we should probably mention our interviews with published mom authors, like,
Declaration of Charge.
Yeah, we probably should.
We should also mention that we discussed what it takes to be a writing mom.
Sort of like, mom writer and Hollywood actress Brenda Straff.
Yeah, you're probably right.
But should we mention what we do with the kids while we record the show?
Now that, we probably shouldn't mention it.
Yeah!
Check out mom writers, talk radio every week for interviews with awesome mom authors, such as Jacking
Charge, and writing discussion, and much, much more.
This claimer.
No kids were harmed during the recording of this trauma.
Except when my daughter threw a card or brother.
But she wouldn't have done that anyway.
All right, ladies.
Thank you.
And welcome.
Mom writers.
Yeah.
You know, that seems like it could be a very complex job to be a mom writer.
Be at home, have the kids thrown crap at each other and trying to write,
ooh, definitely only doing it in nap times and when they're nursery school, I presume.
So that brings me to an update about my mom.
Yesterday, we were awaiting the results of another scan that she did.
And unfortunately, the news is not good.
She has cancer in her lung, which is a real bummer if you only have one left because the previous one
was removed due to cancer.
There's also also spread a bit onto her ribs.
So, even though this news was a shock to all of us.
It, we were prepared, I think.
Certainly, my mom was ready.
You know, she's every single time she's been back to the hospital for something.
After everything was cleared up, then there was another bit of bad news.
So it's interesting time, very interesting time for us as a family.
My sister has flown in from Italy this morning.
She's going to be there through Sunday.
My other sister, of course, lives in the Netherlands.
And we're going to go out and have some fun.
My mom has a little shack where she used to go regularly on weekends.
And so we've reopened that.
So we'll go hang out.
It'll be the kids and mom and Bob.
And I'm sure that's going to be, you know, fun at the same time.
You know, it's like there's really only one topic of conversation.
And either we're talking about it or we're not talking about it and thinking about it.
Or joking about it, which works too.
And it would be a hell of a lot easier for everyone, particularly my mom.
If she didn't have, you know, if she wasn't in pain, that's the equality of life is what it just sucks.
So there's lots of things to think about and decisions to make and directions to go.
And as the doctors have said, you know, there's no reason to give up hope.
And that, of course, is I'm not one to do that ever.
So whatever, you know, direction my mom wants to go in, we'll go.
You know, whatever doctors she wants to see.
If it's all, if I got to get some witch doctor from the deepest jungles, we can do that too.
If she just wants to pursue a better quality of life with the, you know, better pain management.
Whatever it is, we'll do.
So it's going to be a funky, funky mother's day.
Very funky mother's day for us.
And you know what, I'll just say, and I appreciate so much all the wonderful thoughts and emails that you guys have been sending me over the past.
What is it now? You're in a half that we've been going through this.
But you don't have to do it every single time.
You know, it's, believe me, it's okay. I really appreciate.
Just think of her, send her positive vibes and thoughts and that'll be cool.
So it's not the totally bum you out.
I thought I'd read out this little story, which, you know, is one of these joke emails that circulated.
It's about having mom over for dinner and I thought it was so funny because this is totally something my mom could have done.
And you're like it, I think.
So Brian invited his mother over for dinner during the course of the meal.
Brian's mother couldn't help but keep noticing how beautiful Brian's roommate Stephanie was.
Brian's mom had been suspicious of a relationship between Brian and Stephanie and this had only made her more curious over the course of the evening.
Well, watching the two interact, she started to wonder if there was more between Brian and Stephanie than met the eye.
Reading his mom's thoughts, Brian volunteered, you know, I know what you must be thinking, but I assure you, Stephanie and I would just roommates.
But a week later, Stephanie came to Brian saying, you know, ever since your mom came over to dinner, I've been unable to find the beautiful silver gravy ladle.
You don't suppose she took it, do you?
Brian said, well, I doubt it, but I'll all send her an email just to be sure.
So he sat down and wrote, dear mom, I'm not saying that you did take the gravy ladle from the house.
I'm not saying you did not take the gravy ladle, but the fact remains that one has been missing ever since you were here for dinner.
Love Brian.
Several days later, Brian received an email back from his mom that read, dear son, I'm not saying that you do sleep with Stephanie.
I'm not saying that you do not sleep with Stephanie, but the fact remains that if Stephanie was sleeping in her own bed, she would have found the gravy ladle.
Bye for now, love mom.
Never try and lie to your mom, I guess that's the, that's what we learned from that one.
Jeff Tinnan, Tinian, excuse me, sent me an email and I, you know, for a second there, I thought you might be right, hello Adam.
I have a theory about Rogers absence of late, we're talking about Roger Smalls, of course.
I actually think he's got himself a girlfriend, and that's why he hasn't been in touch.
I have so many friends who had some point in other have gone quiet after bagging a new squeeze.
Leave it a month, I'm sure he'll be back in touch once the novelty is worn off, all the best from Jeff.
And say, excuse me, I know that's disgusting, but I just needed to do that.
Well Jeff, funny enough, I think that your theory may be true because it has been almost exactly one month since we last heard from him.
I have been Roger here, I'm so sorry to not sending you any recordings for a while, but I was very upset by comic suit blogger's siblings, he too was me in crayon on his website.
Now, I'm not sure why I hate his gun going like him, as the rats call me ugly.
I know I'm not actually buried head for anything when it comes to looks, but let's just talk into some girls that go out drinking and go fed,
and he won't know how in the trash if I am.
Now, I've decided to do the same thing that he does, and demand a public apology from him, because I think as long as he's got a hole at his ass,
he's going to continue to be spite-loom-boots people, which I don't think is any way to get on in life.
It's all I've got to say now at him, I'm not saying another word until he issues neurology.
So, by for now, Roger.
And while he's at it, he can apologize to Russell B.T, he managed wine scene, and everyone else on your comments board too, because he's a nasty piece of work.
By the way, will you stop talking about that blessing computer game?
I'm sure it's heavy-working, sat down and talked about space invaders for half an hour, then he's losing all his audience.
Now, when the people think podcasting is key key, the reason people listen to your show is to hear how much pets your life is compared to theirs,
not to talk about dungeons and dragons and high schools.
So I am so angry, I should go, I just thought someone should help you, goodbye.
Oh, Roger.
You say me, my brother?
Okay, so I do take this seriously.
It sounds like you're angry at comic strip blogger.
Now, I think he actually, I think he's been pretty nice.
He's said that he's given me advice to do things, to help you out, you know, send you money so you could get on second life.
Excuse me, I need to say the virtual world, second life, where I am sometimes to be found at the curry castle.
Anyway, it's good to hear your voice, that's for sure.
Let us know if it was a girlfriend that distracted you, but if it was really just comic strip blogger that made you so mad,
I think we need to sit down and talk.
And you know what, Roger, I would love to get you into the second life virtual world, because I think that you and comic strip blogger,
maybe you guys could meet on neutral ground, you know, meet over at my place, and let's talk this out, okay?
Because I don't like that.
You're the original stalker.
I'm sorry.
It's just what I call it.
It's a term of endearment.
You're the original stalker.
And please, Roger.
Please come back.
Now, what was it, Roger was saying at the very end there?
Hold on a second.
Let me just see what was that he was saying about me.
That's what people want to listen to.
Well, it's funny because I received a comment.
I see it received a comment about me and my success.
Hey, Adam, it's PDF from Love House Radio and interview with a stranger in thedaddycast.com.
And of course, Love House Radio on Second Life.
You know, I think I figured out a couple of keys to your success.
And one is that you like to push the limits on anything.
And it's to learn how to overcome obstacles.
So use Gmail as an example.
There's a four gig limit.
Somehow you've gotten to open it up to more.
So actually, there's a two gig limit.
And I was able to open it up to four for myself.
I'm not supposed to talk about it because I used various back channels to make that happen.
That was, well, also I used this show to make that happen just by begging for it.
And of course, now, you know, I'd love to go back to the trough because I've been deleting stuff every single day for the past.
And I don't know, three months.
You know, so I'm deleting stuff from 2005, which I really hate doing.
I don't know if it was death threats from the pod father or what.
I've been in second life.
No, no, no.
It's just an awesome board of directors is what that is.
I'm down with it two days.
There's a $150 limit until you're 45 days old.
But you partnered with the right people.
You created groups.
You gained more land.
I mean, you've ever came that obstacle.
I have a little surprise in that question why you didn't go the option of buying an island.
I don't know if it's, you know, because potions of building third life or what the thought was.
But I'm thinking you could even use a little relation in it.
You could have the pod show peninsula.
You could have the curry countryside.
You could work all these things plus you'd sell off lots like it was nothing.
I mean, everybody would just kind of follow along with currently residing around the castle.
But anyway, I'm definitely entertaining and impressed with your focus and drive.
And come on down to the love house.
We're only two to go down from the cat.
Oops.
Looks like you got cut off there.
Yeah, you know, first of all, I love seeing PD love in the virtual world second second life.
Because we actually, you know, we particularly early in the morning US time, which is afternoon here on East Coast,
at least, you know, we actually have pretty meaningful conversations.
They're short, but it's like having a quick little ICU chat and we sit around in the circle and we took on the ball.
And if you want to hear more about that and you're listening to this podcast on Syria Stars 102,
you'll have to download the show at dailysourcecode.com tonight.
We should have a new digital flotsom.
If it's the one that I heard just the other day, you're going to love it.
You're going to love it to bits.
Michael Butler will close up the evening with some pod safe tunes.
And up next, we have Mark Yoshimode Nemkoff and the hell coast, the hell way players.
I'm sorry, with the PCH on 102.
And I just wanted to continue on that one thought because that is actually something that is,
I think pretty interesting to talk about from a business case.
You've probably seen this woman, and she chung, or you've heard of her.
She's this girl who has made a small fortune.
I think it's valued like $250,000 on doing just what you mentioned, PD love.
By buying up virtual land and then creating something there,
reason that people will want to be there and buy land from you,
which of course raises the prices.
And if there's any game element to this virtual world,
it is that, it is making money on buying and selling land,
which I'm so completely not interested in.
I just do not give a crap about that.
And also, there you go, PD.
I'm looking ahead because there's some changes coming that are going to drastically change
what this particular virtual world is and what makes it tick.
And that is the use of teleports.
Now, of course, in real life, it would be nice if I could just sit here and say,
you know what?
I'm going to pop over to the Pod Show HQ San Francisco office and just stand in the teleport
like Star Trek and be there.
So unfortunately, that's, well, although experiments are being done,
I don't think they've done it on humans yet.
In second life, the virtual world, my wife makes me say that.
That is possible.
However, the restriction currently has been up to 300 meters within the same
sim, the same simulator, which is basically if you buy an island,
then you have your own simulator.
And so you've never been able to go from, say, from island to island through a teleport.
But when this teleport feature gets included, well, then all of a sudden,
it won't really matter where you are because people can access you from anywhere.
And it'll, I think it's going to matter about the people that are there,
the people that you meet, the experiences that you have.
I was talking to, I was a Jeff Smith, Jeff Smith, Kevin Reeves and...
Crap.
Why am I spacing out on this?
Hold on.
Jeff Smith, Kevin Reeves.
Give me the other Nashville guy, William.
Oh, how can I be so stupid, hold on.
When I, when I figured out, I'm going to go, oh, duh, of course.
Here it is.
Matthew Ebo.
Duh.
Okay.
How could I forget?
Right.
So they're planning, and I'm not, I'm not quite sure what they're doing,
but they're planning on a US Podsafe showcase, and they're going to do a little tour.
And so I thought, well, you know, when we open up this other place that I've been building in the virtual world,
called the Podsho Palace, maybe their first, you know, their first dry run could be doing it in second life.
And I'm talking to some short, you know, each 15 minutes sets or something.
And it would, um, it would get a lot of people acquainted with, uh, with their music.
Uh, you'd meet other people who listen to podcasts, and maybe some maybe we'll have like,
oh, I'd love to have Don and Drew, uh, in our VIP area, do a meet and greet.
It sounds, you know, tin foil hatty and all that, but, uh, you actually will be chatting with Don and Drew,
and you actually will be listening to the live music of Matthew Ebo, Kevin Reeves and Jeff Smith.
And Jeff, I got a killer piano for you, man. I know you're into the crazy piano stuff.
So just a thought, um, and that's the kind of stuff that I believe will, will keep this exciting.
So that's what I'm doing with Brittany.
I have two women in my life. It's fantastic.
Okay.
Speaking of, uh, when am I done here with this, um,
Wait a minute, I'm a little confused. Ah, here we go. This is what I was looking for.
Hey Adam, this is KFC from podcheck.com inviting you to join us at a pagan wedding
in the stones at Stonehenge on our summer solstice coming up June 21st at sunrise.
It's sure to be a fantastic event. I understand Patricia is also a witch.
Um, not real clear on all of the different pagan witch dialects. I don't know how that works,
but our misdemeanor podcheck from 2005 is a witch is getting married at Stonehenge in the stones at sunrise
on the summer solstice. So I will be over there the week of that wedding,
hand fasting, whatever, and was a wondering if I might be able to meet up and see you,
perhaps get a tour of curry cottage or something fascinating like that.
And be, see if you might be interested in attending such an event and being involved.
Sounds like something really neat and fun and exciting.
So I offer that up to you. Please let me know.
All right. My contact information is podcheck.com.
KFC at podcheck.com. Um, so I look forward to hearing back from you.
Right. Hope you're having a fan tabulous day.
Make them smile.
Yes.
You know, if you've never checked out podcheck,
she's a member of the podshow podcast network.
It's some awesome stuff.
Some great videos like naked women parachuting, like really cute naked women parachuting.
I didn't, I didn't see any naked guys parachuting.
Otherwise, I think it would make it even better, or at least entertaining for all sexes.
And I, you know what, I thought that Stonehenge was for the druids and not for witches.
And I say Patricia's a witch, but you know, she's not an official one.
Not with any clan.
Although I, I have suspected her flying the broomstick once in a while.
So she's very in touch with with nature and all that groovy stuff.
And she talks to the animals.
They talk back and she understands it and all that stuff.
Um, so yeah, maybe we'll hook up at Stonehenge.
But I have to say, I don't do tours of the cottage.
I've got to have one place in my life.
Just one.
Despite the occasional paparazzi, just one place where I can be completely safe.
Yeah, I'm longtime listener for Minneapolis.
You know what, before I get to that, just on the marriage thing, Alex Foucombi, Foucomb.
Uh, sent me an email.
He said, uh, according to what I heard on Delta Sierra Charlie 382,
you had a hard time proving that you're married to your wife.
Well, I mean, I have the paperwork.
It's just not officially signed.
And so he's suggest, why don't you get married to her again?
And you could confirm your vows this way.
I guess all you need is a chapel with City Hall or a courthouse.
Well, why don't you get wed in second life?
Dude, go listen to that episode again.
And then tell me you think my wife is actually going to do that.
Time in.
I just heard the earthquake promo again on your show.
And I want to please let you know that I've gone to the earthquake website.
At least twice, possibly even three times to see if earthquake is available in my area.
I'm in the market for looking for DSL, table service.
And with the problems I've had with my local table provider.
Blocking 48, so I can't do web servers on my system.
I wanted to see if great points would do the company for me.
I was wondering if there's a way to change this advertising 2.0 model
to let very point know that I'm a DSC listener.
And I've already got a relationship with them.
I've got a relationship with the early source code.
I know you I trust you.
You've recommended earthquakes.
And now I know and trust Earthlink.
And I was wondering if there was a way to express a back door or something like that.
So that I've never, I hadn't, haven't given everything to my email address for the contact.
But if I knew, they're going to treat me different because I'm a DSC listener.
I want to give them my email address.
Anyway, keep up the good words.
Love the show.
Okay, so I do appreciate what you're saying and that you want to be my back door man.
But of course it would be wrong if they treated you any different from any other customer just because you're a DSC listener.
However, there is a way that you can show your appreciation.
And this is something that's kicking off in, well, very shortly.
In fact, you know what I can do.
I can, all right, I'll let you hear something.
It hasn't been officially approved by Earthlink yet.
So subject to change, et cetera, bloody, bloody, bloody, bloody, blah.
And just take it at face value.
But I just want you to hear this.
And this is only for the listeners of the Charlie.
Because there will be a way for you to express that.
In fact, you could do it very, very artistically.
So just between us, guys, right, under the no damn announcements rule,
you didn't actually hear this.
You stick of advertising that sounds like, well, advertising.
Maximum strength relief to buy current insurance.
Fast as selling diet tell.
Did you ever wonder who writes those jingles that make your head explode?
Do you think that you can do better?
Well, if that sounds like you, then come on down.
Howdy and hello.
It's Marty Slick here and welcome to Earthlink to make advertising better challenge.
That's right, Bunky.
If you think you've got what it takes to make advertising better,
here's your shot.
Thanks to our friends at Earthlink.
Watch shows offering a chance to create the perfect act.
Enter the pot show, make advertising better challenge,
and you could win valuable prizes.
Tell them what they'll win Sheila.
Thanks, Marty.
Just create a spot endorsement or jingle for Earthlink,
and you could be one of the lucky winners chosen to have your advertisement
played on the Pot Show Network for which you will receive real cash payment.
Real cash payment?
That's right, Marty.
Real cash payment and finalists will also receive prizes.
You can enter as many times as you like, so get creative.
That's incredible.
And the winner will get their ad played as part of the Earthlink campaign.
That's right, Marty.
And real cash payment?
So what about us?
Well, if the spots are good enough, then we'll be rendered obsolete.
Absolutely.
That's right, Marty.
Just one challenge in advertising as we know it could cease to exist,
opening the world to a new and better form of communication
that would be more entertaining, informative, and even accurate.
That's right, Marty.
That sucks.
Think advertising sucks.
So do we.
Think you can make it better?
Pot Show and Earthlink are about to give you that chance.
Take the Make Advertising Better Challenge.
Create a great spot.
Jingle, we're endorsement for Earthlink.
And you can make big bucks having your ad played on the Pot Show Network.
So take the challenge.
Go to adchallenge.potshow.com
or you can find the link on the website of this podcast.
Make advertising better now.
Dayfox.
I just want to suck it.
Those balls are so big.
Unbelievable.
Okay, so you didn't hear that.
And please, yeah, stop.
Stop with Firefox.
Go into adchallenge.potshow.com.
It's not up yet.
Okay, stop it already.
You didn't hear one single word of what just happened.
Okay?
Hey, Adam.
This is Jeff Hines with the Friday Night Dance Party podcast.
And you know, summers coming up soon.
And we don't have a theme yet for summer of 2006.
So I selected three songs from the Pot Saved Music Network.
And I thought, might represent the theme for summer of 2006.
And I'm going to be playing them every week on my podcast for
Friday Night Dance Party until June 21st.
To see which one is voted theme of summer of 2006.
Selection number one.
You can do them about the weather, my friends.
So make the most of it around the expected hot weekend.
That was summertime course only by Little D.
Selection number two.
Summer time by Brother Love.
Nice play.
In selection number three.
The guy said it's sunny here.
We've been waiting for the side here.
The sun is up.
Summer time by Brother Love.
Nice play.
In selection number three.
The guy said it's sunny here.
We've been waiting for the side here.
The sun is up.
This guy's up here.
This summer.
That was this summer by spoil sport.
Like in that.
So you can go to Friday Night DanceParty.com to cast your vote.
And podcasters play these songs.
Let everyone know that we're going to be moving and grooving for a theme for summer of 2006.
And this is Jeff Hines with the Friday Night Dance Party podcast.
Alright Jeff, great idea man.
I really appreciate that.
That's cool.
I like that last one.
Man, the cowbell just fits so nicely.
Alright.
When the pod father promises the pod father delivers.
Simon James.
Originally from the UK now living at Barney Beach, Australia.
It begins with a hundred violence play.
No one said you can be heard.
Somewhere in the summer.
The music carries on.
The world's begin to say.
With everything going on.
My life.
You know that.
She goes to his job.
She rolls and has drowned.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
She's always coming up.
With all this crazy stuff.
And you just can't let it go.
She's breaking all the rules.
The people here.
She's a one step ahead of the game.
But just when you think.
She's got no more tricks.
She'll knock you over backwards again.
With everything going on.
I was real in my life.
You know that.
She goes to his job.
She rolls and has drowned.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
She goes to his job.
Simon James, the pod save music network on your daily source code today,
buy it on the pod save music network tomorrow.
Or yesterday, if you're in Australia, very cool.
Of course, links in the show notes, which you can find at daily source code.com.
I also cross post that on curry.com.
Yeah, it's actually in the file itself.
If you look on your iPod or your I River, you should be able to see them.
Okay, a couple of things just before I go.
People been asking me, why does my mic sound so good all of a sudden?
What did I change?
Nothing.
Well, actually, I did change one thing.
I finally got a plot filter, which, of course,
the power of my power of my piece,
the potential power of my piece,
still is plopping a little bit.
But what it is, made me do is I'm talking a little bit further away from the microphone,
just because I can't close mic at the way I used to.
Because you know it, and that's, you know, I like being close to the shaft.
Ladies, you know what I'm saying?
It's a, it's a Freudian thing, no doubt.
So maybe that's it.
Maybe I was just completely overloading the microphone,
but everyone seems to love it.
So it's nice and crisp and sound good.
I'm talking more over it, actually.
This is the high LPR40 for those of you that are interested.
And I did a little bit of tweaking on the TLA 5052 stereo valve process.
But otherwise, I did absolutely nothing.
No change whatsoever.
Adam and Curry.com is my email address.
Send me some feedback if you want to daily source code.com
for all the latest shows, show notes.
And of course, the latest podcast and the podcast feed.
And Curry.com, if you just want to argue about the European Union,
which, by the way, I am thoroughly entertained by.
Thank you so much, everybody.
See you tomorrow, sending your tunes for the fabulous Friday festivities.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it.
On the high performance podcast delivery network from pod show and line light networks.
I love it.