Delta Sierra Charley, 3-2-9er.
This podcast is not, I repeat not, family safe.
I take a look at my enormous penis and my troubles start a melt-in-away.
I take a look at my enormous penis and the happy times are coming to stay.
I got a saying and a dance when I glancing my pants and the feelings like a sunshine day.
I take a look at how my enormous penis and everything is going my way.
$60 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
I'm adjusting his attitude, curing.
I got it.
Oh, yeah, everybody.
It is fun.
I give a sleep.
I want to try.
Beyond playing with your sleep is fun.
I need a little luxury.
With your arms around me.
And the feeling that you're on high.
You give all my everything I do to go.
So I'm all I can think of getting up my ear.
I need a little luxury.
With your arms around me.
And the feeling that you're on high.
I'm the free that I hear.
And I want you there.
I need a little luxury.
With your arms around me.
And the feeling that you're on high.
And the little luxury.
And the music dot pot show dot com.
Hey, everybody.
How you doing?
Welcome to the daily source code.
Three, two, nine are coming to you from Amsterdam, the Netherlands.
Well, we haven't done this in a while.
We haven't done the cast blaster solo set up.
So just a quick note on that.
This entire show is being recorded and produced on on a wafer thin note book.
The only external piece of equipment I'm using is my wireless microphone.
So I can roam around.
Of course, I'm tethered on tethered to the laptop with the headphones.
But anyway, so all processing everything is all going directly through cast blaster.
Actually, I know I found something really cool.
When you use cast blaster the way I'm using it now, not within an external mixer.
The songs actually are written out digitally into the file.
So those of you who've been working with me on getting sound volumes just right and really working on.
Yeah, tweaking the sound a bit.
Let me know how it sounds today.
So in the Netherlands for simple reason, I was going to visit my mom.
Now the plans really got messed up yesterday.
What was going to happen is I was going to be picked up by Roy and I think Nick was going to come along.
They were going to pick me up in Sessner 172 since the Delta Shira is in pieces still.
Although I do believe the re-opholstery of the chairs is being done as we speak.
So that one couldn't fly.
Oh, with smaller aircraft, there's a couple things you got to watch out for obviously.
And one really important one is icing.
And the conditions at Farrow's airport would just perfect, perfect icing conditions.
And quite honestly, it was pretty crappy all around.
I was planning on flying from Farrow's in the morning to a Rotterdam.
Then hop in a cab.
Actually, taxi Eric was going to meet me there taking over to my mom.
Would hang out and then I'd drive back late to last night.
And then would kind of hang out in the hotel today.
Do the show and then leave.
Unfortunately, due to icing, I had to make a choice between not going.
Or going on staleosis, lovely aircraft.
Of course, easy jet.
I got to tell you, you still can't beat that for just efficient travel between European states as I would call them.
Of course, the whole trip was just marred with all kinds of interesting episodes.
I got to get work airport, went in, went through customs, and you know,
I just put my belt back on at the security and the fire alarm went off.
And it was like a bell, and then there was a fire alarm.
Please, what do you say exactly?
It was a pre-programmed voice, but it was really nice.
Please depart through the nearest exit.
And I've been in a number of evacuation scenarios, none of them life threatening.
And this one also turned out to be a false alarm.
But I must say, the public that was there.
And I'm going to have to presume that most of them were British.
Certainly the way employees really helped everyone find the exit get out.
It was really within a minute.
The entire departure lounge was empty.
It was unbelievable.
And of course, doing all went out, turned around, and got in line.
It customs again, to go through the whole thing all over again.
So I got in late last night.
Well, not late, but actually in time for late dinner with my banker.
I have a banker here, Ferdie in Holland.
And I said to her, you know, well, where do you want to eat?
Said this is a place called Vuong.
Victor uniform Oscar November golf.
It's right off the lights of playing.
And she sent me a link to it.
And I looked at the link and I said, I'll wait a minute.
I know I didn't know if it was Audrey Rangers.
If it was his restaurant or one of his sons.
But I do know Andrew.
And I have met his sons before.
They've got a couple of clubs and restaurants.
And actually they do a lot of investments in high tech.
And they have a consultancy bureau for US companies looking to do stuff in Europe and the Netherlands and the Far East.
And so I fired off an email.
I said, hey, dude, you and your popular place.
They were able for me.
So yeah, of course, it was like, you know, it was a real celebrity moment.
It worked out.
I could call the owner and get a table.
I was cool.
And then after that, and actually Audrey and his son Rob joined us.
And we chatted a bit and they opened up a club, I think.
Wow, let me think was it almost three years ago called Jimmy Wu.
And Jimmy Wu is the place to go in Amsterdam.
They can ask any celebrity in Hollywood who's been through Amsterdam.
They will tell you that they hung out at Jimmy Wu's.
And what it's funny about is when I first met Adrian and his sons of Jimmy Wu was still being built.
I've never actually seen it completed.
And it was quite impressive.
It was very, I'm not much for clubs and drinking.
As you know, I like my poison administered in different ways.
But it was nice.
It was definitely a good hang.
Even that one hour time difference between the UK and the continent.
And kind of messed me up a bit.
So, you know, I don't know.
I was awake at like 630 UK time, which was 730 here.
But yeah, I know it only slept like five or six hours.
I was just weird.
Right now, I'm doing the show.
Gonna get it in the can up on, well, of course, you're listening to it now on.
A serious star is 103.
And obviously the podcast.
And then I'm going to have some lunch.
And then I'm going to go visit my mom.
Stay for dinner.
And then I'll go back around.
I'll leave her.
Erica picked me up around eight and then it's back on the plane and back home.
And then we start celebrating the weekend because it is the Friday.
And turned on the news this morning.
Wow, big news about this Danish newspaper that published a cartoon of the
Prophet Muhammad with his head and his, I guess it's, it's not a turbine.
The proper name is, but basically his head was kind of like a bomb with a, you know,
like one of those wily, wily coyote bombs with a fuse ready to go off.
And that has really stirred up a lot of crap in, in Europe.
Muslims are really pissed off.
And it's spread now to France and Germany who have also reproduced this picture.
The news was showing it.
They were showing the picture on television.
And I think there's a bit of confusion here.
Now between, you know, is this a freedom of speech, a freedom of expression,
debate or, or, or move, or is it perhaps we still need to be sensitive about other
cultures, other religions, et cetera.
And, and take that to heart.
You know, so I'm not quite sure what the consensus is.
But definitely, there's tensions are running a little bit high, certainly, in some European countries.
Speaking of which, if I don't play this now, I'm in deep shit.
Hello, Adam Curry. This is quasi-tholic.
And this is Anthony, the stupid bit from the quasi-tholic election, right?
And the word on the street is that you screwed Louis.
You screwed Louis.
This is serious.
This is a matter of fact.
That's how we screwed him, man.
We were supposed to get in the series.
Same like feet, but that Adam Curry doesn't know how he uses backwards count down time over there.
Serious?
Oh, wow.
Anyway, Adam Curry, it looks like somebody's gonna have to pay.
Right, put it this respect shown to quite stone.
First off, we're gonna have to fire that Roger Smalls here.
Wait, wait.
Oh, Roger Smalls.
The eagle has landed.
Get out of town. Get out of town.
You're supposed to do all split.
Roger, don't dig the normal garbage.
Get out of my car.
Oh, sorry.
I dig just two.
Get out of town.
Right.
Some blood is gonna have to hit the ground here.
What is going to spill tonight?
Shall we stay in here when it's the flock of goats?
Stoke a betshe's preparing the gun.
We are going to slay a goat.
Right here on your show, Adam Curry.
To show you that nobody disrespects quite slowly.
Or to spill a betshe's like that.
Nobody.
This is what happens, Carly.
Oh, my goodness.
That is one bloody goat mess.
One bloody bottle of goat.
The next goat.
That's what happens, Carly.
And so in the meantime.
Tell all you listeners to go to quasi-tolid.com.
Tell them to do it.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
Where are flink?
We believe in an internet that safe from viruses and scammers.
We believe your personal information should be just that.
Personal.
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe.
Where are flink?
Make this smart choice.
Visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
Just realize I haven't had a single drop of coffee this morning.
You know what we call up and we call room service and get some.
Let me see, could I have a speaker phone here?
Yes, there we go. Room service.
It's an old-fashioned dialer.
Check that out.
What the hell is that?
Well, that's not all right.
Let me, uh, I'll go through the operator.
Hey.
What the hell is this?
Oh, man.
Can't believe it.
All right, forget that.
I'll order some during the last song of the day.
The last song of the week.
Boy, it's been quite a week, hasn't it?
A lot of technical stuff has gone wrong.
I've spent probably the equivalent of an entire day fixing email problems and computers
and all kinds of crap.
The blackberry is still on the fridge and I have to go through that whole process and call up
customer help and give them our tax ID number and not looking forward to it.
Now, to get this set up perfectly, I've got to put that up there.
Yes, yeah, I was worried about that.
She's going to be the two-saw.
Okay, it has a preset volume.
Okay.
So while you hear that very faintly in the background, do we try that again?
I want to second.
Let me see.
I think I can set the sound settings different in cast blaster.
This is where the whole system kind of breaks down when you want to do multiple,
there we go, preset.
When you want to do multiple sound files, let's see if that's what we're doing.
Natural, sexual, natural, sexual, natural, sexual, sexual.
It's an encourage, metro, sexual moment.
David, David, David, David.
And encourage, metro, sexual moment.
Yeah.
Well, we have had so much fun in the past couple weeks here at the metro, sexual moment corner
that we're actually getting some pretty serious players to jump on board and give it up with some...
Oops.
Oh, shoot.
Oh, man, this is sucking so bad.
That's true.
Oh, you know what?
Let me...
Oh, God.
I'm so sorry.
This is...
That's true.
That's true, that's true.
Hey, Anna.
It's يا about the telephone.
What kind of texting is that?
It's really easy toризide.
Good ли pas.
Now, when I share my husband's favourite mentally-fectoral shaving tip,
When he showers he uses a product called sugar scrub,
you can get it just about anywhere.
It's a mixture of sugar
and a central oils.
He likes it on his face when he showers to exfoliate, dead skin.
a dead skin, and the oil protects the skin from the harshness of the blade.
He doesn't do it every day, but when he does, I love touching his face, and it smells good, too.
Thanks again, Adam.
That's Callie from Geek Brief.
That's Geek Brief.potshow.com.
Well, I heard heart shatter all across the universe there, as it turns out, Callie has a
see a husband, oh man, love the show Cali.
Hey Adam, it's Mark Yoshimoto and M.Coffin.
Since you're always looking for a metro-sexual tips, I thought I'd throw you a bone.
Calm down, that's just a figure of speech.
Now, when I first moved to Southern California or Planet Siliconia as we call her on the
hell, I went and got myself an apartment by the beach.
I bought myself a brand new convertible and proceeded to drive around with the top down
everywhere I went.
And if it was just going to mail some letters or my weekly donation of cash to poor
starving children in Africa.
What I ended up with only after a few days was a horrific sunburn on my forehead.
What I needed to do every night when I got home was moisturized.
So I proceeded to try a number of products and not only did it help keep my face from
peeling off of my scalp.
But I noticed it made my skin look a lot better, too, and over the years, I've kind
of honed my routine down to an exact science and now I'm going to let you and your listeners
in on my secret.
And if you're expecting me to make a joke about rubbing a freshly-aborted cheap fetus
on my face, well, that's just not the case.
It's not funny and trust me, the little bits of after birth actually clogged your pores.
But I digress.
One I do.
Is wash my face with a soap I discovered after receiving it in a gift bag at some Hollywood
function.
It's called Dr. Bronner's 18-in-1 hemp peppermint pure castile soap.
Okay, okay.
Calm down Adam.
You can't smoke it.
Let me trust me.
You'll only end up passing out with a terrible headache and waking up wearing someone else's
underwear.
Dr. Bronner's soap is completely 100% organic and not only will leave your face cleaner
than you ever felt it, but the peppermint oil is a natural anti-biotic to kill unwanted
bacteria that may accumulate in your pores.
Then once your face is dry, use a product called BioElements Urban Detox Vitamin Serum.
Now, what does that do you ask?
Honestly, I have no frickin' idea, but I've noticed that it does seem to smooth the tiny
wrinkles in your skin and, you know, you smooth a hundred little wrinkles on your face
and you can tell the difference right away.
Now, what Urban Detox also does is help your skin absorb the moisturizer and that's the
third and final step.
When I'm moisturized, I use O-lay complete.
It's light, non-greasy, and won't clog your pores.
It also has the SPF-15 and doesn't smell like a Las Vegas call girl or your favorite grandma
and, you know, Adam, if you're into those kind of things, well, maybe you'll have to
try this new product called Hor by Mabelene, but that's all up to you buddy.
Anyway.
This is Mark Yoshimoto and M-Coffin' Sure enough, that's my Metro-sexual tip.
So, when you hit your mid and late 30s, you have to try harder to look good and, if I say
so myself, I sure do look good.
Well, at least that's what my wife and the several runaways I've picked up at the bus station
tell me.
Mark Yoshimoto and M-Coff, if you listen to this podcast on the Serious Stars 103, he'll
be up next with the Pacific Coast Highway and after that Metro-sexual moment, Mark, I have
to say, you now are officially...
A really big hair fat.
And, carries Metro-sexual moment, yeah.
Yeah, okay, getting used to the equipment here.
Okay, a couple more minutes left before we hit the satellite window.
Looks like we figured out this countdown clock problem and, as actually, as Kevin Sheldon
Bach pointed out, your solution is to blame Fenton's file important, important.
Yeah, that's almost true, of course, it's not PWB's mistake or his fault himself.
And the problem here is that I'm timing this show on my computer and then it turns
out to be 10 to 15 seconds longer on his computer.
And a couple of people sent me pretty much the same reasoning behind what's going on.
Here's one from Garen Heber.
He says, he said, I do audio professional programming professionally, the problem is the sample
rate on the sound card relative to the clock on your computer.
Neither of them is exactly correct, much less in sync.
What's going on is that, over the course of your show, the sound card is recording at a
rate just slightly too slow.
When played back on another sound card that's slightly faster, not necessarily more accurate,
just running at a slightly faster pace, the show ends a bit early.
Audibly, there's a slight pitch shift, but it's so small about half percent that it isn't
noticeable.
OK, well, yeah, I understand it and he broke it down into, you know, basically on both
computers, you're going to wind up with the 1800 seconds by 48,000 samples per second,
which is like 886 million samples or whatever, but I still don't understand when when
a show says it's 24 minutes and 30 seconds of my computer shouldn't it say it on every
computer?
Anyway, Cas Blaster Mike has jumped into this, he also knows a hell of a lot about sound
recording, obviously, because he's building this program and I'm sure he's going to
come up with something.
Well, I didn't actually, I do want to hear you.
You can have a transmission from Matthew Ebo.
Hey Adam, Adam, can you hear me?
Yeah, I got, I'm in the engine room, I can't hear you, but this is Matthew Ebo.
I don't know if you listen to my podcast or not, but I do the whole thing for my Starship,
just outside the Earth's atmosphere and took your advice and I'm converting the whole
ship to biodiesel, so we'll see how that works.
But I wanted to let you know, I played a show last night, actually, with Kevin Reads and Jeff
Smith.
You probably heard of him, he played both of whom I do show that played all three of us
in the show.
Actually, we did a little pot-safe showcase last night in Nashville, Tennessee, and man,
these guys can cook.
I got to tell you, we got to do more shows like this.
I'll keep you up to speed on this, but man, you should pay attention to this kind of stuff.
I think we're going to do some great things of pot-safe music live on stage in 2006.
It's going to be something to watch.
Anyway, keep up with it.
Oh no, it's starting to smoke.
I got to get going that, this and I'll talk to you later, make sure you have the good work
all right.
I love the show.
Galactic biodiesel, amen.
Okay, once again, you're more than welcome to sing along.
It is our biodiesel piece too.
You know, I'm converting a lot of people.
These all engines are being sold quite a bit here in Europe, particularly popular
as the Volkswagen Passat I believe.
Trying to do my fader here.
Oh, that's not a good work out there, man.
Where was I?
Yeah, so people in the coming very interesting, actually, I talked to the restaurant guys about this
restaurant.
Either you're going to sit on this last night at the restaurant about this.
Man, what an opportunity.
Everyone who has a restaurant can have their entire fleet running on.
French fries.
Gotta say goodbye to everyone who's still checking the show out on a serious satellite
stars 103.
Up next, we'll see if it goes that way.
Followed by a mange, Don and Drew.
We've got the pot safe crew on the way.
I'll see you guys on Monday.
Bye.
You heard the satellite window closed coming through the little, the man the speaker of this
portage is absolutely correct.
It's like the size of one of this earbud just sticking your ear.
So, I won't be in San Francisco for another couple weeks still, but I cannot wait to see if I can
fire up now.
Every single time I think about Trinity, I keep thinking about the fuel supply.
It is below one quarter tank, so I've got a schedule of, so when I'm out and usually I
arrive on Sundays, of course, that's when the biofuelo waste is closed.
We're finally going to do that sound seeing tour.
A filling up Trinity.
The bio diesel beast.
If you've never heard of this, check out curried.com and search for Trinity.
You'll find out all about it.
She could talk.
You hear her fake.
I don't for grouping in her tank.
We're Trinity.
Trinity.
Yeah.
Hi, Adam Kelly Walker from Bloomington, Indiana.
I'm on the campus of Indiana University for a track meet.
And one of the schools attending is Murray State University.
I'm looking at one of their buses.
And on the back, it says leading the way in alternative fuels.
This bus powered by biodiesel.
Clean, renewable, farm, grown.
Pretty interesting stuff to know that one of the universities here in the Midwest is running
their buses on biodiesel.
Anyway, I'll also hopefully in the next week or so have a promo for you for the Indiana University
mini university podcast.
It'll be one of the first podcasts to come from the campus of Indiana University.
Thanks for everything, Adam.
Thank you.
Thanks for checking in.
And I wonder if it's 100% biodiesel or is it mixture?
Because you can mix this vegetable oil-based biodiesel with any amount of petroleum-based
diesel that you want.
And any measure, it all works just perfectly fine.
So I think that, you know, Willie Nelson's biodiesel.
I believe is, I think it's B80.
So it's still, it's only 20% veggie oil and 80% petrochemical.
I believe it could be the other way around.
But the Trinity still crews none 100%.
And I played that audio comment outside of the Trinity theme music,
because I just can't seem to get the levels right.
Chad said, Adam, how do you figure the state of the Union address was one of the mill?
Was Bush saying the US needs to wean itself of oil not a surprise enough for you?
No, it wasn't actually.
I took it a little bit differently.
I didn't take it as wean yourself off oil.
I thought it was less dependency on foreign oil.
And I believe that was specifically directed towards the Middle East.
Of course, there's there's oil in many different places.
But no, I did kind of expect him to say that.
I mean, look at what's going on in big oil industry.
Shell.
Shell oil.
Was it Shell?
Who reported yesterday?
I think it was.
Like, you know, it's something like 13 billion pounds of profit.
I mean, come on.
The people are now actually saying, hey, dude, wait a minute.
We're getting screwed.
We're paying these exorbitant prices at the gas pump.
And at the same time, these guys are making billions and billions of dollars in profit.
So it doesn't make sense that that's the message he was trying to convey.
But I thought it was, yeah, I thought it was kind of what I expected he would be saying.
A little bit humble or maybe, but yeah, I think it was, I mean,
state of the union somehow the words just don't weigh as heavy as they used to.
I don't know what it is, but I haven't seen the type of analysis that you see
maybe 10 years ago.
And I think that's purely because there's so much communication.
You know, there's, we all have our own opinions.
We're already talking about exactly those opinions before the state of the union address is even made.
I didn't enjoy on C-SPAN.
I was able to watch the, the minority response.
And in general, you know, when people ask me what's it like in the States, I say,
well, you know, there's a lot of red state blue state stuff.
But when you get down to it, man, we're all just people working and let me tell you,
people in America work much, much harder than the countries I've been in in Europe.
This, this, I don't know what it is.
And it just seems like people enjoy it more, maybe.
I don't know.
But well, of course, if you don't have a job in the States, then you basically will
have a job in dry and blow away with the wind.
Maybe that does have something to do with it.
Hey Adam, piggy love from Love House radio.
Just wanted to give you a quick comment on the splits for the pot safe music network.
But I first heard you talking about the splits to be honest with you.
And maybe I'm just not business minded enough as a podcaster.
But I never thought of the podcast you're getting any of the split.
I thought the split was going to be replaced with that one.
How did that sneak in there?
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
I guess I played that one yesterday.
You know what?
I think it was a mistake to do this show without coffee.
Well, I bet nitches for us is trying to hold my horses out.
I want to get serious.
Yeah.
Is that sure?
Was it looking?
Man, I'm bent.
Ever since the day we met.
Now I'm falling in deep prey.
Three hours and night ain't enough.
Yeah, just call their baby.
Lord help, they may be.
I'm just a little love.
A little in love.
Something tell me there's no such thing.
Here the next thing you know you're out by and a ring.
A man's got to be strong and I'm trying to hold on.
But be in that tough thrill, too.
Because I'm all about her.
One thing's for sure.
I'm just a little in love.
Here the things rose.
Neighbors getting notes.
She's been over three times this week.
Every time I see her,
I'm thinking that I must be.
A little in love.
Something tell me there's no such thing.
And the next thing you know you're out by and a ring.
A man's got to be strong and I'm trying to hold on.
But be in that tub's real time
Cause I'm all about her
One thanks for sure
And I'm just a little in love
Well I guess it sounds crazy
It's too late to save me
I know there I know her
So I must look funny
Down here on the one here
Five just a little in love
A little in love
Something tells me there's no such thing
And the next thing you know you're out behind a ring
A man's gotta be strong
And I'm trying to hold on
But be in that tub's real time
Cause I'm all about her
One thanks for sure
I'm just a little in love
And I'm just a little in love
So I'm just a little in love
Just a little in love
And then I'll do it for another week
It tells us here a Charlie
The Daily Source Code
Thank you very much for listening
DailySourceCode.com
Where you can find the latest show
On the podcast feed feedback
To me, audio is welcome
MP3's, I'd love it if you stick it up on a server
And just send me the link
It's atomoodcurry.com
Thank you very much for another great week
Have a great week in everybody
And I'll see you
I'm Monday
Another poncho podcast
Stick it in your ear