This is Soccer Girl. I just listened to the first episode of Shadow Falls and it's scared me
crapless.
It has come to our attention as you have decided that Twitter was not a full planet, but we will show
you who are the primitives in this solar system. If you do not need our demands, brave actions
will happen to the Earth. There will be global warming. It increases in currency, instability,
and we will start to be able to manifest like a terrorist.
All demands, we demand to meet the state of the Pluto as a planet.
Number two, we want oil and large planet. It's pretty damn cold out here on grill.
And number three, we demand an unlimited supply and sense sale.
And if you do not need our demands, we will start killing one of the time, starting with Adam Curry,
host on the daily source code in his little tiny cabin, in the afternoon 7th of a story, when one is girlfriend in England.
Meet all demands. You have been warned. This is Delta C ever Curry, four, five, two.
With sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I come from justice at downtown. We have people like one of these poverty in the right now.
Well, there's a love trash and fire, so forget about the lies. Oh, I can do this sunrise.
Please take time to see where you dwell as much like the place I've been.
I'll wake up white my green eyes for the same reason. You just have me to lie my life.
It would have come wrong, stay at the street and not rape anybody because that's where I do.
I only said I had track and hear me about the fact I'm very still busy.
Oh, this life is too bad to watch you just go back to the ground morning in mind.
So I grab with off horse, so I won't walk, but that's been my ramen that's fine.
Just verbalize the way I run, how good I smoke, yes I grow up in this hearing.
No life I stole, it's a life I've made, and now you've been told.
Now there ain't no trash bags, I look at the shape, back to the glass and blood up in the street.
So keep it in the final line, I can't see the base line, but life is broken, I need to see.
Oh, this life is too bad to watch you just go back to the street and not rape anybody because that's where I do.
Please take time to see where you dwell as much like the place I've been.
Don't talk about me, wait that I want to talk about myself, I don't play.
Don't talk about my dog, I have your own leads, but don't tell me.
You're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you
you're the best man, you're the best woman, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the most man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man, you're the best man
From their new studio album titled new and improved, which is coming out October 3rd already available now on the podcast
Music Network music on podshow dot com and of course you can find a link at daily source code dot com
Which is working again. Thanks for all the
Coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey known as gulfard in the curry caught as this is the daily source code
Couple hot topics today
First of all plenty of feedback on Liam the 20 year old 21 year old scumbag who's going out with my daughter
Ha ha ha ha a lot of you responded to that also some pod save music talk will get too later on and
You know the typical stuff coming in on the voice
I
Yeah, why do you put a plus in front of that well that only works in your mobile phone if you're using your mobile phone
Then if you're another country and you feel the urge to call the Charlie you won't have to dial any country access codes
plus one two zero one six two five six three five seven
Hey Adam this is Corey you may remember me from my last year I had last year
A PSA that you played on this phone right after hurricane Katrina to encourage people was they could do for the
To relieve with the hurricane effort. I got a podcast the 501 key three cast
You're not calling about that though. I'm calling because right now
I'm a bundle of emotions this weekend
I'm getting married to the girl that I love Katie Roach and
Since I don't have a mountain top to yell from I thought that the early source code would probably be the best thing that I could get
I'm so in love with this girl and I if you could just play this out to the world
I'm so looking forward to this weekend and
Being together with friends and family and I just want as many people to hear it as possible
I love the show man
I was just listening and it's kind of a calming voice to hear you talk and while I'm getting ready for everything driving around doing all the last minute
And so take care and thanks. Oh, hey, by the way. I used to be a scruncher
Macomba now you can make me into a folder
Does your future wife know about it? What is she that's the important information when you need to know can scrunchers and folders live in perfect harmony together
That of course is the real question
Congratulations on the nocturals check in from time to time. Let us know how it's going and
Shoot since I'm naked pictures
portions of today show brought to you by the accurate target cast if you want to hear about
The first episode is all about the sound system of the accurate RDX SUV go to accurate dot pod show dot com
It's a target cast so
It's basically a podcast about the product
You might find it interesting if you have listened to it give me some feedback on that as well
Just call in or send an MP3 file if you wish. Hey, I found out about the riddles
I
Got pretty bored after after three riddles and I think it was going to be nine of them
And I was really trying to figure out who this was, but you know it was a combination
If you've listened to the past couple of episodes of the daily source code, you then you know what I'm talking about
Really a combination of really crappy sound quality of these riddles that were there were being called in and it was supposed to be a promo for a new show and
Turns out
It was all Susanne's doing at the diva cast and
It's funny because I'm actually already subscribed to the diva cast
I I know
Susanne and Robin of course from inside works and
It popped up on my radar a couple weeks ago and I started listening to it and you know what you don't need to come up with any complicated riddles
It's a good show. I'll happily promote it for you. I do have some suggestions though
The last episode it really got good and interesting because
Even though yeah basically you you you put
You put to four divas in a room and you get a lot of diva clutch, you know and so that's
That's not it is less annoying than I thought it would be because in interwoven amongst all of that
We're some really honest things you guys were talking about
lesbian feelings
masturbation
power
Was it
Pressure power pressure hoses
You know if you can if you can just keep the honesty coming through from time the time real honesty how women really feel
As a guy. I'm very interested in listening to that
And I just bet I just bet there some women out there who would really enjoy listening to it as well
diva cast dot pot show dot com and thanks very much guys for the riddles
Next time just you know send me a promo
and
It's good for the voice now because the first thing you were talking about the
Charist and
The first thing that popped in my head was when you were talking about that was you know I grew up and watching
All kinds of air air more movie airplane movies were
You know either there's a high jacker or there's a something wrong with the plane
And the first thing that the air sewerist says to the pilot or something
You know don't tell the passengers
We don't want to fight in them or whatever and I think that's
That's it totally the opposite of what's going on here. I mean, they're just like you said they're just scaring people and all that
I just if I took the same approach as the
As I do in these movies and like I'm sure they do in real life because they don't want to scare people
Is you know, I think we all be better if they didn't
That they're I totally agree with you when you say
You know don't tell anybody
You know just quietly get these guys and then put them away
So I just thought I'd leave that note
I'm currently driving around here and
I wanted to call so that I don't forget about it so
All right, popular and that's why you put a plus in plan of in front of the one right
So you could call immediately from your cell phone before you forgot, you know
That is kind of interesting and that's the reason I played this this piece of feedback is because
It does seem like you know all the old movies and I'm talking movies from
Before the 80s probably it was always about you know we don't want to alarm the population we want to keep
Everyone everyone's feeling secure
And there's a lot to be said for that and it seems like we're doing exactly the opposite
really does
from
From the president through the media all the way through all the way down because it it just results in in so much
Action, you know, it's a action immediate reaction
It keeps people scared keeps people watching television and keeps people
scared and and
keeps people scared and that's what it does
You know, I'm I'm a bit disappointed with all the aviation podcast that are out there
I have a whole channel on my podshow plus account you can find it at atom.podshow.com
It's a whole channel with nothing but aviation podcasts
And I love it because I I'm subscribed to the channel and once I'm new pops up it's it's right there no matter which show it's from it's an aviation show
I know that and so I listen to it
I'm you know, I'm hearing references to the security measures and the terror threats and the
fear that's being spread but I don't really hear our aviation
Producers of independent content coming up with anything earthshattering and I thought we'd get more insights into everything
Maybe they just don't know or maybe they're afraid to talk about it
You know looking for looking for some action there
This is what this is supposed to be about you know we can get some different noise from people who are in the front lines
Just a subtle hint
Was a USA today article that came out that who sent this to me Mark Lawrence
Elite security lines bug some but not others
I don't want to get into the whole conversation again, but there is some real good information there about who actually owns the line
The property the lines are on what the job of the TSA is and why there can be different types of lines
and why it's not a an equal basis that all are
All are made forced to wait
And some different opinions interesting to read up a little link to to that story in the show notes
So yesterday Patricia and I were talking about Liam this is a 21-year-old kid who was
Almost Christina's boyfriend my 16 my just 16-year-old daughter
I express express my my feelings and of course Christina walked in and
And she'd heard most of it, but she's a you know
She's a real trooper
She has her opinion she she lets it know be known what she feels and what she thinks but you guys man you don't you don't sugarcoat anything
Is the first response to Liam
I had to look that up Eddie Haskell fictional character on leave it to beaver the kind of kid your parents
Don't want you hanging around with and
Notorious brown nose or towards elder
Fantastic I got to get a clip of Eddie Haskell and show it to Patricia because she wasn't in America when that was on and it never really
Indicated that well outside of the US but
Excellent excellent excellent example of the kind of guy I think he is
I had him this is Stephen Damning South Florida. I was just
Listening to your latest daily source coat and about your your daughter and being 16 and dating a 21-year-old swine ball
Very interesting to hear what other people go through because it's coming for me too
I've got two daughters five and
Ferry and I'm waiting for the day just and here's what I was told by a good friend
I think you need to take some of those goals records and and various other
Things from your career down off the wall and put a few nice glass cases up with guns and
Don't have to load them you don't have to use when you don't have to
Hey Liam come on in man. I want to introduce you to my friends. Yeah, they're over here my friends Smith and Wesson
Shoot anybody but when somebody walks in to date your daughter. They should know that you like guns and
That just might help a little bit. Yeah, hey, dude
I've been known to smoke gunja and I like guns. You really don't want to piss me off. I don't already guns myself
But as my daughter's approached the age of 16. I may be
tempted to make that purchase and put those glass cases on my wall as well
I am 43 years old by the way. I got a very late start having kids. I got two little twins in the five-year-old daughter as well
so
I feel your pain and I know it's coming for me too. So I am a folder my kids are folders
And I come from a long line of folders have a wonderful day
We'll talk to you soon. All right. Thank you. I do have a couple of firearms
Some menacing looking ones. I've got a Japanese sub-machine gun that my grandfather brought back from the south Pacific
I have no ammo for it, but I could definitely flaunt that one around
The interesting idea. I don't know how effective it will be, but I do understand where you're coming from and
You just wait my friend. Call back in and what about 11 years when your first kid hit 16? We'll talk again then, okay?
And whenever there's something that is troubling me whenever there's something that that I need to learn whenever
I need to just like in shadow falls. I need to turn to my elders for answers. There he is!
Oh
You've got questions. He's got a sad life repair man coming after you sad life repair man
What's he gonna do? He'll fit your misconceptions and answer questions to
There's nothing in the universe that he can't do for you sad life repair man
Sad life repair man
Yeah
My body. Uncle Jesse
Peter give me some advice on Liam first. I got to say I always love it when Patricia's on
But having raised two girls I was screaming during yesterday's show in fact when Christina showed up
I had to play that section three times because I was laughing so hard. I was missing stuff
That girl has a sharp wit
But that's not why I'm here
Because of your description of uneasiness looking at all of those
Hot young babes the same age as your daughter. I had a similar experience once
One of my daughters brought a girlfriend home one
Summer after noon and they asked if they could change the channel on the TV to see something on MTV
Shoot it might even have been you. I don't remember and here's why I don't remember
My daughter's guest
late on the floor on her stomach in front of the TV
Prophing up her head with her hands elbows on the floor. I
Was seated on a sofa behind her. I
Happened to look down at her
She took my breath away
She was wearing
tiny little
Terry cloth shorts
Her beautifully smooth tan legs revealed the faintest whispers of tiny
Laund hares listening in the sunlight streaming from the window
I followed her legs with my eyes
First those perfectly curved calves
Then to her firm young thighs and then to the curve of her ample but a
Extending out of those tiny little shorts
Immediately I could feel myself responding physically to this incredibly
Lushes sight
Almost as quickly my mind started trying to construct some fantasy some scenario and then she turned and spoke
Thanks for letting us watch that Mr. Fenton
What channel were you watching? I'll switch it back for you
Never had the words
Mr. Fenton ever cut so deeply
Clearly I was a ledgerous old man who should be ashamed of himself
Please this is between you and I
Don't ever speak of this
That was just about the most disturbing thing you've ever sent to me, Peter
What the hell is wrong with you, man
All right, thanks for the advice I guess
Yeah, it got worse and really got worse yesterday. I didn't even realize how much worse it got
I'm total doofus showing my age
AC
Prof Ross here
It was named to
Do see four five one. I just get this out feeling that Christina and Liam are just cringing when you originally called it panic on the disco
Thank God at the end of it. You changed it to panic at the disco
Being a father. I'm just afraid my daughter's gonna laugh at me one day and I don't know if we want Liam out of the picture
We got to get the names of her bands right
That's it, man
Scrunch her then fold there. I
Can't believe I did though. I didn't go back and listen so I take your word for it
Probably my brain was going a little bit too fast for my mouth and I wanted to say panic
I could have said panic on the disco panic at the disco on the podcast music network
That's probably where I got messed up. Yeah, yeah, that would be like really really stupid
She didn't correct me so she may not have caught onto it immediately because
Usually she does correct me
Quickly when I say something stupid. Oh, but it got much worse
Hey Adam was there from the doctor's your podcast right here
Wait wait some listen the new Charlie
What is it that's so 451
panic at the disco
But the sins and not the tragedies
This song is following me following me every bar. I have a club every radio station
I listen to every store the freaking wall everywhere for Christ's I was
I
Skate this song. I was a freaking wall man
It's by the order and I have the goddamn song now. It's on my morning Charlie. I'm trying to have a cup of coffee
Well, he late afternoon when I call out of my heart at whole bed
Had my cup of coffee, you know listen to Charlie
That is that song again. Oh my god. I had her to song to follow me this way
Says mercy plague and their dance sexy Danny. I'm quite out with a heavy people ever heard of changing the goddamn song
To grab an all forgetting another band. It's on the right traditional radio
Yeah, coming like I'm modified folder
I took all of it around the hand move it from the head and set a hand and then I use it
Great, find us at Dorcissure dot blog spot dot com door to be
Yeah nice phone connection
Yeah, try some decuffs and say on next time, maybe you know
That's interesting point you make there
I have not heard that song before the first time I heard it is when it showed up in a top 10 list in the pod tip music network
I saw that it had just been added to the PMN
I know panic at the disco are of course
I'm not familiar with what their current singles are. I just don't listen to the radio in the car
Sometimes I'll turn on BBC, but it's usually more talk than then music sometimes virgin radio
But then it's more because of my sentiment to my age
Um
Who is that interesting
That it's kind of a reverse role play here instead of the you know the the young up and coming hip stuff
That is independent coming through what we used to call college radio making it into mainstream now
It's these mainstream players who are trying to make it into my world from the reverse direction
Now I may not be the norm
But I think it's pretty interesting to see this happen
There's also some some big issues with
Established artists putting their music on the ponts hit music network
Which are going to discuss in the continuing podcast of the daily source code those of you checking out serious stars one
Oh two if you want to hear that part of the conversation
Go to daily source code calm listen to the show. It's episode dsc four five two
We got more cool stuff for you guys and
Here on the podcast let me get it started because there's some issues outside the United States that
I haven't really been ignoring them. I've heard about them, but finally someone put it into a concise
audio feedback and
Was talk about it. Hi Adam. This is Norman from the German noncast podcast together with two other people
I'm also doing the pot parade the so-called potsafe music charts
Which is very popular year in Germany
Every fortnight we present potsafe music in a way that can be compared to traditional radio charge shows for example from the eighties
But of course, it's free and available as a podcast
Love the German accents. Yeah, and your English is impeccable dude. It's so incredibly good. You're it's nice
It's very nice to listen to but it's it's kind of funny the same time. It's like Colonel Klink sending me audio feedback
Many tracks are taken from the potsafe music network as well and until now it was very pleasing
Because these bands and artists listed there often is established nice and productive email contacts with us
Right on okay
I'm with you so far at the moment. We are experiencing some new and unforeseeable difficulties because of the fact
That several well-known bands are now listed in the potsafe music network
He is Jürgen another well-known potcaster from Germany who is also playing potsafe music in a popular weekly podcast show dude
It's just like a multi report from Germany. Hi Adam. This is Jürgen from the German podcast cafe
There are some serious issues and a lot of emotional discussions in German podcast forums
Concerning the PMN and music from well-known artists in the PMN as depurble or toothpick or panic at the disco or Alice Cooper or James Brown
Could you please send me a link to where these forums are I mean?
I'm subscribed to a couple different
RSS feeds German podcast RSS feeds, but if you could really show me where the conversation is going because it's
When I just parse my news reader, you know, it's it doesn't always pop out and I can't always get
Context without seeing you know the full story
Just the the synopsis isn't enough for me. I can read the German
I just need to really focus on it. Please send me some URLs where I can follow along with this conversation
But I know where you're going because this is a big one. Lee to mention two of them
We cannot believe and by the way German lawyers confirmed to that not officially but in private discussions
That these songs are really potsafe because they are listed in the German Gema or American ASCAP
Database by the majority
Playing these songs in a podcast would violate German copyright law and I predict the German Gema would sue every podcast that was playing these songs
Without a so called newly created podcast license from Gema. Okay, let me just hop into this for a second
There is a difference in jurisdiction between ASCAP BMI
Who handle the United States territory and
All the other
Versions of ASCAP BMI they're not affiliated in the Netherlands. It's Buma Stemera
As I said into Germany it's Gema every country has their own version of this and
The way the potsafe music network operates of course was predominantly built with
With the United States market in mind and now we're seeing you know that there are some other issues
Is that any owner of
Copyrighted music of the words in the lyrics in the United States
Can offer any type of license here she wants to anyone
Within the United States jurisdiction that that much I know for sure
So part of the deal with radio stations is
And television stations and any other broadcast medium is hey if you play this song
You have to pay a royalty and here's your rate card the potsafe music network
It says hey
You can play any song that I as the owner of the words in the music put up on the potsafe music network
And you have to pay me nothing as long as it's a podcast if it's broadcast then it's a different story
But every radio station pays a set fee for their ASCAP BMI license
So that will be if if a podcast aired for instance podcast on serious as a perfect example serious pays hundreds of millions of dollars
No, I'm sorry, maybe less it's probably like 70 million dollars a year to ask at BMI and and all of the songs that are played are recorded reported
And and some they go into the magic cloud over to ask at BMI and then they figure out who gets what
But for the podcast anything that's listed on the PMN can be used however you want now there's another part to that
Which is the record companies who own the master the physical record itself
The
If you want to create a and this is the unclear part in all legislation right now is okay if it's on a podcast is it actually
Similar to a broadcast so you can give away that performance right
Yes, everyone agrees, but the record companies who own all of the masters
So the actual physical product that is then being copied from
A file into your file onto someone's player
That's a a real distribution right and
You can only hand that over if you own it so most artists
Establish artists don't own those masters as an example
Alice Cooper probably does not own the rights to
What does he have up there? I'm 18 so he probably doesn't have the rights to that he doesn't own the actual master, but
He does own the words and the music so he put a
Live recording so he owned a apparently he or who or some record label that he's involved with owns that master
So there we have it. It's okay because the owners of the master said go ahead and put it up on the podcast music network and then the owners of
The copyright the the performance right the words in the music also said it's okay go ahead and put it up
Asked BMI
Although they do have an exclusive license for broadcast
Even then it would be possible in theory in theory. I'm saying for an owner of
Music and words to tell a radio or television station
You know what you can play this and you don't have to pay any Askcott royalties over it that would be possible
It would be complicated because of how the whole system works and how it's tracked
But that would be in theory possible this is where the subtle difference lies
And as we listen to the rest of this audio comment which I do want to go through because I I really appreciate the conversation
It's going on in Germany right now
The the gamma as with the Buma in the Netherlands
Have a almost God-given legal right to be the sole representative of
The performance rights for for the music that is signed up and is represented by them
And when the artist actually signs up with those organizations
They literally sign over any other right to that organization so they do not have the right as they do in the U.S
With Askcott BMI
To hand out a different license to a different group of users of their music
They have essentially said okay Gemma you represent my music for all types of broadcast
Whether that be podcast or radio or television or any any other type of performance
You own and represent those rights
They don't really own it, but they represent those rights exclusively
And that is the main difference
So I think
You're right what's continuing with the comments he where it takes us
So German podcast us would highly appreciate your help in terms of legal security
Playing PMTunes from let's say depurple
Why is it allowed to play for example woman from Tokyo even though they are listed and licensed to all
major copyright authorities
A DSE for for one and for for two you mentioned that when an artist plays these songs live here or the label
Owns all the rights and can do what he wants even putting them on the PMN
might that be the glue to serve our uncertainty
As I mentioned before help is highly appreciated here in Germany
Thanks
Just servers and bye bye
I hope you don't mind our terrific German accent at him
Gugain is living in the south of a very in part of Germany about 500 miles south of my place
We both are and have been very interested in music and we are both record collectors who even know you from your former times at MTV
So we have got a main advantage compared to let's say
younger podcasts as who might not know rainbow depurple or Gary Moore
But these podcasts who don't know any of these artists and who are playing one of their songs in their podcasts
Might get into serious trouble for doing so without having had the intention to violate some maybe existing local laws
Like you can said there are several discussions going on at the moment
But especially German right authorities are sometimes very slowly and unflexible
So it might take some time until things might become clearer in the meantime
I might suggest the following is it possible to mark these bands an artist for example with a short note
That their tracks might not be pot safe in some other countries
Another possibility would be to list them in a separate additional directory not to exclude them
But to give the people the chance to distinguish between traditional pot safe artists and those who might not be pot safe in the traditional meaning
Don't get as wrong. We really like the fact that bands like depurple or rainbow or people like Gary Moore James Brown or Joshua Kadesen
Published some of their songs within the pot safe music network as well and we hope that there'll be others to come
But for now, it's sometimes very difficult for people and especially podcasts from outside the USA to figure out what can be played and what not
Maybe you can help us and feel free to play this MP3 file in your show if you want to
Thanks very much and greetings to you and all your listeners
This was Norman Austos from Gootus low in Germany. Goodbye. All right. Thank you
Whoa sounds like a big undertaking. I think first we got to find out if this is really true that it's all other countries accept the
US that would make it very easy
So everyone in every individual country would have to see if indeed the performing arts performing
Rights organization that represents
These artists that they do indeed have the exclusive rights and that no other rights can be granted
In Europe it might actually be pretty simple
It's something that could be changed at the European Union level although that could take a long long time
Really, it's the artists. I would have to say. I mean, it sucks for for podcasts or some other countries
So I think we definitely need to put some kind of
Some kind of message up there so that they understand
What the risks are but flagging everything. I mean, there's no way. I mean, we'd have to put
a dedicated person on that 24 hours a day
I just don't see how how we could actually make that work how make that a viable situation
There's too much research and so it would have to be done when artists are submitting anyway
So it's a really valid topic of conversation. I want to open this up and let's see if we can come up with some solutions
But I do think you're right and I do think it is because of an antiquated
Performing rights
System outside of the United States
I'll let's stay in Germany for a second
Hello, Deutschland
Hi, Adam this is Thomas long time listener from Germany
I'm 41 years old and I work as an anesthesiologist in a common hospital
I'm also a mech user and I wanted if you know having switched to windows know that if you ever use your
I'm making a home for the production of Charlie and if so for which step in production process
Come on give us a little geek talk every now and then okay bye home and folder
You want some geek talk man. You want more geek talk
All right, let me play this first. Don't give you some geek talk
Hey Adam it's ID which are initials, but only a few people know what this can't for
But feel free to guess and I'll tell you if you're right
I've been listening to the Charlie since you started way away back when and I just wanted to tell you that I adore you
Patration of course your gorgeous kid
I love the family dynamic. Thanks for inviting all of this podcast or specialist guys into your world
Um, recently I've been listening to two weeks with the Charlie that a time meaning I'm sitting at work
Catching up and generally
I'll have a comment. I want to add but
The relevance you've got you passed. It seems that topics to ground longer on podcasts and they do another media
However for me to come and I'm something that happens in weeks to go seems a little silly
So generally I don't call or send something to you
However, I could want to ask you how you're mad. Hold on before you ask me that
Yeah, that's a really valid point sometimes it gets kind of complicated
Where I'll get comments really good comments on a topic that that you know occurred maybe weeks ago
And that you're right. That's why sometimes this stuff does get drawn out a little bit longer
I haven't quite found a solution for yet, but you know that is kind of the whole
You know the there's beauty to the
Time shifting and there's some downside from the production and to the things
However, and good want to ask you how your math was and if you were back on your math, they're still working on your PC
I either missed that update so very very long ago or you didn't tell us
I'm really happy to hear the object that worked well for you
We can both think my red stick computer geek flashboy friend Wayne
So the amazing ability and finding that particular piece of software
I also wanted to tell you how amazingly impressive your ability to go on with such a busy schedule
after your mother's passing
She seems like such an amazing woman and I just get the positive feeling that she's proud of you wherever her energy resides
Thank you so much for all of your efforts and thanks so very much for the hours of entertainment
Information and content that make my work day bearable and so very much less dramatic than it normally would be
I adore you so I'm a further by
That's very cute. Thank you very flattering
Okay, so for our German friend and
This young lady, you know what it's it's funny
I don't use a Mac at all. I have not used a Mac in weeks. It's maybe even months ever since I got the Sony Vio
And I haven't given you an update now of course. Yes Patricia has an eye Mac downstairs
I've got an eye Mac in the curry condo. We use that pretty much exclusively for video conferencing
Patricia uses the eye Mac
for looking at real estate websites predominantly and she loves it so and and I do enjoy you know
Just grab in the Mac and and getting something done sometimes. However, I do immediately notice that the whole user interface
Everything's a little less snappy than on windows. It does have that nice kind of rounded edge polished feel to it
But I have not missed my Mac at all. I've thoroughly enjoyed the amount of applications that are available for the windows platform
As an example
I do my video
show
per version for profit. I do that on
A PC program called visual communicator. I've not found anything well there are programs. Please don't send me a million links
Yes, there of course there are programs for this on the Mac as well, but this one really floated my boat and the performance is great
The speed of this machine. It's a dual dual core
Intel processor is
Very fast and coding goes very fast. I'm just generally extremely pleased battery life fantastic
It's not exploding which is nice
Even though it's a Sony and a Sony battery is not overheating
But I can literally you know undock and and use my my via for hours
Doing anything not having to take any kind of you know, I just select the via optimize power setting whatever the hell it is
You know once you get used to the machine
Then then you kind of know you know what works best and it's it's fantastic
And it's light too. It's very very light. It's lighter than any than any Mac book
It feels a little less durable of course. It's more plastic
I love the built-in webcam. I know you can get that on a Mac too, but I'm just giving you all the
I'm giving you everything. It just feels good. I'm loving it. I am I'm not missing the Mac at all. Do I like Mac?
Absolutely
Although I must say in all the audio production I've done on Macs. I think that I've had a more enjoyable experience using
Adobe audition on the PC for a number of reasons
Not the least of which is the speed and the stability of the programs and
Just seems to be less hassle once you've figured out how the audio works
You know on the Mac you have to figure out how audio is routed and works and what control panels you need
to find that on the PC. It is a little bit different
But once you're in it, I don't know. I'm sorry to say I just really don't see a difference in productivity
I've been able to get all the keystrokes down to what I want to get it to. I'm feeling very good about the PC
No real issues now
I have done some aesthetics that make me feel better. I'm not using I'm using the actual Mac background
that you would find by default installed on any Mac computer product
I have a dock down at the bottom so it kind of emulates
It emulates a Mac. I have Mac icons
That's another thing. I just I didn't want to have to get used to windows icon. So I use Mac icons. No problem. It's just a
aesthetics, right? And I kind of enjoy the task bar. That is kind of fun to have stuff sitting there and all kinds of
programs out of the way that only pop up when you need them. So in general, very very happy with the experience
All right. It's gonna be a little bit long today's show, but I did just want to play a couple more things for you.
Hello Adam. This is Karen from Virginia. I'm responding to your request for listener profiles
My day job is as a social worker and part-time tour guide on the weekends at a local history site
I've been listening to the Charlie since about October
The podcast I'm going to hawk shamelessly is music Virginia dot potio dot com focusing on
Artists from Virginia and I just turned 48. I'm divorced and proud of it. He doesn't even know what he missed and
Let's see right now. Those kind of relationships just are not
For me so and believe me you would not want to see a naked picture of me and about the big debate
Suscending from the from the bottom or over the top doesn't matter as long as it's there when you need it and I'm a folder
And can I say tailwinds even if I'm not a pilot? Bye. No, not really
But you made me so happy with all the other stuff you said. It's okay
Thank you. I've been saving all of these listener profiles that you've been calling in. I have I must have about
150 now and
I'm going to if you don't mind share those with our
Business development and sales department
Because I'm I think I'm getting a very good idea of what the audience make up is and
I'd like to be able to bring you more relevant advertising relevant to you
um
And I and just on a personal note
I'm really really enjoying learning about you guys
I'm
I'm not surprised about the average age which seems to be around 33 32 33 I should do the math
Not surprised well now. I am surprised about the type of jobs you guys have and what you do for a living and where you listen
I this just it's totally blowing me away and I really appreciate you sending that in it's
I think if if I know you better I'll be able to serve you better
Are you being so kind of so if you bet about any chance?
Hey Adam
This is listener dug and Utah checking in with a little item on a Dutch invasion of Germany
Yeah, I know that's a reversal in historical trend
Nevertheless in the Sunday New York Times
We can review section there's a little blurb at
About how the
Germans are upset even pissed off with the Dutch because
While the Dutch are doing nothing to close down the coffee shops in Holland
relying on the tax revenue from the
200 million dollar annual trade
They have nevertheless crack down on the growers
And so the growers have moved to the forests of Germany and the Germans are having trouble controlling the Dutch growers in Germany
This seems particularly odd. I don't know if there's violence involved which would not seem particularly
Dutch
But apparently all the seed contest and so on that's all in a longer being produced in Holland, but in the forests of Germany
I thought that'd be an interesting
Curry for 20 like moment for
Okay, this is dug out. Oh, I dug nice. Well, you know
It's this is almost like the national hobby in the Netherlands not a day goes by
Well, you don't read in at least one of the newspapers about some apartment or some home or you know just the some in conspicuous dwelling
Usually in in a in a in a structure of more of the same types of dwellings hence apartments
That it doesn't turn out to be just rented by someone who is not living there, but has several hundred plants growing
And they usually steal electricity. This is the the only guys who are really going after this big time as far as I can tell in in the Netherlands is the electric companies
Because it takes so much energy and they're losing their quote losing so much revenue on
On these growers these illegal growers that they're the ones that are basically finding out who's doing what they look in
They look at anomalies. I guess across there they're power grid and then they zoom in and it's more for those guys than anything
That that they're being hunted down, but it seems like everyone is doing it everyone is growing it
And I think you're I know we got the $200 million annual trade number from I think it's much much higher than that much higher
Oh, yeah, gobs higher no doubt about it and it's being transported throughout all of Europe
I mean the Netherlands is is I think the number one producing country now
Really really huge
So no wonder that they're moving down south through Belgium that they're moving over towards the east towards Germany
It's just I think it's that they're probably not even going for any other reason then the power company to
On quite as hip over there to what's happening
Is their violence involved? No, I have yet to read one report of actual violence involved
These growers
Particularly if they're smoking their own dope. No, I'm saying
The New York City to wind up today's Charlie Jody Aaron and orange soda
Sips it on the coke and round
Wish I had an orange soda
To cool me down and quench my thirst
The only question in my mind
Would be a great could have tasted
And if this world exists
If it goes beyond my dreams we could take me there
So that we can share
That's one
We shall was a roller coaster
Making people scream all day long
Come on climb up to the time
Everybody sing my song
Listen
And if this world exists
If it goes beyond my dreams we could take me there
So that we can share
That's one
And they see
And if this world exists
If it goes beyond my dreams we could take me there
So that we can share
Life's more than it makes more than it makes more than it makes more than it makes
Wish I had an orange soda
Yeah that'd be nice nice orange soda
Jody Aaron from the pot set music network links to that in the show notes the daily source code dot com where you can comment on today's episode
You can find all kinds of links all kinds of stuff. It's groovy. Come on over dig me
Everybody this was fun. I'll talk to you tomorrow. Of course a Friday. We're flying to Amsterdam
I'm gonna try that trip again
So I'm not sure if we should be able to do a show maybe I'll do one Thursday night for you
DailySourceco.com adamantpodshow.com take care everybody bye bye
Yeah
This podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from podshow and line-white networks