Potcho is pleased to bring you the following killer content direct from the all new feature-richpotcho.com
Get it! Play it! Dig it! Dig it!
The third and fourth edition folder, for your own problems with your family.
With 15 keys, a gun just stuffed in the truck.
Bigel! The five packs are split up right out.
We don't need no naked man!
It's Adam Curry. This is DSC 495.
I was 16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
podcasting is Adam Curry. Adam Adam, a lot of curry.
Podcasting from Gilford, a supper-look serving,
is shows called the Charlie DSC or the Chacha.
He fires up slips in spite of the law.
Ha! Travels the globe open new markets like Nixon.
Plates for naked pictures from PMM fixings.
Lady Patricia, how what can one say?
When she co-hosts it's just like a bright Sunday.
He's the pod father who normally isn't the one.
Daughter Christina's PSTQ is such fun.
She cracks on the pikes and likes to rock out.
Something Adam's pink is going to fall in.
That was all about.
The penis sponsor is birthed in Go Daddy and Smanda.
What's out five shows a week and sometimes a week end up.
His calls from CSB Uncle Jesse and some of them are odd.
He's a confidate as his courtesy of Jersey Todd.
The police hides might be red and he doesn't act hurried.
Don't think that his podcasting vision is blurred.
He has grand plans and great schemes even bolder.
He's not a scruncher of a roller just upon a fight for me.
Yes, she avoids the sun is creeping in.
Through that she cuts us onto the bed she's lying in.
And with weary eyes she turns to the face of shame.
She can't hide the snow these skies with his.
And now she cries to what she's lost with tears she whispered.
And in the dark the dead of night she holds his back.
Turn out the light.
Through the lijn and sheets,
you hit the lights a life bread.
I'm a scar of the leaves she lies a secret
She can't let go, she can't let go, she can't let go
And now she cries through what she's lost
It's eerie eyes, she whispered
And in the dark, the dead of night
She holds his hand out the light
And now she cries through what she's lost
It's eerie eyes, she can't let go, she can't let go
It's eerie eyes, she whispered
Yeah, I really don't know what it is
Not actually, I think I do, I think it's the radio guy in me
When of the days get shorter, the nights get longer and darker
And the weather gets a little grisly
Chili and rainy, you just want to pull out records that kind of reflect that mood
Which of course completely breaks down if you're listening to the daily source code
In Australia, it's fucking summer over there
It's just years and years of doing the same, I can't really help myself
Hope you don't mind, and the pot's safe music network
That from the UK, the called Cedar Falls
It's the ballad for a lonely heart
What are we today, episode 4?
What are we saying?
Crap, 4.95 already
Can you believe that?
Although I must say, Patricia and I went into Gilbert into town yesterday
And it kind of feels like that season is upon us, you know?
You've got the commercials on television, you've got the lights that are being strung up
They haven't quite been lit yet, but
I don't know if I'm ready for that
Tell us this
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
Brand new week here on the daily source code
Lots of stuff to talk about, had a nice weekend
I hope you had a really nice one
Besides the debugging, which is continuous and ongoing
That's kind of my job to sit over here and debug a number of things
First of all, the UK site, I'm in a different time zone
So I also can do things when other people are catching up on some sleep
And just a whole bunch of little gnarly buggies, particularly the channels
And some feed stuff that got fixed over the weekend
Which is really very nice to see all that
So now everything's updating across the board
I learned a couple things about the system which I didn't know
If you go to patcho.com you look at the homepage
Now we have a, I think Cali Lewis intros
Different piece of the site every day
And then there's a screen cast that goes along with it
The video page, which I believe goes up today or tomorrow
There's stuff in there that I didn't even know was there
It's really fantastic
So yesterday, yesterday we went town
We had a nice day together
I almost didn't do any work until
I think around, let's see, we got up, we had some like a late breakfast
Then we went into town, we walked around, we shot
I bought Patricia a Tom Tom navigation system
Now the Jaguar has a navigator
Or what we call here in the UK
Satinav, satellite navigator
But the interface, the input, the user interface
The way you input information is so completely wrong and confusing
And that's, you can even get over that
But the way it displays the information is just, it's just no good
I mean, it's a very expensive car
And the satinav is just shit
And they're all the same, all Jaguars
The crap, absolute crap
And these Dutch guys who created Tom Tom Go
I believe is the official name
You know, they've taken the world by storm with their systems
And let me tell you, they're doing more than just creating a satellite navigation system
If you haven't seen it, go to TomTom.com
I think it is TomTomGo.com
It has little suction cups you can stick it on the window
It's a nice, small display unit, all touch screen, very fast
But it connects to your phone
And this is, they're really going way beyond giving you satellite navigation information
It connects to your phone through Bluetooth
So you can use it as a speaker phone, you can access
In fact, I was able on the E61, able to access my text messaging
My address book, able to make calls, all hands free
It'll show you who's calling it
It's basically an extension of your phone screen
Which is really fucking cool
And then it can use the data connection
To call out and get information
So I loaded it right up with all of the speed cameras
Which it gives this knife a little
Little radar warning blip
When you were in 500 feet of a speed camera
And there's a couple that I didn't even know
No, I'm not one who speeds off and of course
But I did find a couple that I didn't know about
It can get you weather, you can update the system
It's traffic obviously, it's really, really good shit
These guys are tying in all the bits, love that company
And all car manufacturers really need to take a good look at what they're putting in
System-wise
I don't think I would buy a car with a built-in navigator
If I could leave it off, it was an option
If I could say just don't give it to me, I'll just put one of these in
I'm sure I would do it
Not getting paid for that by the way
It's funny, now I got to display more what I'm not getting paid for
than what I am getting paid for
And so Saturday
The weather was not great
Although the ceilings were good
Broken cloud at 2,000 feet
Scattered at 2.5,000
And then the ceiling was probably about 8 or 9,000
Maybe even higher
Yeah, 8 or 9,000
But there was wind and gusts
Significant gusts, up to 35 knots
But I had a kind of like a
Well, I had a meeting with my banker, Ferdy
And those of you who listened to the show
Or have ever seen any of my pictures, my flicker pictures
You've seen her pop up from time to time
She's been with us for seven years
And she's just fantastic
During the week, so she said I'll just come to
Hill for some international airfield
Which is a grass trip
Just south of Amsterdam
So I'll come there, we'll have some lunch
She always had to go over a couple things
And I want to see her again too
That's always nice to get a personal meeting
Up close and personal
And so Dan and I assessed the weather and said, screw it, let's go
We were doing
Almost, we were doing 197 knots
On the way over, we made it from Farrow
To Hill for seven and an hour and ten minutes
So strong, of course we had the wing in the back
We were flyin' man, was that like 450 kilometers an hour?
It was fantastic
Very, very bumpy, turbulent landing
Because of the crosswind and the gusts
I pulled it off okay, but man
I'd never been in that much crosswind before
And which is kind of the whole point of doing it
And having experience that
Have a nice lunch, she took some pictures
Which I put up on, you can find it at curie.com
I added a flicker set
And so it was really a nice relaxing day
Because when you're flying in general
But certainly in those conditions
You just can't think about anything else
But flying and it's so nice to just take your mind
Completely off of everything
And I was very energized
To dive right back into bug stomping
And QA testing and doing all kinds of stuff
Saturday night
Oh no, good weekend and I hope yours was good as well
And even though we're busy
There are still lots of questions
You always bring the following camera content directly
I really got to change that
Yeah, we're going to install our comment feedback system
The doesn't add a promo like that
So that's on the way
That's one of the things we're going to fix
So this audio of course came from the PDA
It was some positive here
Just with a bit of quick feedback about the new push
So the new unbetter
Is it like an extra level of unless or un-less level of beatiness
Anyway
I know that you say that it is based on feedback directly from people
And so having heard that
I didn't bother saying this beforehand
And quite frankly that I have a lot of time to
Give feedback anymore
Anyway
So happy we could use some of your time then
You
You say it's for listeners
And I certainly have a listener
I listen to a lot of what to us
And quite often I just like to
Download an episode
And listen to it on my MPF player
Which doesn't have Wi-Fi
Or 3G or anything with it
Yeah, I know
Quite probably in the future that
Will be something that MPF players can do
But at the moment
I just have to connect it to my computer
To get a podcast onto it
And
And there's nothing on pod show
That makes that easy
I still have to find the right show site
To find the RSS file
And then go into the RSS file
To find the MPF file
And then have to download it from there
This is really interesting
Once I heard this bit of the piece of feedback
I knew that
That you've been
Consuming podcasts for quite a while
Maybe even making your own
Because anyone who knows to find
The RSS XML file
And then copy it
And then paste that into a browser
Has been doing this for quite a while
And you know I'm going to
I'm going to finish a comment and then I want to respond to this
Because this is really critical
Very important
The link gets it
Might make more sense as a link to the MPF file
Or
Something that would help it
And we download the podcast in
Question because it's just
Still hard to
To download and listen to an episode
Just one episode about having to
Subscribe to the whole thing
Of any of the podcasts
And you want people to be
Other listen to these things
And not just at a computer
Or at some fancy
3G wireless enabled mobile device
So
Just something to think about
For your next level of unbeateness
Just just make it easy for someone to download
One episode
That's all I'm asking for
As a listener
And a folder
Thank you
Good bye
Oh man
Okay, so you make a very good point
And I understand exactly what you're saying
And we did listen to feedback like this
That people wanted a way to just download the file
And
You know, don't think that a lot of
Thought has not gone into
What we do and do not put within pod show
Plus and why we do or do not put it there
And the most dangerous thing I found
And I fall into this all the time
Is if you're used to doing things a certain way
It's very hard to see the simplicity of
Something new
For example
Before I switched over to Windows
I'd been a
At least a 15 year long
Mac user
And my previous experience with Windows
Had been
Windows 95
Windows 98
I actually used for quite a while when we had
Think new ideas
And
I think
NT3.1
But really Windows 98
And I don't think I've ever even played with XP
Except maybe briefly
But not really use it as an operating system
More just as a system to run cast blaster
And
My perception
Of Windows is that it was very complicated
And there was lots of
You know things you had to do differently
And shit that didn't work
And even the
The five dot three naming convention
Was still kind of stuck in my head
Remember that where you couldn't name a file
With any spaces or anything like that on Windows
To this day I still find myself
Not
Writing a file name
With spaces for fear that one thing with
And Windows will not be able to
Understand the space in the
In the path to the file
And it will break something
And it's just something that's in
Great even though I don't have to
Manipulate myself into doing that
Because that's been fixed
And this two with podcasting
We're so used to
Finding an orange and white XML icon
Which I think was the worst marketing exercise
And technology history
Because you basically click on that
As someone who doesn't know what's going on
You get this page of what looks like code
Or a
Just a play link which is a
Direct link to the MP3 file
Boy you can get different results there
Can't you? It might open up the file
And your Windows media player
It might open up a new web page
Or a tab with a quick time plugin
Very dissatisfying experiences
As far as I'm concerned
We really did a lot of testing with people who
Were not familiar with all of these
I'll just call it the baggage of podcasting
If you will or the baggage of
Indicated content
Because that's really what it is
We have to move one step beyond
So when someone comes into pod show
Plus and they see a very simple play it
I think that kind of solves the first
Issue of I just want to play something
Then if you want to
Subscribe to something
We've even taken the subscription moniker
Because it's just to complicate
People think it costs money and they stay away from it
This is from tests really user tests
And not small ones either
You know we really do evaluate this stuff
New people not all people not
Exit not podcasters not people who have been
Listening and and chugging along
And copying links and being heroic at
Getting this content delivered to them
So when you click on play it
It opens up what we call the mashboard
And no one has complained about that
Everyone loves the new layout
Love the organization
And right there is a link that says download
So if you want to download it
You click on that file and it will download
To your wherever you have your download set
So usually to your desktop
So that's where we solved it
I don't believe that people are
Looking for the experience anymore
Of clicking on a link and then having
Something unrelated
Almost happened playing a file
Within a quick time plugin
And a big white page just doesn't
Makes sense to me from a media perspective
So that's why
We don't put the download link
Right there underneath play it
It may be handy for you
But I think it's you know this one
Extra click to get to the download link
And you know you could of course
Subscribe with a number of different programs
To get it onto your
On to your portable device
And we actually have a little
Widget for that in the works to make that even easier
But the way things are going
We feel that we've made the right choices
And we have done it based upon
Audience feedback and you don't sound to me
Like your typical audience member
I think you've been along for the ride for a while
So again, just think of things that
You were completely convinced
Would just suck about a product or a service
Because you've experienced it
In the past
And what's another good example
Like
The MSN, MSN chat
Oh man, that used to suck so bad
And I've really stayed away from it
And except I installed it recently
Because that's what Christina uses
And I see all these changes and all these upgrades that I've been made
And I think you know I've been such an early adopter
That the big massive people who are now seeing this type of
Channel application are seeing it in a whole different light
And are getting a whole different experience
From the get go
So it's really about the experience that audience members
Who are not familiar with how it works under the hood
It's really what they're looking for
They just want to point and click experience
And I would have to be very honest with you that
Obviously for mobile devices
We have two main focuses
One is the iPod and iTunes
Which we support fully
Right down to the iTunes namespace in the RSS
And the other would be mobile devices
Because it looks like Microsoft
Is not going to be supporting podcasting in the next year or so
And this is purely because of time
It wasn't talking about the zoom that it's not supporting podcasting
No, it's not
And it doesn't do a whole bunch of really cool things
Like synchronized wirelessly through Wi-Fi
Which I believe technically it has the capability
I think it has the hardware
No one's really told me if it was a Wi-Fi connection that's in there
But it's kind of the same thing
This is
What can we do to actually support that device
I have some ideas
They will support podcasting
They just didn't have time
They didn't need to get something out quickly
And they kind of followed the route of let's license
They made some
Not very courageous decisions
Let's put it that way
And I think that they underestimate
The power of podcasters
If podcasters could
Have had and maybe they still can have some influence
On what the zoom will do
In regards to podcasters
Oh man, I mean talk about some major adoption
Talk about people with real audiences
Who can really promote a product that they would love
What an opportunity, what a missed opportunity
I don't know how I got there
You know what?
I would like to hear what you have to say about it
We got the voice mail lines wide open of course
6-2-5-6-3-5-7
Good old Peter
Who like he has nothing better to do on his weekends
He said hey man, you never mentioned the UK number anymore
It's probably because you don't have a phone jingle
So let me do one for you
4-2-0-7-6-8-1-3-7-5-3
Ah, you are just too kind here
Oh man
You open up the door and he comes right in
But in a close window
The satellite repairman
Coming after you
What's he gonna do?
He'll fit your misconceptions and answer questions
Dude, there's nothing in the universe
And he can't do for you
The satellite repairman
That's right everybody
Uncle Jesse, I'm the way to close satellite window
And have so much more to do
I got Roger Smalls
I've got an awesome song
Another pot-safe song coming up
Ah, a response from
Ah, from the inside works folks
About about port city PD
Unfortunately, you're going to miss that
If you're listening to this on
Serious satellite radio
Channel stars 102
So be sure to go over to dailysourceco.com
To download the show
You can find it from the handy download link on the
Mashboard after you click play it
Take care, bye
Meanwhile, you guys are still here
And this young man
How's he going?
Thanks a million for saying
Liberty Jones
And that your support
And all the podcasts is getting behind this
It's been massive help
We're playing podcast convention
Accessfield in London on the 18th of this month
He's coming along
And he's trying to introduce us
We'd be really faced
And so
That's right
And catch you down
Cheers bye
That's so cool
So the shakes
And I wonder sometimes
I'm so tuned into the
To the accent
That I understand that perfectly
Excuse me, since I was blind
I should be saying
Folders with Splendid, I guess
I don't know, not paying me
Yeah
I was wondering if you can always
Understand what the if you're in the US
What the English folks are saying
Because sometimes it sounds
A little rough through the phone
But anyway, shakes performing at podcasts
On UK
This coming Saturday the 18th
As far as I know
I'm in pocket
I'm going to be there
We're going to finalize plans
I think I just might go
I don't know if I should go next week
Because next week is kind of like
Thanksgiving week
I'm just not sure
I have half a mind to go next week
Maybe visit some family for Thanksgiving
And then stay
The next week
And then come back
Which will make it a little
Make it a December
Or maybe I go this after Thanksgiving
That's right
And stay the first week of December
Something like that
Just before Christmas
I want to get a visit in
I have no idea why I said that
I'm spacing out a little bit today
Let me see what else I have on my list
I had some things I wanted to mention
Oh yeah
Catscast
Catscast.podshow.com
She put in some old footage
From when we did a live broadcast
From Vegas
You should definitely see that
If you want to see more embarrassing shots of me
At the time I married
Seven couples
Who were prize winners
That's a promotion man
That's the kind of stuff I love doing
We got to do some more of that
Yeah
That's the kind of stuff I love doing
We got to do some more of that
She's ready
Y'all
Here's another message
Wrong
Rages
No
Stop
Hey, I don't like your hair
Just be listening to your argument with Patricia
On four nights free
About British and shit
I just like to confirm that you're right
You're not flat to share an erect penis
On television
On many branches
On every branch
My hard work
Well, of course
Thanks
So thank you
Mr.
I tell you what, if you come up to me at podcastcon, UK, this coming Saturday, I will give
you my new address because I'd love to meet you.
Everybody wants to meet Roger Smalls and isn't it interesting how you don't hear from
the guy from months?
I'm telling you what, three months at least, Roger and then all of a sudden, just around
the time that there's an event happening podcastcon, UK, it starts to kind of heat up a
little bit and sometimes I wonder if that isn't by design.
You're not just your regular run of the mill stalker but something special going on.
Why?
In fact, I know there's something special going on with you, Roger.
Yes, censorship in the UK, I've got a lot of response on that people, a lot of people
mention that indeed you are not allowed to show a fully-recpiness on television or I guess
not in any other type of publication in the UK is that true or in the changing room
with more suspense, especially the Guilford Branche.
He has indeed Roger, I'm sure that's a problem.
Speaking of censorship, last week I received a piece of audio feedback from Robin and
Suzanne from InsideWorks and we've had lots of these delayed back and forth conversations
between shows, particularly here on the source code and they were very offended about the
promo that we were running for port city PD, our new cop show which you can find at port
citypeditapodshow.com, it's a great show.
They said it couldn't be on the homepage and I basically threw it back at them and said,
hey, look, it sounds like you guys got some baggage and you're projecting that onto me and
these are your personal issues and that we don't censor content.
We want everyone to have a fair shake no matter what it is.
We should have the bedtime stories, my kids read, that should be on the homepage but it
needs to be switched around.
We need to be able to get the audience that is out there, this is craving for stuff and
when it was deeper into it, I said, hey, port citypedita, you know that violence, you know.
And what is violence, you know, do you see any blood in the promo now?
Your average one of the day, you know, episode of cops is more violent than that.
It's also real and they responded, which is really nice.
Hi, Adam, this is Suzanne and Robin from InsightWorks and the Deva cast and we want to
respond to your DSC 492 from 8 November regarding our thoughts on port cityped.
Suzanne and I've talked a lot about this since you're a lot, Adam, thanks for not censoring
us.
Thank you.
Well, we realized as we came to this from different perspectives, Suzanne and I,
number one, Suzanne is anti violence.
Number two, I was approaching it from a business perspective.
And number three, we had a couple things in common that we really felt about that promo.
So first, Adam, regarding me and my anti violence stance, I realized you are so right.
Oh, my gosh, this is my stuff.
I own it.
It's my baggage that I was trying to thrust upon you.
So thank you for pointing that out to me and what I really had to figure out was why I was
doing that and what I've concluded is, as a family therapist, I am saturated with violence
and my day-to-day work.
I work with battered women, inner city kids, right now I'm working with clients in the
judicial system.
I see a lot of stuff.
So for me then, when I want to watch something to relax and for entertainment, it's really
uncomfortable for me then to go and sit watch anything else that's more violent because
I feel like I kind of live that.
So that you are so right, it is my stuff.
And for me, I watched Port City PD, one of the episodes I liked it.
Well, actually, I did too.
So I'm not nearly as anti violence as Suzanne and I'm not.
Well, it wasn't very violent.
You know, when I actually watched it, it wasn't very violent.
Right.
From my perspective, I was more concerned about the business aspect of having that
promo on the front page of Potcho.
I like the diversity within Potcho.
That's what I want to convey is, I'm not against any content in the Potcho system.
I'm not.
I think it's fantastic.
That's what's going to make Potcho bigger and better.
And it's a symbiotic relationship.
When I grow my audience, it helps Potcho when Potcho has a bigger audience.
I have the opportunity for new audience members.
So it's a benefit to all of us.
I like the diversity.
I don't want to censor any of it.
From the business perspective, I see that front page of Potcho has been a really
critical space.
And people will judge what's beyond that page by what's on the page.
It's a delicate balance.
I really don't know the answer.
I have noticed in the past, if I remember right,
when Mark Yoshimura Nemkoff had wears my fucking latte, when the promo first came out,
it was fucking.
And now it's f-striking.
So somewhere it changed, I don't know.
I just got a jump in there.
This is lovely, guys.
I think, as far as I know, Mark Yoshimura Nemkoff censored that himself, the reason
I believe was to be able to get it onto iTunes.
So I think he censored it for iTunes to pick it up, otherwise it's not even the explicit
label doesn't work.
They just won't display it.
I believe that's what's happening.
But I'm sure Mark will correct me if I'm wrong in that.
But as far as I know, obviously no censorship from Potcho on that.
Well, I think it was your censorship.
That's for sure.
But something changed.
And so I just approach the whole thing from that business perspective.
Right.
But what we do agree on Adam is no censorship.
And when you use that word, that really stunned for me, because I thought, oh my God,
you're calling me on my stuff.
And how could I be censoring something?
Robin and I were both active, duty, military.
We fought for the right for people for our first amendment and to be able to burn the flag.
And a few years ago, remember hunting when we got into a big debate.
We got into an argument with some other people.
They want to do have legislation so that people could not burn the flag.
And I said, that's insane.
It is exactly what this country is about to have the right to say what and do what you want
to do.
Last thing I wanted to bring up was grief.
I do my very best not to judge anybody else's pain.
The death of your mom, the death of my mom, we have both suffered a huge loss.
And I make no judgments that yours was any worse than mine or mine was any worse than yours.
So Adam, thank you for listening to us and helping us get clarity on our own thoughts.
I'm sorry if we exasperated you, but we sure appreciate your time and energy in responding
to us.
Thanks so much and bye for now.
Love you, man.
They'll win.
You know, I love you guys too.
And I really mean it because you made some real from the heart comments.
I was able to make some real from the heart from the soul comments back.
And we've come to some resolution here.
We still kind of agreed to disagree.
That's okay.
But you're right.
It is totally all about balance.
And you know, it's everything we do is about a balance.
That's what I guess what media is in a way, you know, because everybody's different
and you want to be able to reach as many people as possible and send them in the direction
they want to go.
I don't want to force anything on anyone.
I don't want people to have to watch something that they don't want to.
But yet there's a, there is a fine line between serendipity and discovery and searching
and context and all of those things.
And, you know, we're finding our way too and it ain't easy.
But this type of feedback helps.
There's a lot of feedback that really, really has helped tremendously that I've received
over, over the course of our unleashed.
And another one I'm going to play for you right after this, which I think you're like,
I liked it a lot.
But first something else from the Pod Save Music Network, which is also close to my
heart from the Sunshine Variety Club, simply titled Green.
I like Green.
When I think of all the colours in my rainbow, it's only one thing.
That's right, me too.
The Bond Mix of the Sunshine Variety Club's Green.
And I'm just noticing something on the Pod Save Music Network.
I guess we have the option to sell a track now enabled for any artist to sell their
stuff, 99 cents for any track you find on the Pod Save Music Network.
You get a little store, so a little area.
So if you buy something, you can go back and download it again and again and again.
That's DRM-free MP3, which means the artist is building up a trust relationship with
you.
Pod Show takes nothing of that money.
Nine cents goes to the transaction company and the full 90 cents is passed on to the
artist.
We will make fees available for people to hell is that, oh, it's the last one, hold on one
second.
That's a big funny.
Hey, moody.
I'm recording the source code, man, can I call you right back?
The hell are you doing up?
It's early.
I didn't run.
Screw that.
Okay, buddy.
I'll call you back in about half an hour.
I don't know where anybody is these days.
He's in London.
Sorry about that.
So what I don't know yet is if this bylink is also surfacing on Pod Show.com slash music,
you don't have to check that out.
I hope it does because that's kind of the whole point.
That's really the listener side.
But it is surfacing.
It is working.
So if you have tracks on the Pod Show music network, you want to sell it.
You want to get 90 cents per track, not a problem.
It's just a matter of ticking off a box on each track that you want to put up for sale.
All right, one last one about the unbated.
This one I thought was pretty cool and just goes to show how, even how obvious things
are how people still don't see them.
And it's not their fault.
It's completely our fault.
Hey Adam, it's Chip from Top of the Pod SACE.
First of all, I want to commend you with a wonderful job everybody's done with the Pod
Show.
Plus, unbated version, it's exactly what everybody's been asking for.
It's amazing.
I'm loving it.
I love going on the Pod Show.com slash music part of it and looking down at the bottom
right.
You can just refresh the web page and you get a different top 10 list every time.
Like Top 10 Accapellas or something like that.
That's really, really cool.
Plus, I've been messing with my profile and my shows profile that set it up even better.
And it's easier to use than the original version was, the beta version.
So hats off to you and everybody.
I know everybody's been working hard and probably everybody's gained a lot of gray hairs
from it.
But it's really paying off.
It really is.
I got a question for you because I know that you use cast blaster and I've been using it
for a while now and love it and I really enjoy the live vibe that I get from doing
it even though I'm not very professional at what I do.
But I haven't been able to figure out how to do this one thing.
And that is to use the full functionality of cast blaster.
Right now what I do is I'm making MP3 with cast blaster and I save it to a file and then
I use that file to go into the pod show plus.
I'll write my show notes including the hyperlinks and I'll paste it into the online area
on pod show and then attach the MP3 to it in upload.
But I know in the configuration of cast blaster there's an area in the bottom right
that says server and it has an address you can put in your email address or password and
then there's a little box to click that says use pod show servers.
And then you should be able to I guess publish it and instead of hit and save as in the
save show you could actually upload the show to the server directly.
Now how do you do that?
What is the address that everyone needs to search for to do that and pass wars and all that
kind of stuff?
I'm so glad you asked this okay so this is what's kind of interesting.
This is definitely not clear in the application I'm just going to go to the configured
tab here.
So it says server of course you know I think there it should give a little more on those
let's see what's in the help hold on a second.
Mike has always done a good job of help let's see under Configure let me go to server.
Here's server.
Enter your podcast server details here address is the URL of the server example www.mysite.com
slash my podcast user is your login name password is your password note that the download
path is often not the same as the upload path for example if your podcasts are being downloaded
from blah blah blah blah okay so we have to work on that particular piece of help I don't
think that really is saying what's happening there.
Let me explain it to you if you would just play along with me for a second go to the Configure
tab in in Casplaster so that's server part now you can actually enter a FTP server in the address
so if you would have so for instance I have what is it let's just say I have FTP.curry.com
so there I'd put FTP.curry.com and then my email address that is also incorrect that would
typically be then the user name and password would be the password and so what it does is
when you click publish first you save the file then you upload the server it will open an
FTP connection shoot that up to the FTP server put it in the proper place as defined by
the path in the address and you know just basically upload your show there and then you still
have to do all the manual you know linking to it etc. from a web page and you still have
to do the RSS feed if you want people to be able to subscribe to it so if you click use
podshow servers pdn the address field you get a whole bunch of asterixes and then you enter
your basically your your podshow credentials so your my login is adam at curry.com that's why
it says email address because your your login on podshow plus is your email address that you
supplied when you signed up and the password is the password that's associated with it that's how
you configure it and that's how you get upon clicking the publish button that's how it then
gets sent up to the podshow delivery network and how it automatically is added to your list of
shows the show is put into your RSS feed and well I think you're gonna be able to get it to work
also if I put my show notes in the cast blaster show notes and I do get this upload functionality
to work will the show note show up just like as if I was doing it in the version I do now with the
hyperlinks and all that kind of stuff in there just curious on your comments with that oh by the way
also I've got another another question for you hold on let me address this first so yes the answer is
when you do that not only does the file get uploaded and inserted into your RSS feed but everything
you have under the described tab so the title the episode subtitle summary the show notes the
tags all of those are filled out on your episode page automatically so you only have to do it once you'll
also see in there under show if you have more than one show you can select a different show to upload to
now all of this metadata by the way is also written into the ID3 tags of the file so if you open that
up on a player that understands how to read this data it will show all of that including the image
that you put into it that'll be the album art and although it's already working under the hood and
hasn't quite surfaced yet on pod show plus the image art will also be associated with each episode
on the web page so it'll actually be pulling that out as well so it is a beautiful process created by
people who make podcast myself as a primary tester but if you go to castblaster.com
there's a great lively community there for them with people talking about all kinds of stuff in
fact there's already a pro version in the works of which I have an alpha version haven't really
had the time to mess with it in a real life production situation because you know it's alpha so it
could mess up and I usually when I'm doing the show I'm fitting it in between doing a whole
bunch of other things so I just didn't have the time to really do it properly and for what I see
Mike is also working on a video version of castblaster so it's quite a powerful platform and the
beauty of it is it's all in one self-contained little beautiful package you record you click save
you I always like having a copy on my hard drive and you hit you know upload to server it's done
it's it's published everything is taken care of no more copying pacing of any stuff it's just
in there it works and it's a beautiful thing you had one more thing I'm an ass cruncher but a
nose folder so does that mean I need to search for professional help anything you can say to me
with help a lot thank you it's interesting because I too have noticed that I have cruncher tendencies
as I am an ass folder and a nose cruncher the interesting isn't it maybe we should seek help
maybe we should all right everybody that's it for today I'll be back tomorrow with another source
code will be up to 496 working on the 500 not doing not I don't have anything special plan but
would not mind intros for 96 97 98 99 and 500 and beyond I love it when you guys do that take
everybody have a great day bye get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high
performance podcast delivery network from pod show and limelight networks I love it