Let's see, sound, yeah, spliff, yeah, senseo, yep, oh, we're good to go.
Delta Sierra Charly 311, $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next
generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just taking this battle curry.
Hey, you're a dude, isn't it?
Yeah.
I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do.
Oh!
20 years of winter tired, give up blow when you do it last.
The huge ballad, a huge ballad, a huge ballad, I do, you, you, you, you, you, while my mom dat I.
That's all
Time will die
Never take it
I'll take it
Time will die
Time to die
I'll take it
Time will die
It's forever
In the world
They'll be fine, we'll be in a skylight
But it's fine, but it's fine, but it's fine
But it's fine, but it's fine
They'll be fine, but it's fine
It'll be fine, but it's fine
But it's fine, but it's fine, but it's fine
They'll be fine, but it's fine
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, real, got a fine and another thatア'll win the hit will the life. Tearалиu you tell a lot of things I hear. yeah, yeah, yes, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah
oh
Goes without saying that you just can't go wrong in a Friday
with too much cowbell.
Golden Gods, found them thanks to Todd,
walked out, he sent me, I actually showed up this morning
in my email, he said, check out the Golden Gods
on the Podsate Music Network, totally dig it.
Just can't get too much cowbell.
I see that from the streets of London,
the cornfields of Iowa and the Gold Coast of California.
As they say, the Golden Gods make the kind of rock
and roll, you'd only find in your stone
or uncle's record collection.
Yep, somewhere I'm somebody's stone or uncle, I guess.
Back to doing the Delta Shara Charli Tag
at the beginning of the show.
Even if I vary to just a little bit,
you guys really seem to need that
for your mobile purposes.
So we'll just keep doing the tags at the beginning.
Hey, everybody, it's Friday.
Hi, yeah.
Last show of the week for me.
You know, I'm getting ready to head off to the Bay area.
And today we're going to do not just the Metro sexual moment,
but also we have got a Trinity segment.
And dude, the news came in yesterday
about John Stewart hosting the Oscars.
Wow, man.
That's going to be an awesome show.
I'm sure of it.
This guy is so good.
I finally found out where to where I can see the daily show
over here.
It's on, if you're in the UK,
he's on Sky Channel 165.
That's more for I think is the name of that channel.
They got some really good stuff on that.
So now I've pre-programmed everything.
Now I've got all the,
it's basically like a Tivo only.
It's made by Sky.
And you know, it doesn't have all the cool Tivo things.
As far as I know, I don't know if anyone hacking these
these skyboxes yet.
But now I also can record the tonight show
and late night with Conan, although, I don't think
I don't usually watch that.
Once in a while, I have an interesting guest on.
No letterman, unfortunately.
Boy, I certainly was able to see the letterman
or Riley bit didn't take long for that
to show up all over the net.
That's what I love about this stuff, man.
It's like, if something's, if someone's talking about it,
you'll get a hold of it.
You don't even have to go searching for anything.
It just kind of pops up.
Some friend will send that right along to you.
So congratulations to John Stewart.
That is phenomenal.
Man, and he is, he seems like,
I wish I could hook up with him again.
His people will definitely facilitate a meeting
if I have a proposal.
But I don't really have a proposal for him yet.
Nothing that'll make his people happy, I don't think.
Working on that.
But he was cool when he worked at MTV.
We worked at the first MTV B-Chowst together for a while.
Isn't this nice guy?
I genuinely think that he is the same guy
that you see on TV.
Okay, what else will we do today?
Some more pod save music now.
Oh, also a bug in my Macintosh,
one that I don't think has been documented very widely
and kind of stumbled on this bug by accident.
Let's do that right now, hold on a second.
I actually had some pro most stuff.
Well, you know what?
Now, I'll tell you what.
I got some really cool promos.
I think you'll like these three in a row.
I've been very selective today.
So listen those three promos.
Then we're gonna talk about this Mac audio program,
problem, this bug, which I'm not the only one
that has it and it's a really freaky one.
And quite honestly, it's pissing me off
as a podcaster who uses his Mac for sound.
What's up, everybody?
Hey guys.
This is Kyle.
And this is Jamie.
We do the naughty karate podcast.
On iTunes.
When you got a chance, check out our boy Squid.
Yeah, that's how that sounds like.
Yeah, that sounds like a comic book.
Six, six, three.
Did you hear it?
That was exactly what I was talking about.
And that's fathobo.com.
And after you check that out, check us out
where at naughtycaraddy.com.
Forever dudes.
Hi, yeah.
That was just around house, kicked to the face.
Hey Adam, it's J. Martinez from the TechX Podcast.
Feats.febrater.com slash TechX.
Just sending you some audio feedback to say thank you
for playing my promo on DSC 308.
I've gone for about 40 listeners then to about 124
as a 1224 PM today, January 5th.
And it's all thanks to you and Father Rodrick
from the Catholic Insider.
I just want to say thank you.
And I will be recording more.
And hopefully you'll stay subscribed.
And enjoy the rest.
Tonight, I'm just going to give you guys a preview
is called the title tonight's podcast,
which I'm going to be recording is called Abroca Password.
So if you'll tune in and enjoy what I have to say.
P to you later.
Oh, God, Christmas vacation.
Why have you done to me?
I've become a mini a chair out of curry.
I have botsers wedged at my butt.
I'm drinking, not some to say oh, but scar books.
And perfect.
Oh.
If this is happening to you and your podcasting daily,
you're a hardcore podcaster.
And you need to rock on man,
one of the revolution.
Yeah.
Paid for by the Confused Casc Confused.
Hyphen Casc.BlogSpot.com.
Find our feedback.
Feed Scott FeedBurner.com slash Confused Casc.
And email us at Confused.CascacGameel.com.
Peace out podcasting rocks.
That's about R-O-X-P-B-O-C.
Yo, woo, elite.
I got to lift that one, T-S.
It's the revolution.
That's great.
He's 13, a budding podcaster,
doing just fine as far as I can tell.
So you heard it.
You heard the problem.
Some other people had heard this before.
In fact, Tim Pritlove said that he's kind of,
he admits he's sort of happy that I ran into the same audio
loop problems with my power book
in the last few minutes of Delta Sheriff Charlie 309.
This bug seems to be related to the new 15-inch power book
with optical audio interfaces only.
OK, I have the 15-inch power book.
I don't exactly know what the optical audio interfaces are.
Does that mean there's something new going on inside?
Tim says he's suffering from the same problem.
And he knows at least three other people
with the same configuration with exactly the same problem.
He goes, and I think it would be helpful if you could bring
this one up in one of your next shows.
It's a really nasty bug affecting all podcasters.
And it more than one time ruined my recordings.
This is very, very freaky.
Now, I know that certainly some people
had Apple listened to this podcast.
So let's find out about it.
Is it something that can be fixed?
Is it a hardware problem?
Or is it a software problem?
It certainly seems to be very intermittent.
I actually rebooted my computer before doing the show,
just to make sure that I'd be kind of fresh with a clean boot up.
And amazing.
You don't hear it happen very often.
It usually happens when I'm using, you know what?
It could be a quick time thing.
Because I think that it only happens when I'm using iTunes,
when I'm using a quick time, I'm trying to think
if it's ever happened while I was watching like a Windows
media clip or something.
That could be, but certainly gosh, OK, well,
we have to start tracking this and start paying attention
to when exactly it happens.
Obviously, a culprit that comes to mind right off the top
of my head is a quick time.
But it certainly is not very good if you're using your machine
for podcasting.
Hey, what's going on Adam?
It's WooCash from Polish Detroit podcast
at Polish Detroit.com.
As you can say, from my strange, different accent.
I'm not native speaker, but I'm the host of one
and only Polish language podcast in the United States.
I just found out from Delta Sir Charlie Trio
and I that you have the same problem as I have.
I'm talking, of course, about this freaking audio loops
and new power books.
I'm just curious, maybe your listeners knows how to fix it.
It's really, really annoying.
You know, I have brand new shiny power book
and this loop just makes me crazy.
Yeah, yeah.
So I'm waiting, maybe somebody will help us.
Right on.
Polish side from Detroit, y'all.
I'm going to get on your ass, Apple.
So let's get working on this.
Let's figure it out.
You know, buggy's appear, buggy's do happen.
Let's see, we can fix it.
I hope it's not hardware related.
That's a real pain in the ass, for everybody involved.
Could just be a software thing, but it's definitely annoying
and it's definitely popping up at the wrong moment.
So far twice.
I think actually three times in a show.
I've never really restarted a show because of it.
Because, you know, I think it's kind of,
you know, oh, the, hey, look, if I had restarted a show
when it happened, then we never would have known about it
because I would have just thought it was an intermittent thing
that only I had, which I can totally
believe looking at all the stuff that I've got loaded on here.
So, all right, so we're going to pay attention to that.
See what becomes of it if you have any clues.
If you're a Mac, Mac head, send it on in.
Let's find out about it.
And since we still have more than 10 minutes to go on the satellite window,
I'd let everyone enjoy the Trinity moment.
Okay, for those of you who are new to the show, this segment is called Trinity.
That is the name of my Mercedes station wagon 300 turbo diesel from 1984,
which runs entirely on bio diesel.
I have learned quite an amount from the discovery show, dirty jobs,
and I'm really clued into how all this stuff I think should work.
So, let's see, things to point out in today's Trinity segment.
There's a, oh, this is kind of cool.
There's a car driving to China on biodiesel.
And you can check that out at ownisexperience.nl
I guess they're going from the Netherlands to China, entirely on the biodiesel.
That's cool.
Melanie Hartner says, Adam in response to your question,
hemp and cannabis are of the same plant family,
but hemp does not contain the same active ingredients.
The one we love so much.
And can be purchased here in Canada in any health food store.
I have someone my fridge in fact, she says it tastes great on salad.
It's quite expensive though, about 10 Canadian dollars for a leader,
but it's for human consumption, so maybe there's a less expensive version you can get for your car.
It says Melanie.
I mean, that would be the ultimate dream, right?
To be able to make biodiesel from hemp.
You know, that stuff grows like weas, right?
Okay, let me see, I've rigged everything here,
so I can do the audio comments much easier.
Here we go.
Hey Adam, this is Lucien from Planet TV.
Hey Lucien.
I wanted to see if I could give you a little more insight into the biodiesel bio fuel discussion
you're having about your new American ride, Trinity.
The first thing you need to know about bio fuels
is that when internal combustion engines were being developed,
two types of engines were designed.
Engines that ran off highly refined oils, gasoline type engines,
and engines that ran off of basically just purified oil,
or slightly refined oil.
And that was a diesel type engine.
An important thing to also note is that both of those engines
were originally developed to use either gasoline
or purified oils from both petroleum oil
and vegetable oil sources.
Now diesel type engines can run off either purified oil, vegetable oil,
or petroleum oil, or a slightly distilled version of that oil
called diesel.
Bio diesel is diesel fuel that is derived from vegetable oil sources
or animal fat sources.
Modern petroleum diesel engines could run on straight vegetable oil
but the engine wouldn't last very long.
They make it work and not ruin the engine
requires a conversion kit.
Not counting homemade kits,
the only professional conversion process available
for a modern petroleum diesel engine to convert
to straight vegetable oil replaces the injectors
as heaters to the tank and replaces other components necessary
to run the diesel engine on straight vegetable oil.
These professional conversions can also run on pure biodiesel
any bio diesel blend or on straight dirty or petroleum diesel.
A professional conversion of this type is the only conversion
that could be called a true bio fuel or bio diesel conversion.
And once completed these are true bio fuel cars
in as much as they can run on any fuel from purified vegetable oil
whether it's weight-special oil or pure pressed vegetable oil
or bio diesel or petro diesel or any combination of these.
Cars that have had these professional one tank conversions
have had hundreds of thousands of kilometers put on them in Europe
and in America.
And they afford their drivers a much broader variety of fuel sources
than a typical diesel engine.
This is possibly what you have in Trinity.
The Berkeley Depot will be able to tell you specifically
what type of engine and conversion you have
and also which type of fuels to use in it in order to make it last.
And finally, most engineers will tell you that even though
a professional bio diesel conversion will allow you to run any type of fuel
through the engine, most mechanical systems benefit from choosing
one type of fuel and sticking with it.
I hope this gives you some insight.
If you decide to try to make your own biodiesel,
there are several good systems that are available as kits.
Drop me an email I'll let you know.
Keep up the good fight.
And thanks again for watching my video podcast,
Planet TV.
You can still find it at dailyplanettv.net.
Thanks.
All right.
Thank you very much.
So yeah, please do send me any links you have to buy
a diesel manufacturing kits because that is what I finally decided upon.
We have to go through the process of adding,
I think it's what is it's glycerin and lie.
No, I'm sorry, methanol and lie.
A byproduct is glycerin.
There you go.
Methanol and lie.
And that then, you know, there's a process to base.
It's a refinery, a little refinery in your garage.
That's what I want.
I'm so into that.
I might even have a little bit of space at the condo
where I can sneak something like that.
And if no zs neighbors don't make too much problem.
I'd rather rent a garage somewhere.
We can set up a cool little factory.
You know, get our babe co running,
our Bay Area biodiesel corporate conglomerate.
And then finally,
Darryl Q-Lax has added,
and this is kind of what Lucien touched on.
Did you know that the first biodiesel was actually the first fuel
used in a diesel engine?
Yep.
The diesel used peanut oil in his original diesel engine,
including his demonstration at the 1900 World Fair.
He intended that his engine,
but used readily available biofuels.
The diesel engine was considered to be a strategic advantage
to the German war machine.
In fact, Mr. Diesel died mysteriously.
Shortly before Germany released a huge fleet of diesel submarines.
The fact that Mr. Diesel was friendly to the US,
great Britain,
and France is considered to be a factor in his death,
although nothing has ever been proven, of course.
It was only when the lubrication oil industry,
wow, direct spin around for a long time.
When they found that two of their useless byproducts,
gasoline and diesel could be used in these new engines,
and that these alternative fuels were even considered as fuel.
But soon after intense government lobbying,
gasoline and diesel fuels became the most common fuel
for engines around the world.
And these facts come from the book,
the clean power revolution by Troy Helming.
All right,
so we're up to speed with just a little more bio diesel industry information.
And almost 100% convinced now that the only thing
that is different on Trinity,
it does not have a straight vegetable oil heater and conversion kit,
but it does have new hoses because the regular rubber hoses
seem to dilute a little bit quicker using the bio diesel.
So that's it.
We've got to make one of these refineries in my garage.
She could talk.
You hear her fake.
I don't feel pooping.
You're Trinity.
Trinity.
Yeah.
Right on, everybody.
Okay, let me see.
Still looking for a good word for video podcasting.
Ron Strupe says,
since podcasting uses an iPod,
this name podcasting.
If you use a video camera,
cam casting by a camcaster.
Yes, I'll take the credit for the term and share the history with you if you promoted.
Hurry before Steve Jobs takes the credit for it.
I don't know.
Cam casting.
Yeah, it's actually not too bad,
but I think that video podcasting.
We have to come up with some net a name for it all because,
you know,
what are you going to call it Photoshop casting?
You know,
it can all be casting.
I think somehow we've got to change that.
It's like having a mind space.
Wow, did you read that article?
It was huge on dig.com about the,
the corporate history of dig.com.
Very interesting where these guys came from apparently from xDrive.com.
And well,
there's a lot of,
I'd have to say,
almost accusations.
It has a very accusatory tone,
this article.
And I don't know if that's entirely warranted.
But it does talk a lot about what's happening with the data that my space users
are willingly providing.
Because, you know, you are basically,
you know, handing off all this information.
It goes back to one little piece in this article.
And I don't have the link handy,
but I got it off of dig.com.
So you can find it from there from the homepage.
What they're saying is that
there's a corporate culture that dates back to spam email lists
from the founders of my space.
The corporate culture is that people do not read the fine print.
So what is being insinuated?
And I do have a my space account somewhere,
but I haven't honestly haven't really used it.
What they're insinuating is something that could be very true
that basically all of the information you enter
and all of your data,
not just on aggregate,
but down to your individual,
your individual data is basically being used
to advertise to you.
And of course, that makes sense because that is entirely
the my space model is 99.9% advertising.
And so I guess the big question is,
does it really matter?
Well, of course it matters.
And it's your data.
I think it would be great if you could take all that information
and bring it over somewhere else and put it in some other system.
Maybe you'd want to have that data reside in Yahoo 360
or in Orcad or in Friendster.
And I think that this is the kind of stuff
that Steve Gilmore keeps hammering about.
I've listened to a couple of Gilmore Dailys
and Attention TechPodcasts.
It's really starting to dawn on me what this means.
For us users of this stuff,
you're not really thinking about it.
Because at the end of the day,
there are 35 million people who are using my space
who are just loving the experience,
having a great time.
Apparently they're clicking through on ads
that I guess are relevant to them.
And the whole thing is working.
The question is, do they know actually what they're doing
and what's happening with their data?
And I think that that's a pretty healthy conversation
to have because obviously if you're providing a service
to someone who's enjoying it,
you'll be even better if everyone knew
what's happening on both sides of the equation
and then you could probably even find tune that data.
You could get users of your product
to submit even more detailed information
about what they're really into
or what that particular online persona
of the day is interested in
that they're using.
And then Christina has a whole bunch of different accounts
for different stuff.
Hey, satellite folks, have a great weekend.
The Pacific Coast Hellway is coming up next
and I'll talk again on Monday right here
on serious stars 103.
And for those of you who are listening to the podcast,
this is where we really get down and dirty, right?
What's it going to...
Oh yeah.
Okay.
If you've never listened to Pacific Coast Hellway,
I suggest you subscribe to it.
It's a great show.
It's about 20, 25 minutes every single day.
So it's the perfect length for a podcast.
And Mark Yoshimoto and M.Koff went into...
I love it when he goes into these rants, man.
He went off into something so beautiful yesterday.
I want to play...
Actually, it's five minutes exactly.
So if you've already heard the show
if you are a subscriber or if you just don't
dig what he's saying, you can shuttle past it
and you'll find me on the other side of the next five minutes.
But it's brilliant, man.
So would someone please tell me?
What the fuck?
Mainstream media thinks it's doing with its feeble attempts
to get into podcasting.
I mean, do they really think
they can just slap any old program
into an MP3 file?
I can just see the execs talking about it now.
Gee, Bob, you know what sounds totally exciting in hip?
Hey, let's throw nightline into an MP3 file
and we'll be riding the bleeding edge.
You know what else rides the bleeding edge?
That's right.
A tampon.
And I'd much rather put that into my ear
than what Mainstream media is
shitting into the pipeline.
I mean, who are these guys kidding?
A national public radio is getting into podcasting
national public radio.
I mean, what?
Come on.
What can be more cool?
Then listening to a mind-numbing
all things considered peace
and resurrection of traditional dancing in Belarus
in the post-Soviet era on your iPod.
A piece of electronic hardware,
no one in Belarus could afford
even if they traded their children for it.
Speaking of which,
we had to intern guy in trade
for a use to us to drive
and I gotta say we feel kind of ripped off.
Now, do any of you even know
what NPR stands for?
That's right.
No pulse required.
And then there's PBS.
I mean, who the fuck is listening
to Jim Lair's NewsHour podcast?
I can only assume that while
flipping through the channels,
people have accidentally stared deep enough
and the Lair's black soul is eyes
long enough to become hypnotized
into subscribing to this fun fest.
Hell, if you think watching
the NewsHour is boring,
think how boring it would be
with no exciting PBS graphics.
I mean, if PBS were so fucking entertaining,
they wouldn't have to send their young
female PAs out through my neighborhood
selling their bodies for donations
in the first place.
Wait, make of it.
What?
She was from the Girl Scouts?
Oh, cookie?
Oh, I thought she said,
never, well, they're over 18, right?
Oh,
anyway,
you want really boring.
There are over 100 podcasts
on the iTunes directory
for weather.
Many of them from mainstream sources
like the Weather Channel
or your local television station.
I mean, is it just me?
Or can't you just turn on a TV or radio
anywhere and get the weather forecast
in about two minutes?
I mean, first,
who thought this would be a good idea?
And second, who's putting this
onto their MP3 player?
What's next?
Traffic updates?
I mean, listen,
we're not saying that every independent podcast
is great.
Lord knows there's a tremendous amount
of shite out there.
Ignition, I'm looking at you.
But you, as a consumer of entertainment
and information content,
should demand that if the corporate
powers that be are going to do something
that they call podcasts,
that they should at least give you
original content, taking other media
and ripping them into an MP3 file
doesn't make it a podcast.
It makes it a fucking repackage.
The only network doing anything
that requires a little bit of thought
isn't the major American ones.
No, it's the Brits.
Now let me say up front
that I don't really find the Ricky Jervais podcast
all that funny.
But at least you have to give the guardian
unlimited props for doing
an original podcast.
I mean, full of content,
you can't get anywhere else.
Now, what do we get from the American media
companies?
NBC nightly news?
Fuck, nobody's watching that on TV.
Why the hell would I want to watch
Peter Jennings on my little iPod screen?
What's that?
What?
He's dead?
Wait, wasn't that broker?
Jesus, who can tell?
Jennings broker, live dead,
not much difference to me.
Now, do you know what kind of fucking
con job box tried to pull off
as a podcast?
It's build as a Simpson's podcast,
but you know what it really is?
A guy just some dude talking
about the Simpsons.
It's like, well, last night Homer did this
and Bart did that tune
and next week when Homer does that
and Bart does this.
Did anyone listen to that
steaming pile of Matt
graining's post-Barito
bowel movement?
It's fucking pathetic.
They didn't even have
the wherewithal
to make a real commercial.
Why that crap cast
is still in the top 100
is a fucking mystery to me.
Actually, no.
It's not too much a mystery.
It's there
because it's got a Simpsons logo on it.
And they're lying to the public.
They do the same thing
for the family guy, please.
Oh, please.
American public run
from this shit on a stick
like you would run
from a guy
with shit on a stick.
Welcome back
if you've shuddled
through all of that.
Mark Yoshimone and Enco
from the Pacific
of Elco's players.
Great job.
And that rant goes on
for at least another three
four minutes.
It's really, really good
and it's so incredibly true.
And you know,
look at iTunes.
You know, yes,
the directory
does have all kinds of podcast
available,
but look at what they're really
highlighting.
Okay.
Look at the ratio of
mainstream
to independent.
And I'd say two things about that.
One, first of all,
of course,
that's what Apple's going to do
because those are all the relationships
that Apple has.
They've been inside Hollywood.
That's how the whole iPod came about
is because of
basic concessions that they
that they made as a company.
And that's,
I'm pretty happy they made those decisions.
Now let's not rely on
the iTunes and the iPod
as are only source of distribution here.
Okay.
There's another shoe actually
that hasn't dropped yet.
There is another player
out there.
You know,
there is a really big
player out there that just
really hasn't
hasn't presented anything yet.
But I have a pretty good feeling
that something
will present itself
very soon.
Do you hear that radiator
man that we've got to get
those things?
We've got to,
what is it?
Where is that Roger
Smalls going through my trashy
hand?
No.
Sounds like it sounds like someone's
dragging a
note,
create a note bottles across the street again.
Since it's just
us podcasters and podcasters
and there's here,
a couple more things.
I do actually want to do
a metro sexual moment.
But there was some pretty
cool audio feedback
that I got
about advertising.
And I wanted to share that
with you from Ed Roberts.
Hi, Adam.
This is Ed Roberts from the
Kent City Weather podcast.
You know, I've been doing
some thinking here about
advertising lately
as many of us certainly have.
And I think we're really
missing out on something
that's really important
when it comes to advertising.
Yes, we definitely need
to market to something
that our listeners are going to
be interested.
Absolutely.
Mark research companies
make millions of
dollars every year
doing this exact
thing for traditional media.
So the idea certainly
isn't new.
The only difference
is in this respect
with regards to podcasing
is that podcasters
can reach a much narrower
and more specific
market than traditional media.
But most importantly,
podcasters have an
intimate camaraderie
with their listeners.
Traditional media has not
had this for years.
As a podcaster,
your listeners
respect what you have to say,
even trust what you
have to say,
which could be kind of
dangerous depending on the
podcasters you listen to.
But they respect you
in the fact that they actually
take the time to listen to you.
If they didn't
respect you,
they would not listen.
In a way,
you can kind of compare
a podcaster talking about
a product they enjoy
or even more importantly,
a product they use.
You can kind of compare
that to celebrity
endorsements,
at least what they were
supposed to be when they first
started.
Here's a person
that you respect,
and that you consider
maybe even knowledgeable,
talking about
and using a product
that they enjoy.
Hey, you know what?
If it's good enough for them,
you might be good enough
for me.
If they tested out
and really seem to enjoy it,
maybe I should do the same.
And really,
your listeners doing
the same type of thing
back to you or to your
other listeners,
does the very same thing.
This is
social networking
and it's fine.
A social networking
monetized.
Well,
I just want to stop
at that for a second.
This is social networking
monetized.
Interesting concept,
like that.
That's really what it is.
And that's what I believe
the future of advertising
is.
And generic,
one of the mil
blast you with
whatever type of advertising
simply does not work
in that type of environment.
It's not really
fair to your listeners
and in a way,
it's not really
fair to your advertisers
as they're really
not getting the full benefit
of what advertising
and podcasting can do.
And it also
required a bit with the feedback
that you played back
in episode
310 of the daily source code
talking about how we just
filter out
generic advertising
and to be honest,
I do that
with the earthling stuff
quite frequently,
actually.
And it gets worse
with the
broadcast across
the pod show spectrum.
I've seen several studies
here recently
that say,
you know,
those in the
18 to 35
age range,
which is prime target
for advertisers
that they have a pretty
highly sensitive
to BS detector.
And those kind of
advertisements
certainly follow
those links.
So we really need to
figure out how to
make that work.
And I really think
that needs to come from the pod
caster
or your family of listeners.
Shoot.
I was at the store today
and found myself
buying one of those
M3 Power Rangers.
Goodness.
Anyway,
keep up the good work.
If any of your listeners
happen to live in the
Kansas City area,
make sure you check out
my podcast at caseyweather.org.
I'll be hitting episode 300
here on January 7th.
So I'm catching up to
their Adam.
Good luck.
Right on it.
Thank you very much.
So yeah,
of course,
what you need to find for that
is also advertisers who
are open to that.
Advertisers are usually
a pretty conservative
bunch.
They spend a lot of money.
There's a very little way
to recognize how
stuff is working.
Except on,
you know,
the whole industry,
of course, is based on a whole
bunch of bullshit.
Statistics like
arbitron like Nielsen.
In an
own way,
banner advertising,
you know,
you really just can't
quantify it down.
You know,
the big dream of being able to
know exactly what's
happening everywhere
at every minute,
you know,
that is never appeared.
And that's not going to happen
because of just how,
you know,
the network just is not a
constant state across all clients
and all servers all the time.
You've got proxy servers
and all kinds of
routing and firewalls and
asynchronous communications.
They're really just don't
allow the tracking that
advertises or marketers were
promised,
I think quite honestly,
by techies.
The probably is far back
as as the mid 90's
when the first dot com
stuff really started to happen.
So it will come down to that
relationship.
And it will come down to.
Um,
solidifying that relationship
with your listeners.
And that's why I like this
concept of a registered listener.
Um,
Do it.
If you were registered
with your listeners,
we could have eventually
gone to your let.
And, you know,
had them send a,
an M3 power
razor tester kit to any
registered listener who
raised their hand.
You know,
hey, that will be pretty
fucking beneficial.
For you,
for me and for them.
Metro,
you know,
And I really do appreciate it.
Thank you for taking the time to send in some
audio comments on today's
Metro sexual my Adam.
This is Luke.
I never comment about the topic of
skin conditioning that you've been speaking of
during the Metro sexual moment.
What happened to me is totally preventable.
I live in an area,
not known for much son,
Seattle.
And I'm in IT,
which means I don't have a window in my office.
I don't son Bay,
then I've never been in Tanymuth.
But last year I was diagnosed with skin cancer, basal cell carcinoma, it's referred
to the as the easy cancer.
What I thought was just a pimple that had never healed quite right is now a 4 inch scar
above my left eyebrow.
When I go outside, I have to dress like the invisible man.
Some protective clothing, gloves, a wide-brimmed hat, sunglasses, and the ever-present
sunscreen.
I'd like to encourage listeners to the DSC, both men and women.
Then when they look into skin conditioners and moisturizers, to try and look for at least
an SPF-15 in his multi-spectrum, it means it covers both UVA and UVB, or to use sunscreen
and not just when they go to the beach or the pool, and definitely not just in the summer.
My hope is that ensuring this, that one person out there won't hear the doctor say, it's
positive.
For more information, please check out www.skincancer.org.
Right on, dude.
Thank you.
I've bombed out the Metrosexual moment there for a second, and hopefully that bites.
But okay, heat of warning there, make sure you look out for moisturizers, et cetera, products
that do have some sun protection factor in that, and that, of course, has been backed
up by many doctors and many studies.
Hi, Adam.
This is Andy Bellittle from the AndyCast podcast at AndyCast.net, and I've got a little
something for your Metrosexual moment.
Go right.
Hello there.
This is Bunsen, how do you do it?
AndyCast Labs.
Personal hygiene division.
I'm here with my good friend, Beaker.
We were given the task of finding the best disposable razor for today's Metrosexual
man.
We found there to be no clear type winner, but there are some critical messages that
need to be told.
First of all, the lady's chick has estrogen implanted in it.
She let Razor, has progesterone, and the vibrating extension in the vibrating razor is nothing
for any man to eat.
Some of the things that we found within Beaker did some testing was some breast tenderness.
Did you see, baby?
Desired to go shopping.
A constant question about the size of what's asked in a pair of jeans.
This has been Bunsen, how do you do from AndyCast Labs?
I hope that put a smile on your face at him, happy new year to you, and love the daily
source code.
This is Andy Bellittle from the AndyCast podcast at edicast.net.
Alright, do thank you very much.
Okay, and then the kicker for today, I'm really excited about this.
Matthias Berser from Germany, first he sent in his tips, he says, instead of using foam
or cream to shave, are you shaving oil, you've talked about that before, it's hard to get
in Germany, says where I live, but available in boots stores all over the UK, so give
it a try.
Well, I will shaving oil.
My favorite is summer sets shaving oil, but King of Shave is also great.
I basically oil, it's basically all the rub your wet face with instead of foam or gel,
but you can also combine those products.
One advantage of you do not combine them is you'll be moisturized by the shaving oil
and when your finish just dry your face done.
Oh yeah, and you can also use together with electric shaves.
I don't know, man, I think you should still moisturize even after you do all that.
Now here's the, the, he's the got me really excited.
The company I work for says Matthias Berser, high tech electron lithography tools.
One of the core components is a scanning electron microscope which can be used to make
quite high magnification images.
Maybe I'm able to put some razor blades in and we can find the differences between
the ones which come with the razor and the replacement blades.
Also, some of the tools are equipped with a device called EDX and short this can give you
information about material composition with a resolution of about one micron.
So what do you think?
My only problem right now is I broke my wrist no boarding after Christmas and I'm home
sick, but happy listen plenty of podcasts since I have the time.
No promises when I can do the experiment.
Well, Matthias, no problem, my friend, can't wait to hear the results of that.
Yeah, I think you should take it down to a micron level and find out if there is a difference.
If those scumbags are given us great blades in the pre-sale pack and shitty replacements,
be nice to know.
Okay.
Oh my goodness, what are we doing?
I 41 almost 42 minutes, great.
Okay.
And that is the Metro sectional moment for today for Friday.
It is the 6th of January, 2006.
The next time we speak to each other will be from the Curry condo in San Francisco,
it will be there for almost two weeks, so it is going to be quite a shift on the oil rig.
And I'm going to miss the girls, obviously.
Thank you all so much, by the way, for sending in your links to videos, videos cut to
pod safe music, lots of videographers, people who have video editing tools, interested in
the concept.
Okay, this is what I want to do.
I want to think about setting up something similar to the pod safe music network and have
some kind of relationship between the two.
I think this is all going to be a part of the unlabel as we discussed yesterday, so let's
just don't stop experimenting, but I got to think on how we can mold or shape or put this
together.
I would love to have your input.
I think we need a place where videographers, this really comes down to the unlabel.
It really does.
The videographers can make videos for a pod safe music tune.
You of course, you could have multiple videos for it.
Something that can be shared around, something that can be distributed, and the concept
would be that people would get interested, would buy something, buy a CD or some merchandise
or a track or whatever, and then the maker of the music video that instigated the purchase
would get a piece of it.
But that's, we got to fit all that together, and of course, it's never 100% accurate,
and you can't really, as far as I know, it's not going to be very easy to track people
from their devices through to a purchasing affiliate system, but let's work on it, because
I think there is something there, and I think music videos, which originally were known
as promo clips, video music promo clip, it's really what it used to be known as.
It was a promo clip, it was to promote the video, and it's still used to promote the song,
really.
The video is used to promote the song.
So there's something there, something there for sure, I've got to think about it.
Let's see, this is Betty Loveette from the Pod save music network, down to zero.
What the feeling, when you're feeling, your step and light lift making your number
one, down to zero, with a word to leave them, one of the ones, now I am walking which
will feel that down on the ground, down to the ground, down to the ground.
All the way down to the ground, round new demand, first glassing steel, just flows through
the crowd, walks off with your man, send you rushing through the mirror, rush back
out and say, there's no beauty in you, then get it one, all the rhythm of when
I walk the warm sense beside you, more than your heel, little waves come rushing
in.
So take the word from your head, thin again, never again, she'll put you up alone, then
you're hot and stiff, then you fall.
You're gonna know how to steal more grind, when you're thinking about your mama's
own this song, taking to your bed, think you're fine, eating, sleeping, but you dream
of nothing but love and sin, and gonna hard hit you fine, can bring more pain than
love, listen, listen, who would you fall, when you fall, when you fall.
You know how to steal more grind, when you're thinking about your mama's own listen,
take it to your bed, think you're fine, eating, sleeping, but you dream of nothing but love
and sin, oh, when you fall, when you fall, when you fall.
All at my door.
Ready to live at, down to zero, from Epitaph Records, one of the many record companies who
have joined the Podsafe Music Revolution, and it's real simple how it works, you go look at
the show notes for a podcast, who plays music from the Podsafe Music Network.
If you hear something you like, go to the show notes from the show notes, you should be able
to link straight to the artist's page and the Podsafe Music Network from there.
You can find out about them, listen, other songs, of course, links to their own websites.
They might even have their own podcasts, places to buy, and very soon hopefully a purchase
tag right there so you can buy the track or buy the album by some melts.
Hey, everybody, have a great weekend.
I'll be traveling.
I will talk to you again on Monday from Curricondo in San Francisco.
Bye-bye.
Potcho.com makes no claims regarding the quality of its pod shows or the sanity of its producers.
Listen at your own risk.