This is Soccer Girl. I just listened to the first episode of Shadow Falls and it's scared me
crapless.
With $16 million worth of airplanes stuck to his lips, whilst sucking on the P2 and the
next generation radio content in his ears, it's the daily source code episode 450 with Adam
Curry.
You talk of the game, but you wrap your guilt around me, when you don't get your way.
You bleed on this plane, clean your cut, wrap it up, take care of your own pain.
Cause it's you, not me.
It's gonna set you free, and I'm sorry, but I don't have the time, and it's me, not you.
It ends up feeling used, and I'm sorry, baby, but I'm not responsible.
Why can't you let it go?
Yeah, because all that joke crying about, happened to years ago, all more.
You hit rock bottom now, you're pacing into flow.
But what I'm talking about is climbing out when no one's ill, but you're wrong cause it's you.
Not me.
It's gonna set you free, and I'm sorry, but I don't have the time, and it's me, not you.
It ends up feeling used, and I'm sorry, baby, but I'm not responsible.
Go somewhere, go and stand up by yourself.
Cause I ain't taking no more, I need the reason no more, and it's me.
It's gonna set you free, and I'm sorry, but I don't have the time, and it's me, not you.
It ends up feeling used, and I'm sorry, baby, but I'm not, so sorry.
It ends up feeling used, and I'm sorry, baby, but I'm not, so sorry, baby, but I'm not.
I'm not, sorry, so sorry, baby, but I'm not, sorry, baby, but I'm not responsible.
Lord, clap, I'm not responsible from the Podsafe music network.
Hey, everybody, good morning.
This is a different time for me to be recording the Daily Source Code.
It's early Monday morning, and you probably woke up this morning if you went to your podgeo
plus a con or your iTunes or whatever, and went to, oh my goodness, there's a source code already.
That's right, but the time you're listening to this, I'm probably midway the English channel on my way over to Amsterdam with Patricia.
She has some paperwork that she's got to take care of for our complete integration into Britain.
So, it reminds you, this is something that, you know, going actually from the United Kingdom to the mainland to the continent and flying back.
Landing in both places in one day, I have to point out is something that Hitler never accomplished.
I had a question about the Podsafe music network on Friday, and answers came streaming in.
Hello, Adam.
It's Martin, aka GD, from GD's Bite Size Bonus.
Congratulations to you, young man.
You've actually got round to play in Paper Rogers at long last.
Yes, he's on the Podsafe music network, but if you've been listening to my show Bite Size Bonus,
by sizeblownest.podshow.com, you'd have been hearing paper a lot.
We've been playing the last 18 months, and she is tremendous artist, as she's a lovely young lady, and she's from Wales.
Now, he's a personal invite to you, Adam.
If you want to see some great live music and meet over podcasters, come down to Podfest.
Yes, Podfest.
Thursday, the 19th of October at the Purple Turtle, Canada London, that's the 19th of October.
Oh yeah, by the way, I can fold her fold, of course.
Purple Turtle.
Hey, dude.
October the 9th was that what it was, Podfest.
Semi, a URL, a link.
So I can find out more about it.
If I'm in town, you bet you, of course, I'll drop by, I'd love to.
It looks like I'm going to be here all through September, since we've got all kinds of cool stuff happening with Podshow UK.
Why am I doing this show so early in the morning?
Well, because, well, I knew I had to fly with Patricia, and I couldn't do it a Sunday.
Because Sunday evening, last night, the night we just are moving away from Christina.
Lovely daughter celebrated her sweet 16th birthday on her actual birthday, which is nice.
It's a bank holiday in England, which means that everyone has Monday off, so she had a party from six to midnight at the stoke to pub in Guilford.
Very, very hard.
If you've been following along, very hard to actually get a place that will allow teenagers because there's always, you know,
It's always a little bit of a problem.
We had done it, I think, perfectly.
Actually Patricia did it perfectly.
It was essentially a place where you could have a wedding reception or any kind of party.
And it was an Alice in Wonderland theme, Christina.
And I have do have pictures in video.
And of course, I'll be showing that soon on the perversion for profit, my video show.
That'll be on next week.
You know, she was dressed like Alice in Wonderland.
And it was great.
All these kids showed up with, you know, like, money, ears on, and mad hat or hats.
And they really, you know, well, not every single one of them.
There's a lot of tattoos.
They were, had nothing to do with Alice in Wonderland.
They were just on the kids who came.
A lot of pants falling off asses.
But we didn't serve alcohol even though many of them were over 18.
Most were probably between 16 and 18.
But of course, they were more than welcome to, you know, walk around the neighborhood, find whatever they could.
And it actually turned out great.
Everyone loved the, what was that stuff?
The J2O.
Some sickly sugar drink.
The kids love that shit.
They just, they were drinking it like no one else's business.
Of course, I'm counting them.
Each, you know, go up and get three, four bottles.
Yeah, sure, go ahead.
Because it was just a regular bar, you know.
I'm just paying for great food.
Christina had a DJ who was great.
You know, kids brought some of their own CDs.
But he had a real good mix of stuff.
And Christina was really, really, really, really happy.
And at the end of a day like that to hear, say,
Mom and Dad, thank you so much.
You know, that really did it for me.
So I'm so happy.
And I didn't even have to drive the brand new convertible into the,
Into the party with the, with the bow around it.
I said, though, I will have some footage of that.
Next week on perversion for profit.
I have a, a new version, a new show ready to go.
My video show.
You can find that pfp dot pod show dot com perversion for profit.
It's not up yet when I get back from from Amsterdam tonight.
Then I just have to do my segments.
I think you're really going to like it.
I'm starting to get a real feel.
People are sending stuff in.
It's, you know, it's going to be about 10 minutes, which is really nice.
You know, if you have a video iPod or some other,
Or even your laptop, I guess.
You know, it may be just something you can check out on the train.
If you drive in, obviously, a little more difficult or it work.
It's, uh, I think you'll get a kick out of it.
We got some, uh, some good clips on for you.
Uh, let's see, voicemail.
Still getting, I didn't go through the whole voicemail box.
I saw there about 25 messages waiting.
If you want to call, though, you know the number,
But now, plus one, two, zero, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven.
You can find that a daily source code dot com in the show notes.
Adam, I like your show.
But you got to stop demonizing the scrunchers.
I mean, come on.
You putting out a survey to try and find out who,
Not who, but how many people scrunch and how many people fold.
Uh-huh.
And then you tell the audience what you do.
And you make it painfully clear that anyone who doesn't do what you do is.
Is consummately evil?
Yes, you are.
I mean, scrunchers are even doing the results a little bit.
Come on, man.
Lighten up on the scrunchers.
In other news, house prices in the UK.
Uh, did you know a little site called up my street.com.
You can punch in the postcode for the house that you're looking to buy.
Not having to buy my alley.com.
That's a different site altogether.
Out within a specified radius.
How much houses around that are selling for.
It's a great little research tool.
Check it out up my street.com.
Okay.
That's it for today.
Adam.
Thanks a lot.
And I might want to mention my name.
Yes.
It's David Wink.
I'm 32.
American.
Listener and London.
Since about May 05.
And I love the show.
I know.
Tailwinds.
Oh, scruncher.
Pilot and scruncher.
There is a disproportion amount of scrunchers amongst pilots.
I've noticed.
Yeah, I really love the fact that you guys are still calling in with your listener profiles.
It's really helping me understand who you are and trying to tailor the show more towards
Torchee.
So far, average age about 32 and the scruncher still have it.
Did I say that?
Did I say scruncher still have it?
Hi, Adam.
My name is Matt.
I'm 32 years old.
I'm responding to your call out to have your listeners calling and introduce themselves.
I'm doing that right now.
Again, when he's Matt of 32 years old, I do not have a podcast.
I was introduced to your show by Guyning Joe Barlow.
Finally, a slave podcast.
It's going to be a slave.com.
And I know I'm a little late.
Probably.
I'm catching up on your shows.
But I live in Ohio.
And I work for a college in Pennsylvania.
And I was driving back to Pennsylvania to come back to campus to do some more.
And I was catching up on your podcasts when my ear buds in.
And my wife was sleeping.
And I heard the call out.
And I thought it's probably not a good idea for me to call right now.
Because I really didn't move my wife's face up to me saying hi, Adam.
I'm 32 years old.
You get the idea.
So anyway, I just wanted to say I like your show.
And I was supposed to do it as much as I can.
Oh, hello.
Is this going to late?
I'm a folder.
All right.
Thanks, dude.
Appreciate it.
Yeah, keep those calls coming.
It really helps.
Hey, I wish you could wish that this were live.
Sometimes I missed that.
Because, you know, if I knew that where you were right now was also middle of the night.
I got a candle burning here on top of the the console where I create the magic.
Just the glow of the secondary monitor kind of against my face.
I've got one light dimmed in the background.
Everyone's asleep.
I don't know.
I think Christina is just about going to sleep.
She was obviously pretty excited.
I wish you could feel that vibe with me.
I wish you could feel it.
Yo, AC.
What's up?
It's AB.
A big crack radio.
Hey, man.
I've been listening to your past few shows.
And I'm just curious, man.
What is your perspective on all this kind of cultural sex.
Nakedness thing that is going on.
Like Europeans have a very different perspective on that.
And, you know, it's very different.
Why do we Americans seem to be still fairly uptight about things like naked pictures
and press releases that talk about how to women.
I mean, give me a fucking break.
You know, I was looking on the web and I think it's ABC ran a story.
Just tell your listeners, like Google, like Google naked.
Number times men think sex.
Go Google that.
And you'll find a few articles about this.
So, you know, it's like just reality here that you might ask somebody for naked pictures.
In fact, you know, maybe it should just be the normal, you know, mode of interaction.
Hey, nice to meet you.
How about some, could I see some naked pictures with that be cool?
All right.
Thank you very much, here are mine.
Very good.
I mean, what the fuck is my space all about?
You know, it's basically that.
So anyway, man, love to hear your perspective.
And I'll talk to you soon.
Take it easy.
All right.
A to the B from the C.
From, you know what, I just googled that.
Times men think sex.
Okay.
Top link.
Primetime live poll.
American sex survey from ABC News.
Sometimes it's just about sex.
Usually not the vast majority of Americans are monogamous and happy about it.
Expressing satisfaction with their sex lives and abroad preference for emotional
commitment and sexual relationships.
That's bullshit.
Most by far prefer marriage to the single life.
Yeah, that's different.
The vast majority of Americans are monogamous.
I don't believe it.
I just don't.
When you call in, please say if you're a scruncher, folder monogamous or not.
Let's see.
57% of Americans have had sex outdoors in a public place.
Half talk with their partners about their sexual fantasies.
42% called themselves sexually adventurous.
29% have had sex on a first date and about as many of had an unexpected sexual encounter
with someone new.
How many?
What's the percentage?
They're 29%.
Almost a third.
15% of men and 3 in 10 single men aged 30 and older have paid for sex.
Okay.
How many times they think about it?
It doesn't.
Man is like a whole article.
Oh, here.
Sex in gender gap.
Think sex about everyday men.
70% women.
34%.
Enjoy sex.
A great deal.
Men.
83% women.
59%.
Okay.
Come on.
You know what it is?
I think that it wasn't at all the Puritans who the Pilgrims who wanted to leave this
debotuous place, this England.
I mean, isn't that just in the culture of the United States?
I think it is.
You know?
But it's there.
Mm-hmm.
It's the hidden underground.
It's coming out.
Listen to some of the eroticopod casts.
There's some.
There's some kinky shit going on in the States.
It's okay.
You know.
We can pretend.
We're not doing anything nasty.
Have you ever listened to the weekly radio address podcast?
I love this show.
And I rediscovered it in the program guide on poncho plus poncho.com.
Yeah, I know I'm Hawking it.
But it's cool because we have a whole bunch of channels there split by genre.
And this was in the comedy channel.
I forgot all about it.
I think at one point we actually had the real president's radio address.
They're instead of the weekly radio address podcast.
And it was okay because it was just a funny thing.
And now a message from the president of the United States, George W. Bush.
Good morning.
The airline security of the American people is a top priority of my administration.
We cannot do it alone, however.
We rely on tips from the public of suspicious activity area ports.
This week I learned of a direct threat to our nation's airliners in an important telephone call.
I'd like to play that call for you in its entirety.
George, this is Samuel L. Jackson.
I'm here today to make sure you go see snakes on a plate.
Sneaks.
I know that sounds crazy, but I don't give a damn.
So listen.
I mean, it suits you.
Get about your regular job.
Working for a lousy government paycheck and stop wasting all your free time.
Hacking away on the golf court.
He knows.
Go get your home boy.
Richard.
And go see snakes on a plate.
I will.
In accordance with Mr. Jackson's urgent warnings.
The Vice President, Dick Cheney and I plan to investigate the serious threat at the
APM show tonight at the Regal Cinema's multiplex.
I hope all Americans will join me in thanking Samuel Jackson for his fourth rat attention
to our nation's air security.
Thank you for listening and God bless you.
For a complete archive of the President's weekly addresses.
Visit weeklyradioaddress.com.
Whoever came up with that was the original was that for the mini I think it was.
We get the personalized custom phone call and you fill out a couple of things.
So the variables are all read by the actor.
I mean, that that that that Samuel Jackson stuff.
I mean, it was circulating the net for weeks.
It was very good.
It was well done.
Excellent.
Excellent promotion.
But then.
But then they have the President respond to it.
Yeah, that way.
That surprised me a bit.
Hey Adam, David, that guitar man from Central Park in New York City.
I was listening to the source code the other day and I heard you mentioned that when you get to New York,
you'd love to hang.
Just, you know, let me know.
Man, let me know when you get to town and we'll definitely love to meet you.
I'd love to talk to you about stuff.
This is by the way in the background.
It's just a new song I'm working on.
And if you thought you had something to say about old exon, you know what?
You play this track.
Maybe I'll send it to you today.
You play this rough of this new track.
It's called the Religion Song.
And you just ask for people's opinion.
You'll have a whole damn show.
Anyway, the main reason for this shout is,
is that you know I've been doing this podcast called I Love the Company.
I'm coming up on show number 100 should be this week because I do when every single week day.
I'm going to do it Friday.
And the main purpose of the show is to do kind of what you started.
You know, find unsigned independent singer songwriters, artists, you know,
who people would never hear otherwise.
And I play him here in New York City.
The difference between my podcast and others that just play songs and rotation
is that there's a real network here at I Love the Company.
In other words, it's kind of a six degrees of separation thing.
You know, my guitar player Roger Bartlett played with Jimmy Buffett for years
and I work with Scott Burrow who's Eric Clapton's friend.
And the drummer on my last album played with Hall and Oats.
You know, that kind of thing.
And so it's kind of this kind of an extended kind of network kind of thing.
But here's the thing.
Since you started the Podsafe network, I'm finding really, really, really wonderful artists.
And when I play them on my podcast,
they've got an open invitation to let me know when they're coming through New York.
And I make them a guest at one of my gigs.
So far, Cassandra Kubinsky.
She's on the Podsafe network and she's been out three times
to Central Park.
There's a woman named Megan Palmer that I discovered never met her.
But I loved her stuff on the Podsafe network and she's coming in from Ohio.
So she's coming out next weekend to play in front of a few thousand people of my audience.
And they're going to love her.
So it's that kind of thing.
Would you get the word out there that if there are New York based artists
because I'm not here from anybody from New York.
All right.
Tell them to give me a shout and send me an MP3.
And you, my friend, when you get to New York, let's hang.
Dude, thank you so much.
And you know I will definitely look you up when I come to New York.
He's that guitar man.
That guitar man.com David Epolyto.
He's the guy who you see playing in Central Park.
You know, that was such a great piece of feedback.
Except for the hall notes reference,
you know, that just that was a little too freaky for me.
All right.
I'm all four, man.
If I just play one song and that'll give me a whole show,
then give me your opinion.
I heard about a man who could split the moon
and even get a wolf to talk.
Then I heard about a man jumping out of a boat
because he thought he'd like to take a walk.
Then I heard about a man who said he hadn't his hand.
The deed to the promised land.
He said take out your sword in the name of the Lord
and kill your brother for a pile of sand.
Some say there's a big king watching it all,
but to me he sounds pretty unfair.
Turned in rivers to blood.
Then create an afloat.
Now I ain't saying because I wasn't there.
Kind of absurd to be taken the word.
Of another that I don't know well.
And it seems to me that a king that mean can't be big enough to help.
Now we got late night pictures on TV.
Mothers make a baby hose.
Born again to celebrities.
Rabbis on your radios.
Each one swears they heard the word.
Assured they got it right.
They say be the call of building another wall.
Get them all another reason to fight.
Now when he born me to get a nice clean slate,
but we don't waste any time.
We tell them follow the rules.
In the churches and the schools.
At the temple and the mosque and shrine.
We tell them scary tales and fairy tales.
A kiss common sense fair well.
Don't tell them all that a god that small can't be big enough to help.
Now we got late night pictures on TV.
Mothers make a baby hose.
Born again celebrities.
The rabbis on your radios.
Each one swears they heard the word.
Assured they got it right.
They say be the call of building another damn wall.
Get them all another reason to fight.
Now I don't mind saying that I like prayer.
To what?
I'll never know.
I keep reaching out for something.
And not for nothing I'm content to let it go.
Because I've seen a little heaven in my time.
And at times I've been through hell.
And it got smaller enough to understand.
Never was big enough to help.
No when it got smaller enough to understand.
Can't be big enough to help.
Amen.
Like guitarman.com David Epolyto with religion.
Yeah, I got you figured out, man.
You are the Bob Dylan of our generation.
That's what it is.
You're going to.
Someone's going to finally catch on to what you're saying.
You watch.
Let me see.
I was going to say crap.
I don't remember.
I want to welcome Brian no of the Frank Truth to the pod show team.
He was already a member of the family.
But he's really been helping out with the serious stuff on stars 102.
And we got some cool stuff coming your way.
I want to play one more thing for you here on the podcast Friday.
I played one of the three finalists for the Earthlink ad challenge,
which you can find at adchallenge.podshow.com.
And it was actually David Epolyto.
He was the first contender.
Which I believe we're announcing this week.
Big prize.
Two grand.
Your commercial goes into rotation.
And shit.
It's just kind of cool in it.
Here's finalist number two.
Is your computer a hacker magnet?
It won't be anymore because Earthlink is here to save the day.
With downloads faster than speeding bullets.
And firewall that is more powerful than a locomotive.
It has an anti-virus system that cleanses your PC with the click of a mouse.
It's a player.
It's a plane.
It's Earthlink.
Perfect.
Internet from outer space.
It linked to Earth.
The powers and abilities far greater than those of normal high speed.
And prices so low that it will blow you out of this world.
So make the right decision and turn to Earthlink as your internet provided.
I do it if you win.
You have to split some of that dough with Michael Butler.
And American Heartbreak.
Interesting.
David Epolyto used some of his music.
But I'm sure we can clear that.
No problem.
I'm sure Michael will be cool about it.
But you're going to have to give up someone at down.
Alright everybody.
So be on the lookout for a perversion for profit sometime later this evening.
You can find it at pfpopapahbox.potato.com.
And if you guys think for the source code, drop me a note.
Adam at podshow.com.
Or of course, where you can find archives and comments at dailysourcecode.com.
Take care everybody with bye another pod show podcast stick it in your ear
Get this podcast and more great ones like you on the high performance podcast delivery network from pod show and lime light networks