This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy!
The DSC for 54 American Muscle.
Hello, my guess.
It is daily source code episode number 454.
You are listening to Adam Carey.
The blackberry's in there.
And I am a monkey.
I like the bananas.
And I like to block all these things with my Tablet PC.
The very good on my blog.
And I like that little dog.
Can't stick, block.com.
And you won't guess.
Just keep listening.
Don't touch that fast forward pattern.
Some gay staff can be gathered at the public sex.
You can't deny you saw the picture.
Because she hasn't been nothing.
You can't deny they weren't feeling.
Are conceiving all in a sense.
You can't deny they didn't know.
But just as far as death.
You can't deny it up to you land.
Don't flee to your own real life.
You can't deny they weren't feeling.
Just keep listening.
Don't deny they didn't know.
And you won't guess.
Just keep listening.
Don't deny they didn't know.
You can't deny you.
Hold the trigger.
And the shot won't burn inside.
You can't deny it didn't take you back.
You won't know.
But just as far as death.
You can't deny that when you took a head.
But you didn't know.
But just as far as death.
You can't deny that you land.
Don't flee to your own real life.
You can't deny they weren't feeling.
Just keep listening.
Don't deny they didn't know.
You can't deny that when you took a head.
But just as far as death.
Strucker chasing red just one of the 23,000 tracks available at the Pods and Music Network.
Hey everybody how you doing good to good to see all again there sitting with those earbuds
jammed in deep sitting at your desk in the car on the bicycle, daily source code episode
number 454 good to talk to you again.
No real set show or format today I just wanted to go through all my voice mills with you
which I was doing this morning since we hadn't spoken and there was now three days and
there's just so much good stuff coming and I'm just going to go through it with you
I thought that's going to be experienced listen to someone's voice mail see what kind of
shit they get every single day some great aviation in the past couple days I will bore
you just a little bit with it we had to go to Amsterdam twice on Friday Patricia had
to go to get a copy of her driver's license we need two forms of identification when
we go later on in the month when we get our when actually Christina and I get our E.E.A.
visas with meaning we will be official and can live here thanks to the graces of the
lady Patricia so I got Captain Dan and we took off Friday morning it was yeah that was
it was just reasonable weather it wasn't too bad drop Patricia off then we went to
Antwerp to go see the wing commander came back and went back with Patricia and then
Saturday morning you'll recall I think I told you this the second of September we
were going to go spread my mom's ashes in the butterfly park that we'd found and
weather was pretty much crap new was happening I was going to stay overnight and come
back Sunday so the plan was to go from ferrox which is the the big holes ask airfield
here near the curry cottage to fly across the English channel Saturday morning stay
overnight in Amsterdam then fly back Sunday morning so we had pretty much and this is
what I love about aviation weather reasons you can really pretty much get your window of
opportunity down to you know about half an hour and you'll be right on and we left at
what do you leave at 9 a.m. yeah we left at 9 a.m. local UK time just as it was
starting to rain and the rain is not a big deal not afraid of rain that's just
liquid sunshine but it's the cloud cover if that's too low below us and say
excuse me this and say a moment brought to you by sessna aviation below a thousand
feet it gets really messed up if you're going VFR visual flying rules which
means you're pretty much under the clouds but the terrain in the UK does rise up
here and there so you don't want to be too low because you could be eaten mountainside
so that was actually okay the crossing across the channel was nice but then the
cloud cover really came down and it came down to maybe I was like 700 feet
around Rotterdam and here's something and I'm going to tell you this story and this
is not like oh boy how cool was this this is really actually a very dangerous
situation we ran into really stupid on our part I have to say you have two
tanks in in this aircraft one on each wing and there's a separate indicator for
each tank and you have a fuel selector which you can select the both tanks or
the left tank or the right tank and it has a gravitational pull system so
basically the just because of sheer gravity the fuel flows from the wing tanks
down into the you know the carburetor and through the engine etc now I guess the
you know the trust always trust your instruments doesn't really apply here
now we had you know lots of wind and it was kind of it was it was rocky we
had a luggage on board so it was completely conceivable that our right tank was
emptying out quicker than our left tank and so we decided Captain Dan and I
to put the fuel selector onto the left tank for a while now this could have been
a very critical mistake and in fact it turned out to be one only we were
extremely lucky as it turns out and the other systems have a fuel pump by
the way and this fuel pump you use when you take off when you land just in
case for some reason there's not enough gravity you hit an air pocket or
something you'll always be sure that fuel is is being pushed through into the
into the into the ignition system into the cylinders that could you know
through the engine you need fuel to run so when you switch tanks you also turn
on the fuel pump briefly etc now there's a fuel pressure gauge which
basically shows you that there's fuel flowing through the lines and we're
above Rotterdam we're actually just about to go down to the clouds at 700 feet
so this is always a moment where you kind of looking for a hole and there
really isn't one just you can barely broken see the to the broken clouds you
can see the ground and so we're descending maybe from a thousand feet down
from the cloud in the clouds essentially to underneath the cloud layer and I
see and Dan says at the moment I see it that all of a sudden the fuel pressure
gauge is you know hitting the the bottom of the range like oh wait a minute
and as my hand my left hand reaches out towards the fuel pump the engine
stops and by this time I've hit the fuel pump I I threw the fuel selector to
both and the engine caught again it was without a doubt one of the scariest
moments of my aviation career now could we have landed yeah we were above
field etc but that was not the plan and you know at this happened we were
lucky it happened there what if it happened on final right before landing and I
just wanted a little bit of extra engine speed you know air speed and I just
wanted to rev the engine and quit there that could have been disastrous so
got on the phone with wind commander William and man there's a whole bunch of
physics involved in this and some some knowledge which was very good
Sessna makes crappy as fuel indicators in fact so where the right hand fuel
indicator was indicating that we were almost empty even though we're
flying on the left tank in fact it was reverse and it's it totally freaked me
out and so now of course the rule is you always fly with both and you know I
know the endurance I know how long I can fly but you never switch from left
to right in this particular aircraft and it's big big big piece of knowledge
and it was very very scary but anyway so we made it fine and Sunday it was
even worse weather but it was like 40 knots headwind going back and we
till we came back to this airfield we'd parked the aircraft and it was like
three in the afternoon because that's when the weather was finally going to
let up and we were the first people to fly out of the airplane was the only
one I was sitting on the on the airfield and so we hopped in and man there was
some real flying some awesome I mean this was like 40 50 knots gusting headwind
rain all before we reached the English channel and that was an even half way
over the channel and we could hear this guy going from he was coming from
Holland he was going to Duxford which is the famous airfield here in the UK
where they have an airfield museum he was flying a spitfire and so he was
behind us so we knew what he had just come out or he was just going into and
you know at a certain point we had clear skies was beautiful over the
channel but really you know our air speed was you know no more than 90 knots
that and this thing can do you know 160 so it was like real heavy headwind
here this guy in the spitfire gone it's bloody awful and made great
the channel bloody awful it was like a movie and we were being thrown left and
right but that was a completely safe situation it was just real aviating was a
great birthday present because of course that was Sunday my 42nd birthday and
now it's good into all the stuff you guys have been sending me because it's
been so incredibly nice and you all had something interesting to say to help
me feel good about my my new old age hey Adam it's Mark Yoshimoto
Nemkoff and you know with your birthday coming up this Sunday I thought I
do something for you and I was thinking about back in those days when you were on
MTV and I used to watch you and I was an elementary school and I never thought
the day would come where I'd actually be working for you good times good times
so I wanted to do something special and since I can't buy you a helicopter or anything
I thought I'd write you a song you know it's thinking maybe I'd write something
that reminds me of every rose has its thorn or some piece of crap like that
you're still kind of furry and your nipples get hard when you get cold
Mark your lyrics of killing me I tell you once cuz I'm no fool the daily sauce
code is burning fucking cool you're my buddy and I won't break with your
my favorite big head fat go yeah happy birthday Adam or maybe at this
point in your life I should say happy birthday Adam thank you Mark Yoshimoto
Nemkoff do not only do deserve another writer yet another one that you need
one my nipples get hard when it gets cold thanks all that about happy birthday
happy birthday happy birthday happy birthday
well in the maze and arranged that one for me she's got the my Marilyn
podcast and she sent me a naked picture with Marilyn Monroe I think I
seen that one before let's see lots of stuff about Liam hey Adam it's Matt
to tell you the match today in history podcast a couple things concerning
Christina and Liam my best friend as a daughter who's 15 and when she was a
little girl and he and I were in the navy together we came up with an idea of
how to foil a future boyfriends and it starts with you taking a picture of
yourself naked from the rear you'd have your hands in the air as if you were
maybe holding something over your head or you know maybe about the throw a
football and you take that picture and super impose it on a picture of a
polar bear standing upright and then you blow this picture up you hang it on
your living room all and then when Liam comes over you don't mention the
picture you just let him see it and then have say Patricia walk by and look at
the picture and look at you and go oh honey you were so brave that day and then
just walk on and that way our ladle sit there and try to figure out what the
hell you were doing wrestling with a polar bear probably defending your
defending your family or something like that I you know I can actually just use
the picture I have with Michael Jackson you know it's just a scary and also
and I borrowed this from the movie lock stock and two smoking barrels I don't
think guns are the answer I think knives are the answer because it's much
easier for the lad to come over and for you to be sharpening set of knives
and tomorrow quotes from that movie not a regular knife but a big fuck off
shiny knife that's bound to get the kids attention especially if he's not very
sharp you know bright shiny object might get his attention anyway and one last
thing yeah he does wow thanks you know you had the only one who suggested
something other than guns to scare off the much older boy friend of my daughter
and the podcast is helping just find by the way a couple of christina's friends
heard the show and they they played it for Liam only the good bit and now he's
afraid to come by hey Adam this is done calling from Katie Texas this is
response to the color from South Florida on the Charlie 452 just positive
telling me this call I have suggestions for guns in the cabinets he can
introduce him to nothing wasn't might not work for you live given the local
laws besides guns are relatively recent in the human psyche swords that's
picked it 4,000 years of dealing with them we still have an innate fear of
them so my sort of question is going to be quite prominent when my daughter gets
to that age I have a friend who has a six foot long clay more that's sharp
it he was out practicing one's own team to pick up his daughter and he
walks off a three inch branch in a single school because you're bringing my
daughter home early right right yeah just how you'd like to know make your
folder good folder feedback that's for sure yeah there's something to that
you know and then of course I told y'all about my fencing history and this
fits very nicely into this whole swords versus guns thing hey Adam wait
for a while here just listening to the daily source code and I had to call in
on your comment about after doing your exercise lunges and the comment about
being on the fencing team and making the comment that fencing was
faggotty dude what other sport I don't think I said faggotty I think I said
fanggy teaches you to kill somebody with a single stroke missed true
I could fancy in high school yeah we thought it was a little faggotty too
I tell you it was a good workhead and when we got to play with the savers that
was kick ass and I was never in your caliper competition we were more just
guys goofing around with the swords but our teacher had been on one of the
coach so he knew what he was talking about you know as he said if you think
this is a 50 sport if we take the tips off these and don't use the pads I
could kill all of you in five minutes he was a great teacher be cool dude
take care oh and yeah folder of course folder I knew it yeah I never got to the
savers I think that's why you know the fencing outfit just look kind of lame
you know with the with the like the nickerbocker height pants and then the white
sports shoes and the socks the knee socks hey of course now with my new
ostracized thanks to Amy Mac of course the pants look kind of good and I
don't know I haven't seen him in a week so maybe it's work maybe maybe
we don't have to worry about him at all Adam Dougmore the Clinton Doug show
Clinton Doug com Adam please don't play the boys smell message anymore the
jingle you know that well no more please please don't play that anymore thanks
I appreciate it oh Adam we bread no smoking please over easy I buy to
window seat scruncher thanks dude you mean this one you got it put it in
your mobile phone don't forget the plus in case you travel outside the
country now listen to this voice mail this is the shit I live for hello Adam this
is John Cartwright I was forward at your website by my marketing guru
okay now listen she was forwarded my website by her marketing guru in
Europe and wanted to I just want to share little or listen to your little
pizza on after science and one or two years interested in trying
contrast in trying now I thought she said tontra let's listen to that again
did in trying contrast what is that is he saying tontra interested in
trying contrast I think I think I'll pretend it's tontra that you said
interested in trying contrast I'll send you the details for my website and
would love to speak with you and I'm possibly giving you a tontra session
radio or on the iPod I found number in California is okay so we'll take
out a phone number and in Ireland you can reach me at two sides in Ireland as
well she's close by five seven eight six and I'll be here in Europe next week
okay thanks I look forward to hearing from you bye now with those for oh man and
and now I don't know what that's about it sounds like tontra lessons
it's for my website and the details for my website well sounds like she wants to
do something with me on the show I'm all for it I'll even fly to hey I'll even
fly to yeah to Ireland for her hey everybody it's time again to play
unemployment show dot com's hit game show hi or not hi all right told you I was
gonna be a ringer that's right this is the only game show that dares to sniff
out of our featured celebrity is hi or not hi let's meet the contestants contest
number one can cook up a mean souffle in the kitchen it's Frankie V
thank you that's all you got to say hello hello and contestant number two is
and I was a contestant yeah I just said you are hello and contestant number
two is happily given up dating both men and women say hello to Greg he
betty I'm a region's your host gentlemen you know how to play the game so let's
get right into it we don't know what we're gonna do is say hi or not
hi okay it's like dealer no deal only in the gay or you are not a Jew or not
a Jew exactly right this Rex Roseman not a Jew I can already tell we'll have to
redo this for the promo but that's okay this week's price package includes
round trip airfare to gilford to rummage through a quasi celebrity's
garbage because that's right this week's featured mystery guest is none other
than Adam Curry oh yeah so let's let's get right into it gentlemen hands
on buzzers okay this is I you can be being I'll be bond this is audio clip
I'm gonna hand in his buzzer please wait till the end of the auto clip before you
by the way I'm down the stems here on the condo this is bad news we got no
Gmail and we're down to stems Christ man what there was the word coming to
contest number one Frankie V what do you think I definitely say hi hi
contest number two Greg hi as well the correct answer is hi round two is
he's down to stems I mean you know that's like that's a dead giveaway all right
well round round two it you can always change anytime you know it's interesting
to switch once in a while it's almost like when you smoke a different kind of
weed you can get really used to some kind and then you smoke a different kind
and then it really makes a difference contest number one Frankie V I'm gonna stay
high and I'm gonna say not high on that one the correct answer is high and
sensing a pattern though it's it's time for the lightning round everybody okay
are you ready here we go hi it was I too soon
excuse me
hi is a good guy let's let's mix it up here contest number two what that's you
that's you Greg oh hi and Frankie V and the correct answer is hi and that
brings us to the end of today's game show higher not high your winner the one
the only Frankie V yeah this is Regis right with a big bag of weed yes but
you'll have to buy it yourself you'll have to score some for your own take can we
take uh funds from the possibly we okay you guys take hey pal the unemployment
check is not for uh medicine oh no it it it helps me it's it gets me into the
mode you know what I mean indeed indeed well let's see what's up here when I'm
high this is your host Regis reminding you to check out unemployment show dot
com for all your high or not high game show needs thanks for listening everybody
hi it's my desk it's on the
it's so many of those I thank you so much I think you so much I'm
got got some cool presence too I wasn't expecting anything I got a
portable fridge for it works on 12 volts as well as 220 volts put us here
for in the studio it's fantastic so it's and it's stocks too came stocked and then
I got like it was like Beckham Beckham Cologne David Beckham I'm like what kind
of message is that sending me and I would also I get you know the kind of
stuff you give to dad right but I you know my present I already had it that
flight back was definitely my present oh get Patricia on the show tomorrow I
think we found something we may have it's I mean all the signs are pointing in
the right direction I want to get too excited but I think we might have the
new curry cottage hello Adam this is Craig Horton I live in Jackson, Tennessee
I just want to give you a shout out as you ask some of your listeners to
call in and kind of let you know who's listening I don't think a demographic is
always quite what you think it is for instance I'm a 63-year-old grandfather
after four years in the Navy during the Vietnam War I worked for 26 years
for the state of Tennessee and retired and then worked for a number of years as a
mortgage broker and by the way good God the home purchase system in the UK has
got to be the most bold up thing I've ever heard of in my life it had to have
come over with old build a conqueror and if it was already there when the
Norman's got there then they should all be damned to hail eternally for not
changing it thank God I didn't have it was bad enough in the States but nothing
like that but anyway I have spent a lot of time in front of computers I have two
PCs a desktop and a laptop I listened to a lot of podcasts and I'm subscribed to
a number of video podcasts yours is one of the first I ever listened to Adam I've
been listening to you since I think you were the double digits then you've
turned me on to a lot of podcasts and took I want to thank you for turning me on
to Leon Parsons I think she's the most delightful person in the world I've told her
any mail said I'd listen to her read a cookbook and a golly bill man just to hear
her giggle is enough to to brighten your day and by you know this is this is
such I love this listen to this guy this is a what a listener and if he ends
this up with folder or scruncher I'm going to plot myself yeah Lim Parsons is
great and I do remember playing I'm not even playing I told you that I didn't
think I had a promo at that point and I met Lynn and a producer two three
weeks ago two weeks ago in London wow great people very creative and yeah
the giggle is is her for real and she's cute
the way the lady Patricia is an absolute delight I'm fascinated whether I love
to hear her talk I'm fascinated by her English it's so good and talk about a
life at him geez it's got to be wonderful living with a woman that can life
like that because I don't care how low you get how bad your day has been I've
pissed off you aren't the world to hear her life a time or two has just got to
said everything right so yeah you're so right oh you're so right how many times
has she not just at the last at me in fact even when she's laughing at me
it works and you're right you absolutely right I'm going to play this for her
later on tonight so I know she'll come on the show tomorrow I envy you that I'm
married to a wonderful woman myself she can't life like that well but she has a
pretty good one in teaching me on track but anyway I'll end this long ram and
shout out thanks for your program I enjoy all of it I enjoy listening to your
lifestyle so I think it's fascinating it's certainly different for mine I'm
pretty boring and in a lot of ways but a good one I've been very fortunate I
look forward to hearing many more DSC's best of luck to you you're wise and you
lovely donor bye bye isn't that beautiful as fantastic you people keep on
doing that keep on calling the voice mill number with with listener profiles it's
so cool just to hear who you guys are I'm blown away I really really am for
years have been on top 40 radio stations I knew what my audience was teenage
white girls that's what it was and probably the same on MTV but this is so
diverse so different ages from 17 to well here we go 63 oh Adam it's great
Gordon injection Tennessee again yeah I left you a voice mill just a few minutes ago
but I forgot the most important thing I'm a folder of course as was my father
before me I am a very straightforward I ever that my wife and my son are
scrunchers it happens in the best it sure does okay there you tailwinds but I
can do what Lynn Parsons roaming garden knows is up your bomb yeah hey guys thanks
you very much all of these great messages very very cool let's take it home
with some burn and shall we yeah moved on without me maybe one day we'll see
things the same feeling sorry I ever felt this way feeling sorry
no one else to play
I never saw it coming I expected it should be somehow feeling sorry I ever said I
can't sorry but I'll echo for that time time on my side in a powerful dream
that no one understands for me I'm feeling sorry this ever dreams and I understand for me
I'm feeling sorry this ever dreams and I understand for me I'm feeling sorry this ever
time on my side in a powerful dream that no one understands for me I'm feeling sorry
this ever dreams and I understand for me
I'm feeling sorry this ever dreams and I'm feeling sorry this ever dreams and I'm feeling
sorry this ever dreams and I'm feeling sorry this ever dreams and I'm feeling sorry this
ever dreams and I'm feeling sorry this ever dreams and I'm feeling sorry this ever dreams
and I'm feeling sorry this ever dreams and I'm feeling sorry this ever dreams and I'm feeling
tomorrow back in the full swing of things Christina goes back to school tomorrow so the show will be delivered probably earlier than then you've seen for the past couple months because
well it's good you know Liam's back to Birmingham and the show continues now Christina's back in school and
tomorrow get the lady Patricia and we'll talk about the new curry cottage adamant pod show dot com thanks for listening everybody bye bye
get this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from pod show and line-wight networks
I love it