This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 375.
You could say this podcast is explicit at times.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this genre.
To get through.
I've been making my plans.
I've been calling my fans.
I've played all in my hands.
Cause I really want to.
Crack it out.
I've come before the rock charts.
We just didn't know the rock charts.
Crack it out.
So I've put the big wings.
I've been hoping to get out.
I don't turn out a fraud.
Living for the applause.
Well, that's a late new.
I even changed my name.
This fucking session for fame.
But my head is the same name.
And it's when I'm mature.
Crack it out.
I've never forgotten rock charts.
We just didn't know the rock charts.
Crack it out.
So I've put the big wings.
So I've been making my plans.
Crack it out.
So I've put the big wings.
Don't make me the one.
Crack it out.
Break it down
Not just pot safe, but
Kind of a pot safe anthem as well
Crank it out
Every shine from Caliph for an I.A.
From the pot safe music network
Music.potshow.com
And the irony of course is that
That song is completely a
Pop-Tard crank it out too
Which makes me just love it all the more
Her fantastic
Everybody how you doing
It's Adam
You're your friend
And your ear buds
Coming to you from curry cottage
Started out really nice this morning
We had some sunshine
It's kind of gone away
But temperatures are nice
And spring is in the air
If you look at my
My flicker page
You can see a couple of pictures that I took
I think two weeks ago in the back garden
And it's really starting to look very very beautiful
And what a song that was
How to get it all rocking and rolling
So a couple of things I want to talk with you about today
We should be able to fit in a
40 minute Charlie for you
Which seems to be the
The overwhelming requests for the length of show
You know this guy Tom Scrooting
He's a Dutch guy
I think he's
Well it's a Dutch name
So I presume he's Dutch he
Move to Australia
You actually I don't really know his background
I don't even know if I've ever had an audio
Comment from Tom
But he used to listen to
My radio shows in the early early 80s
I'm talking 83, 84
And I believe he also has lots of air checks
From my earlier pirate radio work
In fact he's become kind of a
A collecting point for all of my media stuff
Which I'm really happy about
Everybody should be so lucky to have
Someone to document their stuff
And before we left the castle
I sent him a huge cardboard box
Just filled with cassette tapes and
Gosh knows what
And he knew with the agreement
That he would digitize it
And he put it up as a podcast
Which of course I'll put a link to that in the show
No, it's if you're interested
It's really if you don't understand
Dots you're not going to like all that much
But he's also finding all these pictures
And I posted one this morning on curry.com of me with meatloaf
From about 20 years ago on stage
And the story, the story behind that
Trying to think
I think it was John Farnum at the time
Had a huge hit with your voice
And he was either
I don't know if meatloaf produced that record
I think they also they did a song together
And I can't quite remember what it was
It was like
Man my memory
And this is not the short term
We know why that's failing
But the long term now
I can't remember what the song was
It wasn't a big hit
And so they both came to promote the record
And they came to the studios in the Netherlands
And I think John Farnum was late
He was coming in from the
Maybe he was coming in from
Well, not coming in on the same plane as
As meat as we call him in the biz meat
And so they had to practice their song
You know, do a camera rehearsal
And that's what you're seeing there
As me on stage
Pretending to be John Farnum
And it was I had to say
It was really cool to do
I've done that a couple times
With some pretty big artists just stood in
And sometimes I was actually broadcast
That actual take
Anyway, so Tom came up with this great picture
Of one of my very first cars
Which I'm going to put a link on the show notes
As well
It's Aloncia
And
And he said, you know, you would promise
I can't remember when
But apparently I'd promise to tell the story behind the car
Well now that you see the car
It was I bought it off the car
Dealer just down the road
Bruno who later was incarcerated in the UK
Because he welded like 50 kilos of cocaine
Into the gas tank of a Jaguar e-type
Was trying to import
So this guy was right on the up and up
Right, what'd you expect from a second and car dealer
And so I needed new front tires
And he got me two new tires
At a cheap price
I had no money at the time
I was just starting out on the in my TV show
And it was almost like in a test period
So they were giving me very little
Very little money
So I had to get the cheap tires
And then I was driving to the studio
The next day
And this was all still very, very exciting
For me, I can't believe I'm actually driving to the studio
And I'm driving on for those of you who live in the Netherlands
Fraylons of Ech, which connects the highway
Between Amsterdam and Utrecht and Hilversum
You can kind of take a short cut
Which is I'd say
It's kind of like that road that all the stars
And Hollywood take to get to the valley to the studio
So that's kind of this type of road
So lots of celebrities take it in the morning
And I'm driving along
And man, I'm like man, there's a lot of shimmy in the wheel
And the shimmy seems to get progressively worse
And just as I'm coming into Hilversum
Just into the intersection
Both wheels completely, front wheels completely fall off
Axel's breaking
Not some bolts flying all over the place
Meanwhile, I'm about three minutes away from being late
So I literally just ditched the car
Run to the studio
Because I was definitely afraid I was going to get in trouble
And then sometime near the end of the afternoon
The cops came into the studio
And there was a BB gun, a BB hand gun
Which of course was Bruno's
And it was in the back seat
Or underneath the back seat
And so they took you in for questioning
And this is like my second or third week of work
This is my get to work car
Needless to say
I was able to explain everything
And maybe that's why they got Bruno a year or two later
But it'd be cool to hear your first car story
If you have one, if you have any interesting car stories
Because sometimes they can be fun and pretty personal
And this really only works if you
If you look at the
If you look at the picture
So check that out on curry.com
I'll put a link to it
I'll put it up on the flicker page
There you go
Chris Murray says Adam in
DSC-37
You played a sample of the radio stations
Available to you as you drove to Farrow
Because that's right on the flying sound scene
I was surprised that you only played FM stations
Really?
Do you not have a DAB radio in that fancy car of yours?
Yeah, well no, I don't
That's the digital audio broadcast standard
Which I presume all stations across Europe
Have to switch over to that initially
And that really is what's going on
In the automotive industry
When it comes to radio
Look at the states we have serious and XM
Bating it out for each other
Clearly serious on the winning hand
And in Europe we've got DAB
So if you actually, well you can't take your car from Europe
To the US doesn't make them much difference
But look at all these incompatible standards
Even though I know DAB will happen in the states as well
But that was, these were upgrades that were planned 20 years ago
In conjunction with the automobile industry
This stuff was done on purpose
Because that's the distribution outlet
And boy, what a disruptive technology
MP3 became, huh?
Because all of a sudden we're just burning CDs
Which everybody has, we're, we've got earbuds in
You know, if the folks from Omni Outliner Pro
Or listening, I use your Omni Outliner
All the time from my show prep
And I really, really love it
But something happened with a recent upgrade
Which I don't understand
When I, when I save an outline that has MP3s in it
Or even if I export it
About half of the MP3s
And I can't quite figure out why
Which ones do it for what reason
Convert to quick time movies
So they actually have the dot MP3 extension
Then they get a dot MOV extension
And then they won't open unless you manually remove that extension
And it probably adds seven or seven to ten minutes of prep time
It's pretty annoying
If you could figure that out for me, I'd really appreciate it
And I've been on the network for a couple of weeks now
But I want to introduce you to these two women
Personally
Well, maybe not personally
They'll do it personally
We interrupt Adam Curry's Daily Source Code
For this important montage
From roomgirls.com
Video podcast repeat
This important montage from theroomgirls.com
Video podcast
I am Karla
And I'm Karla
Welcome to Rumor Pearls
We're two sisters
Woohoo
Both of them all
Here, Ben
And it's now
No community service going on there
I'll tell you that much
Click here
Vote here
I've gone MTV, I believe
It's a video I've had
But to Karla, that is a diamond ring
Essential
Nothing like cheap wine
Look at the freaking size of this ad
When they become rich and famous
Which we will
$2.99
I'm a graphic designer
I'm not a graphic designer
They're cute
They're pretty cute
I actually check in the bottom
I'm like
Oh Jesus
But anyway
You're getting that
Well, you know what?
One little thing, the one thing I was thinking
I'm younger boys
Is you can train that
You can train that
That's the good thing
There were already following
I know
They are trainable
They're trainable
We'll take that
Hey Adam, we're the Rumor Girls
I'm Carla
And I'm Karen, we're two sisters from Portland, Maine
And we want to tell you a little about our podcast
We're the podcasting trendsetters here in Maine with our new video podcast
It's like sex in the city meets the real world
We have a wide range of both male and female fans
Girls want to hang out with us
And guys want a data
We've even started to expand our Rumor Girls brand
With our new audio podcast Rumor Girls on cut
We're all the dirt comes out
And the most exciting part of this new show is
We're a part of a pod family
A pod show network
So visit us at Rumor Girls.com
For a little piece of the action
Oh stop teasing
Just stop teasing William
I gotta get a Patricia up here
I gotta get on the show today
Hey Adam, this is Matt
Alfred Matt's basement workshop
Hey, just want to let you know that you and your listeners are welcome to come down to the shop
And check out what I'm doing
I got a little podcast
All about woodworking
Both the amateur's perspective on it
So we're talking about
We've been talking about tools
And we're going to start getting some design
And furniture building and everything
It's another one of those hobby podcasts
It makes me a hobbycaster
I'm not sure, I gotta work on that name anyways
But you and the listeners are more than welcome to come on over
You can check me out at iTunes
You can check me out at podcast alley
Hey, just come on over to Matt's basementworkshop.com
And you can check out the show notes and the links and everything
And what did you just come on down in?
The door's always open
And as I ask you say, maybe you'll put on a little ear protection
And put on some safety glasses
Alright, I'll be looking forward to hearing from you
And take care everybody
Straight grains and sharp blades, buddy
I think I played that one already
Didn't I? Straight grains and sharp blades
If not, I really like it
Nothing like a bit of wood after the rumor girls
You know, I got to
I really wanted to ask Patricia what she thought of her short stay at
The draft and darts
Hold on a second, you know what I'll call her
That's what I'll do
Because she was there for about half an hour, 45 minutes
See if we can get her on the line
Hold on a second, I'll put her on a speaker
So you guys can hear too
You can probably already hear
Yes, she's in Britain
I can tell by the ring
We're locating
I can hear the phone ringing last
It's probably right next door
Oh man, this is this is lame
Hold on a second
I think her phone is upstairs
Hold on
Let me call the home line
They usually does it
I wish they could make blackberries not do that
That'd be so much cooler
Okay, you can actually hear the phone
Hey baby
Hey listen, I'm in the middle of the show
When I wanted to ask you about the
About the meetup we did at the bricklayers arms
Can you come and talk about it
The meeting?
Yeah, with the podcasters
In the spot where we were
Yeah, exactly in London
Okay baby, thanks
Okay
In the meantime, well Patricia's coming up
We go over to the listener line
Which opened up yesterday
If you're, we have two numbers one in the states
65 65 657
Or in the UK
Hi Adam
It's Neil Ford
Just a quick voice message
To say a lot of the phone number idea
Really cool
Meet back and leave
Audio comments
While catching up with the DSC in the car
Actually brilliant
Great to meet you all
Sunday
And thank you to Ron
You and Chris
Thank you Timack
It's a British podcast interview
That was really cool
Thank you
And one last thing
It was Paul Nichols
I've cast Paul's
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Thank you once again
Which headphones
You know, keep producing the DSC
As many times and as long as you like
Yeah, great, cool
And I love the numbers
Thank you
Bye
Because I wasn't 100% sure all of a sudden
It's just the paranoid set scene
Hey babe
Hey Adam, that's a taxi elevator
Oh yes
The glass elevator
Did you see any golden tickets laying around?
No
Because we're going to hand more out today
Oh, is that?
Yeah, we're going to do another developer cast
I was going to do it yesterday
But Aaron, you know, Aaron O'Neill
Who's the database
Yeah, Australia
She's off on a course at a
SQL course or something
She keeps emailing me saying that
There's a whole bunch of nerd guys there
And it's horrible
Yeah, I was just having lunch
Not that the listeners care
No, because they won't see it
I was in the middle of my lovely lunch
Hey, I got this
So I have this phone line now
So people can call in
I have a new jersey number
Which I thought will be nice and new jersey number
Listen, it's a great number
2016256357
It's a nice number, isn't it?
Nice numbers
And I sound nice
And have a UK number
O2076813753
I don't like that number
No
Thank you for agreeing
Listen to this
Listen to this for a second
Hello, Adam
Roger, yeah
Actually, I don't mean it's not
He's pulled but that's my impression of Roger
Oh, good to do
Anyway, good to make you do the day Adam
And
But it's actually
Don't say it's normal
It's nice and 18 Patricia
Because she had a bit more time
And I just love Patricia
I think she's brilliant
I spent a couple of minutes just having a really good chat with her
And whatever
There we go
Now it's sunny, isn't it?
How do people turn out?
You turned out to be a longer and thinner
I thought she was probably turned out
To her and probably wider than you thought
Well, but there we are
Are you talking on the show
About a couple of things
First of all, the DSL days is sweet cowboy
But off my drum kit
And
Yeah, definitely
Well, yes, the American
British
Not because I thought you would say that
You know, you can basically think
What I said yesterday
Mm-hmm
Is that
I noticed that while I was in London
That when you're in American
It British women just
I don't know maybe I was reading it wrong
But it's like they start flirting with you immediately
Really?
And I was saying maybe the other way around as well
The Americans were just rolling your head
This
Don't pop the balloon yet
Oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah
Okay, baby
Men are so stupid
Oh, thanks
Let's listen to what Paul has to say all that
It's funny, and I absolutely look at any of the
Costs of the states
I like how warm the American's flow cover
Lots and lots of American friends
A lot of business owners
Maybe Paul was getting horny
I don't know
There we go
I'll tell you what the British actions
I think when the states definitely
The Americans are doors
I represented American ideation
Two in company
They're usually a bit
Some very big business with
The sagas
So you'll have something in London
But more than not there is in Louis
Allure in Indiana
And that was good fun
But now I've really particularly enjoyed the hospitality
I think the American hospitality
And
Do you think that's different
The American hospitality from British hospitality?
Yeah
Mm-hmm
Well, American hospitality is like
Take them on over
Let's have a party
The approach is more in your face
Yeah
And I think because of that
You believe it
But it sounds true
Now they always give you
Such a feeling of success
And oh you can do it
How interesting
Yes
That's it
You always feel good
Good for me
Wonderful
Exactly
But they really know
How great how you will make it
You know
How about the Brits though
I remember Eve on and I had once
A
An appointment in one of the hotels in London
When we used to live in Holland
Yeah
And it was from a records company
And it was with the Star Sisters
And so we had the guy
The guy was over there
We had to meet in somewhere
I said we were waiting for him
And it took a while
But then finally he came
With a very big mouth
Hi girls
It's so good to see you
And remember the above
I was in America
And I know that yeah
And I know there was something
And we had to wait
And he had a sort of remark
Like
Oh
Doesn't matter
Because you're going to be rich
And you're going to be famous
Anyway
That was his, you know, right away
Right
And it gave us a very
It made you feel good
You feel good
But judging from the royalty statements
Judging from the royalty statements in the UK
He didn't do such a good job
No nothing happened
But you know that moment
We look at each other
Oh that sounds good
You know
So how about the bridge
It makes you feel good
Well the bridge of our very
The bridge of our very
Almost
And they, I think they wouldn't
Exet your raid
No
Redden
You know they would
Take it back a little bit
And you know what I mean?
Hold back a bit
And hold back a bit
And not to exaggerate
It's more the truth
I guess
I hope so
Well
We don't have a lot of people
It came over actually
Mary
But very nice
Very talkative
And very
Absolutely
Yeah
And you know
We had dinner right away
With our neighbors
Straight very
But I was not
And we'll not flirt with Mary
You always flirt with everybody
But anyway
I had a great time
Meeting the guys
Yeah
Well let's listen to the rest of Paul's
Comment then I want to ask you about that
He's far, far, back to probably
But she's saying that
She should be warm
Service
But when he got so restaurant
Or something particular
I'm sure you've noticed this
The service over here
That's true
Girl
Yeah
Absolutely
We were at the Ivy
Which is supposed to be the bomb
Digity restaurant
It took forever
To get our food
And the lobster that you had
I was raw
Oh
One half of it was raw
And you told the waiter
And then he was like
Oh, that's a bummer
No, I said to him
You said you're done
I said no
And I didn't like it
And he said, oh
I'm sorry
And that was it
That was it
It's right
I'm sorry to hear that
Yeah
And that was it
Okay
But it's true
It's true
Because in America
If you order something
If you order your food
It needs to be good
It needs to be exactly the way you want it
You can tell them
You know the way you want it
Nobody will say anything
Because Americans
100%
Quality
Folks listening to a
Serious Stars 102
If you want to hear more of
The lovely lady Patricia
They'll have to download the rest of the show
A daily source code dot com
And of course
We'll meet again tomorrow
Same time on 102
On Serious for the Friday festivities
Lady Patricia
Children at her feed
On 101
How you make ends meet
Who pays the money
Now who has the money
When you need the rent
I don't
I'm so bad at that
I don't not very good at the lady
I never liked that song
I haven't
Didn't have a couple of Beatles songs
And you're coming out again
They're going to remaster them
And you'll be able to buy them digitally
Yeah
For the 20th time of
Bought the Beatles
Records
At the month
cassette tapes on albums
On CDs
Frank Frank Sinatra
Son was in the city
What's his name?
Frank Junior
Frank Sinatra
How cool is that?
Yeah
My name is Frank Sinatra
How do you look?
He doesn't have the looks of his day
And who is his mom?
Yeah
That's a good question
And the first is
Nancy
Nancy with laughing face
What is Nancy's daughter?
No, Nancy is also his daughter
But it's the old Nancy
And the song was about his wife
I guess
So he's son was in town
And he promoted a little bit of the show
That's going on in that
Patricia by the way
It's completely all over mainstream media
She keeps me up to speed
And what's going on?
Who's shagging who?
If I knew that
I would have known a little bit more about it
But anyway
So to show Frank Sinatra is in town
Which is absolutely great
Great reviews
The theater production
Yeah
And he said that the orchestra is great
Wonderful ballet
And he said
And then the guy from the news
Said the anchor man said
Do you think most more artists could do that
Like your dad
Be like Frank Sinatra
Have a show like this
And he said you know what?
The Beatles you'd have that
The Beatles you'd do
Isn't it a great idea
Well, they're what?
Remember there was Beatles mania
Don't you remember?
No, not like that
I mean with real footage
Oh, okay
And now with the songs and a band
And then and every
That would be great
I would go
Yeah
Hey, we're going to see Joan Collins
I got the tickets
Oh, yeah, that's right
She has a one woman show
In evening
And evening with Joe
But Joe
Yeah, we just think it's amazing that she can still stand on her legs
That's not true
You think that
Let me finish up this bit with Paul
I want to talk to you about the podcast
Back in the side back in the side
So over in the states
It really is very, very good
Anyway
That's my
Sorry, I'm sort of like an idiot here
Yeah
I'm sort of like a horrible talking
So I'm about finally
I'm sort of an idiot
And that's more
Daly and spit than my boss
And you're on to sign
Hi, everything's okay
Yeah, all the way best
Right now
All right, thank you
So
Yeah, I'm my team, yeah
So you came to the podcast
There's a draft and darts
Yeah, yeah
What'd you think?
It was a fantastic
What were you expecting?
It's that I had to leave
Because it was getting too crowded
And too smoky for you
That's not very good for my little heart
But
You have a big heart
It's so huge
I can see it pounding
Through your chest right now
I know
But it's not that healthy
So I see you stand
Looking at your chest
In a pub
Ah
But it was very nice
The guys were so nice
Yeah, we had a nice chat
What'd you talk about?
And well, the funniest thing that I came in
And I didn't expect to actually
What happened
Was high pressures are nice to meet you
And remember you said this
He said that and was so cool
When you said this
And I thought
Oh my god
Well, people listen
These are what I've been telling you
Yeah
You know, because we are having a normal conversation
And you know what?
And I have no idea
To say I really enjoy talking to you like this
We should maybe we just have headphones and microphones
Wherever we sit
So we just talk like this
You open up more
Well, you have a mic in front of you
Maybe it's
Maybe it's not just a mic that makes me open up
Maybe it's anything that's long and hard
Oh
Oh, you got to hear this from Angie
Hold on a second
Listen to this
Hey Adam
I know I'm not actually a listener
But I couldn't resist trying out the feedback
So mine pretty cool
Yeah
So you should have share a lot on Friday
The one thing that's really stuck in my mind
Is this energy
Because you should have a strap on
Yeah
Anyways
Talk to you later
Didn't know me stuck in your mind
Yeah
My good seed you shouldn't say those things
What's going to happen?
They're going to beat me up
Yeah
He doesn't
Sometimes I tell you
Yeah, you don't like that one
Don't say those things
Yeah
Ever since I started web-logging Patricia
And I have had an ongoing
Let's call it conversation
About the things that I talk about
Oh, I argue yeah
No, well
Well, I don't agree
I don't agree
I
Understand you will
You know you're telling things
And you're writing them down
It's what people want to hear
You're very good in writing it down
Oh, then
I'm not good in writing it
Oh, I'm not good in writing it
No
Maybe more when you're writing it down
Well, maybe it's better
I don't write it down then
And
And sometimes I don't like it
Because I think it's too private
And I meet people
And you know, they tell me a sort of a whole story
About my private
Oh, but like
That's well, first of all
Would you rather have people
And magazines make it up
All the time
Or would you rather that people have an opportunity
To hear what you're really like
Yeah, but they might just
That's just a exaggerated
And make this a whole
iE hamburger
Who might exaggerate
All the cosUM's
Oh that c falagher
There are things that I don't
People wanna know
Who?
It's a about me
I'm saying things about me
Not about you
Yeah, hello
I'm married to you
Yeah
You know
So
But I'm not ashamed
Of me
No, I know that but I am
I'm a lady.
She's a lady.
You know there are things.
And you know I am honest.
I say a lot.
And you say lady things.
I input you know, I'm still a lady.
A lady.
I love that.
It's Linda.
Hello.
There's another.
Another.
That's not an.
Not just a fly.
No.
Hello.
That's not a fly.
you have some insurance for you. Computer says no. Computer says no. Yeah. It's so
horrible, but don't we like it? It's on in the States. Little Britain. You've got to
watch that. If you look for it. I think they're shocked. I wonder if they broadcast
all of it because sometimes there's stuff in there that I'm like how that could
well maybe you could make on basically I guess. And they probably think that those
English people are nuts. That's right. I have to go there. That's what they're
probably said. I have to go there. You know, I have to go see the theater. Meanwhile
they're thinking man there's some horny shit going over there and then you came
now we got to go to Britain. Get us some boaty and Britain. Yeah. Right. All right baby.
Well thank you so much for her. So yes it was fun. I had fun in the past. My people huh?
Yeah. Yeah. Lots of people were there. Yeah. When you were going I think there was like
50. I know. I heard that. It was quite a mess. I missed a lot. And I have to say good
looking guys. Yeah. Yeah. Think so. Yeah. Real man. There were a couple of ladies that
ladies there too. Yeah. Just a couple. Yeah. Okay babe. And nice ladies. Exactly. Anything else?
No. You want a cup of soup? Oh. Your homemade soup? Is this the vegetable soup with ginger?
Yes. It's very good for your body. Yes. Well why don't you give me 20 minutes of
finish the show and then I'll come downstairs. Okay. And you can give it to me. All right.
What? The soup. Oh. Okay. Okay. Come on. It's your mind out of the gutter woman.
Bye bye. Okay. Bye bye. Thank you, honey. Just hang it up on the mic. Yeah. It's
not a good sound. What's not? You're sound that that's just the headphones. The sound
is great. Believe me. It sounds great. I'll play it for you later. All right. But I don't have
a good sound. You have a great sound. Just not in those headphones. That's what I mean.
Oh, I say hello Adam. It's Lord Colo podcast here. Regarding your discussion on
British and American accents and effects, they might have on the opposite sex on your
Delta Sierra Charlie 3-7-4. Well, yes, I too find that my marvelous
British accents makes ladies turn to jelly and throw themselves at my feet whenever I'm
in the United States of America. Not that I would take any notice at all, of course. What
would mean being happily hooked and bound to the wonderful Doctor Joe? Who I believe had a
rather splendid chin leg with yourself in London at the weekend? I understand that the
touch he had with you in her stupidestly sexy British accents involved the virtual
world of second life and donations of virtual marital appendages to Americans might call
a cock. Anyway, standardly titillating dialogue, I'm sure. We've been playing around a bit
in second life. We've even spent New Year's Eve at a wonderful party thrown by Sir Eric Rice
who has been doing some interesting audio and video podcast. I've over at Slack Street.
Go and check an album, look for spin-math in it's really rather splendid. Anyway, I was wondering
if you might pop a link on your blog side menu which links to your carpool in second life
and tell us what your second life name is. That would be wonderful. And finally, I was also wondering
when someone in second life does something really, really bad, did they go on to life row?
And after people died. Unfortunately, cut off there. He was on a roll too.
Yeah. And I definitely want to do that. I definitely want to put a link to the curry castle
because you can do that with second life. You can link to it from with a web link and it'll
open up second life and it'll take you right there. I'm just not quite done building. In fact,
I'm really not done yet. But listen, what happened yesterday? So, excuse me. So, what I like so
much about second life is you can yeah, you can build all this stuff. But they've got a whole
money flow and I'd like it so much because I can just spend money and buy whatever I want and then
I can adapt it. You know, that's a great way to learn just to buy stuff off the shelf and then
mess with the scripts and mess with the textures and the stretching and resizing and rotating
and customizing it all. And all of a sudden yesterday, as I'm about to purchase, what was I buying?
I think a waterfall. I get this message that if you're younger than 45 days old on second life,
you have a credit card limit, which is $150 US. So, I don't know how many second life
linden dollars that is, but you can tell I've spent quite a bit of money. But you know, land and
shit is expensive. And that castle, what do you think that sent me back? So, I'm like, well, wait a minute,
I'm looking all over the site and there's no way to buy more money until you're 45 days old.
And this is like, I can't believe this. Is this this is make it really a game? I mean, now I have
to go off and I have to figure out a different way of making money until I can cash some in.
I mean, this is not easy for guys for girls. Yeah, I mean, girls all over second life
make money by dancing in their escort services and in those all kinds of ways. And, you know,
that's really how it works. Guys coming with a credit card, they make chicks dance and I call them
chicks because that's what they are in these avatars that nothing more than chicks.
Some of them are escorts. You pay him for sex. And I'm reliably informed. And, you know,
that's how the money flows through the whole system. They go out and shop and buy shoes and
bling and all kinds of trinkets. It really, it really is art replicating life in this case.
And, you know, I think it's going to be a hell of a lot harder for a guy. I mean,
I'm sure that I could sex up my avatar and I could make some money in the blue boy club,
but not exactly my idea of fun, if you know what I mean. So, I sent off a message to second
life and I said, help. I want to spend more money. Can I please spend more money with your service?
Anyway, yesterday met a couple more people online. If you saw that Google video that I posted
a link to yesterday, this actually, I was surprised there's only five and a half thousand
concurrent connections at any one time, which doesn't seem like a lot, particularly for the amount of
horse horsepower they have to put behind this system to be able to render that, you know,
all of that stuff, only five and a half thousand streams. I make an only magic if this thing really
hits the big time. What is going to take to make that work and there's sometimes this horrible
lag that occurs and, you know, it really starts to harsh your mellow, particularly if you're building
something. But I met Spin Martin. I was out shopping and he was looking for fountain. I think he was
spitting up his place. For those of you who don't know who Spin Martin is, that's what was just
mentioned that audio comment by Paul. That's Eric Rice. It's funny because in real life, I probably
would have told him to go fuck off after some of the podcast he did about me and Podgeo. But in
second life, we were surprisingly civil to each. I don't know. My brains and overdrive.
Angie B was in yesterday. I was really cool to have Angie in the had her in the castle and
tour to around and it was the most time we spent together in communication ever, probably.
And I apologize for being like, I guess she was offended by something I said about her voice
work. Angie, you know, you're the dulcet tones of Miss Angie B, you're so beautiful and so sexy.
You know that. Anyway, I apologize. I tried to give her a beautiful dress. That's what I've been
spending on my money on. But I purchased the dress and then I couldn't give it to her. The only thing
I can do with this dress is wearing myself. Ah, wait a minute. Maybe that's how I can make some money.
Enjoy all kinds of music. Then lend me your ear. Here at the Ed's Mix Bad Podcast,
listeners enjoy all genres of Podsafe and independent artists. Excellent. You can even win a prize
on the Mystery Sound Contest. And for all the geeks out there, there's Ed's software tip.
New segments are being imagined at this very moment. So join me, Ed Oved, by downloading an episode
today, simply point your browser to Ed's Mix Bad.com. Music has always been part of your life.
Even from the one, it brings out the best in you. It brings out the worst in you.
Some music can affect your emotions so much. If you're not careful,
you might just get yourself a speeding ticket. Other music may be the tipping point.
That can push you to end life itself. So why not learn all you can from the artists
that affect you so much? That's just what we do here on Podsil Radio. Every show we feature a
single artist from the Podsafe music network. One that is so amazing that they can
call your emotions to explode. My thanks to Adam Curry and the Podsil podcast network
for inviting Podsil Radio into the lineup. Together, there is no emotion that we can't control.
So you there, Podsil Radio.com. Joe and welcome my friend.
YouTube have some dulce at tones. I'm really trying to stick to this 40 minute schedule. I'm
going to go over again today. But since we had the lovely lady Patricia on the show,
I'm going to skip the bit I want to talk about, which is fame and privacy. I'll keep that
for too. I'm going to do that tomorrow as well as I've got some excellent feedback on the silent
birth, the Scientology Silent Birth Treatment. I'm almost called the Silent Birth Treatment.
So if you have any if you want to weigh in on that do that today because I'll be talking about
that tomorrow on the Friday edition of the Charlie and I would really love some jam and songs.
I love the fact that you keep sending me suggestions just because it didn't get played doesn't
mean it's not in the queue or I haven't, you know, queued it up for for some other day.
Just keep the suggestions coming tomorrow. I really want a party that I really want to crank it out.
One last bit I want to do is from when you know when the Dutch start speaking English,
sometimes it can just be so endearing and this guy is doubly so because he does his show and this
feedback while on his skateboard. So and I'm curious, I just listen to Delhi source calls 372
at least I tried to listen to the last Delhi source go and you know when you're angry
Deep in your heart. You know what to do. Yeah, man. Think again. Deep in your heart. You know what to do.
Well, I'll have you know that I was skating when I was 12 years old. So that's what 29 years ago
28 years ago. No, 29 years ago. Oh, man. And I actually walked around with a little
tube of graphite my pocket and you know whenever my trucks got kind of jammed up or cruddy.
Because of course it couldn't you know we couldn't really afford the good stuff and I was living in the
Netherlands so we had kind of shitty boards but so I skateboard footballs like to invite you to our home
base in the Amsterdam Skate Park. Leave your old setup at home. I will hook you up with some new gear.
You're who? Yeah, we're going to roll a little bit around and bend your finish.
Yeah, all right buddy. I got you. All right one last song for today.
Here we go. This is traffic from the Alice project on the source code.
What else have you on your daily commute? How many of you have buckled up? Only to find you still
sitting in a long line of cars. You go in nowhere.
Slow. That's right. Sometimes I can't tell if it's an accident or road worker comes.
I mean I even get to my destination. Hey, I've got some place to be. Why are you in that truck?
Lookin' down at me. Why don't you keep your eyes on the road?
I don't even want to get there.
Can't you help me decide which route to take? I'm torn with indecision. I've been sitting here for half a day.
I'm afraid my car is going to overheat. Or is it just me? Is there anyone in the entire universe
that's happy to be stuck here like ants in different colored ants? It'll long line just wait
to get through the tunnel.
This time. So I've gone half a mile and I've got nine miles to go.
Nine miles to go. And the traffic report is getting me nowhere.
I'm the only one who has to get there. I have no.
I'm the only one who has to get there with my time.
Sitting in the light. Sitting in the light. Sitting in the light.
Sitting in the light. Sitting in the light.
The Alice project from New York City and the traffic song. Thank you very much to Melinda from
my Maryland podcast to convince the band to sign up for the pod save music network. Really appreciate it.
And it's good to have this type of tunes in the network. Loving it. And a big hello and goodbye.
The Chris Rockwell on his way back home. Gonna be completing the roll out of the
purchase. Well, we're ready to go. Basically. We're just waiting for everything to open up.
The developers coming into the pod show plus who have received their access codes. Now I believe
and the podcast delivery network. They're going to be able to see some of this and see some of
this development and Chris is going to Idaho where he'll be working. He continues to work with
Potcho, but it's going to be an Idaho. I'm going to miss your fat ass pooping in the office. Dude,
big time.
The portions of the show brought to you by Acqueview. Listen to Heather and Janelle at download.acqueview.com.
And of course, if you want to get a really good deal on a domain name, go to godaddy.com.
Use the code dsc1 on checkout. And that'll get either domain name for only $6.95.
Feel free to register a wacky one for me. By the way.
And I'll just mention one more time for those of you who won't get to website and want to call
right now if you're in the States 2016256357, if you're in the UK or in Europe, although
if you're in Europe calling the States is probably cheaper. O2O768137553. And tomorrow we're going to
really blow the house down with some Friday festivities. Thank you for staying subscribed. Thank you
very much for listening. Another Potcho Potcast. Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network
from Potcho and Limelight Networks. I love it.