Merry Christmas from all of us at punkuadeo.btpodshow.com
That was Tony talking then. I don't know how you talk. It's good in it.
Bye
everybody Adam here. This is Delta Cia Charlie 521, a podcast of Adam
Carey who likes to drink senseo your coffee. I, on the other hand,
a like to drink tech-lity. Hi! Back off!
Telly, everyone's cup of tea. Whatever you drink, make it tastier by adding
splenda sweetener to it.
New years he's approaching and we're all of us.
Cause oh seven can't be worse than oh six was.
Tom Cruise jumped on Oprah's couch went after broke shields,
but a grouch proved he's the nuttyest guy on her when he and Katie had a silent bird.
Mel Gibson got pulled over by the bus because he was driving really bus.
Checked in a rehab to kick the boost.
But what's he going to do about hating?
Choose.
Last year with a lot of crap all the dealing with the eye-a-toolers,
pay three bucks a gallon for our guests.
Last year was a real humdinger,
Paris Hill thinks she's a singer.
Hope next year is better than the last.
Mark Dolly's I am in congressional pages asking for picks and what their ages.
A lot of elections were uncontested because half a congress scout arrested.
Approval ratings are down for bus,
doesn't seem to know as head from his touch.
The president may not be too brave, but he's smart enough not to hunt with
Cheney.
Last year was a real humdinger,
Paris Hill thinks she's a singer.
Polarized caps are melting fast.
Last year was a lot of crap all the dealing
with the eye-a-toolers.
Hope next year is better than the last.
I hope next year is better than the last.
Hope as long as the last episode of the year.
The next year is better than the last.
Hope next year is better than the last.
Hopefully next year is better than the last.
Hope this year is better than the last.
everything to fuck up, but it's okay. And we got a good show for you today. A little bit
later than normal, but of course I spent a little bit of time preparing because I wanted
to do some 2007 media entertainment predictions for you. Everyone loves to look back at the
predict, you know, I looked back for my predictions from last year and I don't think I did any.
I certainly didn't do any on the weblog. I had to go into the way back machine at archive.org
to find my old weblog because of course the archives are all busted and broken through the
numerous moves and shifts to servers. No, no reason for it other than just complete chaos from
my domain name management systems. But I didn't find, yeah, I found one, I found a podcast
from the 30th of December 2006 daily source code. It was like episode 320 or something like that
where I was talking about comic strip blogger who would put a number of predictions for 2006 on
as a list and one of them was that Pod Show would be acquired by Yahoo. No, he said Ron Blumen
Adam Curry will sell Pod Show to Yahoo or AOL for $400 million. And I was laughing at it then
and still am CSB. But thank you very much for opening up the show. Very helpful.
So I got some of those for you. And of course, you know a final final thought of the week should
be final thought of the year and it won't really be a final thought. It'll be more like a looking
forward. What have I learned from 2006? Great news in the New York Times. It was, um,
see yesterday. Of course, you'll find a link in the show notes of this. Um, about the Marie Claire
mast head. And I think I've told you about this previously, but Marie Claire, which is a very
famous women's magazine, um, has a podcast. You can find it at Marie Claire dot pod show dot com
M-A-R-I-C-L-A-I-R-E. Marie Claire dot pod show dot com. It's called the mast head. And it's,
I'm very proud of this. It launches January 2nd. So you can already see a trailer online as a promo
clip and some background information. Um, it's, it's, if you saw the devil wears Prada,
then you'll recognize some of it. Only it's real life. And as we follow, um, the editors around
of Marie Claire, um, which, of course, deals a lot mainly with fashion. I should say lifestyle
and fashion. And this editor, editor and chief, she's fantastic. This British woman. She's so made
for the part. Really spot on. Um, so anyway, read the, the article in New York Times, um, and,
and then check out the trailer. And you might as well get the show because when it comes out
on the second of January, I think I, I think you're really going to like it. I showed it to my
own personal little test audience here, which consists of the left hand side of the spectrum,
Christina 16 and a half years old, and the right hand side of the spectrum Patricia 57 years old.
And guess what? Score on both points. Um, see what was in the news. Saddam Hussein.
So this is something I don't really understand. So the guy is going to be executed. He's been,
um, he's been sentenced to hanging to death by hanging instead of any other quote, Hugh
Maine way, um, because it then equates him with the common criminal. And I presume that, you know,
this is an Iraqi thing, because I don't think it came out of the, uh, the war crimes court in the
haig. Um, and it has to by some strange laws. It's very hard to get, you know, to get the truth
out of newspapers. Again, the only truth in the newspapers is in the advertising. It's very hard
to find out what really is the full story. But apparently what I've extrapolated is that the sentence
has to be carried out within 30 days. And, um, it could even happen as soon as the next couple of days.
But now, and here's the thing I don't understand. It's going to be done in, you know, in like some
closed off secret place. And, and, you know, Krike, look at what we've gone through in Iraq.
Look at all that's happened. Look at all the coverage we have. Look at, I mean, even though
governments have really tried to stop, um, the images of our soldiers coming home, um, in boxes.
You know, there's still there's so much horror to be seen and so much horror to be felt. I mean,
why don't we make this a prime time special? Where's Haraldo in Iraq when you really need him?
You know, let's show the world what it really means to hang someone. You know, I really don't
understand why this is going to be hidden away. I don't like that at all. I think if, if we're going to
do this and if, you know, because no one is saying stop the execution. You know, so let's see it.
I think the public deserves to see it. I really, really believe in that.
Hey, if you don't want to watch it, you don't have to. But, you know, that would, that would really,
you know, it's like we're, we're so in the middle ages, still, you know, shooting hot
LED each other in a fucking desert. But yet when it comes to the hanging of, uh, of a criminal,
who killed thousands of people, oh, well, you know, we don't want to, that would be too shocking. We
don't want to see it. Bullshit, I say. I say, put that shit on the air. Prime time.
I don't know who this is, but put shit on that hole. Okay, message received.
Hey, Adam, this is Scott up here in Alaska. Did you know a band in the Pods eight music network
is going to be starting off this new year for the United States or anybody else who's going to
be tuning into NBC's New Year's Eve party, which is going to be hosted with Carson Daily at Time Square
New York. Yeah, that's right. Their panic at the disco and from their CD, a fevery
can't sweat out. This is our song, a time to dance. Happy New Year, Guy, and everybody else here
on the Daily Source code.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Give me, give me, give me, I'll explain it, give me, we're life
Shotgun, you say what I need
Shotgun, what we shotgun, what we need
We'll see it choose this role
It's a boy and make it seem too slow
Come here, come here, come here
Cry
Remember we did from the tears and the teeth right out
To the vibe
I'd better be
For so many boys
Highly in the edge of the midnight
But we hope for change
Change
Baby, baby, baby
How's it going, won't you?
Where is your boss here?
Oh no, no
You're bullying a trigger
Falling the trigger
Oh no
How's it going, won't you?
Where is your boss here?
Oh no
You're bullying a trigger
Falling the trigger
Oh no
Come here, come here
This is screaming for love
Oh no
Come on, come on
This is screaming
This is screaming for love
Come here, come here
Come here,, come here
Come here
Come here, come here
Come here and come here
Come here
Come here, come here
Patricia said a headphones got a real nice set of AKGs, which he tried out. She said she loved it.
She loved the sound and well, probably she had all kinds of stuff to do today. So I couldn't
couldn't drag her in. I'm sorry. I'm sure we'll have some kind of recordings over the next two
weeks during the moves. We also went to to check out our our stuff yesterday. As the famous
George Carlin once said, when it's your things, it's your stuff and when it's someone else's
things, it's their shit. And so we looked at it with both eyes. At the stuff side and the
shit side, boy, we had stuff in storage or shit in storage for so long. Over two years and stuff
has just kind of like rotten away. You know what? Besides, I don't know, there must have been 15 boxes
full of admin, which of course you have to slap a slap around for seven years of your life in
case the taxes decide to audit something. And boy, I'm happy I've always slept that stuff around
because I've had many and all of it. But we also found I think at least a thousand. You know,
the, you know, the CD, the Patricia made for her for a cosmetics company with four tracks on it.
And I've played a couple of them, Misty for me, Foggy Day in London town. Two others, which
escaped me at the moment. Well, I think we have a thousand of those completely new in the box.
I mean, I had no idea. I thought we were completely out of stock. So we're going to do something
with that in 2007. I definitely want to give them away or maybe even better sell them and then
give them money to charity. It's really, it's a nice CD. And, you know, the number of people who
listen, I'm sure at least a thousand would like to have a CD buyer. So that's something that we
found was pretty interesting. What are all these heavy fucking boxes? Oh my God, it's CDs,
the ones we thought we didn't have anymore of. And my face is a little bit reconfigured finally.
Well, actually, the face is still kind of the same. But somewhere around mid, mid morning today,
the penicillin finally kicked in. And, you know, penicillin makes me a thar jick and, you know,
and sometimes little scratchy and itchy, there's, oh, you know, I think everyone has probably
some light form of allergic reaction. Maybe you might not even notice it. But this isn't heavy
ass shit. And I've got like two separate boxes. And one of them I have to take four times a day with
eight at six hour intervals and the other one three times a day at eight hour intervals. And that
does require quite a bit of that administration. Thank God for for Google account. Really makes
a big difference. Still love to hear from you. You know the number by now, I hope.
Now, I'm hoping that by the time I get my studio set up in the new in the new cottage that I'll
be able to create a couple of my own best of Charlie's. I have about five slots left. If you
want to create a best of Charlie, 24 minutes and 30 seconds long, it'll air on the daily source
code feed as well as on serious, serious stars 102. So you can put your own plugs and shit in there.
And I just go crazy. Do whatever you want. Email me first if you're going to do it though. Okay. So
I so I don't have more than the 10 slots that are available. And so no one gets really disappointed.
And again, if you if you just call into the phone line, I'm sure I'll be able to slip something
in myself in the next two.
Next week's top stories in offbeat, entertainment and technology news. Plus, find unique stories
you won't see anywhere else. Forget network news. Find out what's really going on in the world
around you. For more information visit www.literallyeverythingblog.com. That's www.literallyeverythingblog.com.
I don't really have any new years resolutions to speak of other than to keep on riding the wheels
off this motherfucker called life. But I do promise myself that I'm going to do a lot more
blogging. I tried this past year really to do everything in audio and what I've noticed is that a lot
of the facts get turned around. Things I say people hear things the way they want to hear them.
Sometimes I miscommunicate things as well. And things come across incorrectly. Or when I hear people
spit it back, I'm like, oh, that's not exactly what I meant. So I'm going to do more blogging.
And I don't know if you looked at Podshow Plus recently, but the blogging tools have gotten a
shitload better. We have a fantastic fucking editor now that's built right in. You can do all kinds of
cool shit. You can embed stuff from your gallery directly into your blog post. So if you have
a picture's uploaded, then you can select one and it'll just insert it automatically.
We're going to do the same for video. The same for show episodes, the same for tracks. And it's
going to be all kinds of cool shit that you can do. Really, it will become a true social media network.
We're well on our way, I think, but it's going to get even better. And there's some other
things I got to fix as well. Adam is party and quick one mate. The levels your podcast is
DSE520 was coming through loud and clear in my ear buds. I had them jammed in deep as you do.
And then I made the mistake of letting it play out. So the advert for the end,
little blue nerd rums out. And that's really not very good is it. So could you have a look at that
for us? It really does suck ass as you chaps with today. Thank you. Bye bye.
Well, what would you chaps say then? It's so funny. Parkie cracked me up, dude. He goes on the
forms and yells about me and yells about me. But he'll still listen and call in and help me out.
And that is much appreciated. Yeah, the problem is all mine, actually. It's not it's not pod show.
Here's what happened when I reconfigured the studio. For some reason, I've set up, well, I thought
I set up the proper routing, but I just can't get enough signal into cast blaster. So I'm running
consistently at about minus 10 dB, which is definitely soft. And it's, uh, you're right. What's happening
is you're turning up the sound to be able to, it's all digital. So it's not like you get anything extra.
You just want to be able to listen to the show. And then when the show is over, you know,
incomes 0 dB and it blows out your ear drums. So what I'll do is I will remind you with the
end of the show to turn down the volume. And then by the time I get the studio, rejiggered and
re-fixed, I'll have that fix as well. So it's, uh, it's not happening. It's impossible that it's
happening with every single podcast that I'm sure it's only happening with the daily source code.
Just because, uh, what's coming out is, uh, it's just the levels are just way off.
Although they are p-dub approved. I'll have you know. Let's do it today. It's Friday.
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday. Food about Friday. I am spinal fund for the week.
Well, I tell everybody, well, I promised you. Well, yeah.
Gotta be sufficiently prepared for, uh, for predictions for the new year. That's what we're
going to do in today's final thought of the week. Here are my 2007 media entertainment predictions.
The music sales industry is going to suffer a total meltdown in 2007 as several established
artists without a current record deal will crack the online social media networks.
Now, all those sales will not be significant. Mainstream media will build a case against the big
three labels, touting their demise. And that's going to make shareholders nervous, which will
result in a stock tail spin and an exodus of management. Now, the only people left to run the
joints will be lawyers and they won't be able to maintain sufficient levels of creativity to keep
the business viable. Now, the artist responsible for the upheaval will manage their
online customer base through their own online presence, utilizing, you know, the myriad of
APIs available to them for sales, for messaging and media distribution through all kinds of channels,
like PMN and LCD baby. Independent record labels will become management facilities for artists
and mark my words, they will start to invest in talent. The music publishing business is going to
flourish in 2007 as new players innovate on licensing terms and become talent development agencies
in some cases this will, in fact, be the current independent record labels. You're liking it so
far. A small group of software engineers will become rich and famous after they realize the
weak link in the iPod chain is iTunes and they're going to build an open source cross-platform
iTunes replacement that will open the floodgates to new content. Whatever you do, please don't
send me email and tell me that's already happened because it hasn't. It'll catch on when
it's the right application. Now, because of this and other mobile-playing options, drive-time audiences
will surge for audio podcasts. With this surge, though, public radio programming will also
surpass the audience of commercial radio. Because let's face it, public radio ain't bad, folks,
as we could shit there. Furthermore, in 2007, Jiselle will start a celebrity call-in show titled,
I don't know who this is, but stop fucking calling Jiselle asshole, where host Jiselle tries
to guess the identity of celebrity phone callers based on sexual clues. Okay, made that one up.
In 2007, at least one video blogger will grow a huge audience that will grow very quickly through
viral and social media networks. In other words, you're going to peer about it through IM or
read an email, maybe stumble upon it otherwise, but you will be hearing about it. The socially
disconnected will become aware when the local weatherman quips about it during his evening report.
That's how it works. It's what viral is all about, or let's just call it social.
The serialized programming of these, this video blogger, or maybe even more, will strike
a chord with the audience because of the words, the writing, the timing, delivery.
It'll be highly consumable and accessible. So-called production value will be of no importance.
Now, on the other side of this spectrum, for 2007, I predict opinion based in dramatic video
programming will attract audiences that demand innovative production values as different from expensive.
It's innovative. Both types of programming will be able to build their brand into valuable media
properties, advertisers, check this out in 2007, and we'll have to audition to sponsor these programs.
By the way, I'm going to post all of these in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com,
not today because I don't want people just reading it. I want them to actually listen to the
fucking show, but I will post them after the new year, so we'll have an online record of it.
In 2007, members of online podcasting communities will come to realize that a community of
podcasters is about as silly as a community of broadcasters, and they will split into three
main factions, broadcasting for part for profit, podcasting for dummies, and podcasting to save
the world and win valuable cash prizes. By the way, podcasting for dummies is a metaphor,
it doesn't mean you're dumb if you don't want to make money. Okay?
In 2007, reality-based talent shows will become the new mainstream record companies,
making hundreds of millions and revenues from syndication, SMS voting, and licensing.
Every record they will release will be a huge success. Unfortunately,
they're only going to release one record for 13 weeks to stay in sync with their video programming,
so we'll see hundreds of similar talent-based reality programming on television, on cable, online,
all across the internet, all with their own distribution networks and targeted audiences.
Potential contestants will soon be scouted just like record companies used to do
in the darkest corners of the crappiest hell holes on earth.
And Simon Call will suffer physical injury after sore loser or cost him at a public appearance.
But that's not really that hard to predict that now is it?
Search-based advertising will level out mid-here as advertisers increase budgets for sponsorships
of media brands that they want to identify their own brand with. Brand advertising pricing in 2007
will ship from cost per thousand to an audience engagement metric.
Furthermore, let me just give myself a little more time there. The creative artist agency in
Hollywood will begin packaging programming amongst multiple brands that will include media properties
outside of the traditional mainstream media domain. In 2007, an advertising form known as the
infomercial will gain critical acclaim as spot advertising shifts from 30 seconds to long-form
programming concepts. Will it blend anybody? And finally, prediction for 2007, the tech world will
hardly take notice or complain about the demise of the Gilmore gang after Steve Gilmore
tries to gain attention by quitting the show and his job at Potcho.
Shortly thereafter, former Zif Davis and tech crunch technology reporter Natalie Delcante will break
through the Wall Street Journal's web 2.0 smoke screen reporting with a series of audio and video
programs produced exclusively for the Potcho network. Wait a minute, that's not a prediction.
That's already true.
Yo, what's up, AC? This is Jersey Todd, the official musicologist of the Chacha.
Hey, you know, this week had me thinking about the life of the potsafe Godfather, Mr. James Brown,
and while I'm incredibly sad about his passing, I have to think about his life as a celebration.
I also have to thank him for the many, many good times that he caused in my life. I also have to
think about the thousands and thousands of artists that he influenced. His sound is all over the
Potsafe music network in one way or another. One of the bands that you can really hear JB sound is the
band's Shag out of New York. This is something a little different than how the Godfather would have
done it, but I think he would have approved. This is the band's Shag with the song,
Boba, Boba, on the Daily Source Code. Hey, have a great week everyone. I'll talk to you soon.
Boba, Boba, I stand on top of the world. Look around and you've been all the
Potsafe, I stand on top of the world. I stand on top of the world. I stand on top of the world.
I stand on top of the world. I stand on top of the world. I stand on top of the world.
I stand on top of the world. I stand on top of the world. I stand on top of the world. I stand on top of the world.
I stand on top of the world. I stand on top of the world.
I stand on top of the world. I stand on top of the world. I stand on top of the world.
I stand on top of the world.
I stand on top of the world. I stand on top of the world.