This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 418.
Can you dig in?
$60 million worth of airplanes trapped to my house.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky ingredients.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
I'm testing kids, I don't curry.
She works nights.
She sleeps days.
Oh, she gets them in their coffee.
At a 24 hour cafe and she just wants to find someone.
Who'll understand her?
When she gets home, she wakes the kids.
Oh, she tells them all the story.
About the fun of things she did they go to school.
And she's alone inside a head.
And for a flash, I'm on in the night.
She keeps the cool.
She tries not to stress.
As she quickly cleaned her head.
It feels like everything's a man.
She takes a moment to see herself in the mirror.
And for a flash, I'm on in the night.