Delta Sierra Charlie 356 Mr. Look, I am Detective Mahoney, and this is Detective Maloney.
I detect.
Mr. Love, you were picked up by one of our officers after some complete recording.
It seemed you were walking around talking to yourself, and you were asking people if they wanted to answer five questions.
Can you tell us what this is about?
It was for my podcast.
A podcast, it's a sound scene tour.
A sound scene tour.
Yeah, it's...
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Okay, right after you mentioned to the officer some things, I set all some red flags.
Basically, who are you sending up the river?
No, no, my eye river to create an MP3 of talking.
Don't bring the military police into this.
No, no, not MPs and MP3.
Look, we just want to know.
Who you're working for? Who is the godfather?
No, no, not a godfather. It's the pod father. You know, pod show, it's Adam.
Who are you sending up the river for the godfather?
No, I'm using my eye river to record interviews told the officer that the pod father, godfather, whatever,
was going to let you quit your day job.
Right, right. If my interview with the stranger podcast goes on pod show.
No, no, no.
What case? What are you running drugs for this pod father to?
No, podcast. Look, we just want the truth.
Who are you working for? What are you doing?
Is prostitution involved with his love house thing?
No, that's love house radio. That's my other podcast.
Love house radio interview with the stranger there.
Stop talking to the riddles. You need to come clean or throw in your mark.
Like the DSC, Adam Curry?
LSD.
No, no, no, no.
Yeah, Adam Curry.
Curry from MTV.
Yes, Adam Curry from MTV.
Look, missed a lot.
Just listen, just listen to my pod.
Point. I'll listen to it.
And I'll tell you what I think.
Okay, here, just stick to your redden.
Okay, that's not too bad.
Yeah, and you can find it. You can subscribe at lovehouseradio.com
or interview with a stranger.com
And go to podshow because maybe it'll be on their one day.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky drinks, baby.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Oh, fantastic.
It's Adam Curry.
I can't fall down.
My feet don't touch the ground.
I need to see the wire underneath.
The crown below.
For the last.
You know.
Well, help.
To save me from reality.
I'm losing ground and I'm feeling fast.
I see the sound of a trouble fast.
I never want this to be.
I know this isn't right.
But this is the light.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
I'm losing ground and I'm feeling fast
I've seen the sound of the trouble fast
I never wanted this to be
I know there's no right, but this is life for me
They sure know how to kick ass down there in Texas, don't they?
It's the longest running reality show in the business
Good morning, it's Monday, coming to you from Curricondo
It's been perfectly timed, we had a beautiful weekend, the sun was shining both on Saturday
It doesn't look like it's going to be really nice today
Just looking at my 180 degree view here from the bay over to the mountains over to the city
Looks a little bit overcast, no matter because it's a week full of all kinds of cool stuff surprises
I'll be the things that we don't know about of course, good things planned
This weekend though, I hope you had a good weekend
Of course, I was up way too early on Saturday morning tried to sleep and didn't work out entirely
Made until about 830
Even though I don't remember what I did Friday evening, I think I just went home and collapsed again probably
Yeah, just hung out all day and I'm sorry, I didn't hang out all day
What am I talking about?
Around 2 o'clock, I went down to the basement here at the condo all the way down to P4
And there she was in all her glory, Trinity hadn't looked at her since I got here
Left rear wing, a little bit soft, so cranked her up, of course, started no problem
I love that after not having run for weeks on end
Right over to the Sanoko station, whatever it is here, paid my 50 cents for the air hose, jacked her up
And then went out to the biofuel oasis in Berkeley, California
This is the place I've been talking about that I hadn't been able to get out to
And of course, I only had about a quarter tank left, so it was either that or pooping in it
And I don't think the fuel filters are ready for that yet
So Trinity, my biofuel oasis beast, bio diesel beast
Took her out there, this place is really cool, this biofuel oasis
It's basically a garage, literally with the garage door open
And they have two big vats away in the back of
I presume as a biodiesel that have a nice kit there
With, I don't know how big those, those storage tanks are, but they're big and plastic
And they two of them fit side by side in a regular car garage
And it's just one person there, now I had my gear with me
But I didn't just want to jump out and say, hey, I'm sound seeing
I actually want to talk to some folks over there and learn a little bit about
About their operation, so it was just one person there, she was brand new
But she said that she would get someone to get in touch with me
So I can go out there and actually properly interview any of the owners
I think it's an owner operated type deal, it must be six or seven people
Who worked there judging from the pictures on the wall and stuff
And so you basically you back your car in and there's a real pump there
In the garage, it's a kind of an old one
$3.60 a gallon
Which is fine, I don't know, I don't have to go through the hassle of making it
And of course, that's not $3.60 which is going to some jackass oil company
It's going to some people who are actually trying to do something
And so I'm happy to pay that
So a couple of observations, first of all
Now this is kind of in an almost like an industrial area of Berkeley
On was it fourth street, I think it is
And so you know, you kind of expect to see some trucks around
Or some beat-up cars
Particularly the ones that would be going to get bio diesel
Well guess what?
While I was there, I think I saw at least three high-end Mercedes-Benz CDIs
So that's their diesel injection
Whatever, so I don't know what the C stands for
But luxury cars and not old ones, new cars
So that was really hard warming to see that people are actually going out
And going out of their way to go and get bio diesel
Just whatever their reasons are
But it's not because you got an old car and you're experimenting around
Like myself, people are really seriously into this
So that was, that was just fantastic
Cash or check only, no credit card
So probably not this day, but probably next time
I come into town
Which will be somewhere in May
To late April
That's when we go out there, I'm going to interview
Really nice operation though, biofueloasis
I think it was a biofueloasis.com
I'll make sure I put that into the show notes
So then came home
Ron and Martha called me up and said let's go to a movie
I was funny, actually went back out to workly
Not Berkeley to
How it's the one town across the bridge
I'm a little fuzzy this morning
It's not even 645 yet
The movie of choice was firewall by Harrison Ford
Definitely a movie just to go out and see a movie
Technically
Because this is such a typical Harrison Ford movie
Where he has some kind of job
Where he can get stuff done
Bad guys come in, kidnap his family
They force him to do something, he gets pissed off
He kicks everyone's ass, they walk away
With smoke in the background on the hill
And it's all a beautiful thing
But in this case, it was about
Breaking into computer systems and about firewalls
And I'd have to say in the whole plot
There were about
Probably about five holes I could have driven
Trinity through sideways
From a technical aspect or from basically
How the hell could they think that they would never get caught
Doing it this way type of aspect
Because there's just there's no way that
That what they were doing was untraceable
It doesn't matter
Basically, fun to go out
Fun to hang, fun to sit in the movie theater
It was a good theater by the way
One of the AMC with really good sound
And the picture was nice and nice
I don't think there's a bad seat in the house
That was really nice
That was almost like a shark jump for me
When I'm just looking at Harrison Ford
Doing that again
And then I just chilled out
I went to Ben on time
Sunday morning got up
Had a nice long eye chat with the girls
Who were back home
God, I love
I love eye chat
When it comes to video conferencing
Just for reliability, full screen, nice audio
All the little bits and kinks
Worked out, you know, being able to use
Your webcam, not having to use
External microphones or headphones
And just a nice combination
Macintosh really does it well
Patricia's got the eye Mac and home
I've got, well I have an eye Mac
He was using the power book
With the external eyesight
So I could take it wherever I was doing stuff
And continue to talk with it
It just really works
Despite the time difference
Between the two locations of the condo
And the cottage
It really, it almost, you know
Patricia was making foods
I just wanted to reach out through the screen
And grab it, that's how real it felt
And then I had a nice walk
Walk down to
First I went to comp USA
Just to always wanted to go to comp USA
And hang out for a little bit right
Excuse me
Nothing there though
Actually I was looking for a video camera
Because I wanted to do another victim
Like Charlie, another video music cast
Which you probably already saw
By now if you checked out the feed this morning
If you are subscribed or you looked at curry.com
And I picked up this
Let me just grab it here
So picked up this camera
Which I've already seen in
In a different apple store
It's the Sanio
Exacty
As an xxray alpha Charlie Tango India
The C5, the exacty
This thing is small
It's probably about the same size
My blackberry I wouldn't feel bad slipping this into my pocket
It's very thin
And it's a steel camera
And a video camera in one
With kind of a pistol grip
And it reminds me
It almost reminds me of one of those
There's like slow scam black and white kid
Video recorders you can get it toys
Or us
If you have your Cnose
30 bucks or something except this one actually has some quality
The nice thing about it
The real beauty
Is that it doesn't have a tape
It records all everything to an SD memory card
You got a two gigabyte card in there
Which should be good for about
Things are good for about an hour and 15 minutes of continuous video
And I really really like this thing
I played a lot more than yesterday
Of course hence the
The new video cast that I put up
But I'm going to be using this
Throughout throughout the next couple days or weeks
And of course I'm vacation
Let's see if I can
If let's just see if it works
I mean that that's always been the problem with
With regular video for me is
Okay, so you got to go hook it up to the computer
And then you've got to go find the spot
You've got to read in the tape
It's never really made it easy for me
This thing is cool
If I can do it, let me go
Why don't I do a little
Let's see
Should I do a little a
A little quick movie here
There we go
That's the sink
We'll do a little movie here of the setup
At the condo
So you can see
There we go
Okay, I'll post that along in the show notes
Nine seconds of video
Oh please enjoy
Let's see
This week I promised the unleash
Of the pod show pdn
Podcast delivery network
And the pod show plus
Listener extravaganza
So on Friday we had a full-blown meeting
We all sat down
Talked about the actual date
That we're going to unleash all this stuff
As you know we've had some delays
Based upon the implementation of strong mail
So that we can actually send out emails
And of course we'll be talking about that
Again in this podcast a little bit later on
So it looks like it's going to be delayed
By the 10 days delay that we had
Had to put into the schedule
Before the
For the email fix
And of course I'm going on vacation
From the first until the 10th of April
And I don't I do not want to be away
When it unleashes come on
That would totally suck
So it'll be right after that
That's so funny
But of course
I'll be jamming with you about it
Up until then because we're so close to
To getting all this stuff right or at least
Write enough to
To unleash
Hey what's up? What's up? It's Markus couch
From the scene scene and pod show
Music rewind
And I'm here to talk about rewind today
And we've just launched
Episode number 25
So you can go to rewind.podshow.com
And check that out
We've got the usual suspects on board
From the pod show music gang
Namely CC Chapman, Michael Butler
Myself
We've also got some guest podcaster clips
We've got jersey Todd from the jersey Todd show
Tokyo Dan from what's happening in Tokyo
We've got podcast fix hosted by Dan Cody
Who is in the reverse engineers
Great pod safe band
We've got Jasper from the plan nine rock show
Rubberhead
From rubber room radio
So make sure you check out rewind.podshow.com
And for all you music podcasters out there
You guys are invited to join the party
Yes even you can get in on the
Serious satellite window
If you'd like to find out more
Just go to rewind.podshow.com
Click the submission tab
And you'll be given more info
On how you can participate
Now before I go I want to mention one other thing
Because of the fact that we've opened up rewind
To all these great guest podcasters
We've really developed a community
A network, a backbone
A pod safe music artist
And pod safe music podcast
So to flourish this new community
This new network of pod safe
I've started pod safe music forum.com
It's really a place that we can all discuss pod safe music
We can discuss technical issues
Legal issues anything you want
So if you want to participate
Anyone is invited just go to pod safe music forum.com
This is Marcus Couch
Take care
Right on buddy
Glad you feel better two markets a little bit under the weather
He was really he was pretty sick
So he's back and got it was so nice
Yesterday just rolling out a couple of those pod safe music shows
What is it?
I snowed their ultimate mix pod cast
Came in I've been listening to bass 20
I've been listening to the chill cast with Angie B
And of course the pod show music rewind
It really works
This stuff works and then just as a
Kind of like on a on a lark
I have my old iPod here with all my other all my all my license music
Which you know, I don't have any license music
I don't think anymore on any computer anywhere
It's all still on that iPod
It's like my archive device
And I ran through a couple of songs and you know
It's just like
First of all most of the songs that that I have in my iPod
Or 20 years old by now
They're from you know mid 80s
90s yeah like 10 to 20 years old
It's just you know I couldn't get that excited anymore
I just really couldn't
I'm so I'm really turned on by all the new stuff
And that's never happened to me
It's never happened to me
Hey, what is today spring?
Is it the first official day of spring today?
I
What is it today is the 20th?
No, I can't beat the spring start March 20th
Yeah, it's really confusing
It's not just spring that I'm sometimes confused about
But mother's day
Mother's day
And father's day as well
It doesn't seem like we've made any
Any progress in some kind of international standardization of when mother's day is
Mother's day in the US
I don't know when it is but I know that it's different in the UK
And I know it's different in Belgium
And I think it's even different in the Netherlands
It sounds like every country is just arbitrarily picked their own mother's day
And it seems the same with father's day
If anyone couldn't enlighten me on that
I'd be much appreciated because
I've got a lot of different moms in my life
They've got to send something to and I'm confused
Hey Adam, it's Matt Snodgrass
Since there's been a flurry of news on the Chuck lately
Where they have a lot of commentary
I'll try to get through these rapid fire
First, regarding the proposed end-to-digital rights management in France
Which I wholeheartedly support in theory
However, in reality this just means that iTunes and other online music stores
Will simply close down their French stores
Yes, they will take the stance
I'll just take my ball and go home
Second, but you're an internet
I think I've broken this absurdity down to a simple formula
In no other business scenario, just the supplier of goods
Charge the producer of goods
More because the producer is shipping a lot of goods
In this case, the goods being data
And after much thought, I realized the term for what these ISPs are proposing
You know, don't drug dealers do that
The words, using force to obtain money from someone else
And that term is, you guessed it, extortion
All right, third, I can't tell you how excited I am
To start buying my pot-safe music on the PMmen
With a couple of suggestions
First, pot show has to take at least some piece of each transaction
To cover operating expenses of providing such a service
Well, you know what?
Let me just see who's about to say something else at home
Otherwise, if things just blow up to millions of downloads a year
Then you're paying all that for all the extra bandwidth
You know, Matt, Matt's not dressed Jackson from time to time
It's always good to hear from Matt
Interesting, you bring that up because this is something that we've been talking about
Quite a bit at Pod Show HQ
And we feel that there, that may not be necessary
You know, we've had a lot of conversations about what everyone calls
The split, what's the split man who's getting word?
What's the split?
And at the end of the day, you know, when you look at all the parties that come together
And selling music, it's
There isn't that much to divvy up, you know, if you want to give the artist a fair shake
And I think the only other person we should be helping in any transaction
Besides the, you know, the standard nine cents for just the processing fee
Which, you know, I can't do anything about
Is the person who helps sell the song
So that would be in traditional internet, internet speak that would be in affiliate
It's not about the bandwidth, you know, we're going to be giving away the podcast
It's not about the delivery network, anyone who wants to use it
So, you know, that's going to be a lot more bandwidth than being used on, in fact
It's almost ridiculous how low the bandwidth usage is on the, or how
We've gotten used to such huge numbers, let me put it that way
And bandwidth usage that what PMN uses is almost nothing
So, you know, I think that we will benefit as Pod Show in other ways
Which may be a little more indirect
But I think it's just going to be worth it
You know, now that Pod Safe Music has almost become a, you know, a word like Kleenex
Can, yeah, it's actually we've gotten it to a verb yet, I Pod Safe
I don't know, so we're not quite a zerox territory, but definitely a Kleenex territory
So, I don't know, but I do know that the minute the email registration works
We're going live with all of the music which means any artist who has the music on the
Pod Safe Music network can start selling
You'd like a victim of your own success
Second, please encourage the artists to include entire albums when it launches
A kickass album like Black Lab see the sun
Would never see the light of day if only two tracks are available on the PMN
And believe me, it is a kickass album
All right
I'll try to wrap this up now with just a quick comment on the trial decision
What the fuck
What kind of dick-lic judge can't clearly see a fucking case of theft laid out before her
Hey, how about this? I go steal her car with no repercussions and just promise not to do it again
I bet that'd fly
Okay, I got that out of my system
All right, lastly, I just want to let you know that you've inspired me to finally create my own podcast
It's called the Daven match show
So y'all check this out
It's a comedy podcast available at DavenMatchow.com
Ribbit
I've got a lot of ribbit feedbacks
Hey, if you're listening to us on serious stars channel 102
This is the pod show Pacific Coast Hellway is next followed by
Yeah, use radio dawn and drew and lots of great stuff up until 10 o'clock eastern time tonight
And I guess I'll just have to figure out themselves
They can download this entire podcast and listen to it. It's entirely
But I couldn't fit the daily source code dot com into the satellite window a couple of promos for you
They're good ones today too
Looking for a hookah
This is the place
The rock and roll geek is cruising for love
Not for himself, but for those who need it most
It's Michael Butler's hookah enough a podcast with one guy one girl or two of each and the rock and roll match maker
Michael Butler trying to make it all happen
Would there be a hookah
For a breakah
Whatever happens you'll hear it all
On Michael Butler's hookah
Subscribe at podshow.com or visit the website and hook it up podgast.com
Hey Adam this is chef Mark from the remarkable palette podcast in NYC
I told you that I was working on a big announcement and I got a couple of my friends together to join me
Yo, this is Steve Wasser, and this is chef dance census of the gastrologic of podcast
This is chef time
Come on to you from the chic podcast head quarters in Chicago. This is Jim John Drow from Jim's kitchen
This is Jennifer from the guilty park and even though we all have our own food podcasts
There ain't no mother
Chef you'd go and down there be
Yes, we can all get along
That's right guys. So we're here to announce the launch of the culinary podcast network
You know, we all share a love of gastronomy some of us are professional chefs and others of sesco bonds
You may already listen to some of our shows so we thought we'd collect together the finest quality food podcast available on the web
So you can get them all here in one place hot out of the oven
Along with the folks you've heard here
We also have Don Janoba from all you can eat in Vancouver the guys from hungry magazine in Chicago
And San Francisco's own chef mark from chef marks culinary adventures
So you may get to see that chef mark truffle wrestling match after all Adam
You can find us at culinary podcast network.com
You can even throw in those w's if you want or subscribe to the aggregate for all of our shows in the iTunes
Directory just look for the culinary podcast network. Thanks Adam talk to you later
This is so incredibly cool chefs with an attitude. I like it
Very cool. I subscribed immediately. I love the aggregate feed which kind of makes it a channel for me
So I always have the latest one showing up. This is great. Congratulations great idea
Sounds like you got a great group
A symbol there and anything we can do at pod show to help you. I'll just let me know
Totally totally totally into that concept and it's so hard, you know, it's a to organize people into doing anything really
So congratulations guys very cool
Whoa
You found the mark bar show
Oh yeah, babe. Hey everybody my pot show is a weird combination
We talk about interesting stuff space travel time travel gadgets interesting stuff for network
Happens and life in the Netherlands and there's just a couple of things we talked about in the last few shows
Plus we do have the best of the pot safe music network
And the best of it all it's not just a fantasy
It is a reality check it out
www.markboss.com
Eight out of ten listeners agree the mark bar show
Early rocks
That's for the others
Well, I'm one of them over
Yeah, I think that's enough. Okay.
www.m-a-r-k-b-a-a-r-s.com
Right on Mike Alpharomio Kila Bravo Alpharomio Shara.com, right?
Yeah, you know, I got a I got to say that I've been reading a whole bunch of reports from the Netherlands
Of course where I grew up and lived there for a couple of years before we moved to the UK
and
There was a one particular podcast directory. I think was it podcast
I don't even know which one it was but you know they kind of shut down and said podcasting is dead and
Holland and no one's doing it and then all of a sudden people started sending me promos
And I hadn't really received a lot of Dutch podcast promos in the past so it was nice to
Nice to see him come in and nice that they're in English so we can share them and
It's I think it's I think podcasting is very much alive. They just have to kind of find there
I guess I have to find that groove, you know because it is cultural that that's really what I'm noticing
The Dutch audience who wants a different type of podcast on the podcasters were making up until now
A lot of politicians doing podcast in the Netherlands. Of course, you know the politicians always say
I had just started a podcast and I do like one episode and then I just stays there you subscribe to the feed and nothing else
Come through I think the minister of
Defense to the podcast the minister of the interior to the podcast. They all jumped on some some form of virtual
Bandwagon that they saw rolling around a rolling along but
It's all talk no, I'll talkers no doers. Hey, there's more from Holland check this out. This is
Actually, it's really shitty audio quality which I'm sure was a mistake, but the bit in the middle is so worth listening to
From the Nau Weekly.com podcast which is a brand new podcast where we talk about
Well stuff that happens in Holland and I want to mention that a few Charlie's ago you
Or a few penises ago
You mentioned something about not using the word Jesus
But using your name. So we we put this to the test and well
I just wanted to hear you what happened this week at the at our place. Hold up hold up
Oh
Gary
Man, oh
Well as we now know
Yeah, this sounds good actually. I'm gonna we're gonna use this
So check out a podcast is on www dot the Nau Weekly.com and
Oh, it's there every week for you to hear buy at him. I don't know what's what's going on
But it sounds like you got a grounding issue somewhere in the in the mixing in the routing channel or something
But otherwise, very funny. I believe me. I would love it. I think it's it's a great marketing boy
Please do not take the Lord's name in vain or or his or his son Jesus Christ
Please don't just use my name when you hit your thumb really it's better for everybody. I'm I'm sure of it
I was just listening when I was listening to that. I was thinking about garage band the new i-life oh six
I picked up a copy of i-life oh six
Since I was at the Apple store anyway and
It was pretty interesting
The interface is a little bit little bit cleaner a little bit different
But but really the garage band seems to be much more stable. I had an editing project
Something I've been working on called the green tech podcast. That's the working title
That's going to be the final title and
And I just decided I'd start editing that in garage band to see how I did and
It you know once you kind of get the hang of it because it is a little different than
You know using pro tools or audacity or deck or anything like that
But when you kind of get the hang of it it does start to flow a little bit. I'm about
30% through the project so I'm gonna do the whole project on garage band
Hopefully it won't let me down and then I'll give you my full assessment, but so far I have to say
And I would I've never edited anything on a windows machine. I really only use the windows machine because cast plaster runs on it
And lots of talk this weekend
on the
Particularly on a curry dot com in the comments going back and forth with comic strip blogger
um
I really you know I have a whole bunch of mixed feelings about comic strip blogger. You know we're kind of getting into it
He was sending in comments regularly which I was happy to play and
And if you were listening last Friday
He kind of went off on a tangent that I took
I took issue with
And you know that he's he really tried to defend himself on the boards. I don't think he got away with it
And I don't know if this is just a language issue, but it really doesn't matter what the issue is
It's the way that comics re-blogger do it's the way you respond
And if I swear to me because you know he'll send me emails
Which just anyone who has ever had an altercation with daywiner will recognize this type of email
It's really amazing
Where an email shows up that says do not for do not post do not blog
This is for you and you only privately you may not do anything with this atom curry
And I've received those emails from Dave winers and sure many people have and
And
And it's just like it's actually it's the same type of thing if you have an ongoing relationship
If you've ever had one with whiner
You know you wake up one morning all sudden. He's like totally off as rocker and you have to apologize to me
You ridiculed me and yeah, it's like oh my god, and so I received a couple of these
A comic should blogger emails and he is saying that I have to apologize to him
For calling him out on his uh what I felt was an anti-symmetic comment
And I didn't do anything more than to call him out on it whether it was intentional unintentional
It didn't sound right man. It really didn't
But you shouldn't get all been out of shape and end to then go threatening this stuff like you know I'll go back. What is it?
You have to apologize to me
uh
Wow god, I'm gonna read this whole thing Adam. See I repeat. I expect your apology on next podcast
I mentioned Ron's ethnicity without any evil intentions just an adjective as many people do no
Dude you listen to the Howard Stern show too much. Okay. That's the problem
You trying to do like Howard Stern type humor and I can hear it. I really can't and I know you listen to it
Whether it's legally illegally streaming or not however you get a hold of it. I can tell you even use that as part of your defense
But it's everything's within context man and it was not within context and and I feel that we should be able to call you out
And you shouldn't be so
Dicky about it, you know, just uh move on next window please. Now I think you did kind of apologize
But I'm I'm definitely not going to and you know there's there's no reason to get all
Huffy about it. Just go back to stuff that you care about man. Don't get just
Anyway, so we send you a whole bunch of audio quotes, which I'm not gonna play because they're just not relevant not funny and
And not the CSB. I want to have on my show
Hey, I'm Mike Sulee from Ottawa, Canada here love the show
I work in the voiceover IP space and I've been listening intently lately to this bullshit about
Telco's wanted to charge both end points for bandwidth use
And bitching because power users is actually dared to make the most of their internet connections
All I want is a pipe and I know this pisses off a lot of ISPs because you don't fit the profile for the quote average user
That some marketing droid you can barely figure out how to open his email came up with
I must say that I'm really tired of this shit
I tried to make your eyes piece in Canada and if I don't use the operating system that they want me to use
At the times of day that they want using only the programs that they want me to use
They want nothing to do with me
Right now my eyes p rocks because it's smaller and it isn't too full of itself yet
They're customer service actually has a clue it's amazing
Now the telco's want to treat me as a second class citizen and charge both end points for traffic
The each end point is already paying for from their ISP
That's the last straw man. Fuck them
We need a serious push to turn these assholes into the utility that they're supposed to be
They need to provide an unbiased pipe and then shut the fuck up and collect the revenue
If the pipe goes down or performs poorly, they need to be penalized
I mean it's the way of the future if I get my way
I think that everyone needs to start lobbying with their governments to make it happen
It should be like the damn telephone
The internet is an essential service now and we need a reliable unbiased playing field to keep it that way
Anyway, that's my rent for the day man
All right, dude. Yeah, I feel the same way and this is this is you know really the email conversation is now coming to the main stream
Remember we were talking about this probably before you ever read about it in the New York Times as an example
But this whole idea of good mail which is this
You know this service that a well and apparently now everyone has signed up for it a well
MSN hotmail Yahoo and there's even a Gmail person on the board of on the advisory board
So I understand you know, so they're all in on this and and all the conversation revolves around what I think is exactly the intent of the ISPs
It all revolves around
Spam so we're stopping spam and the way we're gonna do that is we're gonna charge people to send certified mail
And all of that's fine, but the thing that no one seems to be talking about is that
It's almost like getting like all of a sudden having getting really bad credit
You know, which can happen for a number of reasons it can happen all by itself without you having anything to do with it
It usually these mistakes happen or there's some kind of fraud
Which by the way is how you often wind up on spam blacklist is through fraud or someone use your mail server
Of course, I know there's all kinds of things that should be done, you know, there's mistakes everywhere
But that's usually how you wind up on a blacklist and before you know it you can't send out your own personal email
This is an issue the corporations have all over the world right now as we speak
Just sending a small small companies, you know, mom and pop shops are running into this problem
So now they're all going to have to pay these huge fees which you know, maybe 300 bucks doesn't seem like a large fee
But it is you know and and who died and made you more the fuckers God excuse me excuse me
You know, you're just weaseling it's it really is weaseling in onto something that is supposed to be open and free and yet it sucks
Yeah email is absolutely broken, but this is not the way to fix it. I'm sorry
This is completely wrong and you know what there's not a day goes by that I'm not rocking my brain for some other type of solution
But this is
About the free flow of information without gatekeepers without having to to pay for
Your email to get through that was not the way the system was designed it was not the way it was intended
And I'm really I feel bad that this is just moving ahead, you know, because
Look there's no time the same thing with us. We're paying these you know it's like
$80,000
I'll rage this amount just so that we can send send off emails and how the you know actually arrive. It's
I don't think legislation is the way to go by the way. I think the whole problem here
What we're seeing down at the bottom and this goes you know goes right into the same
The same issue of ISPs wanting the charge on both sides of the equation
You know, so they want to charge Google for sending net, you know, for the traffic that they send onto their network and now
They're saying yeah, it's people kind of backpedaling into it by saying oh, this will be for a guaranteed delivery or some horse crap like that
The problem is it's jealousy
It's jealousy at the top, you know, it guys and I think it all it really has to do with Google people are looking at Google and saying hey wait a minute
There's a business model where guys are taking all this stuff that other people create running it over our pipes
And they're and they're you know, there's there's big is GM in market cap and then in value
It's jealousy. They want a piece of that they see that their models will never grow that quickly and that they are becoming commoditized
So the only thing I can say is if you guys are really this big and this powerful you network guys
Then you should go buy the content companies go buy a piece of Google, you know what I'm saying?
Okay, aggravated excuse me, you know, pull your fucking wallet out and do that, you know, if you look it's like it's like
People who invest in airlines, you know, not a good time to be invested in an airline with with fuel prices, you know
You're gonna lose your shirt. I'm sorry. Just get over it already, but don't try and hijack into streams of other companies
You know, it's a piracy it's absolutely piracy
I know I have faith in the in it's certainly in the United States and it's people and it's consumers people who are consumers
And even legislation if it has to get to it, but I don't think that will ever surface that would just kill so much
I think we would have to take to the streets and riot if they if they really want to go through with that
I think I'm not the piece about that here. Hold on a second. Let's see. Hey Adam this is Eric Bergen from green room radio
And I just listened to the Charlie 355 and
Listening to that final song Kevin Reeves wasted just incredible. What a great song. Oh, this is really
Just what a great song
Yeah, but it it reminded me to send in some audio feedback
Regarding an issue that I've been thinking about for some time and it's regarding the pod safe music network now
I love the PMN I use it all the time and I totally get your idea of the unlabel and how it works and that
You and the other other people that facilitate the PMN are not in control of its content and then should not be in control of its content
And I get that and I love that the idea that it's not a store, but it is a resource and a
A hub of all those great music for podcasters and and anyone else who discovers the music through podcasts
However, here is my question
For so long now musicians and artists have been trying to get their music heard in the the best way possible since the beginning of the recorded sound
Artists have been always you know always working towards a better quality sound
In recorded music all the way from vinyl now to not just CD anymore, but super audio CD
And now we have the dual disc which you can you know flip over and play the album in on the DVD side in 5.1 stereo surround sound and
All these other inventions to make the sound more better
Wow, that was bad. But anyway, you know getting the sound the way the musician would want it to sound the way it sounds in the studio when you're creating the music
Oh wow, I don't know where you're going with this, but
You know
Back in the day when there was really like in the in the UK or in Europe when the real top 40 stations with the pirate radio ships broadcasting on AM only
Medium wave man people mix their shit down the studio on the crappy as speakers to make sure it sounded good not
You know, it's so the it sounded good on the device they expected their consumers to be listening to
So, you know, there's no way you're going to replicate well if you have enough money in the right room and and enough drive
Yeah, you can get pretty close, but you'll probably never replicate
What people are hearing in the studio. I think it's very different. You know hip hop is it's very tuned towards the clubs and and car stereo
So I'm not too sure about that, but let's see where you're going with with the whole story and I know that when I buy music from the
iTunes music store sometimes although I know I'm getting a compressed sound and not so perfect
I know that the quality for the most part is going to be really really good
I really enjoy the AAC files that they sent out. I don't know how you feel about that in in relation to the standard MP3 file, but I well first of all are
Our pod show plus player which would be able to use from any web browser will of course recognize them and play them also the enhanced version which is is really sweet
So I don't care, you know, it's
It's kind of an open format
You know, and now of course I get a ton of emails people saying it's open. It's closed. It's open. It's closed
I don't know where I will deploy it so it works for me, but I definitely support MP3 above all else do enjoy it
Some of the files that I've downloaded from the PMN are occasionally
Not up to quality and I don't even say a little bit more than occasionally. I would say 50% of the time the quality of the track
Isn't up to par now. It's it's fine for playing on a podcast because
When you know when you're doing a podcast you're
compressing it to sometimes even mono sound
But for those people who who want a high quality sound especially the people who are buying the tracks
Is there any way that we can have a restriction as far as the quality of the file that artists are uploading or
What do we do about that just because I feel that sometimes the the sound isn't up to where
Other people like listening to and and the musicians would want it. I think higher themselves
So that's just a bit of feedback for you
I would love to hear what you have to say about that this is Eric Bergen from green room radio the arts and entertainment podcast had green room radio dot com
All right, Eric, thank you. Yeah, let me let me give you that my thoughts about that so going back to the unlabel concept where every
person who is a member of the label which includes listeners
podcasters artists other people who want to promote music fans for instance
Just you know if you take all of that all those pieces transactional piece all of that
We're all together you get the unlabel and
The minute you start making a whole bunch of restrictions I think it'll become very difficult the way I see this playing
Is that we're going to we're going to really mel the pod safe music network into
Well, it already is kind of a mini social network. We're going to we're really going to
Mel that into a social media network. So right now you have song pages you can see who played a song
You can get information about the artist
But I think what what we're really missing there is some user interaction or listener or podcaster
Who can basically say you know, it's so you'll be able to place comments or or
The call them recommendations if you will but you'll be able to respond to each individual song into the artist and
And I guess what you might do just as if you were going to download a piece of software and by the way
Is there any difference between a dot ex e file and a dot mp3 file? I mean, yeah, what happens with it once you get it
Maybe different but it's still just data you're downloading you've got
Programs that that crash and break and spy have spyware and are you know, crap and you have ones that are really good and how do you know about it?
Well when you're downloading I at least I always look at quickly at the reviews, you know, and not the star rating by the way
I actually read what people say if I go to version tracker for instance or window tracker dot com if I really need something for the windows machine
You know, so it's
I think that that's the best way to handle that and if artists are really serious and
You know if they think that they can go without a record company. This is the stuff that record companies do
You know, they make sure the quality's out there and it's the and the notes the right bit rate and it's uploaded properly and
You know if you're going to do that yourself then as an artist you need to take the time. You know, it's it's 99 cents someone's paying
Which may not seem like a lot but look at the competition the competition is what you hear on iTunes
So I'm pretty sure that the artists will catch on quick enough if they're really serious. Remember this is all about
A concept of they're no they're not really being a need for labels and by the way, there's plenty of
Independent record labels who are uploading their stuff and that's fine, too
We're actually going to make that a little more apparent so you can
Go in by artists as well as by by record company
If you want to search around so we're really doing our our best to make that as as broad as possible
But again, I think that you know if we want to be a store
Then we'd have you know if you do one thing you've got to do everything the what we have discussed
And I'll just mention it again is we will be working on the ID three tags when you submit your song
You'll actually have to post X
Number you know pieces of information you can of course fill out everything you want but
The ID three tags will be
We'll be written in properly. I guess some kind of rule if the ID three tags are already there
Then we won't write them in or something like that but we're moving along and I appreciate the feedback because
The only way we're going to get this unlabeled really roll and is is by working together on it
So from the pod safe music network as the last song of the day
About five people sent me this link. I don't know why maybe it's some kind of
marketing
initiative that is
That has been undertaken. Let me just see if I can find some information about this particular
I'm going to my
My playlist here on the pod safe music network David it polito who was from
New York
Also known as that guitar man from Central Park since 1992 has played to hundreds of thousands around the world
But as most at home on sunny weekends in a little patch of grass in New York City Central Park with a guitar on his shoulder
But boy he gets around and he certainly takes the train
We call you Mr. Cell phone guy because we don't know your name
The only thing we share is that we all got on this train
We don't know each other we won't be together long
So it might surprise you when we break out in this song
Talk louder
You're the cell phone guy and here's what we think of you
Though you're rude and self-important still we love you
So please talk loud talk louder
Now that's the seventh call you're dialing or receiving
We all need to know the crap you did last evening
So please talk loud
You've allowed us on your train so we'll try not to make a peep
We know you get a call each time we hear that piercing beep
Never mind the woman next to you who's trying to get some sleep talk louder
Another phone call to your wife is why we're waiting
We all think your private life is fascinating
So please talk loud talk louder say can you hear me now each time the signal scatters
Because you know that you're the only one that matters
Hey, please talk loud
Make calls about that business lunch and everyone who came and all the TV shows you like and those you think are lame and your friend
Larry needs the play by play of last night's Yankee game
Talk louder and laugh out loud as if you're living in a funnel and say I'm losing you each time we hit a tunnel
Please talk loud
I opened up my eyes today at dawn's first early light
But as I sipped my coffee I knew something wasn't right
Because I won't feel complete till I know what you did last night
No, wait
That's not true
No, wait, that's just not true
I
Shut up don't you know this song was meant to be ironic
We think you're boring dog of noxious and moronic
You talk so loud hey shut up
If you're getting dirty looks you should expect a
One more call in that damn phone is up your rectum
Because you
It's got a whole bunch of songs on the podcast and music network check them out David Epoito and I'll make sure to put a link in the show notes
You can be whisked off to it automatically. Hey, good news today is a reasonable hair day
And I'm really happy so I won't have to spend hours coffee
coffee because today Cali Lewis our fearless leader from the geek intelligence agency agency is in town
She'll be at the pod show HQ and we're doing something together on taking my camera with me
So I don't know if I'll be putting that up as a as a Victor Mike Charlie or just as something separate
But I'll definitely be shooting some footage and I'm looking forward to a to meeting our fearless leader
So you all have a great day
We back tomorrow as I said. I'm here all week. I'm here. I'll be here all week folks. It's a condo
Flying back Saturday for a rival Sunday morning and
Missing the girls, but glad to be out here and kicking some ass getting some shit done a lot of fun
So Adam and Curry dot com for all your feedback daily source code dot com for the latest pod shows
Pod casts and for the show notes and of course curry dot com for the ongoing conversation
We will undoubtedly have with our friend comic strip blogger
Get this pod cast and we're great ones like it on the high performance pod cast of liberty network from pod show and line-white networks