Delta's Yeracharly 338, it's good to be back home.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just a kid, I don't care.
Somebody told me you're a San Francisco.
Somebody told me that you're not on top of the world.
You probably walkin' down the street with your earbuds.
Champs so deep in your ear, yeah, you go and death.
You probably found this little MP3 for free.
We're looking play this, but not on the radio made this.
Just so I could let it go, there's anyone around here.
Still have a radio and anyone here at all.
Anyone here at all.
You should go and see a mountain cool bird seen.
It's way cooler out there, yeah, I think so.
But maybe you just like it in your cozy little world.
You can play this, but not on the radio made this.
Just so I could let it go, there's anyone around here.
Still have a radio and anyone here at all.
Anyone here at all.
Maybe I'm just better won't you save me.
I'm from my hell.
Maybe I just like it if you turn it off now.
Turn it off now.
Forget about a sound wheeling West Virginia.
We can make it on our own.
And we're doing just fine.
I can't afford your record, but it's out of sight.
We can play this, but not on the radio made this.
But not on the radio, hey now.
Switch off your radio, off your radio.
We can play this, but not on the radio made.
Just so I could let it go, there's anyone around here.
Still have a radio and anyone here at all.
Anyone here at all.
That's the Jeff Smith.
Not on the radio.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
It's Friday.
They come into you from Curry Cottage in Guilford.
The affluent suburb of Surrey in the United Kingdom, just southwest of London.
Got in this morning from New York.
Great trip, as always, as expected with Virgin upper class.
I did something new this time.
They have a special sleeper section, which is basically the forward portion of the upper deck on a 747.
It's really nice, because the flight is only 6 hours.
It's like no nonsense and you even get where you check in and actually when you book the reservation.
But especially when you check in, they say, do you understand what the sleeper cabin means?
And basically no nonsense.
You've got to shut up, you've got to just be quiet and go to sleep and you've got a night cabin.
That's it and then the wake up for breakfast if you want.
And then actually put a little stamp on your ticket that says,
What is it? Oh, I don't have the ticket anymore.
Something like sleeper cabin has been explained to this passenger.
I guess they need that so that they can tell you to shut up.
So that was really nice actually.
And it was, it was, um, what was your name, Liz?
I think I think it was, yeah, Liz.
Nice cottage last.
And she woke me so nicely, so gently.
It's really weird because I really was asleep.
And I was asleep on my back.
Usually I'm a, I'm a side sleeper.
And I'm asleep on my back.
And then I just feel something on my leg.
And it was, I don't know.
I think I enjoyed it a little too much.
Hey, Jeff Smith, who you heard with not on the radio.
He's the guy behind.
Oh, such a illustrious thing, such as, uh...
Or...
Sorry.
Got no Roger Smalls for you.
Just wanted to play the jingle again.
Um, you can find Jeff Smith at TheJefSmith.com.
Hey, you know, um, last night before I went to bed, uh, or actually while I was in bed,
and I was, uh, trying to unwind and I knew I had, uh,
the whole Thursday to do a couple things, which I'll talk about in a minute.
I flipped on.
I actually flipped through a couple of, uh, a couple of the late night talk shows.
I just missed, um, John Stewart show, which bummed me out.
I usually watch that every night, religiously in San Francisco.
Um, so actually I tuned into Letterman.
And of course he had some, you know, pretty funny, uh, Cheney jokes.
Um, but I noticed something.
Look at the microphone on his desk, which I presume, of course,
is, uh, it may be hooked up, but I don't think they actually, you know,
the way it's pointed doesn't seem like it would be a functional way for that
particular microphone to work, but look at it.
Doesn't it look just like the Hile PR 40?
Without the logo, but I mean, the structure, the, the way the,
the casing is built, it looks exactly like it.
So the question is, hey, is it a PR 40 with the, uh, label removed?
Um, is it a knockoff of the PR 40, just a prop?
Or was the PR 40 modeled on that microphone, perhaps?
I just thought it was interesting, then, just point that one out.
Now about Dick Cheney.
I know someone who knows Dick Cheney very well.
Uh, in fact, I know someone who knows Donald Rums, Rumsfeld very well.
Uh, Colin Powell very well.
Uh, George H. Bush very very well.
And this person is actually in my family.
Uh, I know him is Uncle Don.
I've always known him is Uncle Don.
Um, you can Google him if you want.
His name is Donald P. Greg Golf Romeo Echo Golf Golf.
Um, and he, so he's my uncle.
He's married to my, uh, my father's sister.
And I got a beautiful email from him, uh, on Wednesday as well.
Wednesday evening.
And he said, you know, um, and I really, I should have realized this.
Um, that, you know, communicate.
Of course, there's been lots of communication by email and phone.
Um, and he said, well, you know what?
I can move some stuff around tomorrow.
Uh, I was actually planning on seeing a carry-wise burger.
Ice burger?
Carry-wise burger?
Ice?
And there you go, my uncle worked at the CIA for 31 years.
I believe he might have actually run it for a period of time.
Then he got heavily involved in Asian affairs.
He was in Vietnam for four years.
He was also the ambassador to South Korea for a couple of years.
And when George H 41, as we say, was vice president, Don was,
I know he's a personal advisor.
He was on the VPs personal staff.
I don't know if it was security advisor or, well,
we're going to find out because I am going to interview him
in the not too distant future.
Because he's just fascinating guy.
70, yet years old.
And currently, for a while, he's been the CEO of something called
the Korea Society.
And the Korea Society is a nonprofit.
And its entire purpose is to help Koreans
and Americans, North Koreans, as well, understand each other better.
He's also been in North Korea several times.
And he's met with the regime.
And he has been, I believe he's been instrumental in some
of the negotiations and the table of six,
or what are the meeting of six, whatever it's called.
So really, kind of stupid of me, not to have thought of
hooking up with him much, much earlier.
So I said, you know what, I'll drop by the office.
We had a great Korean lunch.
It was really weird because I walked in and everyone's like
Ambassador Greg and Ambassador Greg.
And I'm 41 still calling him Uncle Don.
Could help it.
And so, you know, we had some family conversation,
which was really nice, just have a nice lunch
and sit in this beautiful library surrounded by pictures of
presidents and him and all just fantastic artwork,
Korean, just literature, all kinds of stuff,
all over the place, really fascinating.
And we really started talking about politics, of course.
I mean, this is a guy when I used to stay at my cousin's house,
which, of course, you know, kids of the ambassador.
He had a red phone and it was literally like,
you pick that one up and you get the situation room.
I do remember picking it up once and hearing some,
and didn't, you know, I was just like,
I'll just pick it up and listen to the dial tone and immediately
it was like, you know, White House operator.
What's wrong with the Greg?
So I, you know, I said, you know, we just went on,
you know, he had so many, he has a lot of frustration
because he knows Korea so well.
And obviously North Korea being on the so-called
Axis of evil.
So he's a guy who's a Republican who is not at all happy,
not at all happy with 43.
George W. Bush, he's very, very vocal about it.
In fact, his Christmas card was, was a beautiful Christmas card
with a picture of Don, his wife, Meg, the Korean ambassador
and his wife, and 43, George 41, George H.
No, Barbara wasn't there.
And he had actually written on the picture, you know,
Merry Christmas, this is the good Bush.
And I believe some people were very upset and, you know, wrote
some other message on the card and sent it back to him.
But, you know, this so this guy's very, very politically minded
and very outspoken.
And I said, you know, but you know, you know, a whole bunch of these
guys in the regime and of course, the topic was Cheney and he said
something very interesting. He said, I do not recognize Cheney.
He says, this is not the guy that I work with.
He's 180 degrees, the opposite of the Cheney he knew.
And I thought that was pretty interesting.
But he has all kinds of just fascinating insight into what's going on in the
world and then he had a guest speaker in and he's caught me. He's slick.
You know, he's sitting with me for like an hour and a half and then
he goes and meets with his speaker and I introduce his name.
We're talking and then we walk right into the auditorium.
He goes right to the podium and introduces Ian Bremer, who's from
the Eurasia group, which is also very interesting.
This is another guy I want to introduce. I just want to introduce
some of these people because, you know, it's so the quality of information I
received and just an afternoon was so much better than any publication
or news program or just anything that I've been able to learn about
what's going on. And, you know, so of course we talked a little bit about
podcasting, which he had not heard of. And I said, look, you know, I had
really love to have you on the show and just ask you questions.
And he said that he would be delighted to, there's going to be stuff that's
off limits. I think I probably have to ask him first, you know, if there's
stuff I can't even ask about because, you know, throughout the years, I'm sure
as, you know, growing up in family, you know, you hear stuff that maybe
not, maybe isn't meant for, for rebroadcast, particularly in the
earlier agency years. But I'm really excited about that. So in the next,
I'd say in the next four weeks or so I'm going to try and make it happen.
I'm going to have the ambassador on the show. It'll be, I think you're really, really
enjoyed and he has great stories and he does accents when he does stories,
just a, he's a great storyteller. So that was, that really just perfected an
already perfect week, even though I was dead dead tired, just from running around
in the, in the snow in the city, it was very productive and it's good to be home.
Patricia is leaving in a couple hours. She's, as, as I think I told you, she's going to
rhododam to help her sister open up her accessories store.
And I don't know what it's, I should ask her what it's called. So anyway, she's
getting packed up and then Christina and I will be here for the weekend. Then on
Sunday, as Patricia is headed home, I'll be heading out to San
Fran for a week out on the west coast. Because, you know, there's some really
important stuff that has to be done. Like getting Trinity ready to be
pumped out. Let me see. Okay, let me see. I, I something I want to talk about,
but let's just, let's do some some audio stuff first. Okay, then we'll get to
go back out to Adam. It's got me from Geek Brief TV. Since the Charlie's
a testing ground for podcasting, I'm wondering if you'd be willing to
help me try something on the brief. Now, I know everyone's mind goes to a
slightly inappropriate place when they hear the term Double Ender. But for
people who don't know, a Double Ender is a technique where people in two
different places talk on SkyBrown Foam and each recorded conversation. The
two files are edited together, so you end up with audio quality equivalent to what
you'd get if both people were recording the same room. I want to do that with
video and I'd like the first experiment to be an interview with you. Here's how
it work. We set up a time for an eye chat and we have TV cameras rolling
on both sides. We do the interview. You send me your aunt and I'll
mash it up with mine. Mm, dirty. What do you think? Wanna give it a
try? Okay. How can I refuse and offer for a double ender with you?
Of course, I'd love to give it a try. I'm going to be in San Francisco. You know, we
could try the double ender between two rooms or something. You know, just in
case, you know, the distance is too great in the ass. If you haven't seen
Callie, you must see geekbrief.tv. Great gadgets, great presentation. It's
very consumable. It's short. It's fun. It's surprising. There's always
something else going on. And then, of course, there's, uh, there's Callie.
Podcast listeners around the world. You're invited to party with Matthew
Evil. Thursday, February 23rd in Nashville, Tennessee. Join Matthew and
friends of the French Quarter Cafe to celebrate the release of his new
album, Beer and Coffee. It's an all-ages show. He'll take it
rice. No cover charge. And if you tell him you heard about it on this podcast,
you'll walk out of there with a free prize. I know you're
Thursday, February 23rd in Nashville, Tennessee. Matthew and his band will play the hits
from the new album, like wasting my time. I'll keep wasting my time again and the top
by rated song, Drive Away. Drive Away. The show starts at 830 p.m. Visit
www.matuevil.com for driving directions and more details.
Oh, man, we had some good talks over at a serious, uh, serious satellite radio
HQ about Podsafe music on the bird. Nothing firm that I can talk about yet, but
we had some really good conversations. And they're really kicking some
ass over there. It's every single time I go back to serious, there's more
shit, more paraphernalia rolling through the hallways, but it really
actually it has a very early 1980s MTV vibe to be, to be honest with you. And
that's just, you know, besides the fact that Steve leads a sitting in
office overseeing things, it really does have that vibe to it. And it's
cool, man. It really is. And it was, what a great trip. Great to hang out with P
dub as well. And he'll eat. So, um, I was reading in the financial times, I
believe it was probably Thursday's financial times, uh, but the reports were,
you know, all over the place that, um, now there are more pictures of Abu
gripe, uh, more pictures of detainees of, uh, apparent torture.
And, uh, these have been obtained out of the Freedom of Information Act, and the
government doesn't want them to be out because that'll cause unrest amongst
Muslims and blah, blah, blah, blah, and you know, I'm like, okay, uh, I
think that there is some process. As far as I know, there's some process
taking place. And, and of course, you never get to the people who may be
ultimately responsible, but people have been held to account for the
atrocities that took place in Abu gripe. To me, you know, and this comes
right back to the cartoons, and really the atrocity of, uh, of what the
mainstream media is really doing. And to be honest, how influenced
heavily by of all things, an episode of Boston Legal, um, James Spader, just
fantastic actor, but the writing on that show is very, very clever, and
and it does intertwine between reality and the twisted reality that is
the law firm that includes Captain Kirk. I mean, let's be honest, right?
And Candace Bergen, and we did have the lockler go, man. I was digging around the
show. If you really want to make a stir, and you really want to help in
the outrage that clearly there's outrage about the invasion of Iraq,
um, there's lots of confusion about what's going on, but, you know, in the
meantime, more than 2,000 soldiers, US soldiers have died. Over 300
British soldiers, I believe, uh, Italians, certainly one Dutchman. I'm not sure
about the Japanese, but they're also part of the quote coalition.
And during the Vietnam war, the media really brought that war home. And what they
did was, they showed our young men and women dying on foreign soil. And it
caused an incredible outrage. And as I was thinking about this and that
Boston Legal episode influenced me and thinking about this whole cartoon
controversy. I'm like, you know, you want to be, you want to be a really big guy
and really publish something that's really going to get some attention and we'll
really get you in the news. Publish some pictures of dying marines,
GIs, mail, and female. Publish some of that. And, you know, and this is not, and this
is just, so I'm very clear, this is not out of disrespect for our service men and women
quite the opposite, quite the opposite. It's about time that they really got
respect for what's going on over there. And I feel that our media has not given them one
single ounce of respect. I mean, even the pictures of the coffins coming back,
drape with flags. Remember that? Those pictures had kind of been, they tried to
muffle those away as well, because it's not good from morale. Come on, media, do your
fucking job. Please excuse me, excuse my French. I hope that we can start a conversation
about this, because, you know, now that I've been back in the States for a week again,
I'm really thinking, where is it? Where are the pictures that will actually cause outrage?
That will actually start a real conversation. And this kind of comes back to the, to the White
House as well. You know, this whole chainy thing with, you know, trying to hide from the media,
trying to cover up the story. Look, this is what what's happened. These guys are just like the
Danny came movie are referred to, at least once a quarter, where they're writing the book of music
and they sit in some university basement for 10 years writing this book. And by the time they
come out, jazz has happened and has, has evolved. And, you know, they've completely only written
maybe one quarter of the entire book of music. So too, with this, with this, with this administration,
who've been in office during an entire internet revolution, yeah, Al Gore invented it and all that
shit. But broadband has come really come home. The tools are there. We're creating. We're able to
communicate very fast, very efficiently with each other. And these guys just don't know what happened.
They're still doing it the old way. They're not even trying to cover anything up. But the old way
was, you know, hey, we got to, you know, draw the wagons in a circle. Let's come up with how we're
and by the way, Uncle Don has some shit to say about this as well. Draw everything in a circle,
get everything, you know, completely positioned and do it all the right way. These guys can't
deal with the speed of communication, the speed, which, which the constituency is living at,
that's what's going on. That's why their PR nightmares continuously, because they're still trying
to do it the old way. It doesn't work anymore. It does not work.
Hey, man, that feels good to do that on a Friday. Hey, pretty soon in about two weeks, we'll be
moving to channel 102 on serious. Currently, you're probably listening to the daily source code on
serious stars 103. Glad to have you. If you really want to know what all the cool, uh, if you really
want to hear all the cool stuff, then you have to check out some of these podcasts. Go to a podcast
dialie.com, go to podshow.com or any podder.org or podcastpickle.com. You could check that out as well.
For you guys in about five seconds, uh, Mark Yoshimaru Nemkov will come on with a
Pacific Coast highway and after that the illustrious match Weinstein, and back on the podcast here.
I have a, a Gmail inbound Gmail from Hank Garner. And I thought was a good question, a fair
question. Adam, I'm a devout listener. I have a question for you. Does your daughter know about your
quote, recreation? Just wondering, Hank Garner? Hank, yes, she does. Talking about the recreation.
Remember now, I grew up in the Netherlands. I moved there when I was seven years old and
very interesting country. It has changed quite a bit since, uh, since I live there, at least the
first time around. Um, but there was, and it always has been in the Netherlands, um, culturally
completely accepted. If you want to smoke a plant, that's your business. And it's not a process
plant. It's just a plant. In fact, it's a, it's a, it's a weed. It grows just like a weed. Uh, so to are the
drinking laws very supple in the Netherlands. Um, certainly when I was a child, if you were sick, if you,
if you, at least look 16, you could walk into any bar and have a beer. And it really, none of these
things were a big, big prostitution similar, um, regulated, um, kept under wraps, um, prostitutes
plate, pay taxes, they have regular health checkups. This two has changed somewhat in the years.
But because it was there and opened, it's no big deal. And nudity, I remember watching, uh,
comedic shows that would come on at 730 in the evening and, uh, and they would be naked women
walking around and either for humorous purposes or whatever, but uh, there's no shame for the naked
body, uh, in the Netherlands. And that, that two has changed a little bit. Um, but that's the environment
that I grew up in. And so all these things were just not considered a big deal. And guess what,
if it's not a big deal, then it's not a big deal to have to try these things to an excess. Now,
what they did do in the Netherlands is made driving very difficult. Most people will not get their
license on the first go around probably two or three times that you'll have to take the exam before
you actually pass. I think that's pretty smart. If you take the combination of all those things and
also, you know, they really need less cars on the road and such a such a pimple of a country.
Um, so I, uh, this is, this is it within my DNA that it's just not a big deal.
And, um, when Christina was growing up in the US, she certainly did not, uh, know about any recreation,
uh, for the simple reason that I wouldn't want her speaking of it, uh, at school because in the
US, they would probably come and throw my ass in jail. I was really worried about that. Really.
Um, so, um, but, um, no, she knows what it is. Of course she knows what it is. She's 15.
She goes to public schools. She knows what everything is. Believe me. But it's no big deal. And she
doesn't care. And she doesn't, um, she doesn't want to use it herself. She doesn't want to smoke.
She doesn't smoke cigarettes. Uh, she doesn't drink. Um, and I think it's all just because it's
no big deal. And if she wants to, then, uh, she knows where she can get a drink. Or if she wants
something else, she knows where she can get that. She doesn't have to do that outside. So that's
our vision on parenting. And I have to say we're really, really proud of this kid that we've, uh,
we've produced and put on earth. We really are. What's this? Oh, yes. Oh, no. The
cinema playground screens. I was a movie. Hey Adam, Jim from the cinema playground.
I do. In honor of our one-year anniversary and our hundreds show, I have a new test for you
in your daily source code listeners. I'll play three movie clips. You guess the movie.
Okay. It might be a tumor. It's not a tumor. Uh, the Schwarzenegger.
Good morning. Good morning. Good morning. Oh, and in case I don't see you,
good afternoon, good evening. Jim, uh, do you carry in the Truman Show?
That one I know.
The sportos and motorhips, geeks, sluts, bluts, waste oils. Do we be the kids? They all adore it.
They think he's a righteous dude. Classic. Isn't that the principle from Ferris Bueller's Day off?
Here they are one more time before giving you the answers. Give yourself extra credit for
knowing the year and the actor of the movie. All right. Might be a tumor. It's not a tumor.
From kindergarten and our star Arnold Schwarzenegger from 1989.
Good morning. Good morning. Good morning. Oh, and in case I don't see you,
good afternoon, good evening and good night. Jim, carry in the 1998 film The Truman Show.
Sportos and motorhips, geeks, sluts, bluts, waste oils. Do we be the kids? They all adore it.
They think he's a righteous dude.
In 1986, 80 McClurg and Ferris Bueller's Day off.
Wait, I deserve a boring day off. Thanks for playing. Your feedback is appreciated.
Feedback at cinemaplayground.com. We'll talk to you soon.
Please remember to replace the speaker on the post when you leave the theater.
Visit the cinemaplayground at cinemaplayground.com.
Very cool. Congratulations on 100 episodes. There's a lot of those that have popped up recently. Very cool.
This is not good at this. You actually pulled some movies that I have seen. And of course Ferris Bueller's
Day off is such a classic and it was hard not to recognize Schwarzenegger. The boy,
do I miss those hit tests? Oh, I wish we could do hit tests again. Really?
Hey, Adam, this is Tokyo Jo from the newly released Made in Japan podcast.
Hey, TJ. I just wanted to come in briefly and a couple of things that came up in Delta,
Sarah, Charlie, 335. I see that Howard Stern has received some interest again from some
of your listeners. And I was reminded of his thoughts or I lacked their love about podcasting when
you're first talking about him a few months ago. So I decided to take a look at what podcast
Ali is showing for statistics. And I see that as of today, there's 14,627 podcasts listed on podcast
Ali. Now, it's thinking at each of them averages 100 listeners. Now, I know that not every podcast has
100 listeners, but if you consider the DSC and Don and Drew probably make up for quite a bit of us who
don't have the 100 listeners on average as yet. 14,627 podcasts times 100 listeners is 1.5 million
listeners. Now, in the end, that may not be many just yet. But I think the important point of
all this is that that's 100 or sorry, 1.5 million listeners listening from around the world.
I've liked and I've listened a stern for a number of years when I was in the States,
but on terrestrial radio or satellite radio, I can't hear them at all here in Tokyo, obviously.
And you know, from that perspective, isn't one reason that podcasting is better than radio,
it's simply because it's reach that can go around the world. And secondly, and briefly,
this whole thing on advertising, you know, I heard the the communal earthling idea yesterday,
I think it's great. But like some I said, also on the PSA's podcast, the impact of the
burp in the Sinsayo comment, it's hit me like a ton of bricks. And I'm so in tune with the burping
idea that anytime someone around me burps, I fall off with the Sinsayo, I actually board it out.
And now all of my Japanese colleagues and friends, I'm sure they think I'm nuts,
because you know, Sinsayo's not here and none of them have it, of course. Anyway, association
advertising for my perspective really works. I don't care if you burp or fart at him,
don't matter at all. This stuff really has my attention. I think it's something worth pursuing.
Hey, keep it up, Adam, and thanks. All right, man. So two things, first of all, I think there are
some podcasts of stirring around. And I believe that there's like a daily one minute or something that's
uh, I had a meeting with Jennifer Betcat at serious. She's a formerly of AOL and she's actually got a pretty
difficult task of integrating their website into their programming, which, of course, is not necessarily
in the DNA like it is with podcasting, not of broadcasters. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
comic strip, a blogger. Guess what, dude? Your wish is my command. Jennifer has promised me
that the serious pod shows will be streaming. It's coming, my brother. It's coming.
Now, regarding the earth link and advertising, yeah, the sound advertising, of course,
was a tremendous experiment and I'm very happy with it. I can't even deprogram people. In
fact, when I tried that, I got lots of people angry about the whole burping thing just by itself.
So it is kind of limited in scope, because I don't have that many more bodily noises that I can
that I'm guaranteed will show up within each, you know, within a half hour, basically, in any given
half hour, and recording the show. So it's what somewhat limited in scope. Now, I'm a little disappointed
for all the noise, all the pushback, all the the the flames and the ranting about the earth link
advertising. So here we are. A Tuesday, I have a strategy, a strategy meeting.
Thank God, it's not a steering committee, but we have a strategy meeting about the next earth link
campaign. And this is going to be user generated. So, you know, now I've heard from lots of people,
but all the people who yelled the loudest haven't come up with any really creative ideas,
and I'd really like to hear from you because here's the opportunity. You know, you get the
determined, how you want it to happen. So, you know, it's real easy to slag it, but now let's
come up with some creative stuff, looking forward to it. I got plenty of ideas. I'm just very curious
to see if some of the loud mouths have ideas. Hey, Happy, what are you doing? I'm about to jump
on the information super highway in that old plunker. You got a better idea? Sure, do.
First one. What can earth link give me that? I don't have here already. Earth link can give
you an internet safe from viruses and scammers. Earth link can keep your personal information
personal with free antivirus software of firewall and a spyware blocker. But I want to get on the
information super highway. Come on, get in. Earth link has high speed options that really need.
I love earth link. Earth link. We revolve around you. I love it. Thank you. That's the
bedtime stories go for there for you. One thing up today's end of the week's shows with email
from cyber, cypster DJ, cypster DJ from the cypster space electronic podcast. Good day Adam.
Just found this great song from the P&M. It's pretty funky. It's called Preacher Man by Oh,
yeah, and I think you're like, you know what? I did totally dig it. It is kind of funky. It's like
electronic with tau whites playing.
Come here, come
Come out of the pool, down from steeple
Better you find a random one
Where the people's digging, you found a show
Don't touch it, it'll be a different person
Can't feel it, please, man
Can't see it, please man
Can't just see it, it's a man
Please, come in
Can't just come in
Can't you come, man
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
see its no toohing payment, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
The sun to feel me in the red
To feel me in the red sun
To feel me in the red
To feel the blue
Well, pretty much a man
On the pod safe music network
A music dot pot show dot com
New servers in place
New structures
tables, whatever crap I needed to be done.
And Chris Walkwell said it's already.
The purchasing is ready.
So I told him make it so.
Number one, make it live.
It isn't live yet, but you should be able to test on
pod save for peace today, I guess.
Hopefully Chris is hearing this today, right, Chris?
Today.
Otherwise we're both going to have to
teach other on president's day in the office
because I am the president.
All right, everybody.
Thank you very much for traveling with me to New York
and back again Sunday.
I take off for San Francisco.
So it'll be from the Curry condo on Monday.
It'll be fun to see if Trinity still starts.
If there's no flat tires.
Some interesting guests on the podcast coming up this week.
Oh, we'll talk about bird flu.
And we'll talk about biodiesel and just all kinds of stuff coming up.
Fo show daily source code.com is where you can find the podcast
feed to subscribe to the show.
And of course, latest episodes.
Adam Curry dot com for all your feedback and have a great weekend
everybody. Bye. Bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.