This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy.
Delta Sierra Charlie 429er.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this show.
You are not seeing the forest with a wing DMM?
This dude is a pot-roar, we per seels in the duke doctor.
We've seen him on TV our whole life.
Super friends, we're the woman,
Stones, we're the last of the life.
I can be like any one, I see.
On a record at a bonus leave.
This is everhoo.
Dolls ain't the most of cash never on TV.
We are, we are.
The last of the sea for the heroes.
Over the 1970s.
We are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are
we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are we, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we are, we
Sitting home alone, waiting low control In the silence home, no one left to go
No more super heroes on the 19th of the days The last time I see more heroes
The last time I see more heroes The last time I see more heroes
The last time I see more heroes
We are we are The last time I see more heroes
You know they are just days when you wake up and you need some American hardbreak
Today being one of those days Thursday everybody how you are doing coming to you from a very foggy San Francisco
Finally the weather is back to normal yeah it will be cool again
Yeah coming to you from the curry condo
It is the coolest bachelour pad
Except I am missing all the girlfriends to clean up
and cook and do stuff for me
gonna do stuff for me man. It's like I'm all by myself. I need to go home. I'm so
ready to go home. Patricia promised Monday we do a show. I can't wait after a
whole bunch of a week end of debotry as I have planned for. Speaking of Michael
Butler, of course you can find last of the superheroes, American Heart
Break on the Podsat Music Network link to that in the show notes. He is the
host of the San Francisco podcasters meetup and last night I went to my actually
was my first podcaster meetup ever shame on me. I have to say it's never quite
worked out for me to be able to attend one. But Richard Brueher, a Joe
Carpenter, they gave me no choice really. They said you're coming. You got to
come tonight and it was packed. There's a lot of fun. Met a whole bunch of
familiar voices, they will put faces to it a lot of the familiar faces there
as well. Two of the youngest podcasters or the world's youngest podgoat.
Let me see if I have my- Oh, I'm bearing me. I got my cards here. These
girls were too cute. They were so sweet. What is this? One, two, three, listen to me.
One, two, three, listen to me. Dotlipson.com. No, listen to me.
No, two, dotlipson.com. Sarah and Nina who do the podcast by kids for kids and
they got business cards. I was so cute that came over. I Yoda presented last
night, which is one of the reasons I wanted to go. Tim Mitchell, VP of
Marketing, showed what the- what is it? I Yoda independent online
distribution alliances doing very similar to the pod safe music network.
Except they- they actually have paying customers that would be the
record labels who pay them to help them disseminate and sell music.
And one of the ways that they obviously correctly see is through podcasting.
So I need to re-look at their license and see how close it is to the PMX. I don't
think we're very far apart. And the groovy thing is pod safe music network really has no
customers. Yeah, I mean, if you buy something, if you buy a track, but that
might asn't come to the pod show that goes to the artist. For podcasters, I guess
really is the audience primarily of the pod safe music network. I work a
place for them to go and find stuff to play on the show and promote and
become passionate about. And then on the other hand, it's also a place for
independent labels or artists to put their stuff up and make it available.
It's a- it's a place without customers. Oh my gosh. Who would have
thunk it? I finally have some time though to socialize with the- with the
pod show folks. I was really nice. You know, I had my usual 1.5
more tinium was bouncing on my head by then. I just can't drink. But you can't
smoke anywhere. Can you? I guess. At least not- no, you can't smoke anything.
Certainly not what I like to smoke. And tonight I'm socializing again.
Ha! And this has been a long time coming. I am going to a show- I don't know,
is it- I don't think the show was caught. I think the person- the performance is
mink stole. And I'm going to be taken out tonight by our very own database
dominatrix aerononeal. And she said this is the show to go to. And we're going to be
a perfect pair. She's, uh, I don't know, she's 5, 3. I'm 6, 4. It's going to be just like
going out with Patricia. Only a little bit different. But I look forward to it. It's
going to be fun. So I'll have a full report tomorrow. And now that I finally,
you know, caught up on my sleep and I'm about to go home as usual. I think I'll be
able to handle it and still have a kick-ass Charlie for you tomorrow and Friday.
Today, this afternoon, I think it's eastern time. Do they have dual feeds?
Cali Lewis of Geek Brief TV is going to be on MSNBC. I'm not even sure what she's going to be doing
there. I presume she'll be interviewed. I hope so, at least. But I'm sure that we're going to
stop work at the office to see what's, see what Cali is doing. By the way, I love Cali's new
haircut. Or do you say quafuia? Her quaf is so beautiful. It makes her look even more energetic
and bubbly. And as we say, Cali, looking good. Cori and Jen, in 20 seconds, tell us, what is
bucket? It's bucket. Well, that explains it well. No, it's a show about every day stuff. Yeah,
funny things from our lives together. TV shows, the news. And we talk about the latest
movies and sports you talk about sports. And there's potty etiquette and kitty high jinx.
tons of pods safe songs and don't forget the monkey news because everyone loves monkeys.
Throwing a dash of geek talk and Jen stories about smoking catnip? We shut up about that already!
I was 13 years old. And um um um uh um um um um um um uh um uh um-
we curse a little too. For out of five, Dr's agreed. It's a podcast. It's bucket.
Find new episodes and other information at bucketpodcast.co
I don't know if you've ever listened to the Gilmour Gang, Steve Gilmour has a gang of tech
pundits and they talk about the latest news, usually about an hour, sometimes an hour
and a half, sometimes longer, sometimes shorter, there's also a daily version, Gilmour Daily.
You can find Gilmour Gang at GilmourGang.com, G-I-L-M-O-R-G-A-N-G-D.com, big controversy going
on.
And this actually does kind of qualify everything.
with ten euros, ready for ten.
Tenfoil had moments, tenfoil ad moments
and now its time for the tenfoil hat moment.
So you kinda gotta know the players who are
who revolve in San Francisco,
who make everything shake and move.
It's quite a little clusterfuck here. I don't think the rest of the world cares too much, but in San Francisco
It's just wonderful to hear these guys
Yappin about other guys, and it's really it's just it's like a it's like a scrapbook knitting fest for geeks
But it's pretty enjoyable to listen to if you're into tinfoil hats
Let's see who's on the gang. I think Docs rolls is a perpetual gang member Jason Calacanis
of
Weblog Zankin, of course, now AOL on the new Netscape. He's
I think he's now a permanent gang member. I think he's fantastic
I love it when people just say what they want to say and Mike Arlington who is
Very well known in Silicon Valley for it was a tech crunch. I think and his meme around him also hit tech crunch. I'm sure is his and
You know, he is
The site that he has a lot of people
You know, we'll bring Mike Arlington in to promote you know their new stuff that's coming out and and he's got you know super VIP parties and he resigned from the Gilmore gang because
There was this other guy on a Nick car. I think it is now. I don't even know who he is
But there's this big bruhaha and it's and it's all over
The the blogger's career
But you've got it you've got a listen to a show
I think
Gilmore is releasing it in either two or three parts because it's it's exceptionally long
I listened to the first part last night when it came home and it's great because
Forget about the the topic of
Whether it's tech or geek whatever they're talking about doesn't matter when you hear raw emotions come out. That's what's cool
And you've never hear this stuff on the radio anywhere because you just imagine this type of show running an NPR
It would I mean it would shake so much up because you really hear people get pissed off at each other and that's nice
I mean it's anger's an emotion too. Just as valid as happiness
So you might want to check that out
And this stuff happens from time to time and and I I just love it
That's the netting scrapbooking fest of the geeks
Yeah, you know someone sent me this a survey came out. I heard about it in a different show
Was it the BBC who wrote about this hold on let me just get this it's about to email
And the just of the story as I pull up the page actually the title is more than 95% of email is junk
It's spam error messages viruses and this is a report from email monitoring firms
Hmm, who's an email monitoring firm a return path?
Hmm, that probably a firm that sells something
Email security firm return pass at 99% of the computers at monitors that send mail have been taken over by spammers or virus writers
You know what I would agree with that. I would have to say that that a large percentage is spam and and it could actually be spam from people
You know, but it's still spam. I just send you a crap. You don't want to know about but here's the frightening thing
You know how you get those emails
That's a you know Viagra. There's other ones Xanx
Which is a well known
Was it a
Suppressant no
Xanx is an anti-depressant? No, it's not I don't know what Xanx is but it's supposed to take your fear away and a Patricia
Was prescribed Xanx because if you have a heart condition, what can happen is if you feel something going on, you know like oh
I have a chest pain. I don't feel too good
you know your your fear can
Can take over and that fear can turn into adrenaline adrenaline takes the place of oxygen
Less oxygen in your bloodstream can actually make your chest hurt more if you have a heart condition it can you can spiral downward
So it's very important
But I caught it the other day
And she said
Yeah, oh, you know, I saw this other place where we might be able to buy Xanx and and I looked at the email message and it was
Completely one of these spam emails with like you know four lines in the in the email message itself, you know
Want cheap Xanx want cheap Viagra
But she had bought it she said and I said but honey, this is spam
So no, I know it's spam but you know
You might be able to get a cheaper there I blew me away my wife is very intelligent
I would never buy something from a spam but she doesn't care today
It looks like someone had an offer there and I was interested in I don't care how they presented it to me the words were stupid and lame
It worked for me. I went to check it out. Well, of course
I have forbidden her from purchasing anything through any of these unscrupulous people, but
This is it, you know, this is wide continuous because
It just fucking works
Do you know the perfect family great jobs great marriage perfect kids
Loads of money and no worries. Yeah, that's all. We don't either kids life work life
This is my can Chris of the kids life work life podcast
We both have jobs that we sometimes love and sometimes not our marriage is sometimes for better and sometimes for worse
Our kids are perfect when they're sleeping and payday always seems to be a few days too far away
We know we're not the only ones living a life like this
Listen to our show and join an hour adventure because we try to balance kids marriage work in life
You can find us at kidswifeworklife.com or search for us in iTunes or your favorite podcast directory
Hey Adam
It's just Karen Karen Karen hearty on
Deadly source code 427 you asked for people to send you requests for you to talk about 80s bands
I'm going to do just that. I became a banjo. We fan about 10 years ago
So I missed out on the first half of their career. Do you have any stories about them?
Yeah, I got a story about banjo V in
There was the Moscow music piece festival and this by itself was a pretty interesting gig because
Moscow was still behind you know an actual wall that was in Berlin
There was no glass no stay was still very much communist Russia and the reason why I was organized is
Doc McGee who at the time was I don't know if he still he may still be banjo v's manager
He was also motley cruise manager at the time
He had been caught in some scandal involving smuggling. I think of marijuana on a private you know
Leer jet into my am and part of his punishment was he had to do community service
So he came up with a brilliant idea and was to do an anti
alcohol and anti drugs concert in
Lenin Stadium in Moscow
And on the bill some of you may remember this on the bill. We're banjo v motley crew
Azios born the scorpions
Gorky park which was a fine Russian band
Skid Row was the and of course MTV covered the event and I was the one that was sent on the chartered plane
It wasn't by no means a private jet. It was a chartered plane like a
737 with you know seats that barely reclined pretty much an easy jet before a very long flight from New Jersey to to Moscow
With one stop in Germany to pick up the scorpions and a couple things happened on the way that were there were notable
I don't know if I've ever told this story before but
Azio so Azio I'll get to banjo v in a minute, but Azio and
And the rest of Black Sabbath actually were on the plane. These are butler was on board and Sharon Sharon
Sharon who looked completely different. She was a little
Puggie English
Housewife literally but totally in control of of Azio and had to be because
You know anti drugs anti alcohol concert or not. I mean this plane was just booze and
so I'll never forget seeing Aussie standing in the
In the in the in the in the in the island of the plane near the laboratory and the laboratory was occupied
And so Aussie's you know standing they go share
And he let himself right there piston his pants and it was like okay, and that was you know
We were only 45 minutes away from New Jersey. We just left the airport
So I knew that was gonna be quite a trip and
One day I could get into all the different things that happened, but on the way back
And everyone was it was a two week trip everyone was just completely ripped and and you know
It had been a very intense time
Doc McGee had his personal doctor who takes care of his artist was along for the ride
And I don't know do you remember the Halcyon scare
Well, so the house Halcyon
I don't know which way I should tell you probably already figured it out
But anyway, everyone had a hard time sleeping in the seats really sucked and so
Banjobe's personal doctor
Hand it out these little pills to anyone who wanted to get to sleep, and so yeah, I'll take one of those and boy did I sleep
I don't remember anything that happened after that in fact
I was pretty fucked up for the two weeks after that because it was apparently this Halcyon stuff
Which
Only six months later
After this trip was taken off the market because it could cause severe depression and had you know suicidal tendons
I
Okay, maybe next time I won't take the little yellow pill from the guy in the doctor's code
Okay, so just a little banjobe story for you if you have more bands from the 80s or 90s
Particularly the hair bands, but I can probably do it on almost anything you want to hear a story
Decended into the adamaccurry.com or call it in voicemail numbers in New Jersey
2016256357 so if you're using Skype put plus one two zero one six two five six three five seven if you're in the UK
want to call it the London number it's
Four four so O2O actually in London 768 one three seven five three
We do it on time
Perfect four more minutes until the window closes
Sit and there's that's the politics in the daily source code and they stay here
And this is Dan the previous could be show
waking up on a hot South Dakota morning
It's gonna be 112 degrees
In the mountains today and anyway, it was quite nice to hear some politics in the daily source because Dan was from believers
But regardless of art and affiliation
Once you're always taken into what's going on and yet
Exercise in the Bible for this in the resource
Kind of Jefferson with a dream
Keep it out man you don't have to get into part of the politics
But we're coming up in a pretty important midterm
Could be city will be carrying with gusto and
What I'm doing so is thank him sit
By the way, man Dan from the previously be show once again a little history lesson for you very briefly
A lot of the detention with Israel began in the mid-19th century
when many European Jews started to return to
Their home they're holy land, which is where they're currently at now
They're well funded and the causal on a resentment it just placed many steps in
In the living in the area the waters of Israeli inception were 1948
1967 and 1972
And in 1948 when Israel declared herself state after many years of Zionism and
Continuing escalation
Jews in the Palestinian homeland
She was immediately attacked by her neighbors
Egypt, Syria, Lebanon, Jordan, Sidney, and I just know this shit
So anyway
This is fantastic
48566772
All right, so what you're saying
Dan from creepy sleepy show is that we were about do another conflict
Which I'm just calling a war I call him as I see him
Big difference though for the first time in any type of situation like this
The media is no longer controlled by
governments
The media in fact in 1970 most European media was 100% was all government controlled owned
Et cetera and even in most countries in Europe mainstream media is now commercial and have different different agendas
Their own agenda primarily
But we really have the media now so things have changed but I don't think that
The leaders of any party any country have have changed very well along with it or really recognize or realize what's
What's gone down so I think first of all that makes it seem a lot worse because it probably always was this bad
We just didn't see it that bad and
And
The only thing I'm missing kind of is the debate
I'm not I'm not I'm not seeing the debate a lot on web logs which I find a little bit disappointing
But I stand by what I heard I really do and I do not understand how this works if
President Bush
Arguably the leader of the free world
Literally said in a moment of
Complete honesty there's no doubt about it. He wasn't bullshitting Tony Blair because
That only happens when we're on camera. That's when all the bullshit comes out whether you're
President or whether you're you know
Mary hard of entertainment tonight the bullshit starts when you're on camera
So off camera. I heard it a sod has to call has Bulla and tell him to stop that shit
Could somebody please make the fucking call already
Comic strip
All right, so we're getting it set up comic strip blogger one of the illustrious
Personalities who appear on the daily source code. I'm going to set up an interview with him
I have to give him one month's notice and it has to be on a Saturday
But it'll actually come over to a to the UK to do it and
For more about that and
All of the Friday festivities those of you on serious 102 will have to tune in tomorrow
Because if it goes hellwise next for all you guys
And CSB of course has sent something in force little present. I know that you are cooking in the
Potential juice and you hardly see the word outside of Potential ink
But let me tell you about the problem in blogosphere
Namely despite Google claiming that it does not evil the blogging service on by Google
Blogspot is hosting several slender blogs where anonymous scam people are attacking others and the
Google refuses to take down such blogs with slender. I have seen blogs where anonymous scam
Is ridiculing people's wives people's houses and just trying to destroy people
Probably because these people are in competition with these scam anonymous bloggers
Yet Google refuses to remove these blogs where anonymous scam
Attacks people in criminal way conclusion this Google has
Do no evil principle is the biggest bullshit on this planet
Let me tell something to Sergei brain one of two bosses of Google in his native language ration
Well, what are you doing Sergei to be another as a shithead to the problem?
But at least you have to pay attention to the company in the august rationality
Potipity new data. Okay, so keep funneling your blackberry keep cooking in Potential juice. Yeah, you know
Oh my gosh, he speaks Russian now, too. We've had Polish. We have German. We have English. We have I've seen him
Come up with some Dutch. He does Italian Russian the man never ceases to amaze me. I'll bet you speak some
Finish as well. I mean, didn't he work for Nokia? He must speak some finish. Well comics are blogger
You have just witnessed human nature. I see no difference between what is happening in many places in the world take the
The Israel Lebanon conflict
You know you could say the same thing as like the Google of this war is America and they refuse to take down the blogs
You know, I still kind of wonder you know when Israel sends a couple of bullets up a Lebanon's ass
It does say made in America, doesn't it? What is on the Lebanese missiles? Who makes that shit that they make it themselves?
They buy it from someone else. You know, who's the Google of them? Who's making that stuff for them?
It's just human nature comics are blogger. I don't think you you shouldn't even look too far behind these things
It's just it is I really believe it's human nature
Eventually people just get into rifts with each other. It happens on every single mailing list. I've been a member of
Every
Every community particularly in an online world where everybody is equal this happens
And happens it's nothing to do about it man. If I went after everything which I thought libeled me
I would have no hours left in the day to simmer in my pod showed juice
Mm-hmm
Part of the interview that I'll be doing with comics to blogger or with what I thought was jacic rootowski
I don't know why I was saying well
a J.A. C.E.K. is to me. I wanted pronounce it jacic and
That's incorrect because here's the correct pronunciation of comics or bloggers
real name. Yeah, thick
Yeah, thick
Yeah, thick, yotsick yotsick yotsick rootowski now
I was listening to that because that CSB actually pronouncing his name. I was listening to that and
I could hear something in the background. Let's listen again. Yeah, thick
Yeah, thick
Do you hear that? It sounds like a kid in the background
List this one. Yeah, thick listen closely. Yeah, thick
Yeah, thick
It sounds like some kid is talking to another grown-up
Okay, so we know a little more the puzzle is starting to come together comics to blogger
Most likely has a wife and maybe even a child
Mm-hmm
Naptate on the Troy needs an iPod contest member. I'm giving away an iPod
Video iPod no less
Let me see now. I got to go for a shoot. I got to go to my site here
I'd asked you to put all entries into
The comments a daily source code dot com
Some people continue to post it at curie dot com. It's it's not gonna be valid if you post it over there
You know, I want to have it in one place. So don't send it on email either. Let's see
Yesterday's okay. We got some comments here
Let me just run through a couple of the entries. I remember this is an ad hoc competition
So a void where prohibited by law. You know, it doesn't cost anything to enter
You know, I'm not a lawyer. Praise Murphy yada yada
Adrian has an entry. There's more to podcasting than iPods dot com like that one. That's good
Troy, what is Troy saying? I don't know what Troy is saying
Here we go. This is from
RDFHG
Nice handle. I would like to win but I'd rather buy my own iPod dot com
Yeah, I like that one. That's good. What do you have here iron mask and iPods not just for porn dot com?
Yeah, it's very cool freshly registered from godaddy dot com using promo code DSC3
Thank you very much
You can use any of the pod chill promo codes by the way. It does not have to be for DSC use it for your favorite show
Let's see here we go. Oh, this is a this is a long one
Screw Troy. I can barely afford a cheap domain name let alone an iPod dot com. Oh, man
This is getting bad
By the day
Remember the original is Troy needs an iPod dot com and Troy is still very much in the running
Of course, I'm the only judge
Let's see
Here's another entry. I want an iPod by listening to the Charlie. Yeah, very cool
And of course, there's Troy with his original so I'm gonna keep this open a little bit longer
Maybe another couple days maybe midweek or so we'll choose the winner
I always have to give people a little bit of time to catch up because you know not everyone's on the same listening schedule as as the production is
Oh, what's this firefox one dot five dot oh dot five ready to install
Firefox is just completed downloading an important update. Oh, it must be restarted now. No, you can't restart
Dude, I'm in the middle of my show
Helicopter crash and Afghanistan Kevin toffel sent me
No, I'm sorry that's Kevin is for something else who sent this Alexander on-off
And unidentified helicopter crashed in south eastern Afghanistan Wednesday reportedly causing casual casualties
few other details available apparently two
Dutch
Troops were killed in this crash now. I'm very worried about this because the details are completely sketchy
But the guys that I the Dutch marines the air division
Who flying the chanook helicopters who I was with in in Iraq. I know a lot of them are
Now in Afghanistan so Han
Who was Corona one in Iraq is now ghost 13
He's a pilot of chanook and has a has a full crew
In fact, I know that he's one of the guys that went down in Iraq with that Dutch helicopter
Up on top of the mountain successful landing everybody fucking walked away from it
So I hope that this has nothing to do
Oh, I mean it's horrible that anyone has been hurt or or killed in a crash, but I really hope it's not any of these guys
So if anyone has any information please let me know
Really really like to know if possible
Okay, so as I said it's just two more days
Sorry, that's a major stretch in y'all
And then I'll be back on a different schedule so I can do the show
I'd like you know, it leisurely 11 a.m. instead of getting up at six every single morning and
Tomorrow of course
We'll be thank God it's Friday edition of the Charlie and I need your
Music
What are we gonna play let's rock it out?
I haven't heard from the official musicologist in a couple days jersey Todd, you know, let's let's get some cool gems
Please get them for me send them to me email them to me at amacurry.com spam by the way solved
Played a couple different songs by these guys
And but not this one apparently
Outfit's called get go three check it out
Yeah
Too far gone below to ever make it back on deck
I'm a spec between the timbers of a foolish ship ride and rivers of philosophy
And for the crap out of any bomb dumb enough to listen to me
The courtroom's the place for this face taking the stand looking my hand
We'll never before have a bad bad attention
Or maybe just the ones but the guy was so strange there
You never showed a lot like terror and if he didn't want the advert to have been made
I wait until the fence I guess my best defense was to suffer in silence
I never find the words when I'm confronting violence
And anyway do you know anyone who thinks that fast when they know the next words going to be
There last so the one consumed with regret my beautiful faces intact yet
And I said I need you to like me
I like you didn't fight me
I need you to like me
I said I made you to like me
I like you didn't fight me
but when I was the time I was drinking in the Memorial
The music on the box sent me, well, higher, and if you need to have a song that was
long with the rhymes all the time that I let my fighters and fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa
fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuff
fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa
fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffafa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa fuffa f
If you have never made a podcast and you want to make one, go over to, oh, holy, it's
one of the power.
You have to last there.
Order.
Castblastard.com and download Castblastard.
It's available for Windows only currently, or it's available for Windows only.
But you can download a version that'll let you record 10 minute podcasts for free forever.
And if you sign up for Pod Show Plus and you want to make a podcast there, you can actually
upload everything, your show notes, your RSS, all the podcast feed stuff, all the stuff
you have to have, but don't really want to know about, we'll be generated automatically.
And it integrates perfectly.
Now, we've also been in contact with the Ubercaster guys.
I believe the Ubercaster is now available for beta download.
I don't know if anyone's tried it out.
No one has sent me anything.
Any, of course, I'll be looking for an audio comment about it because my Mac is still in repair.
My power book.
Hopefully it's going to get fixed because there is some data that I wanted off of it at the very least.
But we have been in contact with them.
And we've made an, it's called an API and application program programming interface,
which is basically a way to connect external programs to the Pod Show Death Star engine.
And it's something called the MetaWeblog API, and with a couple of tweaks and changes there.
But it's all documented.
You can find it at developer.podshow.com.
And the Ubercaster guys, as far as I know, are implementing the API.
So when you're done recording something with Ubercaster on your Mac, you'll also be able to
shoot it all right up to the Podcast delivery network.
And of course, that's open for any other program.
I hope to see audacity implement as well, pretty soon.
So that's, that's it.
They think that got to get out of here.
I got to go to the office.
Hey, everybody, take care of yourself.
Thanks for listening.
Adamaccurry.com, dailysourcecode.com.
I'll see you tomorrow for a thank God, it's Friday edition of The Cha Cha.
Another Pod Show Podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this Podcast and we're great ones like it.
On the high performance Podcast, delivery network from Podshow and line-white networks.
I love it.