For the first time ever, the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr. in one action-packed DVD collection,
own all 27 episodes, the cult hit, including all new interviews with Carlton Koo.
First thing that Brisco did that impressed us was, we're not only to come in and really read the dialogue well as an actor,
but he also did a standing flip in our office.
You've flipped too for Brisco County!
If you like the kind of TV you can't get on TV, get your copy of the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr.
Available now on DVD.
Delta Sierra Charlie 476, scruncher!
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
30 minutes?
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need not sticking 30 minutes.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Oh, I guessed it, it's an angry curry.
It's like I picked the wrong week when I'm fed of each.
Welliffu!
Every one's in my room...
...legshirt, Laink, and so the boys.
And everybody with sameake still isn't right.
As the customers are down above.
How I know what to be Vocalist now.
Bye, colos, tutorial!
Hey, you don't tell me if it's your size
I'm just too old around
I'm just too lazy to take your side
Every one said I'm just too old
It's just too old just in time
I'm just too old around
Every one said I'm just too old
It's just too old just in time
I'm just too old around
Every one said I'm just too old around
This song is exactly how my head feels right now.
The other side, hey you kicking off episode number 476 of the daily source code coming
you from Northern California from Curricondo.
It is the Chacha, hey everybody, how are you doing?
As you can hear, I've got more equipment here.
You hear a little bit of it, I don't want to reduce that reverb just a little bit.
Yeah, yeah, I found a mixer at Pod Show HQ, audio mixer, and so I stole that.
It's not that nice sound, well actually, I don't think anything can really help the way
I sound because this is the way I sound.
Yeah, I've been snorting this blend of people.
Oh man, did I really get hit by some kind of bug really, really bad?
And of course it came at, you know, the perfect timing is when we had all that crap going on
for the past, was it 36 hours of PodShow.com being down and then the site's being up
and the media files not being delivered.
There's really only one thing I can say about it.
There are three people responsible for this mess, which is now as far as I can tell.
And so right now we're Wednesday, we're hump day.
It's not even 6 a.m. and I'm cracking it here at the condo.
It's still dark outside.
I'm at the Baker's Rack Studio.
Now there's really only three people who are responsible.
Ron Bloom, Adam Curry, and Bart Parsons, the CEO of GoDaddy,
because there's no one specific reason why this went wrong.
We have a partnership with GoDaddy as we do with the limelight network.
It's all part of the podcast delivery network and we ported hundreds of domains over from
other places like network solutions and just all the stuff that we had registered all over to GoDaddy.
And until we're really big account and GoDaddy's aware of it and of course we know how to
set an auto and renew option.
You know, we're not totally stupid, but we have a specialist account and things just went wrong.
And of course there's no reason for us to let GoDaddy to let that happen to one of their
bigger clients.
So shame on all of us and on behalf of the three of us and certainly on my path, I apologize.
Really, really apologize to our thousands of podcast delivery network users.
And of course, to the millions of listeners who use Pod Show.
So hopefully, hopefully this won't happen again, oh man, that was so painful.
And then I got hit with this, and I'm sure it has something to do with it.
I got hit with this bug, man.
It's just, you know, my nose has just been like Niagara Falls.
I was up at four this morning, because my body was telling me, hey, you got to take care of some business.
So I have a nice cup of Earl Grey tea here, huh?
Earl Grey, of course, you only want that with lemon, not with any milk, because that really tastes like crap.
And luckily, you guys are going to pull me through this today, because you've been sending me all kinds of
really cool stuff to talk about and to play. So let's get things underway here.
Hey Adam, this is John. I just want to thank you for turning over me on to Dave Appalito,
and that guitarman.com, room of girls, Angie Gay, and all that stuff, but especially that guitarman.com.
It's, uh, it's just great, and uh, keep up your good work, and enjoy your show everyday.
I listen to you and, uh, David, um, religiously, almost, um, like get very depressed when you
win the guys on honor, don't get a show on her, that's problem. So keep getting those shows out.
Thank you very much, and, of course, I'm a folder with a little scrunch tendency. All right,
you take care, man, and have a great week. All right, bye.
All right, dude, thank you. Yeah, I think, uh, I think we got David on the network now.
I'm, it's all this crap that was going on. It was kind of hard to keep track of a lot of things,
because email, of course, also broke. And now, what is this with, with, um, with, is everyone
getting these mortgage company and loan things, uh, on email? It seems rampant all of a sudden.
I would just get, you know, and, and they have an old New York address, and they use that in the
subject line, and, and then it's like, you know, uh, your shit's being repossessed. It's just a lot of
that spam coming in. I can't seem to get rid of it. Some about that scruncher of folder thing, though.
I've noticed that, of course, I am a world renowned folder, but when I blow my nose,
and, and, and it's, I've noticed this several times over the past, uh, you know, 24 hours,
I'm a scruncher. I do not, I, I just grab the paper and I just scrunched around my shnaz and I blow.
And I'm wondering, why is that? Why don't I fold? It's, um, I mean, obviously it's a very different type of
crap us that were, uh, that were taken care of here, but, um, I just thought I'd point that out.
And, of course, it gives me another reason to play this.
Hey Adam, it's Karla from theroomagirls.com. Um, just responding to last Friday show when you said
that you bet that I was a scruncher. And you're right, I am. Um, and Karen was a folder and she claims to be a
folder. But one night, as girls often do, we went to the ladies room together at our local pub.
Wait a minute, I just want to get a visual. Don't go too fast with the story.
Okay, Carolyn Carla and the ladies room together. As girls often do, um, reliably informed.
And I found out that she is by, all right, we're sisters, get your mind out of the gutter.
Anyway, yeah, she claims to be the perfect girl next door folder, but he really is by.
She does it both. Anyway, it had a blast at the ex-girls. Thanks for all the parts your swag.
Cheers, bye. Yeah, thanks, girls. She is the, uh, all-American girl next door.
They both are. And it's nice to have a combo, you know, to have a scruncher and a folder in the, in the,
in the mixed, that's cool. And lots of people on vacation, still calling it into the Charlie.
Hi Adam, this is Franco from Roca hospital. Did you ever receive a voice message from the
multiviland? Well, here it is. I'm here doing a great vacation at both trip and the
multis. Doing some great surf, just relaxing, eating fish, drinking beer and listening to the Charlie.
What a great, great trip. Take care and say a lot to all Charlie listeners. Bye.
Hi, Franco. Thank you, dude. Calling in from the Maldives. No, have not had a call from the Maldives,
yeah, Franco from Roca, Stitalia. Of course, amidst all of this crap, which seemed very significant
to us and to others, you know, there's a lot going on in the world. Pretty amazing that North Korea
claims to have set off a new, underground, new thing. And I have had my eye on the TV quite a bit
and, and on different websites, obviously, trying to get some more information on the news. And
when I'm waiting for is this size, the size of a graphic results, you know, that actually,
because North Korea says, we fired up a new, underground, okay, but are there ways to measure that?
Maybe I've missed it, but it's certainly what, you know, all I saw is like both CNN and Fox News,
this sense sale moment brought to you by Splenda. Mix the two together for a great new high.
You know, both CNN and Fox News, you know, were reporting on the news and what they kept
showing was, you know, like missiles going off, you know, just a continuous loop of missiles firing
into the air. Dude, it was an underground explosion. It was a totally blown out of proportion
image for what took place. He's, he's no notice of default for 11 West 42nd Street. That's
shit, just keeps him in. That's my old address. That's from, what does it, 14 years ago?
Anyway, so if anyone has has a pointer or a web link where there's some actual size,
a graphic, is that the word size, a graphic results or tests or graphs that we can see that they
actually did fire up a new guy, I'd love to see that, just to know for sure. And, you know,
as fate would have it, of course, I've been promising you an Uncle Don conversation,
my Uncle Don who worked with a Bush senior as his personal advisor. I think our security advisor
worked at the CIA. I mean, he's a lifetime career politician, does not like the current
administration at all. And although he is, as far as I know, he's still a Republican. And he was also
ambassador, South Korea. So as fate would have it, he and his lovely wife, Meg, Aunt Meg,
are traveling in Europe. And they're actually going to be, they are leaving, they're circling
around and leaving for, couldn't you? They wanted to see my sister. They're leaving from Amsterdam
on, I think, the 22nd. And I actually arrive in the UK on the 22nd. So I was like, oh, I'm going
to be in New York next week for some, for some meetings. And it would have been perfect to go and
hang out with them. So I just don't want to do it on the phone. You know, I just really,
I really like to do it face to face to, you know, to get a really good long sit down session with them.
So if the world doesn't blow up, hopefully I'll be able to do it in about five weeks or so
when I get back. People are definitely listening to the Charlie. And when their name is called,
they do respond. The view outside my window is of a clear blue sky and a deep blue ocean.
But it's not the view from my office in Abu Dhabi where I remain a regular listener of the Charlie.
Instead of be a radiant ghost, I have before me the Mediterranean,
seen from my hotel room in Can, on the front of the era. Twice a year, my job requires me to attend
the International Television Program Market to acquire content for the TV channel we operate in the Middle
East. But I wonder how many of the media professionals here in Can this week
fully devised as I do. But very soon, even television people will be shouting,
we don't need no fucking transmitters. I thought for the day from Malcolm soon back home again
in Abu Dhabi. Thank you very much Malcolm from Abu Dhabi. In Con France,
living up the high life, is that the, uh, medium? Uh, that is that? Yeah, it's the big, big, big
conference. Malcolm, I really appreciate you calling in and just letting us know that you're okay.
Your voice, man, you know, you could call me all day. I could listen to that. It's so beautiful.
Really, really is safe travels back to Abu Dhabi. And keep us, uh, keep us updated on what's going on.
I'd love to, you know, hear what you really, you know, what the vibe was in, in Con at the, uh,
at the festival. Well, it's not really festival. It's where all the deals are done. It's where
all of the people who make television programming go to sell their shit and they sell it to
as many channels as they can and big deals are done and it's champagne wishes and caviar dreams.
Malcolm, let us know. And of course, lots of blow and hookers, right?
Adam A, man, it's Jay Mac again from putite.com. Hey, I wanted to, uh, drive you quick message,
Howard Stern was talking about to this morning, man. He was saying, um, he listened to Jay
Thomas on, on serious stars. And he also listens to that to that iPod guy, the old NTV DJ is what he said.
So hey, man, we should know Howard's to it. So there you go, man. That's it. Um,
Dr. Waiter, man. Dude, Jim Mac, thank you so much, dude. That really makes my day.
Yeah, you have no idea. Yeah, um, I have, there's two, um, two heroes of wrong word, but there's
two guys in radio that I have, that have influenced me tremendously. The first, uh, from like 1980,
81 was Scott Shannon, uh, who was in New York and, um, took Z100, W HTZ from, uh, worst to first
in the market. And it was, and I was doing radio at the time in Holland, and it was so new,
so different what he was doing. He was really directing this morning show with multiple personalities
and pre-produced bits. And it's something that had never been done before. And it was just fantastic.
You know, even though we laugh about it now, shit, who's calling me this early? Go away.
You know, we laugh about all the rim shots and the cowbell stuff now. Uh, of course,
you know, I still use the cowbell, but he was a tremendous influence. And, um, and I was fortunate
to work with him, um, in the, uh, in the late 80s, just as, you know, the whole format of like a
morning zoo was starting to become very stale and, and just lame. Um, and we still, uh, email with each
other. Uh, and he's, uh, still, um, running WPLG, not PLJ, 95.5 in, uh, in New York. And so around, uh,
the time when I actually came to New York in 87. And, uh, and, uh, and I was still very high on, uh,
on what Scott Shannon was doing, you know, Howard Stern had just kind of risen to the top and was
kicking everyone's ass in the ratings. And, what Howard Stern was doing, it just blew me away.
I'm like, I can't listen. This is fantastic. This guy is just talking, just speaking his mind. He's not
rushing. You know, it's, uh, sometimes he has a band that he plays some music, but you know,
miss it. It's just, it's open and honest. And I loved it so much. And I so desperately wanted to
emulate what he was doing, um, no way you can do that on Z100. Although I tried to do it a little bit,
you know, I did the morning show for a couple of months, but the format, even the processing,
the sound of that station doesn't really allow for the room to breathe and for you just to talk
slowly and calmly and have some fun and let the room breathe is really what I'm talking about.
It was just something Scott Shannon used to say as well. Um, and an MTV, you know, I really,
I, I love trying to just be honest and and say the stuff that I felt. And because it wasn't live,
you know, all that good shit, I told you all the good shit on MTV never made it to the air.
And I was like, well, you can't say that because that might offend someone or, you know,
that person won't come on the video, music awards was so fucking political. So, um, how it was
a tremendous influence on me, um, and, and totally drove me, I think, to creating the type of show
that I'm creating today, uh, just by listening to and enjoying what he's been doing. So the hat,
to know that he's actually listening, even if it calls me the Big Hared Fag X MTV VGA iPod guy,
I'll take it. I really will. I'm very, very happy. No shit.
No, let me do one of these. Hi, this is Brent with Potts Show Radio. 7, 14, 81,
2, 63, 99, 348, 769. Now, what was the third number I named off?
You don't remember, do you? I do. That's kind of like what it's like being an artist thrown
in with a lot of other artists on the show. By the time the show is over, chances are,
you don't remember who they are. Here on Potts Show Radio, we featured the hottest potstate
bands on the planet. In each week, we dedicated an entire podcast. There's just one artist.
So when you're done with the show, you will know more about them than they know about themselves.
Give us a try. PottsShowRadio.com. 81. I'll just save you the trouble of rewinding. It was 81
was the third number. I got to think about numbers. I'm really good at remembering those.
PottsShowRadio.com. See, what do we have here? I got the satellite window closing and just a little bit.
A lot of people called in about, about what I was talking about, B.T. PottsShow and PottsShow
in the UK and what PottsShow would be doing in Ireland. And I did make a rather large snafu
by basically something like an American idiot saying that the Ireland is a part of the UK.
What I meant really is that Ireland is a part of B.T.s market. Now, let me just,
let me just go back and say, when we fully launch, which is coming up in,
what is it? Less than three weeks now.
We fully launch B.T. PottsShow in the UK. It'll be available worldwide. I mean, you can go to
B.T. PottsShow.com from Japan, you know, not a problem. But obviously, what we have on the home page
will be surfacing there, the top results in search. It'll be UK centric. That's the whole point.
It's like going to google.co.uk. Excuse me. I'm not, I'm not going to say it.
Now, the part of the deal with B.T. PottsShow is that, you know, we're going to use their marketing
muscle. You can imagine if you just look at the television in the UK, how much money B.T. spends
on advertising, on print advertising, television advertising, radio advertising, advertising in the
tube, advertising on the ceiling. They advertise everywhere. So, you know, one of the big reasons for
this partnership is, you know, to take advantage of that. And so, we will be wherever B.T.
Markets, wherever that. Fuck is that. Someone call me and let's go away.
Crap, how many of you freaked out when you heard that, huh? Go on. Oh, shit. My Skype is ringing.
Sorry about that. So, anywhere that B.T. has marketing, B.T. PottsShow.com will be marketed there as
well. And as far as I know, Ireland is a part of the mix. Hi, Adam. This is Gabriel here. I'm from
Dublin, Ireland. And I was just thinking to D.S.C. 474, where you had to call from Tanya there,
asking whether B.T. PottsShow was going to be willing at services in Ireland. And I noticed that you
got a little confused with the why she saw this B.T. wouldn't be involved in bringing
pod shows, Ireland. And I wasn't quite sure why you were confused about that. And so,
I looked at your website and I see how you've got an a little line there explaining how
you're explaining that B.T. PottsShow is in the UK. All of the UK. Just to explain,
I understand that you haven't been in the UK for a long time. Just to explain, the
public environment isn't actually in the UK. It's a totally separate independent country.
Gernsey, like you mentioned there, is a dependency of the Arctic Kingdom, but there are public
environment isn't. B.T. is only been in Ireland since about the 90s when it took over some
Irish telecom companies. But it's not actually the Irish division is quite separate. So,
I don't know, there's a fair point there. Just so, you know, folder.
Thank you. I would have picked you as a scruncher, actually, but I appreciate you coming clean
on being a folder. Okay, you know what? I'm even more confused now after listening to that, but
yes, B.T. PottsShow will also have a marketing presence in Ireland. That's because, you know,
they're there. So, it's all a part of their bigger vision, which literally is called B.T. Vision
interestingly enough. I do not want to forget to thank all an engineering and actually,
just about everyone at Pod Show for the past two days. You know, we had some crap come down.
It affected everyone. You can imagine if we're not serving shows, besides listeners, producers,
podcasters, there's advertisers. There's so many different things that come into play.
And it was a great fire drill. And it was nice to see, you know, the team really pulled together.
Everyone work on this. I think Richard Brueher, hey, and Joe Carpenter called hundreds of people
sent out emails, really did everything we could. And that's about the best we can do.
But really, really appreciate everyone's pulling together and making it. It's just nice,
man. It's nice to see. We've got a fucking team and a family who give a shit.
All right. So, the satellite window is closing. Oh, you know, I'll do this real quick for those
you listening to series.
All right. Keep those phone calls coming. Those of you on series stars 102, talk to you tomorrow.
Those of you still hanging out with me. You're going to love this. So it was only two days ago when I
did my roast recent show. I don't think I haven't looked at stats actually, but and those are fixed
too, by the way, the stats. So I'm reliably informed. I haven't checked them myself. And I mentioned
that we had a new sponsor, Splenda, which is, it's a sugar substitute, but it comes in flavors.
And it's in the yellow packets if you've ever seen them in the sugar at the beverage center,
at your office, or wherever. And so we've had that at the office now for a while and
and I have been kind of mixing and matching it. Obviously, I knew that they were going to be a
sponsor and it's cool that we closed the deal. But what really blows me away is the amount of people
who responded to that. Oh, no, second. I'll just, I got like a couple emails here. Let me just see.
I'm using that Google notebook. Have you used that? We just copy stuff from the web and then
and then you can put it right into a notebook on the browser. It's pretty interesting. All right.
So here's a sparkle. Hi Adam. You have discovered the ultimate and coffee flavors. The thing
you really have to do is mixing. Make a big cup of coffee. Let's say a double sense sale at French
vanilla and hazelnut. Too bad it's not available in the UK over here. You can only get their normal
stuff. Oh, I wonder what they're going to be rolling out to the flavors, the flavors to the UK.
Can you bring some over when you come back from the USA? I'd love to have some in sunny Bristol.
Yeah, I think that's a really good idea. I should take powdery substances with me on the airplane.
Yeah, they really love me. Andres from Germany says, can't get any here.
Love to have some. That's cool. And it went even further. I actually got,
uh, hold on a second. I actually got a really beautiful audio comment about it. Yeah. What's
this? Hey Adam. This is Ron from zips71101.pocho.com. I just found out about a week ago that I'm,
I'm diabetic. And of course, that means no sugar, no candy, nothing like that. Zilch, zero,
gone. You can forget about it. It's not going to happen. I was really bummed out because I really do like
Coca-Cola. And so, um, a friend told me about, uh, diet Coke with Splenda. You know,
I kind of turned my nose up and I said, I don't drink diet drinks. And I'm not going to start
doing that. I'll just do without drink water. She said, no, you really should try it. So I said,
okay, so my wife went off to the store, picked up a pack of diet Coke with Splenda. And I'm hooked.
Man, it tastes great. It is really good. And there's no bad after taste. It's wonderful.
I've also tried Splenda in coffee and tea. And who knows, maybe in the morning, I'll try with
some kind of cereal. You know, it might, it might be a great thing for me to have for breakfast,
because as a diabetic, you have to have breakfast. Well, um, also, my wife picked up some sugar-free
candy made by a wrestle stover. And it was, uh, let's see, these are, um, caramel, mandallians.
Man, they taste like the real deal. They have Splenda in them. And they won the best taste award
and it shifts best, dot org for 2006. It's just unbelievable to taste that this candy has.
And it's all because of Splenda. My wife just told me that she made some homemade soup.
Vegetable soup. And of course, it has tomatoes. And it has a little bitter taste. So to get the
bitterness out, she usually has just a little touch of sugar. Well, she told me that she used Splenda.
I said, well, let me try it. So she had just got it off the stove and, uh, it was still hot.
And so I went and got me a spoon and took a little dip. Delicious. Unbelievable.
I can't detect any change in the way she cooked it. It still had that same great taste.
And now I found out that we have flavor blends with all the different flavors of coffee.
And I'm not a big coffee drinker, but you know what? I don't mind the blends.
So if you want to bait a tester coffee, flavor blend drinker, sign me up, because I'm going to try these things.
By the way, Adam, don't worry about messing up the domain name. I've even done that myself. Who hasn't?
Uh-huh. So, uh, don't feel bad at all. By the way, folder. I'm not going to tell you if I have
folder on scruncher. You'll just have to tune in to the next podcast. Find out.
That's a zip seven one one zero one dot pot show dot com. Sheo, dude. Thank you so much.
And that you can't write that shit. And now I'm actually intrigued. You know, I'm thinking, I've never been
anyone to take a sugar substitute because I'm, you know, I'm like, that's it. If you're fat.
And, uh, maybe I should get a little better education on what sugar can do. I do, I do take sugar
and my coffee and my tea, yeah, sugar in the morning and sugar in the evening, sugar in the summer
time. Maybe I should be, uh, maybe I should be doing maybe I should have this blend on my
wheaties. I don't know. Definitely love to hear from you about that. And once again,
welcome to blend as a sponsor of the pod show, uh, network. All right, I got one more song before I go,
uh, actually it was a recommendation from a listener. Hey Adam, uh, Kevin from first person show
with another song for you and the Charlie listeners. This is a song that I found out about from Shelley
from Shelley's podcast today. It's a group called The Famous and The Song is Midway.
Some describe it as a bit of a country punk song. I don't really hear that. I don't hear that
country, but it's a great song. Rocks and it's got really hilarious lyrics if you listen to the
words. So I'll be like it and take care. Bye then. Scruncher folder. Oh yeah, folder. Mm-hmm. Okay.
Yeah, actually, I've played the song before on this very podcast, The Daily Source Code and I do
love the lyrics because I too before I die will have wanted to have seen the world's smallest horse.
On the other side of the plywood counter, with all the advantages. It's okay.
It's now magic. It's just a few left of the food there. The developer here is just a ring toss away.
Fill off the ride on the midway. Fill off the ride on the midway.
One more time of the last time. Get to see the world's smallest horse. What a pity thing for a
rattlesnake or a seasy-top kitchen. And if you take me home before 10 o'clock, I will wash my face on
every day. My homework can't even call this a fair part. But it's not so fair to me.
I was in lost. I met you at the boots just like you said to do. Big Texas like what?
Seven stories tall. What did you expect?
Fill off the ride on the midway. Fill off the ride on the midway.
Who I nearly died on the midway. Fill off the ride on the midway.
I actually had one of those. The seasy-top kitchen.
Given to me, buy the guys in the seasy-top. When I interviewed them in 1983, I think.
So all I need now is to see the fucking little pony thing and then I can kick the bucket, right?
Everybody thanks so much for listening to the Daily Source Code for today. Adam at potchow.com and
DailySourceCode.com for the show notes for today. I will talk to you tomorrow, everybody. Bye-bye.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network
from Potchow and Limelight Networks. I love it.