This is Soccer Girl. I just listened to the first episode of Shadow Falls and it's scared me
crapless.
Delta Sierra Charlie 433
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm tired on a jump mode check.
Dead dreaming of the Midwest and you know what I love the best.
It's coming home to you.
Tell me I will man guess close to you.
Isn't how he holds you?
When all he knows is you.
Tell me I will man guess close to you.
Isn't how he plays as you?
When all he knows is you.
I wish you could not protect your weight.
Backstays you can't afford I hate.
A weak little on the subway.
I'm out to ever watch you.
Talk about America's two ghosts.
You know what I love the most.
It's not your where it loose ghosts.
I'm coming over me.
Tell me I will man guess close to you.
Isn't how he holds you?
When all he knows is you.
Tell me I will man guess close to you.
Isn't how he plays as you?
When all he knows is you.
When the wild is red.
You say you want to stay in bed.
And when the wild is white.
You say you want to make it tonight.
You solve it.
And when the wild is done.
You say you want to have some fun.
I say it's better than I am.
I can say you want to make it tonight.
Tell me I will man guess close to you.
Isn't how he holds you.
When all he knows is you.
Tell me I will man guess close to you.
Isn't how he plays as you?
When all he knows is you.
Tell me I will man guess close to you.
Isn't how he holds you.
When all he knows is you.
Tell me I will man guess close to you.
Know the hell of warrior sunrise in this grid.
I kick it off with Mark Mulman.
Tell me how a man gets close to you.
Hey, how you do in everybody.
That's right.
It's bright and early.
It is Wednesday morning in the curry condo.
I am going home.
I can't believe I am going home.
It's been three weeks to the day.
No, three weeks and the day.
So by the time I get home,
that'll be tomorrow three weeks and two days that I've been out here in
in Pod Show HQ vicinity.
And as I said, I'm very much looking forward to going home.
But everyone who's been listening to the daily source code knows that.
Man, I must say I'm pretty darn invigorated.
Yes, it's been a fantastic couple of weeks.
We've really achieved quite a lot.
That's just from a personal and company perspective.
And I think we've actually had some fun on the show as well.
Although I have to tell you, I'm really looking forward to doing another show with Patricia.
So I'm hopeful and confident.
I'll be able to drag her in front of the microphone tomorrow morning when I get home.
And there's a lot more to go home into the UK for as well.
I mean, there's a lot of cool stuff happening.
Hello, Adam.
And if you can hear me above the den, well, I'm here at London's old court for the great British
beer festival 2006.
And for the very first time, they're podcasting from here.
More on that in a moment, but I can tell you that this morning, I was a judge for
one of the heats of champion beer of Britain.
And before lunchtime, I'd already had inside me seven miles and a bitter.
So it's now gone 10 o'clock at night and I'm starting to feel a bit jaded.
There's a load of people here.
It's great fun.
We've been talking to the organizers of the event behind the scenes.
We've talking to the volunteers that staff the festival.
And we're playing some great podsafe music as well.
So please do have a listen to beercast.podshow.com.
That's beercast.podshow.com.
Thanks again for letting us use the podsafe music network.
And indeed, podshow to host it.
And please, if you back in Britain in time, do come down to World's court for the great British
beer festival 2006.
So cheers for now.
I'm just going to have one more for the road.
Tough job.
Somebody's got to do it.
Yeah, slange it.
Skull.
Prost.
Lovely.
Hey, dude, don't thank me for the podsafe music network.
Thank the artists that upload all their stuff there.
That's what you should be thinking.
And of course, I'm sure you do.
I haven't listened yet, but I fully intend on getting a copy of the show and listening to it.
I'm on the plane because of course I've got my 10 hours coming up.
My, yeah, it's about nine and a half or sometimes depending on the win, 10 and a half hours.
Now, being here in the condo and you have to know the condo that I'm in is it's a beautiful building
and it has fantastic facilities.
It has a wonderful, it has a movie theater, which I've actually never checked out at all.
It has a swimming pool.
It's got a hot tub or it's got a sauna and it has a fantastic gym.
And every single time I come here, I tell Patricia,
yeah, man, I'm going to get into the regimen.
And I'm going to start again.
I'm going to work out every single day when I come back from the office.
And of course, what has it been every single day?
I come back from the office and I collapse in front of either my laptop or the television,
or both, sometimes.
And if you've listened to the daily source code before,
you know that Patricia makes fun of my physique all the time,
which of course is exactly what a guy with my physique wants to hear.
And one of the things she keeps on pointing out is that as the years grow on me,
the ass is declining.
And so I was a little bit worried about coming home.
I don't think there's anything I can do about it now anyway,
but I was very worried about coming home and her looking at me and saying,
hey, you look at shambles.
Look at that, you didn't work out at all.
Which of course, you know I didn't work out.
But we have at Pod Show HQ, a fantastic show.
It's the fitness attack with Amy Mack.
And if you haven't seen it, you can just go to podshow.com,
you can search for a fitness attack.
I think it's in rotation on the home page,
so you'll probably see it pop up there as well.
Amy Mack does a 60-second workout.
And she's also actually helping all of the pod show employees,
those who are interested and motivated twice a week,
with exercise at the office.
Which is another thing I didn't participate.
What is it made in?
So I asked for some help.
And I said to Amy Mack, I said, you know, Amy,
I really need to get my ass back on track,
because, look, my wife is 15 years older than I am.
She should have a man with a much better physique.
So she says that she has a program for me
that I'm going to start with today.
Today will be the first day.
Now it is a quarter to seven here in San Francisco.
So it's a little bit early, but never too early to start.
Now she said, I needed to have my wireless mic
hold on a second, which I have here.
Let me just look it up, oops, that's the receiver side.
There we go.
Okay, I'm, uh, how's this?
That's something we just changed the location of the microphone here for a second.
Okay, so, uh, this is the wireless mic.
This is the, uh, the other mic, G, what a difference, huh?
Okay.
And, uh, that's all she said I would need.
So let me fire up.
Episode number one of Amy Max, daily source code,
AcerSize.
Yeah, don't leave me back.
And this is day one of the AcerSize workout.
For the next 60 seconds, your ass belongs to me.
Uh huh.
To get this party started, I'm going to need you to lay down,
bat on your back.
For each bed and feed eight inches apart.
All right.
Ready for the next part?
Yep.
Okay.
I hope you're wearing your wireless mic or headset.
Yep.
I got to need you to put your arms down your sides,
calm to this side.
Don't just seal it.
Now your favorite part,
thrust your booty towards the ceiling and make a bridge.
Keeping your knees, hips, shoulders, all in a straight line.
Oh, crap.
Look for two seconds.
Hold it.
You'll slowly come back down and we'll paint nine more times.
Nine?
As you were doing this, you want to make sure your body's on the heels of your feet.
You should feel this in the back of your thighs.
Your butt and your stomach.
Don't forget to breathe.
Keep your stomach in both ways as tight as possible.
We call this exercise the floor bridge and it is one of many that you want to
through to achieve those bones of steel.
Use the side to get more fitness tips.
Check out the fitness attack podcast at fitness.com.
Potion.com.
I'm going to do listening so if you aren't breathing hard for the next
minute or two, I'm going to know you are doing exercise.
Until next time, as you're saying is.
Oh man.
I didn't feel that in my ass, Amy.
I felt it in my back.
How can my back be attached to my ass?
My assurse eyes muscles.
Oh crap.
I'm dizzy.
104.
It's time for the 104.
I'll have moment.
It's not funny.
I actually am dizzy.
All right.
This is a 104.
I'll have moment.
So if you're not interested in 104.
I'll have crap.
You might just want to fast forward about three and a half minutes.
We got to a very beautiful place yesterday at Potio Plus.
We had a lot of reports from people saying that they had one specific page
on Potio Plus that wasn't loading fast for them.
And it wasn't everybody.
It was basically all over the globe.
There were different results.
And what happened was, is once you're logged in my page,
literally would take anywhere from a minute to five minutes before it finally loaded.
This was a problem we've been working on for quite a while.
And that we finally fixed it yesterday.
And since sale moment brought to you by Amy Max Fitness Attack, link in the show notes.
So we finally fixed it.
And there was a call out in the comments on curried.com.
Actually, not on dailysourcecode.com.
By the way, dailysourcecode.com is going to be the place to leave comments
on the show as I have some other plans for curried.com.
And so I won't be crossposting eventually.
But we still have some work to do on the way our blog feature works in Potio Plus.
Anyway, so there was a call out to explain exactly what happened.
And I'll just try and do it the way I think I understand very well what happened.
But essentially, if you look at my page on Potio Plus,
you'll see that it's really several different modules.
And on the right-hand side, you have some recommendations of shows to listen to
new listeners who was popped up channels by new listeners or channels who have just been created.
And what we found in the code, and this is really an esoteric type of problem,
the hang was actually occurring when the images for the connect or the new people,
the cool people, which I think is three images, was being called for that page.
And the way it was being called was actually because we're moving our servers around
and our images servers changing in location.
So the developer that built this particular piece of code put in a link to an HTTP link.
And you could have referenced it to the actual directory on the server where the images live.
But he referenced through a URL, which of course is a podshow.com URL.
What's interesting is that three of that we have a number of servers in our cluster for all this
load balancing that we need to do. But three of those servers, somehow this is the real issue
that had to be solved. Three of those servers were somehow misconfigured.
So when they're actually requesting something from Potio, from their own domain,
for some reason, something was just hanging there for, well, anywhere from a minute to five minutes.
So obviously, we all we had to do was just patch that one line and figure out what was
misconfigured with the servers. But essentially, when someone requests a page from Potio,
the load balancer points you towards a certain server and it has intelligence in there and
caching and knowledge. So the next time you go, it's probably going to send you to the exactly
the same server for load balancing purposes. So people who had already had this error once were
pretty much getting it every single time. And it was great, man. I just sat there yesterday,
well, like, five of us were going through all the different scenarios and we found it and
and gosh, darn it, it's so nice to see it load and so fast.
Learn something new yesterday, talking about spam. I got an email from
Nick Zitler. And this is something I did not know about Gmail.
So to note about Gmail, you can curb spam and such and check this out. When you enter your email
address into a form or anywhere, particularly where, hold on, I just got to pull down the shades
for a second here. The sound is so nice, but I can't quite see the screen. There we go.
So you know, let's say you fill out a form to place a comment somewhere and there's a possibility
of the email address mine show up. Here's what you do. You enter, so let's say my,
your Gmail address is budhead at gmail.com, just as an example. If you enter in your email address
as follows, which in this case would be budhead plus, and then you enter, let's say you were posting
on, on the Don and Drew forum. Now we wouldn't spam you with that. So let's just as an example.
So you do atom plus Don and Drew at gmail.com and, and, and Gmail, then understands that that is a
specific, a specific email address that you use. And I guess then we'll route any, any mail that
comes through that from that particular place with that email address, of course. It'll place
it into your spam folder. So it'll still come to you, but it'll be seen as spam and then it'll
put it into, you know, that kind of breaks down that I think about it. What if I sign up for
automatic notification of comments? Hmm. Anyway, Gmail is doing something a little bit smart there.
So, you know, I should just paste that information into the show. I don't know if I did a very good
job explaining it. Wow, there's a lot of interesting stories. I don't know if you've been following
some of the geek talk about Dig and Netscapes new, well, new, relatively new.
What we call, what's it called now social bookmarking site? Of course, Netscapes is a Jason
Calacanis is kind of taken a lead from Dig and created his own version of that. I think with,
with different different objectives, perhaps a different end game in mind, but it is pretty much the
same idea. But what's happening now? And when I get this story from, oh yeah, from Valleywag,
they'd receive an email. It turns out that media companies and media companies, particularly
marketing companies who are hired by other companies to get them, you know, to get them
press and PR online are actually hiring people. So let's say, you have company A and there's a
story about you in the New York Times. They will hire hundreds of people to dig these stories
to get them higher ranking on the social bookmarking sites. Nothing legal about it, of course,
but it is very interesting to see marketers jumping into the space and what does this mean for the
quote, integrity of a place is like dig. You know, this is something to keep your eye on. I'll post a
link to the email that Valleywag received because I think you'll, you'll definitely next time
you visit a site like Dig or NetScape, you'll probably look at it with new eyes because you just don't
know any more. Is this really something people dig or is this something that is just being pushed
up the chart for a fee? And maybe that's an interesting debate we can have. Is that okay? Is that not
okay? Can the the real quote, zeitgeist of a community actually outweigh the long green of marketers?
Would love to hear from you. Send it to Adam at curie.com or please post it in the comments at
dailysourceco.com. Are you interested in psychology and what makes us tick and personal growth
in the inner life? In the integration of mind, body and spirit, if so, then you need to get on the
couch with Dr. Dave. As he interviews leading edge thinkers from around the broad world of psychology,
you'll find the shrink wrap radio psychology podcast at www.shrinkwapradio.com.
It's all in your mind. You should really listen to that Dr. Dave show.
The people are tuning in. Extremely popular. I've met Dr. Dave a couple of times and
listened to a show and liked it very much and I kind of drifted in and out. I've re-subscribed
I got the show through pod show plus. There's a lot of good stuff there. And for those of you who are
into what your mind is doing, it's an interesting little piece of your body. We talk about it a lot
on the Charlie. What's going on in your head? You might want to check it out. Trinkwapradio. Was that
Trinkwapradio.com? I believe it is. Still working on the show notes. You've probably seen that I'm
no longer posting a long run down. Interesting debate as well about this. Some people never go to
the show notes page. Some will go to the show notes page. After they've listened to the show,
which is always kind of been my hope, is that show notes is more like a reference
after you've listened to the show to go. Oh yeah, I want to go check out that song. But of course,
exactly the opposite seemed to be happening. At least for a majority of people.
And that ascercise gave me sense. The opposite really was happening where
people would go to the show notes, look at the show notes, and then make decisions about
the actual program attached to that based upon those show notes. And so I'm thinking, well,
you know, if that's really what people are doing, then I should probably make the show notes
more attractive, more like a headline. Now, lure you into the program. And then of course, there's
a lot of die hards who want to treat at least this podcast more like a weblogg so they can
deep link into specific sections of it. That I don't like. That's like, you know, I just paint
the picture and people only want to be able to see the middle piece or the right-hand corner,
you know, that I'd rather you not listen if you're going to do that. What I do hope is that we'll
have ways for and we have some of them, but we have ways for people through a through pod show
plus to actually point out pieces of a podcast and hand off a piece of a podcast so you can
listen to the whole thing or go to exactly the point that someone referenced you. But really,
I think I have to make it more of a headline to draw you in. And of course, the trick is,
is at the same time to also provide the information for people who just go there for reference.
So I'm working on it. And of course, this takes something that I don't have a lot of,
which is writing skills. Be prepared for some weird-ass show notes as we, as I go through this,
this very trying period of my life. The unions are up in arms. When I say the unions I'm talking
about after and sag, sag being the screen actress guild after being the American Federation of
Television and Radio Artist. The way it works in mainstream media, if you actually work on a union
project, let's just take a television series as an example. If that television, you know,
there's a, there are set deals. It's like a union, you know. So it's, it's all about compensation.
And if that program is distributed in a certain way, you will get what they call residuals.
So if it's actually re-eared, in fact, I did an episode of Swamp Thing once. Man,
I wish I could find that. I don't have a tape anymore. I starred in an episode of Swamp Thing.
And to this day, I still receive probably on an annual basis about $2.60 of residuals
because it'll, it'll air somewhere on, I think it, air originally on like the USA network or
something and then it goes into syndication for years. This was probably 12 or 13, maybe maybe
maybe in 15 years ago. So, so it's old. But, you know, so what happens when a show like that is
eventually sold through the iTunes Music Store, which I always find an interesting contradiction
in terms it's a television program being sold through the music store. But, okay. So you can download
it and watch it on iTunes or watch it on your, on your video iPod. Should I be getting residuals
from that as well? And of course, the actors feel that absolutely they should. But this is,
you know, it's still kind of been an experimental period. And, and, you know, obviously,
I think these production companies and movie companies don't want to give up anything.
Oh, crap. You know, it's too bad you're listening to us on serious stars 102 because you
can't hear the rest of this story and the last song that I've got lined up for the source code
listeners. However, specific host hellways coming up next, then we'll bring you Dawn and Drew
American cliche, which is a show that is really popping out. Michael Butler after that,
the Frank Truth with the Brian Know, all about the life and times of Frank Sinatra and then
East Radio and Scott Siggler winds it up with his patio book adventures between 930 and 10
Eastern Time. And I'll see you guys again. I'll talk to you guys again tomorrow from the cottage
back in the UK. Take care, have fun with Mark. Okay. Right. So, a whole story about who sent this to me,
Bill Berger sent this to me. And it's a really long story. But it seems like, you know, we,
excuse me, I think we could actually run into a, uh, run into another strike situation.
Because, you know, it's tough, you know, if you think that you, that you really deserve to be paid
for every, um, extra sale of a product and if that was, uh, not the initial agreement to go back
and agree to new industry standards. And I'm watching this very closely because, uh, if anything,
the work we're all doing together is non-union. And, uh, the main reason is because, you know,
I don't think anyone is, uh, is getting really rich off of, uh, off of the independent vibe yet,
uh, sure, uh, we're making money. Potcha was making money, but, you know, the, what I'd be able to,
uh, finance shadow falls if we had to do it by, uh, the union rules. No way. But of course,
those union rules for actors and producers and directors and engineers, etc, are based on, um,
a very rich history of knowing how much money can be made with these projects. And we just really don't
know, um, we really don't know yet. So it, it may be a little early for, uh, for union calls, but I'm,
I'm hoping that it may not be necessary at all that everyone will be able to, uh, in fact,
I'm hoping that the marketplace will be so huge that we won't even need that. It'll just be
a matter of picking the right projects and being in contact and being in the right communities.
Um, the great example is, uh, is Jeff Smith. I mean, uh, I hope Jeff. Jeff, are you listening? I hope
you're charging people for all this great work you're doing. Um, you know, Potcha was certainly
paying Jeff for, uh, for the stuff that he does for the daily source code and, and for other, uh,
other projects that that we've hired him for. Um, so I, you know, I think that we're going to find
the marketplace is probably going to eliminate the need for that and we can just work on buy out contracts.
But I don't know. I really don't know. So it's interesting to follow very closely. And, um, just, uh,
two more things. Well, one, of course, the voicemail numbers. Uh, remember now tomorrow,
we're doing a show with the lady Patricia. So if you have, uh, anything for her, uh, make sure that
you get it in as soon as possible. Plus one, 201, 65, 65, 65, 7. That's our number in New Jersey
and in London plus four, four, two, zero, seven, six, eight, one, three, seven, five, three.
Righty, Amy Mack. My assur-size is making me burp. Last night when I came home, um,
I saw that in my video channel that I have set up on Potcha Plus, which I believe is
public. So you can, you can watch that channel as well. And essentially, it's the most recent
episode of a number of podcasts that I've dropped into that channel, all video podcasts. The most
recent, um, release from Ted, the technology engineering design conference, which is held every year.
And, uh, what was it to think that was Monterey this year? Uh, there was an, and you know,
this really amazing people, uh, speak at this conference. And it's fantastic that they're making
this available for the public to watch. Completely sponsored by BMW, by the way, uh, which I think
is done at a really classy, really nice fashion. And I think it's so, so worth the content that I'm
getting to sit through, uh, the same BMW, uh, pre-roll spot and post-roll. It doesn't bother me at all.
Was a demonstration of multi-touch computing. And I, and I, you have to watch this. I'll
go, I'll put a link in the show notes to this. It's going to blow you away. This is the interface
I want for my, for every single computer I use from now on. The idea being, I'll just kind of
try to explain it. But you have to see it to believe it. Imagine, um, um, a large flat screen about
the size of, I don't know, two place mats. And, you know, where if, if you have a, um, if you have a,
a pen-based computer, like a, uh, what do they call those things? Notebook, not crap, tablet. There you go.
It'll take one touch point. And that touch point is either going to be your mouse or it's going to
be a brush stroke or it's going to be, uh, uh, uh, uh, a pen stroke, something like something like this.
But multi-touch, which apparently is not all that new that of technology, it's just the processing
speed is now quick enough to actually do something with it. With multi-touch, you can actually,
you know, put any number of pressure points onto this screen, which is kind of at a, I don't
like a 45 degree angle in front of the, the person who is demonstrating it. So if you put, you know,
all your fingertips, tops down, then all those, your fingertips, all the fingertips would,
would actually do something on the screen pressure sensitive as well. So he was showing some very basic
stuff like, um, uh, a lava lamp, uh, and you're actually looking at the screen, okay? So that,
so you're, you're interacting with the screen at the same time, which, of course, is cool because
multiple people could be interacting with the screen. And that was just a warm-up, then he showed
what you could do with pictures. And it was like, it was literally like rummaging through pictures,
but really doing it, you know, on, on your desktop and arranging them. And, uh, oh, let me,
let me make this one bigger and let me move the table top a little bit. It, it was, it totally just
blew my mind. And I don't know how far we are from application. I mean, this is how I want
cast blaster to work, man. Imagine I could be touching multiple faders and, and, and buttons,
and it would be responding in real time while I'm looking at the actual, at the actual screen
where I'm making these commands, it goes so far beyond the mouse and keyboard. And, of course,
you can render a keyboard right there on the screen. And by the way, make the keyboard bigger,
smaller, change the keys around, um, it'll blow you away. That is something I want you to go to
the show, and let's more check it out, because it is, uh, it's astounding. And then last night,
uh, after that, as I was rummaging through the most recent shows, um, then I wanted to catch up on,
I, uh, heard, uh, the latest from Transdance. This is a Candace Loopers from Band Tracks.
It's got a new show on the pod show, Transdance.podshow.com. It's actually Transdance.
That's good. Just see the link in the show notes. They got permission for this, uh,
PLW summer club mix of group is in the heart through Ioda.
We're now, uh, helping push this out to podcasts. Very cool. Good working with you guys.
Happy to play this as well, link in the show notes, group is in the heart.
Feel free to ask your sides of this, and if you want to.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, a weird cat, never ever, never
Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high?
Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in
high, who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high? Who's in high?
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo
-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-
Now, there's something you can ask for size too, man.
Group is in the hearts.
The PLW Summer Club makes, thanks to Iota, the independent online distribution alliance.
So I think that this is a major outreach from Iota.
I'm not quite sure how it went down with Canis Lupus band tracks, but he was able to put
a link to the song in the show notes.
So, and he said that he had permission to play it.
I think that we're so close to working together.
And in fact, it's so cool because Iota basically has a whole different customer base.
They're working for the labels to help promote the independent labels product.
And we're all about labels or artists, doesn't really matter.
We just want people to be able to share this music.
And of course, we also have a purchasing system of the positive music now.
We're not completely rolled out yet as we have a lot of moving parts, but there are a lot
of songs already for sale.
And pretty much anyone who specifically goes and requests it through the help desk email
at the Potship Music Network can get it turned on.
So, all we need now is just that last bit to make it, quote, pod safe, although I guess
it almost is pod safe.
But, you know, I have no way to report back.
I have no way to report back to you guys that I played it.
So, you know, why don't you make an Iota account or something or let's work on it.
Please give Michael Butler a call and try and figure this out because it's cool.
And I really love playing that song, and I thank you very much.
Okay.
On my way home to see my girls to hug with my babies, I'm so homesick.
Atamacurry.com, dailysourcecode.com for all of your comments.
Remember, 20 is an iPod, will be giving away the iPod to the most original domain name
as a registered through any domain name service, but my recommendation is go daddy $6.95
since if you use the DSC 3 code upon checkout.
And if not, I'll just see you tomorrow with a lady Patricia.
Take care, everybody.
Thanks for listening.
Bye.
Another pod show pod guest, stick it in your ear.
Get this pod cast and more great ones like it.
On the high performance pod cast delivery network from pod show and limelight networks.
I love it.