It's time you got in the game.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Get a domain name, free quick blog, and complete email.
Get in the game at GoDaddy.com.
The world where people think that show 500 was important, comes a far more important
number.
Now, on your podcast listening device, comes a show that represents the one half-meg milestone.
Keeps across the globe recognize the importance of numbers like 8, 16, 32, 64, 128,
256, and now, DSC 512.
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, the $16 million worth of
airplane strapped to my ass, and the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Testing is a victory!
We're at the heart, we won't
Let's go, we value who we are, we won't
We're any of the soil, your young mechanic can be a panic
We just could look you down
And if army, it can be a stormy
If she dances with all, we stop it then
We're at the heart, we won't
Let you do it, we'll keep you ready
Go on, try your luck, you may be tired of that
We're at the heart, we won't
I won't, we won't, we won't, we won't
Hello, let's do it, yeah.
Hello, let's do it, yeah
You shoot Petra is your way
O'er that we can pursue, yeah
She threw, all the pieces thin
Say it the light away
The blue righteous is always crazy
Shut her a loop you hear
Hey, we don't know how to do it
and now, it's to shoot them
You have a blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue,
blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, pink, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue
opened up the show by telling you that it is indeed the mystic 512. I've been trying to
play that song for you for two days in a row. How is it possible that I went to California?
I went to Los Angeles, that is, and that I stayed at the same hotel I stayed last time,
but I swore I wouldn't stay at the Beverly Hills Hotel, which of course is the epitome of
old world old fashioned Hollywood. And it shows because they still haven't fixed their
goddamn internet connection. It was impossible for me to really tight schedule. You know,
when you're in LA, you got to do breakfast meetings. It's like 730, and of course you don't finish
up the day until 1030 at night after you're done with your dinner meeting. Everybody take in meetings
and there's just no time in the morning to dig around. You know, I would need to get my pod
safe music. I need to be able to upload stuff. And in the morning is when everyone else apparently
is on the network at the Beverly Hills hotel. So I'm sorry. I wasn't able to get a show out to you.
But it's good to be back in the condo. And let me tell you, man. I have been there. I've been,
I have been to the Death Star. There's a lot of confusion going on. Hollywood, my friends.
Everybody is running around trying to figure stuff out. And yeah, I know everyone's got to be in
the new media. We've got to be doing the new stuff. Even if we aren't making any money, we want
to do stuff with you. And let's take another meeting. And oh my god, it was, it's like the whole
town is just going nuts because they're not sure how to how to participate in the stuff we're
doing online. We met a lot of great people over the past two days, though. It was great to see
Tony Costas from Costas a World, Sharon Bam from Rock and Roll TV. Oh, man, we sell so many people.
Crank you. You met the guys from G-Living Live. Of course, we also met people at like
William Morris Agency. C-A-A. I see it. It was fun though. It really was. Yesterday, I just got
to tell you though. I was, I was so fed up with everything so fed up, just even having breakfast,
just listening to the conversations at tables. I should have recorded that. I would just too busy.
I wasn't thinking. Anyway, so I had this whole thing planned out. I was going to use the
the dial tone system, which apparently really works. You know, where I basically give you the touchton
dial tones and you hold your telephone up to your speaker and it actually will dial. I was going
to give you my room number to dial so that, you know, we could have some fun with it, but I didn't
have a line anyway. We'll be doing more with the dial tones later on, but perhaps we can still do
have a little bit of the fun that I'd planned for you while I was in the Beverly Hills hotel.
It's a real sing-along free hall. And, uh, no, I don't think it's pot safe.
I just found the head. And, one day, he was shooting ads and food up through the ground. Come
above the link through the hall and answer. Right, who? Texas T.
Just thinking, oh, gentlemen, can folks said, Jed move away from them, said California is the place
you're to be, so they loaded up the truck and they moved to Beverly Hills that is some swimming
booths movie star, Josh. Granny and me always has to dance this little number. If you'll take my
part, I'll try to take Granny's part. What do you say?
Hey, it's all for all the fellow dude, try to keep out of the world, huh?
Now it's time to say goodbye to Jed and all this kid. They would like to thank you, folks,
it's kind of a drop at the end. I won't invite you back again to this locality. I have a heap
in heaven of the hospitality Beverly Hills. That's what to call them now. Nice folks,
y'all, come back here. Much back. Yep. That's all. You know it. Earl Scruggs,
Ballad of Jed, Clampett. Yeah, that was good. Of course, there were some good parts of the trip,
you know, hooking up with Mark Yoshimura Namcoff, hadn't seen him in a while. And it's always good
for me to to see Mark in person because, you know, sometimes the thing he says, I'm
Pacific Coast, hell away. I just so brash and so mean and it's good to, you know, look at him.
So I can just go, oh yeah, that's right. I understand now. Hey Adam, it's Chris Conley from CC
radio. biz and I was listening to DSC 511 and you said this. The sky is completely red. The sun
is just coming up over the clouds and the distance over the day. And even though,
in fact, I'm going to actually put down the shade here so I can see what's on my screen.
You know, there's an old, uh, damn, that's loud. There's an old sailor's, uh,
rhyme that says, uh, uh, reds, uh, reds guys at night, sailors delight, reds guys at morning,
sailors take warning. I don't know though because I've had some really nice red mornings here in
in the Bay area and the days have been just fantastic. Oh, yeah. And I just wanted to mention
after spending two months on a lobster boat, what I realized is that sailors take warning in the
morning because of red skies, although it may seem like a nice day being sunny, the water is affected
by the wind and the wind will pick up. Now, living in the city, that affects the weather.
And frankly, your safety isn't determined by the wind. So that's why that's all Adam.
All right. Okay. Folder. Folder scruncher. No, no, no, giveers, no takers.
Okay, a couple more days left in San Francisco. It's going to be great because we have our, uh,
our second annual holiday party coming up on, um, what is it Friday?
Yeah, that should be cool. We've got a lot of, I think we're going to have about 125 people.
Now, of course, the spouses are allowed to come and and kids and bring in some people up from,
from Los Angeles, um, oh, by the way, as I came back to the condo yesterday, I took a look at the home page.
And there were two things that I thought were that pretty damn interesting. The first one,
Cali Lewis appeared on the MSNBC with former colleague of mine, Allison Stewart, to give you the, uh,
was that?
You hear that something's changed. You know, the gremlins have been in,
been into the, uh, into the condo while I was gone. I also had everything's feeding back and beeping
all over the place. Anyway, um, so that was pretty cool. There's a nice clip of that, uh,
that you can find in the home page of podshow.com. Um, and then, uh, the high fish show,
um, Lika and Kevin apps went to the premiere of the new Will Smith movie.
And they got, uh, they got a one on one with Will Smith and they got some of the excitement there,
the premiere, and they got the mayor of San Francisco. And, uh, I was really proud. Like, yeah, go.
And very interesting to see, um, Jada Pink at Smith, who, um, you know, it's, it's funny. Once
you get a different type of crew once, you know, if it's not someone from entertainment tonight,
you know, or some real, you know, real mainstream, achy type entertainment show, and it seems to be a
little more, you know, in the groove in the vibe, which the high fish show is completely all about.
All of a sudden, people start talking very differently, and you should really take a look at this,
and tell me if you don't think, uh, Jada Smith, uh, Will Smith's wife is, is kind of throwing a
little different attitude into the mix, which I'd like, because it seems like it's much more her,
much more real, but it was just something that, uh, that I really noticed. Um, you know, uh, I really
wanted to hook up Barry Barry is the guy who does, uh, cure him radio, radio, cure him, and, uh,
Barry, um, maintains a lot of the forums at castblaster.com and helps, uh, castblaster Mike out.
As you know, we're working on, uh, castblaster video, which is, um, that's going to be so cool.
You should check out, check out testing one two three dot pod show dot com testing one two three,
uh, and that's new world's one two three dot pod show dot com. That's, uh, castblaster Mike,
and I, I really, I think that what the guy is doing is fantastic. Um, he's really using his,
he's eating his own dog food as he's testing along. So he's putting himself on camera, uh,
while he's testing the application. Anyway, long story short, uh, that, uh, I really want to
hook Barry up and play his winter promo, uh, but Barry, dude, two minutes long. Hi, this is Barry
J and Jess from Radio QRM. Hey there. Well, it's that time of year again. The towns and villages
up here in New Hampshire are decorated to the hill with all sorts of colorful lights and inflatable holiday
decorations. We'd like to call this the Christmas season. Josh 11 o'clock. The Grinch by the front
porch is small. Heart won't be growing three sizes a day this year. When we're not out hunting
inflatable holiday decorations, Jess and I do a weekly podcast from the Menanda region of New Hampshire.
Josh frosty at two o'clock. No more birthdays for him. The show is a little home spun humor
reindeer at five o'clock Josh. One down seven to go, a little news. Josh, over there,
Snoopy by the Christmas tree. No more dancing in the backyard for him and a little fun with
life in New Hampshire. Josh up on the rooftop. Santa!
sin is going to be running a little late this year. Oh yeah, and we also feature great music
from the pod safe music network. So check us out at radioqrm.com or visit our pod show site at
radioqrm.podshow.com. Oh no. Is that an inflatable snow globe with the entire cast of
root off the red nose reindeer inside? Barry J. Hand me my hell of sir.
Radioqrm does not condone the destruction puncture or dismemberment of any decoration for
the Christmas season. No actual inflatable holiday decorations were destroyed during the making of this
promo. Well, maybe just one. If the use of the word Christmas offend you, grow a thicker skin.
Yeah nice Christmas spirit there guys. All right Los Angeles was in the Christmas spirit.
You know, it's always so weird to be roaming around a relatively warm climate and seeing all these
unbelievable Christmas displays. As we were right in Beverly Hills with no fucking internet.
The houses were just extraordinary. I'm kidding around about about LA, but there is definitely
some, there's a lot of people who are in California who are really dissolutioned
with what's going on in Hollywood and they are showing up and that's what's really cool.
I really, I really like the talent that's that's walking around there that just no longer fits in.
And I'm not talking about just, you know, people who never got a break. I'm talking about people who
have had many breaks and are just sick and tired of the whole process.
And there's a lot of people out there with big fuck you money who also just want to do something cool. So
that's the good news. But it's exactly the way I remembered it really is. Let me see if something
else was going to say about, hmm, crap, I can't remember. I'll tell you what, I'll go look at my
notes and you think about the spirit of Christmas.
What do all of a sudden? Hi. Hello. I'm the spirit of Christmas and I can give you everything you want.
What do you want for Christmas? I want everything you have. And you computer and you house?
One woman, two woman, three woman, everything. Well, I'm okay with that. But money?
How much? As much as you can, pal. Oh, a million? A million is that okay?
Ah, that's that will get me started. Okay, I need you to do something.
What would you like? Yeah, I need you to close your eyes, look deep into your heart and send all
your love to Adam Curry. He is a very greedy man. Yeah. Can you say I love Adam Curry? He needs you.
Okay, I love you Adam Curry. Adam Curry. I love Adam Curry. Thank you, buddy. Merry Christmas.
All right, thank you. So, uh, getting back last night. Uh, and we had a little delay because the
day was all fog-bid, day area. So, uh, I think we left about probably about an hour later than scheduled.
So, I got in around 10, 10, 30. You know, like, it's been very short nights, no more than five
hours each night, really, not kidding. So, maybe I can get six, you know, maybe even seven. So,
I mean, bed by 11, 15, 11, 30. And, you know, I've watched a little John Stewart turn that off and,
you know, I'm drifting away. It goes pretty quick with me and my phone rings.
Now, this is not a normal time for my phone ring. I did know, however, that Patricia was on her way to
Rotterdam once again for more rehearsals. And I think she's doing the first, uh, she's recording two
shows for Dancing With The Star. So, it'll be the first show. And she calls me from the airport.
She says, okay, I forgot all my medicine. They have to know as, uh, as someone who has a
minor cardiac issues, heart medicine is pretty important to take with you. And, uh, I could get it to
or, you know, by tomorrow, but that doesn't really work. So, the plane is about to leave in like,
you know, 25 minutes. Um, Christina is still fast asleep because, you know, it was a really early
morning flight and Patricia's like, what the hell am I going to do? And, you know, I'm kind of
out of this dead sleep and like, uh, it's like, okay, what are we going to do? So it's like an hour.
So trying to figure that out, getting cabs to pick up medicine, rescheduling flights. Um, and, uh,
so it was, uh, once again, a short night. But, uh, it was just like one of those things, man.
Whenever, you know, this is really why when I'm at home, I don't want the phone anywhere near me
in the bedroom. I don't want to be able to hear the phone when I'm sleeping because there's nothing
I can do for you anyway. I'm asleep. You know, people have phones next to their bed.
Now, I can understand maybe for security reasons. You might want to be able to call out in the middle
of the night. But, you know, I just do not want any phones name because this always happens.
And so last night, a prime example, of course, but I have my phone next to my bed
when I'm here because, you know, I want to keep, keep tabs on my girls, and I want them to be
able to reach me. And that's not the only disturbing phone call I got.
Okay, I don't know who this is or how you know to sell. But she's been gone now for four days.
So if he's there, or if he talked to her, tell her they're calling it right away.
That's pretty disturbing.
Is that the same? Let me just see if it's the same guy. Hold on a second. This is, uh,
I haven't over here. This is that guy when he was pissed off at,
and whoever he thought was calling to tell, let me listen to see if it's the same guy.
Hey, I don't know who this is, but stop fucking calling to sell, asshole.
Is that the same guy is this?
Okay, I don't know who this is.
I don't know. Hmm, that doesn't sound like the same guy, is it?
Hey, I don't know who this is, but
Hmm, or how you know to sell. Well, I maybe it is the same guy.
But she's been gone now for four days. So if he's there, or if he talked to her,
tell her they're calling it right away.
Look, I'm not going to do any more outreach on this one, my friends. This is really freaking me out.
Please, feast your ears on this.
I wouldn't mind a couple more new operas. I don't have anything
All I want is I just want one of those for my own, the start's with
the world, the world, the world, the world, the culture of the series.
Or something like that.
So as always, when I'm feeling a little bit blue, and I just don't know what to do, I reach down deeper.
Excuse me, since I always blend up. It really throws me off well.
I'm good at this, almost insulting.
Fuck me. I didn't work the way I wanted it to.
The opening of the show today was hooray for Hollywood by the Star Sisters.
That is one of Patricia's, the Lady Patricia's projects. A lot of you
called into the voicemail numbers. And I think what was it? Friday or something when I asked you
what this was? I'm just playing a little bit of it for you, okay?
Most of you got it, right? But you only got half of it, right?
And it wasn't date from 1969. Of course, that also is the Lady Patricia with the
Fisherman King, as many of you said.
Yes, indeed.
That's all. Yeah. What a lot of you don't know is that the band backing
her up there is none other than the world famous focus. And you probably got to be at
least born in the 60s. Before the 70s to even have an inkling of who
focus is or was young acrimon, some of you may recognize that name, focus known from
focus focus definitely a very tight world class band. And it was cool that the couple of you picked
up on that. I don't know, first time corner, I believe at least it's the DSC size tech.
I'm from Birmingham, England. Your logbooks, the form V5, she had to just describe the car,
you know, the CC, what kind of car is the engine number, stuff, etc.
Oh, I'm on there. Hope to see it. It's the big cool, the registration document as well.
It's the form which shows cool V5 at the top. It's usually a feet page dock opens out wide there.
Hope that helps. Bye-bye. Oh, uh, I think I'm a scruncher. Yeah, but I can't be asked.
Okay, then you probably are a scruncher.
So, you know, this is the, this is what I got to take care of when I get back.
Crap. Hey, those of you listening to us in serious satellite stars 102. The show's about to end
for you. So you're going to miss this awesome song, the Marcus couch sent to me from the scene
scene, which I'll play in just a couple of minutes. But there's a lot more cool stuff coming up for you guys.
So take care. I'm also looking for that song. I realized that I hadn't loaded it in. Oh, there it is.
I loaded it into into cast blaster. All right. So a lot of people, this is my registration
order. The license for my car and I live in the UK and they're asking for my log book.
And it turns out the log book is an old English phrase or that the haven't basically updated the
the forms to reflect what it really means. It's your registration is that you own the car.
So now I have to send my original insurance certificate. I have to send, well, I'm not supposed to
send. I'm not even supposed to have an MOT, which is a ministry of transportation like certificate
the car is roadworthy because it's new, you know, it's like a year old. It's a new car. So that's
kind of confusing. And then it's supposed to hand over my registration.
I don't know. It's the, you're busted, Jordi, Joseph, there's something in the, in a series of
minutes. And this isn't the thing I say. And it's just the main thing I forgot to remind you
of, do not, on any circumstances and you love to do to anybody. No matter how they are, never,
ever let that thing out you say. And you hand that door in the door, you've lost your car on the
mode basically person who then filled in that document then becomes the legal owner of it. You never,
ever, ever give it to anybody. So it will red tear off a little bit of the bottom, that's basically
the transfer of ownership and once that's gone, so as your car. Cheers, mate. Yeah, cheers, mate.
So is that officially a conundrum? Was that what it is? I think what it means is I can't just send
the shit via mail. I have to actually go to the some special post office. And what do you care?
And you just want to hear me bitch.
That's the number for everyone in the UK to call in. I think I've got it though.
I'll let you know how it goes when I get back next week and then take care of all that crap.
For those of you in the States, I've been honest, how often are you walking along and you
just start singing that tune to yourself plus one two one six two five six three five seven.
I've just wanted to tell everyone about it. So it's exciting. It doesn't mean it's just planned. I didn't
explain why I've got past it. We've just done, we are just done for my first video.
I'm going to have some fun. I don't want to have video format. We've got six kind of tasks.
It's video problems. We've been doing some virtual slam. I'm pretty excited about this.
And it depends as we've got this time. I'll pull back a ton of what's in parent, you want to
meet him, see the name, don't stray far and the studio is prepared. You can check out my videos
and post what's on the slam either website. So go to there and now it's a slam. I don't
know how often it's been interesting to talk about. I have a slam either post or talk from
and I have one of the URL of the URL. What do you think of this video in text video and post what's
there? I think so. Well, I like it. Obviously. If you've never listened to the slam idle podcast,
you definitely should. And so now also with video. I think though Simon, you might want to choose
a little different background. Because you sent me this in video as well. You know, standing in front
like the door, I'd look kind of doorky. So choose your background carefully, my friend.
What's up, you guys? This is Evan from Cage 9 and you're listening to The Daily Source Code.
Frozen in my face beside this entire place. She's got to make she's got to make
she's got to make what she's right on time. Why? Because it's all in this time.
And she's feeling that she's so close in my eyes. But that's not too late. I'll get some deep
blades. And there's a way, a way, a way, a way for her to fly.
A last blow to buy.
She's got your friends, but you can't be sure.
Because they're singing songs she's never had before. She's a dead piece, she's not dead.
And I think she's afraid I'm afraid to be rich enough. Why? Because it's all in pain.
And she's jealous. And I think it's a way, a way, a way for her to try.
But that's all too late. I'll get some deep blades. But that's a way, a way, a way for her to fly.
A last blow to buy. And I think she's running out for her to run fast.
And I think she's jealous. And I think it's a way, a way, a way for her to fly.
And I think it's a way, a way for her to fly.
And I think it's a way, a way, a way for her to fly.
Crash. Ah, sorry.
Cage 9. Now, that's the title of the talk.
That's a Friday show.
Please, pilot error disregard.
Yeah, Marcus Couch is bringing these guys on the pod safe music network.
Cage 9 lasts a lot of buys what you heard.
And Friday will play another track that will be up on the PMN.
Very cool.
I know that Marcus has been playing these guys.
So, I'll support it.
Shipman, I'll support anything pod safe.
Really, I will.
And I also support English Blokes calling up drunk.
I had a misparky.
It's a...
Oh, yeah.
I'll say.
And I'm completely salted.
I've had a...
...absorbing marvelous afternoon, Tokyo.
We've, uh...
We met at the, uh, the greats in, uh...
Chef of Marcus, which is, quite in the race in, in the West End.
And then, uh, we went on for Matt as the, uh, brutal blow, which is, uh,
uh, since the white sausage.
Now, bear in mind that this is like a Friday night.
And the only thing, Parkie has...
I guess he has nothing better to do than to call me, call the voicemail, when he's drunk.
And then we had a marvellous afternoon, food and drink, and then we went on for a mess.
So I warned you about this phone call, and I'm absolutely, absolutely, also, B.B.
So this is Friday evening, and that's the rest of Friday evening, I'm absolutely slaughtered.
So how to show me nice whenever you get this, because I'm absolutely bugged.
Take care, bye-bye.
It's very interesting. Usually around Friday night, I usually get about, you know,
three or four calls like this, of guys just completely hammered, and they're all from the UK.
And they start, and you may be, it's because they can't help, but, you know, when you're drunk,
you start singing songs, and maybe they can't help, but sing along with this tune.
Plus four four, two, seven, six, eight, one, three, seven, nine, three, plus four, four, two, seven, six, eight, one, three, seven, five, three.
All right, I got to get out of here. I'm still some, some chock-full days at, uh, at Potio HQ today.
And, uh, I should give you a real proper update of what's going on. Okay, let's
so tomorrow I won't do any, and I won't do a whole bunch of promo and feedback and crap like that.
I'll just tell you exactly what's happening with Potio, and what we're up to. I got, I got to really
make a list, so I can remember it all. So if you're interested, join me then. Otherwise, of course,
Friday will be back with the Fubar Friday festivities to get your music in for that as well.
Adam and Potio.com, send me some email, or check out anything you want to know about the show at
the show site, dating source code.com. Take care, everybody. Have a great Wednesday.
Another Potio Potcast. Stick it in your ear.