Find this podcast and others like it at the number one new media network,
paucho.com.
Better faster, stronger, stronger.
And now with new minty fresh scent.
Hey, this is Carmen Tyler.
And you're listening to the 500th episode of the daily source code,
and the real pod fodder Adam Curry.
We're 500 podcasts under my ass.
In the next generation, social media network in my ears.
Delta Sierra Charlie.
5-0-0.
This is the worst moment of my entire life.
It's a daily source code at the floor 500,
it's a daily source code at the floor 500.
With your dinging and your list up hot fodder Adam Curry,
with your dinging and your list up hot fodder Adam Curry.
It's a daily source code at the floor 500,
it is the daily source code at the floor 500.
Congratulations on achieving this amazing people podcasting and for the brand new Hot Show Blossom.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation
radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Hello, Curie.
Thank you for being a friend.
Travel down a road and back again.
Your heart is true.
You're a pal and a confidence.
I'm not ashamed to see.
I hope it always was day to sway.
My head is off.
We'll just stand up and take a bow.
And if you're through a party invited everyone you knew,
you wouldn't see the biggest gift would be for me.
And the card attached would say thank you for being a friend.
Thank you for being a friend.
If it's a car you lack,
I'd surely buy you a catalog.
Whatever you need in a time of the day or night.
I'm not ashamed to say.
I hope it always was day to sway.
My head is off.
We'll just stand up and take a bow.
And when we broke it all out,
with walking keys and hair away,
I've got fear even though it's hard to hear.
I will stand with those and save.
Thank you for being a friend.
I hope it's a thank you.
Let me tell you about it.
Thank you for being a friend.
I hope it's a thank you.
I hope it's a thank you for being a friend.
That's right.
Might as well start to show off with it.
With the thanks.
Thank you for making 500 episodes possible.
500 episodes possible without doubt it would be nowhere near that amount everybody how you
doing this is daily source code Delta Sierra Charlie episode 500 coming to you from the
Curry condo in a very misty northern California San Francisco to be exact good to have
you all long for for this 500th episode I haven't done a tremendous amount of preparation
I don't think I really ever do a lot of preparation for you know those round numbers
We've had some interesting ones episode 200 of course was at
Nome decks in Seattle that was just coincidence. I could have actually done episode 500 yesterday
Or I'm sorry the day before I'm messed up already. It is now Monday. It's very early in the morning
As you know, I'm on my San Francisco schedule, which is a healthy 5 a.m. wake-up call and a diet of caffeine, aspirin, and maroine
And I'm feeling just fine. It was Saturday with the podcast con UK
About 180 200 people in in London
got together and
Had a an independently organized conference regarding podcasting a lot of the I would say almost typical discussions
Conversations which regardless of outcome if any
It's always good for people to get together and get those neurotransmitters
Bob and off each other
Anyway, so I could have done episode 500 there, but I definitely didn't feel that was that was appropriate
So so first time from from San Francisco
For the for the next 500 and really and I said this at podcast con UK is I was asked to introduce the shakes
Who perform live fantastic fantastic performance
Everything fucked up everything went wrong, but because they were just so funny about it
It really really worked and of course once things were cranked and they were slamming
And I actually said that I realized that those 500 episodes the majority of those certainly not all
But the majority have been created in the United Kingdom and I thanked everybody there who would
Sent in comments intros openings pod safe music and and as I was sitting down watching the shakes
I'm thinking fuck I forgot to say something else
There was one other thing I wanted to say particularly to that audience is I wanted to thank everyone there
For making myself and my family feeling so welcome in the United Kingdom
There's been every single time we had a question or or you know a yanks versus the Brits moment or just something like whoa
What the hell is going on here?
The it was literally yes listeners, but a lot of the podcast community in the UK who chimed in sent me audio comments and have helped us
Learn more about the country we live in which we're enjoying to the extreme amount I have to say
Um
So of course if you want to know about podcast con UK all you have to do is just to troll the voicemail lines and there's our trusty
Yeah buddy Paul Nichols
Adam heights for Nichols here
Just driving home after the podcast conference and
I've just got so many things buzzing around my head up just to adjust the program and it was a couple of podcasts
The bands were fantastic the guys on the panel were fantastic
Thanks for coming thanks ever such a lot of again for helping to sponsor the
The podcast conference it really was a great success and I'm really looking forward to the next year
And what a great was and you don't see me chatman just
Such a good like
One great photographer is why we chat just like a side
Well lovely like
See you soon mate, but it's indeed a lovely blow. Yeah, we had a good time and afterwards we all went to the pub and hung out
I think it's a longer time of actually hung out in a pub and I enjoyed it very much
Particularly because I was able to have a a true traditional bitter
And not shows. Oh, man, that's a young spritz thing right there
So as Andrew Gold's said at the opening of the show, thank every single one of you for being a friend. It is truly appreciated
Independently produced audio entertainment audio entertainment
The internet is not something that you just dump something on it. All right, you just drag them
Curious I love the run is
Who cares if you're stumbling above
Oh, yeah, there's more where that came from coming to you from courty cottage
We caught it we caught it courty cottage
Wow, that was awesome. This is the daily source code everybody how you doing
Episode 500 love it with all the stuff you guys are putting together as fantastic
Even the
Even the artwork for today's show is extremely appropriate
I think if I say anything I need to talk about that happened over the week and of course some day morning
I left bright and early
Virgin Vs 19 to San Francisco
You know same old the same flight same chair actually I always get 12k
I love sitting on the right-hand side of the aircraft for some reason
Wasn't very full the flight and I wasn't at all that tired so it just you know
I still maybe an hour or so so by the time I went to bed last night around
Oh man, it was like a 10 30 or something like that
PST time I was tired. I was pretty ripped
I saw the queen movie the queen on
On the in flight entertainment system which truly is a fantastic
Selection date refresh it every single month at the beginning of the month
I was a pretty fun movie learn a little bit about about the monarchy and I think now I understand
Of course not having gone through the
Gone through the events of princess Diana's death in the UK. I can understand now where a lot of this hatred
Towards the royal family is coming from
Just very interesting and another great great history lesson
So even though we've got
Oh man, I have so much stuff to play
It's gonna be probably a little bit longer show today and again
I didn't produce or prepare anything. I just basically collected all the stuff you guys was sending in
I'm just talking all the bits uh putting them all together. However
There was something that I'd asked Andrew Grummet to do
Well actually he came up with it himself
Remember we had this problem with juice which is the pod catcher formerly known as lemon iPod or lemon
um
With the new uh with the pod show plus upgrade version 2.0
A lot of users of juice all of a sudden found themselves downloading
a whole bunch of pod show
Podcasts again
Which of course is not desired behavior and
Well now we're fortunate enough to have Andrew Grummet
One of the lead developers on both those prod well on iPod or lemon iPod or iPod or lemon and juice
To be working with us here at pod show and
And so I said you do what happened there how do how do we do that and and you said you know what?
I'm gonna dress this and I'm gonna do a DSC style with an audio comment
plus one two
Is this thing on oh
Hi there Adam. No hold on a second Andrew
Man why are you uh why are you in mono? How is that?
Ah
So of course, I don't have my uh the right mixing board here
I the hell is that a mono?
Oh that sucks so bad
um
I have no way to fix that right now
Shit
You know what it's so good
Oh I feel horrible now all I was like I have this uh this different mixer here
Uh at the at the condo. I don't think I can make it into a stereo fuck I just listen in mono
Andrew Grummet here um
I uh I'm sending you this comment to respond to Paul Smith's question about
Pod show shows read downloading in his juice receiver
Well uh I'll have to take the heat for this one and I'll explain why
Have to warn you though. I had to dig around in the juice code quite a bit to get the sensor and it's gonna be a serious
10-foil hat moment so oh hold on a second hold on a second if it's a 10-foil
Oh
Pod casts are syndicated through RSS as many of you know RSS of course really simple syndication feeds
And just about all software programs that read RSS have a basic decision to make as they examine the contents of the feed
Have I seen this item before if I haven't it's time to download the pod cast
If I have seen the item before no further action is needed
So in the early days of pod casting we use the media URL
HTTP colon something something something slash podcast.mp3
We use that URL to determine if an item had been seen for
As pod casting evolved and people started changing hosts and domain names
We switched to using the RSS gooid element which if preserved when the pod cast changed domains would still be seen by the pod cast receiver as
quote unquote the same item and
That way a person could move their their pod cast from one place to another without causing redown loads
So once we had a good support to juice if you came clear that we could support even more obscure edge cases
We had a handful of people who at some point wanted to start reusing the same media URL
Something like you know food.com slash latest.mp3
I wanted to use that same URL over and over again for their pod cast
So in the old days juice would simply download the first version of that file and seeing that the URL
Was the same
Would stop there and then and none of the further pod cast would be downloaded
But if the pod cast changed their good each time that was enough to tell juice to read download
Even though the same URL was used
Okay, so coming back to pod show plus
When we launched v1 back in July we forgot to put in the gooid element
We finally added that element just before the v2 launch. Oh, sorry just after the v2 launch
So what happened was that juice saw the change in the gooid it changed of course from nothing to something
It saw that as a directive to read download even though it had seen the URLs before
So bottom line atoms right something did change in the feed
There is a much we can do it easily at this point since for most of folks the the you know download
Saturation is now in the past and in any case the problem will have cleared itself
After the read download so if you managed to catch things on time
Just go through your subscriptions and mark any pod cast episodes that you've already seen before as skipped
You can do this and juice by using the down arrow in the space bar quickly alternating
After clicking in the episodes area for the pod cast
So in some my apologies to folks for the bandwidth squeeze
You may now return to your regular porn downloading schedule
Yo
I was thinking of all kinds of appropriate punishments for Andrew
for doing that and I was thinking maybe we should make him suck a gallon of beer through a straw kind of
Emulate that bandwidth issue everyone's had
But now I just think and hey man if you just make your shit and stereo that'll be good enough
Hey there Adam Howard Greenstein here and I just wanted to wish you congratulations on your 500th episode of the Charlie
Usually I'm one to send you funny bits like I did for DSC 400, but you know this weekend
I had to spend some quality time with the family and it really was wonderful to be able to do that
So it didn't happen enough of time to create something really amazing, but stay tuned to have something in the works
And it will be a lot of fun and we'll show up as the intro to a Charlie in the very near future
I hope so
For me and my family to you and yours
Happy Thanksgiving
Congratulations on the new place and congratulations on 500 shows and
When you get a chance add me to your playlist. It's a chat and a song over there at Pod Show and
You know, it's just a small thing. I do for my friends a little chat and a song
Perfect podcast anyway Adam congratulations on 500 and take care
All right, I would thank you very much buddy
Thank thanks to all of you for calling in and leaving all these nice messages on our phone lines
Of course, we have two of them one in the U.S. and one in the U.K. and
Don't forget you need to put a plus before each number if you're dialing it from your cell phone
I've figured out that I can't play those to the the U.S. and the U.K. voicemails
After each other because whichever one is last is the one that sticks in your head and so we've got to really promote
You get number a little bit better
So I'm here for the Thanksgiving week and of course work work continues here. I have no idea in a of the
First of all first thing I'm gonna do this morning when I get in as I'm going to
Sit and meet I think at least ten people who have not met yet who have joined since the last time I was here
Which was only a month ago
And of course I'm going back
for a quick week at home and then I'm coming back for another ten or fourteen days just before the holiday
Celebrations and of course second week of January we are moving house
So I've got a lot of stuff to do back in the U.K
And so you know, I figured I'm sure that there will be some lost souls here
It's always that way
You know during the holiday is always someone who doesn't have a place to go to or the plan wasn't
Go to go visit their family this year and so I'm hoping that I can pull a bunch of people together
And we can go out somewhere and we can have a nice Thanksgiving dinner
And you know of course that this this girl from San Diego Giselle has been calling up with some really
Sexual stuff she sent me a picture by the way as I asked her to and
I could get in so much trouble
She's very cute and she's then what she sent along with the picture of the thing she said
I can't even be repeated on not even on this show and
So you know what what's kind of like and I just I
Thought it was a joke honestly when she first started off
And now I'm starting to get a little bit worried
Particularly when I heard
This call come into the voicemail line
Hey, I don't know who this is but stop fucking calling Giselle at home
Oh
That so here's what I what I think happened is she's been calling this this number and her boyfriend
Either saw the numbers dot well obviously I didn't call her
But he probably saw that number is dialed or received or thought it was received on her phone and called
Because she does call in quite a bit
That guy sounds really fucking pissed off listen again
Is now they at home
Oh man
And he sounds like seven feet tall like and beat me to a pulp
I think I'm gonna hang back on this one. Hi Adam. It's Phil from Cornwall just to let you know
Had a listen to the latest tweet
77 and it's titled as to you mate the
We're referring to you from
55 minutes 41 seconds and for Twitter. I think it's fairly
favorable
a piece
And not that you need the
Family whatever but
There you are
Will Harris from slash.net was there and mentioned he saw you so
If you're in a mood John's more like for the show so you'll probably will download it anyway
Just thought you'd like to know
Here's my tellings folder. Bye
Yeah, thanks for the heads up. I got uh now I do listen to uh to Twitter
And as you just referred to I wonder how they knew that
Usually I only listen when when I see in the show notes the chondavor acts gonna be on
Because it is a long show and I have you know even I have to
Select as to you know when I'm gonna listen to but I've gotten a lot of people saying that there's something on the show that I need to listen to
Hello Mr. Craig. It's a listener from Canada
Who unfortunately I didn't have the chance to listen to your show for the past months
But don't worry. I listen to you all summer can't be motivated during long work days
I just listen to Twitch. Would you say you listen to if John C. Devore Act is a member and I will admit
Yes, I sometimes do that myself
Well, it just maybe bumps on my priority list
But I think you should take them off on it because
On their deal
Because I think it would be really interesting just here your side of the whole story
Well, not your side of story, but we're in pain
That's a little interesting, but I do I do agree with some of you
Oh, okay, I get it. Ah, yeah, some guy it's podcast con UK interviewed me and he
He's a sometime he does a sometime appearance on on Twitter. Oh, okay, so what they were ragging on my
My sweater and they have some kind of bet. All right. I will listen
I'll have to find out what the Twitter boys are up to folks on serious satellite
If you want to hear the rest of this podcast, you're going to have to go to daily source code dot com
Because it's just outlasting the satellite window. I'm so sorry
Pretty good
Pretty good thought here. Hey, Adam. This is more cramsy in Austin, Texas and to simplify things
Why not just call it
D-S-C-D
Yeah, for yeah for for for Roman numeral
500 is that it I guess the D
I don't know. I mean for those of you who are wondering why these are numbered
It's something we figured out a long time ago. It's so much easier for people on the go to just
Hit the play button and know right from the get go if it's a show they've heard or have not heard
And these is way to do that is obviously by by numbering it and people do it kind of seem to remember that
And as mainly done for the nano users who had no display
But also for lots of other mobile devices that just you know don't display
Thing this show note to the title in in a fashion that you know that you could probably do on the go if you're driving et cetera
So I will just keep on going 502 501 by by tomorrow and I want to wind up today's celebratory episode with song from
Actually it is these song. I have to say that really got my juices flowing
Two years ago over two years ago
When we well I guess when we started numbering the shows
It was all talk back in the time
I think that we smartly had all kind of figured out hey wait a minute. Maybe we we should not be playing any music because
This music licensing thing is is very complicated. This is before the pod set music network as well
The music licensing is complicated and we got something really interesting going here
Why don't we just stay away from playing music all together because the last thing we needed
Over two and a half years ago is to have you know the RIA brand podcasting as some type of
elicit pirate activity and and so that's literally what it was there were very there were still little equies
Remember that we used to talk about it's the who was it who said that's still the liquid
Podcasting is nothing more than solid liquids which of course is partially true, but it's become so much more
But I do recall bumping into a band online who had their there's their songs online
Available for I think was a preview listen or whatever or no. I had one song you could actually download and they were selling
There's CDs on CD baby completely independent four girls from New York and I really really thought the song that I had found which is for off of their CD was so appropriate
In so many twisted ways is to what was happening with with this thing that at the time wasn't even called podcast
podcasting we didn't really have a name for it
That I you know, I sent the singer of the band and email and said hey, would you mind if I if I played this song?
Oh my I'll my show over here and I send you I'll give an example
She said yeah absolutely knock yourself out and so I put a link back to to their site and where they sell their CD
And as I said I you know iTunes even and no, I'm sorry not I would they selling it on iTunes
I think they might have had it on iTunes at that point
but definitely a CD baby and
And and I played it and then a couple other people who were experimenting along with us in those early days played it and then a few weeks later
I got and email back that said hey, you know, we're actually
selling CDs because of this and that's when I got that's really
When when Ron and I started to work on the pod save music network, you know, how can we make that I mean obviously it's working
There's there's I can now legally use content to fill up my show which I love doing it's it's you know to me
It's the same as
Someone's sending an audio comment. It's you know, it's someone's passion their art their their soul
And you know, they want to get credited for it and and if possible, they you know, they have a business model
They want to make some money so we came up with the idea for the pod save music license
And so really was in those early days this song that band that got my juices flowing and they have not stopped
In fact, they're they're pumping quite quite fast at this very moment
Of course, I'm talking about the listidious bitis and I want to be famous
That girl I want to be famous
He got it's art is how parties that's spy
I want to be famous go to Paris on private flights
I want to have lovers by the score
Movie producers knocking down on my door
This is the fate that is in store
For me
When I'm famous, I will wear the great trench coat and fake red hair
So they all will know that it is me
When they see me how they'll smile and me photo grass to sign
I will say sorry babe talk to my assistant
I want to be famous
Tabloids will bring what I eat
I want to be famous who I do will be news on the street
Then when I'm old, I'll have a ball
Then be shocked that I'm living at home
When I enter the gas will fall to the knees
And then I'll snap the throats on my head of peace
But all I don't want one in cheese when I'm famous
Spameless, famous, famous
So exhausting
I want to be famous
La La La La La la!
La la.
Wow, I will be a Marby dog
If you fished head and have said
Oh
And I hate the attitude
And oh, whoa, whoa!
Everybody, I won't get high on
I don't get high on colored pills, Martini's dry
A little way and just a touch
I wanna be my famous better than all of my fellow much better than all of her
I wanna be famous slowly and alone at the end
I'll end up bitter and ugly and old
Not just my body, but also my soul
But a legend is my goal and a legend of being
When I'm famous, not only I'll give for the little people
I don't have kids when I'm famous
Hey, my famous famous, bye-bye-bye
From New York City, the Sylvia's Bitties, and famous
You see how music really is the soundtrack to our lives
Or I used to be radio and convinced it's things like podcasting
Because it really took me back in time to those days in the curry castle
And, you know, just north of Antwerp
And, and was just playing the song over and over again
And it was, it really, it was so funny and it still
It fits in in so many ways
I think you know what I mean
Anyway, you know, we're working, we've been working the past week on
A big pitch for a very large advertiser
We have a pretty, I think a pretty cool idea for them
And it's a video pitch and so a lot of
We ask a lot of people to help out
Because this would be a big network wide thing
And, and obviously it kind of shows an overview of a pod show
But also podcasting in general is that you're just what is out there
And when you look at it at all the different shows and all the different
Creative talent it's just we've done that we've accomplished so much
In a relatively short amount of time
That it really gave me chills just keep watching this thing over
I'm like wow, you know, I forget the pitch part
I'm just like, look at all the stuff that's been created
And look at how rich our lives have become
Because of what all all these creative people have have tasked themselves to do
And, you know, I certainly still feel as my mission to enable as many people to do that as possible
So thank you all very much
This is it for episode 500
Tomorrow
We'll do 501
Another pod show pod cast
Stick it in your ear
Get this pod cast and more great ones like it
On the high performance pod cast delivery network from pod show and lime light networks