Delta Sierra Charlie 3-4-3
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do. Where are flink?
We believe in an internet that safe from viruses and scammers.
We're Earthlink.
We believe your personal information should be just that, personal.
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe.
Where are flink?
Make the smart choice, visit earthlink.net
and discover what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
60 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Fantastic. It's Adam Curry.
And it's Tuesday, every month,
coming to you from the M4 hotel in Amsterdam and Netherlands.
It's the Charlie on the road.
A bit of skimming, perhaps.
Screaming like a stone.
Over the surface, a floor I know.
I smooth rock that my home got has thrown.
And I'm just looking for my home.
I'm just looking for my home.
Back to the wall, back to the wall, back to the wall.
Into the corner, into the corner.
Screaming like a stone.
Many miles traveled here.
Many, many more love to go.
And I am not afraid of the things I've found.
No, no.
And I won't be afraid.
The fire starts flowing down.
And I'm just going to the wall, back to the wall, back to the wall.
Into the corner, into the corner.
Into the corner.
And into the corner.
And the war fought through the road now into the crew
Great
Skimming like a stone
Over the circumstance, the war I know
Of the truth, the rock that my home got has thrown
And I'm just looking for my home
And I'm just watching
And I'm just coming
And I'm just looking for my home
My carico, and skim in kicking off Tuesday's edition of the Daily Source Code, everybody
how you doing, coming to you from the Amstall Hotel and Amsterdam, the Netherlands, that
will of course account for the difference in the sound.
I think I sound a little bit nasal.
What I've done is I've hooked up the Portage A laptop with a running cast blaster.
All I've hooked up externally, of course, our headphones, which I'm monitoring the signal on,
and I've got my wireless live set up.
You'd love this actually.
I like traveling with this live microphone because it's so incredibly small yet.
I find the sound to be better than most small microphones.
And I really, you know, if you want to have a carry on and you want to fly with
easy jet and you want to take two laptops and a change of clothes, your court clothes, no
less, you really got to slim it down in size.
So, no big mics with me on the road today.
I've got the love clip on to an avion bottle actually.
Here we are.
Today is the day of the big trial.
It is me against the publisher of this gossip magazine that took pictures from my flicker
site and published them across three pages of a spread in their magazine.
There's some other things that go along with this lawsuit, for instance, the publication
of my daughter's school and how she is taken to school and picked up every single day.
Of course, just the whole idea that some, um, editor, some chief editor gave some, some
greasy guy with a camera, you know, gave him the assignment to go follow my daughter
freaking creeps me out.
So that's what we'll be talking about in court today.
That's a 230.
It's still relatively early.
It would be none of you in the UK.
So 10am here and I got the show all set up for you.
So we're talking a little bit about the suit today, a couple of things I want to run through
and you know what?
It's so cool to be in Amsterdam.
First of all, it's really, really, really, really cold.
Got up this morning and it was snowing and they're expecting winds of up to 30 to 35 knots.
So it's going to be cold, windy and snowy and the room is, I can barely even heat the
room up.
And this is such a great hotel.
I got to tell you, it's, I've been here with three or four times in a row now in just a couple
months and, and no wonder when royalty comes to the Netherlands or when the stones come
to play, they all stay at the Ansel Hotel.
These guys definitely do get, you know what, let me, let's order some coffee here, hold on
a second.
Let me see if I can do this room service.
I definitely need to be caffeinated.
Let's see.
There we go.
Good morning.
This is not a room service.
I'm out here.
Good morning.
Could you send up a pot of coffee for me, please?
I've got a share with you.
Room number 414.
Yeah, you wouldn't happen to have senseo coffee, would you?
No, I'll just a pot of coffee will be good.
Okay.
All right.
Thank you.
Well, we'll have to change that.
No, won't we?
No, we just have Nescafé.
What does that mean?
So last night, I'm like, I'm sitting here.
And of course, when you're an Amsterdam, you know, there's certain things that I like
to sample.
It's a very particular to the culture and to the commerce of the city, but it was so
called, and so I called my buddy, taxi, Eric, I said, you got to hook me up.
Now, of course, global chillages, global chillages, the name of the coffee shop, where I usually
get my medicine from, which used to be right near the bunker in Amsterdam.
Remember those days, so the how cool is this?
So I said to Eric, I said dude, it's too cold, I'm not, I don't want to go outside.
He says, no worries, and so he sent one of his cab driver buddies who was in the neighborhood
of the global chillage facility, they go pick up a little order.
And it's funny because the order was pretty specific, and the first thing they said in
the coffee shop was, oh, it was Adam back in town, hey, tell them to stop by one of these
days.
Okay, moving on, oh, you know, I forgot to say on yesterday's show, what an incredibly
cool time I had on Friday in San Francisco, every Friday we have the Fubar Friday at
Pod Show, which means probably run four o'clock, sometimes a little bit later, usually
not much earlier than that, in fact, we probably, we usually have to drag one or two folks
away from their computers.
We just stop, you know, when we have the Fubar Friday consists of, well, always consists
of alcohol and food, and sometimes it's at the office, we've had some pod save bands
show up to play, sometimes we present to each other what we're doing.
But as I said, it's usually food and alcohol, and this past Friday, we did it across
the street at 21st Amendment, which is this great bar, which is just right next to the
Pod Show headquarters.
And Adam drew it and invited a small intimate list of friends and fans, so it was about 40 or
50 people in addition to the 30 people that we are at Pod Show, and it was fantastic.
I met so many incredibly amazing people, some who had traveled great distance just to
come up to the, to the Don and Drew Hangout, it was, it was absolutely amazing, it was
great meet and all you guys, a couple of podcasters there as well, and they're starting
to send me emails and promos and just shows I've never ever heard of before.
So just wanted to say that that was a, you know, it really was a lot of fun.
And kind of a, like, I can't, hold on a second, we just check and see how my microphone
is still in here.
Okay, we're good.
I'm battery power.
Oops, almost knocked over the microphone stand.
The Avion Battel, interesting and exciting news as it looks like we're going to be opening
up.
Well, office, you know, I'm sure there'll be an official announcement about this at some
point, and an office is not the right word, but we're opening a pod show LA, or maybe
I should say we're opening up a shack and Venice Beach, which will be primarily occupied
by Mark Yoshermode or Nemcoff.
You've probably heard of, heard me talk about him.
He does the podcast specific coasts the hell way.
And, you know, we're going to be doing something which I think is exciting, and certainly
in the podcast arena is different, we're actually going to think up stuff, think up shows,
think up ideas, and produce them, and produce them with, well, I would have to say, you
know, independent talent.
Yeah.
And of course, in Los Angeles, there's a lot of independent talent out there that's waiting
on tables.
So we're looking at a drama series, which actually is written, and I've seen the backstory
and heard the characters, and it's just, you know, it's phenomenally exciting that we're
going to be doing that.
They'll give some other things in the works, there's some video stuff that we'll be working
on.
And all this is, you know, super, super low budget, I mean, just listen to Pacific Coast
hell way.
I mean, it's got a three series for Cry 6.
Game show, I think we're working on, and what does it, there was another, I can't remember.
Anyway, so, you know, I'll be letting you know more about that as time goes on as weeks
progress, and as we have stuff to show and tell, but I'm really excited about new productions
coming on to the scene, and this also means that there's going to be more opportunities
for voice talent, for production talent, for writers, my gosh, writers, so hard to come
by.
In fact, just in general, it's hard to really hire great people, an email showed up, what
is it?
Let me see if I have it here, an email showed up today, an internal pod show memo.
Let me just share this with you, Kevin and Sue, are reviewing applications for three new
positions at pod show.
We're looking for software engineers who specialize in PHP, Java, C, and email.
Do you specialize?
I think email applications is probably what that means.
If you know someone with these skills, who may be interested in working with us, please let
me or Brian know and check this out, if pod show hires an engineer who comes to the company
specifically through your referral, you'll be eligible for, oh my gosh, $1,000 hiring
bonus?
Wow, dudes, let's, hey, I want $1,000 bucks, come on, come on, work for pod show, we'll split
the $1,000 bucks, okay, I promise you, so that just goes to show how hard it is, everyone
is like working at Google, man, holy moly, it's unbelievable, those guys are hiring like
300 people a week, if you want any type of engineering down, you're either going to get
a very different type of engineer, which, by the way, we have, and I'm very, very happy
at all the, all the talent that we have within the company, but you're not going to get
you're classically trained engineer, and that's for sure, I'm quite honest, for some
reason, Ron and I don't seem to attract a type of person.
Hello, Adam, it's me, Matt, I'm going to make it quick, because I've got to go to the
arrow, where to drop me, Hermana off, I'm speaking a little bit of Spanish, because it
was in Miami too long, I'm going to make it snatchy, snappy, I need help, my Gmail is
at 100% and it's bouncing email, it's said when I signed up for the Gmail that I'll
never have to delete another email, I don't overuse it or abuse the Gmail, I've had it
for over a year and then it fills up, I've been increasing in requirements of space and
a very, very, very standard rate and it's bullshit, so I need more space, and I announced
it on my show, but I don't think the Google's listened to my show, but they do listen
to your show, I need my space, why don't they just change it so they figure out how
much space you use, you know, you're a delta and why don't they just let you just go up
a little bit more than that delta every day? Why can't they live up? They said you never
have to delete another email instead of giving me more space than they put a fucking delete
key on my goddamn Gmail account, that's bullshit and they're lying and so much for
do know we've a okay, I mean I can get over the China thing, I'm not Chinese, you know,
in America, you're not censoring fine, you're not Chinese, I like Chinese food, but
this I'm not even complaining about the censorship or whatever, but listen, I need space
for my goddamn Gmail for my bloated lesbian account, I am not going to give people a
different email to mail me because Gmail lies about how much space I have and I'm
just please fix it for me, oh god damn, I've already talked for two fucking minutes,
god damn Google. Oh yeah, match is back and it's pissed and bloated as ever. Good point,
match, you know when I really think about the the offering that Gmail makes, I have to
agree, they do really make it come across as if you'll never have to delete another email
again and that your account grows with you. Now I got this 4 gig a 4 gig account, which
is my special little when you call it, my little geeky hero of the nerds gift, but that
hasn't grown, in fact I've been deleting email for the past month or so, I've been constantly
hovering around 98%. I don't know what to say, I guess I could go back to my channels one
more time. At the end of the day, I'm willing to pay for this stuff. I love this service
so much. Honestly, it pisses me off too. Maybe with a new offering, the corporate Gmail,
maybe we'll be able to purchase space at some kind of unlimited amounts. So I'll look
into that for you, and then we'll just get a pod show account and we'll be able to give
you unlimited space. I hope, I mean, it's almost, you know, a Google really, first of
all, it's not do no evil. That's incorrect. It's don't be evil. I see this misreported
all the time in every thing in the New York Times, in Newsweek, in Time, all over the internet,
Google never said do no evil. They said don't be evil. There is a subtle difference there.
They are like crack dealers. They give you this shit. And, you know, it's like, hey,
come on, I'm going to send you an invite, special party, come on, don't you want to be cool?
Like all the other kids and try some of this. And so you start smoking the Gmail crack.
And then you're really getting to the shortcuts and you get into the labels and the fact
that you don't have to delete a single solitary email. And then just near the very end,
all of a sudden, it's like, oh, you know, we're not there. Maybe we'll drip a couple more,
just a couple more grams of the good stuff to you as you start to near your limit. But I agree,
magic, you get one MP3 in the email and boof. That's why I continuously ask, please stick your
MP3s up on a server and don't just email them to me. I'd much rather say email them to me.
And I'll pay for it. I will pay for that Google. Magic, I'm going to bat for you. I'm going
to go look for it. By the way, just regarding email in general, I've noticed that I've become this
neurological filter for looking at my email. If you want to get through to me, first of all,
don't expect the days of, hey, I just went through my entire inbox and I feel really good that I
clean it out. Forget about it. I currently have 21,441 unread emails. That's not to say that I haven't
seen the emails. Now, this is an important point. And just in general for your email etiquette,
I think the, you know, the important things that you should be doing if you want to get your message
across, you know, obviously something that I think everyone starts looking at in their inbox.
I'm looking at my inbox right now is, is the from. Okay. So who's it from?
And I'm just looking at the list in Gmail. So who it's from is going to make a difference. Of course,
I can set up, you know, all kinds of, and I've done this before. I set up labels and filters. And then,
you know, basically you wake up one morning and see your company label has, you know, like 35 emails.
Like Christ, man. So it just becomes as burden. And I'd rather kind of had the serendipity of,
I hope I catch it all. And if not, so I want to resend it, it appears at the top of the list.
So the next thing I look at is the subject line. Okay. Subject line is really, really important.
And in Gmail, actually, the first, I'm going to say the first 10 to 15 words of the first line
of the email actually show up kind of grayed out, but they show up as a preview on each individual
lines. You've got the sender. You've got the subject and then you've got the first couple of words
of the usually the first sentence, almost the first sentence. Despite if you hit a character turn.
So it's like here, what I get Todd from ID3 podcast mags. ID3 podcast mags. See, this is no good,
because he used the, his from and subject are basically the same. Hi, Adam. I wanted to write
and introduce myself, my name is Todd. Okay. Oops, hold on one second. That's the coffee.
Don't go away.
Okay. Right. Sorry about that. I will get to the cafe in just a second. So anyway, just in general,
we should be looking at our email etiquette and take a look at Gmail. I think it's, I think that's
pretty good. You know, within those three pieces of information. And in addition to that,
Gmail also gives you a little, what is a little indicator if the email is sent to you on the
two line or as a CC, which is also important. And that's really, you know, that's, you got to
market this stuff. And even if it's, if it's a purely business, you've got to just know what,
I mean, eventually we're all going to wind up in some version of the place that I'm in today.
We, you really will. It's just a complete information overload. So I kind of treat it like my
news aggregator. You know, it's like stuff goes by and traveling is the worst, because if you travel
and then you open up your email, you know, their emails that may be two or three screens deep.
Forget about it. You just can't get to it. Oh, for the days of an RSS based system.
Ah, sometimes I go to bed thinking, how can we make it better? How can we make it better?
Email here from Paul Sabie. Adam regarding yesterday, uh, Roger Smalls. I, I'm pretty sure
Roger said in the past, he does not drive. You know, I thought he, maybe I am confused with the
mini Paul, but I thought Roger, I thought Roger Smalls also said ones that he, maybe it's not a mini.
Oh, shoot. Well, the maybe wasn't him that was in front of my, you know, coming away from my
host or driveway. I thought that he was, he had driven a mini around Gilford. Maybe I'm wrong. So,
okay, then maybe it's someone else I should be concerned about.
Ah, let me see. Ah, a message. This is, uh, shoot. Have no, you know what? What is this?
No, I won't do the message right now. Let me move on to, uh, since we're about to, uh, close the window here,
on the folks checking out the podcast on, uh, on Syria sidelight stars one or three. Yeah, just really
briefly on this lawsuit. Um, I lawyers picked up something really, really cool, which I just wanted
to share with you. The fact that these, uh, that this magazine grabbed pictures from Flickr
means they automatically entered into a license with me and I'll read this piece that they found
on Flickr, which is just fantastic. Um, here it is. By exercising any rights to the work provided
here, which of course I have the creative comments, you accept and agree to be bound by the terms
of this license. So Flickr actually in, in their wisdom have created, uh, almost a, uh, a
ulla, an end-user license agreement, which is very comparable to when you, uh, open up the CD-ROM
for Microsoft Windows. Uh, there's all that, you know, that sticker on it and all those, that really
fine print essentially says the same thing. It says by opening up this envelope, you hear by
agree to the terms of the license, which is written in these really fucking small letters. Uh,
so I just thought that was brilliant. So I, I feel really confident about today and those of
you listening in on the stars 103, uh, you'll have to tune in tomorrow, uh, to hear, uh, how it went
down. The actual judgment may not be for, for 14 days. I, I now understand. Uh, of course,
alternatively you could always download the podcast at dailysourcecode.com. Pacific Coast
Hellwise next for those of you on the satellite followed by East Radio and Don and Drew.
So we'll continue here. Let's get to that message.
And I've been closely into your body since I'm up in for the full spirit of my 15 year career.
I'm the human side of perspective of a deep understanding of the fundamental tribe and purpose of
the industry. I've been informed of particular opinion and skill set to a discussion on the
evolution of the industry in its future. It starts there with over 10 to 15 years ago,
distracting the attention and stealing our time. I'm talking about technology and innovation,
it's a faster and becoming exponentially more dangerous. I'm going to be fine,
better equipped and sharply focused, more invasive, where are you taking this and having more
cleverly humanity? You know, I really hope you guys can hear this guy okay on your ear buds.
Um, I got the the most volume I can get out of cast blaster on this particular piece of feedback.
He's got, it's like he's standing in a brook or something, but he does some of some really
interesting points to make. Um, so let's just continue to listen.
I enjoy my videos. I like pre-packaged food. I like to learn how to offend with my personal
hygiene. I like comfortable clothes and lifestyle. I don't get into this as fast and
what I'm undertaking with information and I like you from time to time, would like to be
not aimed. But I also just want to trade my hard earned currency for the product to service
in my choosing and be on my way. I mean, the price of the volume is marked. I've fought over
the tax in touch with the antibiotics, and to the next time I choose to participate in its process.
Look, I realized when this is breaking news, I didn't report to be the chance to be on the
subject. Maybe you can see this tomorrow day. Or maybe I'm just can say that the only exposed exposure
it's well. I am an anonymous American, and I am a conspicuous consumer. And if I
complied to identify it specifically exposed, the most least is that it was in this video cycle.
Are we going to talk about the focus on its ever-advolving acquisition of my American mindset?
From the LEDD to the idolatry and micro-solvering on the films, from the technical
sports and it's faithful followers to the infotainment and product placement, propaganda and
policy and politics, the media in all its mass restrictions, constantly snatching your attention.
I mean, it's time just sensitizing and distracting us from fundamental universal human concerns and interests.
Wait, wait, wait, I just want to stop you there for one second, because this stuff is actually
really good, and we should have a live conversation about it. I just just about grabbing
attention for a second. Let me just say that the amount of time I spend on bullshit that takes
my attention in my email is more, it's in minutes, it's more time, and it is definitely more
frustrating than sitting through any advertisement, listening to any commercial, and that's just
purely by volume. Just want to stay that.
Then, adding the reason I'm coming to you with this is simple. I've firmly believed that the
future of making an advertising is on a promotion based platform. In other words, the messages
that shared and will be acceptable are imposed to a person around the inside. Are the ones from
companies who respect our time and attention as a most valuable asset can suit us such. The
evidence, practically the way that it has minds here is our time to focus attention to the energy
and the energy that I value of such. If we possibly share a more multi-mixage in my case,
why for years, we do not deserve even a respect or a met patronage.
So, let's say, I want information on your product or service, I can easily find your
on my own. In the 30, having a pre-sayship to sell product or service,
I would be more than happy to spread that message to my student once, that being found
has colleagues, family and so on. That's what the example of this course and the permission
based marketing of which I speak, is your relationship with sincere employer? It's in there.
No, no, I don't come for you to illustrate it for such an individualism. So, be it.
The heart of compensation to have a family, of course, at the birth rate.
Just one little brief thing there. I have no relationship, commercial relationship with
either Senseo or Apple. So, those examples weren't the best, but I do understand the gist.
No style of gossip, much better. Now, in any respects, if you're much appreciated,
I don't afford a possibility of working together in the form of my self,
depending upon what you're doing. That's it. That's what you're looking at.
And I really like it. I don't know what to say about it.
All right, and honest American, thank you very much. Well, a couple of things about that.
In an ideal world, and let me just say one thing about RSS, I don't usually like to talk
about all the technology underneath everything. But RSS is pretty critical in our world today.
It is the default methodology for publishing and subscribing to information. One thing I could
imagine, and it would be great if it really worked out. But I have my doubts,
is what if along with this podcast, there was a separate feed. And this feed was, and you could
subscribe to this. In fact, you would be encouraged to subscribe to it. And this feed contained
advertisements. It could be audio advertisements. It could be video advertisements. It could be a
PDF. It could be a number of things that would come through. And you were subscribed to that.
The theory is, in this case, is that you would subscribe to it. And you would listen to the show
and that you would know that there would be products and services that would be advertised.
When you want it, based upon your permission. So, you make the decision to go and look at the
feed of commercials or advertisements. The theory there is, is that they would contain information
that you would be interested in. Not very easy to do, by the way. There's some real easy ones.
Pretty much everyone may at one point in time want to drink a coke. But otherwise,
it's to individualize it would be incredibly beautiful. But I don't know if that's going to be
possible. And of course, the, you know, the issue really is, is will people subscribe to a show
and to its associated advertising feed? I think in some cases, we could actually try that out and
see how it works. Of course, the other way is to say, well, you know, here's where the advertisements
are. They're at the beginning or at the end of the show. Or whatever the mashup is that you're
making, we just happen to call it a podcast today. You know, have a, have a, have a listen if you want.
At the end of the day, there has to be money coming in. And I don't feel that, what you're
suggesting there is a little bit too much of a one-way street because, and I'm not talking about
podcasts, who are podcasting to bring you the love that they want or, you know, just have something
to say. I'm talking about people who want to produce and write and create something and they're
art, you know, just like an artist can make a song and put it out either in iTunes or sell the CD through
CD Baby or these days as we ramp it up, be able to sell an MP3 through the podcast music network.
I mean, why is that, you know, we have no problem at all paying 99 cents for an MP3 that is usually
three to four megabytes in size, whereas I create an MP3 every single day, which is 20 to 40
megs in size. And, you know, no one's going to pay me 99 cents for that. Yes, it's a few people
mind, but not enough to, I don't think enough to blip the radar. I really don't, whereas I've seen plenty
of sales of MP3s of independent and pod safe artists do quite nicely. Yeah, I'd settle for a
couple grand a month. So, you know, the dialogue is open. Let's, let's continue thinking about
this, let's continue thinking, better and smarter because not only do we have, are we changing
media, we're changing, advertising, and perhaps the way advertising is brought. So, very open to
it, of course. I got something here from, from K2 at the office. He sent me this link about
watermarking, which is, in other words, digital rights management. And, let's see, what is
this article from? This is from KatherineCramer.com, and the title of the article was,
was it, watermarking as a strategy for insisting on corporate creators, is DRM the killer app
for corporate authorship? And, and the gist of this really is, is that DRM is not necessarily
being put in place only to stop people from copying stuff, but it's creating a gatekeeper role.
And, the theory there is that if you have consumer devices, which today may support, you know,
quick time movies in MP3, but essentially have all of this watermarking recognition technology
built into it so that if you play a Hollywood property, let's say a movie, or a CD for a major
label, that it will play on that device. Then, of course, the only thing they have to do is
once the device is, once they hit on the right device. And, by the way, Apple could do this
at any time they wanted it. I don't think they will, but at any time Apple wants, they can say,
you know what, we're not going to allow MP3 to play anymore, and they could just shut it off,
and then what? I mean, of course, there'll be plenty of players, but you understand the basic,
you know, the basic problem here, that when you popularize something, and let's just face it,
you know, the Ricky Javez podcast is very successful, besides the fact that it's good, but mainly
because Ricky Javez was a well-known media personality with some well-known media properties,
and queue factor. Isn't that what it's called? The queue factor.
So, you know, popularizing devices that could then potentially just shut off any other type of
content playback, could be a huge problem. And that just goes right in line with what we're talking
about the other day, about a second internet being built, which will charge companies for access
to their customers, about the mail spam, you know, the email services that make you charge,
you know, that make you pay $80,000 to ensure that your emails are actually delivered. I got a
couple of emails from people saying, hey, man, that really solves some problems that I was working on.
I didn't understand why my email wasn't arriving, you know, on registrations. Yeah, no kidding.
All right, let's talk briefly about the pod safe music network.
Adam, over the PMM, I've got my podcast to account.
What have been the ratings? You know, it's all gone. I want to be able to hit the button and say,
you know, that's a good song, you know, give it a little more credibility or that's a bad song, you know,
I don't not too happy with it. I'm seeing the great purchase button, then I'm not seeing any
ratings pop up. So, if we could get that brought back into play or, you know, at least,
what happened to why did you get rid of it? The other things on remember me, yeah, that's a nice
feature to have and you know, I enjoy it, but there are sometimes when I want to be able to hit
log out and see what my listeners are going to see when they hit the link, you know, is it just
working right because I'm a podcaster and automatically, no, or, you know, it's just, so are we going
to get a log out button? Or am I going to have to go in and remove cookies each time? So,
can you see your insight on that? So, thanks, Adam. Bye. All right, man. Okay, so first the log
and stuff. Right now, we're writing a cookie to your, to your machine. So, you stayed logged in,
you got that right. There will be a log out function, there will be an automatic log out function.
This is all part of bringing everything together, we're incorporating podshow plus, which is our
listener interface, soon to be released. We are integrating podcast alley, integrating pods
of music network and so you have one single sign on for everything in the podshow universe.
So, you're kind of stuck in the middle there, we will be enabling that, you know, the automatic
log out or just a log out button general. I've always been a big stickler about the PMN where I
hated having to log in every single time, but I understand that everyone thinks differently about that.
So, that's cool. That's being worked on. Then the ratings, I don't know what happened to the ratings.
Somewhere in the back of my mind, I remember a conversation about it, but I'm sure Chris Rockwell will
give me the, the load down. And when he hears the show today, I think that this might have just
been a temporary interface thing where we're just, because we're, we've put the, the buy logo in
next to every single song, although on almost every single one of them, it's still great out as we
continue to continue to test the purchasing function of the MP3s through the pod save music network.
And also the whole idea of the listener interface, right now the pod save music network is really
just a meeting place in a licensed place, if you will, a place of licensing and exchange
for independent artists and for podcasters. Of course, as a listener, you're more than
welcome to come in. Right now, all we really have for you is a way to do some rudimentary search.
It's not the best in the world where aware of that. You know, you can listen to songs in full
length with it, which I think is very cool. And of course, you can, you can purchase the MP3s
free and in the clear. We will have a much, the entire pod show plus will have an integrated
listening experience so you can, really, as a listener, you can do a lot more with the pod save music
network. So that's also on the way. We're playing with it right now. I mean, just that we have this
player that is so freaking phenomenal. Let me see, was there something else I'm going to say about that?
Now, see, there's another question here about the pod save music network. Ben Lurchon,
listening for about nine months now, but I was excited to hear something other than pod save for
piece available for purchase on the PMM and waiting too long for this. Love the concept of
pod save music. Ah, okay. Here we go. I heard on the daily source code 342, I could download
American Heartbreak and Matthew evil. So I clicked the pretty green button and gave all my info to
clicking by that includes my birthday. Right. I'm 15. I have a visa box card, which is kind of like a
debit card. Pretty cool. Check it out at visa box.com, BUXX. So I never expect any trouble when
I sign up to buy something and it sort of surprised me when clicking by a told me that could not
sign up unless I am 18. Good point. Hmm, I don't know what the deal is with that, but it seems like
that would be a shame. I think I thought that by law, you only had to be over 13 to participate in
commercial transactions. Something I'll definitely look into because we'd like, you know,
why just try lying on the sign-ups. You would have it. Just say that you're 18 and then report
back to me if it worked. Derek Richardson checks in. Hey, Adam, hope you're well. Just given
update about purchasing from the PMM. I registered. It took about 15 minutes, which seems very,
very long to me, but after that, perfect. No problems. Now I have purchased copies of every day
were Christmas, best of luck with the court case today. The fuckers. Yes, okay. One regards from
Derek. And then, oh, this is from Michael Butler. I'll hold on. I'll do that in a second. Let me
just move that down in my list. I want to play one last podcast I've song for you. I was going to
do, oh, yes, this is the internal podcast. A question that's come up more than once regarding
the podcast music network. I Adam, this is Martin from Southampton in the UK. I'm a long time
listener. Ever since I got my iPod, what two Christmas is ago. I wanted to ask you for your opinion
on internal podcasts and the use of music from the Podsafe music network. I suppose I should
probably explain what I mean by an internal podcast. I work for a large IT company and we're already
doing podcasts, which go on our customer-facing websites and listen to my customers, etc.
But we're also starting now to use podcasting internally for sales, training, new
production announcements. That's sort of thing. Now, I'd like to start one of these
podcasts, these internal podcasts myself. And I'd kind of like to use some music to top and
tail the show. Give it a bit more interest, make it more listenable. And I'd really like to use
some music from the Podsafe music network. So I'm just wondering what the deal is with using that
music internally when, of course, my feed won't be available on the internet. It's only on our
internet and how you account for that. Anyway, love the show. I hope that you can give me an answer
to this. Bye. All right, dude. I don't think it's a problem, actually. I don't think there's anything
in the terms that forbid you from doing that. As long as you report back, and obviously,
so what I understand is you can't actually put a link to the podcast itself. Well, if you report
back to the network, and you place the links to the song pages and the artist pages themselves
in your internal show notes, I think that's fine. Shouldn't be a problem. And use this as as
your evidence and court, if there ever is a problem. So I could grow incorporated, came out with
a new video. I don't know if it was last night or the night before, but I watched it last night.
Oh, man. Soccer girl, I love you. You're out of your mind. Very, very, very, very creative.
Hey, man, I'm ready for this, this court case today. I want to go kick some ass. I'm going to
line that up with the piece of Podsafe music. Michael Butler, of course, the Rock and Roll geek.
Frequently, let's me know what's going on. He works with lots of people helping them get on the
PMN. And that includes some labels, East West Records, a label that's part of the Warner Brothers
group. They have about 10 subsidiaries. Have put up some of their lesser known acts onto the
Podsafe music network. So you can go look for East West Records. You can just search by it
and you'll see them show up. And then, and this was kind of cool. This came from,
see, a suggestion internally at Pods Show home. Let me just bring up the page here for a second
for this guy, because he was pretty interesting. His name is Val, was it? No, not that, not Val Davis,
the hell. No, no, no, no, no, no, shoot. Here it is. Ola, onabule. God, I don't know if I'm saying that,
right? Ola. Ola, onabule, maybe it's that. It's kind of like a seal-looking guy,
which makes sense. And I'm reading from the bio here. Ola is considered to be the UK's finest
soul singer songwriters and performs over 100 shows a year in the UK Island in Europe. He's emerged
as an artist of distinction, honing his writing and production skills at the same time evolving
into a passionate and committed performer. So it was Greg Mann from the Pods Show sales and marketing
department who passed this on to a Michael Butler. And you know what? Shit kicks ass, man.
Oh, where you're gonna go? And now that soul town's gone, how you're gonna do?
What has been so long? What's your life right at the tip of the Larry Assants of Koo?
In Street, Saturday and Friday, I still ain't gonna lie for you. I don't know about his food,
it's my life right at home. What you're gonna say? When they talk it down,
that I've the peak of its day, it wasn't nothing, nothing but a plane change turn.
You know, say so times the way it's all gonna be, and someday we'll build it all again.
When we've had enough of the sentiment, the bottom of the zone, and then we'll start a fresh breeze and a bend-o.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh
When you're gonna see
That's all sounds
And all those beautiful people you use to know
Well, they ain't so fast
You riding high in the front of skies
Just be in the past you're proud
If we were dreaming your heart, something that may be
You thought that you'd better change in the world
You'll say, slow down, so pretty, yes, but it makes you new
Someday we'll feel it all again
When we were having love, I was searching for you
Love too much of a lonely day, we'll start a lecture
Let's go, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Where'd you gonna go?
Now that's so, tell us, oh, oh, oh, oh
You got it, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much
I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about hey, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about so much, I'm talking about American, I'm talking about American, I'm talking about American, I
So, tell me, just go
I feel like I'm not done
You're not done
So, so, so
So, so, so, so, so, so
So, so, so, so
So, so so.
All this year
When Mine, the doll have in disguise
all this time is pretty smooth
as the, Melanie, the Boyd, and Stevie Wonder
Donnie cast a plate, Stevie down
You can ...
UK's Finest, All I On Nam Piance
I hope that's the right pronunciation
Maybe when he gets the email that I played him on the show so the PMN
he'll give me the exact pronunciation.
All right, I got to get going here.
God, I wish my wife were here to give me a metro makeover.
My hair looks like total shit.
And you know, this is gonna be cameras and all kinds of reporters
in the courtroom today.
So that's so, I got to go spend like 45 minutes getting this thing.
This dead cat on my head looking somewhere half decent.
So I'm getting another one of those.
Oh, well, what you said was really good,
but why the Donald Trump hairdo?
And I will, anyway, so I'm back tonight,
flying liquidy split, I hope,
with the staleos airlines, with easy jet.
And tomorrow I will give you a full rundown,
full report on what took place, what happened.
And I know for will actually get,
if we'll get any kind of judgment today,
but certainly within the next 14 days.
So thanks for all the well wishes.
And send me some feedback, adamantcurry.com.
Fuck, I just send it.
Just attach your shit to a Gmail, okay?
Will ya?
Let's see if we can get the account blowing up again
and reach out to those guys
and see if we can purchase some more space for poor old magic
from me.
Atamercurry.com, dailystoresco.com
is where you can find the latest podcast
and the feed to subscribe to this show.
Thanks for listening.
Now I will see you tomorrow.
Another pod show podcast, sticking in your ear.