This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy.
Delta Sierra Charlie 416.
You're less than an hour.
Aircraft from here will join others for around the world.
And you will be launching the largest aerial battle in the history of mankind.
mankind.
Words should have new meaning for all of us today.
We can't be consumed by our petty differences anymore.
We will be united in our common interests.
Perhaps space today is before the July.
And you will once again be fighting for our freedom.
Not from tyranny and oppression or persecution.
And from annihilation.
We're fighting for our right to live.
To exist.
It should be with the day.
The Fourth of July will no longer be known as American holiday.
As the day with the world declared in one voice,
we will not go quietly into the night.
We will not vanish without a fight.
And we're going to live on.
We're going to survive.
And there we shall be.
Long history today.
Let's the Fourth of July again.
Battle rockets light the sky.
And I was looking for a telephone.
Just to call and ask you out.
And kids are running down for stamina.
With their spark dwells in their hands.
Release the barricaded St. Mark's place.
Tonight they're yours and far in land.
I toss in turn on sleepless nights.
To try and find the words to the same.
How can I be so dependent?
Please don't leave on independent stay.
So I went to the pole, the shruster run.
Down on second they're the blue.
I sat down and had myself the sandwich there.
I had a cup of chicken soup.
Walking home I saw the fireworks.
That's the first thread wide and blue.
I don't know how I'm going to live my life.
Three thousand miles away from you.
I toss in turn on sleepless nights.
To try and find the words to the same.
How can I be so dependent?
Please don't leave on independent stay.
Let's the fuck up July again.
It's a daily source code for July 4th 2006.
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
Apologies right up front for the noise in the background.
There's a heat wave in Europe and most homes in certainly in the United Kingdom are not air conditioned.
And the cottage, well, would you expect a cottage to be air conditioned?
Of course I do have the warmest room in the house.
So I've got two units here going full blasts, the blinds are down.
And we kicked off the show with the Goodman Brothers Independence Day.
Of course the link to that in the show notes.
So here we are.
Doing a show, doing a podcast.
And you are probably wondering how I'm doing, how everything's going.
And what the hell I'm doing podcasting at all perhaps.
That's a fair question.
So for those of you listening for the first time,
my mom passed away this past Sunday.
And I refer to the previous show on daily source code.com.
If you want more information about that.
I wasn't quite sure what to do with the show.
My mom and knew very well what Ron and I were always up to.
She loved Ron very much.
That often.
And she felt that he was good for me.
You know what I mean?
So she always had a good vibe, which was always very interested in what we were doing.
What we were up to, she knew about what was going on in the UK.
And she also knew that the next couple of weeks were going to be pretty big and pretty important for us and for pod show.
And for me personally, of course, and she was very interested in what we were doing and how we were going about it.
And of course, everything all comes at the same time.
And I had a decision to make.
Now, first of all, I totally acknowledge that I am absolutely still grieving,
even though just about everything.
I think everything actually has been taken care of.
And you know, I'll talk about that in a bit.
And I definitely need some emotional time.
We'll need that in the not too distant future.
Just to chill out a little bit and sort some things out.
It's very interesting.
I've never had anyone close to me die ever.
Not this close, obviously.
And it kind of comes in waves.
You know, it's.
I'm paying attention to it.
I'm really, you know, and all the appropriate messages are going off of my head.
I definitely appreciate anyone who thinks that I probably shouldn't be podcasting at all.
But it really does feel good.
It's so yeah, just enlightening.
It feels good.
It's cathartic.
You know, I can get stuff out there.
And you guys are my buddies.
Damn, are you?
The outpouring of love and.
Messages of stories and personal stories.
And oh, man, this has been so great.
My sisters, I don't think they ever really listen to the podcast.
My sister and Italy does.
But bandwidth is so messed up there.
She can't listen to it very regularly.
It all only had work.
And of course, she.
She's the kind of person that wants to be working at work and not listening to podcasts.
But they they also heard the show.
Because of course, I consulted with them.
And, you know, just hundreds of comments from all over the world.
And there were phone calls to to pod show HQ, people wanting some flowers.
And it was just unreal.
I really didn't know how close we are.
And, you know, a lot of people sent me messages.
And lots of voicemails as well.
Thank you.
Of course, you know, a lot of them I felt were just personal.
And I'm not going to share those at all.
But really, really, really appreciated it.
It's, you know, a lot of people would say, well, this podcasting really has created something special.
Of course, it's not really podcasting.
It's, it's much more basic than that.
It's the fact that we have this communication.
And that we're pretty open and honest with each other.
And we're not forced by constraints like time and another issues to sound to be fake.
I guess that's it.
That's what makes it so beautiful.
And the internet is full of that.
It's not just podcasting.
But wow, when you add that dimension of voice, it really does make a difference.
I feel.
So I wrote a couple things down here.
Yeah.
So again, thank you everybody who commented or sent person.
It's so, it's so amazing.
I look at my inbox.
And I have it set to 100 messages per page.
And every single one is, is about my mom.
Just beautiful stories and nice little quick notes.
It doesn't matter if it was long or short.
It's just fantastic receive all that.
And not a single bit of spam.
There's not one penis in larger in the 100 on the top page.
It's so magical.
But we did touch each other with this.
And so, you know, I talked to this long around,
and around there to get back to the fact that I talked to a number of people,
talked about, you know, considering what's going on in my life right now.
And I really do want a podcast.
And just, you know, I took some advice from some, some wiser people,
my wife, my business partner.
And we all agree that mom probably would have kicked my ass if I had not continued through this next period.
And just, you know, had some fun and gotten on with it and do the task at hand.
And that I know, hands down.
There's no, there's just no doubt on my mind whatsoever or anyone else's.
So I'm definitely going to do that.
I just wanted to share one audio comment that I got just to give you an idea of how deep this went.
This was so deep.
It's just beautiful. Listen to this.
Hey Adam, I just wanted to wish you my condolences on the singing mom.
This is Michelle from Seattle.
My cult once or twice before, but I lost my mother to learn cancer when I was 12.
I kind of know what you're going through.
I was pretty young, but, you know, at least, you know, I think it's cool that you had a satisfying relationship with her.
As an adult, I got that with my dad before he passed away, but I didn't get that with my mom.
So, you're a lot deen that regard.
And I wanted to say, you know, you can, I mean, I'm sure you're a pretty enlightened guy.
So I'm sure you know that she's either, she's either her energy,
her beautiful energy is out enriching the world and making it a better place now, or, you know,
depending on what you believe, or she's just free of all pain and all that.
All the stuff she had to go through there, and so, you know, where you should start, you know,
she's probably still herself and just without all the, all the yucky stuff that she had to deal with in the physical world.
Either way, she's, I'm sure better off than she was there at the end.
So, let me, man, I'm thinking of you. Okay?
Bye.
Thank you, Michelle. See, this is what I mean.
This is not about my mom. This is not about me or my family.
It's about all of us as human beings.
And we all have hardships like this, and, you know,
life on the planet can be extremely short.
That's for sure. So, ride the wheels off this motherfucker, will you?
And go hug someone you love.
And so, even though my mom is not in the physical world,
one thing I know for sure, you're stuck with her, because she lives inside of me,
as she lives inside of my sisters, and really many other people,
because amongst all of these, all these emails and comments and voice mail feedback,
a lot of people talked about my mom about the things she would say.
She always had, well, what she called sampler saying,
I don't know if you remember, I don't know if you know it all.
It's a very American thing.
What was it, is it crochet work or is it a needle point, I think.
You create a needle point for on the wall, and it has some kind of slogan on it.
Like one that sticks out that hangs on my mom's wall is the road to a friend's house
and never long, and this is a tradition really from her side of the family.
But she had a couple other sayings and rules that she lived by
that I'll share with you today.
And again, you know, I'm not going to try and push this away,
stuff will pop up over the course of the next, whatever, you know,
and shows, and I hope you don't mind, I hope you enjoy it.
It'll just pop up.
Maybe I get Jeff, say and say, oh, maybe I get Jeff Smith to do a jingle for my mom moment.
So my mom had a big thing with butterflies, and she had this from her mom.
In fact, they were very similar, beautiful blonde.
Kind of Marilyn Monroe asked classy, big bed of Davis eyes,
and my grandmother's nickname was Whiffy, because she always whiffed the golf ball.
And my mom's nickname was Breezy, but they also had this butterfly thing.
And so my mom always wore a butterfly on her left shoulder,
and she had an enormous collection.
And by the way, it should be cremated everybody who attends that very small ceremony
will take a butterfly from her box and wear it and take it home with them.
And man, she had everything all set out.
So anyway, I want to give you two of her life slogans, which I really like.
So one of them is, if nothing changed, there would be no butterflies.
And the one I heard her say a lot in the last couple of months was,
I used to complain about not having any shoes until I met a man with no feet.
And so my mom was full of stuff like that, and she loved to write stuff down.
She had this folder that we weren't supposed to open until it was time.
And so we did after she passed away, and it was really funny.
She had written all kinds of great personal notes to us, and she even had a...
We have kind of a morbid humor, I guess, in the family.
But she wrote this whole thing about, hey, you know, dude, if I'm incapacitated, pull the plug.
It's so good we all wanted a copy of it.
It was very, very funny, last will and testament.
And there was some other personal and private stuff in there.
But then she'd also written her obituary, which was placed in the newspaper today.
She wrote the invite. She was very specific, had taken care of all of her arrangements.
And then there was this separate invite because she wanted, and my sister has it.
She'll get me a PDF file. I should read it to your verbatim. It's hilarious.
My mom, of course, really was a little bit too old to be a hippie, but too young to be a hippie.
Wait a minute, I guess she was too old to be a hippie.
And she was kind of in that in between the 50s and 60s.
So she definitely grew up with the Bobby Sox, and she is from the rock and roll era.
Which, of course, is why I know the lyrics, almost every single 50s hit you can even think of.
I can verbatim sing all that well. I know the lyrics. I'm not a fantastic singer as we all know.
So she said, my children here by invite you to honor my last wish, which is a 50s rock and roll party.
So we're reading this like, oh man, it's so typical of my mom.
I spent a lot of the past day and a half or two days organizing this.
Well, I'm not going to tell you too much because we still want it to be pretty private, but man, I'll take pictures.
And I got it completely figured out, worked out, arranged. It's going to be awesome.
And everyone's very excited and intrigued by this whole thought. And I think it's great.
You know, if that's the way she wants everyone to say goodbye to her, it has kind of an Irish vibe to it.
Only typical of the way my mom would do it in her 50s fashion.
So I had a lot of fun putting that together, actually, and it was not easy getting it all together at the last moment, but
the only mom we're going to have a ball. Now, okay, onward because we got a lot of stuff to do today.
A lot of cool stuff to talk about.
The number one thing is now, of course, you know, pod show is my family as well.
And everybody knows each other. We're still thank God. And hopefully we can stay this way for a long time.
We're small enough in work force that we do know each other.
And we do feel like a family.
Everyone has really been grieving along with us, also for their own personal reasons.
But I just heard that we're going to have yet another baby introduced into the pod show family.
I'm not going to tell you who yet because this was internal. I don't know if there's, you know, let's just, I think they're on the way to the hospital now, and I think we've got a fourth of July baby.
So, you know, it's the whole thing just really is, it's kind of in sync there. It's starting to balance each other out.
And I'm so happy that finally I'm old enough to be in a company that can legitimately make little baby podcaster t-shirts. I just love the whole
thing.
Wait a minute. She didn't want to play that. He's what I wanted to play.
Adam, this is beautiful room from the Netherlands. It just occurs to me which dates you shoot day for pod show, pod show, pod show, pod show, pod show.
Not only one day that's excellent since you're independent from the record labels, that sort of thing.
So it should be an independent day, the 4th of July.
I wonder if that's true. Well, I think it is. I don't know of course.
Dude.
Bye bye.
Okay, I know you're touched, but you can't be Dutch and that blonde. Yes, of course.
That's what it's been about all these weeks.
We've been leading up to the freedom of your, your media independence day, pod casting.
We're launching or are really unleashing pod show plus the pod cast delivery network.
This was a date that was I think brilliantly chosen by by the by the team.
Ron and I just took this as a recommendation and love the idea.
For a number of reasons one, not a lot of you are going to be paying attention to me today.
So we can kind of ease into it and we can, you know, we can mess a lot of stuff up without disappointing too many people.
Additionally, it's a, it really is very symbolic. I love that.
And so here's 50 people who have given up their major portion of not all of their 4th of July to do this.
You know, I, I can't say how blown away I am by it and how excited I am to have all of this happening today over the next couple of days.
It's going to continue. Well, we're, it's an unleash. It's a, it's a public beta, which means,
well, we're doing our darners and we'll be communicating as much as we can and you'll be feeding it back and yeah, we're going to have some fun.
I hope I really hope you like it. This is like the unveiling of, you know, this piece of art that we've been working on secretly in the lab for such a long time.
And now I've seen so many different versions of it and, you know, things on so many different test servers.
And I'm, I'm even confused about what I'm seeing anyway. It's, you're going to love it. You really will. It is a totally different way of enjoying media.
Whether it's audio, whether it's video and we certainly plan to expand. You're going to see the podcast, music network being integrated in some really cool ways.
And we got, we got a lot of work to this is just ground zero for us. This is just what we're starting.
So keep checking podshow.com sometime today. It's going to be up.
In fact, let me take a look right now.
And what's the time? It is 608 PM in, almost a second in Guilford. So let me go to podshow.com.
Let's see if it's up. Nope, still the old homepage. Okay.
All right. So that means it's what is it 10 AM in San Francisco. I think it will be another hour or so.
And then you might see some changes starting to happen.
So be on the lookout for me online. I should just be in there as Adam, daily source code will be in there.
And there is lots of ways to communicate and talk with each other. If you're interested in doing a podcast, you could try that out today.
The minute you get in, you can try, you can start podcasting immediately, whether it's for one person or just a tester for your friends or if you're a pro.
Go ahead, give it a whirl. Please. But also check out how I think we've made your life.
Oh, easier with the factor of 10, just on managing all this stuff and how we can interact with each other.
Can't wait to hear what you guys think of it. So also be a look. I'll look out for Winthorbe Valentine and Balthazar.
There are perusing through the whole podshow plus empire, spreading their seeds of good love.
And we've got the site guy and all kinds of stuff.
So what do we have now? 22, 22 and a half minutes. Perfect.
I am going to play a song that I heard on CC Chapman's accident has she had a special edition.
Now stuff like that catches my eye and I'm definitely going to listen to it.
It comes from Jesta and I think it's so appropriate for today.
It's of course called Independence Day, but listen to the lyrics because it's about us.
Everybody's talking about the internet works. Ben with responses and advertising in service.
Everybody's talking stuff so until that show, I hear my voice cry on that show section.
Everybody's talking about net neutrality.
Everybody is talking about net neutrality.
Every body's talking about net neutrality.
They're talking about net neutrality.
Everybody's talking about net neutrality.
Make it a podcast, if there's not believe it to, see that it won't last
We're on the phone for July
I'm not a rocker, I'm into plans and stay
I don't care why the lessons seem like safe
This music's free, you don't know what's happening
I'm not a rocker, I'm into plans and stay
No matter what the R&A they say
This music's free, you don't know what's happening
I'm not a rocker, I'm into plans and stay
I don't care why the lessons seem like safe
This music's free, you don't know what's happening
I'm not a rocker, I'm into plans and stay
I don't care why the lessons seem like safe
This music's free, you don't know what's happening
I'm not a rocker, I'm into plans and stay
No matter what the R&A they say
This music's free, you don't know what's happening
I'm not a rocker, I'm into plans and stay
No matter what the R&A they say
This music's free, you don't know what's happening
I don't care why the lessons seem like safe
I'm not a rocker, I'm into plans and stay
No matter what the R&A they say
This music's free, you don't know what's happening
I'm not a rocker, I'm into plans and stay
No matter what the R&A they say
This music's free, you don't know what's happening
We've got a rocker, I'm into my plans and stay
No matter if the gensets just send it away
Just sure I'm in
We've got a freedom, you see
Just independence day, you can find that on the Pod Safe Music Network
As we unleash Pod Show Plus today
In the Pod Capster, theLibric Network
I'll probably do another update later on the
the evening my time much later or very early tomorrow morning once we've unleashed
and well we've seen how the system behaves so we're leaving these servers alone
so you'll definitely be able to find the podcast if you can't get through or anything else
goes wacky but you know what you may actually just have a fantastic time I'll talk to you later
bye bye another pod show podcast stick it in your ear
get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery
network from pod show and limelight networks