Delta's here at Charley, 3-5-7.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm testing kids, Adam Curry.
From the Curry condo in northern California, no sun but it is San Francisco.
Good morning everybody, it's Tuesday.
Get your country head on.
No sign of weather, not a cloud in the sky.
Taking it easy, I was doing just fine.
As God has my witness, I was mining my business.
When she flew in the town, it's like a tropical breeze.
Face like an angel exes along as you please.
I'll never forget it.
I got all caught up in it.
She was the object of my affection, then.
When changed direction.
Lock down your shutters and your doors,
but I'll love you for sure.
I'll never see when she rains down on you.
You've been telling me you've been warned.
You don't know what you're meant for.
She's a perfect star.
Once she comes, you'll never be the same.
So you better stay away from her again.
She held like thunder when the sky opened up.
I started shaking when the lightning struck.
My poor heart was breaking,
where every move she was making then she.
The ride over just as quick as she came.
She probably don't even remember my name.
I wrote down the speechless trying to figure the pieces.
Just another seduction ever.
Path of destruction.
Lock down your shutters and your doors,
but I'll love you for sure.
I'll never see when she rains down on you.
You've been telling me you've been warned.
You don't know what you're meant for.
She's a perfect star.
Once she comes, you'll never be the same.
So you better stay away from her again.
You'll never be the same, so you better stay away from Hurricane.
Life can't be scissors in your doors, but it'll hurt your motor stores.
Lord and mercy wins you race down on you.
You've been told you've been warned, you don't know what you're in for.
She's a perfect storm, better stay inside, where it's safer than now.
Once you come, you'll never be the same, so you better stay away from Hurricane Jane.
Colin Ray, Hurricane Jane, kicking off this Tuesday's edition of the Charlie Good Morning,
everybody from San Francisco, California.
It is another one of those days.
Overcast has been raining yesterday.
It was just horrible.
It rained.
It's not supposed to do that in Northern California.
You know?
Yeah, tough getting out of bed this morning.
I got to tell you.
You just can't watch John Stewart with the Daily Show and get up at 6 a.m.
It just doesn't work that way.
It's too much.
Hey, some stuff to talk about today.
Actually, pretty light on the audio feedback and stuff like that,
but we're going to roll out a Trinity segment because it's about time for that.
Congratulations to a serious satellite radio.
You may be listening to the show right now.
A channel was a serious star as 102.
Over 4 million subscribers now.
Wow.
That one really fast.
It was 3 million.
They reached just before Christmas.
I think we're just before the New Year's and already now 1 million extra.
So kicking some ass.
That's very cool.
More mainstream.
Are you here that?
I am the morning podcaster.
Kevin Flanagan sent an email and said,
The Air America has moved their podcasts to a pay for fee service.
I would pay, but think that for topical time sensitive material, the cost is too high.
That's too bad.
You know, Air America was, I don't know if they were even official podcasts.
It was all over the map.
I must have at least four or five different podcasts feeds that I'm subscribed to.
I'll none of them work anymore.
I think I've deleted three or four others.
But I think they have some major financial issues.
Never really got Air America off the ground.
So to speak.
And I really good day yesterday despite all the crappy weather.
Cali and Neil were up at the pod show HQ all day long.
Cali, of course, are fearless leader from the geek intelligence agency.
And, you know, it's funny because, you know, I have the new camera, the Sanio C5,
which I picked up at the Apple Store.
Yesterday was kind of my first day experimenting with it and learning how it worked.
And it's limitations.
One thing I noticed right off the bat, which I kind of knew when I read the specs before I even bought it,
is that it doesn't have an external audio in.
So you're kind of left to the device itself with it's built in stereo microphone.
And because it's so small when you use the zoom or even when it's focusing,
and it will invariably auto focus the minute you turn it on.
You can hear the motor worrying on the audio tracks.
That kind of sucks.
And of course, you have audio really is so important when it comes to video.
And so I did this whole thing.
I recorded different bits of clips and last night I came home,
dumped everything into what I used.
I used the eye movie.
And I remember, man, it takes a lot of work to get video stuff going.
It's a lot of waiting around for stuff to import and stuff to render.
And so I have, like, a four minute clip of a day in the life at Pod Show HQ,
which I don't know if I want to release it yet.
I think I want to look at it again and go, because it's really,
I don't know, I don't know if it'll be interesting.
It was interesting to me.
I don't know if you guys would like it or not.
Because of course, I'm not in it.
Most of it is other people.
And the other people that I was seeing throughout the day.
So it's a lot of Ron Bloom.
There's other Pod Show folks in there.
Of course, nice, significant pieces of Cali.
And a baby.
You know, it was a go figure.
So I'm going to review it with a couple of people today.
I see if they think it's worthy of putting it up there.
I was just pretty interesting.
Common I got from Michael Bauer, who was listening to,
see, DSC 340.
I'll just read this for you.
I thought it was interesting that you played the song about people talking loud
on their cell phones.
Recently heard an interview on one of the MPR shows about this very subject.
Turns out, the reason this happens is because cell phones,
unlike landline phones, do not play feedback to the user.
The fact that you can't hear yourself makes you talk louder.
And this, of course, sounds completely logical.
And I do recall, I think the old analog cell phones actually did have that kind of loop
where you could hear a little bit in your ear.
So the email goes on, you may think, like I did when first hearing this,
well, why not loop it back?
Yeah, that's exactly what I was saying.
Well, apparently it's not that easy landline phones do this through the phone company.
Your voice actually hits the phone company's exchange
and it's bounce back as feedback since it's over copper wires.
This happens really fast so the delay is very small.
Cells transmit wirelessly to much slower rates.
Of course, this would cause it delay.
You probably noticed this when in a heated conversation,
we have heated conversations never.
Anyway, the interview suggests that the problem will most likely be fixed by cell phone manufacturers.
They should place circuitry in the phones that repeat what the user says.
This causes the users to speak softly.
That's very interesting.
I have no idea what, it's probably just laziness that they didn't do that
or probably a power issue as well because it all takes power to do that.
But, gee, wouldn't it be nice if all cell phone conversations automatically just were dim down
30% or 40% wouldn't that be nice for the overall world volume population?
I think that's a pretty good idea.
It doesn't seem like a hard thing to do these days.
Now, of course, with the battery life that they can get out of these miniature batteries.
I thought just popped through my head, but she can't remember it's too early.
Hi, I'm Mr. Bobeski here.
I've just been thinking about your recent Charlie,
talk about your suspected power failure in your apartment in San Francisco.
The reason I'm thinking about it is, I'm just sat here in total darkness
because we've just had a power failure here in Newbury, in Barsher, in England.
It's 9 o'clock on a Saturday night.
Now, that's a really rare thing to happen.
So, okay, big deal.
Thing is, I've just been watching the War of the Worlds on DVD.
Literally half an hour ago.
And of course, that's all about power failures and lightning strikes and other things due to alien attack.
What's made it even weirder, really surreal, is somebody's just had a firework party in the neighborhood.
And there's all sorts of, you know, fireworks, bangers and explosions going on.
So, I'm thinking it's just a local power failure, but it could be the start of something else.
Getting nervous here.
And we never heard from them again.
Yeah, it's, you know, it's really funky when that happens.
You know, when the power goes out.
And in the States, it gets a little bit more used to it.
But in Europe, it never, and rarely ever happens.
And for it to happen, I don't know how the UK is.
We haven't had a power failure yet that I know, at least that one that wasn't, you know,
caused by excessive use of hair drying equipment and compressor limiter simultaneously.
And maybe it does go out a lot more often in the UK than I know.
Now, I'm telling you, I am so fuzzy today.
There's just, oh yeah, now I know.
Yeah, I was going back to actually to the phone call comment.
Yesterday I actually had, not a heated discussion.
Well, maybe it was a little an emotional discussion.
I called Patricia from the office on IChat.
I had my ear buds in and we love doing this.
I've told you about this.
She gets on her end on the, on the IChat.
And it's, it's really, it's a very, it's a very personal thing.
You know, you can really communicate well.
You can see nuances and we can smile at each other.
And it really does feel quite natural, actually, at this point.
But there were some teenager stuff that was going on back at the cottage.
And, and that's when it all breaks down, man.
And you can't talk to a, you can't talk sense into a teenager through IChat.
That just doesn't work.
It doesn't work through phone calls.
You really got to be there in the room.
So I was feeling a little bit frustrated about not being home.
And being able to help out with it.
It's not a big deal.
But, you know, it's a teenager thing.
You know, teenagers can get also and then get stupid.
It's talk to say, stupid stuff.
Oh, well, what do we have left?
Five days less than then I'll be back in the, in the arms of my girls.
And then, of course, where was it like five days after I get home,
then we're off to, to Portugal for vacation.
Did I tell you that?
That we're going to Portugal.
I think I did.
The last rooms available in all of Europe, apparently.
This is the, the big Easter holiday.
And all of the United Kingdom takes, well, not all.
But it seems like everyone won the lottery.
And it's all taken off this year's.
Hey, what is this?
Certainly, you remember this fine music.
And you're welcome to sing along if you can.
Okay.
It's a little bit on the soft side today, the Trinity theme song.
Starting off with, oh, first of all, we have a slogan for the Trinity segment.
This comes from Sean Murphy.
It should be green my machine.
Actually, this is the big promotion that I've been thinking about.
We need more of those FAQs.
If you're new to the daily source code.
This is a part of the week where we just talk about bio diesel and alternative fuels.
And anything that has to do with changing the way we consume power or the types of power that we consume,
whether it be electricity or shoot, you know, stuff that you throw in in your tank.
And we are working on a sponsor for this segment.
So we can actually do some more with it.
Now we're working on what I used to call the pimping of Trinity.
Now, of course, I like this new slogan, the green my machine contest.
Maybe something we could build out if we can get the sponsor interested enough.
The first machine to be green will be Trinity.
I want the servos in it to pop up and down.
And of course, it's going to be a big, a big slogan on the side that I'll say.
Save the world win valuable prizes.
I think that pretty much says it all.
That's all we need to know about Trinity.
I don't know.
Hey, there Adam.
This is Matthew Ebel, skyping in from about the 76 miles above the surface of the earth
in my spaceship, the UTF revolution.
And you thought you got high, huh?
Alright, sorry about that.
Hey, just wanted to let you know.
The whole biodiesel thing didn't really work out for the starship here.
It doesn't really go so well with my engines,
matter of fact, cost a lot of problems.
And I'm actually just now in the engine room,
putting the final touches back on the engines,
reverting it to its original fuel source,
which, of course, is pulverized AOL CDs.
You know, I'm still surprised that all you earthbound types
still haven't figured out the full potential of these pieces of shit.
Wouldn't it be awesome if you could actually
use those AOL CDs to run your car on?
Can you imagine how far many millions of miles we could drive
with all the excess CDs that are just out there?
Anyway, I just wanted to let you know how happy I am
that the Podsafe music network has been selling some of my tracks for the last few days.
Now, it's only been a few days.
And a bunch of people have already rushed out to pick these tunes up.
Alright, we'll be talking more about the Podsafe music network.
This is actually somewhat older comment I've been saving for Matthew Evel,
specifically for the Green-Mine Machine Trinity segment of the show.
Moving on to Dan Kinsella.
This is surprising.
And now that I think about it, I believe I saw a sign on the wall
at the biofueloasis the other day,
which related to this.
Dan says, I'm a long time listener to the DSC as well as follower
of the biodiesel technology.
I recently went looking to buy a new diesel car to try the technology out
and found out I couldn't buy one.
In New York, California, Maine, Massachusetts, and Vermont,
it is not possible to buy a new diesel car due to emissions issues.
And then this is all along article.
And maybe someone can condense that down for everyone listening to the show
and explain exactly what the deal is.
You can't buy new diesel cars.
Is this a plot or what?
You know, all of us, we all get turned on to biodiesel.
And now you can't buy the cars.
I gotta tell you, this sounds very suspicious to me.
Hey Adam, Eric here from EricRites.com.
Just wanted to drop you a little biodiesel info.
We're in the paper today that the governor of Indiana,
Mitch Daniels, announced that the Lewis Triphus Corp,
will be building the world's largest biodiesel plant from Claypool,
just north of Fort William Indiana.
Really close to me.
Anyway, just wanted to drop you that note.
It's a $135 million project.
That's just awesome.
And it will definitely be the world's largest biodiesel plant.
So I'll send you the link.
And I'd just want to let you know.
We are definitely moving forward here in the heartland.
Going free.
I'll make my daughter.
What's she green to?
John Roberts e-mails that Oregon buses are running on biodiesel.
When he sent a link there.
No audio link unfortunately.
Let's see.
Luis Petuz checking in from Colombia.
The government is very big on using compressed natural gas in cars.
It's at the same as LPG doesn't sound like liquid petroleum gas.
There's even a government bonus of 500,000 pesos.
So that's about $223.
As you switch your car over gasoline prices are held here.
So I took the plunge.
I own a 1994 Nissan Pathfinder.
And I had her converted to run on CNG and regular gasoline.
Not only is she running cleaners since CNG is a cleaner fuel.
But I'm spending more or less a third of the running costs as compared to gasoline.
CNG refueling stations in the northern part of the country are plentiful in the comm.
And the conversion allows my car to run on conventional gasoline or compressed national gasoline.
No problems for running out of gas since CNG is mainly methane.
I wonder how long until I can fart in my tank.
Okay, Luis.
Thank you.
I really made my morning here.
And then finally, DN Metzger.
Hold on.
Send me a link about a biodiesel here we go.
Biodiesel rental cars coming to Los Angeles.
The bio beetle echo rental cars, which started out on the Hawaiian island of Maui three years ago,
opened for business near Los Angeles International Airport with four cars fueled by filtered vegetable oil.
How cool is that?
These are the things we need.
And I think this is the, you know,
they have a whole bunch of really good car rental services in Los Angeles.
I used to when they're a lot for MTV.
I used to rent from the budget because they could, they would let you rent any car you could imagine.
So if it was, you know, you wanted a Rolls, you could rent a Rolls.
You wanted a Corvette, you could Corvette.
You wanted a Mercedes S500.
Anything you wanted to rent and they'd actually pick you up at the airport in the car that you wanted to rent.
So these guys are once again on the tip and it was a great way because, you know,
you could kind of get a feel for the car that you might never buy or you might actually want to buy.
But, you know, you want an extended road test.
So that's a good way to get into it and see that there really is no difference running on, on, on biodiesel.
Well, there is one big difference and that's, it just, it just smells so nice.
She could talk, you hear her fake.
I don't forget being in her tank.
We're Trinity.
Trinity.
Yeah.
Do you want some tech news? It's different than the ordinary boring stuff.
You found the bits of Silicon Hell podcast from deep in the heart of Texas.
It's Craig and his techno-possy.
Your buddy in mind, dude Mac.
Perfect.
And Neil.
He's not too hungover.
Wow.
And whoever else shows up.
Listen to this fine work of mortal achievement.
Gonna bits of Silicon Hell.com.
Or subscribe on iTunes.
It's at SiliconHell.com.
Yeah, was it?
I found this, this great not actually didn't just find it.
I went searching for this great screen saver for my Mac.
I can't remember exactly how it came up with the idea.
But I was, I was, yeah, it was a rummaging around on flicker.
And it turns out, of course, if you go a little bit further than your own site on flicker,
then it is really a social network.
And if you know the right tags to enter,
you can get all kinds of very interesting pictures.
And I'm big on screen savers, not for saving my screen,
but for the information they provide.
And if you have a Mac running OS,
you'll know that you can use an RSS feed.
So I want it an aggregate RSS feed.
So what I found is the screen saver called,
it's the 1,0001, 1001 screen saver from Mac OS X.
And what you can do is you can set filters for,
for flicker tags.
And basically, this thing will just sit there and pull in one flicker photo after
another base upon your, your filters.
And it's really, really cool.
I suggest you check it out.
Hey Adam, feed up.
Hey, satellite requirement.
Eric Bergen's comments displayed some common misconceptions
about how the word compression can be applied to audio.
Yeah.
First, MP3 is a file size compression scheme,
not an audio compression scheme.
It is designed to have the least possible effect on music files.
Some compression schemes can be used to make a file smaller
and restore it to an exact copy of the original.
That kind of file compression, however,
doesn't make files much smaller at all.
Scames like MP3 can make much smaller files.
But the price you pay is that when it is decoded,
some information is missing.
Often you won't even notice that.
But of course, the smaller the file, the crappier the sound.
But it is not the same as audio compression.
That's something completely different.
Audio compression is used to raise the loudness of quiet sounds
and lower the loudness of the loudest sounds,
making the difference between the loud and soft, less and less,
depending on how much compression is applied.
It is achieved electronically and has nothing to do with MP3
or any other file compression scheme.
One thing I think he's right about, though,
is that the podsafe music network should try to establish
some minimum standards for file size compression schemes like MP3.
Of course, this, even if followed, wouldn't guarantee sound quality.
A poor original recording will sound poor even if it's reproduced perfectly.
I would like to recommend that submissions to the podsafe music network
be at a minimum 128 kilobytes per second
at a sampling rate of 44,100 Hertz.
If it's a stereo recording or 64 kilobytes per second,
at a sampling rate of 44,100 Hertz, if it is a monoral file.
Both of those settings provide about an 11 to 1 savings in file size
while still sounding just about indistinguishable from the original
for most people's ears or most people's cares.
Ideally, especially when it's intended to be used in a podcast,
which is going to add a second file size compression,
submitters should shoot 4192 kilobytes per second at 44,100 Hertz for stereo,
which is approximately a 7 to 1 reduction in file size.
When an MP3 is played back in a podcast,
and that podcast then gets reencoded into an MP3,
that effectively doubles the amount of audio information that gets lost.
It might even be more than that.
That can lead to audio that has a kind of a squishy, swirly sound,
which is not at all pleasant.
Or correct.
Uncle Jesse!
Excuse me, I have to go close a window.
Long way to go for a bit, Peter, but I appreciate it.
Buy everyone on stereo, see tomorrow.
I think, by the way, it's kilobytes and not kilobytes per second.
That's a common misconception, but it is very critical.
It is a pretty short kilobytes.
Yeah, we'll be talking a little bit more about the pod save music network.
Just a few more things I wanted to share with you today, because some good comments came in.
This next comment is actually a comment on everything's crackling and cropping out here.
It's about the multi-tiered internet.
Now, there's two real conversations that we're having about this.
One is about the so-called good male scam, which I'm just going to call a scam.
The other one is about, well, really stems from this interview on Heather Green's podcast
at Business Week, where the CEO of SBC, AT&T, was pretty emotional about saying that he was pissed off.
He really felt he was unparafraising now, but he was pissed off that Google is using their pipes to make all this money.
That's really what it came down to.
Now, there are some very good points to be made about different types of traffic that run over the internet.
And I had asked for experts to chime in.
And here is one that, the first time it came in, it was, well, actually, you know what?
I think he explains it in the beginning, listen in.
Hello, Adam. This is Mark Milliman.
I apologize for the poor quality of my last message to you.
Hopefully, this will sound much better than getting the hang of cast blaster.
Also, I'd like to give my appreciation to all of the podcasters out there, including yourself.
I've really found what a challenging job it is to put out a high-quality podcast consistently day after day after day.
I can't even get this little note out.
I'm trying to understand how long it takes you guys to get these shows done that you will put out there for us.
So, thanks again, and keep it up.
All right, so here comes his comment.
This is a good one, listen in.
Hello, Adam.
lately there's been several misconceptions in the internet press, as well as two listeners of the Charlie,
including yourself concerning the R-Box desire to charge for prioritizing packets, the right over their backbone, and their access services.
This conception one is that they're doing it to reduce spam.
This is false.
That is a separate issue entirely.
It should be addressed as a separate form.
Okay, so we agree on that.
This has nothing to do with the good mail scam and with spam.
This is about the, I was almost a threat that AT&T SBC says, hey, we're going to start charging companies for pushing this data down the pipe.
And it doesn't even, well, I don't know if they're talking about large data or not.
Google doesn't seem like there's large amounts of data being requested on an individual basis.
On aggregate, of course, it is big.
So this is more about that particular statement.
This conception number two is that they're doing it to control the content that runs over their backbone.
Before you, well, I'll listen what you say first.
Probably false.
And the reason I say probably is the fact that two executives from the two largest Starbucks in North America
make some very public statements concerning this exact issue.
Truth be told, their true intent is to provide priority for packets that travel through their back bones and through their access.
Okay, so let me just say one thing there.
I don't believe that this is about controlling the content either.
I believe it's just purely based on jealousy and the jealousy or envy may be a better word.
And this is not new.
This is the same thing that happened with the cable networks.
I remember, man, 10, 15 years ago, the cable networks.
These guys thought that they were NBC and then they started charging for access and creating their own special channels.
Let's be honest, everything at the cable company does themselves when it comes to media and entertainment pretty much sucks.
Because we call them trench diggers.
They dig trenches and pull cables and connect you up.
The DNA of these companies, any telco, is not media and entertainment.
So I think that they're just looking at their investment and saying, oh shit, man.
We spent a couple billion dollars.
The grant it wasn't their own money.
A couple billion dollars.
And we're getting some pretty predictable returns on this stuff.
And why everyone seems to be using it more and look at these Google fuckers.
There were $100 billion dollars.
See, they're a boxer in a unique position because they provide both the pipe and distribute content over it.
They know the providing the pipe is somewhat a commodity service and full of competition.
And they also know the providing or distributing content is highly lucrative and very profitable.
So they would like to also distribute the content exactly what I said.
Now, because they have both the pipe and distribute the content, they can also control the complete user experience and provide a higher quality user experience.
Then third party providers don't provide the pipe.
By the way, they have another advantage is they already have an existing billing relationship with the end user, which is not to be underestimated.
But they also know from past experiences when they give preference to their own content distribution.
They get hauled in front of Congress and for the FCC for being anti-competitive.
Not just that, but their own content sucks ass.
They are creating the ability for third party service providers to pay for priority traffic to run over their internet pipes.
Now, all packets are not created equal.
And that's a good thing.
Because streaming packets that for IPTV and VoIP are very time sensitive, whereas browsing the internet, doing internet searches, getting email, or even downloading the Charlie, is not time sensitive.
Well, hold on a second.
I mean, if you can't get the Charlie, you'd be Jones and Pretty Bad, my friend.
It doesn't matter if your web search takes a half a second longer.
But it does matter if your VoIP call packets get three to half a second, because that will drop the call.
So, third party service providers can now pay a little bit extra to have this packets expressly routed through these backbones and internet access pipes.
And for $5 a month extra, I'd gladly pay that to VoIP provider.
So, I can guarantee that I have fewer job calls, less echo, and higher quality conversation.
Wouldn't you?
Same thing with streaming video content.
I'll tell you, make a lot of DRM issues go away if we could stream everything reliably.
And throwing bandwidth at the problem is not an issue.
So, I hope that this lays some of the misconceptions concerning this issues.
And we all welcome this with open arms.
And also pay attention to safeguards that need to be in place to prevent them from abusing this, should they choose to in the future.
Thanks a lot, Adam.
Take care.
Bye.
All right. Well, I really appreciate the feedback.
And first of all, I obviously understand and agree that having some version of quality of service is very important when it comes to, you know, having connections that really are guaranteed to work.
So, voice over IP.
Yeah, of course, I want my phone calls to be better. That makes a lot of sense.
You know what? And one explained in this manner, and you know, maybe you do want a really, really fat pipe for your, for your Xbox live experience.
And that would really make it into an experience.
I can kind of get into it, but I'm, you know, just the way it was communicated if anything.
You know, the telcos need some PR help, man, because they get, they really rely on everyone up with this talk, you know, and it gets miscommunicated and then typical copy-paste culture format.
You know, everyone starts just adding a little bit of, of nastiness on top as the message gets passed around before you know it.
We all hate the telcos.
But it is very interesting because, and I've had long conversations at the office about this.
People watch them harder than I am. Because, you know, it does put them in a very, very interesting, well, they already are in a very interesting spot in our food chain, you know, all of our content rolls through their pipes.
They do have the ability to, I mean, already, the big telcos are doing all kinds of stuff to traffic, and, you know, particularly when it gets down to the ISP level, if they happen to own the ISP, there's, you know, all kinds of restrictions and port blockage.
And you name it, you know, and part of that is because it just got out of control.
Man, we're seeing all kinds of denial of service attacks currently on several of our servers and, you know, what are you going to do?
It's just an ongoing battle. It seems to be the cost of doing business. And if we could get some help on that, I wouldn't mind paying some extra.
Oh, God. Oh, it's, I need some help. Somebody please. Oh, it's Angie.
So I'm pretty excited to find that you guys are rolling the Podsafe Music Network into the podcast delivery network.
So we have one super site to go to and log in now.
Let me just clarify a couple of things Angie's talking about here.
Rolling in may not be the right word. It'll still be accessible as the music as the Podsafe Music Network.
But if you use the Pod Show podcast delivery network, the integration will become a lot easier. That's for sure.
That should make things a lot easier for us, shouldn't it?
And of course, we'll have APIs for anyone to integrate that into anything they want to.
There's a couple of things that I'm hoping developers are working on for the full launch of the PMN.
Namely, I would really love to see.
Hey Chris Rockwell, you're listening to this is about you.
An album titled Field Added In and release date added in.
I use this information when I'm announcing tracks and I would sure like to be able to stop Googling that and just have it automatically.
And as an artist, I want people to know where they can buy the songs that they like.
They kind of need to know what CD it's on.
Also, I'd love to be able to order the songs so we can put the newest at the top or the most popular at the top.
And I would love to have a longer description field for the artists because you can't say much in the teeny tiny box that's on there right now.
And you wait until you see what we're going to trick this baby.
So we're going to trick it out so bad.
It's going to be all of those things you've been looking for.
And you'll have to give us a couple of weeks to ramp up.
There's a lot of integration stuff merging of data bases and all kinds of technical things, but everything's up until now everything you said is on the list.
Finally, as a band, I would feel a little bit more comfortable if we had the option of setting only like a 30 second clip from songs.
I'm just a little nervous putting like every song from my two CDs up for the podcast.
I know that the listeners have access to the full song through the PMN.
And there's all that software out there that allows you to rip audio directly off of websites.
So, Angie, Angie, you have little faith.
Please.
This is where it breaks down for me.
Look, this is an unlabel.
Okay.
First of all, I don't think that you would even want to put all of your songs up on the PMN.
But not as, you know, for marketing purposes, perhaps.
But I think that there's a, you have to kind of figure out the ratio and what you do.
It's kind of, it's nothing out of the ordinary of what radio or MTV you're doing.
You release a, what used to be called a single, which of course is not really released as a single anymore, but is released as a part of a CD or a part of an album.
And that's really the promotional piece.
And then, you know, we can buy love spirals on through CD, baby, I think.
So it should be seen as a promotion if someone wants more than they can easily go buy the CD.
Thirty-second clips just don't do it for me.
It really doesn't.
That's, you know, that's the iTunes experience.
And the only reason iTunes does it is for exactly the reason that you mention because they have DRM,
which means you can, you know, make copies of this, where you can make copies for yourself.
I think five copies or five different machines is what it's limited to.
But the reason I don't make full previews available, of course, is because it's very easy with software as you mentioned to go and rip it off.
But here's what's happening.
This is not about a controlled area, you know, where people, there's so many different ways to rip off songs.
You could either, but this is a ton of ways to do it.
It's really, really simple to steal stuff from Pods' music network or anywhere, really.
And never pay for it.
But what we're seeing, and hopefully, I'll get an update today on our strong mail situation.
If the emails are working, I think they were testing, yes, they have to noon in the last night.
We're going to open up sales, so anyone can make as many tracks as they want available for purchase on the Pods' music network.
You'll see that this is an exercise in humanity, okay?
This is more about consumers for the first time proving that we're not thieves, okay?
And Angie really has much as I love you.
You know, you're already supposing that there are thieves out there in the audience.
And guess what?
There are absolutely, but I truly believe, and we're already seeing in our Alpha Beta Zeta test of the couple songs that are for sale on PMN,
that people are very happy to go in and support the artists, because it's not really about buying it.
It's a shit about 99 cents, and that's not the big deal, the big deal is about supporting the artist.
And I think that that's really what, it's the same thing with software.
You know, there's no difference in my mind between a zip file or an EXE file or an MP3 file,
except in the runtime and how it's used, the actual data.
And you've got to put stuff out there, that's the only way it works, it really is.
So while I understand that you're nervous about it, let's give it a try.
Okay, don't put all your tracks up, but make your tracks available for purchase, as soon as we go live with that stuff.
And I'll ping you to make sure that you know and get you any help, which I don't think can need because all it is is just checking a box.
It's 30 second clip, no harm, no foul.
Anyways, looking forward to seeing the full lunch, you know, I'm gonna be right there.
Checking out tracks for, hey, here comes a promo, chillcast.podshow.com and to be signing out.
Oh, the toss at tones of Angie B.
Hey, I'm Russell from Darkman's podcast here again.
Just a quick one this time, just let you know that I'm a papers head five of Darkman's and I've just got my first response from a PMN artist that I've been playing.
But gone from the problem, didn't know you in birds.
There's replied saying thanks for playing and sent me a ID for my shower along with it.
So I just thought that was great from him and I hope that the other PMN artists are as equally good at acknowledging when podcasts are playing their music because I think I think podcasts will appreciate the feedback.
I know I certainly do.
Yeah, that's all catching next time.
That's really how the whole unlabel thing comes together.
Again, it's an experiment in humanity and you know, I got to say that there's probably not a song that I've played on the source code that I don't get a personal email from the artist from the band thanking me for playing it.
And I always reply kind of in the same manner.
It's like, you know, just keep on bringing the cool tunes.
That's all I want. That's all that it's about.
And this is how we promote podcasting.
This is how we promote independent music by working together.
And it's the podcasts, it's the artists, and it's the listeners.
And you know what? It's freaking working.
So my video, which I may release today, was cut to this track.
Listen to the words. I think you'll understand.
Everything I need.
Better than the old dead frequency from underground.
Who've done the sound?
Come set the fire, burn the old dial.
Time is now.
You are never alone.
All I know is a drum.
Can't stand the thought of all the same.
And you are wasted.
You've been brought to the bone.
It's like, when you call you into show.
And you're in the same.
The same, it's like you're wasted.
And you're not able to take it over.
You can't find people taking it over.
And you're not even taking it over.
And you're not able to take it over.
We're in control, everywhere you go
Once we start to flow, you're in the know
Let the police see each other, it's not the lead
Suck away the green, break out the beach
The parade for free, kill the radio crew
You are never known, all I know
But the crown can't stand a daughter
For the tag that you have wasted
You've been brought to the moon
Save me all you've been shown
You've been the fucking tag
Time that you have wasted
I keep on taking a lie
The invasion is coming closer
But the invasion is coming closer
I keep on taking a lie
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
monk, as I said from the Podsate Music Network.
Just one last thing before I go, I posted something
at the end of the day yesterday, San Francisco time about
creative comments and about a comment I had made earlier.
And let me just elaborate on that a little bit because I found
time and time again that writing just doesn't work for me.
Whatever I write, I'm just a bad writer.
It usually gets misconstrued to the words,
good, and overanalyze, and picked apart, and then before you
confusion, which is really why I like audio so much more as my medium.
And let me just give you the genesis of a real quick.
As the lawsuit against the Gossip Mag started to heat up,
and we're getting closer to the date,
actually even before I filed the lawsuit,
I'd reached out to creative comments to Lawrence Lessick
personally, actually that came through,
it actually the introduction or the raising of the issue
was done by a student of his.
That's how it all came together.
Now just to make a very long story short,
I felt that there wasn't a lot of help that creative comments
had to offer for me.
Although I think I misappropriate or misrepresented that
the absolutely did certainly Lawrence Lessick said,
hey, let me know if there's anything I can do.
So there really wasn't anything that can be done.
I just wanted some open communication.
And I didn't really need creative comments help,
so I don't need any financial help for bringing the lawsuit.
But just kind of got me at an emotional level.
You have to understand that in the Netherlands,
whenever I do anything,
I'm always ridiculed for it.
And there may be reasons for that, too.
But the press was extremely mean and hateful
about this, of course, I was suing the press.
So what does the press do?
They jump all over someone when they want to make waves.
And there is a Dutch chapter of Creative Commons.
As I now know, it's volunteers and it's maybe a little less organized
than I thought it was.
And I didn't hear a peep from them.
Not a word, not a single hay.
There's something important coming up,
nothing on their weblog, nothing in the press.
And then after the lawsuit, I hadn't still had not,
I actually sent a professor, a link and said,
hey, I posted, here's the judgment.
Here's what's going on.
And he said, okay, I'll take a look at it.
Didn't hear back from him.
And so the next message I saw was this press release,
including the director or manager,
whatever of the Dutch chapter of Creative Commons,
saying, well, isn't this great?
You know, it was a fantastic for Creative Commons.
And this is all good news.
And Yipity, hey, and I'm like, you want a fucker.
You know, where was the backup?
And it felt so typical.
It actually felt very typically Dutch to me.
Because this is almost cultural.
It's like, oh, I'm not going to say anything.
But oh, you know, the war is over.
We're all going to jump out and rejoice.
And so it just piss me off.
And I wrote a piece on my weblog,
which kind of mischaracterized the relationships.
So it had some email back and forth with Lawrence.
It's funny.
We had more email about that than about the whole case itself.
And I just called it out and said, look, my bad.
I was emotional.
But, you know, what do you guys do?
What does the whole point of Creative Commons?
You know, where was the voice behind me?
I just didn't feel like I got any backup.
And so, you know, everyone kind of copped to all the mistakes they had made.
And really, we said, hey, this is a learning experience.
And let's figure out how we can make it easier for the next time.
Something like this comes along for someone else.
And so I just want to read this email that Lawrence sent to me.
Although it's belated, unfortunately framed.
Thank you for doing what you did.
There are very few who do things that really benefit the public far more than they could ever benefit from themselves.
That's what you do here.
I can express adequately how happy I was when I saw you were going to do what you did.
I was extremely eager to help as I had long hoped we might be able to conspire more closely.
And earlier efforts to reach out hadn't seemed to connect.
Wow, man.
That's, I don't know what that is.
I don't, not quite sure what he means.
But email in general is just a shitty way to connect when it comes to stuff like the hate email.
Anyway, Lawrence goes on, I read perhaps incorrectly a desire to keep distance and control in this case.
So I didn't push it.
See, that's where that's where weblogged postings and stuff just doesn't connect.
I didn't want to keep any distance or control.
I just wanted some backing and some voices out there that could help me out because there were very few voices pushing for me.
So that was just a total human error miscommunication on both sides, obviously.
Lawrence says I'm just happy it ended in a way that made principle clear.
Right on, your story makes me think we should raise a defense fund that we keep set aside for people in your circumstance.
Legal rules limit what we can do in that regard, surprise surprise.
But it might make sense for both the movement and individuals to create a common defense fund.
If you'd be up for suggesting it, I'd be happy to take the idea.
Yeah, I think it's a good idea.
But maybe it should be not in a monetary form, but it should be in a form of assistance.
So I could contribute, if I were a lawyer, I could contribute some hours, which, of course, is directly relatable to money.
But, you know, some lawyers actually have a quota of pro bono work.
They want to fill up that could be one way.
I'd be very happy to testify or do anything that I could do.
I'd contribute my time that way.
And really I think what we need is kind of like an FAQ of exactly what an organization like Creative Commons can do.
And again, I wasn't looking for financial help and it still seems like perhaps Larry thought that's what I was talking about.
But I was really just talking about some backing, you know, just some more voices out there in the blogger sphere,
while I was attacking the problem and not only after the fact.
So I think in general, this whole situation has been really, really good.
Good for Creative Commons, good for the intellectual property rights of individual creative people who are using the internet
as their distribution, medium and vehicle.
But it's also been good as we learn more about how we should be working together and what Creative Commons does
and how it can be utilized to strengthen our position in the Creative landscape even more.
So I'm really happy we worked all of that out and, you know, it's just just so ironic.
Web logs and everything sometimes make it much, much more complicated.
Alright everybody, that's it for today's show.
I'll be back tomorrow.
We'll be over the hump and I'll be, I'll go to bed even earlier.
So I'll be even more coherent.
Another pod show pod guest.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this pod guest and we're great ones like it.
On the high performance pod cast of Libri Network from Podjo and line white networks.
I love it.