Hey, this is Dan Patterson from the Creepy Sleepy Show.
You want creepy without the sleepy?
Check out Shadow Falls, Pod Show's brand new audio drama series.
It's terrifying.
Terrifying.
This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 4-4-0.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
It's time I'm gonna need you to keep top the margin.
Snap, snap, snap your fingers for me.
Good good now we're making some progress.
Come on, just top, top, top your top to the beat.
And now I believe this may call for a proper introduction.
Well, don't you see?
I'm a narrator and this is the floor.
I'm a narrator, this is the floor.
And I got the disco, the only difference between martyr-derman suicide is press coverage.
Ain't that the truth?
Newspapers around the globe plastered today on the front pages with the news of the
thwarted part terrorist plot to blow up planes from the United Kingdom to the U.S.
This shit has got to stop.
And I think I got some solutions for this.
First of all, this is what has happened right now, of course, nothing happened.
And I think we should be grateful nothing happened.
But I still would like a little bit more information about what was really planned.
I mean, all these stories of now we have liquid bombs.
If we didn't have dirty bombs, which were supposedly briefcase, nukes that are supposed
to go off all over the world, this has been the discussion for the past five to 10 years.
Now we have the liquid bombs, which can be carried in, they'd be formula bottles and detonated
with iPods.
We are so out of control right now that I'm still taking my shoes off at airport security
for some guy who had some matches in his shoe or something that was supposed to explode,
which didn't.
And that was also a very unclear story.
And we're still taking our shoes off for that.
So for the unforeseeable future, there will be nothing on the plane, nothing except the
inflight entertainment.
You want to be able to bring your own headphones because of course the liquid gel could
be explosive.
You know, what'll happen next is some guy is going to get caught with a stick of dynamite
shoved up his ass and then we'll all be subject to cavity searches and flying naked.
Actually, it's not such a bad thing.
It could be kind of interesting.
But you know what I'm saying?
Was it John of Kennedy who said the only thing we have to fear is fear itself?
We really got a grip, got a grip on ourselves right now about this.
And I have some ideas.
I couldn't get this leave last night.
I was thinking about how can we solve this terrorist issue?
One thing that's, what do I hear in the background?
Is regular sounds of the affluent suburb of Surrey and Gilford?
What can we do to actually stop this?
You know, security is just not going to work.
The example I gave you is not that far fetched.
You can't.
You just can't live a 100% secure life.
It's impossible.
Airlines can't be responsible for that.
It cannot deliver on that type of promise.
And people are really freaked out about this.
Are they even calling me?
Hey, Adam, it's Carmen Tyler.
You know, when I was watching the news this morning, I kept thinking, oh my gosh, you know,
how crazy is this?
So I was really concerned about all my friends in the UK.
And I just want to tell you to please, please, please, stay safe.
Only fly if you have to, obviously.
And of course, don't take any liquids of whatsoever.
So I just wanted to tell you that, to stay safe.
And just knowing that, you know, we have people all of the place thinking about to you
and praying for you and hoping that everyone over there, all my friends, you know, that
everyone's safe.
And hopefully, I can get these people who are doing this and trying to plan these crazy
things.
But again, just stay safe.
Oh, Carmen.
That's so sweet of you.
And I really do appreciate it.
And I can just, can you just tell by the sound and a voice that she's really freaked
out about this?
Don't get freaked out.
If I had to go to San Francisco today, I'd get on the plane no problem.
I would get on the plane yesterday.
I will get on any plane at any time.
I've really changed my attitude about this.
First of all, it seems that our security services are working quite fine, although the
new Scotland yard has had a couple of bumbles recently, picking up terrorists who turn out
not to be terrorists at all, which doesn't help.
I think really, it, as incredible as it may sound, I believe that Hollywood can actually
solve this problem.
You see, I don't know, I'm only going by what I have in the newspapers, and I guess there
has to be some semblance of truth in them.
Apparently of the 24 people they arrested, most of them were British.
One of them even prominently featured on the fine tabloid the sun.
Only just recently converted to Islam six months ago.
And of course, he was a very nice boy.
And the neighbors never suspected anything.
And we still don't know if he actually did anything, and we know very little actually
about what actually went down, although we got some pretty strong big words from George
Bush and from officials here in the United Kingdom that this was a plot for unprecedented
loss of life.
I mean, it's pretty scary stuff, you know, so the follow-up better be pretty damn good and
better be pretty quick, because if you're making these claims about how horrible it was,
I really want to see some evidence of that.
And swiftly, please, because otherwise you're just prolonging this fear effect and I don't
like that at all, because I don't like being scared, and I'm not scared, you cannot be
scared of these things, and then you can't live your life, because the trash can next
you could blow up.
The train could blow up.
You know, this is the whole point of terrorism, okay?
And we're really propagating it a little bit too much without enough information to back
it up.
Okay.
So that said, I think Hollywood can save us.
I really, really do.
What we need here is some influence, and one of my talking about religion, of course, has
been used throughout history to kill people.
It's been used quite effectively, and all kinds of religion, probably every single religion
at one point has been used or misused in war or as a reason to kill people.
Now why is this happening apparently with why is the religion the faith of Islam being
used for this?
Well, because there's not enough challenging information, I would say.
I mean, if you have some wise man who has studied your religion, I'm just going to leave
it religion as not agnostic, actually, it seems a lot easier, because it could be used for
any religion.
Anyone could be motivated to this through religion.
You know, you've got antique books and scriptures and history that goes back thousands
of years and interpretation, and it's very easy, very, very easy to influence someone
to do something fucked up.
It's not that hard to do.
So we need some countermeasures here.
We really do.
And I think we need an illusion on a grand scale because look, you know, if you do something
wrong, in the world, let's put it this way.
In the world, there's always someone who's going to go record up for everybody else.
And does it matter if you're in kindergarten, if you're in grade school, if you're in the
work force, if you're in government, it doesn't matter.
There's always someone who's there to fuck it up.
Always someone is going to do something to mess up everybody else's game.
That I think is just human nature.
You're not going to stop that.
Why do people stop or why is it a small amount of people is because there's something,
but there's some penalty that is above you.
And the penalty is, you know, the teacher's going to kick your ass, you get sent to the
principal's office, you'll get fired, you can go to jail.
I mean, we have all these things that up in society, but when it comes to, this is what
your God has told you to do, well, you know, what's the consequence for not doing it?
Neal Dixon is escaping me.
Neal, I'm recording, stop it.
Excuse me.
Senseioh, brought to you by Bridecaster.com.
So, you know, there is no visible or known consequence for going against your God.
So what if Hollywood had God speak to everyone, and it could be your own God, it could
be God, it could be Allah, it could be Buddha, it could be whatever, you know, I'm thinking
very much along the lines of, well, like walking on the moon, and of course, we all know
we didn't actually walk on the moon, but we all believe it because we have great pictures
of it.
I'm one of those guys, indeed.
There's so many different examples of things that really aren't proven, but have been
proven to people because they sought with their own eyes, they think, but they really
sought through television or read it in the newspaper or heard about it on the radio.
So why don't we bring together like Spielberg and Copperfield, and instead of the propagating
the myth that if you become a martyr and in this one particular instance, again, trying
to be as agnostic as possible, but right now we're talking about how Islam is being misused.
So instead of propagating the, who knows, it may even be truth, you might get 42 versions
if you become a martyr, I don't know, but we've got to create some kind of offensive
here.
There's no amount of weaponry, there's no amount of security that is actually going
to stop anyone from doing this.
So we've got to have God's peak.
We can make this happen.
We could have a real illusion.
We've done it before, like JFK.
We all know we got off by the CIA, no one can prove it, so we had the capability, certainly
the United States and that it came together, have enough governmental talent and creative
talent to put together this high, this very high illusion.
The basically says, hey, if you think that the message you'll get 42 versions is right,
think again, you know, don't go blowing up airplanes, don't go blowing up people, don't
go killing people because you wind up in hell, that's the only message we have to have
some kind of counterbalance, and a part of that by the way, might be to put a lot more
learning about all religion on, on television, BBC, do more about it.
We need some counterbalance here.
We've got guys who look old and wise and who have Xbox 360s to keep you busy when they're
not preaching, preaching nasty religious stuff to you, that got him hypnotizing kids.
So we've got to hypnotize them back, we've got to use what we have.
It can be done.
Think about it.
Don't just scoff at me, think about it, there is no other solution, but to counterbalance
the message that is being sent about what happens to you if you become a martyr.
Where's Copperfield's number?
I'm going to call myself.
Today's true world of business and leisure travel, you need someone who can show you
the ropes.
I'm Matthew Holden, and I travel to a different country every week, and I share the good,
and they're not so good of my travel experiences.
Call him aboard and subscribe to Pad Asia.net today.
Listen and learn from Matthew and the team about how to get the most from your travel.
Pad Asia.net is a free weekly travel and leisure podcast for business or leisure travelers
and brings you in valuable travel tips and information.
Subscribe today to Pad Asia.net.
You can find Pad Asia podcast online at Apple iTunes, music store, or Pad Asia.net.
For what you need to make your travels easier.
Pad Asia.net podcast.
And are the Asia.net.
Hey Adam, David Ipolito here, that guitarman from Central Park.
Yes, I am doing a podcast.
It's called, I love the company.
People can find it at thatcontarman.com.
I just got to say, I'm so glad you got that $16 million worth of airplane
strapped to your ass, because I'm a little different.
This is a new song I'm working on.
I got a piece of wood and six string strapped to my shoulder.
But listen, you know any artist that I find on the Podsake music network
and I've found a lot of great artists for the podcast.
If I dig it, man, I'll play it.
And if any of them are coming through New York City, tell them to give me a shout
because I will have them sit in as my guest artist in Central Park
or down on pure 45 or American concert hall.
Introduce them to a whole new audience.
It's getting to be a very small campus man and thank you.
Thank you for what you're doing.
By the way, you're not the first person that I heard you the other day on the source
quotes.
It's a guitar dude.
It's a guitar guy.
It's guitar man.
But I've been called all kinds of things.
Even the James Taylor guy.
So I had a write a song about it.
I'll send it off to you.
David, I actually apologized because that was a completely
insensitive of me and I should have known better.
And of course, it all would have taken us from me to just look at a website
to know that it was that guitar man.com.
Because I have always kind of detested being that MTV guy
or like the big haired fact stuff like that.
So I can make up by playing that song that you sent me.
I love it though.
Through my nose, David.
That guitar man.
When I open up my mouth to sing something happens to my voice.
Something that I can't explain.
It's really not by choice.
Imitating other artists.
It's not what I'm about.
But when I open up my mouth sometimes.
Somebody else pops out.
I don't mean to do it.
It's kind of silly I suppose.
But when I sing James Taylor songs,
I just start singing through my nose.
Imagine sounding like jumping in.
I'm sure the Julian can relate.
I dreamt I didn't sound like me.
Although I think me a young's great.
I sing low like new diamond.
When I sing sweet Caroline.
And when I sing like Paul Simon,
people seem to like it fine.
But I don't mean to do it.
It's a talent I suppose.
Like when I sing James Taylor songs,
I just start singing through my nose.
Sometimes I'm Jimmy Buffett.
When I sing a key where song.
I can sound like Barry Manelow.
But that's just sick and wrong.
I get tangled up and dealing.
I'm Charlie Daniel's southern draw.
Or even William Shattner when I pause for no reason at all.
But I don't mean to do it.
I'm an asshole I suppose.
And when I sing James Taylor songs,
I just start singing through my nose.
That guitarman calm.
David E. Polito.
Through my nose.
Short sweet and very mental.
Very to the point.
A portion of the show brought to you by the new AccurRDX.
They have a target cast.
Which is not a podcast.
Trying, you know, it's not a,
I was like, what's the one post over there?
Oh, a parking from from the UK from London.
He said, oh, it's another advertisement posing as a podcast.
No, dude.
It's a target cast.
It actually says it's like an info commercial.
Only I think it's really good.
If you go listen to it,
you'll hear that there's some real information in there.
If you're interested,
if you're not that target cast is not for you.
It's only for people who are interested.
So if you're not interested in buying an SUV,
if you're not interested in AccurRD.
If you're not interested in learning about the surround sound system,
if you want to hear Grammy award winning producer,
how he was involved in the design of that system,
then go and listen to AccurRDX.
More people sending in comments about the new fear terror in the skies.
Hey, Adam John here,
lawyer listener from nearby send in the affluent several of us.
Sorry.
More time listener.
I don't have my own podcast.
I'm a scruncher.
But thought I would give you a tip with no MP3s or laptops
going in any of the intercontinental flights.
These days,
he throw you out of talk to B.A.
about making sure that the daily source code is on there.
In flight entertainment,
because there's a lot of people that are going to be bombed out
and without their daily source code to listen to you on their long flights.
So that'd be a really good source entertainment.
I get in touch.
Thanks, man.
Great.
Well, thank you.
Well, you know what's going to happen now is people are going to actually use the
in flight entertainment to find out how incredibly lame it is.
Although I must say on Virgin,
they've got good movies.
They refresh those every month, so that works for me.
But you watch people saying,
yeah, I actually listen to that in flight entertainment.
Socks ass.
Where's my iPod?
You mean that detonation device you have?
Not just regular ass listeners affected,
but some regulars as well.
Comics trip.
Hiya.
Adam Kerry.
Here's comics to a blogger from comicsstripblock.com.
I must admit something.
I have been defeated by terrorists.
Why?
Well, I had etiquettes from for a visit from Germany.
Let me just translate because I had listened to it three times.
He says he's been affected by terrorists because he had a ticket to visit the UK from Germany.
London.
Already paid for this weekend.
Outbound flight was on August 12th.
One Saturday, but I can't set my flights.
And the visit to London.
Due to the hate and security at UK airports that resulted from the massive terrorist attack
that was just prevented by British police.
I would like you to tell me.
What do you think?
What do you see?
Listen as think.
Was it correct behavior on my path to cancel the visit this weekend to London?
Basically for tourist purposes.
Due to the situation on British airports.
From my excuse, I can say that I have read that BBC such messages like, for example,
passengers have been urged to contact their airlines and not travel unless it is absolutely necessary.
So I fought it by consolation.
I would not exasperate the situation.
But I feel defeated, I feel bad.
Some even say to me, some things like,
no, you idiot.
You did a wrong thing.
People like you are giving the terrorist exactly what they want.
So you do.
I think cancel my visit to London this weekend.
Yeah.
Poor CSB.
Well, you got to do what you got to do.
I think that it will probably help with congestion because everything is pretty messed up right now.
So that will help somewhat.
So I think that's why they're saying it.
It's not only travel if you absolutely have to.
And if you didn't have to, you don't have to.
There's no big deal there.
But of course, you're giving terrorists exactly what they want them out of where these terrorists are from.
Fear of fear itself is what it comes down to.
And quite honestly, I think that if, you know, I'm an American, you know that.
I also feel very European.
Soon I'll be an official resident.
Well, I already official resident in the European Union.
I guess that's senseless.
But I feel that if we can send troops over anywhere in the world.
I don't care what they're fighting for.
They're obviously fighting on our behalf.
Then I can take my my shots as well.
So I would get on the plane for sure.
This of course is my mother-in-law who is calling.
And my mother-in-law has the habit of letting the phone ring for about 50 rings.
I'm just not going to leave my studio here.
What I will do is tell all the folks on Syria satellite or who are listening to Syria satellite.
Stars 102 that we've got a great lineup for your Friday evening.
Of course, so we hear every weekday afternoon from 6 to 10 Eastern PM.
Up next we've got Pacific Coast Hallway followed by Don and Drew.
Then in over your head, we should talk rather third.
The scenes in East Radio at 9 o'clock and winding up with Scott Sigler.
And I'll see you all on Monday.
And the phone will probably still be ringing.
Hey, what timing it stopped?
Uh, hold on a second.
That's something that else I wanted to say about that.
Anyway, if you want to call in, happy to hear from you.
The voicemail numbers put it in yourself on now plus 1, 2, 0, 1, 6, 2, 5, 6, 3, 5, 7, rewind.
Plus 1, 2, 0, 1, 6, 2, 5, 6, 3, 5, 7, 9 or if you prefer and you're in London.
It's easier for you, 0, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3.
I've been asking you to call in, tell me about yourself.
Wanted to learn about our listeners.
I have to say, I think that the average age of the daily source code listener is hovering around
30 years old, which is very interesting.
A lot of people who are in technology.
Of course, the women are always holding them back and women never want to call in.
I know you're out there.
Give me some more calls if you don't mind.
And of course, when you call in, just let me know.
And obviously, I can't play all of these on the show.
But, you know, I love hearing who you are.
And I'm adjusting the show towards what you want and where you listen to it.
So the more information you tell me, it really is, it's better.
Hopefully, it just make a better show for you.
So, you know, include all the pertinent information, like your age, where you're from,
when you listen to the show, maybe what other shows you listen to.
And, of course, if you're a scruncher or folder.
Hey Adam, this is Audra from Conqueror, New Hampshire 31.
I've been listening to you since, let's see, last, last, last May.
So over here now, enjoy the show.
Let's see, I owe my own business.
I have two free children and I'm a folder.
Thanks.
Right now?
Of course you're a folder.
Excuse me, gastronomic.
It's a more I'm going to go flying.
I'm going to go practice on my landings.
As the only part, I still got to kind of work on.
So Captain Dan and I are going to a couple of grass strips.
So I can't smoke the tires too badly, because that just gets really expensive, dude.
So that'll be on tomorrow's schedule.
I think the Patricia and her sister have something planned for Sunday.
And then on Monday, I hope to get them both on the show.
So we can, yeah, about have some fun.
Oh, hi, Adam.
May is column.
So again, let's go back for a whole event.
I'm listening to DSC for 39.
And I don't say off taking your advice to Google,
I'm going to participate in Google images.
I'm going to 16 year old, but very happy.
Thanks.
Bye.
Uh-huh.
And the pictures you saw are probably the ones that she made for Playboy Magazine.
When she was 50 years old, five years old.
She was on the cover of Playboy, the Dutch Playboy, four times.
I think when she was like 28 or something, she was also in the US Playboy.
But indeed, just Google Patricia Pi, Papa Alpha Alpha Yankee,
you will not be disappointed.
Hi, Adam.
Ten Elliott.
They're going to be forward up.
Hey, I was listening to DSC for 34.
And you mentioned the book on marketing.
One of the best pieces of marketing advice I've ever heard is
Quit trying to market the groups.
If you want to market to architect pick one architect that you know
and solve his problems.
Because often times, we as a market group represent a large number of people who
have the same type of problems for doing the same type of work.
If you take a market group and that in which half of the people are hot and
half of the people are cold and you design something where the temperatures
in between, you get half of the people who are too cold and half of the
people that are too hot and therefore the product is acceptable to nobody.
Keep up the good work, dude.
Stay dangerous.
Folder.
Excellent.
Yeah.
Thanks, man.
Well, you know, that's exactly what we've been doing.
And it hasn't been pleasing the podcast community too much because
people are used to doing things a certain way that you see certain elements
and we've been working on our, on our stuff, podshow plus for listeners.
And so we've picked listeners that we're trying to delight.
And of course, we're there for also not delighting or in fact even
confusing other groups of people.
Hello, Adam.
Paul Nichols here.
Podcast Paul.
And I'm just a few very quick things.
The first thing is podshow plus I really do like the idea of the thing.
But I'm a complete techno-thobe, not techno-thobe.
I can't, I just don't understand anything really.
I don't know.
There's an F.A. Cube that that would do it doesn't mean anything to me
to be honest.
Have you got like a complete idiot sky to it, please?
And what's this feed vacuum thing?
I can just about turn on the proper vacuum.
I can't even work out how to fix in the attachments.
But that's another story.
And, oh yes, I'm a 38-year-old male from Birmingham.
Married with four kids or boys.
And I'm neither a folder or a scruncher.
I am a rapper.
I don't mean one of those nice blokes that rhymes his lingo.
And with Doctor, I sort of wrap it around, I think, three fingers.
I actually thought about that a little bit as I was laughing me bum.
I mean, I really think of that idea.
But much more important than that.
Are you a standard or are you a sister?
In fact, this is always in trouble.
Oh, hold on a second.
I really liked that.
There was a gem hidden in there.
It does work this stuff, you know.
So what is the point of this folder scruncher?
The point is, everyone does it.
Everyone does one version or the other.
And exactly what I hoped would happen is now starting to happen
when he was wiping his bum.
No, it's so proper the way he said it.
He was thinking of the daily source code.
That would be the whole point of the answer to that.
Because you can't really ask many people.
Can you call or go to them as you set the water cooler and say,
how exactly do you want me back inside John?
Because that give you a strange look.
But we can talk about it and it can't be.
It's the done thing.
I'm a rugby player.
So I've got big tackle, if you know what I mean.
And I can't really understand the logistics of if you're a sitter.
How do you do that to you?
Give yourself a half now.
Some by going around the back or, well, there's no space to go around the front.
Another more wife is a sitter.
But like I said, she has a rugby tackle.
But anyways, some standar legs apart and stay together slightly.
If that means anything to you.
Just imagine the Ministry of Civil War.
If you know the faulty towers, sketch or other issues,
you should say multi python.
Anyway, this comment is brought to you not by my show.
So I'm not going to promote that.
But the absolutely fantastic Lynn Parsons red light zone.
And if you haven't heard it, it is absolutely blooming brilliant.
Really, really love it.
Okay, all the best mates.
See ya.
Bye.
Yo dude.
Oh, what's this?
Extra audio.
All right.
Yo man.
Yeah, I'll tell you just because you ask.
I'm a sitter.
But that's not important.
I think we just leave it at scrunching and folding.
It's innocent enough.
It doesn't gross you out too much.
And whenever you're folding or scrunching,
either way is good.
Just thinking of me.
And that's what it's really all about.
There's a lot of racket going on here.
I think the girls didn't understand.
And I was going to go do a show.
Hey.
Female caller.
Hi Adam.
This isn't a call.
And I wanted to call for three reasons.
The first reason is that you still haven't told us that Sebastian
box story.
The second reason.
I'd love to have an earthlink challenge again.
All right.
You want this.
I'll do this Sebastian box story next week.
It's another one from Moscow.
But it's pretty good.
Okay.
And now the earthlink thing.
Maybe a product that I can relate to and that I use and that I have something to say about.
It was a great experiment and hopefully the advertisers are listening and you'll have something
for us real soon.
The third reason is you can check out my show at somethingmissing.podshow.com.
Thanks to the efforts of Pod Show.
I was finally able to get up and running on my own.
And now I've got something to say.
Oh.
And even though girls should never admit that they actually go to the bathroom.
I'm a scruncher.
Oh.
Actually, I think this makes five.
But Patricia, we love hearing you.
Every morning getting the DSC is a lot like getting a little gift.
And when it's with Adam, it's the excitement of getting a box from Amazon.
I love getting boxes from amazon.com.
But when you're on, it's like getting a box from red envelope or something with just
really pretty packaging.
So please keep coming on everyone's in a while.
She will.
I promise you.
Yeah.
Well, first of all, very successful the ad challenge.
And of course, the ad challenge will continue because it's not just specific to earthlink.
The ad challenge will remain.
So yes, I can totally see what we have more products and or services.
And hopefully we can build this out into something much on a much grander scale.
But it really does seem to work very well where each individual podcast.
There's a relationship between the producer who is often also the host.
But the producer of that show and the audience.
So it only makes sense that you have a conversation with your audience about stuff that you're
promoting that you're advertising, etc.
So in this case, we started off with earthlink.
Here's one of the finalists, by the way, which is vying towards that thousands of
dollars of prize money.
And of course, the reward of actually being the chosen commercial that will run in
pod shows.
This is Steve Webb with the Life Spring Family podcast.
You know, it's not often that your local cable company does any favors for you, right?
But when I signed up for high speed internet, they really did a good thing.
Included with our high speed internet access was access to all of earthlink services.
I wasn't too impressed at the time because I'd never used earthlink.
But as I started using the earthlink email, their parental controls, their pop-up blocker.
Well, this was long time before Firefox.
And the highly effective spam blocker, I really began to rely on earthlink's rock solid
service and reliability.
Then after I'd been with them for a year or so, our cable company realized what they
done, that they'd actually done something good for their customers.
So, of course, they had to rectify that.
Right.
No more would earthlink be included with our internet service.
If we wanted to keep our earthlink, we'd have to pay, above and beyond the already escalating
prices that our cable company was charging.
Well, there was no way I wanted to give up all the great services and reliability I was
used to.
So, yep.
I've been at paying customer of earthlink for years now, and I can recommend them
highly.
Give them the try and see if you don't agree.
Yep.
There you go.
It doesn't get any better than that.
People willing to pay extra just to have earthlink services.
You know, Andrew Grummit, he had to work on the D-gap stuff.
We were having all those errors, which are fixed now, by the way.
I think all the, well, there's still reports coming in from episode 436 and 437.
So, we pretty much have it all fixed as far as I know.
And he was on vacation somewhere where he did have a laptop, but there was absolutely no
Starbucks or any wireless, any Wi-Fi around.
And so, guess what he used?
Yep.
He got himself a dial-up account with earthlink.
You'd think we had a couple of those on standby.
We didn't.
But he got one and was able to save the day.
There's another endorsement for the fine services of earthlink.
Hey, Adam.
This is a message for your listener profiles.
My name is Richard Brennan.
I'm a slacker from Gostown, New Hampshire.
43 years young.
Long time listener and first time caller.
I just wanted to comment that I really enjoyed your exercise segment for a few days.
I hope you do more of them.
And I totally sympathized with your bones and bones that you were experiencing.
You know, you're back aching and so on.
And I love working out myself at a local gym.
But what's interesting, Adam, that I wanted to comment is that I've created this sort of
activity channel in my real life.
That is, I use the Charlie as my workout audio.
And the pairing of working out on the stairmaster or the electrical trainer.
And listening to the chuck is perfect for me.
For some reason I can do more time on the aerobic segment of my workout.
If I'm listening to you and I've tried other podcasts.
But nothing works like your show and listening to the various things that you can talk about.
When you're exercising like that, it kind of occupies a part of your brains.
You can work out with being without being conscious of how hard you're working.
So ideally, I set up one or two Charlie's to catch up on.
And I do about, you know, 40 minutes on the elliptical trainer.
And you've been my workout buddies since some time last year.
So I just wanted to also make a quick plug for what I do when I'm doing my weights.
The weight segment of my workout, which is I listen to the Randy Rhodes show.
I don't know if you know her show from Aramaica Radio.
She's got a podcast version of her show on iTunes.
Awesome talk show, Radio Woman, who makes fun of our current administration.
She's really funny and really biting commentary.
But she also has a great opening song at him that you'd love.
It's called Bounce Your Boobies.
And I kid you not. You should seriously take it out.
And let me know if you think of that sounds good.
You love boobies.
Yeah. So Adam, when you're doing that bridge, you ask your size.
Yeah.
I was, I think that's what you're called.
And I was also thinking that maybe you should try yoga based on how your back was hurting
towards.
I'm taking yoga teacher training this fall.
And maybe I can give you a few pointers after I'm certified.
You do strike me as a kind of guy that could get into yoga.
But you'd have to first make the decision to slow down and get on the mat and relax.
Anyway, that's for the future.
It's all for now. Thanks for being in my workout buddy.
See you at the gym. Thanks for being you.
No, I have to.
And by the way, I'm a folder standard.
Looker.
Folder standard, looker.
And FSL. Oh, yeah. Oh, boy.
You know, our financial director, Mark Sierra is, I think I don't
if he's a certified yoga instructor, but he's way into it.
And I think during one of our battle against the cookie bulge at pod show,
which is on Tuesdays and Thursdays.
I think he did a yoga class one time.
Yeah. I've already started on my back and I started on that.
Almost two years ago when I quit riding motorcycles.
That's when I really fucked up my back.
Because after a pretty bad tumble I made.
I did want to mention that I spoke to Amanda Monaco of the
Sivius Bitties. I called her yesterday and she called me back this morning.
Just about as I was to record the show actually.
And as she likes the talk, we just talked and talked and it was quite nice actually.
Not able to hook up.
Unfortunately, today is not a good day for me to go into the city.
I got a lot of stuff to do here and then, well, you know, tomorrow already
have my flying set up on Sunday.
The girls have something, I don't know, and that's when Amanda is actually
leaving.
So we promised to hook up in New York.
It will be me, the Bitties, and karaoke.
Apparently, they have some awesome place where they are karaoke stars.
Oh, yes, one other thing, here we go.
So yesterday, if you missed the show,
you know, I hadn't really forgotten our 18th wedding anniversary, but we don't usually
make a big deal out of anniversary.
Little did I know that 18, of course, was supposed to be a big deal.
And so I kind of messed up on presents and flowers and I got some flowers
on the way back from the airport at the gas station.
It literally nailed me on.
And then yesterday, a beautiful bouquet of roses showed up.
And it said Patricia happy anniversary.
Please forgive Adam.
He asked me to get these to you on your anniversary since he was going to be
busy.
And I got toasted, and I just plain forgot.
It's all my fault that he got those horrible gas station flowers.
And it wasn't signed.
I found out who did this.
Oh, man.
Shall we make another contest out of it?
Hmm.
Now, forget about it.
PW Fenton, man.
I love you.
Thank you.
That was so incredibly nice.
I feel to do that.
Oh, Adam, my name is Alex McCoy.
I'm just cooling the kiss on a hot glass listener.
I don't have a hot glass to wear.
But I would recommend the Emirant teacher.
That's WWWG.
Emma and Pete Docscom.
Just laying you know, first of all, that I'm a fall to get that out of the way.
And secondly, to just see if are the you, Patricia, or Christina,
have any recommendations for places to see if fuel food planning to visit.
Sometime next week.
Can you even potentially house one?
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
So places to see in Gilford.
Well, of course, we have all kinds of wonderful things to see in Gilford.
Just stay around the high street.
And if you're with your wife, she'll be plenty busy on a problem.
Go to the castle grounds.
That's nice.
There's a great, a great museum up on the top of the hill.
I think there's even a time capsule there at Gilford Castle.
Yeah, there's lots and lots of nice stuff to see.
But this house hunting thing you mentioned kind of worries me.
So I sent a message, especially we're looking for good places to be in eat, get some ideas.
OK, good places to eat.
Cafe de Paris, or Cafe Rouge.
These are all next to each other on Church Street.
And then the final one is Loch.
Was it Loch Finn fish restaurant?
Great restaurants.
There's not so good areas of Gilford to live.
And also schools, again, if there's anything that's good or not so good.
I mean, don't have a good weekend.
Again, bye.
Sure, sure.
Thanks.
So yeah, you know, we're house hunting ourselves here in Gilford.
And all of Gilford is pretty much great.
You know, there's fantastic schools everywhere.
It's just, it's a fantastic affluent suburb.
But because it's so affluent and because it's so desirable,
it's very hard to find housing.
You know, we've been looking for over a year now and have not been successful.
You know, we came very close and got gazumped.
Our first gazumping.
Of course, it was also on our first offer, which kind of sucked.
You know, just stay away from Gilford.
Don't come live here.
Please.
It's nice here.
We don't want any more problems with housings.
Stay away.
Do not come to Gilford.
Please.
Go away.
Yeah.
iki.
musical just of the Chacha. Hey, is it me or is this summer flying by? And the song I got for you today is all about speed.
It's speed baby from the gentleman. They have a great out-mount called Blonsperfer the gentleman.
This song rocks. It's a lot of fun. You got to turn this up really, really loud.
Because from the pot-safe music network, this is speed baby from the gentleman. Hey, it's summertime. Turn it up real loud, all right?
You got some cowbell?
Speed baby.
I'm sorry to get my song to speed baby.
I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I
I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowsbell. I got some cowbell, oh my god. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell, my dog which is blocking my hand right. I got some cowbell. I got a cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. We got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell. I got some cowbell.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh And, yeah, yeah. So, yeah, it's really like this, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,Yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, so, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah. Yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah,
I'll let you check Charlie listeners. I'll catch you back here Monday. It's gonna be real busy next week a couple of meetings in London
I'm planning on my first solo cross-channel flight. Oh, boy. That's gonna be plenty to do
Hope you'll tune in with me until then Adam and Kurt Adam and Potchio.com and
DailySourceco.com for all of your comments and all that stuff. Take care everybody. Bye. Bye. Bye
Yeah, this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from Potchio and line-white networks. I love it