This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
The show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy.
Delta Shara Charlie 319.
Sometimes some atoms on a loan.
And he needs his love right there on the microphone.
So here she is, yes, the Lady Patricia.
The say-to-heads are better than one.
And with this angel from above, there's nothing that they both can't do.
And make you wild as dreams come true.
So grab your earbuds and jam them in.
And let the fabulous show begin.
It's Adam and Patricia.
Yes, Adam and Patricia.
Adam and the Lady Patricia.
Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
My life is brilliant.
What, was I too early?
Sorry, should I?
Do you want to start over?
Keep going?
Okay.
Now?
My life is brilliant.
Your life's a joke.
Your just pathetic.
Your always broke.
Your home may start trek uniform.
Really ain't impressing me.
Your suffering from the illusions of the adequacy.
You're beautiful.
It's true.
Never had a date that you couldn't inflate.
And you smell repulsive too.
What a bummer bein' you.
Well you just can't dance.
And forget romance.
Everybody you know still calls you.
Party pins, but you always have a job.
Well I mean as long as you still could work.
That's where be my sheet.
You're beautiful.
You're beautiful. It's true.
You're handsome.
That's you.
You're beautiful.
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la luzzar
Y'all beautiful, y'all beautiful
Y'all beautiful, this true
Y'all would much rather play fetch by itself
You've got to live with your mom when you're 42.
Guess you'll never grow up.
When it just sucks to be you.
The infallible weird al-yanko, you're pitiful.
I'm not sure the legalities of playing that song, but I do know that the owner of the song,
which of course is not who wrote it, but the record company, wouldn't allow him to put that song on his album.
Oh, really?
Yeah, so he put it up on his website, so I figured, well, you know.
Well, how did you do that when he recorded the song from Michael Jackson?
Michael Jackson agreed.
You don't.
I believe that.
I believe the law is that you don't for a parody, which falls under fair use.
You don't have to have permission, but weird al is always asked permission of all the artists.
So if they didn't like it, they didn't do it.
But yeah.
And what a great singer he is, isn't it?
And how about that beginning, huh?
You know that always irritated me.
That's not what happened there.
And then they say, you know, it's cool.
It's cool.
Yeah, don't even start there.
Yeah, it's fantastic.
Just leave it.
It's so real.
Name another song that has that.
I know one.
I know there's another one.
You know.
No, don't do that.
No, that's not nice.
That's not nice.
Hey, everybody.
How you doing?
It's the daily source code coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey.
No one is killed for it.
Where the cottage is located.
Lady Patricia joining us on the show.
Yeah.
What a lovely song about us.
Yeah, that's the privilege.
That's Jeff.
Just have your own song.
Just like the nanny.
Yeah.
It needs an applause and then cue lights.
Can you Patricia with opening and joke?
Yeah.
How is it, Jeff?
Jeff feels.
Yeah.
All right.
So we haven't heard from you for a couple of days.
We've been for about a week.
I think the last time you were on show.
That's right.
Yeah.
I missed you.
Really?
Yeah, but I had a lot of stuff that I had to do.
For mom and then I had to do some stuff for pod show.
Yeah.
Oh, everything came at one time.
Isn't it always like that?
It sure is.
That's life.
Yeah.
It really is.
But on the other hand, maybe that was a good thing.
I don't know.
I keep showing you, too.
Oh, no kidding.
I'm so tired.
Yeah.
And while you saw Bloom.
He's tired.
He's very tired.
Yeah.
And so is his lovely, lovely lady.
Is he tired too?
Maybe Bloom.
Is she tired?
Yeah, she is.
Are you tired?
I'm tired from wrong being tired.
Oh, yes.
I've heard of this.
I understand him and being late.
And go to bed late.
Mm-hmm.
Not listening to her because he doesn't hear her.
She that sounds familiar, doesn't it?
Yeah.
It's so funny yesterday.
But she's like, you don't hear me.
That's just like Ron not hearing Marta.
I said, yeah.
Trust me.
Test me.
And I tested him.
And he's like something you said 10 minutes before.
Yeah.
And I literally didn't know.
I was telling you something.
But Christina, you didn't hear me.
Yeah, I feel like shit about that.
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to do my best.
I do understand.
You know?
I got a lot to think about.
When men are lazy and not listening.
Like Keith?
That's wrong.
But if you know the very busy, you know, doing something really, really good and incredible.
Oh, thank you.
Then it's understandable.
Well, thank you.
I'll take that as an endorsement.
As long as they're not lazy.
The only thing that's really a shame is, you know,
so here we've had this incredible team of people working so hard to get everything going
out for Cisco and around the world, actually, because we have people all over the world working with us side by side.
Yeah.
And which I'm extremely appreciative.
And you have not yet even looked at podshow plus.
And it hurts so bad.
It hurts so bad.
And you just won't do it.
Yeah, it does.
If this is like, you know, this is our,
Well, haven't had the time for it.
It's our art.
But this is what we've been working on.
This is for all those nights that I came to bed late for all those hurried sex sessions because it was so late.
If there was one.
I got to keep my image up for all those times when I didn't hear what you said.
Yeah.
Now you can, are you afraid that when you look at it, you'll say it was all for that?
No, no, no, actually.
I thought, you know, my time will come.
What does that mean?
To to to look at it.
But in the meanwhile, life goes on around you.
I understand a lot of things.
You can just look at it if you just for 10 minutes.
10 minutes.
Now it takes more.
We need Patricia on the plus.
Everyone wants Patricia on the bus.
You see, you have no idea how good you are at surfing.
I mean, you think that you don't know what you're doing,
but you can get through all those wacky messed up real estate websites,
which make no sense at all.
And you actually can retrieve information and send it on to me.
Yeah.
You are much, much better than you think you are.
I'm getting there.
Yeah.
Now don't be embarrassed.
Look Christina hates it.
Oh.
Well, I mean, she doesn't hate it, but she says it doesn't work like my space.
I said, no, it's not supposed to.
Well, of course not.
Yeah.
But she's given us some great feedback.
And she got a contract.
We're going to sign.
Yeah, we're going to sign.
We've got to get the new printer and then we'll sign now.
She's going to sign her contract.
I guess I have to sign for her since she's not 16 yet.
Almost.
Yeah.
She's almost.
Now she's excited about it.
Yeah.
She's totally into it.
Oh, that's good.
She played those guys who were going to perform in her sweet 16.
She played one of their tracks.
She's becoming such a little, um, little mogul.
Yeah.
Very interested in young groups, new groups.
And, um, signed groups, of course.
And that's nice.
That's, that's, that's very good.
I'm, I'm glad she wants to help them.
Oh, glad we have.
I'm glad we can actually do this.
Because, you know, we were out looking for a place.
There's not a lot of places in Guildford for, um, independent musicians to play.
Yeah.
No.
And not at all.
So, I guess getting your stuff out there on podcasts is really is good.
Yeah.
It's a pod.
There is a lot of talents in, uh, Guildford.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Because there are very good music schools here.
Mm-hmm.
So they're, they're very good educated in music.
Yeah.
And I have to say.
I'm privileged lives.
And I heard a couple of bands that she, uh, she wanted me to listen to.
Really good stuff, huh?
Very good.
Yeah.
I was, I was impressed.
She has to get those in the pod, take music network.
That's, that's what she's working on.
Yeah.
It does that every time, introduce a new band or anything.
That's, that's very nice.
Yeah.
Indeed.
Hey.
Adam, uh, the funny atmosphere.
Yeah.
That's that.
Who's show really is pressure you rock?
You know, you tell like a great wife.
Um, very, uh.
The great wife.
You are the great wife.
You hear that?
Yeah.
I tell you, people love you.
Here, listen to this.
Right.
Very engaging, very sexy.
Flathead, big ears.
Um, I give you guys lots of credit as my wife, Aaron, and I, uh, uh, uh, uh,
I live at our almost six year anniversary.
No.
What are you guys talking about?
I keep your marriage fresh.
I keep it exciting.
I'd love to hear about it.
Um, keep on doing what you're doing.
Um, despite how long you've been doing this.
And it hasn't been that long.
You guys still do a great show.
It's very fresh.
Correct.
Regret from San Francisco.
Yeah.
How do we do it?
I don't know.
You tell me.
I, I think you just put up with me.
And that's about it.
Well, um, I think it is patients and respect.
F patients for each other.
And try to understand why.
Why someone is acting like an occasion.
Yeah.
Acting like a few.
Just take a step back and think.
Okay.
What happened there?
Why is this?
And, you know, where's coming from?
Yeah.
And that's what you have to do.
I think I think what it is.
No.
It's very simple.
You're a mature woman.
Oh, I don't know.
Is that what you say?
You said, oh, it's very simple.
Well, let me finish.
Okay.
You're a mature woman.
You know, most people when they get married.
Or when they share their lives together.
They start around.
Let's say 20, 20, 30.
We're already 38 when I met you.
And I was in between the 20 and 30 age range, like 22.
So you had a lot of patients with me.
Yeah.
And now as you grow older and see now, I have more patients with you.
Just kidding.
Well, there you go.
That's what they might say.
Patients are scanning and respect.
Just kidding.
That's it.
You know, no matter what.
No matter what.
But yeah, I think that's the thing.
And I am a little bit old-fashioned.
I have to say.
That's true.
And you know, it's all for the good.
And I think that a woman should take care of herself.
Oh.
And because you're going to get a lot of interesting response to that.
Well, if you take care of yourself and you feel you look good.
Then, you know, the whole thing around you.
And also reach your husband and, you know, with the men around you.
It works out.
Just, you know.
But in general, you hate men and would not want to live with one if you could choose differently.
I have not a lot of patients for a lot of men.
Sort.
Sort of men.
I went through the voicemail.
Voicemail box today.
I had about 80 different voicemails.
You know, from back, even before when mom died.
But after mom died, I noticed that a lot of women started calling.
And I keep asking for women to call in and leave messages.
And now all of a sudden, there must have been 45% female voices that I heard.
It was interesting that all of a sudden they come.
You know, that's when they come out when it's about emotions and stuff.
Yeah.
When I just want sexy calls or naked pictures, I never get any response.
No.
And now you did.
Yeah.
Check it out.
In celebration of beautiful women around the world.
This is KFC from pod.
Check.com.
And again, the writing rather than convertible to hot sunny day in Toronto.
Where in my bikini.
But I wanted to comment on the beautiful women in London.
I was there last weekend.
It is so amazing.
True.
And we have a new pod.
Check them out on today's show Friday.
3 p.m.
Check it out.
Hot chicks around the world.
Send in your photos.
All right, Adam.
You have an amazing weekend.
And make them smile.
Sounds good.
Yeah.
Now, this is about the English girls.
Letting it all hang out.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, guys walk without sure.
I mean, maybe they're all poo poo.
And they know their manners.
But the minute the sun cracks through the clouds.
Yes.
It's no damn boobies.
And we have a drink.
We have to have a drink and show them boobies.
Oh, yeah.
Another one.
This is that Jeff.
Listen, that will be July.
And glad the boobs are out in London.
You're in Hawaii.
They never go away.
Yeah.
So I missed a couple of really good ones.
Check this out.
This is really cool.
Hey, Adam.
It's Richard calling.
It's 120 in the morning.
And you're down for me on the 50 July.
And you know, Alan, I figured that once England got knocked out of the World Cup that we
thought it was about time, we started a family and what better to do it than on the 4th of July.
So the 1141 PM on the 4th of July.
That might be a beautiful life.
Keepers to a beautiful daughter.
Addison Brewer, hey.
Red hair, blue eyes, six pounds, 14 ounces.
And a nice 12, 22 inches long.
So she's doing great.
Mom's doing great.
And the only thing is, when I'd like to plug anything in here at the hospital.
So we don't get to listen to the BSC for another couple of days.
But we'll get right back on track.
I'll show you.
And I'm still, I'm still in my blackberry on period.
To check for emails from the public services.
And for those people that want to get on the show, take it easy out of sight.
Yeah, that is new baby in the background.
Is that a proud pop out there? Is that cool?
I remember that moment.
Oh, yeah, I remember too. That was fantastic.
Yeah, I was 26 centimeters long.
But really? And what was Addison 22?
What did he say? 22, 22, 24.
Those inches that she said inches.
I think he said inches.
What's she inches 26?
Yeah.
Must have cancer centimeters.
You can carry that in your pocket.
It's my blackberry's bigger than that.
No, it was inches.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because I always think in centimeters.
But it's inches.
Did you hear it? I heard something else. She's a ginger.
Yeah.
We got a ginger in the family.
That's like not a good thing here in the UK.
Yes, it is.
Are you sure?
Oh, yeah.
Whenever I hear someone talking about someone with red hair,
they talk about them like a ginger.
They always say they must be very sexy.
Why?
They are very sexy.
I don't know.
You've never had a ginger.
I'm trying to think of it.
I've ever had a ginger.
Did you?
Yeah.
I'm trying to think.
I don't think I've ever had a ginger either.
No.
Let me think.
No, no.
Don't give me that.
I'm sorry.
Was it not a ginger?
Oh, really?
Robbie Dale.
Robbie Dale?
Yes, that's not.
From a radio Luxembourg?
Yes.
This is the big sound of radio Luxembourg.
Robbie Dale.
He had a, but he had a, he was a ginger.
I'm sorry, Charlie.
And he had a beard, didn't he?
Wasn't he a ginger with a beard?
I don't know.
I can't believe he's not doing a ginger beard.
Yeah.
The ginger beard, man.
Why did you do that?
I don't know.
Robbie Dale.
Yeah, right.
Why?
I don't know.
Does he, is he still alive this evening?
Is he still around?
Well, I'm sorry.
It was in the evening.
Wait a minute.
Where are we?
He was in the evening.
And he had a sort of a blind date that evening.
And Lex Harding was with Ivan.
And with Robbie Dale, I think.
I got, I got Robbie Dale.
And it's best if you go on a blind date with Robbie Dale that you're actually blind.
That would actually, that's better.
I have to say that he's a very funny guy.
Yeah.
And you know, and humor sometimes makes you horny.
That's all.
But, but it all stayed with the dogging.
So I guess his jokes weren't that good, huh?
And now we're from our spine tier.
It's the yanks versus the brits.
Oh yeah.
We'll drive each other crazy.
But everybody knows that it's apparent to see.
Let's just like you and me.
It's the yanks.
And in the brits.
The yanks versus the brits.
Mind the gag.
Okay.
So I just running through all these voicemails.
I found a great yanks versus the brits question.
And one that maybe you and I can help answer.
In fact, I don't even know the way you do it.
All right.
I had them come and see them here.
A long time listener of the Charlie.
I have a question for you.
I was looking through a recent article for my new scientist magazine.
And it was talking about how Americans would like to use their toilet paper
by scrunching it for its brits tend to fall in it.
Perhaps you can say, shed some light on this for me.
Because I'm not really understanding what scrunching it is.
Meaning when it's talking about toilet paper.
Thank you so much.
So the question is, are he read a new scientist?
A new scientist?
No.
But this is interesting.
He read a new scientist magazine that apparently Americans scrunch the toilet paper before using it.
Where's the brits fold the toilet paper before using it?
Hmm.
And I really would not know.
And I'd like you to tell our audience, of course.
Do you want to?
No.
I'm a folder.
Are you a scruncher?
Absolutely.
Folder.
Folder, folder.
Interesting.
Do you think Americans really scrunch it?
I think if you scrunch and bunch it.
You also use a lot of paper.
I think, you know, they just...
How much paper do you use?
Too much.
Really?
Yeah.
Because it's a problem in the toilet.
I remember that sometimes.
And I think, why do I use so much?
But then you use more than me because I never had any.
And I wonder for what?
I'm so, you wonder for what?
For what?
Why you use so much paper?
What?
Oh, okay.
For what?
Let us know.
Are you a scruncher or a folder inquiring mind?
No.
We're from our sponsor.
It's very not done.
No.
But what we do.
And that's why we don't use that much.
It's a good idea what we're doing.
Oh, the...
The bodies.
The bodies for the...
Can't believe we're talking about this.
But it's so refreshing.
It's lovely.
Yeah.
It's always put a box in the toilet.
It's very complimentary.
Complimentary?
To what?
To the service?
To the rest of the service while you're in there?
Please enjoy one of our body wipes.
It's a compliments service of our washroom.
Compliments of that.
Mind the gap.
Yes.
But it's true.
It's very refreshing.
You feel very clean.
And I think everybody should do it.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Buncher or for...
Was it scruncher or a folder?
That's what you want to know.
You should just end it.
Whenever you call in on the show, just end with, you know, instead of saying, hey,
you know, see you just say folder by by or scruncher.
Just so we know what kind of person you are.
And I want to find out what kind of people are scrunchers.
I think scrunchers are a little bit in the hurry.
Yeah, that could be.
And...
I take my time.
I just take their time.
Make sure they're clean.
There's something like that.
I even appreciate the pre-fold.
For serious.
The pre-fold, I really like.
That's what they do when they clean the condo.
Oh, yeah.
They fold the little point in the toilet paper.
I love that.
And nothing.
This condo.
No, this is a cottage.
Don't get me started on the help you selected and continue to maintain.
I mean, I've told you many a time.
I select that because she's spooked like that.
Yeah, but she walks.
She talks like that.
I'm not.
Maybe she cleans like that.
That's not true.
Not true.
So I just want to know that Sid Barrett passed away yesterday.
Of course, that was all over the new Sid Barrett of Pink Floyd.
That was Floyd.
I walked this morning to, it was an Emily.
Was that the name in the song.
Yeah.
That was on BBC 2.
So, 60 years old way to young.
Yeah.
But he was definitely what they say in the financial time.
So they the the the Icarus of Britain psychedelic pop music and he just got too
close to the song or what.
But I don't know what he died of.
I don't know actually I didn't do.
It didn't say it or at least I didn't read the permission.
I think if you live that way that they did, I mean, you have to somewhere. It's shortens your life and they, you know all the bad.
Well, that is true. I mean, all the people we know that were hard-ass rock and rollers all seemed to go somewhere between 50 and 60.
Yeah, 55 seems to be pretty much like Alfa.
A little bit too much of something.
It's not good.
I guess too much of anything. It's not good.
Yeah, I think about it.
Well, no. A lot of sex is good.
No, no, too much cannot be good for you.
For me?
No, for anybody. You can't have too much sex.
No, no, no.
That can also be bad.
Oh.
I thought it was a good attitude.
That's a good idea.
The idea is very appealing.
Yeah.
Those of you checking us out on serious stars 102.
The pod show is just getting started.
We have a Pacific Coast Hellway coming up after this show and that will be followed up all the way.
Until 10 o'clock Eastern time.
As you do every single week day evening on serious stars 102.
And if you want to hear the rest of the show with the lady Patricia
Go to dailysourcecode.com.
So what else do you got?
I'm disappointed.
And what?
I'm thinking about it.
I thought that I always read sex is good for you.
Oh, it is, but too much of anything is not good for you.
Come on.
You can actually physically harm yourself if you have too much sex.
Oh, and you mean like exaggerated.
Well, what are you talking about?
Like four times a day?
No, I don't mean like, you know, doing dull day because I sometimes hear that.
I would have a heart attack if I had to four times a day.
And of course, you know, that's not very good for you skin.
No.
Down there.
No, no.
I mean just in a normal way.
Like, you know, having fun with it.
Yeah, like last night.
I know.
Yeah.
I think it's very good.
And it's good for my heart.
Oh, yeah.
Mine too.
Keep the heart to go.
Keep the heart pumping.
Pumping.
Hmm.
See, got anything?
Anything.
I mean, I got lots of stuff too.
Pumping for low.
I got lots of stuff to talk about.
Do you?
Did you come to the show prepared, I guess, is one of my asking?
No, never.
No, you're not fantastic.
You know that.
But whatever you want to talk about, I'm ready.
I have some things I got to do there.
We're into the final round of the earth link.
Yeah.
Add challenge.
You want to hear this.
This is one of the finalists.
You might have heard this one before.
So this is going to be voted on by the judges, which is basically, you make the commercial
if you know.
So goddamn good.
That's basically what the project is.
Yeah.
We're doing the earthly clues.
That's right, baby.
Earthlink.
Bombastic broadband.
Delicious, darling.
That's Earthlink.
Earthlink comes home to you and brings it home to Mama.
That's your idea, sister.
That's what I'm talking about.
In Earthlink, to help you out with all your internet needs.
It's just good.
Earthlink.com.
Let them know that papa sits in.
Yeah.
That's your idea.
That's what I'm talking about.
So that would be in the song category.
Yeah.
So we got more coming over the next couple weeks.
You can now listen to all the finalists at adchallenge.podshow.com.
I don't know what you can talk about.
Listen to this.
Hi Adam.
This is Alex calling you from Afghanistan.
I just.
From Afghanistan.
Just heard the resource quote about your mom.
I want to give you my condolences and see your family.
And take care.
And know what we tried to get you over here.
Just like you did a couple of years ago.
I was a Dutch in Iraq.
Yeah, okay.
How about that, huh?
Yeah.
I would go.
You know I would go.
Yeah, I know.
But I wouldn't just do podcasts.
I do streaming audio so that you could listen to it live as well.
God, I would love to go.
I really think that would be awesome.
Isn't it amazing that everybody's still there?
The problem is still there.
Well, yeah.
Well, the problem is it's all over the world, baby.
I mean, did you see what happened yesterday?
It starts in India.
Yeah.
Fucking hell.
There were hundreds of hundred and ninety people blown to bits.
Three hundred injured.
They still don't know who they don't know.
Yeah.
But isn't it interesting?
Did you have a different field?
Do you think that when we read about something that happens in India?
Yeah.
Which is actually, you know, I know a lot of people from India, which I was bringing
someone closer to me, but it feels so far away.
Do you think that when the London bombings took place or in Madrid?
Yeah.
Do you think that people in India had the same feeling?
I wonder.
What do you think?
I think so.
Because really, I mean, we think.
Well, you know, if something happens, really close to you, of course, it's a
different experience.
Of course, you know, it's so close.
You think I could have been there.
But so here's today's world where a guy just called me from Afghanistan.
Yeah.
And he feels pretty close.
And India doesn't feel like something incredibly far away country because I know a lot
of people from India.
I know people who travel back and forth all the time, who travel through London.
Yeah.
But still that it feels somewhat removed in it.
And it's the same problem.
I always think about it.
Especially when I see the pictures, I always really stare at it and read it.
And I think, oh my God, you know, that must be horrible.
If you're family or anything or you're child.
I just like the point out that I do not, I do not believe India is fighting
Iraq right now.
I just like the point out.
No.
And I'm very curious.
What is this all about?
Well, India has multiple religions living side by side.
Yeah.
Christians, Buddhists, Muslims.
You know, there's always been huge tension between India and Pakistan.
You know, there's a lot going on over there too.
Of course.
But terrorism is terrorism.
It's moment.
I just, who, who, who was this?
Who is responsible?
Did anyone claim it?
No, not yet.
You sure?
No one claimed it.
Then how do they know it?
Well, I guess they know it's terrorist attack.
They, they too.
Suicide bombers.
That's what they think.
Yeah.
We know so little actually.
And we're so quick to believe what we're told.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I catch myself time and time again doing that.
I just like why do I believe everything immediately?
Yeah.
So we got two new shows coming.
In the next two weeks, one of them will talk about what you listened to last night.
I want to talk about that in a second.
But now, there's all this is new.
I'm not going to show what it is.
But it's a show where two people compete against each other.
And you know, PWB.
Mm-hmm.
Sidelight repairman.
I'm just saying.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So now he is competing against CC Chapman.
And you didn't hear yesterday because of course.
You don't listen to the show.
But PWB said he was like, is it like a really angry?
And like, I'm going to slap CC Chapman down.
And now CC sent in the following comment.
Hey, Adam, it's CC.
Okay.
So I hear this crap from PWB on the show.
And I don't know what's going on here.
You know, Mark, you know, Yoshimoto there says, Yo dude, you know what you guys come
on this game show.
We're going to do a thing.
We're going to have some fun.
You're going to be a bone.
I don't like it.
I get this actually on you.
And it's all good, man.
Whatever.
And you know, Mark's my boy.
So I said, yes, sure, whatever.
We can do that.
And, and then also in PWB's first talk in this trash.
I mean, you know, he's an old guy.
You know, he gets a little crazy sometimes and goes up the handle.
You know, he doesn't really, he really, really hates the Uncle Jesse stuff.
Um, but if he starts to trash talking, then he sends crap to you.
I mean, I thought it was just an innocent blog post.
I'm like, you know, whatever, man, that's cool.
You know, I'm just, I'm the easy girl.
I'm the, it's all good guy.
And then thin goes and does all those stuff, man.
So, you know, I just, you know, PWB, you know,
I don't, you know, I just want a truth, you know, white flag man, you know.
I don't want to get on the show and just totally have the bitch slap.
Some old guys weren't depends on, you know, a podcast around the world.
Come on, dude.
I thought we were friends, man.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I'd give you an ass, weapon, and, you know,
I'd beat you over the hip.
Sorry.
I just wanted to, you know, because I know, you know,
people think you know, PWB and our friends,
and I thought I was too, and then all this happened.
So, you know, I had about, I don't know what's going on next.
You know, I just, I wanted to retort, I guess,
after I heard PWB on the show today.
I don't know.
I guess we'll find out when bone comes out, you know,
what happens, and, you know, hopefully,
PWB and I can work as shit out, you know, because, you know,
I love the man.
I don't know.
Whatever.
Hey, have a good one.
Good to have you back.
Talk to you, see you, man.
See you.
Oh, sounds are pretty fake, didn't it?
Yeah, you know, I know.
You know, you know, you know, you know, you know,
SmackDown, baby.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think it's a really interesting attempt
of getting people to go to bone.pot show.com.
Yeah, that's what he means.
Uh-huh.
I think so.
Real long way to promo it, but I do appreciate it.
Did you actually tell your listeners how incredible
good it was to have a party at the end of your morning?
I did.
And it's our listeners, by the way.
Oh, okay.
Why don't you tell our listeners about it
from your experience?
Because when Adam told me that his mom wanted a 50's party.
Actually, you know what I have.
I'm sorry to interrupt you, huh.
I have the actual words.
Yeah.
That my mom had pre-written.
Uh-huh.
So this is actually on the, uh, what do you call this?
The announcement.
Yeah.
What do you call it in the announcement?
Condolions.
Yeah, condolions.
Card.
The death card.
You know.
Something like that.
Yeah.
So it has butterflies or free.
With thanks to all of you for your love supporting
guidance given to my wife and our mom.
The cremation will take place in the presence of her immediate family members,
her special wish was for us to give a 50's party in her memory.
And we are honoring that request.
And then, you know, a separate slip.
Uh-huh.
You were cordially invited to Valerie's 50's party.
But that was literally what she wanted us.
Yeah.
Now I have to explain that your mom, I know her now for the long time.
And it took me a while to understand her because she's so different than any other woman.
And other.
That feeling might have been mutual for a while.
Yes.
And especially being a mother-in-law.
Now I'm mother-in-laws and daughter-in-laws.
You know, that is always a little bit of a difficulty because it's not your mom.
And I'm not her daughter.
Right.
So it's different.
And in the beginning, I thought, she's not an easy person.
You know, she wants attention with this.
In the beginning, it's like 20 years ago that we're talking.
20 years ago, I try to understand it.
It was very hard.
She was checking me out, of course.
She didn't like me in the beginning because she thought, an older woman.
What is it?
Robbing the cradle of her.
Her own son.
Maybe.
And she had her dreams about, you know, maybe not children.
Because she was not into babies and these sort of things.
But I don't know what kind of plan she had for you.
But so in the beginning, she looked at me like,
Hmm.
I don't know about this.
And she really showed me that.
You know, so it was very hard.
I got to know her.
We had a couple of fights.
Remember that?
Well, not really fights.
You know, words.
Words.
Where we finally said exactly.
What I felt.
How she felt.
That I wasn't.
I didn't agree with her.
But her thinking.
And we came actually very close to each other.
We did understand each other.
We were only 10 years apart.
Hmm.
You know.
So at the end.
When we talked on the phone, we really understood each other.
It was very, very good.
And two weeks ago actually two or two and a half weeks ago.
She thanked me.
For taking care of her son so well.
And nobody else could have made you.
That's a tough job.
So happy.
Taking care of my son.
Yeah.
Tough gig.
Right.
So how about the back to the party?
Yeah.
So when you told me that she wanted to have a 50's party, I thought,
Oh, God.
That she goes again.
She wants something.
You know, I'm not in the mood.
It's going to cost a lot of money.
We're going to invite our people in the mood for this.
I thought she's crazy.
I mean, she's, you know, she's coming up.
You actually thought about how much it would cost.
Yeah.
Really?
I think about that for a second.
Yeah.
I thought, oh, my God.
Because I know your parties.
When you give a party.
I give a party.
It's a party.
And then you come up with all those crazy things.
Like the pink catalog.
Pink.
Right.
Exactly.
So.
I thought, oh, my God.
This is, you know, he's going to go berserk.
And.
And so when the day was there.
And after the ceremony of the kids standing there, around the,
The coffin.
And saying goodbye to her, which was very sad.
Because I felt horrible for you guys.
And, and I felt pain in Christina.
And everybody was crying.
And we couldn't believe it.
Actually, that she was in there.
Yeah.
Because that's what you think.
Oh, my God.
She's laying in there.
The poor woman is in a box.
You know, you know.
Because you know, of course, there's all kinds of images of my mom.
Yeah.
I have the hardest time still getting that.
We're getting the image.
The image of her last moments.
Just not her last moment.
But really that last day, you know.
I just, I was.
It was incredible to see what just for cancer can do to.
It was that's hard.
That's very hard.
That's the hard thing.
When you think, we go back to those final hours.
We were all thinking about that.
You know, everything goes through.
That's what I was thinking about this fucking box.
Yeah.
And I'm being in a box.
Who wants to be in a box?
Yeah.
I don't think she really liked the whole box thing.
No, the box.
No.
Who came up with the box?
Well, no.
She already pre-ordered everything.
No, I mean, long, long time ago, the people should be in a box.
Okay.
Who came over the box thing?
Yeah, the box thing.
Well, you know, lots of people burn their bodies.
Yeah.
So throw me on some, you know, or ration torturing me or roll them in beautiful leaves
and flowers and then let them just, you know.
Torturing me smoke me.
I guarantee you will not be disappointed.
I'll be disappointed.
But come to that party.
And if I can't have a party today, I'm not in mood.
So we all went to that lovely diner.
Really looked from.
Catty's catty's diner.
Oh, yeah.
It was absolutely.
It was a beautiful hot summer day.
Yeah.
It almost looked like a mirror.
The roll right up front and park in the front.
It didn't look so good.
It could smell the park where you could always talk to about.
And that was a beautiful pink catty like.
And convertible.
I think that your mom had the greatest time.
You know, because that's very young.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
She loved that time.
She loved it.
Oh, yeah.
Absolutely.
And it could hear the music from the do-box coming from inside.
The smell of the hamburgers and the hot dogs and the milkshakes.
And we had a great time.
Wasn't that nice?
It was such a beautiful sort of end of a sad day.
Mm-hmm.
And of course, it was sad.
But in a little bit, it was like, it was healing.
It was the beginning of the healing, I think, from most people.
Exactly.
Some people came by, you know, for four hours on multiple buses just to get there.
It was so pretty.
Sweating and hot.
But everybody was so happy.
Yeah.
And we all thought about her.
We had wonderful stories about her.
Yeah.
And we all came together.
And it was a lot of wonderful idea.
Yeah.
It was a good idea.
And maybe this is a very good idea for other people.
Because why?
You are already said.
It's deep in your heart.
It will be there.
And it hurts.
It hurts like hell.
But why?
You know, just ended.
And feeling even more crappy and crappy and...
Yeah.
And crappy and...
Do you want speeches that you're a service?
Because we didn't do any speeches.
Which I thought was kind of nice.
Because, you know, there was no...
Everyone could have their own conversations and...
Yeah.
Well, the speeches were...
What we were talking to each other about her.
Yeah.
Much better.
Because if you have a speech, it's always so unreal.
Yeah.
You know.
You're always going to say something that you think...
I actually don't mean it like that.
Like what sounds so good.
But it rhymes.
But it sounds...
It sounds so good.
You know?
And...
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
That's true.
And she...
Your mom loved honesty.
Oh, boy.
She had the saying honor bright.
Right.
Like honor was something that was inside of you.
And if you said, my honor is bright.
And there was so clear in our family.
You do not want honor bright.
It was not an honor bright.
No.
Where she was.
Oh, no.
That's the way she was.
She did threaten me to spank me with the hairbrush, bristle side down.
Sometimes she said, I'll do it on the wooden side.
Oh.
Let's go.
Okay.
So I had to...
Because that thought it was a good idea.
That was a good idea.
In hindsight.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
So last night we checked out...
I almost felt like...
Like a Hollywood producer.
You know, we're...
You have your own little movie theater.
The...
The Dailys of the New Masterpiece that your company's team is working on.
And so...
And I had not listened to it.
Of course.
We've been working on it.
Well, I say we, but really pod show LA out in the shack.
They're in Venice Beach.
Mark Yoshimura Namcoff.
And the...
And the hell players.
And the whole bunch of...
Really talented actors from Hollywood have been working on this.
And that has all been doing it, you know, in the new style.
Which means, come on.
Let's just get a fucking Mac and throw it together.
And we'll pay everybody.
Did you?
What a concept.
And it's a...
A drama.
An audio drama.
Yeah.
And you have to listen to it.
You just dim the lights a little bit.
And then sit back.
Have a cup of tea or a glass of wine.
And just let your fantasy.
Let's play the promo for a second.
Do the thing.
Let's get people into the mood for a second.
Here.
All not.
See.
This is working.
A bit down.
Of shadow falls.
All the secrets are more clear to protect.
And others will die to expose.
For it is on this ground that the prelude to Armageddon has been battle over for more than 300 years.
This time, it will be decided.
Once.
Actful.
Coming soon to headphones near you.
For every light that shines.
A shadow falls.
To be amongst the chosen pre-register, a shadow falls.
Don't go.
Coming to their headphones.
Near you.
I like that.
Yeah.
Where's the voice, huh?
Oh, my God.
Isn't that great?
This is so good.
I love that thing.
I think he's a waiter.
You're kidding.
Could be our fishman.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
He's got a good voice.
Dude, come on up here and be part of the show.
So we're listening to it.
He's good.
I got to say, I was just, I was like, whoa, this is good.
She was great writing.
Great story.
Great.
Great acting.
Or you have to see it like you don't have to read.
You're just listening.
Well, I've heard stuff on the BBC.
It's not even half as good as what this is.
Yeah.
I mean, it's really, you can find it.
I guess they have the room up now.
Shadowfalls.podshow.com.
So it's coming.
Well, listen to the BBC world.
Yeah.
And they have dramas.
But this is so good.
It's rich with sound effects.
And we didn't listen to it on earphones.
We listened to it just on big speakers with a bass reflex and cuts.
That sounded good.
Yeah.
Now to be able to see world has more like.
Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
Yeah.
Exactly.
So there's a theme song to our drama series Shadow Falls.
And I think you should listen to it because it's out now.
And available on the pod save music network.
From monk.
I am.
It's Molly's theme.
I just became.
I was dead for her.
For us to be, that's means both ways.
You've never asked my name.
I am here.
You'll see.
I am late.
I am naive.
I am fearful of crazy.
I am here.
For my same.
For every life that shines.
Shadow Falls.
I am here.
I am there.
You'll see.
I am alive.
I am naive.
I am fearful of crazy.
I am here.
I am now.
I am alive.
I am naive.
I am fearful of crazy.
I am here.
Monk with the theme for Shadow Falls.
Find it at Shadow Falls. podshow.com.
Get the show now.
I am here.
I am not awesome.
I think you will like this production.
I am so proud of it.
I expect Michael Jackson to come with something like that.
It is so interesting you said that because when I was listening because the way the first episode goes
into the song.
It reminded me of Michael Jackson.
What do you think she said?
Some people are not even legal and a 40.
What do you think she means?
I'm legal.
Now I'm legal.
So that's all she wanted.
Are partying?
Yes, she wants a party.
She wants to go to Disneyland.
Dad, I like Paris.
So we're going to go.
I'm going to go to San Francisco next week and then after that we'll go to Paris.
That's a long time.
You're right.
It's nice.
Yeah.
The nice Disney hotels always fun.
Christina can stay in a room with a girlfriend and you and I can have goofy sex.
In our own suite.
Goofy.
We can we can invite him.
Goofy hot.
He's a long nose.
He's saying Goofy is a folder or scruncher.
And Goofy has his big long nose with a big black knob.
Yes.
The knob.
Goofy.
So that's what she wants.
And she wants a Chanel bag.
Look at the Chanel bag.
I don't even have a Chanel bag.
Yeah, you're legal.
Here's a goofy knob.
The Chanel bag.
Please.
Ah, please.
I didn't know.
You can't have it all done.
Darling.
But that's, you know, that's what she knows.
That's because of MTV.
No, that's not MTV.
That's half the magazines you drag into the house or fill with a crab.
It doesn't mean you have to buy it.
No, but it's.
You can look at it and enjoy it.
It's just.
Yeah.
Whatever.
But I'm from a different generation.
Yes, you are.
We enjoy these things.
Just look at it.
We don't have to.
You actually have to own it.
No, you don't.
I don't understand the, the whole appeal of having.
The sunglasses.
I understand.
Because you don't have to have, you know, if you have the same sunglasses, someone else,
then it's actually not cool.
But this whole idea of having the same bag.
And it's just to say, I could afford it.
Is that what it is?
Or.
I mean, yeah, particularly if you have it at the right moment.
What do you think that's it?
Yeah, you're making a statement.
So that's that's horrible.
Yeah.
They're really used.
Because that's what they see in all those magazines.
You see those stars.
I understand.
Okay.
So it's a good formulation.
No, because this bag thing is different.
It is about having the right bag at the right time with the right dog.
With the right dog and the right cell phone.
You got to have the right cell phone.
Right cell phone.
And if you have all that, then it's just like, but it's always been a little bit like this.
Because you know, it's all those accessories, but using years ago, was having the right car.
For example.
Oh, that's true.
You know, so it's all right.
Yeah.
Yeah, you had to have the right limo.
So it is all about showing some form of wealth of success or something.
It is.
Oh yeah.
It's your version as the women's version of a penis extender.
Yeah.
It is.
I don't really care about that.
But I think if you are a beautiful.
You have a certain personality and when you come in the room, and you have to do it.
First, I think not the bag.
Not the bag.
Not the shoes.
You know.
And I think that's where they're making a mistake.
Right.
And if you see those movie stars, some of them just have it.
Yeah.
It doesn't matter if they have a postal bag or, you know.
Well, I'm just about done with it though with this whole bag stuff.
I just don't.
I love bags because you can put so much in it.
So, you know, I always have the whole thing with me.
Yeah.
I like that.
But you go out and you actually find bags that in themselves become trends.
And you're pretty impressed with that.
Yeah.
Like the one you got was it to Karen Millen?
No.
No, no, no, no.
The one you got to...
TK Max.
They have a whole bunch of wonderful bags.
TK Max is the British version of TJ Max.
TJ Max.
Yeah, I love that.
Fantastic.
No, it doesn't matter.
You know, it doesn't matter.
Sometimes you can enjoy something that's really cheap and you're happy with it.
That's true.
I mean, that's, you know.
Okay.
It's not about that.
Hey, well, I got shit to do.
Oh, sorry about that.
All right.
So you've been so busy.
Yeah, right.
And it's not over yet.
I got to...
But I can see you enjoying yourself.
I'm having a lot of fun.
That's good.
Yeah.
That's a lot of fun.
It's amazing.
Look at the hell.
Look at what's happening.
Look at what has happened.
We've become so used to podcasts reaching people all over the world and the interaction.
And all these, you know, all these experiences and how new music is playing into it.
This has only been going on for two years.
Look how you swear to it.
Nobody.
You know.
But every day, I'm like, wow, I can't believe I get to do this.
Wow.
I see what happened in the short time.
My God.
Yeah.
When I used to play with the real-to-real tape decks.
In my room is a boy.
You know, it's like, that was the dream.
Yeah.
I could have known a little studio here.
And that's what I got.
Yeah.
I got it.
And it's still a mess.
Well, we, I remember my, my dad and I always play with our Ray Fox.
Yeah.
It's real-to-real.
Sure.
You know, and we taped and we did.
And now.
You do some echo.
Dubbed.
That's right.
Downsing bouncing from channels.
A lot of fun.
Cutting with a razor blade.
Yeah.
Good times.
All right.
Now we're officially old and foggy.
Yeah.
All right.
So you want to come tomorrow?
Uh, right.
Depends on if I, if I'm doing something more.
I'm so sorry.
That'd be so appreciated.
All right.
Thank you very much, Lady Patricia.
Well, you're welcome.
Trembed.
I love you too.
Bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it.
On the high performance podcast delivery network from pod show and line light networks.
I love it.