This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy!
Delta Sierra Charlie 458.
Okay, Grandpa, just talking to the microphone.
What?
Yeah, right there.
Right, yeah, that thing right there, the big circle.
Well, yeah, that's the pop filter.
No, we're not getting a pop, okay, just read the paper.
Alright, alright.
Yeah, there you go, right there.
Right.
You can't, you're always counting things.
Back in my day, we didn't count everything.
What?
It wasn't all these numbers.
What do you mean?
Just when you did something and you were done with it.
The DSC.
Yeah, that's Adam Curry, he's...
What?
He's a pilot, so say tailwinds.
So I'm off facing tailwinds, like you were a pilot.
Tailwinds, what did I float?
I'm sorry.
Ah, geez.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
And time's free
I'm playing the game, I'm playing the new year
I'm just laughing, I'm just running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running
I'm just falling for you
It's hard to make new
Guess it's hard to leave
It's hard for money
It's within me
I'm just playing the old one
I'm really got to thank Jeff Hins for making that suggestion. I no idea they showed up on the
pod save music network Jeff of course from the Friday night dance party podcast.
The Carmen Apicy Project which of course I have a member that coming out.
Now in the pod save music network there's three songs gunna rain days or nights
and what you just heard was nobody knew and the way the Carmen Apicy Project works.
Carmen man he's he's been around. Of course on drums he's a very well-known drummer.
Tony Franklin is on this you know him from blue murder probably from white snake,
Kelly Keeling on bass. He was in baton Rouge and I and I have a feeling that Ron
Ron actually produced a baton Rouge record. I have to ask him about that.
So the the guest solo guitar on nobody knew was Brian May of Queen fame. As if you couldn't
hear that very distinct sound. On the other songs that are also on the P and then you want to check
him out gunna rain guitar solo is by Richie Sambora and days or nights. Michael Butler's going to
love that. That's probably why it's on the pod save music network the new Ted Newgeon doing guitar
solo. Excellent. I mean what a way to kick off a football Friday because we really are all
footballer by the end of the week. Football fucked up beyond all recognition. This is the daily
source code episode 458 everybody how you doing coming to you from Curry Cottage in the
affluent suburb of Surrey known as Gilford. Let me get the Joseph Jaffee stuff out of the way right
away. No in no way have we gotten enough punishment in or any really good ideas. There's some good
comments over at daily source code.com on pod show plus. Let me see comic strip blogger things I
shouldn't let him air the second part of the interview regardless. What was another one that came
in somewhere? What is this? LePierre says you may have held your interview hostage but I think it's
pretty safe to say you held his balls hostage. So so far nothing really earthshattering this
coming. This is kind of normal for a pod cast because it does take a couple days for people to catch
up. So I think we'll have to wait until Monday as we have some suggestions streaming over the weekend.
Hey Adam it's Carlos again. Just a scene show for five six and I've started upon a punishment. I think
that Joseph should get a set and amount of listeners to your show so I'm increasing your traffic
from his pod cast and anyone who's done that he can play the interview. So thanks bye.
Yo he's already done that really just by I mean that was the whole point I think and that's kind
of where I'm a little torn over this. I see I disagree fundamentally with what Joseph did by saying
I'm not going to air the second half of your interview because you haven't sent me any link love. I just
thought that was really wrong and I think that he still thinks it's a joke and that I'm actually
making a this is some kind of traffic driving thing that I'm into or that we're both doing together.
Not at all. I certainly don't need his traffic. I don't care if he gets I want everyone to be
very successful. It's not about that. It's just about he was rude. It's fucking rude. That's all.
And he keeps sending me email messages. Are we okay? Are we on the right track yet? And it's like
it's not a game. This is real. And it won't be done until I think the listeners have spoken.
At least the listeners to the Charlie because it's bestowed all that crap on you, apologies.
Hey great news today. Let me just bring this up in the outline. One of our very own board members
at Potio Ray Lane became a granddaddy. So we welcome Walker Hugh Torrance Rollinson born at
945 PM last night, Stanford Hospital, 7 pounds, 14 ounces, 20 and 1 quarter inches.
Welcome him to the extended Potio family. Mom and baby are doing just fine.
Looking at the pictures that came in over email today. Granddaddy's doing very fine as well.
Oh man fantastic. The big question is of course. And this is a fantastic opportunity. We know
Ray Lane is a scruncher. Will it carry through two generations of lanes? That is the question.
Hello Adam. Happy birthday. Happy belated birth. That should say from Colorado. Just catching up on
some DSCs from the past week, listening to 454. And after hearing about you to loud of gas incident,
I'm glad to hear that it was nothing more than a butt-puckering experience. Now we pilots,
we get those on occasion to remind us how fallible we really are. And I could tell that it was
that it was one of those experiences for you. My only take on the whole thing is, hey, use your checklist.
Checklists, of course, are designed to keep us out of trouble and to make sure that we
do all the things that we think we can do via routine. But as you know, as soon as we get distracted or change the routine,
that's when things get screwed up. Just like, you know, for getting to put down your landing gear because you dropped your pencil,
you know, it's that sort of thing. So use the checklist, please. I've enjoyed your work since the days of MTV
and hope to hear you for a long time on the DSC. So take care and folder. Thanks, Michael,
I appreciate your comments. That's a good question. I don't know, Robin from Inside Work, he's a pilot.
I think he may be a scruncher. I don't recall. I should write all that down. You know, this wasn't
really a case of following the checklist. This was actually a case of following the aircraft manual,
which is the most interesting thing about it because it really what happened was an accordance with
the manual, but not in accordance with reality. Now, a butt buckering moment, you better believe it.
When you're engine quits anywhere, even if for a second, it's a butt bucker. No kidding.
Dan and Captain Dan and I spent a couple minutes kind of glancing at each other after that. I'm going like,
fuck man. Dude, that could have been really bad. We were really, really lucky.
So the aircraft manual really, you carry that with you, at least I do. We have it within, within
reach, actually, all to always within reach. For instance, let's say that the landing gear
didn't come down, that we didn't get three greens. There is a way to manually pump them down.
I've never, of course, had to do that, and there is a procedure you have to follow,
and you wouldn't need the checklist for that, but really, I guess it's a checklist within the
manual. So we followed the manual, actually. You know, if the, if the right tank is depleted,
switched to the left tank, turns out that the indicators that Sessna makes are pieces of crap.
So it's always flying on both, but I appreciate it, and you're absolutely right. And
regarding landing with your gear up, you know, that really are only two types of pilots.
Those that have made a gear up landing, and those that will.
For Adam in Great Britain, dial plus four, four, two, seven, six, eight, one, three,
seven, five, three, plus four, four, two, seven, six, eight, one, three, seven, six, eight, one, three,
seven, five, three. Thanks for going on the daily source code. Good bye. Oh,
fold it as concha. Jeff Smith, everybody. He heard this shout out. He heard the call. He couldn't
stand those horrible jingles. I was actually they weren't horrible, but these are definitely nice.
Jeff, thank you so much. I love it. So you got the numbers now. They're embedded into your brain.
There should be in your cell phone. Whenever you're hearing something, whenever you think about something,
just pick up the phone and call. You know, they're not to be about the show. Can be about anything.
Of course, sometimes it's about the show. Hi, Adam. This is Mark Furnish from Albany, New York.
I don't fold or scrunched because quite frankly, I don't go to the bathroom. I think. Okay. So
he's pretty much set himself up. He's a full of it, I guess, on toldry.
Anyway, I'm really interested about what you were talking about editing your podcast and taking
up the ears and the arms and things like that. You know, that's a good point podcasting should be raw.
No, hold on a second. I really want you guys to listen to this because he's going to
misunderstand what I'm saying and I think he doesn't really have a grasp of where my head is at,
which granted could take some effort to get in the same headspace.
So exactly that. I just heard me go, you know, I wouldn't edit that. This show is live to MP3.
You know, I record everything in real time, right off a cast blaster, right onto the MP3 file.
I don't take anything out. I don't think I've, I can't recall ever editing a daily source code
post post creation because I like it when it's, you know, there's an energy that you have to have.
And I don't, I don't want to safety net. It makes me, it's, yeah, that's really it. It's like not having a
safety net. So if I want to reduce the arms and arms and if it really bothers the audience,
I'll do it. I'll work on it. My audience will help me in fact. Charlie listeners have done just that.
But I think you take, you're failing to put into consideration the fact that
good people like yourself have the best top-notch podcasting equipment available to you.
Uh-huh. The best top-notch podcasting. Do you hear the hums in the background? Do you hear the
crunching and the crackling? You sound like you're recording from a professional studio, which you are.
Got to stop you, everybody. I'm not. I'm not podcasting from a professional studio.
I have a cast blaster, which will run on any Windows machine.
I have a, uh, a high-l, PR 40 microphone, which pretty much is is like the, I think it's become
some form of standard. It's a very inexpensive microphone. I believe it's under $200. The mixer
that I have is a sound craft, $150. He listened to this potential meter here. Actually, it's not
crackling now, but it's, it's really, really a sub-standard piece of kit.
And that's the loop. The only thing I have is a stereo valve processor, which, again, you can
buy a compressor for $100. So you could be done for about $500. That is not the type of
studio I think you're describing. Which is fantastic. And I wish I could do that as well.
But when you're just working from a common computer microphone and like a free audio program,
like Audacity, your program sounds like shit. And you want to do, uh,
Audacity has nothing to do with your program sounding like shit. It's just a recorder.
And your cast blaster is free for, for anything, uh, 10 minutes are under. I think there's
enough value there to buy it if you want to make longer shows. But Audacity is fantastic.
Now, that's not a real-time live thing, but it will record. It will let you edit. It will let you
process the sound. It will let you do everything that professionals actually do. In fact, if I used
Audacity, my show would probably sound more, quote, professional. Not the sound I'm looking for, though.
Anything you can't have a try to make it feel better. And if that, I think that means kind of like
taking out the other the eyes or quite frankly, it becomes unlicable. I'd really like to see an
experiment from you sometime. And I don't know if it's even possible. But I'd like to see your
record your podcast from a, just a normal computer microphone that you could get at a radio
shack, or I don't know if they have radio checks in Europe, but any kind of computer store,
and using a free audio software program and do your podcast like that to see how it sounds.
Now, you have years of broadcasting experience. So you sound polished as it is, and that's a good thing.
But I'd be really curious to see how a polished podcast you sound using just every day, cheap,
normal equipment on a podcast, and see how it sounds, and not using the expensive equipment that
the top notch podcast is used. I think that'd be interesting. And if you ever do that sometime,
I think it'd be really fun to hear. Take care Adam. All right. So let me just respond to a couple
things there. First of all, the editing and the quality of the studio. I mean, look, there's a lot of
people on the radio who are in million dollar studios that just sound like shit. Don't belong
there whatsoever. Lots of them. So, you know, it's, it's all about just the quality of the content,
and not about the, the quality of the sound, or, but I will do the experiment with you. Hold on a second.
Let me, let me just grab, I do have a cheap microphone. Here we go. In fact, I, I'll,
we'll say that I don't even have a stand, okay? So I'm holding it in my hand now. Now the trick
would be to turn off the processing. Let me see if I can do this. Hello, hello, hello, okay. So this
is me on a cheap microphone with, so I've turned off that stereo valve processor. Nothing is running
through it. I got to tell you, I don't think it sounds all that bad. I really don't. And I still
hear all kind of all the, you know, the, the crackling and the, and I hear a very distinct hum in the
background. So, you know, will this stop people from listening? I just don't see it, dude. And I just don't
see it. Now, the, what I'm talking about is clearly something else. It's about the, about being
people, about being human. This is not about having, you know, in fact, I think that if, if I,
if you don't use professional sounding processing, it's even better because it's so much more
distinctive. Yeah, this, this is what it sounds like. This is what top 40 radio sounds like.
Oh, man. Hey, everybody. It's a hot dragon flavor for us. You 100. Yeah. Yeah. And then we've got to,
oh, sorry. I got to go to this one. And then, of course, you always have the,
WLT, W light FM. You know, then you've got like the news guys. And in the, and in New York,
news today, Bob, Cassinola is standing by for Bob, what you got down the on the street. You know,
so I think it's more interesting to hear just a regular raw sound with all the
warts and the bumps on it. All right. Let me go back. Now, I will say one thing. I have found in,
in the past, that having a great sound in your headphones, which, of course, is just as much
a function of the headphones, as it is a function of a function of, of your setup and your microphone,
it really does motivate. For me, it does. I really feel in tune. And yeah, I just feel like I'm,
I'm in the show a lot more, like it's really, um, enveloping my entire head.
Smoked some of the only herbs seems to help, too, by the way. Those Republicans in the
audience have already purchased CDs that they are non-refundable.
George Bush lied about weft the mass destruction. Cleating got a blow job.
So there was deception added to the suction, but
Cleating got a blow job. Now what's worse, starting a war, are keeping your coheibas in a human human door.
Oh!
And who got impeached? And what for? All right. Cling got a blow job.
George Bush vacationed Juan New Orleans drowned.
He sat in a classroom with a tower's falling down.
He fucked up FEMA, which fucked up Katrina.
Not to mention the conventions of Geneva,
with 23 civilians murdered in Haditha.
Now how can a man without a brain,
cause a nation so much pain,
cause a world to feel such hate for the so-called United States and how?
Cause a Congress held but act in the face of every fact I have presented here.
The comparison couldn't be more clear.
George Bush authorized leaks of classified information.
To make the case for attacking a sub-renation.
Well, they couldn't shoot him, so they had to shame him.
But if you know a single honest politician, name him,
and you've seen Hillary, can you blame her?
I mean, I'm sorry, Hillary.
We all got a take one for the two.
George Bush, fun, sex head that says that condoms don't work.
If they did it, both your daughters would be framing you, jerk.
Bush lied about his bus for driving drunk.
Clinton's biggest crime was having spunk.
And for choosing a statue, less than statue-esque,
and hiding her under the oval office days.
What else, George? What else have you done?
So research, abstinence, what else have you learned about?
Global warming, missile defense, going a wall from the National Garden.
Fun somewhere, everybody. It's not that hard.
Jack Abramoff, Valerie Plame, Al Qaeda's links to Saddam Hussein.
I will grieve, can you lay our record deficit today?
We're tapping in for leaking water, boarding power, hoarding,
great destroying, crazy, plowing, load of skinless steps.
And to my part, I'll play the pond.
If that's what it takes to get you gun,
I'm on my knees, George.
You can't find that on the pod save music network yet.
Perfect for a Friday. Eric Schwartz, Clinton got a blowjob.
But David E. Palito, my buddy in New York,
that guitar man from New York who plays in Central Park, who has his own podcast.
I love the company. He's working on it.
I heard this song on his episode of Think104.
I'm telling you, David E. Palito, Eric Schwartz,
these kinds are the dealings of our generation.
This is awesome stuff. These are cool songs.
You can sing along. They have a great message.
Very funny lyrics are just right on target.
I was offended though. I have to be honest about the Hillary Clinton comment.
I don't think that was necessary.
You know, Hillary's not ugly. She's a very intelligent woman.
No, I think she was cute back in the day.
Oh, I can't wait for the voice mail on this one.
We can't transmit because something else is already transmitted somewhere close to the secret storm.
What kind of transformation is it?
Could be a soft phone? Maybe a radio.
Can we listen to it?
Let me get the frequency first.
This is a generally speaking podcast network update.
Hi, everybody. My name's Cliff Ravenscraft.
And I'm Stephanie Ravenscraft.
Together, we record and produce the generally speaking weekly loss podcast,
a fan-based podcast devoted to the hit ABC show loss.
From the beginning, our purpose has been to take the casual loss viewer
and turn them into lost a hollocks.
It's work, too. We have thousands of listeners from all over the world, including some of the cast from the show.
Each week, we review the current episode of Lost, where we break the show down into two main segments.
Character analysis and exploring the mystery.
We also keep everybody up to date with Lost and the news.
You can learn who's going to be interviewed on what TV talk show,
and where you can find access to special deleted scenes on the net and things of that nature.
And of course, we're always happy to take a call from our listener line,
where you can be part of our show with your own thoughts and theories.
Here's a clip from a call we received from someone who any lost a hollock would recognize.
Hey, Cliff, Stephanie, it's for it.
Um, heard you guys calling, honey.
We want to invite you to come and get Lost with us.
You can find us on the web at generally speakingpodcast.com.
And if you listen to the generally speaking, weekly Lost podcast,
you'll understand why thousands of our listeners are saying to themselves.
We're going to need to watch that again.
I got to tell you, I'm a big lost head.
Is that starting again? Has the new season started?
Of course, I only watch it on, I buy it on iTunes.
And I usually have a marathon with myself.
I have two types of marathons.
One is iTunes.
When I see a Lost on iTunes, so I load it up.
And I load it up on the computer.
I've really tried the video I pod on the airplane.
And I start to hurt my neck after a while.
And my wrist gets limp.
And then, of course, there's the problems when I'm watching Lost.
So I watch it on the computer in iTunes.
And then I have Comcast cable at the condo in San Francisco.
And I always have a marathon of ontourage,
because you can get those on demand.
Everything's blurring together, my friends.
It really is.
But still, you know, the really nice cinematic stuff,
like Lost, I can't watch that on a small screen.
That's insulting to myself.
I'm not even getting half the, I wind up watching episodes of Lost.
Again, on television.
Of course, I like it.
But I've just amazed by the information that I actually missed
by watching it on a small screen.
Something to be said for that, I think.
Hello, I don't reach again here from UK.
I'm just driving back from work.
It's just gone midnight.
I just listened to the entire stuff.
It was a great person that was on Radio 4 today.
So it's all due away.
It's Thursday now.
No.
Sorry.
It's well.
No.
Oh, shit.
This is why I don't like stuff edited out.
How beautiful is this?
It's all like, anyway.
It's now Friday, but it was Thursday Thursday night.
Probably one of about half past eleven.
And it was called at three cool trees.
It's just quite a good radio program.
It was about how Nashville, a lot of control of the reckoning.
It's literally a channel as mentioned.
And sort of just basically how no one had a complete stop of it.
So you might want to listen to it.
It was quite musical.
A lot of things that I know you've been saying in this sort of some sort of perspective
of how the whole thing is managed by business.
Well, when you think we have quite as much an experience of it,
you just don't notice.
But hearing that from the CRS, then, you know, that was very clear message anyway.
Well, I would like to check it out.
I'm treating it on BBC.
Listen again on the website.
And I say it was called three calls from the trees.
And it was not half past eleven on BBC right there for one Thursday.
Anyway, thanks so much.
Right.
Hey.
Yeah, you know what?
I have.
It's good to have.
I have a set of amount of time.
I set aside every single morning for, for my daily round of podcast.
And I always have a couple of what I would call mainstream slots.
I have a channel.
I actually built up.
And then that channel just feels stuff in.
I think I call it the news channel.
You can get it off of my podshowplus site,
Adam.podshow.com.
And you can subscribe to my entire channel if you like.
And use that.
And listen to the same things I've listened to in the morning.
So I, I, I, I, I, I dropped one MPR show and the New York Times front page to listen to that program.
Of course, I'll have show notes.
I'll have a link in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com to the BBC.
Listen again service, which is kind of, it's pretty cool because you can find what you want.
But you don't have a lot of control.
It's all streaming and you can get a jump ahead a minute.
Or, you know, or 15 minutes.
It's, I don't really dig how they're doing that.
But yes, this is a show you must listen to.
I really recommend it.
And I can understand how you wanted to call in the minute the minute you heard that.
It really talks about how this stuff works, you know, how clear channel functions,
how the, and the country, country music business.
Wow, man, you want to talk about cut throat?
Oh, yeah.
So give that a listen.
If you want to know why, what we're doing is such an incredible revolution.
Hey there.
It's Angie B.
I love spirals and the chill cast.
And I just started a brand new video blog over on Podshow called,
Chillin' of Angie B.
What do you know?
If you've ever been curious to put a face to the voice, well, this is your chance.
I'm just going to be talking about my life and career and whatever else comes to mind.
It should be lots of fun and I'm just getting started.
So, once you head on over and check it out at AngieBchat.podshow.com.
Hope to see you there.
Oh, Angie.
So, Angie's already cut her side of hidden desires.
Which is a drama we're doing together.
So, I have to cut my lines and it'll have to interspersed.
I'm going to do that this weekend along with a new perversion for profits.
So, that should be out either Sunday night or Monday.
It's going to be really busy.
A Ron's coming to town, he's flying today, so he'll arrive tomorrow, mid afternoon.
Of course, he'll be completely wrecked.
So, I'm pretty sure Saturday evening and Sunday and Monday and Tuesday and Wednesday,
I'll be in the city in this, if London town.
We've got some pretty cool stuff working on with something special for us on Wednesday.
I'll tell you about that later on next week.
So, it's busy, but I'm going to be able to get some of this stuff out.
Time for another perversion for profit.
And, Angie, I loved it.
I loved it.
I loved just sitting there watching you.
That was incredibly cool.
Angie just sitting there with a microphone.
Nice.
Porsons of the show brought to you by the Accurate Target cast about the Accurate.
I was at the RDX SUV.
Find that at Accurate.podshow.com.
And if you want to hear all of the finalists for the podshow ad challenge,
create the earthling commercial.
All of the, so you can go to ad challenge.
A podshow.com to see what that was all about.
Of course, now you can't enter anymore.
The finalists, though, and we'll be doing more ad challenges.
I'm sure of it.
The finalists for earthling, you can find an earthling.podshow.com.
And there's another guy on podshow who I always rest on.
No, I don't mean that.
I have his support.
Every single end of the week.
When Friday comes around, I know that I won't have to worry about the music,
because the music college is on the scene.
His name.
I'd like to make a motion too.
I was like really stupidly dramatic.
I fucked it up.
You're on her.
Please don't bang that gavel.
You can try this cowbell out.
Let's don't give a nod.
To the hardest work in lawyers,
Jersey,
I'm a man.
Yeah.
He's Jersey.
I'm a man.
Yeah.
You're on her.
What do you say?
He might even live with this case.
Jersey,
I'm a man.
Yeah.
He's Jersey.
I'm a man.
Jersey,
I'm a gentleman now.
He's Jersey.
I'm a man.
Yeah.
No.
What's up?
I'm happy for our Friday.
He's Jersey Todd, the official musical, just of The Cha Cha.
Hey.
You got your cowbell out.
Yep.
I'm here.
All right.
Hey listen.
I've got some really, really special for you today.
Devon,
Allmond's Honey Tribe.
Yeah.
Devon, Allmond.
Sound familiar?
Yeah.
Allmond brothers.
Devon's of the family.
And don't think of this as just an Allmond brothers.
off because this is great stuff coming out of live wire recordings.
They stuck a ton of stuff on the pod save music network very, very quietly.
Go out and find it because they're all good stuff.
And Devon Almond's Honey Tribe has this great song out called Torch.
You're gonna absolutely love it.
You're gonna put a dent in that silly cowbell.
So check this out.
This is Devon Almond's Honey Tribe on the Daily Source Code.
You're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in it because you're gonna put a dent in
Put a dent in it okay
wake up wake up don't wrong
Oh
There's a human voice in your heart there is a choice
Don't fight the man who you know that you're in hell
Get on the porch and light your torch on over town
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Take down the doors and light your torch up the ground
The right way to go on the burn
Right, right, right, right
I'm afraid of going for a night when it comes
Get on the porch and light your torch on over town
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm afraid of going for a night when it comes
I'm afraid of going to Dark ocean
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I'm ready for Rockstar Supernova.
Wow, Jersey Tyler, the official musicologist of the Charlie, thank you so much for
Devon Alman.
You can find that on the Podsave Music Network links in the show notes at DailySourceCode.com.
Have a great weekend everybody, perversion for profit coming up after the weekend as well
as a whole another week of the Charlie.
Adam at podshow.com DailySourceCode.com and have a good weekend, bye-bye.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery
network from Podshow and Limelight Networks.
I love it.