It's Cali Lewis from Geek Brief TV.
I just listened to episode 1 of Shadow Falls and it scared me.
I know I'm the fearless leader and all, but there are things that get to me in this dinner.
I'm not sure I'll be able to sleep tonight.
Maybe never again.
This podcast is brought to you by Ponjo and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
The show will give you a special code, get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
The show will give you a special code.
Do you have some business to go to?
Just business, everyone.
Yes, special. What's going on?
We have an idea to find a flyer object.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on a second.
What does it say on the object?
Uh, or um, we're going to get a test.
D-S-C-4-3-9.
It was $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm testing here's a battle curry.
Beyond the realm of space and time,
I feel a shoe that down my spine
Never felt like this before
Am I only dreaming?
A million miles away tonight
You'll never leave body next to mine
Through your space I'm gonna fly
With you, never so feel your shoe
I'm not true yet
You're around this world
You're a super natural girl
You are a super natural girl
I ain't not
With you too light
You're a super natural girl
You're a reason
It's from London, he hates David Bowie, it's Jimmy Golding, yeah, shades of Bowie, they're
looking into his pots of music network profile page, influences John Lennon David Bowie,
New Young Led Zeppelin, Jeff Buckley, Ah-han, no shit.
Link to that song on the pot of music network from dailysourcecode.com.
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
Coming to you from the affluent subversory known as Gilford, where today it's in the 60s,
so low 60s probably I'd say, it's a chilly, overcast, and around 930 this morning, there
was a knock at the door.
I'm sorry, the buzzer actually rang, as shit, insert buzzer effect here, and there was a box
for addressed to Patricia standing right there on the doorstep, as City Link just sped off,
they just dropped it off, no signature required apparently, inside just a absolutely
stunningly beautiful bouquet of roses, and a card with no name on the card, unfortunately,
but there's some clues as to where it came from.
Here's what the card read, Patricia, happy anniversary, please forgive Adam, he asked me
to get these for you on your anniversary since he was going to be busy, and I got toasted
and forgot, it's all my fault that he got those horrible gas station flowers, whoever did
this, I love you.
Thank you, even though, of course, Patricia knew that that was on the card wasn't true,
even if there was a moment where I actually contemplated saying that I made it off, I'll
say, yeah, no, I wouldn't have done that, now what I have on, but it was nice, first
of all because she got the flowers, she deserved second of all because, she knows that
people are actually out there listening, and are interested in what she has to say and
how she feels about things, fantastic, very much appreciated.
So the UK is in an uproar this morning, news came that it, all the airports, I think
Heathrow is the main one, no hand baggage allowed on airplanes, there were, I guess, the
Scotland Yard and the SAS and whoever else were all hot on the trails of some quote-unquote
terrorist, terrorist organization who were planning to blow up planes flying from the UK
and planning to use liquid explosives.
So at the time of the making of this charlie, it's a quarter to one in the afternoon, no
other updates on that, but airplane traffic or all plane traffic is just severely crippled.
And for those of you who wrote to me and said, hey, what's the deal with your own plane?
There's no problem, obviously, I mean, they don't care if I'm going to blow up my own
plane.
I don't care if I should about that, so no, there's nothing extra going on there.
Maybe tonight I'll be able to see something on there.
What is that?
I'm subscribed to this very, I love this CNN podcast all in a second.
Let me just look at my collection here.
Yeah, reliable sources, you've got to check this out.
This is CNN kind of looking at itself about how mainstream media is reporting.
And of course, a lot of it is about the war right now.
Very interesting.
I'll put a link to it.
You can subscribe to it in Potio Plus, of course.
And it's good.
It's like, I know it's like a 20 minute show, but I really like watching that.
And there's another one in case you missed it is another CNN video show.
And it just shows the most unbelievable pieces of video from that week.
It's kind of like a huge Fox news injection coming from CNN once a week.
Oh, yes, oh, it's not.
Oh, she's not here, so I can do this privately.
All right, Amy Mac, ask her size, me, baby.
Hey, Adam, Amy Mac, are you ready for day two of your as per size workout?
Yes, ma'am, the butt is running.
Today, we're going to be doing squats.
You remain standing this time.
All right.
Good, thank you.
Place your feet a little wider than shoulder width apart.
Make sure your toes are facing forward.
Forward, of course.
Now put your hands behind your head.
Make sure your elbows are out to the side.
Find my head behind.
Yeah.
Now you're going to squat like you're sitting down on a chair.
Ready, go, squat on, make sure you stick that booty back.
Yes, booty back to put your weight on your heels.
Oh, my heels.
Three, two, your head and chest, stop.
Yes, head and chest, stop.
Four, make sure your knees don't come over your toes.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Five, good.
Really stick that booty back.
Yeah, it's back.
Six, booty all the way back to all the way.
Seven, eight, keep breathing.
Tell me what's going to be this long.
Nine.
Amy, Amy.
Ten.
Yes, please.
Only 10 more to go.
Watch.
Don't stop, I didn't give you a rest.
Oh, crap.
Keep going.
Keep squat, I'll talk.
Just find out more health and fitness tips.
Check out the fitness attack podcast at fitness.
Hotshow.com.
I'm going to be out of breath for the next few minutes.
So be with him.
It's for a good cause.
Have you seen his ass?
It should say like they're up.
Can I stop?
Anyway, this is Amy Mack, and until next time,
answers the line.
Yes, okay, 20.
Oh, man.
Well, I kind of got lightheaded on that one.
Thanks, Amy Mack, and Patricia thinks she was well.
Keep him coming.
Save my ass, please.
Let's see.
Oh, this is interesting.
Let me just read you this.
C.C. Chapman says that his wife's birthday is this weekend.
It's going to wish her a happy birthday on the podcast.
He thought it would be fun to have some other friends chip in as well.
Her name is Laura.
We were according Friday morning, if I get, I want to be to call in.
That's good.
I got no time for that.
Laura.
Hey, it's Adam.
Happy birthday.
Thank you for letting us use C.C.
Abuse, C.C.
Hope you have a great day weekend.
I've been using internet explorer a little bit these days.
I'm completely out of breath from the, quote, from the
ascercise squats.
Very interesting.
It's not as bad as I recall internet explorer being.
I've been kind of on Firefox for a couple of years now.
And I downloaded somehow.
When I, I did something to my window set up and then explore no longer existed.
And there were so many applications for some reason bypassing the default and
asking for explore to start up that I downloaded iE7, the beta version is pretty interesting.
Not bad.
It certainly does Ajax stuff very well.
Couple of, uh, wait a minute.
No, no, no.
I'm going to do this one first.
Yesterday we announced the winner of Patricia's panties in the guest, the, who I love
it, ladies name at the end of our de-gap insertion on all pod show podcast.
Rob Buston was the winner and has this to say about his fabulous project.
Hey Adam, it's Rob us then the winner of the latest contest to guess the identity of
the I love it girl at the end of the pod show promo.
Yeah, um, well, that sounds like a great prize.
My wife might not like my getting another woman's panties in the mail.
I mean, you know, why just get like that sometimes I can put them on my head over my
ears while I listen to the podcast that you want to push it on or is that to weird?
But all right, I don't know.
I mean, don't ever think that giving iPods away is a bad thing.
All right.
I give a podcast, by the way, I'm the host of the of the jersey jam cast, which is on
pod show at jersey jamcast.pot show.com, I'm Buds with jersey Todd, a jersey guys got
a stick together.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I know what you mean.
My brother.
I don't want to meet my brother, but I've never heard ever in my life.
And I lived in jersey for quite a while, never once did I hear a jersey boy turned
down a pair of panties, but if you want me to send you something else, I'll think about
it.
Oh, I'll get jostle on the case.
She's been really good at sending out the prizes.
I got like, you know, prize package people now to send stuff out and came up with an idea
about Angie B of the chill cast.
And of course, I love spirals and I had to do a kind of a soap opera.
And I dragged Marc Yoshimo to name call from pod show LA into it and he totally jumped
on board.
He said, OK, this is great.
We're going to get it going.
It's going to be total soap opera.
So real Wayne and Wanda stuff.
And I think that we're going to let you determine the storyline.
But it's supposed to be hot and steamy.
And I guess we'll do it once a week or whatever we can and I'd ask, of course, Angie, if
she wanted to participate.
At a long time, no talk, huh?
Yeah, I'm totally down for the idea of you and I doing a podcast together.
Angie, I just want to make sure you completely understand it's not a podcast.
It is a hot steamy audio soap opera.
Just want to make sure you understand.
Be great to work with you a little bit more one-on-one.
By the way, I sent Petrition email.
I think, you know, it is high time that you came back to the show and changed the subject
away from folding versus scrunching.
Please, I don't think I can take any more of that.
Anyway, talk to you soon.
Looking forward to an Angie B. That's for show.
Got a couple comments about my Pito suckage for those of you who missed it over the
past weekend was flying my airspeed indicator malfunction and it's a pressure or
ram air pressure, kind of mechanical system, this Pito tube stuff and it's that little
thing that sticks out of the side of every single aircraft, even on the big 747s that
happen right up there near the nose and they kind of look like, they look like machine
gun actually and so the thinking was that a bug had crawled up in there and it blocked
the entry to the Pito tube and here's what's interesting.
The advice I received, I'll tell you from whom in a second, was to see if I could suck
anything out of there, if there was a bug that had crawled in, try to suck it out.
Boy, did the aviators amongst us respond?
Hey, I'm Mr. Rubbin calling another topic at all on my way to Mexico, I thought about
your Pito tube problem, here's where it comes to mind, first off I don't want to end
up sucking or blowing on any Pito tube and first if you're going to do it, you really
got to watch out, make sure you don't have the Pito tube heat on, actually it had been
on, this is one of the things I thought was wrong with it, so this thing that this stick
that's up in the air, if you're flying up at altitude, ice will form in it and then it
will get blocked too, so you have a heater and it literally heats up this metal tube.
So before I started to suck, I did just test and boy, it was extremely hot, you're
right, do not approach a Pito tube, you don't know.
I'm here on your lips, number two, like any analopido tubes, do you really know all the
places that Pito tube has been number three?
That Pito tube is connected to some really sensitive devices, like all Pito tubes, so
I have a calibrated sucked, you could do some damage.
I've been working on my calibrated sucked, my friend.
Now, the actor at potshow.com, that interview is awesome, Ellie Schriner, it's really cool,
some people beside the Eagles, he's on Van Morrison and a whole bunch of other stars.
Yeah, what Robin's talking about here is the target cast that lives at Akira.podshow.com.
I know I plug in this, I'm sure he'll tell us in a second.
Well, it's really cool.
He's re-cutting a whole bunch of these older songs, but he's going in surround sound, so
he's trying to push the DVD, set up for 5.1 surround sound, and that's what that
whole RDX at Akira is set up for surround sound.
He was part of the design team, and then also tuned it to the car, I think it's really
cool.
Why do I know so much?
Because I know the interviewer, she's really hot, and I have naked pictures.
Oh, I stopped right there.
You got naked pictures?
Sorry, you can't have.
Oh, man, I'll send you naked pictures of my wife?
No problem.
Just Google Patricia 5, right there.
She's my wife.
Suzanne.
Check her out.
InsideWorks.com, that's I.N.S.
Y.T.W.O.R.F.
That's Suzanne.
Ben, I work.
Hello.
Bill.
Ben.
Of course.
You're an aviator.
Well, that's not true.
Not all aviators or folders.
So when this air speed indicator problem occurred, I called Wing Commander William, who
does my maintenance.
And this is exactly what he suggested.
He said, well, suck on it.
See, you can get anything out of there.
I said, if it's further than the P2 to itself, then we'll have to blow out the whole
system.
And indeed, that is a multi-day job.
Now, as we all know, it turned out that due to my previous bumpy landing, we'd have to
call almost a hard landing.
Although Patricia didn't complain, so I wasn't all that bad.
The actual indicator had got stuck on the needle stop at the 12 o'clock position.
Just stuck one hair, because, you know, basically when you land you're done at zero
feet, it should be zero feet if everything's calibrated properly.
And so then that bounce probably got it stuck.
But oh boy, there were more aviators checking in on this.
Yeah, I had them.
This is Peter, a listener from Australia.
You'd probably call me an aircraft mechanic, they're Australian Air Force, called me
an avionic technician.
In DSC436, you described how you were trying to clear the P2 probe of the Delta Sierra
by sucking on the end of it.
If you're sucking on the end of a P2 probe, you obviously have no idea of how delicate
the interior components of your airspeed indicator are, please, please, if you think
your P2 probe is blocked, get an aircraft mechanic to have a look at it, those instruments
need to be disconnected and system cleaned out carefully.
Please don't do that.
I would really like to keep on hearing for you.
If you are not blowing in the deal for here and something goes wrong, then I'd be going
to happen.
I do, of course, I completely agree maintenance is everything.
And I'm a little freaked out about it, because I'm definitely going to call the wing
commander now, because he without a doubt told me that it was okay to suck on the P2 too.
I think when he t-shirts now, you know, don't just suck on any P2 tube, do you know
where it has been?
I had him.
Is this Michelle from Mr. Perl's?
Oh, man, guys, if you've never listened to whispered pearls, you've got to listen to
this podcast.
If you want to hear women talking openly about feelings, F screw the feelings about
sex, this is the podcast for you.
I, you know, I've been hearing a lot of guys in your podcast recently.
Oh, I know.
I know way too many guys talking about war and talking about soccer and
talking about that toilet paper thing that we're not going to go into.
And I haven't been hearing a whole lot of women other than your wonderful wife Patricia.
So I thought I'd send you a comment, because, you know, we, the girls of whispered pearls
always strive to give a man what he yearns for.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you for that comment about the podcast, Expo.
What's up with that?
No sex thing.
Yeah, that is kind of funky.
No sex podcast allowed at the Expo, at least no panel required.
I love your voice, Michelle.
Well, I hope you go.
And I hope I see you there.
There was so much fun to be had by the pool last time.
And what was this I heard you say somewhere in there about liking orgies?
I don't know.
I think that was just a fever dream I was having.
So this is Michelle signing off from whisper pearls.
Oh, Michelle, thank you.
And thank you so much for the picture of your sister.
I mean, how great is this?
Michelle sends me this really sexy comment and then sends me a semi-nude picture of her
sister.
Oh, you know how to make an old man smile.
I appreciate it.
First male numbers, programming in your phone right now, plus one, two, zero, one,
six, two, five, six, three, five, seven.
You can reach me anytime through that number.
If you're in the UK, you want to use our London number.
There's no problem.
Oh, two, zero, seven, six, eight, one, three, seven, five, three.
Yeah, because we're bad.
We're nationwide.
We're international.
We got phone numbers in Jersey and London.
It's almost the same kind of place.
I heard my sister's Willow's podcast.
She did another, from the Hills of Florence, which I've pointed to before.
And now, my nephew, her son, that's my nephew, right, her son.
Who I think is, how does Mateo now?
He's 37, right, you know, I should let you hear this, hold on a second.
This will freak you out.
He's really, really, really sweet.
Let me see, the name of his podcast is the Pacino podcast.
So it's patino.ponsio.com, let me see, did I get that right?
Yeah.
His last name is Paci.
So that makes kind of sense that we came up with the patino.
But he heard his mom, my sister, Doopodcast, and now he's completely crazy about doing
podcasts.
And it's like, every day, he's like, Mom, Mom, Mom, we have to do another podcast.
And it's not necessarily the podcast that he likes.
He really loves the whole, uh, pod save music aspect of it.
Let me just let you hear a little bit of his, it's just too cute for words, a little bit
of his podcast.
See what happened.
Did, what?
Oh, here we go.
I play it.
He'll love this.
He has the cute.
I don't even know what he could be saying that is all.
Hey, this is Dan Patterson from the Creepy Sleepy Show.
You want creepy without the sleepy?
Check out Shadow Falls, pod shows brand new audio drama series.
It's terrifying.
But don't.
Don't.
See.
Let's go.
Echo, soon on Mateo, soon on a different set.
But at the moment, soon on a set of things in Bahansa, I thought you were cool.
Can I get out soon?
Pudcast.
I'm sorry, I'm not sure, so I'm going to make a call.
All right.
I wish anybody was saying, I'm sure Franco from Rockcast, Italy.
I would be very, very proud.
Play that Chubby Checker, but yes, today, if you were listening to Syria, satellite stars
102, then you didn't hear it.
I said, just go to dailysourceco.com, but it was this whole controversy about Chubby
Checker versus the original author and performer of the Twist Hang Ballard, PW Fenton,
sent this great piece in.
And so PW followed up with an email.
Hang Ballard told me they did try to screw him out of his royalties, but a copyright
search revealed he'd copyrighted the Twist Four Times.
He re-registered it every time he tweaked it.
As early as 1958, the court tell that his 1958 version was the source of the hit version
and Hank got all of the composer royalties, which is 50% of all royalties.
He had a comfortable life in Southern California, never retired though he kept performing
an oldie shows right up to his death in 2003.
That's cool, isn't it?
So he didn't get it.
I was so sure that he would have gotten screwed, but he had to go fight for it.
That's for sure.
Even though it was plain and simple and clear, he had to go fight for it.
Hopefully a lot of those days are over.
Cause boy, that's a day's suck.
Let me just see what's coming up on Syria Stars 102 for you.
Right after this show, the Daily Source Code, let's see, we have Pacific Coast Hellway, then
it's Dawn and Drew Soccer, Groll Incorporated, Coming Up, Digital Flotson, Email Girl
Talk, East Radio, we wind it up with Scott Seagler between 930 and 10 tonight, right
here on Syria Stars 102.
I'll see you guys back here tomorrow.
Everybody wave goodbye to the serious listeners.
Bye.
Of course, they miss all the good stuff, right?
Like the host.
Andrew Boyz, author of the agency, Sam Dwarr.
From the web kitchen in Belgium, this is the kitchen cast of the kitchen cast of the
kitchen cast.
Let's check that out.
Hey Adam, it's search from Belgium, I made a 34-year-old flash to call for a long time
Charlie listener, and I thought I'd give that podcasting thing to go myself.
So last night, I finished the pilot episode of the kitchen cast.
Now don't worry, it's not a cooking show, and I'm monthly juggling around with tomatoes
and spices and stuff.
It's a show about technology, about flash and stuff I find on the web.
So now I really need some listener feedback, so I invite you to go to kitchencastonpotchow.com
and let me know what you think.
Oh, and one-witting?
Yeah.
Fuller.
Yeah, of course.
Thank you for listening, stay subscribed.
Welcome to the show.
I think it was about the morning when I woke up, there were 63 comments.
You know, everyone's a couple days behind, but we had a major de-gap problem where shows
we're stopping after the first 25 seconds of the podcast, not just daily source code,
but basically across the pod show, podcast delivery network.
Yes, it was a bug, and it's interesting how these bugs flow, and it's like, you may
hear one or two things from someone you think, well, you know, maybe that's specific to their
machine or they're set up, and then you get a couple more, and then before you know
it, this is avalanche, and what's interesting is we actually fixed the problem yesterday.
So I think everyone's DSC 438 was just played without any stopping, but the avalanche
of people calling in just continues, and I completely appreciate it.
I can't respond to everybody, so hopefully if you sent in a bug report, there was some
really good ones, you know, people sending in, all kinds of great, you know, data points
and information.
It's so cool to have you guys helping out debug this stuff.
We got it fixed.
Actually, he had to call Andrew Grummit, he was an exemplification, because the de-gap is kind
of his baby, and I would have to say, because of all the great information you gave us,
we were easy for us to track it down and stomp the bug.
Still took work, of course, but, and so too, have many, many people sent me the notice
that Durand-Dran is buying an island in second life, and going to be performing live.
Well, I think that's my cue.
I think when Durand-Dran shows up, it's time for me to leave.
Nothing against Durand-Dran.
I like the guys, I always like them music, but if you want to talk about 80s icons, that
is definitely Durand-Dran is a true 80s icon, and I'd like to distance myself a little
bit from that.
I don't want to say, you know, it seems like second life is going to become a place
for washed up 80 superstars to gather, not don't want to be a part of that.
So I'm a little bit in flux, I know it, because I know what works and doesn't work
in second life, and you just can't build any sizable audience because the system can't
handle it.
So it just doesn't seem like it's really worth it.
It's fun.
Still like hanging out once and a while at the island, but now the Durand-Dranis have
moved in.
I think I'm going to have to cut out.
The Podshow ad challenge is closing.
We have, I think, 13 or 14 finalists, and in the next week and a half, we'll be playing
some of these finalists here on the daily source code on other Podshow podcasts as well
of course, and only one of them can win, but is all about creating the message yourself.
So instead of the company packaging all their information into a 30 second in your
face slot, take your time.
Come up with something interesting, something to listen to, something that might even
be considered content.
Is your computer a hacker magnet?
It won't be anymore, because Earthlinke is here to save the day.
Yes, it's worth it.
With downloads faster than speeding bullet, and firewall, it is more powerful than a
look on the motor.
It has an anti-virus system that cleanses your PC with the clickable mouse.
It's a blur.
It's Earthlinke.
Perfect internet from outer space that links to Earth, with powers and abilities far
greater than those of normal high speed, and prices solo that it will blow you out of
this world.
So make the right decision and turn to Earthlinke as your internet provider.
So if you win with that, I guess Michael Butler is going to get a PC or ass, huh?
For American Heartbreaks, last of the super heroes.
Interesting.
Hey, it's Miles.
And Steve from the strip podcast.
The past few months have been crazy for us.
We broke big news that Harris Bray was closing, and that Liza Manelli is coming to Vegas
to headline, and our interviews, as usual, produce several juicy nuggets.
Here's Andrew Lloyd Webber being caught off guard.
The name of the production here is not Phantom of the Opera.
It's Phantom.
So as big as spectacular.
It was that a decision that you made.
To be honest with you, you would lose the thing on this.
It was always a breed that was going to be Android with the center that is the Opera.
You lose me on that.
Then there was Joan Rivers offering up this defense of Star Jones.
She just jumped the gun.
They were going to give it a goodbye party.
They were going to make it a whole different thing.
And she's very smart.
They get it from getting fired.
I'll do it on my terms.
And don't let it look like this wonderful goodbye will miss you.
Let it look like what it is, which is your firing me.
And poker champ Chris Moneymaker, wondering something that has baffled Steven Me for years.
The people who just stand around watching live poker games, what do they watch it?
That's my biggest question.
My wife will pick him and watch me in the stands.
She tells me it's the most boring thing in the world.
Because I don't know if I want someone to call you or if I want them to hold.
I'm just in there watching nine guys sit around the table.
And coming in August, a very interesting interview with Chubby Checker.
Gladys Knight and possibly Steve Win, all that more at the strippodcast.com.
I really love that show.
It's so perfect, you know, because all these entertainers come to Vegas.
And I'm sure they're all thinking, ah, it's just some local little thing, you know.
But look at all the mileage we got out of the Chubby Checker interview.
And then the way PDA was able to come back with the hang valid story.
I'm just fascinating, absolutely fascinating.
And these guys, you know, they're so, what's the word I'm looking for?
You just want to open up to them.
You just want to, you know, tell them everything.
And their questioning is so direct yet, so innocent, almost.
But, you know, of course they're far from innocent.
It just sounds innocent, but the stuff they get out of these artists is fantastic.
Congratulations, guys.
Really like it.
Good job.
Hey, here's something we haven't done in a while.
But today is a very special day.
First let us sing along.
Chanty, chanty, quintessential luxury.
Oh, chanty, chanty, fucked by a diesel industry.
New to the Daily Source Code, Trinity is my Mercedes-Benz.
Eggnog Yellow, 300 turbo diesel station wagon, sitting in the parking garage of the
Curry condo.
It runs on biodiesel.
It's 100% biodiesel that I buy from biofueloasis in Berkeley.
And to celebrate, we actually, we've got something to celebrate because today is a very special
day.
Hi.
This is Matthew.
Hold on a second.
One of that.
Crap is that so soft.
Ah.
Come on.
Let's try it now.
Hi, Adam.
Hey.
Jamie here.
I'm Birmingham.
It's the wrong one.
Ha ha ha.
Hold on.
I do something for yourself when I find this, really.
I swear, I got that can't find it.
I feel like a dick now.
You're probably sitting there going, but you are a dick.
No?
Okay.
Here we go.
Hi, Adam.
This is Matt Natillow, the Matt's today in history podcast.
August 10th is International Bio Diesel Day, commemorating the day in 1893 that Rudolf
Diesel's prototype engine, first ran under its own power.
Diesel was actually an early proponent of what we call today bio diesel.
He wanted his engines to run on vegetable oil, other locally produced fuels and even powdered
coal.
The idea of a petroleum-based product came about much later, so really we owe the genesis
of the bio diesel movement to him.
I know you're not in California this week, but I hope the next time you're in San Francisco,
you'll give Trinity a hug in commemoration of today.
That's it.
Now for the Shane's plug, max today in history.com or in iTunes.
Thanks, man.
Folder, scruncher?
Matt, thank you very much.
By the way, I am subscribed to your show.
There you go.
Today, International Bio Diesel Day.
Thank you so much, and...
Well, I would have, you know, it's no wonder I'm not nominated for Best Produce Podcast anymore.
I had a nice driving here from Birmingham.
26 years old.
No, not now.
Just 10, 27 years old.
Okay.
And I am a self-rench here.
I was listening to the source code yesterday.
It's so four, three, six.
And there you have it.
All your cotton had a guy that's flown and I wanted one of his favorite musicians across.
And I think that's an absolutely amazing idea.
Okay, so he's referring to...
The guy who's bringing Jonathan Colton over to perform gigs here in the UK.
I guess you could call that classically.
You could call that a, like, a concert promoter or an impresario in an old fashion word.
This is something I would love to do to get the list of your speedies to come across the UK.
I mean, that would just be absolutely fantastic.
I'm sure there's not the other people that would love to see them get across.
You know, and come and watch them play live either here.
And I've got their album for all their DVDs.
I had, I mean, it would just be absolutely awesome to, you know,
they haven't come across somewhere in the UK and show up to go and watch them.
You're going to be absolutely brilliant.
Okay, man.
Well, I'd love to show you because of the good work.
And I'm a folder.
Of course you are.
You're brilliant.
Yeah.
Well, this is what we classically would call an impresario or an agent.
I guess you would call it or a concert promoter.
And I totally agree.
I think the bitties would kill over here.
This is exactly why I want a, I want you to be able to have a multiple,
you know, you have multiple personalities, multiple assets and pod show plus.
You can see it in action at podshow.com.
So you have your own identity, like I'm adam.podshow.com.
And then underneath that, I have the daily source code.
I should also be able to be a venue if I happen to have a big backyard, you know.
And then that way, think about all the cool connections we could make to actually make that happen.
I think they would kill.
You're absolutely right.
And of course, your wish is my command.
And this is no shit.
Right after your voice mail comment, this is the next one that came in on 2016256357.
Actually, she may have called the London number, a mandemonico of the bitties.
Hey Adam, it's a mandemonico for bitties.
I'm not sure I have the right number for you.
So instead of calling my personal line, she called the voice mail line.
So this is a personal message.
Yes, I do.
I'd share what you know in London.
And did you hear that?
Did you hear the voice inflection?
Did you hear that?
That sounded like a big invitation.
Listen.
London.
Well, I got you on here this.
But I do.
I'd share what you know in London.
I'm in London.
Come visit me.
And I'm staying at my sisters.
Oh, okay.
And she almost muffled the way to stay at my, staying at my sisters.
Instead of covering gardens, darling.
I'm just wondering if you were going to be around on Sunday.
I'm not really on email at all.
Not on email at all.
But my phone number.
Yeah, okay.
So I'll just turn the phone number down for a second.
That's a bummer.
She's not on email.
Yeah.
So let me know.
You can get together.
We can see her.
Oh, man.
Tomorrow's Friday.
If so much to do.
I'd love to go hang out with Amanda.
I've no idea what she's doing in London either.
I should go.
Get any of you.
Hold on.
Who's that?
Someone.
Someone in the blackberry.
It's probably Amanda Monaco.
Let's see.
What is this?
Oh, no.
Unrelated.
But of course, all of this brought me to the conclusions that, yes, indeed.
Need to play more biddies, man.
Haven't heard the girl for a while on the Charlie.
This has to be one of my favorite songs they've done and probably one of my favorite songs
of all time.
Let's see these biddies from New York and a hell of a boy.
It's not like he doesn't know just what to say to make you feel right.
Stay up nice.
Think of him all day.
Well, his song is true.
But his head keeps getting in the way.
Now it's not like he's got a nasty disposition.
He wants to keep you locked up tight.
Knocked up right.
Barefoot in the kitchen.
He's a hell of a boy.
Only.
Only half of a man.
No, it's not like.
The boys are bad days.
Born on the wrong side of town, under the wrong road.
On the wrong day.
He's a hell of a boy.
But only.
Only half of a man.
Just what do you think you will get if you persist thinking.
This is the best you can do.
Say no to your life girl.
I'll be fine.
You know it.
Your life's gonna say no to you.
Easy call.
Life's too short to live it.
So.
No, it's not like.
It's more than you can say.
Do have that pretty boy.
Sit and next to you.
Listen to you.
Hold in your hand.
He's a hell of a boy.
But only.
Only half of a man.
I like it, I like it, I like it.
He's a hell of a boy.
But only.
Only half of a man.
I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I
like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like the guitar, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it,