Delta Sierra Charley, 3-4-8.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
How can you love me when you don't know who I am?
These pages got a lot more thin from the bloodstained dirty hand.
And all I know is I was blinded as beautiful as mighty graze.
I've been a white devil, a holy roller.
The ball can not stand alone with the temperature.
So I just keep wasting the time again and again.
I've been accused of the crime that came from this.
My baby loves me, gives me everything I need.
She'll make a crown out of art, why?
And I'm happy just to bleed.
She knows that I've been trying hard to take my leave.
She likes guns and she makes love like a lion.
There's blood and I quote it in the other song as a TV.
I'm wasting my time again and again.
Oh yeah.
I've been accused of the crime, but inside it will spin.
No one ever told me they would only like to move down with the pins of needles and standing away.
Oh yeah.
Everybody told me I'll be just fine, but it's my time to break that bitter white.
Nobody loves you, we'll rest, you get it by.
I won't keep wasting the time again and again.
I've been accused of the crime, but inside it will spin.
I can't so use that these crimes, but it wears kind of this.
I won't keep wasting the time again and again.
When I'm with it, I'll be just fine.
I've been accused of the crime, but inside it will spin.
Oh yeah.
I won't keep wasting my time again and again.
I've been accused of the crime, but inside it will spin.
Just wasted my time, I keep it under my skin, take it home Matthew, man, I gotta get
down the Nashville again, Matthew Ebal, I'd be the Nashville actually, I remember what
I do there, did some appearance, what is it to peer or the harborside or river side or something
like that, for some top 40 station, I remember Christy Canyon was there during that particular
appearance, Christy Canyon, the porn star, I guess my illustrious past, just looking at the
pod save music network page from Matthew Ebal, you could easily be, you could be Matt
Dylan's brother, you know, if you take away the go-tee maybe, you know, he has kind of
that same shape head, who cares, everybody how you're doing, it's Tuesday coming to you
from the cottage today's crap, otherwise it's rainy, if it were any colder than we would
be seeing snow without a doubt, so I guess that's kind of good, most of continental Europe
has seen plenty of snow in the past few days, oh, there I go again, one day I'll actually remember
to start the show and remove the blackberry from my pocket as I do it.
Hey plenty of stuff to go through today, the conversation just keep on continuing, people responding
to previous shows from yesterday, from last week Andrew Spettings says, Adam, I'm all on my own,
I'm listening to your show for over a year now and love it when I talk to people that
work about podcasts, they look at me as if I'm out to lunch, all I can say is their loss
No, no, no, no, no, this is your job, man, this is where you've got to look burn a show
onto a CD for them, send them to dailysourcecode.com, let them click on a link, send them to
podshow.com, hunt around, go to podcast alley, podcast people, don't send them the iTunes
necessarily because that's where people will start to fall off the edge and also that's where
it's confusing, you know, do you need an iPod, you need all this stuff, so just send them a link,
man, just email somebody a link and say listen to this and make sure it's something that is
tuned for them that you think they're like, he winds up by saying, I agree with you, you're a
view of Callie from Geek Brief TV, go, hmm, yep, Callie and I are going to be doing some stuff
together in San Francisco, my next trip, which I guess is going to be, I guess next week,
but the girls and I are going to go away for the weekend, I'll be telling you about that on Friday
and we got some fun stuff planned, which would be great, the three of us staying in a hotel,
two separate rooms, yeah, and then Monday, we come back Tuesday, oh, maybe I'll even leave Tuesday,
shoot, I don't know, it's going to be another 10-day stamp, that's for sure.
A very long email, which I won't read in its entirety, but I just love the opening from Paul
Russelling. Hey Adam, enjoy the podcast when I find time. It's an interesting views angles
I was astounded last week when I discovered that your Patricia is in fact the lady whose voice
I kind of fell in love with back in the late 60s as the begiling voice of the skull beer commercial
played on radio Veronica. Later she did a couple of wonderful jingles like sailing the moon line with
Veronica, she should do that. I shouldn't be doing that. Let's see, and so on, over what must have
been in one of the first lifts of a commercial singles as the backing track. That's right,
it was no dusty spring field beside the summer is over. Those are still some of my favorite
radio jingles and believe me, I must have heard thousands and remakes quite a lot for various
radio stations I've been involved with. And it just goes on and on and on. I mean, he's he's back
from the the Miyamigo days. Oh, actually, this is kind of funny. He was on the radio himself.
Remember we talked about flicker, the service, and how that name means something different in
in Dutch? He said, well, I was back in the crazy days of Miyamigo, which was another
pirate radio station, actually on the high seas, on the North Sea broadcasting from a ship,
medium wave only, which was the shit back in the 70s. I was an unknown looking for an
interesting name with a good hook. My real name was unsuitable, and we were all supposed to have a
new name. Isn't that crazy? By the way, how this joke is used to change their names. I've never done that.
Oh, actually, I'm sorry. I have a decibel radio. That's true. But this seems like I got paid for
my own name. One of my Dutch colleagues suggested flicker. I thought, good idea. A one word name,
like Roscoe, and we can have flicker stickers, and maybe even flicker knickers. So, right in
early the next morning, six a.m. I hit the air with a new name. Your DJ flicker. I was on the
English service of radio Carolina at the time. We had two transmitters, one Dutch one English,
but we still did some links in Dutch to make matters worse. I'm identifying as a Dutch DJ,
did is you knew an English style of DJ, your flicker. So basically it was DJ Fag, what he was saying,
Dutch. Ah, the days when we used to play nasty pranks on each other at the radio station. Sometimes,
sometimes, just a little bit, a little bit I long for those days. Hi Adam. It's a Simon here from
the Chintware Podcast, which is at www.chimware.org. I'm calling you from Bath in the United Kingdom,
and I just want to say a few things. Firstly, with the court case, I'm wishing you were the best
of luck and court case. You're obviously in the right morally physically mentally, socially,
psychopathically, I don't know, but anyway, choose two of the all the above. Definitely the right.
So, good luck with that. Secondly, for many reasons why I'm calling is that there's problems with
the podcast alley, the podcast marketing system. My podcast, Chimware. I'm trying to get my friends
to vote for it for obvious reasons, and it seems that some of my friends who have hotmail accounts,
which is the worst account ever, but some of them do. I can't vote for it, because I think podcast
alley has been blacklisted. I just thought I thought that like he wants to know because the
votes aren't being counted for people with hotmail accounts, which is the majority of my friends,
so my podcast only has two votes, which is my hand, one of my other G-well friends. So that's
all I wanted to call about. I can't think of anything else. Good luck with the case. Great show.
Keep it up. Love the Charlie, and Tata. Tata. To the pit. Right, court case, judgment day.
Thursday, March 9th, we'll hear what the judge says. I just get butterflies in my stomach thinking
about it. So this is, it's kind of four to it. It's how this has all come together where we're
learning about this whitelist, blacklist stuff, and the incredibly unfriendly email tax that I
believe AOL is going to, they say they're going to start it next month, is going to put on emails,
which is not a spam protection for you. It's just guaranteeing the spammers that the spam will get
through. And when I say spammers, you know, I basically mean marketers who call your name from
somewhere and send it on through. And we find found this out quite by accident, although I have
a feeling that I do recall Chris McIntyre mentioning this to me months and months and months ago about
the email registrations. And yes, it is indeed a problem. And hotmail is the biggest offender. Again,
hotmail and MSN both blacklist all kinds of email, and they will send you to a different company,
a third party, which they use exclusively to have this stuff solved, which costs money.
I should really look into the ownership of that company and find out if there's any,
to any ownership by Microsoft. Anyone can check that out, that'll be, that'll be really cool.
But this is really the multi-tiered internet, even in today's financial times, there was an article
about it where AT&T, who was about to buy, who were about to buy Bell, South, I believe,
are now saying, hey, you know, we're going to charge content companies to have content travel over
our network with any decent speed. So they're talking really about building a second internet next
to the original one. And I think that, obviously, I think this is a really bad precedent.
I believe that it's charging, it's kind of like having your cake and eating it too. And there's
been lots of feedback about it. Hey Adam, how's it going? I cannot believe this deal that they're
talking about where you're going to have two different tiers of internet provider. I mean,
I pay for my internet connectivity. It doesn't just fall out of the sky. So I have my 50,
60 bucks a month goes out there. And I expect to be able to get what I'm paying for. I paid to be
able to go to Google. I paid to be able to go to Yahoo. I paid to be able to go to, well,
I'm not going to mention that site. But how can they then say, yeah, you're paying for connectivity,
but Google didn't pay us two, so we're not going to deliver to you. Now let's take the other side of it.
Google paid for circuits to get on to the internet. Probably pretty damn big circuits.
Now they're going to tell them, yeah, you bought the fat pipe and you are a big part of the internet,
but we want more money because people are actually using your pipes. Google can't put anything
more on the internet than they have pipes to feed it with. And they had to buy those pipes
from someone. If they got a DS3 hooked up to the internet, then they can't be feeding any more
than a DS3 was of content out there, which they bought. If I have six megabit down from the
internet, I can't get more than six megabit, which is what I paid for. Just like on my end,
if I didn't pay for large bandwidth downloads, then I would have a slower connection. But I would
pay less. I don't understand how and who they're going to charge more to. Are they going to
come to me and say, hey, if you want fast connection, here's the speed. And if you want fast connection
with content, here's the premium above and beyond that. And are they going to go to Google and
say, hey, you want fast connection to the internet, here's the price. But if you actually put anything
on the pipe, we're going to charge you extra. Maybe what we should do is we should vote with
our dollars, like you say, but in a different way. Form a group that says, I will only buy
internet connectivity from an unrestricted single tier provider. And Google should go to their
current provider and say, hey, you know, we spend a lot of money with you guys. And we're going
to stop doing that. If in any way, our content will be restricted by anyone else on the internet.
That would make the people that want to bully everybody into the multiple tier network,
instantly irrelevant. They would be other charging for their restricted network and everybody else
would be paying less for the unrestricted network. Just a quick thought in what I know is a utopian
world in my mind. But I don't know. I don't like the idea of destroying the money at the politicians
and hoping that they'll take care of it. I'd rather vote with my dollars myself. So I guess everyone
should hurry up and head over to www.bukaidrivetime.com to listen to the Bukai Drive Time podcast
before it gets too popular. And you have to pay extra because it doesn't suck. I don't understand.
Well, Adam, I'm not a pilot, so I can't wish you to go wins, but in the current environment,
I think it's going to make more and more sense for us to look at each other and wish each other,
single tiered bandwidth, lighter and keep it Ruby. Yeah, okay. So what AT&T and also what AOL are doing,
this is two different coins, two different sides of the coin here, or really all different
sides of the cube of the equation of multi-tiered internet. It is, of course, part of the American
system. It's privatized. AT&T has the right to charge whatever they think they can get away with,
I guess. There's a very interesting article on muniwireless.com, muniwireless, my uniform November
India wireless.com, which claims that the $200 billion that was invested in creating the, or that
was supposed to create the broadband infrastructure that we have today actually came from taxpayers
from tax breaks and incentives for the telcos at in the dot com boom. I'm not quite sure
about the legitimacy of that, although I don't, I read wireless, a muniwireless a lot and they
seem to be pretty much on the up and up, but at the end of the day, it comes down to us to the
consumers. And, you know, if we sit at, I mean, so yeah, there's DRAOL dot com, and I'm sure there
will be similar types of websites that we can express our outrage, but it really doesn't make any
difference. I mean, look at the, look at gas pump prices, and then look at what kind of profits,
the oil companies have made in the past few years. I mean, it's been astronomical. And we continue.
Well, actually, it's getting better, I have to say. We're switching on to biodiesel, we're switching
on to electric cars. This is not about, for me, personally, although it's nice if, as a bonus,
we also save the environment. But you use your pocketbook, man. Use your pocketbook to vote for
what you really want and, and leave AT&T. I don't think you need AT&T for anything anymore. Do you need it
for, um, for telephony? No, you can get that from your cable provider. You can get it from different
broadband providers. So, you know, you can get your internet from them and you can get your television
from them. I think we, hello, dear. It's the, oh, what is this, huh? You're a little early.
Thank you. What do we have? What do we have on the, uh, on the menu today? We have
come a little closer. Something, um, what? Well, not so healthy today. Oh, very good. What is it?
Well, what is it? Well, it's Dutch. Yeah, but it's warm. It's warm. Yeah, but you're, the timing's all
are fun. I know, but I have to go. I know, but I'm in, you're long, sorry. Getting from the microphone,
if you're going to talk, please, I hate to just hear it. You don't make you a lunch. You don't eat.
Yes, this is true. So, and I have to go. I'm going to the center. Okay. Oh, you're for it.
To the center. To the center. Be careful for people stopping following you. You know,
Roger Smalls is out there. Oh, yeah. And, uh, and I was thinking, I think, well, I'm going to
make him lunch because if I don't do that, I don't eat. I'll come back at four, five and I said,
did you eat something? Uh, no, I forgot. I mean, that's not good. So, that's why.
Okay. Thank you, huh? You are my princess. Oh, thank you. My prince. Yes. Okay, baby. Okay. I'll
eat it during a comic strip blogger. Yeah. All right. I love you. Oh. So, vote with your pocket
book for Christ's sakes. I got to talk to earth link and see what their policy is on on all that stuff.
You're just, oh, man. It's, it's, it's, it's nuts. But, you know, the, the press is catching
on to it. That's really good. And we can put them under pressure by walking away. That's really what
you need to do. We need to have a list of, of, uh, internet providers that won't be charging
a premium content. And, and of course, there's going to be some because that too is the American way.
So, uh, former, he'll staffer, uh, Thomas says, Adam, this is actually on the comments, uh, at
curry.com, uh, former he'll staffer devoted D.A.C. listener here to become active. It's best to
tell listeners to contact their own senators and urge them to co-sponsored the bill. Well,
widen may appreciate the support. If you call it his office, his staffers are busy
and have taken care of people from Oregon. So, you have to go and call, um, your representative.
After a quick search of, uh, Thomas.loc.gov, I don't see a house companion bill. So, finding a house
sponsor is the place to start. While AT&T has been a major contributor to Republican, a representative
boosher, B-O-U-S-C-H-E-R. It's possible. He may be willing to sponsor a house version.
Uh, he's usually very good on tech issues. Only time will tell. All right. And then we got another one from,
it's from Jay Barker, uh, says you asked them today's show that was yesterday.
Best way to support Senator Ron Wyden and the internet non-discrimination act. Really the best
thing any legislator can hear is feedback from his constituents. I keep the phone number for the
U.S. Capitol switchboard in my cell phone. I'm a student. So, wherever I'm between classes, I take
three minutes to call, ask for my Senator or rep and leave a message to the effect of hi. My name
is blank. I'm a voter from blank. I would like Senator, uh, uh, or representative. So, and so to vote,
yes, or no, on blank. It helps to know the bill number, but it's just as easy to describe the bill.
So, the main number for the house and the Senate is 202-224-3121. Oh, what I love about podcasting.
You don't have to repeat those numbers. You just pause it, skip back and you can write it down.
The internet non-discrimination act of 2006 is bill number. Estes in Sierra, 288,
India, Sierra, and is sponsored by Representative Chris Cox and Senator Ron Wyden.
And I'm going to do that myself. I was going to do it on Skype on the show today, but everything
broke as usual. Last night, Patricia and I watched a recorded the Academy Awards on Sky Digital,
which is the equivalent of, of Tvoing in, I guess. And, uh, I was disappointed. You know, I mean,
I think it's really come down to, you know, the fact that all we really want to see is
beautiful, guys and girls, beautiful dresses, beautiful attire, some funny jokes. And by the way,
where was all the political stuff? You know, you know, George Clooney, if you have 100, as, as the
show claims, hundreds and hundreds of millions of people watching, what's not an opportunity to say
something? I really didn't miss that. I missed a little bit of the controversy. Good, you know,
I thought John Stuart did a good job, you know, it's, uh, it's not easy doing that.
And, uh, it was obvious the audience who was kind of tough to, to get him on board, but, uh,
I known John for a long, long time and I thought it was pretty cool what he did.
Higher than Kerry. Fuck you very much for the partial and incomplete answer to my questions.
Regarding your question, well, I had been unloferably dismissed by finished fucking bastards,
because I was blocking about mobile phones, all mobile phones. Please note that I was
blocking about mobile phones since year 1996, it means one year before the term block or web block
was coined in year 1997. In other words, I was blocking about mobile phones.
Long before I came to Finland, which is the Bum Hall of the whole world. Unfortunately, a couple
of years after my arrival to Finland, one of my blogs, the one with dot info in internet domain name,
achieved Google Painter 7, Google Painter 7, what was very high then, and this finished
drunkards couldn't stand that I was blocking about all mobile phones and not just
their mobile phones. Anyway, this is a long story that involves industrial espionage that
industry practices, even with use of threats and Viagra, and certainly I will not tell you
it publicly on the podcast. Yes, nowadays I am a fan of Windows Mobile phones, and now this is simply
the best platform for smartphones. Windows Mobile is the best platform for smartphones. And as
example of palm shows, palm uses this platform in their latest phone palm trio 700W
that is available now on Verizon Wireless in USA. I also don't agree that my comments on your
block were one sided and all the same, because I was commenting about different issues, various
several different issues, not just those mentioned in my former audio comment. Anyway, let's
wait till this fucking Thursday, and let's see what this Dutch batch, I'm sorry, let's see what
this Honorebo Dutch Dutch will tell. So, fuck you later, podcast creator. Oh, coming through
blogger, man, that is just poetry. Thank you so much. I just left a little pause there because
the satellite window closed, nothing left nothing left to say. People on the satellite, what the hell was
that? You know, comic strip blogger, this is very interesting. Okay, so I guess you worked at no
here, if I understand correctly, and you kept a blog, the way before the word blog was even popular,
apparently, you'd seem to be the inventor of the web blog. And you were blogging about all mobile
phones. Now, I can understand from nochias perspective, which is, you know, definitely an older
school, not old school, but an older school type of company that they wouldn't appreciate that. You
blogging about, excuse me, yeah, you know what I want to say. You know, you blogging about
all types of mobile platforms. I can understand what they, they have control issues about that.
And so, apparently, they, I guess you fell out or they fired you or you left or whatever,
you're no longer in Finland, then you went to Germany, I believe. What I'd really like to know
comic strip blogger is, what is your vocation? What do you do? What is your skill set? And,
you know, what did you do at Nokia? And what are you doing now? You seem to have an awful lot of
time on your hands. So, very, very curious is to, as to what skillset you have. And,
perhaps we can put that to, to great use right here on the source code. You know, could
Metro, Metro, Metro, Metro, Metro, Metro, Metro, Metro, Metro,
Metro, Metro, it's Alan Curry's Metro sexual moment. She did it up now.
Alan Curry's Metro sexual moment. Hey mate, says Phil Walker, funniest thing happened last week.
I was on a flight from Ken Barra to Sydney and I just sat down on my seat and plugged in the iPod to
listen to my daily Charlie. As I look out the window, I saw a virgin blue. That's the Aussie
Virgin of Virgin Atlantic. A virgin blue 737 taxi in the 737 was in a livery, I had a livery.
I hadn't seen before. It was covered in a Gillette advertisement for the M3 Shaveer.
See this link for a picture of the aircraft. I'll be sure to post that in the show note.
So, there I was listening to the Charlie on my iPod looking at a virgin 737 with Gillette
M3 advertising. I just had to laugh out loud. If only they'd served up some Simpsons and say,
oh my flight. Phil, love the picture. And you know, what is that with all those brands coming together?
Perhaps there's some larger evil plan that I haven't told you about?
See this is the only problem I have with cast blasters. I can't control the sounds on everything.
Okay, let's try again. Hello Adam. Leo Vgo de He, calling from a beautifully sunny
Brisbane in Queensland, the Sunshine State. I was talking to an Australian colleague about matters
Metro sexual, a couple of evenings ago, when the changing no microchill came up.
First it was Metro sexual and then Uber sexual, but what was the word to use in 2006?
Straight away he came back with her mafredude. It's not the most flattering term I think you'll agree,
but a fun one nonetheless. I'm not convinced you should rename the Metro sexual moment
section of the show though. Have a great day.
Really got to work on that show.
Metro sexual. Metro sexual. It's an increased Metro sexual moment.
An increased Metro sexual moment.
Christian. Christian. Unbehound. I think it is Christian unbehound. Adam, for those of your listeners
who are uncertain about how to shave well and do everything okay in front of the mirror,
wouldn't it be cool to let them listen to your Metro sexual moment also in their bathroom
and get the latest tricks from you while they're shaving at the same time?
Because here is the gadget everybody needs for his perfect shave. Yes, it's pretty much a shaving
mirror with built-in stereo speakers and a slot for holding your iPod. Something nobody really
needs but gives you the right feeling for truly being a Metro sexual guy. By the way,
is the Metro sexual moment song from Jeff also available for download my wife and children
are really loving it. Can't stop listening to it. Christian, that dude. Come on.
I don't think Jeff has made it available for download. I don't know if many people have actually
requested that maybe you should make up some more words to it and we could turn it into an
overnight sensation here today. Good morning Adam. This is your friend Ralph.
Otherwise, no, no, no, no. Skip G. I have no podcasts. I have no podcasts with nerd.
For your Metro sexual moment, I would like to recommend a Zeno moisturizing bar. It has natural
coil oatmeal, it has no soap, it has no fragrance, it has nothing but soap and it will
keep your skin clean. Don't like it. You don't need all those other products. This is the answer.
I've been using it since I was a child and now I'm in my, what should I say? It's a
decade and I don't have it again as smooth as a baby's out.
And could be Metro sexual moment.
Hey Adam, this is Dave Jackson. You might know me from the school podcasting.com or the musician's
core but this past weekend. Oh my, I launched another podcast and this one's called The Best of the
Words. Now, we are going to have a lot of fun at this site. There's going to be voting
and of course, there'll be an RSS feed for listeners, but there's going to be an additional RSS feed.
And this feed is going to have two minute segments of Best of the Words featuring content
four podcasters that they can play in their very own show. So a podcaster specific feed
in addition to the listener feed. Now, what is Best of the Words Podcast? Check out this promo.
Hey, who doesn't love a parade? The big marching bands, the dazzling major reds, the funny
clowns and the beautiful floats. And after all those wonderful entertainers, there's that one
guy at the end of the parade cleaning up the horseshit. Well, that man is me. I'm Dave Jackson
and I want you to join me every week as I bring you the Best of the Words bands at the
Podsafe Music Network. It just because you suck doesn't mean you don't deserve a little
exposure. But after all, one of the best episodes of American Idol, those weeks were those creepy,
crazy toned-up people do their best and it's the worst. So join me at Best of the Words Podcast.com
and help us pick the best of the worst. By the end of the show, you'll wish you were deaf.
Adam Curry for us. Yeah. He spends a lot of time over there and his little cottage. He does
English manner. Mm-hmm. Well, you've got a little bit of a look on your face right now.
Is there something that you want to share? Well, this week, I've got a little thing for Adam Curry.
I don't know. That's all right. I assume our listeners listen to Adam Curry and we know he
listens to us a little bit. We'd like to give Michelle out for playing our ad a couple of times.
Yes. Yeah. Thanks, Adam. And you know, I've Google imaged him and he's cute. I guess I'm changing
the subject here. That's fine. Harden me if I seem flustered. I'm thinking about Googling. Are you
diverting from lip gloss to laptops right now? I am. We're into the laptop section. All right. A
Google imaged Adam Curry. So you Google imaged? I like when he says things like wing commander.
And Sierra Echo X-ray Yankee. He starts talking like that. Right. What is that? You know?
What is it? See Sierra? Sierra Echo X-ray Yankee. It means sexy. So you're naughty. He is the same age
as Hank Azaria, too. Really? They're both 41. I think, or 42. Anyway, you know what? My husband's listening.
I had a change in sub-john wine. Yeah. Maybe one day we'll have to get into, you know, things that
I enjoy. Oh, yeah. But not today. No? No. No. So sure make me seem like the freak. Okay, let's go on
to mascara again. Lip gloss and laptops.com. So what is the Buckeye Drive Time Podcast? It's probably
easier to talk about what the Buckeye Drive Time Podcast doesn't have. I don't have an open
microphone while I'm playing a novelty song so that everybody can laugh in the studio and let
you know that it's supposed to be funny. I don't have an intern that I send out into the world to
publicly humiliate by wearing a costume or asking ridiculous questions of pastors by. I don't
have any hookers or escorts or strippers in the studio. Joy said no. But you do get a quick Ohio
moment of fact or a piece of information about the center of the universe. Occasionally sports
from my castredale, three pods saved songs, and three podcast promotions. And something else
here and there when I feel like throwing it in. At the end of your drive, you should feel like you've
had fun, been entertained, or a little bit more intelligent. The idea is to be an alternative
to the regular morning zoo-type drive time. That clear channel has been pushing on you for years.
So check us out at www.bukaidrivetime.com. And if you like what you hear, go ahead and subscribe.
And we'll do our best to help you keep it groovy. I hope you didn't mind all the promo's
one after another. I had to eat those hot dogs, man. They were getting cold. Oh, so good.
Just use me. That was disgusting. Just one thing about the the Oscars. I was just reading
them through the promos and through my hot dog. The ratings were down about 8% compared to
last year. Excuse me. But John Stewart did bring 5% more males 18 to 34. That's so crazy the way.
You know, the way they measure all that stuff and they talk in such abstracts. I was just disappointed
by the show. I really was. It's just like, okay, you know, the best. Yeah, that really was no best moment,
actually. It's just it seems so blah. I'm just jaded or whatever it is. There's just so much more
exciting stuff that I can spend my time on. Three hours of watching that stuff.
We've got a few more pieces of feedback. I want to talk about the pot set music network because
it got a lot of comments about it. Good and bad. So I want to make sure we get to get everything in
there. And some comments from for all. Hi, this is Annie Grubins. We podcast listeners here.
No, Germany. Have started a little campaign to find a logo for our hobby. By wearing this
logo as a sticker or a button, we want to show others that we listen to podcasts and make podcasting
more popular. My listeners have come up with 94 different graphics. And now we are looking
first for the top 10 and then for the winning logo. Please feel free to take the poll 2 at podcast
logo.com. Thank you very much. I'm very curious about the results. You know, I actually looked at
that and there's a whole bunch of really nice logos. There's a couple of them I'd want to use.
Yeah, you know, I think that's a pretty good initiative. Germany is popping wide open by the way
on the podcast front. And I do have a French, a French feedback, but I'll play that one tomorrow.
Somehow I got the the file misplaced or something. Podcast logo. Was it podcast logo dot
dot com? Was it or dot dot shoot? Look in the show notes and I'll get all that info back to you.
We're living here a bit longer than you have though. I originally came over for a six months of
work contract back in 1986. So I've been here for almost 20 years now. I do still spend quite a
lot of time in Holland though because over the last few years most of my work's been in Amsterdam
in Ethiopia. So I spent most of the year easy jetting out at 6 a.m. on Monday morning from
late in the Tuesday, and back from tomorrow to late in the 1815 on Friday afternoon. As quite a few
other people do as well, surprisingly. But I'm not doing these as yet commuted moment because
some are necessarily in between contracts. Although I'll be popping over to Amsterdam again
later this week for a few days. And it was over there that I discovered since a few years back
him got totally hooked on that. So I'd like to make a few comments on the T-pad as you
discussed in the Charlie 346. You're seeing deed that sounds totally disgusting and in two ways
even. First of all, you'd never want to make a petite machine that has just produced coffee.
It would not taste good. Or vice versa for that matter. Suppose we don't work if we actually have
two machines. One for coffee and one for tea. Now luckily I haven't had three of the little bastards,
but that's a difference story. Secondly, I know they're called pants in Holland and most of the
rest of Europe. But if you care to pick a pack of them in a UK supermarket and look at the packaging,
you'll see that they're not called pads in the UK. Pads would not be good. Just imagine.
Somebody's saying, honey, can you get me some pads when you go to supermarket? You don't come
back with the wrong thing. No, in the UK, they're actually called pods. Not pads. So I guess before
you start recording a show, you put a pod in your sensei or machine and make yourself a glorious
cup of coffee. That means your sensei or driven audio show is a pod cast in more than one way.
I'm at Finne Looker Closer. Funny, huh? Our one common common people separated by a common
language. Yeah, I guess the pads thing is kind of a mistake. David Groves sent me an email and said,
you know, I've just, my girlfriend, was it? I don't know how to read that whole thing. The whole
point is he's saying that people who come into the daily source code who are newbies probably don't
understand a whole bunch of things you're talking about. And even though I do try to reiterate
very briefly before I start off on a rant or a story, it seems that the the main things that are,
you know, that need some explanation or that we need an FAQ or a cheese would be great to have an
audio FAQ, wouldn't it? I got to think about that. So some of the subjects that David would like
explain the detail is I guess the genesis behind Trinity. What is biodiesel Delta Sierra is this
your plane, Roger Smolls. Yeah, that's that that needs his own FAQ. You're American who lived in
Netherlands, married a pop star now living between Gilford and San Francisco. Yes, correct. All of it's all right.
We'll do a Trinity segment later on this week and talk about that as in biodiesel. Delta
Sierra isn't the plane and it's almost done. I got an email from the guy in Rotterdam who's doing
the Reopholstery. Both seats are done. The carpeting is done. The side panels and the doors are
done. Now the back seat is the last thing he has to do. I've booked a round trip easy jet for the
three of us to come back on Monday, but with a little bit of luck, we might actually be able to
fly back in the Delta Sierra. And yes, it's the reason I call it that is because the call sign is
November 277 Delta Sierra. Hey Adam, it's Rob Uston from the Jersey Jamcast. I wanted to throw a
quick comment out to you about downloading music from the positive music network and ID3 tags.
A lot of times I download a couple of tracks from the PMN for my show. I pop them into iTunes and there's
no ID3 tag info. It's just using the file name in the song title selection. It's kind of
convenient because then I got to go back and see what song is by what artists. I might do a couple
songs and then I have to go into the info manually, which is not that big of a deal for
me as a podcast or other podcast. It's kind of a minor inconvenience, but once you start selling
music on the podcast music network, it's going to be an issue. It's got to be seamless so that when
somebody buys a song and puts it into iTunes or whatever program they use, the ID3 info has
got to be there or else they're going to end up really frustrated. So if there's a way you can put
a reminder up for the artists on whatever page they upload songs from, I think that would be good
or maybe there's a way you can have the pod safe music network alter the ID3 when they upload the
song with maybe some info that they might enter on a page and as they're uploading the song,
it'll alter the MP3 and put in the ID3 tag info that they want. That would be really good.
So hopefully there's a solution, but it's definitely something you got to look at.
And if you haven't checked out my show, come on by. It's the Jersey Jamcast, which is Jerseyjamcast.plogspot.com.
I play the best music coming out of New Jersey and I'll tell you there's hell of a lot of good stuff
so come on by and any bands that I play that aren't on the pod safe music network. I'm trying
to get them up on the pod safe music network and hopefully we'll get to more bands involved.
So all right, take care Adam. Yeah, good point. Yeah, thank you, we did Jersey Jamcast. Yeah,
very good point. And we've talked about that. I talked about this with comments and promos and feedback
all the time as well. Please. What is wrong with me? Use those ID3 tags. And I disagree with you
that once we start selling, no, no, no, this is an unlabel. This is not a music story. It is not
iTunes music store because in a store things are closed off locked off. There's only one door in
a maybe a service entrance and there's certain ways you have to do stuff and you can look
but you can't touch in the store. In the unlabel concept, the artist is responsible. This is where
I believe we're taking the record company out of the equation. Record companies do all this
stuff for the artist. Now, if you are a completely introverted out of your mind,
whacked out musical genius who can't find the the interest to make sure that your stuff
is marketed correctly, then find a friend who will, okay? And and work out some arrangement with
them. I would I would strongly advise against a record contract, certainly a mainstream record
contract. And as we're just waiting for the email stuff to get cleared up, you know, I've said
that a hundred times but once that's done, then anyone who has a song on the podcast music
network will be allowed to to make their MP3s available for purchase and download free and clear.
And by the way, we're coming up with a very interesting announcement. Another piece of the unlabel
is going to be snapped into place within the next couple of weeks. I'm pretty excited about it.
And you'll be hearing more about that. Of course, I'm under a strict no-damn announcement
so regulation here. But back to the ID3 tags. I think that if artists don't do that themselves,
then people just won't buy from them. They'll say, hey, you know, the quality of that isn't
what, you know, it's this we don't have a store that is offering quality because,
well, geez, man, then we'd have to actually put a whole bunch of people on it and be a lot of
work. And then you keep cutting into the slice of the of the artist himself. And just to remind me,
I want to talk about Ioda a little bit more as well. A report from Ola Christian Vale.
I hope I'm pronouncing that right. Purchasing music from PMN is working nice from the Farrow Islands.
I had to call to activate the account using Skype. But after five minutes, I could buy some
music from Matthew Ebel. Awesome. I cannot buy from iTunes from the Farrow Islands. And I feel that's
discriminating since we are part of the Danish kingdom. And Denmark is accepted by iTunes.
I've contacted the two record companies here to work on that. I will also introduce
podsake music network to them. Excellent. Dude, thank you. What about taking your daily source
code to the Farrows? Oh, oh, the Delta Sierra. I'm sorry via Scotland, then Shetland.
It's a special tricky airport with in flight 14 degrees offset. Yeah, okay, Ola. Don't think I'm
going to be doing any time soon. I'm still looking for a safety pilot, which I talked about
on yesterday's show. Got one who was sent in who couldn't make it. Another one, I'm still
hoping to hear back who actually apparently is at Farrows at Elkogolf, Tangofoxtrot. So God, that'll
be so cool. Another piece of feedback about pods at music. Hi Adam, this is Ed Ovet, host of Ed's
mixed bag. And I just wanted to say that I had spoken to Dan Johnson, who does a podcast in Ohio
called Journey Inside My Mind. And him and I were talking about Matthew Ebel on the chat line.
And Dan turned me on to the fact that Matthew had a podcast. I started listening to his podcast
in my car. And then I heard him talking about Laura Clap and playing her song, hey, hey sister.
And then I came home and downloaded the song from the podsake music network. And then a few days
later, I heard from Marcus of the podshow music rewind, who requested I send him a five-minute clip.
So I chose Laura's song. And I understand you heard her on there. Just wanted to say how it never
ceases to amaze me. How one comment to one person can start a whole string of events turning
a relatively unknown independent artist into a fully blossomed, you know, widespread hers artist
on the podsake music network or on podcasts in general. So the podosphere is quite a community
quite powerful. I guess we owe it all to the power of the internet, huh? Okay, so I just wanted to
pass that little peek behind the curtain glimpse scenario type of thing to you. Take care.
Yeah, thank you very much. That's exactly the way it went. And I heard the song on the podshow
music rewind, which came from you, which came from your contacts, which came from it's just this
is exactly how it works. This is fantastic. And we've got to keep promoting it artists,
podcasters, listeners, all alike. This is how the unlabeled all fits together. Now, Mark Kelsos
says, could you have a gift option? It would be cool for a family of friends to open his email
and see that someone bought you a song. We all know people who like a certain kind of music,
but need to be encouraged to know more about podcasting. Maybe instead of 99 cent purchase,
it could be $5 option to share with ex amount of friends. Mark, yeah, that works very easily when
you have a store. Again, we don't necessarily have a store. I'm going to ask Chris Rockwell what
the possibilities are that that would only really work if it was a function of clicking by,
who's the partner we're using for the transaction piece of the unlabel. So I'll look into it.
But again, this is this is store stuff and this is not unlabel stuff. And hopefully we'll find ways
to fix that. Albert Young Niber, Albert Young Niber is actually sent in a very interesting piece of
information. And this reverts back to how do we pay artists who are outside the US? Now, you probably
know that if you have an eBay or Amazon affiliate account or even Google Adsense, you know,
every couple of months, maybe once a month in your case, a check shows up for whatever amount
you've sold and you're cut of the advertising. And it's very difficult to get these checks processed
outside of the United States, almost impossible, I'd say. And if you do find a bank that'll do it,
they charge you a huge fee, which really almost kind of takes away the whole joy of making any any
kind of money on this stuff. The online casinos use net letter says Albert Young. Maybe you should
look into that. I've won some money with online poker and net letters like a stop between for your
money and you would pod show and could put it in a net, in a net teller account, which is a company
in the UK, they take care of getting it to the person somewhere in the world. We're going to look
into that very, very good. Thank you very much, Albert Young. And now the big news, gosh, this was so
amazing. This came out yesterday sent to be my many, many people in the Netherlands who apparently
the Netherlands is listening. Raymond Port, my buddy, who's been a fan of the show for, gosh,
over a year now, almost a year and a half, probably. It turns out there's a politician in the
Netherlands, a member of the VVD party, which is a center right, not to the right, right, more right
wing. And I guess he's been reading the annual reports of the Dutch ASCAP BMI, who are known as the
Buma Stemera. And this guy is screaming bloody murder and I think he's absolutely right. He says that
it's unbelievable. Now, this is the company that takes money from restaurants, from bars, from hotels,
from elevator operators, from companies, just any, if you have a company, any company, what's
even if you don't have the radio on, you don't have to pay a lot, but you still have to pay money
for maybe the fact that someone's singing in your office. They take it from radio stations,
they take it from television stations, they take it from satellite broadcasters, all that money,
and it's about a hundred million a year, euros, I guess. They have an overhead of 22%
their office alone costs over a million euros a year. That's got to be some shit-nast nice place,
man. And he's saying, you know what, that's to be more transparency. I need to know what are the,
the members of the board making. That's not, you can't find that anywhere. I mean, they spend about
eight and a half million euros a year on salaries. They have a hundred and ninety people working
there. Presumably, people in the field, I guess, maybe they have a really big office, but what
the hell are they doing? Well, it turns out what they're doing is they're taking this money,
which is meant for artists. Now, I believe they're a non-profit. They should be a non-profit.
But they take this money, they collect it. And by the way, it's not like, you know,
your song gets played on the radio, you get your, your 20 cents the next day. Oh, no,
it's sometimes takes up to three years. You know why? Because they're investing that money
into stocks and bonds. They have over almost three hundred investments. And in the past year,
they lost millions of euros on their investments. This doesn't make sense to me. These guys are
taking the money from, that is supposed to go to artists. And of course, many artists even say,
you know, I don't think I see anywhere near my fair share of what I should be receiving. And it's
the same with Ask out BMI and the same complaint everywhere, basically. But they're investing
that money, losing the money, and then passing on whatever else they have after they've hit,
I don't think they, they deduct anything from their own salaries and check this. There's the
Repro-recht, which is a nonprofit, Vidima. I think is, yeah, it's the two combined. Vidima who does
takes royalties for copying of moving images and photocopiers. They receive 19.4 million euros,
but only distributed 6.3 million euros. What happened to the, to the other 13 million euros?
And so this guy is great. Uptrout is his name. Uptrout. Charlie Uptrout.
Alpha Papa tango, Romeo, Oscar, Oscar, tango. Dude, go get him. When I told Patricia that she freaked
out, man. She's like, what the hell? And you know, and she told her dad, who of course is living
off a pension partially subsidized by Buma Stemera. This is nasty. And it's been going on for a long
time. And I've, I've actually told Patricia about this. I said you're crazy. You know, the shit that's
going on there. It's not right. They're keeping your money for years. So, you know, that just goes
to show you how the big, the big organizations think about intellectual property, whether it's my
pictures on flicker or your song, they're stealing from you. That's just the bottom line.
To line it up today, Dermit says, I've just spent the afternoon listening to some good old
Elvis Costello stuff. Radio radio caught my attention. I'm sure you remember it.
Oh, of course, you can't play it, which is a bummer. Here's some of the lyrics.
And the radio is in the hands of such a lot of fools trying to anesthesize the way that you feel.
Radio is a sound salvation. Radio is cleaning up the nation. They say you better listen to the
voice of reason, but they don't give you any choice because they think it's treason. So you better
do as you're told. You better listen to the radio. Elvis Costello, a visionary, a true visionary,
for sure. Well, I just got offline and I'm feeling so fine. I must have had 30 or more.
emails from friends, Lord, where will it end? So much love from these folks I adore.
Well, to be totally frank, a few were from banks, offering great mortgage deals
and three may be four of real little hardcore with a chance to enhance my appeal.
But even with a little spam, I thank God every day for this way to keep in touch with friends
with so many things to say. A little known facts about unnatural acts. So much I never
didn't know. Do they have email in heaven? If not, I don't want to go email me some love now.
Now tell me the truth, is anything so uncool? Could a person be more of a mess?
And to chatter and such and say stay in touch, but don't have an email breath.
Now God clearly meant that an email be sent any time that you have a thought.
And if you're in box ain't scoured five or six times an hour, then you ain't doing all that you ought.
I could I ever stay in touch without my ISP. To let my friends know I'm alive and to find out who loves me.
I clung for God how to use the phone and the mail is way too slow. Do they have email in heaven?
If not, I don't want to go. No, if I can't log on, it's St. Pedro dot com.
And I'm not sure that I want to go.
Jim Turr. Do they have email in heaven? If not, I don't want to go. That's it for the Charlie
for today, everybody. Thanks for checking it out. If you want to find all the new episodes and
past episodes in the podcast feed to subscribe to a staleousourcecode dot com. Send me an email
any kind of feedback left to hear from your audio was preferred sticking on a server. Put your
ID3 tags and send it to atomatecurry.com and I'll be back here tomorrow with