This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Our Delta Sierra Charlie 4663, it'd be national talk like a pirate day.
The Pimmer 19th, 2006, so have asked you lad and lovers, hoist the main sale.
This is the Daily Source Code.
The $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio
content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
On casting, he's Adam Curry.
He has the $14.60 for it.
You can take your speed all the time.
I am resigned to hang around on your front porch and outside your dark.
I rack my brain to let you know.
You're my only smile today, don't you ever go away?
When you're not home, I lose my brain.
I sing this song.
This song that takes me to your front porch and outside your dark.
I rack my brain, I tend to go.
You're my only smile today, don't you ever go away?
Isn't that just a happy song?
You're my only smile today, the jelly breaks from the pot set of music.
Now work, hey everyone!
Are you doing?
It's the Daily Source Code episode.
We're at the $463 now coming to you.
From Curry Cottage, in the afternoon, suburb of Suri known as Gilford.
It's another beautiful day.
We're looking at 20 degrees Celsius.
So it is kind of an Indian summer.
Apologies for yesterday.
We had a flash visit to Amsterdam Sunday.
So we went off Sunday.
Actually, we had a very important engagement on Sunday.
The entire family at the hairdresser in Rotterdam.
This is the guy that we've been using for years.
He's an artist, Peter the hairdresser.
He is so incredibly good.
I mean, for me it's easy, but for Patricia and Christina.
You know, a lot of stuff's got to get done for their hair.
So we took the Delta Sierra.
And Captain Dan went with us, of course, and flew over.
There was a pretty misty actually.
We landed at Rotterdam.
And we were full man.
We had full fuel.
We had baggage in the back.
I love this aircraft.
It is so the right plane for me.
I mean, still a nice 175 knots.
Flying along, getting from A to B.
And like an hour and 20 minutes.
I love that.
And just, you know, anyway.
So it had a great time.
And we had a nice dinner.
And then we went to Amsterdam State at the wonderful Amsterdam Hotel.
Christina had her own sweet.
There was no other room available.
So I went for what I could get.
And she was totally Paris Hilton.
And Patricia and I had her own room.
It was nice.
And we had to get it pretty early to go to the British embassy the next morning.
First we had to get pass photos, passport pictures taken.
And then off to the embassy.
And that was actually very nice and easy.
Patricia couldn't come into the embassy because the point was only for Christina and myself to get our E.A. visas, which is kind of the equivalent of getting a green card because you've married in American in the States.
So now the roles are reversed.
And we're official and legal and happy about it.
So now stuff to do.
That's a stuff to do.
We still got a, you know, close on the house.
And I got to get back to San Francisco.
And there's important questions in life to be answered.
Crap.
Before only it worked.
Hold on a second.
That's such a great lead up to that.
What the hell is going on?
Hold on.
I hate it when this happens.
Why am I not to, don't tell me that this is, this is really weird.
Okay.
I have my voice mail comments.
I cue them up in quick time.
Because whenever I, I transpose the, the A-I-F-F from this, this protocol that my,
Oh, this sucks man.
Oh, I love, this is what I love about cast blasters.
It actually keeps working.
Everything else is broken.
Let me see if I can, well, that's really weird.
Maybe it will work now.
Hold on. Let's say let's check this.
No.
It's definitely crashing and hanging.
Oh, crap.
Let me restart to, let me restart quick time here for a second.
Okay.
All right.
Now back to the important questions in life.
Hey Adam.
This is Andy and Frank from Germany.
We have a question.
You may support us to solve.
We just wonder about if, if you've got a switch.
And you want to get some cool beer.
Is it better to put it in the upper layers of the switch or better on a lower side of the
switch?
We're wondering what it is.
And maybe you can help us.
Yeah.
Where is it colder on a lower side or the upper side?
To talk about the profiles.
We're both quite young around the 20s.
And having some 45 o'clock in the morning, six o'clock already.
And we're listening to your show.
See you, uh, a folder.
Bye.
You know, I really don't know where it's colder.
Yeah.
Of course you don't want to make the mistake of putting it into the spot that's too cold
and then it starts to freeze over.
But I think it depends upon the equipment they use in my friends.
It really does.
Now what?
Now this thing won't work all of a sudden.
Hey, what it is.
The sun will settle into the heights of the show.
The show will be gone.
So we can do some dumb and high fever.
First episode is not for next week.
So as the attendal tell your friends.
Yeah, I mean.
See you next week.
Hey.
All right.
That's the high fee show.
You'll see, uh, you can actually, you can, I think we have a video promo rolling
on the home page at podshow.com.
Kevin F's.
Phil make award-winning filmmaker from San Francisco.
Now creating a, uh, by weekly show called the high fee show.
All about the high fee movement in San Francisco.
Oakland.
And far beyond.
High fee dot podshow.com.
It's the X versus the Brits.
We'll drive each other crazy.
But everybody knows that it's apparent to see.
They're just like you and me.
It's the X and the Brits.
At that end.
The X versus the Brits.
Mind the gap.
You know, I got a lot of problems going on, right?
Totally.
Yeah, Adam.
It's Ray Anthony from the radio guide.com podcast.
How you do it, everybody?
Um, this might be something for your Yanks versus the Brits segment.
Not really sure that I understand that mind.
The gap thing.
By the way, I was hoping you could help me out.
I really, really need to make a men's here.
A few months back, I was doing a vanity search online.
And I came across something pretty interesting.
A podcast, not mine called the radio guide podcast.
The UK radio guide podcast.
Now, I live in New York City.
He's in London.
I'm a former sometimes radio guide currently working in information technology
as is he, both of our wives contribute to our shows.
My shows at radioguide.com.
His is at radioguide.co.uk.
So I had actually found my internet double ganger.
My evil podcast twin, as it were, or maybe I'm his evil twin.
Actually, we're probably both evil.
But I listened to his show and I loved it contacted him.
John Newton.
He's a great guy.
We decided to swap promos.
And he played mine promptly on his next podcast.
And me being a lazy bastard and pretty busy and having released episodes
pretty infrequently.
I forgot to play his promo on my next show, which was a few months later.
So here's where you come in.
Would you please, pod, father?
Please help me make this wrong, right, and play his promo for me on your show.
It would do him worlds of good because you have such an awesome audience and he has such a great podcast.
Thanks, Adam.
Here it is.
Short and sweet.
Recorded in the UK.
Listen to all over the world.
Downloaded onto multiple hard drives.
Deleted thousands of times.
www.radioguide.co.uk
The podcast from the radio guide.
I love it.
Hands across the border.
The yanks and the brits coming together in loving harmony.
Love it.
Excellent.
Thank you.
St. Clair sent me a note.
Willie Nelson's been busted again for pot.
This is really a very funny story.
Let me know.
Of course I'll put the link in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
It's like one of these.
Uh-huh.
Willie Nelson for their members.
For others were issued misdemeanor citations for possession of narcotic mushrooms.
And marijuana after traffic stop Monday morning on a Louisiana highway.
Uh-huh.
This is the best.
When the door was opened and the trooper began to speak to the driver.
He smelled the strong odor of marijuana.
The renews release said.
Duh.
It's a tour bus.
A search of the bus produced.
One and a half pounds of marijuana and zero point two pounds of narcotic mushrooms
according to state police.
They were all released after being issued a citation.
Uh-huh.
Gee.
You think that would happen if you stopped Willie Nelson's bus?
Let's see.
Jeff Reed says congratulations on inking the British telecom deal.
Great news.
I want to let you know.
I'm experiencing issues with my phone service.
For some reason, I can't accept incoming calls.
It gives me.
It gives me a kind of information that the region.
Dude.
We have a very proud of our partnership with British telecom.
But I do draw the line somewhere, okay?
And Joe from a podshow.
Uh-huh.
And that's not a podcaster, Joe, but podshow.
Jersey, Joe.
We call him.
Uh, who works on the servers and lives in Jersey.
Because he's right in the middle of all the time zones.
Uh, sent me this interesting link.
And this is very appropriate because I will be flying.
Either Monday or Sunday.
This coming Sunday or a week later.
I'm going to go to San Francisco.
It is time.
And now that I can re-enter the UK legally without coming up with some story,
uh, it seems appropriate.
I miss a slew of incidents involving exploding Sony batteries.
Virgin Atlantic.
That's my airline.
Announce that it will not allow passengers to carry any Apple or Dell laptops onto the flights.
They announced yesterday the passengers any Dell Apple laptops not be allowed to use a battery wall on flight.
The announcement posted on Virgin's website.
Uh, said that passengers may carry on the laptop itself.
But batteries must be, quote, properly wrapped and stowed away and carry on for the duration of the flight.
Uh, but the airline will provide, uh, power.
So you can still use your laptop without without the battery.
Oh, man.
What's the world coming to?
And says nothing to do with terrorists.
It just has to do with exploding batteries.
And of course, it's not all Apple laptops that, uh, that have potentially exploding batteries.
It's not all Dell laptops.
In fact, it's interesting because I have a Sony bio.
And apparently, you know, and of course, the Sony bio has, uh,
Guess what?
Sony batteries.
So I'm allowed to take that on though.
Very interesting.
I'm going to call the, uh, you know,
We'll do that.
When I, when I make my reservation this time around, I'll record the conversation.
And I'll ask the, uh, I'll ask the reservation, uh, assistance.
You know, because I have the gold card stuff.
My special number.
I'll get into a conversation with him.
See if anything fun comes out of it.
I had him.
It's, um, who, long time.
Charlie, listen up.
I'm fritting and losing air forward.
At the moment, reading wide magazine.
And you made.
Why has made.
Page 55 of wide magazine.
Um, it's got you under the, uh, the September calendar for your birthday.
So you might want to check that out.
Um, not going to show.
Keep it up.
Hold up.
Excellent.
I made it in wide magazine.
All I had to do was exist.
Thank you.
Hey, I'm Mike Wilson.
We've been podcast here.
Um, let you know by now I'm sure that I tune seven as out.
And, uh, there's a firmware update 1.2 for the, at least for the five, the five G.
Uh, video iPods.
However, there's been tons and tons and tons of problems, which I hope you are aware of as well.
Yeah, you know, actually I have been receiving a lot of emails about problems with
students seven about the updateer.
And I've read a lot of reports of it actually,
Trashing all of your existing purchases from the iTunes music store.
And if you have podcasts that you've been saving in your iTunes directory,
it sometimes or maybe always deletes the episodes that are out of certain dates.
I mean, it definitely feels like we've got.
We have to wait for like a installer or upgraded 1.3.
And you may want to stay away from 1.2 as you'll go on to explain.
In my particular case, it makes my computer dog slow whenever it is downloading podcasts or
whenever I am thinking of my iPod.
Yeah, that's right.
It's another new thing is that it takes up a lot of sits.
It's what we call in the software business, a memory hog.
The thing of iPod slow is I want care about as much.
If it's been it takes 45 minutes to an hour to sync up and add two podcasts to my iPod.
It's annoying to hell out of me and I'm about ready to do something that would be very expensive.
But anyway, I thought I heard at one point you had contact with an Apple.
He found out what the hell is going on.
And when they're going to get this freaking thing fixed before there's going to be some severe damage to their reputation.
There are tons and tons of people that have found out in the Apple's forum that are absolutely ticked off.
Now obviously, though the people who are having problems that was at a vocal,
but in some of these sort of 100 or 100 comments I'm already in none of them are,
oh yeah, mine works fine.
I didn't have any problems.
So give a big show.
Thank you.
Yeah, that's how Apple is.
They don't typically respond to stuff like that unless they have a fix ready to go.
And usually they get stuff fixed pretty quickly,
but this is really wise which to win those is because whenever there's something new,
I'd like to have it.
I like to get it.
I get totally caught up in the whole Apple vibe.
I love the way the products feel the way they operate,
but the hardware has been failing.
And now it seems like with the iPod.
I still have, I guess, a fourth gen iPod, which I really,
I have to admit is being replaced now by the Nokia N91.
I'm going to get the,
there, what is it, the Blackberry Killer,
but they talk about is that the N92, I believe.
I'm going to try that one out because it's,
well, we'll just see.
I mean, there's a lot about the Blackberry I really love.
You know, the thumb wheel is a big part of it,
but I think for podcasting,
particularly with the Wi-Fi built in,
really liking that capability.
So I haven't been using my iPod as much,
but Apple will fix it.
They always do.
And when something's really fucked up,
they eventually come round.
You know, they've given rebates on batteries and stuff.
And, you know, I kind of understand where they're coming from.
And, you know,
what the folks at Apple listen,
they listen to this show.
And I'm sure they're aware of it.
And they'll get on it.
I can't defend them for it.
I'm just, I'm actually no longer a user of the product.
I have to say.
If you got something to say in your wondering,
how you can get a hold of this program,
this podcast,
well, there's some numbers you can dial.
Dr. H. Adam in America.
dial.
plus 1,
2, 0, 1,
6, 2, 5, 6, 3, 5,
7,
plus 1, 2, 0, 1,
6, 2, 5, 6,
5, 6, 3, 5, 7,
again.
For Adam in Great Britain,
dial.
4, 2, 0, 7,
6, 8, 1, 3,
7, 5, 3,
plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7,
6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3,
Thanks for going on the daily source code.
Goodbye.
You know what I love?
Hold it as concha.
You know what I love so much about that?
It's just nothing about the tune
that is catchy enough to help me remember the actual number.
I still do not know these numbers by heart.
You can always find them on in the show notes at daily source code.com.
Plus 1, 2, 0, 1, 6, 2, 5, 6,
6, 3, 5, 7,
or plus 4, 4,
and London,
2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3,
7, 5, 3.
Still awaiting the Earthlink ad challenge winner.
I know we have finalists who are winners,
but it's something's got to go in rotation pretty soon.
So be on the lookout for that.
And there's more voice mail.
Hi Adam. I've been holding out to give you a call
about a number of subjects.
First of all, Peter.
That mess he left away.
He goes his friend.
Oh man, I want all the pee stands for a Peter.
You know what I'm saying?
But I love the I am.
I will forever be a fan of his.
I thought that was one of the he best.
You know, that was the best audio comment.
Anyone has ever left?
Okay.
So secondly, scrunch it.
Why the hell would anyone scrunch?
Seriously.
You get shit all over your hand.
I tried it the other day just to experiment.
It's horrible.
The other thing is maybe I'm just cack handed full.
The other thing is, it's BT, wireless broadband,
TV stuff.
Okay, you're chatting away about that.
Whatever, you know, if things will happen,
that's going to be all good.
You get in that first.
Make sure it's done properly.
That's nice.
But I have to say, you were talking about free view
and you say it's super quality.
You know what?
Digital TV in my opinion.
This is a bit of a tin for hot moment.
It's rubbish.
What did you say there?
Hold on a second.
Hold on.
I'm sorry.
What did you say there?
It's a bit of a tin for hot moment indeed.
tin for hot moment.
It's rubbish.
Seriously rubbish.
The amount of bands that they have.
You would think they'd be able to wrap the quality.
But you can see the compression.
There's all this banding and blockiness.
You watch any dissolve or mix.
You know, anything that involves high amounts of solid colour.
You can feel the blockiness or crowd shots.
Okay.
I'm a television professional.
Media wankers and other words saying it.
But media one.
Oh, God, it winds me up.
There's the audio quality and the picture quality of an analog signal.
It's fast to period.
Once it's been snapped up to space and back down again.
Oh, all right.
Ran over.
Peace.
Bravo.
You know, of course.
When you guys are streaming stuff and why have you.
Hopefully you'll have enough bandwidth to make it all look nice.
Like really nice.
Maybe even HD TV nice, which I have to say.
I've always wanted to.
I've always shoot a shoot thing on film whenever I can.
I have to say when HD HD is a list properly.
My jar.
It looks amazing.
It really does.
I'm so surprised.
I haven't even bought myself a digital still camera because I'm a bit old like that.
Anyway, um,
God, what a boring message.
My name's Charles.
Uh, and actually I live in London.
Bye.
Alright, Charles.
I really do appreciate it.
Oh, man.
Tim for a little bit.
At the free you stop as great, man.
I think it just depends on, you know, you still have to have good reception.
If you don't have good reception because it comes in through the air.
You know, you'll have to re-jigger your antenna.
But once you've got good reception, it works.
I don't know.
I'm not seeing the same things you have.
And I'm getting it right off the antenna on the roof.
So it works fine over here, my brother.
She's pretty. She's got a beautiful voice.
She's a nice person.
And a great addition to the quality of music we have to work.
And she just 50% of our current students by switching to guy go.
Well, the last one isn't true.
With all the other ones around.
Fitoia Khan.
In episode 97 of The Pot Show, you will hear the Fitoia behind the music.
Fifties center and white planes.
And I performed near or there.
Back in August and big crowd.
I was very nervous.
But I ended up getting a standing ovation.
I look into my mirror.
I came here to know my mind.
Everything you always wanted to know about Fitoia Khan.
In episode 97 of Mike's Pot Show, check it out at www.markbars.com.
That's m-a-r-k-b-a-r-s.com.
What?
When you eat a hot dog.
What do you think?
A hot dog?
A hot dog.
Hey Adam, what's up?
It's Jersey Todd.
Remember during the summer you played this song from the Children of Selstead primary school?
Yeah, this was the school that was in danger of closing.
And the kids came up with the song as part of the effort to save the school and posted
the track up to the PMM.
Well, I'm absolutely thrilled to say that I just got an email from the school governor
who wants to let everyone know that it's been determined that the school
not be closed.
I just wanted to thank you for helping draw attention to the issue.
I want to thank all the listeners who went out and purchased the copy of the song,
and all the other podcasts who played the song.
Once again, we have yet another example of what we can do as a podcast community
to really help out when we pull all of our resources.
And frankly, I am really looking forward to being able to do something like this again.
Yo, thanks, bro.
And hey, everyone, this song is still available for sale on their website.
And I'll send Adam a link and hopefully I'll put it up in the show notes.
But this is a great thing.
Talk to you later.
Yes.
Very cool.
Hey, I'm cool.
A lot of people sent me email about that.
It's excellent.
And I will put a link to the song and
and to the site, as Jersey Todd mentioned,
the cell-stead school.
And I don't know if it came through purchases of the song,
if we were able to contribute or not.
But I did get a message from the governor as well.
And this was the first audio comments.
That's really why I've only been sharing it.
Please send more audio comments.
You guys send great stuff in email.
It's called the voice mail line number or something.
It's much more powerful when I can play a piece of audio
relating to a topic like this.
Excellent.
I guess we just keep buying the song.
Keep the money coming to this school.
Man, it can never be enough money in school.
Hi, this is Lockjaw.
Host of the podcast, junkie show.
Now, usually I'd be using this time to promote my own podcast.
But recently, I've discovered a show that
well, quite frankly, has me absolutely blown away.
It's called, I love the company.
Put out by David at Blito.
Better known as that guitar man from Central Park.
You know, the guy playing guitar right here.
Every day, Monday through Friday, he plays some great music.
Has some great artists, including himself.
And Wednesday has a special show called The Wednesday Morning Wakeup Call.
Now, the latest episode had me absolutely moved to tears.
Find out why go to that guitar man.com.
Download episode 109.
Well, heck, download them all.
They're really good.
And I'm sure you'll enjoy it.
It's one podcast I can strongly recommend.
That guitar man scares me because he's so damn good.
You know, he's got more talent than any person
person should.
He can sing a song romantic and sweet.
And then you'll laugh so hard.
You'll fall off your seat.
He's on the PM and that's neat.
Because he's not so scary.
Yeah, I love that show too.
I love the company David at Blito.
He's got to go in on man.
He's just five shows a week.
And the short, you know,
they're like 20 minutes, 20 to 30 minutes.
And it's always filled with good fun songs.
You know, and topical songs.
I'm telling you, he's the Bob Dylan of our generation.
He don't want to believe it.
But he is.
It's given us words that have the little more meaning than.
Well, fill in your favorite Jay Z track here.
You know, the last Charlie we did together was on Friday with Patricia.
And we talked about death and about my mom passing and how we felt about it.
And now the work couple months down the road.
And obviously a lot of feedback for that episode.
And I really appreciate it.
I'm saving the majority of it for the next show.
I do with Patricia, which may be tomorrow.
But I did get a lot of comments that I wanted to share in this episode.
Because it's just such a deluge.
And people are really, really clueling into this topic.
Hi, Adam.
This is Jason Gerrit from the Buddhist podcast.
Just wanted to ask a question.
And maybe pass on a request.
First, thank you so much for the peer men.
We love it.
And we use it a lot for both of our podcasts.
It's opened our eyes up to so much talent.
And we've been able to share music with our listeners.
Each time we play a track,
we say it's from the podcast music network at music.potshow.com.
The thing is, we get a lot of email from people who want to buy the tracks,
but the buy buttons have not yet been enabled.
I know you guys have been real mega busy,
but can you give us some insight into when these buy buttons will be enabled?
Or what the time table is, so we can tell our listeners.
Okay, the second thing is,
Buddhism teaches that women support others,
and thereby cause others to support them.
So I think after the last show,
when you lost it with Patricia,
I will before the woman who takes such great care of you.
Love the pop show, love pod show, love your honesty, happy days.
Oh man, thank you.
I didn't lose it with Patricia.
We always talk like that.
And that's the beauty of the reality of the show.
And I bow before her, you know that.
Regarding PMN sales,
we're going to be launching a pod safe music channel
on Podshow Plus, which is going to be,
I think you're going to like it.
Really will be, you know,
we say we have the Podset Music Network for artists
and for podcasters, which was its original and its soul intent.
When I couldn't change anything with that at all,
we are bringing in elements to integrate the audience.
And of course, in part of that is the buying part.
So I believe we're doing everything in one go.
It's, you know, we have a number of tracks already enabled
and selling and that's working quite well.
And I think we're ready to scale it up and to enable the buy button.
Now that, of course, depends on the artists themselves.
They don't have to make it available for sale.
So once that goes, then if you want your, you know,
every artist will have the opportunity to select each individual track
if they want to make it for sale or not.
It's just the beauty of what we're doing with the music industry,
completely changing it around.
Wow, let's get back to death now.
Hello, Adam.
I'm a listener from Pat Singh London and a similar age to yourself.
I used to live in Walkerston and another affluent suburb of Gilford.
I've been listening to a discussion about your mum and also to your advice
to a gigapodcast when you ask them to move out of their comfort zone
and be far more honest you and their shows.
Now, at Christmas, I watched my dad die in hospital
and I remember at the time you talking about your own father's illnesses last year.
Now, you know, you never ever mention your dad
and frankly, it's starting to get spooky.
When my father's death, it affected how I see, think and react to my mum,
my surviving parents.
You are the male architect type in your household
and there must be deeper water still that you've not died into during your podcast.
I want to say, as a friend to you, only via your podcast,
please talk to me about your dad.
Open up your own no-go areas and let me understand how you see that world.
By the way, our proud scruncher, who never, ever buys
colored toilet paper.
And quite frankly, why should you?
Good challenge. I like that.
I think you've made a good point through all my words back in my face.
Well, the truth of the matter is that I do not have a very good relationship
at all with my father.
And this is mainly by his choice.
My parents divorced when I was, I believe, 16 or 17.
And even at that point, I did have to kind of jump into what was going on there.
And I said, look, you know, one thing I want to make sure we do here is there's a clean break.
And apparently he'd been flandering for years.
He definitely has an alcohol problem which he admits to.
And he really wanted to reboot his life.
And it was with new wife and new job and new location.
And you know, there's always a lot of blame on his upbringing.
Always, always, always, always.
In fact, that was used.
I think it's been used as an excuse for years.
Though I had no rules when he was growing up.
And therefore he doesn't know how to play by the rules or something to that effect.
And he also, you know, wanted to new kids, I think.
And he, he remarried.
And here's the interesting.
Well, man.
Just like a whole, a whole novella here that I could, that I could bring up.
And maybe I should do it in parts.
But I do want to be honest about it.
But just to add a little bit of insult to injury.
The woman he wound up remarried, wound up marrying.
I had known.
I was just leaving it at that.
So that's, you know, and then they had a, had a kid.
And what was interesting is that my sisters and I and my mom, of course,
really my sisters and I, you know, and my sisters really tried a lot longer than I did.
Not harder, but longer.
But I saw the writing on the wall very soon.
The man only has one goal.
And his goal is to become a multimillionaire.
And I've tried to help him out with that before.
And that has not been a very enjoyable experience in the, you know,
working together, uh, co-wrote a book with him.
And, you know, just a lot of loose ends that he doesn't tie up properly.
And it just all comes back to the fact that all he's interested in is doing business.
I probably, you know, insult the injury to him.
The fact that I have been successful and financially successful probably bugs the shit out of him.
So, um,
aside the fact for us not having contact for a number of years growing up, you know,
but he was very busy during my, my younger formative years and really wasn't around.
And it's because he was out partying as well.
You know, so it wasn't, it wasn't just work.
And he had a very important job and, and I do value his contribution for what that is.
But there was just never a contact, you know.
I, I can't, I, the times we tossed the ball around in the front or backyard,
I can count on one half of a hand.
So the contact just wasn't there and whenever I tried to re-establish it,
it always came back to business.
He can only talk about business.
Then, you know, he went into hospital as he had a minor stroke and then,
uh, somewhat more severe stroke and he still been rehabilitation.
Um, and, you know, and he's still battling alcoholism.
Uh, and he's a mess.
And, you know, and my sisters and I have tried.
And he, all he just talks about business and we say,
we just talk about normal things for a second.
You know, just forget about it.
Let's talk about life and health and he can't do it.
And honestly, after, you know, many, many, many years of trying,
I kind of like said, I don't care anymore.
I give up, you know.
It's not my job.
He, he left us and wanted to try re-booting.
It didn't work out the way he expected it to.
You know, can't be bothered.
It's kind of the way it feels.
It's exactly the way it feels.
Uh, and I may regret that.
I totally realize it.
Um, but for now, you know, and, and this is not just me.
I have two sisters who agree with this and are equally as frustrated
and have probably equally as easily given up.
That's just the situation in the way it is.
Uh, I'll think about it some more though because, you know,
just surprised me that you wanted this, uh, this honest, uh, discussion about it.
So I'll, I'll, I'll, uh,
Dredge up some more.
I agree.
It's good for me and hopefully not too boring for you.
I had a, uh, day from South Florida here going back.
Um, I just came to this revelation at the, at the share.
Um, I sold my high blood yesterday, uh, in preparation of buying one of the new, uh, 80 gig
work.
And, um, this is the first time I've been traveling, uh, to an appointment, uh,
see one of my clients with out of high blood and probably five years.
I've been listening to the radio.
Man, this sucks dude.
Um, yeah.
Anyway.
That's it.
Bye.
Yeah.
I know it does, dude.
It totally blows.
Those chunks.
And I've been getting Patricia into podcasting.
She's been finding stuff on her own and pod show plus.
She hasn't signed up for an account yet.
She's like, why?
Why should I do that?
Well, because then you can listen all these things and you get the show and it's there automatically
for you and she hasn't quite see the benefit of it.
But she's been listening to stuff and she'd be listening to the Frank Truth podcast and, uh,
I showed her how to watch a, uh, a fashion video podcast and she liked that.
And then there's the, uh, the jazz, the jazz suite.
And, uh, what's the other show?
I like so much the, uh,
hold on a second.
Let me go to my, uh,
What's the name of it?
I'm just going to my collection here,
a pod show plus.
And I'll tell you exactly what it is.
It's the, um, it's another like big band type show.
Uh, I found it through Lindy Hopper Cindy who works in a finance at, at pod show.
Let me see, uh,
collection, here we go.
Let me see if it shows up right away.
Otherwise it, otherwise I'll just put it in the show notes.
Um, it's under music.
It's already scrolled off.
Damn.
What's the name of that show?
I love it.
Okay.
Tell you what.
I'll play one more song.
No.
I'll do this.
Question about my setup.
Hi Adam.
This is Gary Alexander in Las Vegas.
And I'm listening to the, at the show from, uh,
such a brace.
And I just got to the part where the guy was,
was talking about, uh, studio equipment.
And you said that, uh,
you have the high, uh,
I think it's the PR 40 from the second.
Um, that that's about a $400 microphone.
If I'm not mistaken myself.
Uh, I think that that I have,
I have actually tried to find out what kind of equipment you have as well.
And, um, I heard you say you had to help the high, uh,
microphone.
And I think that about a $400 microphone.
And your stereo, uh,
compressor that you have, uh,
is not, you're not going to get the same.
And I know you know this, but I want to mislead the
listeners the way that the show has been going, uh,
on the age here.
Um,
the stereo compressor is better than a hundred dollars,
um, compressor that we may be able to afford out here.
Um,
granted you can get better sound.
All right.
Hold on a second.
First of all, the mic, I checked it online.
The mic is like,
you're right.
It's not 150 boxes like 250 bucks,
but you can get one cheaper on eBay.
And there are lots of microphones similar to the
HIL PR40 that'll work just as well.
But okay, you're right, but it's not 400 bucks.
The compressor, yeah, I'm using a nice one.
And, uh, and that's what I said.
It's the TLA 5052 stereo valve processor.
You better believe it's got a great sound.
But whenever I go on the road,
and I use the cheap $100 limiter compressor,
people sometimes even say they like that sound better.
So it's just a matter of, you know,
of adjusting all the knobs.
You can pretty much get this type of sound out of any setup.
And then if you're lucky, you can keep the setup,
which is problematic for me because I keep moving
and acoustic change and, uh,
the mixer bumps around in the,
in the suitcase and then those settings change.
And, you know, sometimes a little tough.
But in general, I get, you know,
lots of compliments about my on the road sound as well.
So I got to say it's not the microphone.
Uh, that is affordable,
and you really can do it with a $100 compressor.
But that stereo compressor is going to,
if you use a skewer is not on our box.
And I think that the way that you described it,
even though you're telling the truth,
is a bit misleading.
And, uh, even though you have a small,
little mixing board there,
it's 150 bucks.
Yeah, okay.
Well, you probably got four EQ controls on that thing,
which is nothing.
But your tone is coming from that stereo compressor,
as well as that how you're 40.
And, uh, I just feel like that,
the listeners are being a little misled
on how you get your one tone.
It also helps as you have an amazing voice.
Uh, and God kind of gifted you on that.
So that has nothing to do with money,
other than the fact that it's millions.
Holder.
Ha ha ha.
Uh, I can turn it off.
Let me see.
It's now off.
Yeah, the volume is going to be a lot softer,
hold on.
Maybe I can go like that.
So now this, now the process,
two, two.
Yeah, processers now off.
Uh, it makes a difference, but not like that.
Holder.
Now I got to turn it back.
Crap.
There we go.
See?
I mean, I do it.
Then I mess up all my settings.
Ha ha.
Hey, it's the name of that podcast.
I was looking for is Hay Mr. Jessie.
Uh, founded my channels and my collection.
You can also just use the find it function on the podshow.com,
which I'm finding increasingly more useful.
I'd really like it.
It pulls out stuff out of episodes.
You can play it right there.
You can listen to each individual one without the page,
flopping away.
It gives you the, the album art.
It's getting pretty good.
And this Thursday, it happens.
It officially drops episode number five.
Oh, fuck man.
Fuck.
So much pilot error today.
It's not funny.
That would be episode number five of Shadow Falls.
Shadow Falls.
That podshow.com.
I'd just be good.
I was dead wrong.
You roasted King.
That swings both ways.
They're not asked money.
I am here.
I am sleeping.
I am late.
I am not here.
I am there for our breathing.
Oh.
I whisper soft.
Now we're deflating off.
Look for my sign.
Let me light that shine to the shadows.
I am here.
Why are you sleeping?
I am late.
I am here for our breathing.
I am here.
Monk, acoustic version of I have.
Modly steam from Shadow Falls.
We only have one more episode to go after Thursdays episode number five before the end
of the season for Shadow Falls.
You want to go back and listen to every single episode of Shadow Falls.
Podshow.com.
We've got a cast website.
Now we've got a companion show that goes along with the podcast.
It really is bringing back theater of the mind into your oral experiences.
As an AUAR.
Alright, shit.
The shit you hear in your ear.
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it on the High Performance Podcast to
live re-network from Podshow and line-white networks.