This is MV from bedtime stories my kids love.
If you want stories that will keep your kids from going to bed,
check out Shadow Falls, and don't say I didn't warn you.
This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
Show will give you a special code to get great discounts at godaddy.com.
Player prop.
Delta, Serator.
Four, four, seven.
Sometimes, animals all alone.
And he needs his love right there on the microphone.
So here she is, yes, the lady Patricia.
The stage who had some better than one.
And with this angel from above,
There's nothing that they both can't do.
A make you wild as dreams come true.
To grab your earbuds and jam a man.
And let the fabulous show begin.
It's Adam and Patricia.
Yes, Adam and Patricia.
Adam and the lady Patricia.
The business is so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so.
Lo, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The road of me, my dear.
I ask my own man, my guilty, call me.
I can't see it.
But nothing is how to do it.
It's how you land so deep.
Get my make you sad.
This is my world.
You're my secret, but it's all I have to do.
I'm the way I'm supposed to do something.
Nothing is how to do it.
It's all I have.
Okay, let's waste the space.
Well, never well-becase, you can make me grow up
Cause I will waste my time
Well, you're a semi-light
But you can make me grow up
I leave a loud chair in the nice coat drink
Oh, well, never would I have a home to drink
Yeah, bitch, you're from ways I dreamt of you
This moment's gone, but it was meant to me
You might make it sad, but it's meant to me
Hey, you're like a sad pocket, but you don't know
Yeah, bitch, you're from ways I dreamt of you
I'm a semi-light, you're from ways I dreamt of you
It's all I want, it's all I want
Oh, you're from ways I dreamt of you
Well, never well-becase, you can make me grow up
You're a semi-light, you're from ways I dreamt of you
Well, never well-becase, you're from ways I dreamt of you
If I make you sad, but it's meant to me
You're just like my dad, what do you know
You're the person that's never so mundane
And nothing is how to do and it's how to help me
You're the one, you're the one, you're the one
You're the one, you're the one
You're the one, you're from ways I dreamt of you
Well, never well-becase, you can make me grow up
You're the one, you're the one, you're from ways I dreamt of you
You're a semi-light, you're from ways I dreamt of you
You're from ways I dreamt of you
Well, never well-becase, you're from ways I dreamt of you
The same state that spawned the award-winning Don and Drew from Wisconsin, Sunspot.
And some are day, which it is not today.
So much great music out there.
Isn't that cool?
Sure.
Hey, you have a...
You have a hum.
Have a hum.
Yeah, I can hear a hum.
Really?
Yeah, I don't worry about it.
That's okay.
This is the divorce course code.
Episode number, 447.
Sounds good.
Keep in track, just in case you want to do that.
I came a favorite number.
447?
Well, 447.
So we had 444, not too long ago.
And someone said that's a really bad number.
It's a very unlucky number.
And I think in China, something like that.
Well, so...
Well, I don't know.
It was a good day for me.
I'm trying to figure out what this is.
I don't hear it.
No, I hear it.
I hear something.
I hear a hum.
Could be the lights, the dimmer.
Yeah, yeah.
The house is falling apart, honey.
I popped one.
We have to move.
Yeah.
And we're getting closer.
We're learning so much about the United Kingdom.
In their houses.
It is never ending story.
I mean, we learn so much.
Is there a big limiter on you?
Hold on one second.
Yeah.
I got a big limiter on you.
Don't move.
Yeah.
I got a...
Okay.
There you go.
So you have to learn so much.
I mean, it's not easy to buy a house here.
Well, no.
It is not.
I found the big difference.
And for those of you living in the UK,
you may not know how it works in the rest of the civilized world.
And for those of you living in the civilized world,
you'd be amazed to hear how it works here.
No, I'm sorry.
This is a civilized country, but this is not a civilized process.
No, it's not.
In America, and in most countries, we have an intermediate step
when you buy a home called escrow.
Yeah.
And that means that you essentially have put down a percentage of the purchase price,
10 percent.
Yeah.
And you agree...
With that 10 percent, there's a contract that you agree with.
And you agree upon when you're going to pay the rest
and when they have to vacate the home.
And there's a whole bunch of other stuff.
No surveys and all that crap.
Okay.
There's the same.
Yeah.
But here in the, you know, kingdom, they don't have that.
What happens is...
When you go to sign the paperwork, that's when it's done.
So you literally will see people moving out of their home,
or other people are moving in because people are often afraid to move out
because at the very last minute, it could all break down.
Yeah.
So now that's one thing.
But of course, if you have what's called a chain,
because the person that you're buying a house from has to buy a house
from someone else, buying a house from someone else...
Have you ever heard of that?
No.
I haven't ever heard of this.
Whatever.
But so what can actually happen and what's quite common is that five houses
will close.
We'll be sold on the same day, almost at the exact same time,
which could be all across the country.
And people that are moving in and it literally crossing each other.
You know, guy walking out of the couch.
So we're walking in with table.
Yeah.
And it's crazy.
It's crazy because if the chain breaks.
Yeah.
Then you can be, and we're five people are fucked.
And we are, and we are always at the bottom of the chain
because we have nothing to sell on.
So we're just waiting.
And if someone above us is waiting on something,
then we're basically susceptible to that entire chain.
It's crazy.
It is so outrageous.
And real estate agents don't have to pass any kind of test here.
Anyone can become a real estate agent.
In fact, you would be a really good one.
Yes.
You would be a great real estate agent.
Absolutely.
So we're kind of...
I'm a good seller.
Yeah.
So we're kind of in the midst of all of that.
Understanding.
Because every time we're very happy to find something that we think could be, you know,
something that we would like to live in, that doesn't mean.
Oh, yeah.
That doesn't mean you can actually buy it.
No, I'm sorry.
Of course not.
Even if you dangle the money in front of their noses.
Well, that kind of depends.
If they are prepared to leave.
Yeah.
But then even when you agree upon a price and say, OK, so let's just say,
next week we'll, you know, we'll do the contract.
Someone else could come in if they did more.
That person has the legal right, not the ethical right, I guess.
But the legal right to just go settle to somebody else.
That is not very decent.
So by the same token, you know, that the real estate agents here will ask you,
do you need a mortgage, do you have a house to sell,
a lot of blah, blah, because they need to know what they're dealing with.
Because they could also be working for weeks on end or months with somebody.
Yeah.
At the very end, it might turn out that they don't have the money.
No.
Because you never had to put any money down.
There's no commitment.
It's so wrong.
It is.
So complicated and wrong.
Very wrong.
Who came up with that?
Well, and they can seem to get rid of it.
They've tried.
Yeah.
They're trying.
And then there's no tax rule.
Now I understand why they're shows about it.
Of course.
Of course, because you see you are destroyed.
Yeah.
They're emotional.
On the verge of a nervous breakdown.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
So honey, I know you haven't paid attention to the show for the last couple of days.
Oh, don't say that.
It was the truth.
God.
But I've had it long come.
Well, you know I've been talking about did we land on the moon or did we not?
Yeah.
I heard the whole thing you explained it.
I've seen the footage.
Yeah.
You know.
So I got to say that we probably did land on the moon.
I'm pretty convinced.
Yeah.
You gave up?
I think I do give up.
Whatever.
However.
So this whole conversation was sparked because they lost the.
The tape.
That's a loss.
The original moon landing tape.
And still called tapes.
I don't have it on DVD.
No, of course not.
So John Aguilera, who is clearly part of the the Chacha Head gang, has found a copy of
the tape and attempted to us.
So we have, yes, we have the original copy of the tape.
Can you stick that thing in your ear?
It doesn't fit.
It's not at all distracted.
It's just it doesn't fit.
It doesn't stay in my ear.
It's no space.
I have the tiniest ears.
No.
Yeah, ears aren't that tiny.
It's the holes.
Yeah.
You got to go like.
Uh huh.
Quite.
All right.
So while you fiddle with your ears.
Ladies and gentlemen, I present to you.
Of course, this is audio only.
Yeah.
Let me just help you.
No, no.
It's okay.
One is in.
Yeah.
See, it's in.
You got to shove it in there.
Shubby and Mitch.
Permanent.
Yeah.
I present for you the original footage.
Audio only, of course, of the very first moon landing.
Okay.
See, if I got this right.
I'm ready.
You don't have light.
You can take a break.
You can.
Well, the fucking roof over.
Roger, may I call you?
We got these up.
We cannot believe.
You are on the fucking floor.
The police cannot fucking believe it, over.
You are a clear double gun lunatic, weapon's in there.
You want?
Fucking work on the floor.
Over.
By the way, clearing cock.
Are you fucking believing this over?
We.
You.
Over.
And you know that that's probably exactly what they were thinking actually yeah, I am walking on the fucking moon
You believe it? Yeah, yeah, of course
That's what the normal human being would say John Aguilera listener graphic designer Ford Collins Colorado
I'm indebted to you. It's just so funny. That was a great way to wrap that up. Yeah, yeah
But you really believe it. Yeah, yeah, yeah, it makes sense
There's a lot of stuff that doesn't make sense, but you know now at this morning
I was watching the 911
Documentary you know that this guy put together a whole all the evidence
Yeah, and they've done a second version of it called 911 changes. So it's the it's the second version
Man, they do make such I mean, I don't want to get into the whole
You know, it was 9-11 was it really terrorist or was it whatever did they know about it? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
If you watch not the two French guys
There's a little piece of that is in there. This is really all exterior evidence and lots of quotes from everybody
You know, you'd have to go and and fact check every single thing, but
But isn't a great they have footage now of all those things that happen. I mean, you know
Well, the footage doesn't well, yeah, no, I don't know. There's a lot of second guessing people should know
Yeah, if it's really true then it's really frightening. Yeah, yeah, even more frightening than Osama bin Laden
Hey, I just heard on the news that a Northwest KLM plane from Amsterdam
Is returning back to Amsterdam to skip all airport because in several episodes
Yeah, on the BBC London
Because several passengers are in custody, so we'll find out what happened
Wow, yeah, what I'm gonna do a quick check on the new side because they were fighting or
Because sometimes when there's a fight aboard. Yeah, I'd probably have to go back. Let me see go
You know probably English
This
Patricia, what are you talking about? No, I mean no, thank no, the voice drink. No, it was from
People to I think the United States probably San Francisco. Okay, okay. Oh, I see. Let me see. There is
Oh, that's interesting. There's nothing on the number one new site. No, of course not
The Dutch and journalism, please
Well, could be could be drink could be
Well, what it probably is and I'm just guessing here. It's probably
You know what happened the other day with two Asian guys that you know people like oh, I don't trust you
Word about you. You don't look right and they tell you I just saw pictures in the in the paper of them
They're so cute who there's no handsome to two of them. I don't know what they were thinking
Which which guys are these the guys that they were they were they took them off the plane
Because people were
Right right that that was a Ryan air from afraid. Yeah, yeah, they felt that they oh, they were wearing
sweaters and I thought that that was
So this is really interesting. There is nothing at all
on I'm just looking at Google news which kind of goes through all the new. There's nothing at all on the Dutch Google news
Nothing at all
but on the
US Google news
We have a
US plane turn back to Amsterdam. Here we go. Check this out. Yeah, but is a US plane was it was a KLM? Are you sure?
Well, I'm just telling what I heard here two Dutch fighter planes a company that's F-16s
a company to US Northwest I North
Northwest Airlines plane bound from Mumbai back to Amsterdam Skippel airport on Wednesday official said a Dutch air traffic
A troll spokesman said the plane was in German airspace when it turned back
The spokesman for Skippel said the pilot had taken the decision to turn back but could give no further details
Security has been increased at airports blah blah blah blah blah blah
Dutch news agency AMP quote police is saying a number of people had been taken off the Northwest plane and were being questioned
Oh, so I guess it's already landed
Wow
Oh, I'm very curious about that
Yeah, that's interesting
Can that be I bet you I bet you it's just people are freaking out. That's what isn't a nice flying these days
Not at all I got a fly pretty soon
I know next couple of weeks. I got to go back. Yeah, yeah, so I have to yeah, I'll just I got some news
So these are the there was a guy's Louis what kind of cute
The guy said they sent up look at them. Yeah, they're like the gorgeous
I want to send them away
This the right the guy on the right looks like Richard Marx. Look at him
Look at him. It's Richard Marx. No look at the face look at the face look at the face
Look at my eyes. Look at my eyes. Yes, and you're under. Yes, okay. Look at the face and you're back
You're back. So I don't know what happened there people freak out for nothing
Excuse me what you got going on in your world baby. Well nothing
You know that we do miss big brother. I cannot believe I'm saying this
Because you know I hate big brother, but since I'm in the UK
Yeah, they're Britain in Britain. Yes, I followed it and it is so much nice is a big brother that we used to in Holland
Yeah, and and even the US big brother. I've once had nothing interesting, but this one is and we miss them
You know what it was not about they were part of our family. Yeah, right and how sad are we
Yeah, right well, it was very entertaining and now that I see them all in the paper
I have to say that
I'm so sorry for Ashley because she looks such she looks like a winner
Ashley and yeah, Ashley and you know the gorgeous
Yeah, well, you know wake up that the G strings and yeah, this was that you know who wakes up gorgeous
But this is a great way to do a dating show
You know why I mean for you to sit at home and think yeah, I would date her. I wouldn't date
Ashley and what a pain in the ass. I wouldn't date Nicky image
Yeah, but these people all locked up for weeks
Yeah, but that's when you see the true person
Yes, of course doesn't it drive you just mad
What do you mean become a different person just saying if I were at home, you know like evaluating who I'd want to marry
Yeah, but they say that they all changed because of it and they actually changed for the better
Yes, you know, yeah, they kind of came to you. What was kind of forgotten? We're so used to this big brother
But it started off the whole concept of the show was and it was called golden cage before became big brother
Was across between
What was the movie with Jim Carrey? Yes, um, yeah, that movie and biosphere
So it was supposed to be two in one the people actually weren't supposed to be able to leave the house at all
And of course you're not in the backyard or any of that so it was a very different concept of time
Yeah, it was a very different concept of time
So we've kind of forgotten the psychological aspect of what that does
Yeah, but I think it's it's
Every single person in there was positive these people here did a very good job. Yeah, they're a very strong
Actually, that was great product. They all been through a lot personally in but let's not make the end of the day the production
Company did a great job on choosing what to show. I think they do the great job
Building the stories because you know, they really build stories
Forget the games. It's the way they edit it. It's what they choose to show me
Fantastic very well done. Yeah, I really
Good story enters. I would add about it. You respect that but if I see the pictures from
Pete the winner. I've said for the American people don't know what we're talking about Pete and Nicky
I don't know if seen enough of those tongues hanging out
It's a little bit of a freak show
I don't know how long we can keep the guy who want one is a has a severe case of Tourette
Yeah, yes
What was very interesting in the beginning? Yeah, and what you see is that no one no one notices it anymore after a while
If I like to do this no one no one no one cared
Yeah, he's also his mom was the
Violin play miscellaneous in the common arts. So I met his mom. Yeah, not really consciously
No, I'm sure I shook her hand thinking of yeah, yeah, and his dad
He had he didn't he never met his dad and
Actually he knew he still didn't meet his dad because he he doesn't want it now. He's got a hundred thousand pounds
His dad will shoot now. Well, you bet but what I like about his dad is that he doesn't want a
How do you say to appear now because he doesn't want to have all the
publicity yeah, right so
That sounds he'll pop on the scene you watch. Yeah, yeah, I'm the son. It says
This is kind of you being Robin today and no, I thought I'd just play Robin and Howard. No, it said listen to this because
In my eye it was an eye catcher
Robbie Williams says Louis Wolves wants to manage me and sleep with me
He always thinks people want to sleep with him. I don't care
What do you see? I don't care. I really don't care about that doing Tom Cruise
Yeah, his production company broke up with Paramount. Yeah
That's a big deal yeah, yeah, and and so in no now
That really you know, that's his distribution partner. He would he would make the movies at this point
But I don't think that we're doing as expected at the box office
I mean getting a million people to do anything is still a big deal
But I think that people are kind of tired of it
I wanted to say that I think from now on I think it will go down a little bit
This is show business and
I'm a little bit sick of the whole thing yeah, but see I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that because
He is not the one out there about his Katie is Katie. It's the continuous press coverage
You know, I'm going to defend the guy now even though he's you know, I'm afraid of him
Yeah, but he started it
That's so unfair we've been in this exact same position where you're incredibly well-known
Something happens where the you started or not and the press just keeps repeating that over and over and over
I know but until people are sick and tired of it. Yeah, but this is so no
No, no, no, no, no, I'm gonna. He was jumping of the of the cow cheese and and you know, it was a bit
Ridiculous, so he did that once and that's been you know, that's been the you know, does that way against stretch
They've stretched you mean come on. He did some good shit. You know, you know, I was not an
I wasn't an admission impossible, but officer in a gentleman was was great top gun was great
Risky business was great. Yeah, that's what you think. I don't like it
Has nothing and I don't think he's cute
No, I don't think he's cute either, but you know, it's just I'm not gonna pile jump on the Tom Cruise
You watch everyone is gonna be all over of the guy is gonna you're right. He's gonna go totally on the downside of the rollercoaster
He'll come out okay on the other end. He'll probably do some more wacky things because that he doesn't know how to communicate in public
That's yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, but could see it into this first place
And now it's just you know, and the whole Scientology thing. I think, you know, it's it's unclear
What is it? I don't you know, yeah
I don't know, but I'm not gonna I don't want to pile jump
I don't think it's not fair. No, I hate it when it happens to me
You know, I like to do that now and this
That's Paul Joe
Serious stars one-o-two listeners boy you're gonna miss some fun stuff
But if you go to daily source code dot com you can download this entire show
Still to come because if you coast hell way
Don and Drew American cliche great show
I want to check that out then rockin' or geek show Brian no checks in with the Frank truth which you cannot hear on a podcast
East radio Scott singular wind it up. I will talk to you guys tomorrow
So they're gone
So we don't with crews
Yeah, I was done with crews. I wasn't I was already done with it. There's a study yesterday in the New York Times
It was a report about a study this guy is doing is writing a book called
Science of the mind I think and his research has shown that 40% of all adults from 17
Unup
40% of them
Would like to be famous
Really yeah now very small percentage of them think that that's really you know that that's not that's their ultimate goal
But when you think about it that what the position we're in now in in the world in in media
Fame yeah, is pretty much all you see yeah, you know
Whether it's being beyond say whether it's being yeah, yeah, whether it's being
You know the Arctic monkeys
You know whatever it is everything is about even my space you know
Yeah, which I could be the person who has 800,000 friends, you know, and not just in my
800 and stuff like that. Yeah, so there is kind of this fame culture
Yeah, which people all those shows are about it. Well, yeah, and looking you know
Roger you could become a there's the gen famous you can be famous and back in the day when when you when I work
They actually sell famous yeah, yeah, that's true. That's really what it is. Yeah. That's really what it fame, but you know
Being famous yeah, so
Let's just there's something going on with that there is definitely a change and I think that that's what brings upon this whole
You know when someone's famous do you think that
It brought a lot of happiness to people no or more sadness and
Unhappyness no in fact
Is that a word unhappyness unhappyness?
No, I think in the same in the same study the guy says that
It's like before people go into a meltdown they start talking about themselves a lot and using their own name a lot
Yeah, yeah, yeah, and then you know and you have all these examples you know from Kurt Cobain to you name it
But a lot of it just ends in suicide
Well, I have self destruction one way or the other yeah, well of course being in the business for a long time
I'm seeing and met a lot of my colleagues and and very talented people
You have to be very strong
You have to be very strong to survive
You know that there are so many stars that went down because it is it is not easy
It is not easy because when you really really if if it's really your turn and your very famous
It's all about you every day is about you all the people around you talk about you
They laugh about your your jokes
Yeah, it's you know it's you you because everybody is of course
Even living an eating of you and
And in some people don't get that but if you smart you just you know keep on thinking about that
All these people are very hard. It's very hard. I don't think I could do that without you
I'd be lost so you won't I need jumping on couches and talking about Scientology. Yes, so do your world get smaller and smaller
What happened to Elvis personally, of course? They they kept it, you know really really small and
At the end something will happen to these people because this is not very healthy
It's not good and the people who who's a five
You know a very strong people right and they don't have the brain right and they're usually people that then
People start winding up not liking like Madonna
Yeah, no, so you know it is there's no-in situation which is why I feel what do you mean not liking how many people actually like Madonna?
I think a lot of people how many people have really started to dislike Madonna a
Lot a lot yeah, but do you think she's so strong? Yeah, I think that's why they don't like her
I think because you have to be strong people build up uh, you know, she had to change
She had to morph she's had to do all these different things to actually stay current with with her industry
Which is predominantly top 40 music and dance music. Yeah
So you change a lot people get pissed off. I think that Madonna sometimes is not nice because she's actually
frustrated
She knows she's not a great singer. She knows she gets a lot of shit for that and not accepted by a couple of people or a part of
Not fans, I don't know you know it's it's I think with her it's frustration
You know and I remember talking about famous when you got very famous in America
We were together thank God for that and you
Yeah, but that but that was amazing because we went you were already very well known in Holland
You went to America you were still young yeah with a mature woman next to you, of course, yeah
And suddenly in a couple of weeks time yeah, you were the hottest
Vijay on TV on MTV that's almost like having curable leprosy in a couple of weeks time
We couldn't walk the streets in New York. I mean screaming girls. I had to kick him. I mean you
I didn't get any of that asked you
Not a single fucking piece of tales. See there. Essas yeah
Too shay
And you freaked out. I remember that you freaked out because you're not very good at that
You didn't know what to do. It came from you know all sides
Defined freak out, please so people don't think I'm some idiot, but I mean do I freak out well because you had to
You couldn't do anything you couldn't walk the streets you wouldn't what means I freaked out what what?
Because everybody wanted to piece of you. No, no, that's why, but what do you constitute a freak out?
Freaks out because you
You got very tired. No, no, no, I'm asking
What at what point what did I do that you said he's freaking out?
You got irritated. Oh, so I've been freaked out for 18 years baby. You became violent
You hid holes in the in the doors of the apartment. And listen, it's a sheet rock because you know
Yeah, of course, but you know why it was perfect. It was dramatic if things were so irritated
It was so heavy the load was so heavy everybody wanted a piece of you everybody wanted something
Everybody wanted interviews. Uh, I don't know what and when you were young and it happens in a couple of weeks of times
I've seen it and I had to pull your legs. Should I tell you something else? That was a
pool you don't. Should I tell you something else? There was also a lot of frustration there because
I was allowed to do absolutely nothing at MTV. Yeah, nothing. You know everything you said
We had to be sanctioned and pulled through the strainer very frustrating. So I wasn't able to just have fun and just
You know enjoy that was part one and MTV really hated their people becoming stars
They were completely against them. Perhaps for personal reasons, but I'll just take the high road and say that I believe it was
Probably not even not even stupid on their part. You know, it's like keep these kids interchangeable keep them
You know keep them fresh keep them young. Of course. I stayed there for eight years and they fired me
You know four times at least and they still kept coming back and
And want to meet a new one. And I wanted you to know that if it's not good, there's another waiting for you. Yeah
Yeah, and then that was the frustration
Because you are you have brains, you know, and you knew what was going on and it was it was not easy
I have to say it was not easy. I'll never forget the day we used to do music meetings
And the R&R talent was invited to the music meetings, which is basically what are we going to play on the channel this week
And and it was very political at all had to do with the record companies and you know if we did and it was coming to the video
Music Awards, so we had to play something from that artists label and all this stuff so that they're coming and then Gene Simmons
had a band what the hell was the name of that band he produced?
Okay, some I'll think of it and he came in with knee pads
Bards into the meeting jumped up on the table and said who do I have to blow to give to the
There's a strong person, that's an example of a very very strong person business that's business man
You know, well you also had an amenity for a long time which kind of helps
No one knew who the who the kiss guys were. Yeah, very good very good. I've been I've been waiting to play this thing
I don't I've been keeping it in the admin Patricia folder. I really don't remember why so let me just play it because
I've been keeping it for a reason, so let's just listen to this for a second.
Hey Adam, my name is John Hanover.
I live in Bang U Beach, Florida.
I listen to the Charlie first code, daily source code,
and watch out, et cetera.
Some bytune put it on the podcast.
We, you and me, usually go for a bike ride
to the beach on the ocean.
And it's sunshine, palm trees, ocean breeze.
Just the iPod and Adam and Dad.
And I can't believe it turned that bill in down.
Anyway, I'm a graphic designer, photographer.
I use the PC in a Mac.
This is, uh, he was calling in, telling him about himself.
This is one of our listeners.
But didn't we hear that already?
I can't believe you turned McDonald down?
I guess we did play that, didn't we?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Okay.
I'm an idiot.
Uh-huh.
Now who's getting old here?
I'm going to be 342 in, uh, what, 10 days?
Yeah.
No, in two weeks.
Uh-huh.
I was feeling that yesterday.
You know, you know, I heard this.
You know, who Carmen Tyler is?
No.
You've heard her music before.
I've played it on the, on the, on the show.
She was, um, miss Louisiana in 1995.
I mean, stunningly beautiful.
Yeah.
Really heart-lain, beauty queen, 19 year old, 19 years old, once you won.
And she's on the podcast, Music Network.
Oh?
And, uh, really a lot of Christian gospel stuff.
Yes, that I played Amazing Grace, by the way.
Because I figured no one ever plays that song.
Yeah.
You never hear it on the radio.
Which, and she did it was a live version.
She definitely has, has some pies.
But I, you know, I keep saying, you know,
send me some naked pictures.
And she did it.
Well, no.
But, uh, I didn't get this comment.
Hey, Adam.
This is Aben from Reaching Farloos City.
And I just caught the last Charlie.
And I had to call you on this, man.
I'm looking out for your soul here.
You got me a little worried here.
And what I'm talking about is Carmen Tyler.
Now, the last couple of times you've played Carmen on your podcast.
You've asked her for naked pictures.
And normally this would not bother me one bit because,
a naked pictures and really hot chicks that goes a long way with me.
B.
I am in no way the person that needs to go around spouting any kind of values on anybody else with
my track record.
And see, you're a grown man or you can do whatever you want.
But I'm worried a little bit because we're talking about Carmen Tyler.
We're talking America's sweetheart.
We're talking about pageant queen.
We're talking about all around nice girl, man.
We are talking about America and Apple pie here.
And we're talking about a girl that has amazing grace on the
pot safe music network.
You just played it on your show.
We're talking about a lady that has just uploaded three new
Christian tracks to the pot safe music network.
Now, if there is a God and you're looking out for your soul,
even if you're just hedging bets here.
And I'm talking about hedging bets at him.
Think about it.
If you ask Jenna James and for naked pictures,
then you're got probably wouldn't mind at all because guess what?
She's kind of dirty like that and she's going to do it anyway.
But hit an up Carmen Tyler for naked pictures is sort of like
ask an Amy Grant to come over for a threesome or a circle jerk with a
pope or something like that.
It's the things that may just get on on God's bad side.
If you're hedging your bets, I mean, when you go,
God forbid, when you go and your soul is being judged,
do you really want the nagging of Carmen Tyler for nude
picks on that on your soul?
I mean, think about it like pot smoking at him.
He blaze up, enjoy it, and you're open about it.
And it's a really cool thing.
But you probably wouldn't do it if there was a judge or a police officer watching you.
And that's what I'm talking about here.
I'm talking about watching your butt by keeping all your bases covered.
So man, I'm just looking out for your brother.
I just had to put that out there.
Still love in the Charlie and I will talk to you later, man.
Bye.
And that's what America's come to.
Get a life.
That's what America's come to.
You can't even talk.
You can't even see naked pictures of people anymore.
Look at turn on the news.
There's lots of dead people on the news.
Let's watch dead people.
People in the Bible will all naked.
Thank you.
Except for a little leaf.
In my case of huge leaves.
But yeah.
Yeah.
Come on.
It's up with that.
You know humor.
Oh.
It's not even about humor.
I mean, now that's immoral for me to ask about that.
You know.
You don't mind, do you?
No.
Not at all.
I don't see anything wrong with that.
Can I send Carmen a naked picture of you?
Yes, sure.
Maybe she wants to join me.
You know?
No, no.
Yeah.
Now you're talking.
Patricia and Karen.
That didn't sound very attractive.
I liked it.
The guy.
Oh, that's eBay's cool.
He's cool.
I don't know if he's making a joke or not.
I don't know.
But it sounded a little bit pissed off.
He was pissed off.
All right.
What else do we have?
And yet you've reduced smoke and joined next to a police guy.
Yeah.
I have.
In fact in Belgium.
Here's one for you.
Let me tell you.
In Belgium, which is definitely not as liberal as it's northern neighbor.
When it comes to the holy herb.
You were driving the MG.
Remember that the company MG.
Yeah.
And you drove it right on that we're redoing a road.
And the sewage drains were high up in the air compared to the road.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
And you drove it up right under the transmission.
And it's like.
And I was stuck.
He was stuck on the thing.
Yeah.
So you called me.
I showed up.
You know, joint dangling.
But the police was already there.
Next time.
Next to me.
So I get out.
And I'm smoking my dude.
But you did.
And I noticed.
And I said to you later.
Because why I was talking to the cop.
You know, explain to him what happened.
Oh, my.
You came high on.
You know, to pick me up and bring me up.
And you're standing there with a big joint.
And blowing the smoke into his face.
He didn't even notice.
This is my wife's pretty messed up.
Yeah.
And I said to you later.
Did you?
Did you notice?
Oh, I didn't.
I actually don't care.
So.
Oh, man.
All right.
Anything else we got?
Oh, the shadow falls is out.
The new episode.
You want to listen to it tonight?
Listen to that.
Right.
It's episode.
Don't give me that face.
We'll push it before a shit.
Do you want to listen or not?
Yeah.
What is it today?
Wednesday?
Yeah.
There you go.
That's it.
When instead of East Enders.
Yeah.
Listen to shadow falls.
Then we'll do it.
If you're in America.
Just listen to shadow falls.
You don't even turn on.
I'm so lonely.
Yeah.
Let's see.
We want to.
Oh, I promise that we might talk about Christina sleep over.
Oh, fine parenting moment.
Oh, OK.
Yeah.
So it was Saturday night.
Christina was going to go stay somewhere.
Oh, shit.
She doesn't know.
She didn't tell her.
No, no, no, no.
And she can do whatever she wants.
But just to check in and call us certain times.
Like before we go to bed.
Well, I have to explain that I had stories changing.
No, no, no, no.
I had very strict parents.
Very old fashion.
You know, it was another time.
I know.
I was born in 49.
So I was jumping out of the window when I was 15.
Exactly.
We had to.
Yeah.
Boy.
I would have loved to tell the truth to them and explain them.
You know, who I met and, you know, what I feel for the boy.
But I couldn't.
They were disgusted by it.
And they didn't want to hear it.
So that was horrible.
For teenagers, you feel very lonely.
You can go anywhere.
You're not allowed.
You have to sneak out.
You have to lie.
And I said to myself, I'm not going to do that with Christina.
You know, a teenage is a teenage.
She has to meet teenagers.
She has to do fun stuff.
Fun things.
Fun evil things.
Right.
Got to do some illegal stuff.
Christina said, I have a sleepover because it's somebody's birthday.
Mom, there's a lot of girls coming, blah, blah, blah.
And I said, okay.
Where is it?
Okay.
It's only because people go by train here a lot.
Yeah.
That's normal.
It's one stop.
Yeah.
We have little stations.
There's no problem here.
It's just like this.
Yeah.
She went.
And the only thing I always say to her, you can do anything you want.
But keep in touch with mommy.
So you have to call me.
So in the middle of the evening somewhere.
It's just, oh, I have to call mommy.
Of course.
It's great with self.
Just so no, she's fine.
That's different from when we were kids.
Yeah.
Because we were worried.
You know, normally moms would be worried.
Because you don't know what's going on.
There was no phone.
Yeah.
They always said, there was no phone in the neighborhood.
Well, now you got your phone.
So you can call me.
Just the only thing I want to know.
And before you go to bed.
So I know.
I don't tighten up the story, huh?
All right.
But that's, you know, parents recognize that.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
So it's Saturday and we're sitting and watching TV.
We had some sex planned.
Yeah.
But you were worried.
Well, she was supposed to call around midnight.
She didn't call.
And then of course, when we called her.
Then call the whole evening.
When we call her, we get voicemail.
Yeah.
We sent text messages.
We get nothing back.
Yeah.
We got to go to bed.
So my evening is destroyed.
Yeah.
Exactly.
I couldn't go to bed.
I'm like, I want to know.
I got to hear from her.
Yeah.
The young beautiful girl.
I have to know what she's doing.
So around 1230 or so, we finally.
No.
You got to hold her.
Yeah.
I got to hold her.
I hear a lot of noise and laughing.
And I hear guys.
Yeah.
Of course.
What did you expect?
Yeah.
So I said.
Are they going to sleep?
Yeah.
They're going to sleep over to us.
Guy sleeping over.
Mom.
They're ugly.
You know.
That's just friends.
That's a good one.
Don't worry about it.
They're just friends.
Because these days, they have boys and girlfriends.
That's back.
So I'm like, it's not like in our days.
If you had a boy, it was always something going on.
Sexual attention.
These days.
No.
Anyway.
So.
But then she threw a whole bunch of attitude.
Yeah.
It was, you know.
Really unpleasant.
Yeah.
And so then I'm.
You're stalking me.
So then I'm that now I'm getting worried.
I'm like, I want to know what's going on.
So this is one o'clock.
Yeah.
And I said until now, she always tells the truth.
And he said, you said to me, well, this time I'm going.
I'm going to check.
Yeah.
So I jumped in the car.
Talking.
Yeah.
I drove like 25 minutes to the place.
And you know, and they were all sitting on the porch.
I think I'm completely nothing quite neighborhood.
You know.
And I'm hiding behind a tree.
Right.
Looking.
And you know.
I can't believe it.
And then I like stick my head around the corner.
And then there's.
No, the big automatic light goes on like.
And then I'm like, what the fuck am I doing?
Yeah.
Whatever.
Oh, poor girl.
I was worried though.
I'm worried.
So.
And I have to be calm.
Well, sometimes you need to know.
Yeah.
And by the time I got back, we were both too tired.
Actually, the whole evening was ruined.
Kind of.
Yeah.
The vibe was kind of out.
Please don't tell Christina.
No.
Nobody.
Gee.
Shh.
Don't.
I was ashamed.
I'm not ashamed.
No.
You could daddy.
This is what I said when you came home.
I said you're good daddy.
It would have been bad if I'd like stormed up there and said,
where my daughter.
Yeah.
Who's touching my daughter?
Oh, nobody.
All right.
Let's get out of here.
Yeah.
We got stuff to do.
You guys are going shopping.
I've got to do the BG blast with Christina.
We're recording that today.
Yeah.
I want to finish my video show.
So maybe you'll do that way.
You guys are out.
Well, I'm going to go out together because she wants some
clothes I think.
And for her party.
Which is not the week Sunday.
It's her birthday.
She has a big party.
Man, that's going to be a pain.
Yeah.
You know, this is going to be like 50 kids.
They're all going to be sneak and drink in.
I'm going to have to be sure.
Like a fucking police.
I'm not giving them the alcohol.
No, of course not.
But again, think back.
Yeah.
No.
I never drank.
I mean, either.
I mean, a beer too.
No.
But, you know, how about your peers?
They drank.
They did stuff.
No, in my days.
No.
It was not like, no, it was not like that.
I think the smoking was a big thing.
Do you have a cigarette?
I remember that, too.
Yeah.
Sneak and smoke.
Okay.
Well, this was a good catch-up with you.
Yeah.
Would you drop by the house more often?
You're kind of fun.
Let me, yeah.
Let me play a song.
New lyrics, though.
Please feel free to sing.
We were so happy until my PC died.
Got disconnected.
I just sat down and cried.
To search for you.
Believe me, I tried.
I wanted you to be my digital bride.
I loved you.
I loved too.
I was true, I'm not a lifesaver, I weigh 202
I like sleeping with animals and calling for sex lines too
I was gonna tell you when I got to meet you
You took girl, you took girl, you took girl
I love you so, I love you so, yeah
It's kind of like, I heard I liked it
I was all right
It's the Gorski's, they're from Australia
They have a whole bunch of stuff on the bottom of the music network
Would you go to Australia with me please?
No, why not?
I don't feel like it
One day, you may be haunted
You're almost there
You should
I got a lot of friends there
We can stay all over the place
Yeah, absolutely
I know you only go for the five star hotel
We have invites, we can meet you
I'm afraid, we're like it
One hour?
It sounds good
It's beautiful
It really is
We should go
It's a sort of American England
It's a complete mix between
It has the British Properness
It has the Dutch Fuzzella Hight
Cozyness
And it has the American Commercialism
Is that a country from me or what?
Yeah, it sounds very attractive
And the shaders are really hot-looking
Okay
Yeah
Oh look at that
Nice guys, I heard
Very nice looking guy
Very good surfer boy
Oh
Please, I'll stand back for the enthusiasm
Yes
All right
Okay
Now we're done
All right
Thank you, hon
Are you welcome?
I was loving when you come on the show
What?
I love when you come any time
But when you come on the show, it's the best
God
Oh
You will get comments
Yeah, no, God is going to punish me
Yes
For impure thoughts
Yeah
All right
Do you get dinner?
Love you baby
Love you too
Superpot show podcast
Stick it in your ear
Get this podcast
And we're great ones like it
On the high performance podcast
Delivery network from Podjo
And line-white networks
I love it