Hey, it's Adam Curry.
Hey, how are you doing?
I'm great.
How's everybody doing?
Uh, so what's up?
Well, I'm just sitting here counting the money.
We asked for it in small bills.
$20, $50 increments.
And $15,000.
Selling up my pool at the Curry Castle.
Yeah.
And on the eighth day, God did create Marconi.
And Marconi did go forth upon the land and did give a radio unto humankind.
And God did look down from the heavens and smile for radio brought forth much joy and
grieving jams unto creation.
But the evil one, yay, even the man himself, did go forth and take control of radio, and
did make it unto his own image, which was not pleasant to look upon.
God wept for humankind did become a generation of mindless drones.
But they no longer did hear sounds which were pleasing unto the years.
For corporate radio to exude an extremely foul and loads some stench.
Therefore, God did send forth a Messiah, yay, even a golden-haired one named the pod father.
To once again bring forth sounds pleasing unto the years and to bring down the man.
And there was great rejoicing again upon the land for the pod father to give us back control
to the people.
And it was good.
And God did say, fuck corporate radio.
This shit rocketh.
Thank you and now to Tallah day you are listening to the daily so-as-code episode
before 7-1.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my years, I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I know I know my name is hard to say.
It's always this drive that fumble every day.
So what's the best sounds that brought them down the way?
But I'm the country, can't totally be yay.
Now that the name does me justice, it never feels the same.
Forget what I'm going by and follow with.
You can use my real name, just call me all the while I'm home but go away.
I know I know my name is hard to say.
It's always this drive that fumble every day.
So I know my name is hard to say.
Now that fumble every day, it never feels the same.
Forget what I'm going by and follow with.
You can use my real name, just call me all the while I'm home but go away.
All the while I'm home but go away.
My father's making this while I'm in his father's name.
I know my name is hard to say.
It's always this drive that fumble every day.
Now that fumble every day, it never feels the same.
Oh, there's a lot of stars left.
Yeah.
Why did that?
Thank you.
Got an email from, what is it?
Cody Newman, who plays guitar.
I don't know if he sings, and I think he might sing on the track.
And he said, would you give my, would you give my shit a listen?
And I have something really nice about it was kind of raw kind of,
I don't know, it felt good.
I've got another track up there called a riddle in and good stories in the songs as well.
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
It's the daily source code coming to you from the Curry Cottage and the affluent
Suburb of Suri known as Gilford in the UK Apologies about Friday.
I know I didn't, I didn't get a show out.
It was incredibly busy.
I told you that we had all the folks coming in from San Francisco.
Some even coming in from Ontario, California after the podcast expo.
And today it's going to be a crazy week.
We had the digital music awards happening this Tuesday, which is for television broadcast
on Channel 4 in the UK.
But we're going to be there starting today.
We're set up today.
And then tomorrow we have VIP sweet with lots of beautiful people running around.
Which whoever anyone who's a celebrity is basically going to be heard
into our area.
And hopefully they will get quite an experience.
We're going to be streaming all of this live, which is a new experience for
pod show, although not new for a lot of people who've worked at pod show.
But it's going to be very interesting.
And I think we're going to turn the stream on tomorrow afternoon UK time,
which will probably be what is that two in the morning Pacific Coast time.
So yeah, somewhere in the early morning hours as we're,
we continue to hold unditions here in the UK as well.
So it's going to be a fun, fun ride.
And I'm basically trying to squeak out a show here today before I head off for
set up at the, well, it's at the roundhouse.
So it's kind of nuts.
But I think that there will be some interesting stuff to look at.
Keep your eye on BTpodshow.com.
You know, with all these, these crazy days, you know,
there's, there's nothing really quite as important as keeping your mental health
together and your physical health.
And of course, the health of your ass.
And tonight.
Here to save my ass once again.
Amy.
How you doing girl?
Adam, it's Amy Mac.
Hey, baby, how are you?
I'm so glad you felt last week's exercise.
I was starting to worry.
You didn't have any ass muscles to save.
Oh, please.
Today is day nine and you're going to need your wireless.
Okay, hold on a second.
All right.
Ready?
Yep.
Lay down your stomach to the floor.
Don't make to the floor.
Hands to your side.
Hands to the sides.
The shoulder with a part and toes perpendicular to the floor.
Perfectly go to the floor.
Now lift your shoulders off the floor and squeeze your shoulder blades together.
Bring your arms to the ceiling and then toward each other a little bit
to help hold those shoulder blades together.
Oh, that's horrible.
Keep your head in line with your spine so you don't strain your neck.
Oh, Amy.
Now, of course, you squeeze your butt.
Great.
Now hold.
Make sure your feet stay on the ground.
Oh, on the ground.
Okay.
I'm squeezing.
Yeah.
That's what I thought.
And relax.
I feel vulnerable like this.
Round two.
Up and squeeze.
Now you probably noticed that we're working the back muscles too.
But I figured a little bonus would hurt.
Thank you.
Last few seconds.
Squeeze that part.
And down.
Great.
Last one.
One more.
Shoulders up.
Okay.
Squeeze the butt.
Breathe.
All right.
Your homework is to do a couple more of these some time this week.
Yeah.
Well, and of course, let's do a little fitness attack podcast at fitness.potshow.com.
All right.
Okay.
Come down.
Thank you.
Have a great weekend.
I'm spending mine in sunny southern California.
I'll be meeting with podshow towel relations.
And I can't decide if I should have a taco or not shows a taco bar.
What do you think?
Well, anyway.
Until next time.
Thank you so much.
As a result.
Correct.
Yeah.
Of course, Amy sent that to me for Friday.
And I didn't get to it.
So that's what she was talking about.
The Taco Bell meetings at the podcast.
Expo.
Amy, thank you so much.
Yes.
I did feel my lower back.
But that was kind of weird.
I did feel quite vulnerable in that position.
New video show dropped.
That was over the weekend or maybe it was on Friday as well.
The high fee show.
You've got to see this.
This is a video show, which is produced by Kevin App's who did day.
I think it was an award-winning documentary.
Was it straight out a hundred point?
It was at the I think it did well.
It's Sundance.
And the high fee movement is this actually.
I can give you the definition of high fee.
Let me see.
It's a high fee dot poncho dot com.
Since, say, oh, this since say a moment brought to you by the high fee show.
And you spell that hotel Yankee Papa hotel Yankee.
High fee.
High fee show.
High fee dot poncho dot com.
And I know on their site.
I'm going to go to it right now.
They have a definition of what high fee is.
And this will give you a little idea about the show.
High fee.
A grassroots hip hop movement that originated in the San Francisco Bay area that breaks down
the social barriers by promoting sporadic partying.
Wild loose dancing.
Also known as going dumb.
Gaudy and outlanders fashion outspokenness,
witty and farsical slang,
and spastic and positively vived acting out all while remaining free of corporate influence.
High fee.
Damn, high fee.
What is this?
This is one of these days.
I'm telling you.
Someone called me, I guess.
Of course, moody.
Always calling.
Never giving you a fricking second to do anything.
So you've got to see this.
Malica is the host of the show.
As I said Kevinette,
App's produces and directs it.
I think Malica might have been on MTV.
I have some kind of feeling she did that.
But this to me is very reminiscent in a different way,
but kind of the same excitement that we had when Dr. Dre and Ed Lover started doing
Yo MTV rap.
It was something really new, really different.
And this is just, it's just high fee.
Yeah, I'm pity love from local radio and the daddy cast.
Just wanted to let you know on the daddy cast episode 50 that are released last week.
The topic was missing children.
And basically went into a story about a friend who a friend of a friend who had
misplaced their childhood a theme park and they found him after about half an hour.
But when it ended some research on some sites found out,
a list of things parents should do if they ever think their child is missing.
And as a parent, I'm sure you can understand,
especially when Christina was younger.
If you, if they were out of your site for a while,
you really start to get concerned and your mind can get into a mindset of just pure panic,
pretty quickly.
Ah, of course, as teenagers, you kind of expect them to get lost sometimes.
But anyway, one of the things that came out of it was the idea of
creating a packet of information, recent pictures, a description, a list of people
to contact in case your child would go missing.
And I don't know, I guess it's kind of, you know, as a pilot,
you probably understand preparation is a big thing.
So just wanted to encourage your listeners to do something like that to create a packet
or prepare something in case their child would be missing or something
would happen to them or you would just need it.
I always better to have it and not need it than to need it, not have it.
So you never know what your mind's going to be like when a child is missing
or there's an emergency of that nature.
So just wanted to pass that along.
You can listen to the Daddycast episode 50.
If you want to hear the full list of things they, they say to do in the first 24 hours,
but because this is kind of a PSA.
Anyway, thanks a lot Adam.
And scrunch your folder.
I guess now I'm a converted folder.
I've never thought about toilet paper and wiping my butts and much
than I have in the last few months.
Thank you very little.
Talk to you later. Bye-bye.
Proud to have influenced you, my friend.
Yeah, it's kind of a morbid thought, but I thought it was a good topic just to throw out
there because it's true.
Crap, man.
Christina was a she had a nice adventure.
Maybe she waited to talk with Patricia about this on the show, of course.
She had quite an adventure Friday night.
She went to London to go visit someone with Liam and the last train back
was canceled and then she found out how difficult it really is
as a teenager, which did not throw lost at all.
We were in constant contact with her, but this was not our idea of a perfect Friday night
to have her in London trying to grab a cab to drive her back, which
believe me, London cabs, they look at, you know, I'm sure they looked at her
and looked at Liam and said, no, you kids won't be able to pay for.
They've been through that too many times and a long story.
Anyway, yeah, keep an eye on your kids.
Pretty interesting how people are using the voice mill feedback
number as like a voice mill number for me.
And there's all kinds of things.
Invitations to speak at conferences, people trying to figure out
if I'm available for other opportunities.
And then there's this, which was really kind of freaky.
Hi Adam, one of your listeners, and I went to second life because of you,
and my name and second life is Jill Piamma,
who's a T-I-A-M-A.
And I've sent you some messages because as it turns out,
I met someone in second life that knows you from childhood,
and really needs to reach you.
So I like you to email me and I will get your contact information to them
and say it's kind of like a sad message, but I don't want to leave it on here.
Oh, wait a minute, man.
So someone from my childhood is trying to reach me
that doesn't really peek my interest that much because when I think of childhood,
I'm thinking like, who the hell could that be?
And then to hear that it's kind of a sad story,
doesn't give me a good feeling.
You know, typically this turns out to be someone who needs me to help them with something
that I really don't want to do.
This has happened many times before, and what I don't like is,
you know, how come this person look?
It's very easy to get a message to me.
And this message has come in through every single avenue except my email,
and every single avenue except directly to me from this so-called childhood friend,
because it's come through our sales department,
and I've just ignored it.
You know, because it's always like, well, there's a childhood friend.
You know, who is the childhood friend?
Tell me who it is, and then maybe I'll respond.
I'm not just going to jump out and say, oh sure.
Not a problem.
Have them call me.
And preferably have them call me because this is great content.
Hi, this is Barry J. and Jess from Radio QRM.
Hey there.
Well, the leaves are changing up here in New Hampshire, and right now the roads are just clogged
without a state tours.
They drive hundreds of miles just to stare at leaves falling off trees.
We like to call this the leaf peeper season.
Jess, look over there.
11 o'clock by the boulder.
Got him.
When we're not hunting peepers,
Jess and I do a weekly podcast from the Menadlock region in New Hampshire.
Jess, peeper, two o'clock.
That'll look good on the mantle.
This show is a little home spun humor, five o'clock, Jess.
That one won't be bothering us anymore.
A little news.
Jess, over there by the scarecrows.
That was a trick you on.
And a little fun with life in New Hampshire.
Jess, PA plates on the Hummer.
I see it, hold on.
Oh, yeah.
And we also featured great music from the Podsafe Music Network.
So check us out at radioqrm.com or visit our podshow site at radioqrm.potshow.com.
Oh, is that a charter bus from New York City?
Barry J.
Hand me my halitzer.
We're going to be sitting from New Hampshire.
This is radioqrm.
By the way, no leaf peepers were actually harmed during the production of this promo.
If this promo upsets you, grow a thicker skin.
This podcast is rated in PC for not politically correct.
Oh, and folder.
Folder.
Rally?
I think that's Barry J.
It's not Barry from the cast blaster form.
He's an admin on castblaster.com.
And it actually came.
I realized that this morning as I got another email from someone saying,
I'm interested in getting started in podcasting.
You know, what should I use?
And it's been so long ago that I keep forgetting that
your cast blaster was created specifically for this.
And a cast blaster Mike poured a whole lot of it continues to pour just tons of energy
and love into the product.
And it's damn skipy.
I'd have to say.
I use it every single day.
And it may not be the way you want to produce your audio in general,
because a lot of people like piecing bits together and making, you know,
basically doing that all at post editing, putting stuff into place.
I like the idea of old school.
Just turn on the microphone.
You got your shit loaded up.
You just started the beginning and you ended the end.
And cast blasters fantastic for that really good for organizing all your stuff.
Hello. I don't miss Matthew and Newton not so affluent.
Yeah.
I just got a bit of a tinfoil at my moment for you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. Well, you're not okay.
Ten-four.
I know, it's time for the tinfoil hat moment, okay, man. I hope it doesn't disappoint. You got the jing.
I'm making the the the problem at the garage in many house.
Okay, he's talking about our new house where there's a common interest against converting the garage.
It's something to do, link spooky, maybe I know Medieval, the header, link.
Or something to spooky on those lines. Also, what it was, where's Malcolm in Abu Dhabi from there, didn't throw up.
Anyway, take care and love a show. Bye.
I'm trying to sneeze. Excuse me.
I don't think so. It turns out I think all the homes there have a covenant on converting the garage.
And I'd apparently was put in place so that people would park their cars in the garage and not on the side. Why do you know this question, right?
Why do we drive on a parkway and park on the driveway?
But where is Malcolm in Abu Dhabi? I sometimes I'll just send me a little email thing. I'll just jot something off, which I'd always like.
But indeed, we have not heard from Malcolm, his his low enchanting tomber from Abu Dhabi.
Perhaps he shall he'll be motivated soon to weigh in again.
Podcast Expo was held over the weekend, Friday and Saturday, I believe.
Portable Media Expo was the official title. And of course, Pod Show had how to show in there.
As you know, we don't really believe in conferences per se. And we'd like to get people together when they are together and have a good time and participate as we feel fit.
And it was a lot, I mean, if you just look around, if you go on to, what is it?
It's a lot of fun to shoot. There's so many different places you can find information about what happened at the Portable Media Expo.
Not a lot of web blogs, actually, because of course, this is a very different type of medium.
So I'm still looking for like keynotes and stuff happen, which is kind of funny isn't it that it's this portable media podcasting expo.
And there's very little of the event itself. I would have really enjoyed to have heard the keynotes, at least.
Of course, I've read transcripts of the keynotes.
So we had a pretty big bunch of people out there. Of course, we also have a bunch of people out here in London, so it's very busy.
And luckily some feedback did come in.
Hey Adam, this is Mike.
And this is Michelle.
From the Michael Michelle show.
And I've got to make a culpa.
Yes, you do.
Yeah, I do.
Because this weekend, in particular, at the Portable Media Expo, what became really, really obvious to me was how good a job Pod Show is doing taking care of its stars.
I love Pod Show.
And Michelle, just signed with Whisper Pearls for Pod Show.
I'd like to show rules.
Yeah.
Adam rules especially.
Pod Show really rules.
And I just wanted to say, I'm impressed.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, I am.
What's impressive about Pod Show?
Like I said, I think they're making the right moves.
You know, they're supportive of the stars.
And I like the interface on the website.
And I like what happened this weekend.
And I like the little things that aren't terribly expensive necessarily by themselves.
But the show that you're thinking about your stars and that you care like the limo.
And then actually shuddling people around for a couple of days.
It's a classy move.
Like the limo.
We had a Hummer, a stretch Hummer limo.
Which according to Mark Yoshimot, an MCO snowed a little bit of puke.
Because of course, who else is is renting a Hummer limo, but someone is going to get trashed and puke in it.
And we had Andrew, who we affectionately call crayon, his nickname.
It was completely dressed out as a huggie bear, a 70s-type pin, who was shuddling people around.
That was because we had our hospitality, sweet at the Sheraton as we were not allowed to have that at the Marriott.
That was a agreement, I guess, the Marriott and the Borkwood brothers had.
So yeah, so we had to shuddle people back and forth.
It was an interesting vehicle.
That's for sure.
Absolutely.
There you go.
All right.
And that's pretty much what I wanted to say.
And thank you for taking good care of Michelle, Adam.
I love you, Adam.
Peace.
Bye.
Yeah, you got to listen to whispered pearls.
Without a doubt, one of the sexy shows I've heard.
Very, very sexy.
And Michelle, of course, was nice enough to send me a naked picture of her sister, which is almost better than a naked picture of yourself in my book.
Uh, let's see.
Oh, I did see some interesting video of the rumor girls in the pool.
That was kind of hot.
And Angie B was there, too, of course.
Hey, Adam.
It's Angie B.
And that just got back from the Pod Show on Expo 2 this weekend.
And boy, you really missed out on a good time.
Pod Show put on a great party.
You totally missed out.
It was so great to meet all the people that I've been talking to all these months.
Like the rumor girls and CC Chapman and Julian Smith and Marcus Couch.
And met some other folks, too.
Brother Love was really cool.
And had a long conversation with Joe Klein.
Yeah.
Well, they just organized ear off about the old days while we were sitting around.
Cool side doing the wonderful Pod Show rewind live show.
So fun to be a part of that.
So, um, I don't know.
We all missed your man.
Hopefully, uh, you can find in your heart to go next time.
You missed out on your own party, dude.
It was fun.
Oh, well, dude.
It's not like I didn't want to go.
It's like, uh, a man has his obligations.
You know, we had all this stuff set up with with BT with the DMA.
I'm sorry.
And before that, of course, I really would have been tough to travel because my paperwork
was not in order.
Which it now is luckily.
I'm free to cross the border whenever I want for whatever reason I want.
Uh, so of course, I would have loved to have been there.
And she's especially because you were there, baby.
Uh-huh.
Um, by the way, I want to thank Jason Calacanus for that intro to the show today.
Um, he was a, there was a Gilmore gang.
And this is actually, um, and before for me, it was very interesting to listen to this
particular episode of the Gilmore gang, which I think the first two, it's a, you know, it's a multi-hour
conversation broken up into three or four parts.
And I said, listen to the first two parts.
And it was all about pod shows, uh, announcement of our most recent, uh, financing, which is
a series B, uh, it's a term for, uh, different type of stock.
Uh, and the amount is 15 million dollars.
And when I was listening to that conversation with some very intelligent guys, and I, and
I put Jason Calacanus right up there with very intelligent guys, it was quite amazing
for me to, uh, once again, you know, have to witness that when, when there's a topic that
you really know something about and you know all the ins and outs of, of, of the discussion,
here that people usually really don't know what they're talking about.
And these, these guys are analysts, but they're, I'd have to say they're more technology
analysts than they are media analysts and that, and that's kind of where they're making
some, some positions and, uh, just pure mistakes and thought.
And I actually considered today, um, doing one of those.
Let's listen to the whole show and comment on each piece.
Excuse me.
Uh, but I just don't have the time for it, but I, but I, I think I would like to do that,
because it's so funny, some of the things they're saying.
The funniest has to be that, uh,
Podshow is raised this money to, uh,
uh, what is it to, uh,
roll up a whole bunch of other companies?
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's, that's a good theory.
We saw Dave Winner posted and removed, uh, two theories.
One was Podshow needs the 15 million to battle lawsuits from Apple.
Theory number two.
A Podshow needs the 15 million dollars to, for rebranding to evade lawsuits from Apple.
That's too bad he removed the post because it was so stupid.
I'm going to have been great to have had that out there.
Uh, no, it's, uh, because we're enabling people to do what they love.
That's what it is.
We may not be a company that, uh, that goes around boasting about our numbers,
both in subscribers, listeners, and advertising dollars,
but clearly something's going the right way.
I think that's all I really need to say for now.
Uh, and if we want to get into a real conversation about it,
listen to that Gilmour gang and then get back to me.
Preferably in, uh, in audio format because, because that's fun.
So, uh, I'm just, uh, just, uh, ring with a question for you.
Thinking about how, um, when I first started listening to the DSC,
he was really excited about, so I'd rather love and his music and how you'd sign them to be on label.
Well, it's been a little while now, and there's, uh, Kevin Reeves and a number of other bands.
How would you say the, the selection of top quality songs that I'd want to public using now,
compared to when it was just by the love is kind of the one and only of the best,
the best, um, just the question for you if I might want to answer on the DSC.
Yeah. Take care then. Bye.
Okay. So, um, I don't like the question of, you know,
what is the top or what is the best because that's all subjective.
You know, I made like one thing that you hate and vice versa.
And I don't really think it's about number of spins for an artist that says it's better.
It's just maybe popular with a certain group that is playing it.
You know, I don't look at it that way.
However, I like the fact that you're asking how the, uh,
pot-sick music network is doing. Well, it's doing quite well.
Uh, and we're still in the process of integrating pot-shoot plus and the pot-sick music network.
You're going to see some changes, uh, that are coming along quite quickly.
Now, finally, as we're learning how to, uh, create better admin tools for our producers and hosts and managers and admins,
um, what's very exciting is we did it a little tally and we ran some numbers.
Because, of course, the pot-sick music network is in effect of very simple yet necessary.
And I think in a way revolutionary concept, although it's not really inventing anything new,
it's the concept of a very simple license that enables creative work to be used for one specific use.
So we're creative commons is fantastic because it really enables all different types of uses under certain circumstances.
This is the very specific license as it pertains to using someone's song in an audio production.
And a part of that deal is that the person who uses the song reports that back.
So we have a, um, I think on the pot-sick music network, uh, about,
is this a 13 or 18% of the shows that, uh, use and report to the network, um,
have a relationship with pod show, so we know a lot about their numbers.
Statistically, that's a very good sample size.
Uh, when you do all the numbers, it turns out that since it's inception, there have been,
I think it's 215 million spins of pod-sick music songs.
So, and, and a spin would be, I saw I played a song, uh, the top of the show.
And every single person who heard that, I'm going to say, is a spin.
Uh, you could say impression, but it doesn't sound so cool.
So that's how, that's how many different pieces of work have been impressed upon people.
And, you know, when people are listening to a show, they're listening to the show,
so they heard the song, they may have skipped over it.
That's entirely possible, but they were exposed to it.
And I think that is just phenomenal. I love it to bits.
We still need to, uh, finish off with, uh, with the, and that will go, as I've said before,
that will come with the integration of pod show plus and the pod team music network.
We got to get all the songs, uh, and there's going to be a couple things we'll be able to enable the song for sale,
which the artist has complete control over.
We don't have to. We've also got a couple of other ways for you to license it for movies, film,
television, and other non-podcast related uses, which is also an opt-in.
You can check box, one song, all your songs, the individual tracks,
and a couple other opportunities that it's just coming at us.
You know, and all we're doing is just plug it in, given the artist, the, the capability,
to, um, to market their stuff and to monetize on it.
Not a lot of direct monetization for pod show in that, but man,
does it really enable us to make cool shows with awesome music?
I'd have to say definitely.
Thanks for the question.
Got a note from my sister Willow in Italy.
And she lets me know that she started an audiobook cast, an audiobook and episodes,
or a potty of book, of my mom's, at our mom's 1993 novel,
written according to the guidelines of the UK, uh,
Trashy novels.
It's called The Time to Love.
And she's just uploaded the first, uh, episode.
So it's, it's rough.
She says big time amateur hour, but something I wanted to do.
So she, you know, she is actually, she's fulfilling one of my mom's wishes,
which is publishing her book, a time to love.podshow.com.
I, uh, I have not listened to it yet.
I wasn't quite ready, uh, but I've got it loaded up, and so when I go,
when I take the train into the city today, I'm going to listen to the first episode,
a time to love.podshow.com.
Very cool.
Hey, Adam, it's Matt from the Dayton show, and oh, yes, it's a long time.
So I've left the message, and I just wanted to do, uh,
introduce some news and regards to all things butterflies.
A couple of weeks ago, my wife ran in her first triathlon that benefited
breast cancer research.
And as we were leaving, standing, hoping you're tracing,
we were swarmed with butterflies flying all over the place.
And I thought, well, it's not interesting, but, you know,
they could live here there, so I didn't really think much of it.
And then the other day, when I'm in the office up on 31st floor,
I look up the window, and there's a butterfly covering outside the window,
caught in an updraft.
And I thought, all right, that's a little stranger.
And then I said, if you're today waiting to board a flight for the portable media
expo, I look out and see a butterfly flying directly over my plane,
and I thought, okay, now I'm convinced Adam's mother must be looking
over me and over this flight.
So thought that might brighten up your day, and just when we let you know
that I was thinking about that, so take care.
I really appreciate that thought, man.
Thank you for calling you.
And it's not, I don't really, obviously, you know,
my mom's spirit has not taken over this butterfly specifically for you,
but I think it does show that we're in the universe.
We're all connected.
We're all part of the same infrastructure.
It's the same atoms bashing up against each other,
organized into shapes and forms and mass, et cetera,
but we're all connected one way or the other kind of like,
you know, hurricane.
It's not a thing.
It's it's wind that comes together,
it's and wind all over the planet is a part of that.
Literally on the other side of the globe,
while there's a hurricane taking place,
there is a connectedness between between those two,
and I think that's what we're seeing.
And something about this crazy ass network that we've been building this
internet thing, something about it is,
it's meant to be for that reason, you know,
some of that connectedness is I think is going to come out of it,
and we may be 50 years before we finally figure out what we can really do
with an interconnected network like this,
but it is something that's happening and it's,
that is it's very basic form where I talk about the butterflies,
and then that connectedness.
It probably has always been there,
it's just now you happen to see it.
Matt, thank you very much.
Hey, Adam, it's the other Carmen from the cheese pod.
I'm whispering because DJG is sleeping.
It's about midnight here in the states.
We've got to be up at five,
and that's just to let you know how damn special you are today,
that I would call you at midnight.
And the reason I'm calling you is because I was just at a restaurant,
and in front of my ass mouth,
I had done a new iPod lately,
and he meant podcasts,
and that's not good.
So I thought you should know,
there are some people out there who think podcasts are iPods.
I'll pick this ass for you, man.
I don't do that.
I appreciate it, but not necessary.
Yeah.
Some thought about that.
So this is part of that whole Apple trademark issue
that's been discussed at Nazium.
And I, you know, it's probably true.
It probably is true that when people think of pod today,
and today's day and age,
they are mainly thinking about the iPod,
and when they hear podcasts,
if they haven't heard of what a podcast is,
or think in something with your iPod,
I have to agree that that is just fundamentally a fact.
Is it a huge portion of the population?
I really don't know.
Do I think most people don't have iPods,
and don't know about podcasting?
Yeah.
So yeah, there's something to it.
But there's, you know,
why do we have, you know,
Leo Report,
I only read the transcript as I said.
I'd love to see the,
I love to see video of possible of his keynote.
He talked about this,
and he suggested net casting.
I think that's just as bad.
The whole idea of what we're doing,
it doesn't have to be grouped under one common denominator.
It really doesn't.
Instead of focusing on people recognizing the name,
what pod show has been doing particularly.
And by the way, you know,
there you go,
we chose a pod, a pod name, pod show.
That may have some disadvantages,
but instead of going around promoting
our brand and pod casting,
we really try to get the content in front of the audience.
That's the trick, you know,
and that's a different type of, of message.
So instead of saying,
you know,
there's this, this new kind type of broadcasting,
and it's really cool.
I think it's much better to say,
hey, look at this,
or hey, listen to this.
That I think is,
is much more powerful.
And that's really what,
what we've been focusing on.
It's trying to get the great stuff that we believe in,
at least,
in front of audience.
And that comes in many different forms.
It's not just on the web.
It's,
it will eventually be on mobile,
so that there's some stuff to figure.
I think Nokia's doing a pretty good job.
I know comics are bloggers going to hate me for saying it,
but I have to say that pod casting application on their phones.
Ain't too shabby.
But what we're doing in British telecom,
you know,
BT vision.
This is going to be the new television box.
And what did they just announced something today?
Oh, they did a deal with,
I think,
Birdlesman BMG.
So you'll be able to watch videos on demand on BT vision.
So that won't,
I don't think it's going to be for pay.
I'm not sure.
It may be,
but I would think that you can just pull them up on demand,
which would be pretty cool.
And that's,
that what a great deal that is.
You know,
that's pointing content in front of audience.
And giving them a way to get more and find it easily.
That part, of course,
makes a hell of a lot of sense.
So,
did have an interesting experience over the weekend,
Saturday,
morning,
Patricia woke me up.
She says,
I'm downstairs,
just enjoying a cup of tea with the,
with the F.T.
I'm like,
F.T.
I usually use she reads the independent
and the daily mirror,
and I read the financial time.
She says,
no, the Frank truth.
So, oh,
even the Frank truth podcast,
she said,
yeah.
Because I'd set up her iTunes.
So, it would automatically,
you know,
subscribe to the Frank truth.
So, did you listen to items?
No?
Because, of course, she had forgotten it,
or it wasn't paying attention when I showed her.
So, I went to Pod Show,
and I went to find it,
and I put in Frank Sinatra,
or I think maybe she put in Frank Sinatra
or Frank truth,
and it came up with the Frank truth podcast.
So, I clicked play and it worked.
And she said,
no, by the way,
that high fee show looks pretty good.
So, we're talking about it.
Well, that's what came up when I went to podshow.com,
and some kind of promo for high fee show.
Like,
God, this is cool.
Now,
work when the lady Patricia,
who will not listen to my own show,
the show that she's on,
is doing that.
Something very cool is happening.
Oh,
oh,
God,
these were prints,
don't you?
But maybe,
I need some bread.
So,
give her a life,
to the rest of the world.
All we've got is Jesse's.
Yeah, yeah, it's Jesse's.
Yo,
what's up,
Adam and Jersey Todd,
the official music artist of the Chacha.
So, hey,
I figured there's a lot of folk out at the west coast
at the PPM here,
or whatever it's called.
And,
you know,
I'm going out there this year,
maybe next year.
But I got somebody from Jersey,
of course.
In fact, she's a real Jersey girl.
Her name is Jersey Jung.
I played her on my show a couple of months ago,
and she finally uploaded a song to the pot,
pot saved music network,
and I like it a lot.
The song is called How It Ends.
And I love her voice.
I love her texture to her song.
I love the passion behind her voice.
She's got a four song EP out.
She's playing little clubs.
This is the kind of person that podcasting was made for.
Because you're going to hear this song,
you're going to love it,
and a lot of other people are going to love it too,
and play it on their shows,
and get into a whole mess of new years.
So, on the daily source code,
this is Jersey Jung with How It Ends.
Have a great time, everybody.
I give you all that time,
that I can.
So you're going to love how it got,
little man.
If I were a nicer girl,
would you stay?
Oh, no,
I'm going to start in another battle,
anyway.
So, I should have freedom to handle.
Know how it's going to end.
When you're going to give me a hug,
when you care.
You're going to have freedom to handle.
Know how it's going to end.
When you're going to give me a hug,
when you care.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Help!
I'm sayin' someone else to make you alright, where'd youachen?
God's mine should I breathe to hell and I don't, no how it's gonna hell.
And if you're gonna give me love where you can,
if you're gonna soon I breathe to hell and I don't, no, no how it's gonna,
Oh, and you're gonna give me a hug when you can
Cause I'm wasting these days
I'm wasting with them
I'm wasting my time
Yeah, I'm saving your name
I can't turn away
Cause you stay in my head
My mind
You want me to tell you
Know how it's gonna help
Oh, and you're gonna give me a hug when you can
Yeah, I should've put it together
Oh, no, how it's gonna help
Oh, and you're gonna give me a hug when you can't watch that
Yeah, I should've put it together
Oh, no, how it's gonna help
Oh, and you're gonna give me a hug when you can't help
Oh, and you're gonna give me a hug
Yeah, you're gonna give me a hug when you can't watch
Yeah, Jersey Jones
Indeed, from the Float Sigma music network
Hey Todd, you're done hearth that she's phenomenally cute
Excellent, show notes, of course, so we're linked to that song on the P
So we're linked to that song on the P. M. N. In the show notes of DailySourceCode.com.
Is your computer a hacker magnet?
It won't be anymore because Earth Link is here to save the day.
With Donald's faster than speeding bullet and firewall, it is more powerful than a locomotive.
It has an anti-virus system that cleanses your PC with the click of a mouse.
It's a bird!
It's a plane!
It's Earth Link!
Perfect internet from outer space.
Link to Earth with powers and abilities far greater than those of normal high speed.
And price is so low that it will blow you out of this world.
So make the right decision and turn to Earth Link as your internet provider.
I've been Hawking that B.G. Blasho that Christina,
Martina and Schmeer doing. I got some awesome news.
Their sponsor just extended after only I think two episodes. The sponsor extended and said
we're going to do a year and a half for this. I think 16 or 18 months that they're going to do.
That's fantastic. Again, Potio Proud to show the young generation the value of capitalists.
If I can't flex, I can't flex.
All right, everybody, out of PotioShow.com, dailysourceco.com for your show notes.
Beyond the lookout at B.T. Potio.com for some interesting stuff happening.
Starting this afternoon, UK time and starting tomorrow afternoon as well.
We will turn it off at some point, I guess. All the way through the digital music awards.
Beyond the lookout for some interesting stars, some pretty cool people, and hopefully just some fun.
And just let's call it raw fun. Take care, everybody. Bye-bye.