This podcast is brought to you by Potcho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charley, 427.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic, isn't that great?
Ever since Genesis through the fall of ancient Rome.
History repeats itself as we reap what we have so far.
From the slaughter of the Indians and Hitler's Holocaust.
Dinosaurs to world wars and lies forever lost.
Some may call that evolution or comic retribution.
Yet we still create more new enemies.
When there's a peaceful resolution on the break of revolution.
Sing now, forever hold your peace.
Everybody, everywhere.
People left off the war.
Everybody, say your prayer.
Media magicians, we've their webs of deceit.
While greedy politicians watch us marching in the street.
Sacrificing boy on soldiers making evil men get a rich.
Because there's money in those war machines now.
Everybody, everywhere.
People left off the war.
Everybody, say your prayer.
We've got a copy in the government.
People left off the war.
Everybody, and everywhere.
Ey, a, man, brother's insist.
Good morning everybody coming to you from sunny northern California from the Curri condo
It's the daily source code episode number. We had now 427. You know, I'm so sick of this warship
You know, I work hard all day. I come home. I turn on the television
You know, there's no more entertainment on television. It's all warship and an Anderson Cooper in war
I'm so tired of this. Oh my goodness
What is going on just this morning? I woke up flipped on the TV war again
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, I don't know about you. I'm sick of it. I just it's just can't we stop this shit
What is going on? No, but as you heard in the song
It's been happening forever. They never will actually end but think about what's actually happening to your kids
You know, I found this on the pod save music network and this is just a small sample of
What your kids are hearing all day long because you can't avoid it. It's everywhere
You're drowning in war in war
And destroy the peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace
The peace of a troubled world is it men women and children praying praying for victory
Better end
The luck in the world community in the world
Consequence unity and residence the women in a troubled world face war air attack aggressive dictators actions
Conflicts danger
Plumatic negotiate a military
I think it's weird your kids my back to the strange
Listen to this
Who did this this is Kevin Brett find on the pod save music now work it doesn't stop this goes on like 10 minutes to listen to a couple of
Last destruction weapons of mass destruction by helicopter destroy and destroy the peace peace peace peace peace
Landrice peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace
The peace of a trouble will result in military confidining of oil fire
Biological chemical weapons friendly killed friend hypercola fierce resistance and strategic resistance to your weather. Oh, you get the point
die
It's just when you get up
Uh, sorry about that when you get up early every morning and
You do a show and it's just you know, you I don't know my brain works pretty well in the morning and I'm just like
so tired of hearing about this
Okay, so let's try and be positive today good news looks like the weather broke
Remember yesterday I was telling you about the convection fog because it was rolling in over the hills
Of course, I'm right kind of in the middle between the them hills over there yonder and the bay and so you get the warm air and the cool air coming together
You get a whole bunch of fog that was the first clue that was going to start chilling out just a little bit
Yesterday when I walked home where last night I should say around
Actually we were there quite late about eight thirty or something like that before we left
It was me
Mark Steven and Bridget and
It was it was chilly it was actually like oh, this is so nice
I still didn't have to put my jacket on but it was it was really it was
Quite enjoyable San Francisco
Although you think California it's always really it is nice it usually is just nice and sunny here
But it's cool, you know, it's between 70 and 75 degrees it's pretty much a year round sometimes a little bit chillier
And most homes aren't equipped for for really warm weather and we've been having
High in the 90s
Right outside of San Francisco in the valley. It's been triple digits. It's been extremely warm
You know, there's nothing really to this global warming though. Do you think you know
Nothing has anything to do with it. I mean it couldn't possibly be now cut it
Hey
In the 80s I would have done anything to show you my magic garden
Put now what wait a minute to show me what
You let me just roll that back to show me you're magic. What
What I would have done anything to show you my magic garden
I don't know what you said you're magic anything but I still am interested in seeing it now
You can hear all about it in our podcast the outer order show. It's a really fun show where we talk about everything and nothing all at once
We have a roving correspondent Bernard St. Moritz, and he's coming you weekly from a tropical locale
The shows are blessed and we really hope you tune in. Yeah, you can subscribe to us and iTunes or visit us over at
Show.com
So come visit us soon. If you know what I mean
Make an old man happy will you show me that magic thing
Speaking of being old and and last you know, it was funny last night Brigid who works at pod show HQ
She works with the marketing Steven
I think she's about 10 years younger than I am and and and she's a it was a huge a grand grand fan
And so she was asking me questions and of course I have stories about just I mean almost every single 80s
Artists even some 90s artists you can think of and I was like, okay, just give me another name and I'll tell you a story
So new segment here on the daily source code
Tell me about your favorite 80s or 90s band if I had sex with him or if I did anything else
It was interesting. I'll tell you the story because I do have a lot of stories and before I get too old and can't remember
That shit anymore. Maybe be nice to just to lay it down, you know, and and get it out there have a recorded history of of my life. It would be nice
I started
the Troy needs an iPod
Go daddy contest on the daily source code last week and I and I realized I made a slight mistake
So the whole idea was Troy needs an iPod.com
This is Troy who's been trying to race funds to get an iPod and then someone else came in with
Something like I think was I need an iPod more than Troy dot com and I said well
Well, here's a great idea for your go daddy contest now it only costs $6.95 to enter and it's not an official contest
There are no rules and I determine the ultimate winner
Avoid wherever he would buy a law yada yada yada
I said why don't you register a cool domain name and the most original and I think it's not just the domain name
But perhaps the domain that it points to that's something else to consider
We'll win a video iPod
And so what happened is people are emailing this to me. I've tremendous email problems
Which I'll tell you about in a second so I'm not getting all entries. So what I suggest is
Everyone who also because I have received about 10 entries so everyone who's received an entry instead of emailing it
Everyone who is sent in instead instead of emailing it to me
Go to daily source code dot com and then place a comment there
Underneath today's episode so that we have a nice, you know running list of
Of all of the all of the entries. That's awesome pretty funny ones and of course if you
Register the domain at godaddy dot com and use the checkout code dsc3
You'll get that domain name for $6.95
So and and I am for real about the video iPod and I have no idea how long we're gonna keep the the promotion running
At least until the end of this week and maybe next week so go ahead and and do something
So the it's start off with Troy needs an iPod dot com Troy. You're still eligible by the way you could come up with a new one so come up with an awesome
Domain name again. I think extra points for which
Website of which domain you're pointing it to and just leave that as a comment under today's episode at daily source code dot com
Hi, Adam. It's Brian from audioattitude dot com and
This is about this big contest about getting an iPod if you come up with a clever
Domain name right? I
Figure it out could be as good as Troy with my experience at picking domain names being so successful at that you remember
Progress to cast in fact I think some folks over at that what is it raspberry dot com you know the show without the vowls or the site without the vowls
I think they got that idea for me, you know procrasticast raspberry without vowls
Anyway, so I went on over to go daddy and spent some time this weekend
picking out some names and I started out with iPod for pod show dot com
Kind of bland and plus it's pod show plus right so iPod for a pod show plus dot com was my next purchase
But then I that well, so what does that have to do with anything and then I then I got iPod show plus
Just simply that at that's boring. It doesn't say anything about needing an iPod
So then I put I need iPod for pod show dot com and I thought well
Okay, I'm this sucks really
I bought four domain names and and it all sucks
And I thought well it sucks that's that reminds me of of your blog on July 8 from DSC 417
When you were helping some of us who pod cast with our our feed sucking number
And you help this through that and and after that I I sort of in my typical sarcastic way
Asked if there was a way for pod show to come clean my house
Since it was so good at sucking feeds it could suck some dirt out of my house whatever and you said well
You know what if you get a thousand listeners to your show on pod show
You'll come clean my house yourself
I thought okay
That's that's great why not and
So I just want to tell you that I've already got five listeners on pod show and
And actually that's that's going to take about 16 years at that rate and I don't know if you're going to really have the time
In 16 years to come clean my house and I'm not sure I want to wait that long
And so I just wanted to give you this option that if I win the iPod
You know the the deals off and you don't have to worry about coming to clean my house in 16 years
So I thought that'd be really cool and
So I got this domain name at go daddy
I went an iPod and Adam doesn't suck dot com in other words
I win the iPod you don't have to come over here and and suck up all the dirt right
Cool I went an iPod and Adam doesn't suck dot com I thought about I went an iPod and Adam doesn't suck dot or a G because I like or Gs
But it's so giving you know, but I thought well, it's too difficult to remember for people and those
Orgies are are difficult to to think about sometimes
So I decided to stick with this I went an iPod and Adam doesn't suck dot com
What do you think about that well either way Adam?
I'm I'm going to start cleaning so
Thanks for the consideration
I went an iPod and Adam doesn't suck dot com
Emma right on
All right definitely good entry going posted over at the daily source code dot com
Yeah, I love to orgies myself or Gs a good a mind wants asked for a role of toilet paper
I had some extra so I gladly gave
And then much to my surprise the fellow looked me in the eyes and asked me should I fold it
Or scrunch it in a ball and I promptly and most certainly said
If you scrunch it or fold it I don't really want to know it what works for you is not for me to know
A fellow needs some air when dealing down there so let me leave you be in your commode
If you fold it or scrunch it I have a sinking hunch that it would do the bloody job well either way
For I know it's not my place. I'd never rub it in his face all the private details of my toiletry
But at least I'm glad to think we don't do it in the sink in short that may well lead to anarchy
So scrunch it or fold it
Everybody knows that it will do the bloody job well either way
So don't spend your honest wage on some fancy old the day
You know where it will end so use it well my friend
Scrunch and fold it anyway. You please
There's no reason for playing that other than I just wanted to play it one more time yesterday posted a picture on
I'm Craig dot com with my set up here in the condo the new bakers rack with the flat screen
It has everyone's it's all the rage now all the cool kids have the bakers rack for their studios
And a lot of and this whole thread start this whole conversation about standing or sitting and of course
When you need to talk about standing or sitting
Chacha listeners immediately go into well I stand, but I don't scrunch why I stand and I like sitting and full
I just
Whatever you do
Okay, we can stop the whole folder scruncher thing. I just I don't mind is when you send in an audio comment
Just end up with folder or scruncher and then we'll know that you're really a fan of the show
Hey Adam it's Gabrielle from second life. I just wanted to pass the word on to the DSC listeners
That we're going to have an opportunity for them to get together with other listeners and podcasters and
Podsay's music artists this Saturday in second life at the podshow palace mid summer masquerade
We're starting it at 2 p.m
Second life time which is also the same as the specific time and we plan on going as long as we can
Cover everybody in all the time zones. It's going to be a formal event and so I have everyone dressed up in their
Ball gowns and their
Tuxes and put on the masks and come and dance the night away to the pod Saint's music
So I hope to see you there and I hope to see many other DSC listeners come on in and join us for our fun
Right, okay Gabrielle. Thanks. Yeah, I'll drop by. I haven't talked about second life much lately
I've been so incredibly busy and
After mom passed you know, I just I really didn't feel like it
But I have you know, I drop in from time to time and the podshow island is definitely still cranking lots of
Interesting people living there now and of course we've got parties. I think just about every single day
So thank you very much Gabrielle for
For setting that up and let me know and letting the Charlie listeners know what's going on
um
I'm totally
Totally hammered by spam once again. This is this is really gotten out of control
My adamant curry dot com is pretty much rendered useless
I checked um I get about five
Spam messages per second now coming in I'm under some incredible attack and
The way I have my my email set up and it's um
You know this actually I think this actually qualify
I think it definitely qualifies the tin foil hat most
So the way I have it set up as I've got I've got this
Service from a company called I think what is it run box and
What run box does is it allows me to it's kind of what Google is offering now, but it allows you to manage
Your entire domain email because you know Patricia at curry dot com has to work and Christina at curry dot com and there's my sister's wheelo and Tiffany
And so there's a lot of management there and
I haven't set up so that all email that comes to me there is then forward it out to my Gmail account. That's pretty simple
The problem is
After I think 5,000 messages within a certain period within I don't like a three hour period
Then a run box shuts down and says wait a minute. This can't be right, you know either you're spamming or someone else is spamming and they're right
Actually because what happens is all that crap that spam
And it does filter out quite a bit
But certainly not everything you know is then just being sent on to my Gmail so I don't know
I'm just gonna kind of leave it so what happens is is
It'll it actually do receive the message, but it it goes into the run box email box and
And it's so I have to go in there to check it and I think if you send me a message and it and the
You know, it's in that period of I'm not gonna send anything through to atoms Gmail account
Then it does kick back some kind of message about a quota exceeded whatever
I'm just hoping that that'll stop the spammer. You know, they'll eventually catch on to the fact that you know
This is a dead email address or it's not it's certainly not selling anything for them
I just don't know what to do at this point. I mean the only other thing I could think of is to find yet
Another host who can do my my the email from my domain and who has even tighter spam
Controls and restrictions, but in the meantime if you really need to reach me
Send it to Adam at podshow.com and we'll see if we can see if we can keep that email
Address reasonably clean
Just for normal fucking communications. It's so disappointing that email has come to us
Yeah
Thank you very much. Just me. I got them right three small things first one shuttle falls
Right this is Daddy Dows by the way who's living this so voicemail comment. I'm not easily spooked
The only thing that I really couldn't watch on me on was to film the grudge
I'm gonna bit freaked out by that one switch it off
But I was listening a shuttle falls first episode the other night on me on in the house, but one on clock no more
And for myself actually I'm a switch it off
I couldn't listen very much. I was a has on the background next time and I'm absolutely fantastic
Yeah, I bet you that's true for a lot of people but I should try and listen to it together
It was like the second mix I believe that we heard and it is that enthralling you do kind of get drawn into it
And I can totally imagine if you're all by yourself and
Particularly if you have earbuds in because then you close off all ambient noise
I can I can see where you might get a bit freaked out spot on really enjoy that
The next thing was the blog you're running from Carl Alon thing. I'm guessing
That he's referenced to Alan instead of Adam is to block who does a radio talk show program in an orthting
Well, okay, this is the guy who were called in the other day and he and he said Alan and then corrected himself
Of course, it's either the other a Freudian slip right called Alan Robson
You can tell me if I'm wrong, but I think that's where it came from
What I'm wondering is how many people and in the UK are actually
Making a migration over from talk radio or to listen to podcasts like yours where that you know
There's a lot of talk a lot of chatbook more interactive
Just be interested to hear if that was the case we have more not put that you know
So of course in the in the UK
There's a quite a culture of listening to the radio a listening to people talking on the radio or listening to the
Wireless as we say
I think the BBC's doing a great job of letting people know what podcasts are and although at this point
For the BBC a podcast pretty much means
Show that was on the radio and you can now download and listen to on your own terms on your own time
I think the whole I at least they're getting the hey you can get
Audio and video entertainment online as well
That's good thing although I hate to think that people you know are now thinking of a podcast is a is a repeat of a show
But yeah, I think it's helping I think people are getting it the predictions are pretty pretty big for the UK
And there's a reason why we're opening up shop in in Britain
That's certainly where I've come from and the last thing is on Firefox I've got quite a few tabs on anyone time of maybe about 12
Now if you're pod show logo as nice as it is shows up for all subscriptions to any podcast with the word pod show written in and now I can't tell which
Which website I've got open with a tab so I'm just wondering if that's something that can be changed
So the actual name of the podcast shows up in the in the toolbar on Firefox where I'm an explorer
Of course instead of just the word pod show. It's getting really confused anyway. Love the show
You do yeah, of course. That makes a lot of sense. I actually had noticed that myself
I rarely look at at the toolbar. I don't know maybe I have seen it, but obviously
That's not right if you're on someone's a page it should say you know Adam's page or if you're on the daily source code
It should say daily source codes page and I'll do you one better even because of course we'll fix this
And boy, you know we have quite a list of stuff that is either being fixed or is just a pure enhancement
And what's on that list? I cannot share with our serious stars one-o-two listeners because we're about to say goodbye to them two for two Tuesday
My daughter will be on later tonight with pod save the queen so make sure you stay tuned to one-o-two
What we're gonna do is also
Whatever the
The backstage passes whatever the laminate picture is I think we could also make that the icon
To go in the tab which would maybe even though it's gonna be pretty small obviously would give you even more recognition of which tab you want to go to
Thank you very much for that
It's on list one-o-no Adam carry here is comic strip of blogger your European and union crisp on them
I would like to say that I am happy
I'm happy because last Friday
Italy has decided to open up Italy's label market
For workers from new European union countries from Eastern Europe Italy
Legally could wait till 2011
But they decided to open itself fully to new EU citizens now right now without waiting
So now free movement of people
for all EU citizens also from East
European Union is possible in UK
Ireland, Sweden, Finland, Spain, Portugal, Greece
The countries that still are
Resheristic and are blocking freedom of movement of new EU citizens are
Netherlands, Germany, France, Austria, Denmark
So I wanted to say
Multi-Catzi Amigitaliani or Pesiams Philippi in Sieme
Il Futuro Ruminoso de l'Unione europea
Gracias
Viva Italia
It is also good news for millions of Italian Americans
Because now they have proof that the country of religion is not actually stick after all
You're carry keep falling in your blackberry
Yes, I am a folder
Okay
That's comic strip blogger everybody
Thank you very much for the update. Yeah, they're just kind of weird
You know where Europe is definitely trying to become the United States of Europe
But you still can't travel freely and work in you know in another state and you were born in and
Is it really 2012 as I would say 2010 2012 when they legally have to change that man seems like
They should be moving along at a little faster clip
What was I gonna say here?
Oh, yeah, about comic strip blogger. You know from time to time
Post will pop up over at curry.com of
People who really seem to be in some kind of feud with with CSB and you know
I've I've pretty much just forgotten or ignored all this talk about how he's a stalker and how
He's always been writing horrible things about people and some people have gone to the police and
And you know CSB always wants to interview me. I'm thinking maybe we've got this the wrong way around
You know, maybe I should be interviewing comic strip blogger to find out what's really behind this
You know, it's his name really jacic and you know, why did he leave Nokia and you know
What does he make his money with is he independent and wealthy? I mean, I I kind of
You forget about a guy like this. I mean, don't you don't forget about him, but you forget about the whole history and then
It comes back and like you know this there really is something this is the whole reason why I was interested in comics
Your blogger in the first place is because he seems to have this very
murky
You know
Past not just past but but very cloudy is to where he lives what he does
And comister blogger could we turn it around could I interview you? But I mean really where you answer all the questions
I think it's about time that
listeners of the daily source code
Really find out who the who the true comic strip blogger is
Tell let me know if that's okay
some people reporting
some slow down in in accessing
some shows
Sometimes the daily source code sometimes other shows on the on the podcast delivery network
I think I figured it out because they really can only be one answer and it's this thing called packet shaping
Packet shaping is I guess you could say it's made well someone say it's part of the net neutrality to debate and I I totally disagree
But ISPs are getting so overloaded now with all this incoming traffic if we if we should if we really can believe the
That YouTube is serving up 100 million video views a day
Then that's going to be swamping someone somewhere and I think what's going on here is that
You know at certain peak times ISPs are just trying to throttle everything back to make it
You know make it at least accessible to everyone else which of course means we may still be quite a ways off from this all-time
Connected everything comes in flying fast streaming whatever you want
Which is I guess still very good then that we understand how we can
Time delay things and have things automatically download to your drive or to your to your iPod or whatever wherever you want something to go
But it definitely to me shows that the supply
I really the demand if you will the demand for bandwidth is just to far outwaying the actual supply and I think it's going to we're gonna see some interesting moves
So then I truly believe this is being done
This packet shaping this kind of you know trying to to manage all this incoming bandwidth
It's just because they just don't have the bandwidth anymore
They just don't have the networks to support it and everyone's in the middle of you know of some form of of upgrade
And that's about the only thing I can see because and because I am also seeing this now happen to YouTube
I've seen lots of slow downs on on Google
so
I guess right now it's
This is what net neutrality is going to be it's good for the little guy the little guys don't seem to have any issues
Hey Adam this is Jeff Hines with a Friday night dance party and I'm wondering
If you're responsible for an artificial I read in the New York Times today
basically it said that Amazon dot com is starting
to sell groceries online
And actually the number one
seller for last week was since sale
So I'm wondering if you had anything with that so let me know and I'd be dead
here's my five well
Of course I had something to do with that. You kidding me
I mean, I don't I don't have a link up anymore. I used to have a since sale link up at Amazon actually and I would sell
Sometimes five six since sale machines a day and it just got so tedious never cash the checks anyway
Because you get I get the checks in England and you know it's almost impossible to cash an American check
For any size almost outside of the United States or to deposit a check it's very complicated
So and I kind of gave up on it. Yeah, I definitely know that I sold a lot
I mean the whole toy here for me is whenever you whenever you hear a burp
I want you to think senseo whenever you think senseo. I want you to think of daily source code
Senseo
So now whenever you look at Amazon I want you to think of senseo
I want you to think of burping. I want you to think of the daily source code all this has ever been
It's just one big promotion for this show. Okay
Let's take it on a happy note since we start off with the warmongering
It's natives of the new dawn whenever you wake up in the morning
Just remember crap. I woke up and you should be very happy
Because every day you get is a good day my friends
Let's let make today a good day
Wake up as time derives in shine just another day in this life for mine
I take up a deep rep my lungs still took a past he's got to be a good day
Wow, because there has to be stretch out my arms I tail out my worries
Retubernated no end of the possibilities
These are mine. It feels my blood never so becomes cold as I swing from the fire
I'm on some with time. I finally feel fine days as it should be of my own design
There's no one long like me to when I'll rest sleep and dream mine
Decating with them's are all that I need and I introduce a bad day and I hunt truth to be
Because you can't have a good day unless you believe every day good and bad will be around
So let's focus on listening to the park and it sounds a little bit
I'm going to talk about the bad day
Oh my friend, all the facts that we are here
That day next to day I got a good day
Well, but I'm not gonna lie
No one talks about the bad day
Oh my friend, all the facts that we are here
That day next to day I got a good day
Let's get late. The sun finds a whole rise in home, shadows stretch out
A risk-air flies in, flickering in the room, pulling the conversation,
Cones sets in, the moment of meditation, the old days playing back in my mind
The older people in their faces in this moment of time, summer
Wearing smiles on the spot, the wind and misery
Some find tomorrow while others become history
Now we're the wiping in the mighty floor for all the artists
The moon of the stars, all the solar lights are darkness
Could we be dumb as sitting in the convenience hard
As I learn about respect between the close and the pharmacy I
When the farmer in the season of the harvesters learn the soul of seeds
It I leave where the heart is now everything
Loving down the poopy around so that the focus on this and the other five
And it's down all the other way
No one talks about the bad day
Oh my friend, all the facts that we are here
That day next to day I got a good day
That day I got a good day
That really gets me going
All right, my friend, thank you very much for listening
Check me out at dailysourcecode.com
Other great podcasts at podshow.com
I'll be back tomorrow for the hump day edition of the Charlie
Take everybody
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
Yet this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from
podshow and line-white networks
I love it