Hello everyone, this is Karen, you joy-rise queen, wanting to wish you all a very relaxed Christmas.
Stay tuned with joy-rise.btpotchow.com.
Hello, is this thing on?
You're saying you're coming, you're loud and clear.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Well, Adam, I've been looking at your list and well.
Based on the drug trafficking laws on several countries,
I'm not going to be able to get you most of what you've asked for,
but how about we just get you a nice pretty sweater and some extra hair spray
and maybe a cowbell for the condo.
Anyway, Adam, have a happy holidays and, oh, oh, oh, enjoy yourself
on the DSC 517.
Oh, it's $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Do the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky ingredients in it.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Fantastic kiss, Adam Curry.
Do you remember that it's down my Christmas tree?
Don't remember anything for waiting for my phone to ring.
Wake up, better freezing.
Drink it doesn't kill my fate.
You're a strange feeling at my window.
Must be Christmas time again.
Just don't know if I know.
No more chance for me.
I love this Christmas never came.
Every year's the same.
Oh, it was nice.
I got a thing.
I got a thing I got a thing.
fake Sunday night byaran.
Nukeя兰 Perf cooker battlefield.
A night deep dead by quits the setting.
Depending on what Christmas party you look at the other way.
I wish I was never born
See another glistless thing
Just for the moment
No world shines for me
I wish I was never gay
Every ever you say
For the sake of therapy
I've got to be by myself again
I've got to be
I've got to be by myself
With my skin
I've got to be
I've got to be by myself
With my...
I've got to be
I've got to be a lover
No one on Christmas day
Wake up in a freezing
Take it up and kill my pain
Tell me if it had my window
My secret must time again
See you at the Christmas party
But he asked over the year
I wish I was never born
See another glistless thing
Just for the moment
No one on Christmas day
I wish I was never gay
Every ever you say
For the sake of therapy
I've got to be by myself
With my...
I've got to be
I've got to be by myself
With my skin
I've got to be
I've got to be by myself
With my...
I've got to be
No...
No one on Christmas day
I've got to be
I know I can't live with you
American Heartbreak
On bass, Michael Bloodler, of the Rock and Roll Geek Show
The greatest Christmas song ever written
I love the lyric, you know
You show up to the Christmas party with the asshole of the year
Hey everybody, how you doing?
It's daily source code, episode number 517
Coming to you from Curry Cottage in the affluent suburb of Surrey
Known as Guilford in the old Cottage
Still, which won't last too much longer
And looking outside, have you ever heard of the London fog?
Well, we've been in it for the past 48 hours
And it's wreaking havoc on the infrastructure
Now you have to kind of visualize that Jack the Ripper
Type fog that is just kind of hanging there
And doesn't do anything, doesn't move
That's exactly what it's like outside, complete piece soup
And besides the, you know, we're on an island here, right?
And with global warming, you know that the United Kingdom is the new Caribbean
So, ferry boats have had tremendous delays
Because they literally can't see where they're going
Very hard to dock
Because the, well, let's get to the airports
Heathrow
Although they've said it's been closed
The airport hasn't actually closed
Well, first of all, there's 100,000 people in the airport
Who are laying around trying to get flights
Home to Christmas, which God, there's so many songs
That have been written about this problem
Most aircraft certainly can take off in this weather
Because once you get out, you know, then you're above the weather
And then it's nice and bright and sunshiney
And I would say that depending, well, about 40% of the time
40% to 60% of the time according to the terminal area
4 casts and the, and other reports
40% to 60% of the aircraft can land
The problem is that you've got all kinds of delays
Because you can't taxi that fast
You can't see what the heck is going on
On the runway
So they have to space the planes much further apart
I believe there's some de-icing going on
So it's a mess
Complete mess with flights being canceled
Absolutely
And my in-laws are supposed to leave on Saturday
And I gotta tell you, the way the situation is today
And of course there's zero wind
And there's like half a knot of wind
So this fall, if there was wind, the fog could be blown away
I have a feeling we'll have the in-laws for Christmas
Ah, yes
It's interesting that there's an airport called Manson Airport
Which is on the south eastern tip
What's kind of the mid, the mid eastern tip of the United Kingdom
And it's, we call it the crash, like the crash field
In the second world war
As a huge runway
I mean it's astronomical this runway
And these days they can actually fill it up with foam
And that's where a large aircraft would go
If they had an undercarriage problem
Or had to make some kind of force landing
It's a great spot to do that
In World War Two
It was built literally for the guys who were coming home
And you know, engine shot off, wheel shot off
And shit to be able to kind of slide into safety
And it saved a lot of lives
But what they did to invert the fog
Was they lit up fires all around the airfield
And it worked
And I'm wondering, you know, can't we do something like that with Heathrow
Because I'm sure it would work, you know, you start heating that up
And the fog will start to lift a little bit
Anyway, until further notice, it's a real, real mess
Let's see, so much to talk about today on the source code
I've got to get ready
And you know what that means, it's Thursday
Yeah, it is time once again
It's my girl, Amy Mac
Hey, Amy, how you doing?
Amy? Amy?
Hello
Well, Adam, it's day 20
Yes, Matt
I feel so much like Christmas being back in the land where season's changed
Oh, you don't like San Francisco
Yesterday I drove from Indiana down to Tennessee
And since I drive a motorcycle in the city
This was like the first time I'd driven in
I don't know, six months
Let me tell you, I love the roof
Reverse, I'm being able to listen to DSC
And everyone else is podcast and pot safe music
I forgot how much I missed that
I didn't know she wrote a bike, man, that's kind of hot, Amy
Anyway, just because I'm all Holly Jolly for Christmas
Doesn't mean I'm not gonna kick your butt
Yes, I need it
So get ready
Okay, I'm sad, what are we doing here?
Turn on the other mic
We've done squats before
And we've done kicks before
Now, today is our grand finale
What are we doing?
I don't know how to use sound effects
Boy, oh, don't do that
We will combine them
Okay, I'm ready
Follow me
Move the other mic
Start with your feet, shoulder with a part
Okay, shoulder with a part
Okay, straight forward
Yes, they are
Arms clasped in front of you
Clasped in front of me
Now squat down
And then you squat back up
Your left leg out to the side
And then as you squat back down
Bring your leg back in
Now, oh, then the other side
Okay, so kick right leg out as you come up
And bring back in as you squat down
Okay
Seven more, each side
Ready, go
Okay, one
Squat
Kick
Your weight
Squat
Quick
Kick
Yes
Wait on your heels
Oh, none of my toes
Make sure your knees don't come over your toes
Breathe
What number are you on?
Six
And
Squat
Faster, faster
Oh, I love what you say that
I know, that's a favorite
Yes
Seven
All right, great to have
You've done an excellent job in the last 20 weeks
To make that as firm and spectacular
I need to feel
Oh yeah, that's good
Yeah, have a wonderful holiday
Everybody
I'm off to cut down a Christmas tree
Yeah, so until next time
Go kill some nature Amy
Amy sent a lot and I still email along with AstraZeneca
Number 20, which of course is now a pod cast
And she also has the fitness attack
Also available on Espanyol
Gotta cut
What?
Did you do your exercise?
I did my exercise, yeah?
Okay, good
I just want to say I'm going to go Christmas
Go talking to the microphone
I'm going to go Christmas shopping
Yeah
Do you think the DB9 will fit into your bag?
Oh, absolutely
Fast and Martin
Austin, what does what you want?
The Aston Martin DB9, yes, that kind of fit into your bag
No
I don't think so
I'm leaving in the garage
No, it's a ride of wood
I won't fit in the garage
Okay, you going with your parents?
Yeah, I'm going to entertain them a little bit
Yeah
Okay
I was just saying that if the fog keeps up
They may be celebrating Christmas with us
It doesn't
I don't know
Are you already exhausted?
Not okay
It's fine
My parents have a lot of energy
Yes, they do
That's why I got it from
Yeah, it's like triple trouble here
Okay, baby
I'm enjoying
All right, I love you
Bye
Ah, yes, the sound proof studio door
Shushing closed
Ah
Anyway, so Amy said that she's going to continue
Doing the exercise in the new year
Which I'm very happy about
Because I don't mind keeping it up
You know, it's paying off
Amy
Day three now
I'm not being able to send SMS to text messages
Here in the UK
It's with the new E61
The Nokia E61
Which I love so much
And yes, they finally got an engineer on the phone from Singier
Because you know, you go through the customer support
And they run down the list
And you know, you're like, I'm almost bored
Because I've done everything already
I know about the message center numbers
I know all this stuff
I really do
Ah
And so I got a phone call
Yesterday
And I was like, oh, you sound like an engineer
And guys, how did you know?
I was like, you sound like one
I said, oh, my wife would disagree
And I was like, you know what you're talking about
And I said, my wife would disagree
So at a fun time
And we check some stuff out
And I believe that it is a problem between
Team Oble in the UK and Singular
So that's going to take a little bit of
Sorting out to figure out what's going on there
But lots of people been trying to help me out
It really is much appreciated
I've just got a listening to the DSU-515
And a culture problem with the E-61
I had the same problem
Haven't seen me last summer when I was a
Fisting Czech Republic in kindergarten
Back in Holland
Had the same problem
Somehow somewhere
Something changed in the
Installing it
The configuration
Most likely
Somewhere DDB inside the menu
There will be the settings
We said to send text messages as we email
You should change that
So good luck with it
Over
Of course
Folder
Yeah, that was a new one to me
I did check that
I didn't know it's sent to send us text messages
Not as emails
What's interesting is
I'd like to try
Roming on a different network
Now here's what's kind of fun
I bought this Nokia at the Nokia store here in the UK
And the manual
Specifies that there's a place in the settings
Where you can change
Manually changed the cellular operator you want to use
Well, that menu option is not existent
On my version of the phone
I have the latest version of the software
I've updated all of that
I've been through these things a million times
With a million different gadgets
So I kind of know what to look for
But
I have two menu options on that particular menu
Which does not include manually setting your cellular operator
And the instruction book that says here it is
Here's where the third menu item is
And it's not
So it's very very frustrating
Not to be able to send text messages
Because you know
That's how I communicate with my peeps
I completely need it
I think I played these a promo
By these guys on somewhere around the 400
On the daily source code
I think I think I have an advertising agency
But they're still around and that's pretty cool
Hi, this is Matt and this is done
And we're the host of Piotini
The show about the people who make you want the stuff you want
How they do it
In other words, Piotini is a show about advertising marketing and branding
This week we celebrate six months of show
And if you haven't been listening to Piotini
Here's some of what you've missed
Listen, okay, by the year 2010
Traditional TV advertising will be 66% less effective
As it was in 1990
I can't imagine there's a CMO out there
It gives a rat's ass about CMC
Of course there's a thing
You know at the end of the day
Which has a means of fitting
Add messages inside a urinal
The demographic of fat Americans
One sin of life time
Come man, as is moldy
Clean around the idea
One second radio ads
It's beyond August
So I'm going to show the person Matt and Don
I have to say I've honestly never thought of a congregation as being a target audience
And all my life of all my career in marketing
That has never crossed my mind until I saw Christ
The question you've got to ask yourself
What can my product, my service, my way of communicating
My product, my service, whatever it may be
How can this make the consumer's life?
More simple
Well put
Don't forget to tune in each Monday for a brand new potting
And for it again, there's a few people we'd like to think in the podcast and world
P.K.J. for technical advice
Adam Curry for being the pot father
Chris Penn and Chris Brogan for podcast and Boston and of course our listeners
Thanks for listening
We look forward to another six months of shows
So there's a lot of talk now about more troops being sent to Iraq
And the situation of course interests me as a
Member of the world community as a citizen of the United States as
And it habitant of the United Kingdom as someone who's been to Iraq and during more time
And we'll read this to you on March 15th, 2006
Members from both parties in Congress supported the creation of the bipartisan Iraq study group to review
The situation on the ground and proposed strategies for the way forward
For more than eight months the study group met with military officers
General experts, academics, journalists and high-level government officials from America and abroad
Participants included George W. Bush and members of his cabinet
Bill Clinton, Jalal Talabani, Nuri Kamal Amaliki, General John Abizai, George K.C.
Anthony Zini, Colin Powell, Thomas Friedman, George Packer and many others
As a official edition contains the group's findings and proposals for improving security
Strengthening the new government rebuilding the economy and infrastructure
And maintaining stability in the region is a highly anticipated and essential
Step forward for Iraq, America and the world
So I picked this up, I know I talked about it on Monday, Tuesday
Yeah, Tuesday, talked about having read this on the plane ride back
And I took away a number of things from it and I really do encourage you to pick it up and have a read
Because you'll see what a complicated situation it is in Iraq
The main problem is that there are religious factions
So you have the Sunis and the Shias
And without getting all the way into who was in power first and who's what and who believes in what
Let's just say it there's within Iraq there are, you know, maybe you could almost say
It's red state blue state except it's about religion
Which makes it a little bit more complicated
So when you want to build up the security forces in a country, which is exactly what I saw happening
I saw the ICDC, the Iraqi Civil Defense Initiative, I saw them being trained
Excuse me, I think the ICDC is in front of my door right now
I asked trash guys back and up in the fog
I saw that actually taking place and that's what the focus was
In particular the Iraqi forces in the form of the military and the police
And the military is that is the ICDC that I speak of
The problem is you can teach someone to fight and you can teach someone to maintain order civil order as a police force would do
But if they have idealistic differences or deeply embedded, you know
And grain differences in their belief system in their beliefs and that there sometimes can actually be a hatred of the other type of belief
That's going to be a problem because, you know, it's like, well, hold on
Who's protecting who and who's enforcing what and who's right
So it's almost a non-starter and I think that there was a huge lack of knowledge about that going in
And even the training of the forces, I'll be real honest with you
I saw barracks, I saw troops, I saw order, I saw guys following orders
I saw people able to handle weapons
But have you ever seen dad's army?
Have you?
It looked very much like dad's army with the the common dawn would call for a
And about face and half the guys would turn the wrong way
I mean, I literally saw this, we have an video tape somewhere when we were over there
So it was like, okay, these guys are trained, but, you know, it's like real basic training
It's not like the marines all of a sudden
And again, you don't know, you know, there could be two guys next to each other in the same
Battalion and hate each other
Or not agree with the views or not agree with the mission at hand
So that's very, very difficult
And crap, trying to get into a serious story here, got the damn garbage guys
That's actually the recycling guys
So if you read through this, the starter report, there's a lot of talk about that
And it seems apparent to me that there was a big mistake that was made
Sometimes in the whole scope of the world
It's better to have the dictator you know in power than to have no dictator
Because I think that's basically what made it work
I'm not saying Saddam Hussein was a good guy
But I'm saying that a lot of worship appears to have happened after he was taken out of power
And, you know, the real answer should have been that there should have been a very swift replacement of a very strong leading figure
And, you know, there really isn't one
Because, yeah, there's one for the Sunnis, there's one for the Shias
You've got Al-Sadar, you've got the Kurds with 100,000 man army or security forces up north
I mean, it's a claustrophuck, it's a huge, huge, huge problem
And, you know, there's a lot of call in this report for political change
Which essentially means, yeah, you've got to have a leader
You can't have a country pool together without some form of leader
And of course, they've had a couple of leaders who were assassinated
So someone, you know, and I think the U.S. probably has the choice
And this is not exactly what the study group says
The U.S. has the choice of essentially empowering if we want to get out
Right, if we want to leave this situation
We've got to support one of these guys and they're going to be a dictator
It probably won't be a democratic process
But that it seems to be the only way that the only solution for maintaining some form of peace
Someone's got to have the upper hand
And it certainly is not the American or the, quote, coalition forces
Because there's just not enough, you know, and the report clearly states that
Yeah, you know, the forces go in and what does it clear and hold
I think is the tactic, so, you know, clear all insurgents
By the way, are killing their own people, you know, yeah, the killing servicemen in the process
But it's really targeted it, you know, it's the Sunis versus the Shias
That's what's going on, it's the jets and the sharks
It's the same, the history's always like that
And so the minute they clear something out, you know, behind them, shit starts filling in
So it's like, you know, it's like bringing water to the sea
It's just an almost impossible task, except what this report suggests is, you know,
Up the number of troops significantly, and they mean like bringing 50,000 more troops
That should apparently be enough to maintain the clear and hold strategy
At the same time, you know, get a democratically elected leader to be a real leader
I'm telling you, this is tough, and I got to say, I think, you know, the neighbouring countries
Have got to step in and do something here, that would be pretty much the only solution I see
And if it wasn't for the oil in the ground, then I will say that
If it wasn't that this was the world's second largest oil reserve
What would have pulled out of there in a heartbeat
But you know, there's just way too much at stake there
Those of you listening in on serious satellite stars 102, I appreciate the time
We've got another three and a half hours to go on the bird for this evening
So you enjoy that, if you want to hear more of the show, just head on over to dailysourcecode.com
And download it like the rest of us
So yeah, so, you know, I encourage you to go out and buy this report
It's actually it's expensive, it was like 10 bucks or something, 1095
And a portion of the proceeds from the purchase of this book will be donated to the National Military Family Association
Which supports families of all ranks and services including those of the developed deployed developed
Deployed, wounded, and fallen
So at this point, I really don't, I don't think the strategy that has laid out in this book is feasible at all
I think there is a severe lack of knowledge of what is really going on between these two factions in the country
And in the south, there's all kinds of, you know, there's like 13 different provinces
And this stuff, it's very, it's tribal, you know, these shakes, these shakes
You know, it's like tribes and their families and they're related
And it's all intertwined and it's very complicated
To kind of traverse that type of system coming from, you know, a whole different culture
I just don't know if it's possible
So I, I do think that sending more troops in for a defined, clear and hold strategy will fail
Because there's no way I see a leader emerging
It would probably be, and this is not a very nice strategy
But it may be the only one that could, in long term, save a lot of lives
Is to select one guy
Maybe two of them who get along together different ends of the country
Have you seen a bigger rock is, is that big ass country
You know, we've got to get some guys and we've got to turn them into the interleaders
And that means supporting them, support this is what happens all the time
And this time we didn't do, it's, that's the big mistake here
It was an arrogant fucking mistake to think that you can pull a, uh, a tyrant, a dictator out of power
And then everything just falls into place and everyone is jumping up and down
That shows the true, um, ignorance
Of our United States administration and then that of the UK as well
Anyone who joined in wasn't thinking at all about what is actually going on inside the country
Remember all it was, there was talk about the courage, there was about the courage, there was about the courage
I didn't hear about Sunni's and she isn't till I actually went there
And now of course we talk about it all the time
So it's a little bit more than just the courage, there's a lot of shit going on
Read this book, seriously, read it, I think you'll enjoy it because it'll give you insight into something
Um, that we'll go down in history is one of the biggest mistakes
Not so much the invasion
Uh, but pulling Saddam's and who's saying out of power
Without a clear strategy in place as to who was going to fill that void
And if it was going to be filled by a hundred thousand American troops
Big astrategic mistake
I'd love to hear from you all you have to do is calling to the voicemail numbers
I'm going to give you the UK number first
Plus four four two oh seven six eight one three seven five three
And I got a couple calls from Charles the joint London
My message was funny early before I finish my my thing
Hi, this is Charles your joint London
I am I'm a fan of feed up and never any fan of mine
I have the question about what the hell face vanilla was
I know what to know what's an English muffin I'm English I'm not sure what an English muffin is
Is it what I would think a muffin is or I thought he called back with that biscuit
Which is to me something company anyway young source of the rich
So my wings and I think yeah, I think we got to do it now we're from our spine here
It's the yanks versus the bits
We'll drive each other crazy, but everybody knows that it's apparent to see
It's just like you and me it's the yanks and the bits
The yanks versus the bits
Mind the gap. Yeah, it's so cool that you mentioned that man
I can't I can't tell you that I can't tell you that it was so funny when we first got here
I love English muffins. I really do and I was walking around Stainsbury's looking for English muffins
Any autonomous is English muffins every American knows what those are like and of course if I just looked for muffins
I would have gotten what I wanted now
I didn't look for muffins because muffins if you want a muffin in the states is like a what do you it's almost like a cake here
It's like a cupcake. I don't know it. No, you don't talk about cupcake
Do you know cupcakes here in the UK, but anyway, muffins like a brand muffin or a you know a big ass dough bally thing
And and muffins are indeed like English muffins
Hmm
But the French vanilla thing we worked that out
I'm our more saying Adam. I want to say happy Christmas or Merry Christmas. I happy new year
Why is it you guys this is your first is the print again, sorry
Why is it you you call it holidays
You see if you're not Christian then then Merry Christmas isn't going to be offensive
Surely like saying happy fanico
Or what's it quantum the thing? I don't know American can't do it often with both quantum
They're asked a fair anything. I don't know really sure or um you know
It's someone breaking their farms is the end of Ramadan
I don't think I would be offended if they came to it. It's a happy Ramadan
I spent last week and dressed as Santa along with about under 600 other standards
Marching to London, charging and singing and getting drunk
There's a lot of fun. We said Merry Christmas to absolutely everybody
Of all fates color be creed and yellow or actual
Massive smile and a Merry Christmas to you too from everybody said it
And there are people who are even dressed in in a mother's glasses on
So and and you also you've just got to look into your Friday show
You've said Christmas about a time for coming home
So why would you call the holidays? You're going on holiday. You're not going home
I don't understand a way vacation
That's just because it's me holidays
You don't use word. Oh, anyway, bye
You know what they say children and drunk people they always speak the truth
Charles the drunk Londoner dude. I love it when you call in. Yeah, so indeed we call
What you would call a holidays here is what we call vacation
I believe in the United States this whole holiday thing and I do it as well
It's a political correctness deal
Because around the same time as Christmas you have Hanukkah
And I think maybe it was I know I became aware of Kwanza maybe 15 years ago
I'm sure Kwanza's been around for longer than that. I should look it up actually
And they all kind of fallen in the same time frame and by the way
I think the only holiday that consistently is on the 25th of you know is on a set date is Christmas
So it's just easier to say happy holidays
You know, which means happy insert your religious holiday here to you
That's kind of where it came from
But on Christmas I say Merry Christmas and yet Christmas is a place is a time for coming home for the holidays
Oh yeah, what a cluster fuck
So I played the promo for the Jesus interview that is currently running with
What's the name of it's audio
Fuck I don't remember Tom Pacifico's tell away
And by the way it wasn't scripted I found out it was completely done
You know off the cuff and I equate the the interview to
Mel Brooks 2000 year old man a very very old skit and I have to
I was pretty funny and I expected to get some response
To that show was certainly to me playing the promo with clips from it
I got one but I do want to share it with you
I don't know I it's for Nichols here
I just bought that company
And as much as I like your show I absolutely hated
With a passion the promo with regard to the guys who are just really taking the risk that
There's Jesus Christ and I am a practicing Christian and I'm afraid very serious
And I know I've heard the then put your bits and faces on my
You know my load for her all that business bits and places
But what you must understand I think is this when when you're a practicing Christian
And I think Steve actually Steve might have been mentioned before
When you're when you're doing literally in love Christ because that's what being a Christian is a bad
It's a lifestyle choice
It's literally having somebody really seriously installed your wife or your kids
Or something that you'd really daily love
I apologize for about in here for a second
I think there's insulting and I think there's making a joke and having fun
You know it's not like in this interview anyone says Jesus is is horrible
You know and by the way myself my wife my daughter have been insulted many many many many many many times
By many people who you even know
You know but you got to take it with a little bit of grain of a saw
I think there's a lot of respect I think this total respect
But you got to be able to have some fun with it once in a while
You know just fun you can have fun about anybody and everything
I don't think it was truly malicious
I think it was just the creative exercise which I basically found it interesting
And funny to hear what you know what would Jesus say if he was of these times
And how would he speak
I don't think it was meant as an insult
Of course I respect your position but still don't equate it to people insulting my family
Because they've been insulted a lot
And I don't take it that seriously
I don't accept that at all I've got to say
And as much as people think how might be an idiot calling up
Compligning you or not compiling
No no no dude you're not complaining
I appreciate it. I ask people to call in about it
You know I don't care because that's exactly how I feel
And I'd like to put a message that you guys did do it
That's fine
Just let's have a bit of equality
Next one, what did you do?
One bad mechanic
The last of that, what did you do?
One of that bulldozer
It's always the questions we get in the net
Well, because the Christians provide so much comedic value with their responses
You know, we're told that we've got sick and suffering scars
We're not in the pandemic, the idiots
You know, we're normal people
They've made a lifestyle choice
Um, we've got people ready to live
Well Paul, you know, I'll just say one thing
I don't think I recall you calling in
When the Islamic community
Worldwide was extremely pissed about a couple of cartoons
You know, so I don't and also don't think you can say it's only the Christians
If you compare it seriously
But I do have to say that Jesus Christ is definitely a much more enigmatic
I can't even find the word
Enigmatic
He's a much more, he's a better celebrity
He's just a much better looking celebrity than any of the other guys
Completely making a mockery of homosexuality
Or, you know, in a really violent way
It's just as hurt for this not more
So I think you're going to get a lot of calls about it
So that's under there we go
Thanks very much, that's my opinion
See you
Oh, and I mean what?
Yeah
Happy Christmas night
Not happy holidays, happy Christ Christmas
You're best night
Happy Christmas to you
My friend
Come on man
It wasn't wild
Did you listen to it?
It wasn't all that bad
Listen to it
I mean listen to the whole thing
And tell me you can't laugh at the irony of it
It's just funny
Anyway
I appreciate your calling
And you were literally the only collar I got
I did not get an email or anything else
Maybe after this I will
Comic strip
Hi Adam Kerry, matey
I wanted to say something
Regarding this British motherfuckers
Who criticized Potso
Oy, Dweeps
Get real
Adam Kerry is in UK
Not to suck your cocks
But just to give English spaking education to his daughter
And to be close to family of his wife
That is in fucking Netherlands
Oy, British motherfuckers
What do you think you are?
You are nobody because only USA can't
Example
George W. Bush
Listen only to three entities
Good almighty
His wife Laura
And his dog
Tony Blair
So shut the fuck up
British Dweeps
And be thankful
That Adam Kerry leaves
From time to time
In your overly text
Provinces of European Union Empire
Anyway
This breeds and young
Stick
It's bullshit
Because most US Americans
I of non British origins
Anyway
Yeah
I think I'm actually from Scotland
Come extra blogger
One of your better ones
You
Hey, this is P-Dub
And I just need to let you know about a couple of important things
First is about a contest
I'm running
Digital flats
My podcast
We'll be giving away to one lucky listener
If there is one
And electoral voice
Are E-20 microphone
Now if you're not interested in owning
A microphone
You could turn around and sell it on eBay
For around $2,300
So this is a decent price
Listen to digital plots
Number 44 to find out how to win
The second thing is a bit of a pod show business
Please tell Rosie for me
That I need a can of WD40
The satellite windows
Getting a little sticky lately
And it needs a loop
Happy holidays
To all the curries
And all the DSC listeners
Oh
Oh and I always forget to say this
I use a pressure washer
Of course you do a P-Dub
Then need some loop
I think KY just signed up as a sponsor
For a number of shows
On what I've dubbed the erotic a channel
So we'll see if we can get some loop
P-Dub
Hey, I was talking to P-Dub the other day
And so the first two weeks of January
Is going to be really really busy around here
I need to help move house
Which is the way they say it here in Britain
We're moving house
And even though it's from the east side of Guilford to the west side of Guilford
Dude, it's going to be a lot of work
So I'm just really not going to have time to do a source code every day
I need someone to fill in for duties
On serious because I do a lot of stuff every day for serious satellite as well
So the first thing I'd like to get you guys thinking about is best of charles
And preferably I'd like to make the perfect length for the satellite window
Which is P-Dub was at 24 minutes
I think we're 23, 30 or something like that
I think it's 24, 30
So it would be ideal
And I'm thinking about you know
Compilations of good
You know episodes or things that you liked
I need 10 of them
So there's a couple of ways to do it
But I think the easiest way is just to say
Send in 10
And the first 10 I get
And they shouldn't be longer than 24 minutes in 30 seconds
And we'll roll those out
You can put an intro on and an outro
Whatever you want to do
To give yourself some credit obviously
And we'll put those on the satellite
And we'll put it on the daily source code feed
And then somehow I'm going to figure out who's going to be the host of the series shows for two weeks
That'll be fun
We'll make a contest out of it
To Adam Patricia and Christina
This is Steve Webb
And I'm with the lovely lady Leon
And two of my sons Steven and Timothy
And we're wishing you and yours a very merry Christmas
Fill with love, joy, and laughter
May this Christmas be blessed
Beyond your wildest dreams
And may you find the piece that Jesus came to bring on that first Christmas mourn
Merry Christmas
Ah, thanks guys
Hey Adam it's Callie from Geek Brief TV
I just wanted to wish you a very happy Christmas
And thank you so much for a great year
I can't wait to see what next year brings
Alright Callie you too
Merry Christmas
If you're going to watch a show today
Check out the new in the attic
Which I think that just went up
It's in the attic is Rachel Fuller
Pete Townsend's girlfriend and Pete Townsend
And it's brother and the whole crew
And there with razor light
Racer fish
Racer light
On this particular episode
Doing acoustic shit in the air stream trailer
It's really good
And what I like the most about this episode
Is that it usually Rachel does
It kind of like a wide shot
So you can't really...
You see Rachel right
But it's not close up
And it's much more close up this time
You got to see Rachel man
And on the new in the attic
In the attic
I'll show you how to cry
And melt the power
Santa Claus is freaking me out
I have a million questions
Spimming around my hand
Until I get some answers
I'll refuse to give it to me
Like how can a fat man
Fim down my chimney
Carrying all those presents for you
And for you
Do you think you can wake up
To the sound of all those whores
Don't tell me most to cry
And melt the power
Santa Claus is freaking me out
I have a million questions
Spimming around my hand
Since he lives out the North Pole
I'm asking you instead
Tell me how he does it all
In just one night
Night
Night ring dear
And just one slave does not sound right
Maybe Santa travels in him
In hell
No
Festus lives
Painting why to blend in with the snow
Don't tell me most to cry
And melt the power
Santa Claus is freaking me out
I have a Christmas wish list
He's never even seen
But somehow how the stuff ends up being
He liken as mystery
It's also overwhelming for my name
I'm filming for my milk and cookie brain
If only you could understand my grief and nor my pain
So say me please from centre snail before I go insane
Oooooooh
But two fingers
Two fingers
We can be out
My validate my needs
That's not him
Cruely and cat seguro
Should raise ten fingers
Don't tell me not to cry
And not a power
Too close to him
I have a million questions, swimming around my hand and I guess the bed's so
solid if you used to go too bad on Lord Weatherby Santa Claus is freaking me out.
Hey Adam it's PD Love from Lovehouse Radio and the daddy cast, just want to say happy holidays
to you and your family and to spread the love to your listeners and hey check out the
daddy cast at thedaddycast.com to hear about my adventures trying to get those hard to get
toys for the boys and also check out Lovehouse Radio.com for some great pod save Christmas
music off the PMN. We'll take care of Adam and here's to a splendid 2007 horror should I say
splendid. Yes. Splendid indeed my friend so just want to remind you the January 12th of new movie
stomped the yard is coming out and you can find out all about it at the podcast that
do what the hell just happened there. The podcast that Tony cost us is put together
hold on or is it it's stomped the podcast.com again the movie comes out January 12th and of
course if you want a great deal on a domain name head on over to godaddy.com use checkout code
dsc3 get a great deal on a domain name it's well worth it. Take it from the pod father.
Huh quite a show longer than usual today. I'll talk to you tomorrow it'll be
fubar friday send and of course fubar friday for Christmas so you got to send in some great
songs suggestions we'll be yeah we'll be kicking it out for sure. Talk to you tomorrow everybody bye bye.
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT pod show media network
powered by pod show and limelight network control your part in the show at btpot show.com