Hey, this is John Misselli.
And this is Drew Domkis.
From the Don and Drew Show.
Check out ShadowFalls.podshow.com.
It's so spooky you might pee your pants.
Hello, bodies.
You're listening to daily source code number 444.
Magic number 4 and Lady Patricia.
Sticks, twigs, and seeds are never a good thing.
$60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm a Korean one.
I'm a rock.
I don't know how to stir up her.
Suburb of Surrey, known as Guilford, crap weather today, my friends.
Let me turn on the exterior microphone here for a second.
Oh, you can't hear it.
It's raining.
It's really pouring down today.
A perfect for a Friday.
So we've got the festivities ready to roll on the way.
Lots to talk about today.
One of the main topics that a lot of people respond to from yesterday is about NASA,
using misplacing the original footage of the moon landing amongst other things.
Now you know I'm a little bit skeptical about the actual landings that we are supposed
to have made on the moon.
And you certainly sent in your comments.
Hey Adam, it's Carlos again, I was just listening to DSC443 and you asked about NASA
losing the the original footage and the actual, yeah, the person to confirm that yeah, that
is true.
And they also have conveniently misplaced slushed out the original blueprints of the spacecraft
that allegedly flew to the moon.
Okay, bye.
Is that the ones that flew to the moon or the actual lunar module?
I had a great conversation about this with Captain Dan this morning.
Who, of course, does not subscribe to my theory.
So not only have they lost the tapes and I've read this several different reports and
you never know what you can believe, right?
I read one report that said that they had lost seven or misplaced, seven hundred boxes,
including the actual footage.
Now what I understand, the way this was done, now this is the early days of television.
And the way they actually did it is they broadcast a slow scan television signal apparently
from the moon, from the lunar module at about 10 frames per second.
That was a slow scan broadcast down to a monitor in Houston, in Mission Control.
And the television cameras were actually focused on the monitor itself.
So think about all the potential for, shall we say, monkey business that could go on
in that chain of events.
And it's just amazing to me that they've misplaced that.
Yeah, lots of people say it's, the blackberry out of the way.
Lots of people say, well, it happens with government organizations, but not with something
like this.
I still have my first episode that I was ever on television.
My own personal television moon landing.
I got that one.
I haven't lost it.
Lost lots of other stuff.
But then again, I'm not NASA, you know, and how many billions do we pay these guys?
How many billions?
Hi, Adam.
My name's Andrew Gerven.
Did you know the item-profestible fridge or something?
A crap.
That's not what I wanted to play.
I'm sorry.
This is the one I wanted you to hear.
I'm calling in about the NASA losing the footage moon landing comment that was left.
And yeah, that's totally true.
Totally true.
And there are reports out that NASA has lost the original moon landing footage.
It doesn't do them any good if they were covering something up because there's copies.
Everyone on the internet at the footage.
But, you know, whatever's happened, they lost the footage, I sent you a link in the email
that's just coming through.
So just so you have that.
My question for you is, what are your grounds for thinking that the United States government
through NASA did not land any one on the moon?
Why do you suddenly, why are you along with all those conspiracy theorists out there
that say, oh, we never land it, you know, what's your reasoning?
Scruncher.
Okay.
Scruncher, of course.
Well, I'm not a natural born conspiracy theorist to be quite honest.
However, I am a television person.
I've been making television for more than half of my life.
And when I first started kind of reading about the so-called conspiracy, first of all,
it makes sense.
You have made sense at the time.
There was a lot going on between Russia and the United States.
The Russians had put Sputnik into space and we were behind and there was a big push
and a lot of pressure to basically outdo them for a number of political reasons at the time.
So, you know, if you take that into account and then you take into account how often you
are lied to and cheated through television.
And I know this.
This is what I know, and it's all minor stuff.
But boy, the times that we have lied to our audience, both in programs that I've made
for television networks in Europe, for MTV, basically every single production that I've
worked on, there's a lie somewhere along the way.
And you'll witness what's happened with these Reuters pictures, not just the Photoshop
job, but also, you know, a shot of a busted building and then a Mickey Mouse doll conveniently
placed right in front in the shot.
You know, these, these are lies.
These are things that are staged and are placed to evoke a certain emotion.
And of course to a list of certain response.
I think in many cases, it's not politically motivated, it is just a freelance photographer
who's trying to sell his shit.
And that's usually how those things happen.
But if you, I'll give an example, Janet Jackson, when she had, what was the song?
What have you done for me lately?
I was doing television in the Netherlands.
This is, I think, 82 or 83.
She sent out what is now common known as an EPK.
And echo Papakilo, electronic press kit.
And on that is, of course, a new video, and then an interview with Janet, but only
of Janet and the questions are nicely spaced.
So that you essentially can either take out a little clip of an answer of hers or, as
we did, we had a satellite link up with Janet Jackson.
And we even had a little bit of satellite static fuzz there, and then I had it perfectly
timed where I'd asked the questions, and then we'd switch over to the satellite feed
and Janet would answer.
These are lies that are done all the time, and it's so simple.
And particularly in those early days of television, I'm pretty sure that it was certainly
an option that was open to everyone, and whether it was true or not, that remains to
be seen.
It doesn't help that now all this footage is gone, because what do we have left?
We basically have the hoax that is left.
Could someone please answer the phone?
Please?
Pretty, please?
So we don't have the source material.
You've got to be suspicious of that.
On the other hand, I received an email from Chris Aleviado, Adam, I would leave a voice
mail, but I'm very busy.
Oh, excuse me, I heard you say you don't believe we landed on the moon as a heap of evidence
that we did land in the moon.
Apollo 11, 14, and 15 placed laser reflectors on the moon.
That's interesting.
How many moon landings did we make?
Did we make that many moon landings?
Or did they just drop laser reflectors on the moon?
Laser beams are routinely fired at these reflectors through telescopes at McDonald's Observatory
in Texas and at Grasse in Southern France.
Timings of these reflected beams are used to measure the Earth moon distance to an accuracy
of one inch to explain the existence of these reflectors.
The hopes advocates have no choice, but to claim they were placed on the moon by robotic
landers.
A huge undertaking for which there's no supporting evidence.
The simple answer, the Apollo astronauts, placed them there, Chris says, okay, I don't
know anything about these reflectors.
That's the first time I'm hearing from them, but if you have any information, let me know.
Call me on the voice mail numbers, plus one for New Jersey 201 65 65 657 or in London
444, plus 442 076813753.
Now let me bring you that thing that I fired accidentally because this is something
I was looking for yesterday when I was talking with Patricia about it.
This is pretty cool that it pertains to the Edinburgh festival and shadow falls.
Hi Adam, my name is Andrew Gervin.
Did you know the Edinburgh festival fringe or something in Edinburgh this August?
I did.
It's the biggest arts festival in the world, the rule verse 17,000 performers in Edinburgh
and as we speak.
The big booze fest.
I'm an Edinburgh local, but I'm also podcasting from this year's fringe.
The rest of Pod Show might be getting scared to it list just now at the thought of Shadow
Falls.
How do you think I felt yesterday then when I met Western Blakely who plays Breyer
Gent, the voice of evil?
We met up yesterday for a coffee and discussed the production that he's brought across
from Los Angeles with open fist theatre company.
Of course, the conversation turned to Shadow Falls.
Shadow Falls, which is I understand it, is the first professionally produced Podcast
drama.
I am involved because the director saw me in a play at the open fist and liked my
voice.
That group does their radio dramas and then I came in and get to play Breyer again,
which is just a treat.
At this point, that's the only role I'm playing.
The voice of evil, perhaps, you have to listen to all the episodes to find out whether
it's really evil or not, which I don't even know that.
So what's as Western think about the medium of Podcasting itself?
It's kind of like how the internet has allowed people to create something for almost nothing
and put it out in the world and some of that stuff is going to bubble up because it's
going to be really good.
It was a while ago and I'm trying to think of, I think it's Francis Ford Copelo who
said, you know, the next great movie might be made by a 14-year-old girl from Ohio because
the technology is available to almost anyone and that's part of the podcasting is,
okay, I'm just going to put this out, I'm going to create something and put it out in
the world.
So it's, you know, it's a chance to do for experimentation that stuff that I like
about theater is the same thing that can create, be created with a podcast.
It's great talking to Western yesterday and there's actually the seventh interview that
I've done so far that I'll being hosted at podcastingnews.com, but if you want to check
out the rest of that 20-minute interview, as well as the six other interviews that I've
done so far this year, get across to whispertpromt.com, where you can also read the text
reviews of everything that I've been to see.
Thank you very much for taking the time to play this Adam.
Folder.
I do thank you very much for putting that together.
I appreciate it.
That's really cool.
Yeah, the Edinburgh Festival.
That's a big as deal.
And it is a huge drink festival as well.
So the third episode of Shadow Falls drops this Monday, Shadow Falls.podshow.com, and
I've already heard the third episode.
You are going to love it.
I promise you that.
Oh yeah, portions of today's daily source got brought to you by Accur, the new RDX SUV.
If you want to learn more about, in particular, the sound system, the sound system, which
is surround sound, there's a great interview with a Grammy award-winning record producer who
actually helped Accurate with the whole surround sound system together.
You can find that at Accurate.podshow.com, and yesterday also told you about the sad passing
of Sophia Ron and Marta's Little Yorky past the way way too young for Yorky, I think she
was maybe seven years old, and it really sucks.
She was sick for a couple of weeks.
And if you wouldn't mind, would you go over to Sophia.podshow.com, that's with pH, and
and leave a message there.
There's a beautiful kind of remembrance podshow plus site for Sophia, and I know that it would
certainly make everyone who was close to Sophia really happy, and I would appreciate it very much.
It is Friday, my friends, and when it's Friday, that means you pretty much control the
music on the show, and there's one person who always checks in, he is the official musicologist
of the Charlie, the only lawyer with a sense of humor.
You're out there.
I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out.
Please don't bang that gavel.
You can try this cowbell out.
Let's all give up now.
To the hardest work in lawyer, it's Jersey, Ty, and then yeah, it's Jersey, Ty, and Bob, and yeah,
you're out there.
What do you say?
You might even win this case.
The Charlie's inside.
Yeah, yeah.
It was Jersey inside.
All of that.
Jersey, Ty, and Trevor, now.
It's Jersey, Ty.
Oh, yeah, you're going to try it.
Yo, what's up, Adam, and all the Chacha heads?
This is Jersey, Ty, and Adam.
After doing this official musicologist gig now for a couple of weeks, I finally finally
realized that you have some criteria that you're looking for on a Friday song.
Number one, it's got to have a good guitar riff.
Yeah.
Number two, it's got a rock.
And three?
Well, it's something you've got to play that wacky cowbell tip.
Yeah.
The pot-safe music network, I think I found all three.
The band is chasing red, and the song is stroker.
Get that cowbell out.
Here we go.
And oh, by the way, Adam, scruncher.
Big time, scruncher.
You can't deny you saw the footage, because she had one in my face.
You can't deny they won't do anything.
You can't deny it.
You can't deny you hold a trigger and the shot won't hurt you sight
You can't deny it, it didn't take you back
You are not afraid, not hard, you can't deny that
When you took her back, that you didn't like the design
You can't deny it, that you didn't like the design
You can't deny it, it didn't take you back
When you took her back, that you didn't like the design
I need to tell this to you.
Chasing Red.
The podcast of music network.
Thank you very much.
Jersey Todd.
Check them out at JerseyTideShow.com, the official music colleges of the Charlie and
always there for us on a Friday last night went to London with my bride hung out with
our financial team, which is all women and all them beautiful.
And we went to this restaurant called Sketch, which is what is it on the conduit street,
I think.
Wow.
That's a trippy ass place.
I tried to record some stuff to put in the next perversion for profit.
Hopefully it turned out because it was pretty dark, but waiting to see the bathrooms
man.
They're actual, they're like, Mark from Ork, eggs, it's really cool.
Oh, yes.
Come on, baby, back later on, baby.
Hey Adam, it's Amy Mack.
Look at you.
You made it today three.
Yeah.
I'm proud.
I wasn't sure you'd stick with it.
Today we're going to be doing some more groundwork to go ahead and grab your
hands.
All right.
Got the wire.
That's it.
Yep.
You're going to get down on your hands and knees.
Hands and knees.
You want to make yourself a table so you want your hands aligned right under your shoulders
and your knees aligned right under your hips.
Okay.
Good so far.
Yeah.
Now you're going to extend your right arm out in front of you.
Right arm.
And your left leg out behind you.
I hope you can.
Yeah.
We should start my combat to keep you to be nowhere.
Okay.
And those back into that table position.
I'm going to table.
Ground it and you're balanced.
I'm a table.
Now alternate.
So your left arm goes out and you're right leg.
Stand it out behind you.
Okay.
Good.
That's one.
Now back to the other side.
You're going to do seven more on each side.
Feel free to count while I talk.
Or you can listen in for some helpful tips and how to get the most out of this exercise.
Make sure you're breathing and you're staring at the floor so your neck is neutral.
You want to make sure your squeeze your stomach and your butt.
Yeah, yeah.
Really control your arms and legs.
You don't want to drop them or move too quickly.
Right.
Now you should feel some your stomach, back, and butt.
These are your core muscles and they're incredibly important in your everyday activities.
The stronger they are, the less likely you are for back injury, the better your posture,
which also affects your knees and feet.
And of course, the hotter your butt will look.
To find out more health and fitness tips or to subscribe to my podcast, check out
the fitnessattack podcast at fitness.punchow.com.
What number are you at at them?
I'm done.
When you've done eight on each side, it's all done.
Okay, wait.
Hey, I didn't think it was just going to get any easier.
Until next time.
One.
Answer slash.
Two.
Okay.
I had affected a whole lot more of my ass.
Any match.
Thank you very much for the answer size.
Episode three.
Saving atams ass.
One segment at a time.
I did a lot for me.
I didn't feel anything in my ass.
Hey, if you're listening to the daily source code on serious stars 102,
he's what's coming up for you tonight.
As we bring you our pod show podcast block every single week to afternoon.
Right after I'm out of here, Pacific Coast,
Hellway followed by Dawn and Drew, then.
Julian coming in with in over your head, which is all rather third.
And then the scenes in Marcus couch on the scene.
He used radio with Madge Weinstein winding up with episode 10 of ancestor,
which is Scott Siggler's.
Uh, potio book right here on serious stars 102.
Have yourselves a great weekend.
I'll let's talk to you guys on Monday.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
I have a.
I have to say a little problem there with my overall condition.
Hi, Adam Kerry.
Here is your European Union correspondent from crazy.
Comeyx clip blocked.
Ah, I got to give you a jingle, man.
Comeyx trip.
Speaking of conspiracy theories,
it may be that latest action on airports in UK is an attempt by British government
to turn attention away from what is going on now in UK.
What is going on?
Well, since year 2004, when big bank, not to confuse with bank bank, European Union
announcement took place, the biggest wave of immigrants moved to UK, the biggest
in whole history of UK, officially 700,000 people from Eastern Europe just in two years,
but an officially, it is more than one million immigrants.
It is the biggest immigration wave to UK in the whole history of UK.
What is the result?
Well, cancelled tax must be raised soon, and immigrants take jobs away from natives.
So, right wing tabloids are angry in UK, and next year, when Bulgaria and Romania
are joining the EU, the European Union administration may explode.
So, to turn away attention from this shit,
preferably UK government, you know what?
By the way, I have nothing against Shadow Falls,
because Mr. Niemko is a gay guy, but for fact, in the year of continuous care
by terrorism, why not to put you some comedy show, funny, comedy, not horror,
and this is just an idea, because for example, how I stand is running similar
audio show, but it is called Batkrek Manten.
Anyway, he will later, Adam, you blackberry seedling.
Yo!
Thanks, CSB.
The illustrious comic strip blogger.
I don't know, man, I think that's little far-fetched your theory there.
Although, I have questions about this.
I'd like to know a little bit more about what is necessary to create an explosive device
from liquids you can smuggle onto a plane.
In fact, just before I went to bed last night, I saw that there was a report from West Virginia
that a woman had been apprehended there who had liquids with her,
two of which had tested positive for explosives.
I'm like, what does that mean?
She's walking around with nitro.
I can't mess out there.
I'm just listening to all the wonderful profiles you guys are sending me through the voice
mail lines.
I'm sure that we have some chemists out there.
What does it actually take?
What do you need?
I think you need a combination of a couple of things.
That's a pretty dangerous shit, like H2SO4,
which you can't put into a plastic bottle as far as I know.
You got to mix stuff up, which could be crackling and popping.
I don't know, it just sounds a little far-fetched.
I'd like to know a little more details.
I don't even know who did it, man.
Just give me the details of what was actually required to do this.
You know, I'm not looking for an instruction booklet.
I just want to know what kind of chemicals do you need?
How does that really work?
And how do you turn your iPod into a detonator device?
Let me know.
Oh, the Delta tones of Angie B and X.
Hey Adam, I was just wondering when we musicians might look forward
to having our accounts rolled into the pod show plus site.
It'd be so cool when you're looking at my listener account
that you'd see my bands that are on the pod safe music network
as well as my podcaster on pod show would be so cool.
It's speaking of cool.
I'm totally looking forward to doing that pod show drama with you.
Yeah.
By the way, Shadow Falls is also a drama.
Come on, Mr. Blogger.
It's not a horror show.
It's a drama.
Angie, I think you probably got the same email
from Mark Yoshimoto, an MCOF that I did.
We have to basically explain your character
and your background, et cetera.
And so I think Mark is going to be working on that.
My character is pretty cool.
So that's forthcoming.
Yeah, rolling that in is of course exactly what we want to do.
But it's not as simple as rolling it in.
The pod safe music network is a system all by itself.
It's a huge database.
Which already has a couple of issues of its own.
Mainly that there's no separate label entity.
So labels have actually been uploading stuff under,
putting the label under the artist.
Which is of course also not right.
We're working on it.
We're working on a lot of things.
But it's a reasonably big job, I have to say.
But yes, of course, we need to have that.
We need to have association with labels.
And as I think I said the other day,
I also like to have venues in there.
And a couple others you can come up with.
So it's working on a baby working on it.
Hey Adam.
This is Happy and Pearl.
I am the bedtime stories my kids love go for.
And we thought we would check out your audio comment line.
Well Adam, a couple of things.
And we wanted us to tell you thanks for everything.
His downloads have been up 46% since the launch of Podger Plus.
So Adam, thanks for all that you do.
Oh yeah.
But we do have one thing we want to talk about.
After all, we've been through the frequently asked questions.
So best of Charlie, the trip to Walmart.
Don't you think bedtime stories might get rough.
They serve us and say a moment.
Hmm.
Well Adam, we got around.
Sometimes it gets booked and won't have to go from home.
Second line.
Bye Adam.
Bye bye, go first.
Well, I don't have one lined up.
You know, it's a pretty spontaneous thing.
If I do have to belt, I will certainly remember.
To promote bed time stories.
My kids love 46%.
That's interesting.
We have seen quite a network effect since we launch Podger Plus.
I don't know if it's 46% across the board.
But that's pretty amazing.
That is very, very cool.
The year up 46% just by launching Podger Plus.
I'm digging that.
104.
Hold it.
40.
481.
Right then.
I'm not going to call you a dick for putting this out.
I mean, it's true.
You pay more money and make sense, get better service on the plane insecurity.
But if I might have a little kid for a hat今回.
Think about this.
For a sense, the security has been beefed up since 911, and now with these new, new foil
the pack.
The security is stronger, the lines are longer, the lines are slower.
That means there's much more value to being able to get in the short line.
That means I'm sure some people are more inclined to buy first class tickets so they
can be in the short line, almost none of the things.
Which means in a sense, the airlines are now making money off of terrorist threats.
Now I'm not going with certain any way that any airline is beefing up the threat levels,
trying to make it seem like there should be more security just so the line gets slower
so people buy first class tickets.
So, something about that idea that the airlines are making money off of the threat of terrorism
just feel a little longer than me.
That's my 10-fuel hat moment, a helpless thing, no one scruncher.
Well you're a confused scruncher, because I don't believe that.
First of all airlines, making money, excuse me, airlines are most of them are a chapter
11.
They're not making money at all, you know, I fully expect by the end of the year the price
of a barrel of oil, crude oil, to go up to $100.
Mark my words right now.
I said it August 18th, 2006 by the end of the year, a barrel of oil will probably
be about $100.
You know, there was a huge disaster in Alaska.
Did you know that?
I think there's 200, 200,000 barrels a day that were coming out of Alaska.
Who was doing that?
Was it, ah, I can't remember which company was this only a couple, of course.
So they had to shut down because they were leaking shit into the sound again.
And of course, Alaska can't handle that.
If Alaska has another exon disaster, Alaska will be, you know, basically dead.
No, no, no, no.
Airlines is not a, I guess you're trying to conjure up a conspiracy theory there.
I don't believe that at all, not that airlines are trying to make more money.
And also, this is all coming from my rant about business class.
And being able to travel in shorter lines, business class is, for exactly what it sounds
like for business travelers.
And I remain by my stance that business travel subsidizes other classes of travel.
And why is it that governments around the world subsidize airlines?
And they're always trying to help to bail airlines out if it's, if they can at all,
it's not always possible.
It's because business travel is a part of the economy.
Particularly in the United States, if you, I mean, just imagine if, if, if for whatever reason
I couldn't travel to San Francisco, that would, that would hurt our company and therefore
hurting a minor, minor piece, but it certainly would hurt a piece of the economy.
So business travel is a part of the economy.
It's not a part of some kind of luxury class and some kind of class difference.
It's because in business, time is money.
So the less time you can spend, traveling the more time you can spend, contributing to
the economy.
That's the whole difference here.
Please, pair that in mind.
I have a list of states from Spanish stands and it's the English, the long time Charlie
Lissner.
My profile, 44, married to children, listening to PCAs and actually in the hash, just heard
you're a rampant on a 4-4-1 regarding plane business class or a class or whatever you
want to call it.
I had your opportunity to fly to South Africa recently with my company and I flew business
class with South African Airways, let's come over to flown business class in my life and
what a difference it may.
12 hour flight.
I work, I get some good food, I relax, I sweat and I get the ground in, take town, ready
to start working that day, like you got my gear off of the hotel and went straight to work.
It makes a big difference, yes, we paid the price for it, we paid the price, that's what
we want, we want great service, we want great food, we want to get the faster, we want
no chilling and that's it.
It's what it's all about, it's the money, I didn't pay as much as you did only pay
to in half hours of power to fly here so to save power, which is a bargain, really worth
the bargain, but yes, we pay for that and we are the people who do subsidize the economy
class, so there we go, I've got a degree with you, it is really and keep the deep purple
flowy.
Fuller?
Scruncher?
Yeah, full the scruncher, please, let me know.
Yeah, I think maybe part of the confusion is coming from actually saying that business
class subsidizes, if you say the economy class, it sounds like you're talking about a class
of people, but economy class of course is a class of travel.
Again, time is money in business and I think the only reason why I got upset about that
NPR report is because I'm not used to hearing that kind of noise coming out of the United
States, you know, it's clearly not about a class issue about, oh, I get, yeah, sure
you get better food, but it's about being able to perform better, and when you perform
better, it helps the economy, when you help the economy do, you help everybody.
Adam and David, I'm sorry, I don't just listen to DSC441 and listen to your rant about
the security line to the airports and I totally agree with you, man, I fly about a hundred
thousand domestic miles a year for work and man, I got to tell you, I pay more, I
fly more and I deserve to get that shorter line and not have to get to the airport
three hours early.
So anyway, I'm with you, man, and keep on rocking.
I'll try.
This is Charlie Triple IV, that's kind of a nice number.
Oh, we could have celebrated that one, couldn't we?
Now then again, maybe not.
Hey, Adam, Jack Elias, I'm a get Jack podcast.
I often invite listeners at the end of my show to email me to tell me that I suck.
Imagine my surprise listening to the Chacha this morning hearing Patricia tell you
that you suck.
That wasn't nice to her.
Oh, a folder, get Jack, got Podger to come.
Yeah, that's folder's got to stick together, dude, for sure.
The ad challenge is coming to a close.
If you want to hear the finalists and the finalists for the earthling ad challenge, go
to adchallenge.to podshow.com.
One of those finalists will win the $2,000 and will actually, in essence, be hired because
of their creativity in participating, in bringing across the message of earthling to podcast
listeners.
So make sure you go and check that out.
This is the last thing I wanted to play, which came in and came in on the voicemail.
I'm not quite sure what this is and I certainly don't understand the clue or the riddle
yet.
Play along because someone's clearly got some kind of plan and when you Charlie listeners
get something in your noggin, it usually sticks.
Here we go.
The adom.
Oh, adom.
Answer this.
Oh, I also forgot to mention, when women call in, it's fun to listen to.
When you play along for a cast not to miss, this is part one of a promo of nine.
Each with a little ahead and letter in line, play each one on your DSC and see if
your listeners can help find the key.
Then add a dot com to go to our site and now you shall find the podcast just right.
To compliment your family of avid cars, your listeners will certainly dig us and together
we will grow fast.
We send you love-wrapped riddles as our shameless and high as podcasting versions.
We're mable, teachable and eager.
Our goal is to entice you, adom curry, the podcast taught leaguer.
You emanate rays and disguise them as words like the god Hermes, your life is a verb.
You straddle too well to remember to yonder the Netherlands, the Gaple, San Francisco, and
an affluent suburb, how do you do it?
We all do ponder as you, the daily source code to live for us.
You leave us with a leafed buckling and handball a quiver, so sit back, play along, get ready
to ride, part of this is silly, but we know you shall take it in stride.
Canes for first clue, written expressly for you.
Don't strain yourself, it's simple and not hard to do.
To become an article, not just published in print, but one spoken often, and that
out there is your first hand, now you should be hearing from me very soon with the next
riddle.
TPSN.
Okay, I'm playing along, don't disappoint me, and send me some naked pictures.
Would you mind?
Sorry, pilot error.
Hey Adam, it's Neil from the Podsafe Revolution podcast, your daily source code official
Podsafe Revolutionary, delivering this message on behalf of a good friend, Paul Durham
from Black Lab.
He's a bit busy these days, so he asked me to hook you up with a brand new tune, it's
called a river of joy, and it's actually not on the sea of the sun album.
It's a brand new track, it's currently featured in the trailer for the movie The Covenant,
it's on the iTunes Music Store, and it's soon to be on the Podsafe Music Network.
It's known to be different, it's a bit more techno flavored than the sea of the sun
album, but I thought it might help out those Podsho kids kick off another football
Friday.
It's a cheers dude, and of course you don't even have to ask, I'm with you, I'm a folder.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
It's a foul, it's a foul, it's a foul
It's a foul, it's a foul
It's a foul, it's
a foul, it's a foul, it's a foul
It's a foul, it's a foul
It's about to start with your eyes
Rhythm of your eyes
I'm a chicken child
If she was a sweet place
If she could tell her
I couldn't hate her
I couldn't leave you so otherwise
We can keep you, we can keep you
We can keep you
River of Joy Black Lab on your Fubar Friday. If you want to know what Fubar stands for
and well, you got to go look it up. If you be AR, and that's it for your daily show's course.
So it's source code for today as always.
To be our video. Take care everybody. Adam at podshow.com daily source code.com. Have a great weekend. I'll talk to you on Monday.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.
Yet this podcast and we're great ones like it. On the high performance podcast, a
delivery network from podshow and line-white networks.