Delta's Yeracharli 337, the Apple tastes good.
$16 billion worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this genre.
On casting, it's Adam Curry.
One day while I was working hard at doing nothing,
I was sitting around for hours.
And I thought how cool it would be if I had some
Can't get superpowers.
There'd be so many to choose from.
So I'm helpful, so I'm just fine.
And tell that I think I just need.
I like the ability to make a large enough pancake
for all the starving children to eat.
Or I could have a hypnotic finger that could shoot a rib
that'd be great.
I could blast all people to whereas right in the crotch
and take away their ability to form a cake.
On the back straight vision and I could make the decision
if I want to see you naked or not.
The ability to change the law
make things like once and for all
and finally leave a wise pie.
I want superpowers.
Superpowers.
I would like to be able to freeze time
and stop everything in its path.
And I could take someone from falling off a cliff
or I could choose to have someone with me.
I'd take time and bend it
and I'd learn how to spend it
especially with the Antonio.
I'd become an inventor
and I'd make things way better
like an actual good tasting beer.
I want superpowers.
Superpowers.
Like being able to breathe under water
or stop bullets with my face.
And being bent to the pool
to your voice and his drinks
and leave a paper trail without a trace.
But being able to lift a stream
we might object with only the use of my hands.
Or have fire and breath of a thousand
racking to it.
I can have a year out of ten.
And being able to cure all the seeds
in the world and being bent
cows not so bad.
And being put in the walls
I'm not fully material
so the scientists are like going far.
What change everything
to the metrics system
so they're grateful to the waste.
And I give myself the capability
and the way of building such a taste.
I want superpowers.
Superpowers.
Super power
I want Super Power
Yes you told me I want Super Power
Yes you tell me I want Super Power
оп I want Super Power
We Super Power
I want Super Power
Yes you told me Robert
It's not quite a hot shape yet, but it's coming, Mark says hi, and I want super high.
Oh, it's...
Thank you.
You're really super.
So this is a guy who I met yesterday at Sirius Adly Radio when I was in New York.
Well, I'm still in New York, actually.
Early Thursday morning on my way home tonight.
I don't know why, for some reason I booked a flight at like 9.25 this evening.
So I've got, you know, I've got to figure out stuff to do today.
Yesterday, last night, last evening.
I was up at Sirius, and I was planning on doing some recording.
And for a number of reasons that didn't work out, but I was assigned a board-up as we call it, a board operator.
Because it was going to be done in a real studio, quite a treat for me.
And guys name Mark, Mark Seaman.
Yeah, I know.
But we don't laugh about names here on the Charlie now, do we?
And when we were talking, he's just learning a little bit about podcasting.
He started there as an intern, and he's a musician.
And so Ron and I were talking to him.
And he says, well, yeah, he's my CD.
It's called the EP of the Century, Mark says high.
Of course.
So you probably figured out the title that song was Super Powers.
And, you know, I told him about the podcast of music network.
And I guess he's going to go check it out.
But listen to the CD before starting the show.
I kind of let Doug this song.
So I thought I'd share that with you, even though it was damn long.
Like five minutes and 46 seconds.
Yes.
Our trips in New York is just about over.
As I said today, I'll just be visiting a couple more people on my way out of town.
I'm so incredibly tired.
You have no idea.
You may not give a damn, and you probably don't want to hear that in the morning,
because you may be tired too.
But man, I'm just so incredibly beat.
It's been six hours of night.
You know, I've been doing the show.
And PW has been putting it together.
And editing it all in the evening.
And it's just been quite a lot along with all the discussions we've had with
marketing companies, agencies, and many of them old friends.
So good to see them in this new context.
It's just good.
This is, you know, once a quarter, that's what we do.
We're going to write on down in town and go see if we can sell some
quarterback.
So here's an interesting story I heard in the, in the hallways, it's serious,
some water cooler talk.
There was a big meeting recently.
And it's funny because I know what happened, or I knew what was,
I knew something was happening because we got a request.
PW Fenton, and usually when the request goes straight to PW,
who produces all the serious satellite radio shows.
Usually when they go to him directly, it's an end around.
You know, they don't want me to know something about what they're asking.
And so they had asked for a piece of, and they gave out some time code or
something.
Anyway, PW Fenton, I did deduce that it was, it was clearly
Madge Weinstein.
And so he, of course, emailed me and said, you know,
something's up, you know, they want to have this piece.
And I, you know, say that to them and tell them if there's anything
we can help them with, give me a call.
So it didn't hear anything about it.
And that was two or three weeks ago.
And actually, they specifically wanted a piece of Madge,
one of her driving podcasts.
You know, she's always very funny when she's driving.
And during this big meeting just recently, a few days ago,
maybe last week, which was this big corporate, you know,
it's like what companies do.
But it was really the top echelon of the people who are programming
these 120 satellite radio channels.
And the CFO, the chief financial officer of serious,
David Freer, I think it is.
Yeah, as, I guess everyone does a little, you know,
their vision of the company, et cetera.
So the CFO, very interesting.
The first of all, great that this guy is listening to stuff.
That's so incredibly appreciated.
He got up and played this piece of Madge,
which, uh, PWPs can get me the clip.
I couldn't find it that quickly.
Before I just fall down from tiredness.
And he played this clip, and he just was raving about it.
This is exactly what we should be sounding like.
This is different. This is irreverent.
This is, you know, this is the future,
which, of course, is fantastic.
And like we didn't know that.
Like we don't know that it's not the children,
but Madge who's really our future.
But the funny thing was,
that throughout this entire, um,
a praising monologue of Madge Weinstein and East radio,
he was referring to her as this Jewish woman from Chicago.
And, um, I think most people,
know Madge long enough to know exactly what she is and what she stands for.
And it was just a hilarious, uh, hilarious moment.
And I don't know if Mr. Frier knows yet,
but we're happy that you love Madge.
And we all, we all love Madge and what she does.
So I've got a couple things, uh,
lined up for you.
There's actually waiting for the pod safe music network to come back online,
because, you know, we're getting all that sales stuff and everything,
and they're moving servers.
Let me just check for a second.
Hold on.
Let me see if it's back up.
Damn, it's not.
And all of a sudden I realize what an incredibly important resource this is,
because I'm getting ready to prep my show.
Usually, you know, I go through and check what's new on the homepage,
and look at new submissions.
And maybe I'll go back through my playlist and pull something that I've played it,
you know, a few episodes ago.
And, uh, it's, you know,
I'm sorry, we'll be back removing servers and like,
oh, man, that sucks.
Ah, that and the fact that I don't have any sense of sale is,
uh, yeah, without a doubt, that it's bad.
It's really bad.
If anything going home means seeing my girls,
it also means seeing that lovely sense of sale machine.
Well, I have some news report first of all about Trinity.
There is a, uh, a fund, uh, meaning a fund of, uh,
investment money that is called Indo-Street.
Well, I have some news report first of all about Trinity.
There is a, uh, a fund, uh, meaning a fund of, uh,
investment money, that is, uh,
a fund of investment money that is investing specifically in green technologies amongst
which will be biodiesel and to the folks have been listening to the show and they're very
interested in sponsoring our little talk about biodiesel and Trinity and of course
we want to do something kind of unique. So the sponsorship will go primarily towards pimping out
Trinity and of course we're going to turn that into a video podcast. I imagine paint my ride this
will be paint my biodiesel beast or something better than I'll come up with and I'm so excited
about this. You know I've got to figure out some slogan to put on the side what colors are going to
be. We're going to chop the roof. We're going to make it into part convertible but I mean that is
you know that's that's your money and put to good use. I'm telling you I cannot wait
Patricia was excited. She's like wow we'll have like the servo so it could pop up and down like
a hip hop mobile. I say yeah baby you better believe it and we have some little spin and rims so
just wanted to share that with you and as I said we'll we'll be podcasting that. Probably a video podcast.
Okay a couple of emails that have come in regarding at the biodiesel industry and Trinity. Let's see
Halifax and this comes to us from Steve Din. After two years of running biodiesel in a fleet of
buses check this out something is starting to smell fishy in the city of Halifax. The city quit using
a unique B20 which is the same stuff Willie Nelson is selling 20% biodiesel 80% petrodiesel.
So they quit using this unique blend of fish oil based biodiesel in its fleet of municipal
buses this past December after encountering some operational difficulties. What could those be you think?
Well indeed it was smelling in addition according to the uh to the herald the municipality
took up the issue with the supplier Wilson fuel cocks which denied a problem with a fuel existed.
Really was they say that they had problems with the lines clogging up so they've halted the use of it.
I don't know that this is fish oil though. I think that's that may be something all together
different than now just the yeah the normal french fries stuff that we're looking at.
Article in uh wasn't fortune magazine online. I'll make sure I put that put that link in the show notes.
The article mentions 80% of all new vehicles are able to use bio fuels. Of course in that case
we're talking about mostly ethanol mixtures for petrol engines which will have the yellow fuel cap by the way.
And of course it also mentions good old Willie Nelson's bio wheelie. Dude we got to talk to him.
He'd be perfect for a segment on uh on Trinity. Christian Euben uh in in behind excuse me
Adam up to now Germany was known as a biodiesel paradise.
Biodiesel costs about a euro per liter which is pretty cheap compared with regular gas. Yeah that's about half the price.
They're nearly 2,000 gas stations providing drivers with green diesel in a growing market. But yesterday
I was really shocked when I heard that the German minister of finance is planning a biodiesel tax.
The government's going to collect 10 euro since per liter of biodiesel and an even 15% on vegetable oil.
As result of this announcement, German biodiesel stocks plunged harshly more than 10%
I guess more than 10% that is pretty bad. Okay well it's bound to happen. I don't really mind
and I'm not quite sure how it works in Germany but in uh in many countries you know your roads
or you know the the tax in the fuel actually goes or should be going towards making the roads better
and maintenance and upkeep so and it's so it's what it's like 15% yeah that's not too bad.
You look at a country like the Netherlands where the tax is almost 50% on the fuel. In fact
famously one minister said excuse me I have a super coffee here.
One minister famously said that he was going to add 25 cents onto the uh onto the price of a
liter of fuel but we'd be getting it back in two years time or some time period similar to that
he never gave it back. They still joke about that in the Netherlands. Staying in Europe
Paul Frone says hey Adam would really enjoy the podcast this is to regularly read this article.
Oh yeah this is about Brussels. Brussels where the uh European Union where the European
Commission has its part-time seat is really starting to push biodiesel. This is all good news.
Colin Sloman adamant in the listener for over a year and joyed I've worked in the energy industry
for more than 20 years and find your biodiesel Trinity segment fascinating.
But you might be interested in the following article and of course he points to the
fortune article as well but then as a little piece down below a British petroleum to fund
Indian project to produce biodiesel in New Delhi where this petroleum is an ounce of
a fund a 9.4 million dollar project in the energy and resource institute in Andra Pradesh to produce
biodiesel from geotrophic curcus which is a non-edible oil bearing crop.
This is great. Diesel engines rule man you can really just throw anything into them that you want.
Oh hold on we got an audio feedback check this out.
Hey Adam this is Ben G.C. over in Whitton Hills California. I got my road in track today
on March if you want page 102 it turns out that while you can't really poop in a
diesel tank yet you sure can't pee in it and this article called the diesel conundrum
there's a section here called piss on it and I quote urea an ammonia-based compound
one source of which is mammal urine is becoming controversial in diesel emissions control
also known as SCR selective catalytic reduction urea injection into the exhaust for most
chemical reduction of N.O.X. European automakers are interested in SCR as a means of meeting
there and our increasingly stringent N.O.X regulations. So it looks like maybe you'll be able to
pin you in the Trinity's tanks and even help the environment while you're doing it. But you like to know
and here's my plug my son's got a great podcast for teenage gamers it's called game snafu
available on iTunes and at his website two cool dudes dot com k-o-o cool dudes dot com
and me every now and then they let me play various body parts of dust and often on
Pacific Coast highway okay I'm not quite sure what that means but it sounds pretty frightening
alright excellent so there is so much more to learn about biofuel bio diesel as we continue our
quest to saving the planet that's right save the world and win great prizes
and how to's if you have watched the video of podcasts or conference 2006 in Chapel Hill from the
Mac Pro podcast you can see me there in the interview yes during that time I was a learner
I'm willing to learn how to do podcasts and now an official member of Fortune Network family and
in a podcast soon we will be talking about tips tricks and how to's about traditional Indian
cookery talking about tips I would like to share some facts about curry in Indian food curry
as I was derived from a Tamil word spelled as k-a-r-i and tamal is one of the salt Indian language
one of the 26 languages spoken in India and of course tamal is my mother tongue and I'm from
Tamil Nadu so curry means sauce it refers to various kind of dishes which include vegetables,
meats, potato, etc usually pad with right and there is another one called masala or curry masala so
masala has as we've made the spices it's a thick pastey sauce it's a combination of spices butter
coconut milk and different kinds of spices and there is a leaf called curry leaves which
it is used in the Indian cookery in South Indian cookery it is a whole ship it's about an inch
in land it's almost looks like a leaf from a citrus tree it is fried and cooked with the dish
that's all I have to say about in a tip about curry in this small comment and once again thank you
for listening to our show and thank you for having me in your show thank you very much Adam
for your inspiration you're giving us and thank you very much for your wonderful week wonderful work
you're doing for us thank you and you all have a great day bye go what's that
okay had a little tail there on the MP3 sorry about the the the left channel right channel thing
let me just cast blushers pretty cool you could you could just mono the signal but I couldn't find
it that quick you can do it on the fly snow or back to stereo I don't like curry not to be honest
with you whenever I go out if someone takes me out to an Indian restaurant they have to order
for me not to specify no please you know whatever it gets something I'll eat it but no what is it
coriander is that what oh man I just just don't like that at all let me see still to come I
think we can do a metro sexual moment got another potting music song one that I pulled in from
the archives and we'll keep it relatively short since I'm tired I already told you that
and then tomorrow morning when I get back to London I get in what I get a nine o'clock or something
like that so I'll probably get in sleep for an hour or two and then I'll do the show maybe a
little bit later a little bit later than usual and I hope that's something to talk about hope
something goes on today something I mean what am I going to do for all these hours in New York
if you're checking this out on star serious 103 before warned very soon I think within a
week or two we'll be moving to channel 102 they're adding another another channel to the
serious lineup which is what is it called the blue collar comedy channel yeah the blue collar comedy
channel so that will take over channel 103 and we're moving up so you'll have Howard Stern
a channel 100 then you have his second channel which during the day I believe repeats the show
and then they have Howard news or whatever that's our 101 and then conveniently located right next to
that will be 102 and for those of you who are listening to us on serious you can check us out
every day from 6 to 10 p.m. Eastern time 37 Pacific time Pacific Coast Hellway is next then it's
a Madge Weinstein with East Ries Ries Ries Ries Ries Ries Ries Radyope and then Dawn and Drew
and I don't have a clue at all is it good more daily is that on tonight and then I don't know
if it is DVD weekly day or not and we're going to start fitting more more podcasts more new podcasts
into the pod show lineup so stay tuned for that and I will talk to all of you on the satellite tomorrow
for the Friday edition and meanwhile here on the show quick note about advertising since we are
on our Madison Avenue trip Kevin Mason says Adam I'm the owner of an Amazon parrot
well to keep the bird from getting bored we play the radio yes radio is for the birds
the issue comes when I walk into the room the radio station always seems to be playing their
promo toop in their own horn about how they only play two minutes of commercials every hour
if that's so why am I always hearing the same promo my parrot is less repetitive
we're thinking about finding some way to play podcasts for the bird perhaps some big mic
because she apparently likes big mic my point is that regardless of the earthling spots podcasting
is still nicer to listen to let's do the math radio station two minutes of ads per hour plus
bragging about the fact they only have two minutes of an hour of ads is eight minutes
delta share charlie thirty seconds of ads per hour plus burps is one minute one minute per hour
so in other words after download eight delta share charlie to hit the same amount of ads
that I do in one hour radio well as we you know as I've kind of discovered yesterday the most
important thing is the repetitiveness of it that that's really it's starting to bug me too
I don't mind the earthling commercial although you know the the call is going out and
and we have a brainstorming session with earthling next week about this you know this whole idea
of how do we get user generated advertising into podcast so be prepared is your call to action
but the repetitive nature of it that does I must say that does kill me as I said yesterday
it would be like playing the same promo over and over on the show or the same song over and over
because you know we don't just happen to tune in sometime during those you know that that
eight minutes an hour in fact we're actually zapping away during that eight minutes an hour
whatever you do don't don't don't don't don't zap away right now please just stay right there you
believe anything is possible stop fast forwarding don't do that plank we believe in an
internet that's safe from virus hidden scammers we're earthling we believe your personal
information should be just that personal and we believe your internet should be a friend
not a faux we're earthling make this smart choice visit earthlink.net and discover what our
internet experts can do for you earthlink we revolve around you right to yesterday at the
end of the show I played a promo from the Frank Whitt podcast and at the end of the promo there was
there was a line that was it's his funniest cancer I think was the name it's so it's a promo
about the show and the tagline was funniest cancer and I just end this whole thing about about
someone in the pod show family who had been very close to a cancer death and it of course was
completely the wrong thing to play now I did preface at the beginning of the show that anything
could happen because I was just pulling stuff randomly out of my Gmail account and so when I heard this
it just it totally freaked me out and I was you know mostly pissed at myself for not having
checked out what I was going to play so yeah sometimes it worked sometimes it doesn't this was
definitely not a good example of how surprise works well in in in this particular podcast
of course we've done that before and it's turned out differently and my reaction was really
came from the gut and but it wasn't really meant as a personal attack on on the Frank Whitt podcast
and there's all kinds of conversation going on at curry dot com all kinds of comments and of
course now it's all my fault but I don't I really don't see it that way it what it what it taught
me first of all is I can't do that you know that's just way too risky but I just want you to know
that well actually Frank Whitt responded to this so I'll just play it's kind of long so
play a piece of what he said okay so this fucking sucks this isn't like a real show or anything
I just had to put this out because I feel a fallout coming basically we did a promo or Julia
did a promo for us and I retweaked it a little bit and added an old quote of Robbie at the end saying
it's fun like cancer and I'd shot that promo off to a bunch of people including Adam Curry
who I no longer listen to I don't listen to any of the pod show podcast now this is so funny
I don't listen I don't listen get damn it but I sent him a promo and then I just kind of check
to see if he played it I mainly stick with the media podcast as I've told you guys before and
so I checked out his show tonight for him getting ready to go to bed and basically
to see if he'd played he was going to play the promo and as I listened I started to grow
and increasingly nervous because he was talking about so their podcast or match Weinstein who I'd
I'd also listen to a long time ago it had an in a long time was not her show either and
basically her partner had passed away I guess of cancer lymphoma I went and researched this
afterwards because I started to feel so shitty because he played our promo and that cancer bit
comes on at the end and you know he just kind of gets upset and processes you know bad stupid promo
on his show notes and it's really fucking lame that I mean that's a bad coincidence like I said
on the blog post I'm a hypo contract I have to make fun of these things I've watched several
people in my life dive horrible cancer I mean horrible bad and it's awful but you know you got
a laugh at the shit because it's going to get one for of us I mean there's no escaping it it's it's
I mean they don't you know there's no cure for it it's so he basically goes on you know to say
that this is about laughing about horrible things and I'm all for that humor is a great great
of what humor is a great way to to deal with grief and with pain etc but this is just more
a lesson about well we've already gone through my lesson I learned that I you know I should not
be doing stuff and just playing without having previewed it but also it's about context if you
know your own show and you and you create a promo I'm not you heard your show I mean I stop listening
to your show I only stood if see if you play bits when I talk about you when you know your
own show it's and you put a promo together you really have to think for a couple seconds is this
within the context of what this promo is will will people understand all the all the little bits
and quotes in the context within the which they're said and listen to your promo again I don't
think so and of course at the end you know if a part of your show is to make fun of if you are
you know I didn't know you were hyper-contract I couldn't tell that from the promo I didn't know that
you know that this is your way perhaps of dealing with with the with the pains of of living
with someone or yourself with with a horrible disease you know so there's no way for me there
was no context for me to know that so of course it it all worked out horribly in the show
but if you're making a promo you really need to pay attention to that because if I had previewed
the promo I wouldn't have played it and regardless of what I was going to talk about on the show
I wouldn't have played it because you know at this time in my life I just don't find that funny
not in that context now if the if your show deals with stuff like that and you make a joke out of
out of things like cancer you know as as and as and lots of fantastic comedy where pain can
be replaced by laughter of course I'm all for it but I would say the promo definitely wouldn't have
gotten played anyway just because at this point in my life it the way it was presented didn't come
across is very funny to me and that's also taught me a couple other things because I definitely
make jokes about all kinds of stuff that upsets me or I'm or pains me and I very often don't think
about other people who are you know within earshot what their personal feelings may be so I'm just
taking this as a personal lesson no personal offense meant or harm intended of course and let's all
just calm down just revisiting the cartoon controversy for a moment I got an email from Michael
and oh surprise I love it when this happens I love it when when when I get these kinds of emails
because Michael works at pod show and he starts up by saying that's probably the only
muslim at pod show damn one snuck in maybe the the real issue behind the cartoons is the
current war going on between NATO and the caliphist muslims I really don't think it has anything to
do with freedom of expression it's about the current war and is viewed by caliphist muslims
am I pronounced that right caliphist muslims in terms of a war not a liberal idea about freedom of
expression also in terms of immigration you will be surprised how much racism and xenophobia
immigrants from non-white countries are subjected to how can we expect people to integrate when
they are faced without right racism on a daily basis do you remember those no Irish need apply
signs from earlier in the American history but then again what do I know just an anarcho muslim
druid things I've learned by living amongst muslims here in abroad specifically the Netherlands
one of my religious teachers was a refugee in the Netherlands in Delft so Michael thank you very much
first of all um yep you know what actually I do know that a little bit funny enough when I was seven
years old and we moved from the time we lived in Kensington Maryland and we moved I was just about
to turn seven actually we were going to move to the Netherlands for three years this was a time when
a lot of US companies were just setting up shop in the Netherlands specifically places like Texas
Instruments in a couple of early high tech firms and there was quite an influx into this you know
relatively old world country and of course I went to the international school of Amsterdam
so didn't really integrate just like many other cultures you know there was no need to integrate
up picked up with the school bus taken to where all the American and you know other uh the
kids from other countries well but primarily Americans at the time um and boy was I discriminated against
and and in a foreign language which I didn't understand and the only thing I would understand
of these tirays that were thrown at me was you crazy American crazy American and when you're
seven years old you know that sucks and then they'd write shit with you know chalk on uh on the side
walk with a big arrow pointing towards our house now granted you know uh when someone writes fish poop
in a foreign language with an arrow to your house you know it ain't all that bad but at the time you
know I was that was pretty traumatizing I couldn't get a fucking break from anyone in the neighborhood
and there was a different culture and they had um pieces of PVC tubing that they'd roll up newspaper
newspapers into darts and then they'd shoot them at you as you were driving by or or riding by in your
bike and you know and of course had the wrong hair the wrong pants you know everything was wrong
so I do know what that feels like um because discrimination I think feels the same
regardless of what you're being discriminated about whether it's uh race, creed, color, sex,
sexual preference uh you know I think it's where you're from uh it it it feels the same and uh you
I think the bottom line is yeah it sucks but you know it's uh lots of people discriminated in fact
I think that uh everyone feels discriminated against at one point in their life and uh I'm sure
it doesn't help I'm really sure it doesn't help but you know all I can say is maybe this is the time
where I pull out the XNTV experiment again and suggest you go look at that you know look at television
and and tell me that there is in the world that's a picture that's being painted for you
that is just unrealistic and sometimes we get really upset when it doesn't turn out that way
we don't have the white picket fence you know just just doesn't exist man just does not exist
and now that I'm old I start feeling more and more like you know chill out and just ride the wheels
off this mother fucker we call life
well it's pretty interesting to see uh what rebel and rebellion there is against uh the
Metro sexual moment I'm hearing all kinds of podcasts or doing all kinds of you know manly man type
stuff and you know whatever come on you know and people actually know calling me queer and gay and
light-footed and I don't know I just think it's stuff that's interesting to talk about you know
I never get a chance to share any of these intimate grooming tips with any of my friends so I'm
happy for those of you who do to participate and and you know what this probably a whole bunch of
guys right now who just went out fuck I'm I want to fast forward this man I don't want to do with that but
then of course what they missed is this from Cali hey Adam this is Cali from geek brief.tv thanks for
letting everyone know that we moved to pod show and thanks so much for coming to Miami and with rescue
now on the business I want to share my husband's favorite Metro sexual shaving tip when he showers
he uses a product called sugar scrub you can get it just about anywhere it's a mixture of sugar and
essential oils he robs it on his face when he showers to exfoliate dead skin and the oil protects
his skin from the harshness of the blade he doesn't do it every day but when he does I love touching his face
and it smells good too thanks again Adam thank you Cali Cali from the geek brief geek brief.tv
you've got to see this video podcast what's it I think it's the most recent one number ten
number eleven and all of a sudden she she starts dancing to brother love in the show is like
quite a surprise and
Cali you are truly an asset to podcasting and proud to have you in the pod show family
Mike Travers says Adam just want to share my thoughts on the new five-bladed fusion
razor from Gillette it's brilliant I don't know if it's shaved so close because of the two extra blades
or if it's the vibrations but it blows the mock three away my only gripe is that the precision
blade on the back of the razor cartridge is very easily clogged and doesn't want to keen come clean
without a fight I've had less razor burn on my neck and less five o'clock shadow at the end of the
day as far as I'm concerned the precision razor can clog all I want that's all for knock you up
the good work my traverse forest science major at Penn State University well I gotta agree with you man
I've used this thing now for two days in a row it's nice it really is and of course you know
it has a little more you know robust feel to it they've done they've made a whole bunch of improvements
and I agree that the shave is it's quite close and and it does seem to stay closer for a little bit
longer and the precision yeah I don't really have a lot of nose hair to speak of anything else
you know my sideburns are kind of already groomed so
don't really have a lot of news for it but yeah there's a couple of things that I
removed with it hey so we move on from shaving one of these days and talk about something else
maybe we should talk about shaving parts of our body other than then your face
because believe me women notice that stuff too they really do and curries metro sectional moment
yeah okay well what are we at now we're 41 minutes okay I had two more things that I'm just
gonna just gonna do tomorrow as I said positive music network is down maybe time you hear this show
it's back up but plenty of reason to pull out bob gentries upside down now I've been talking in my
past sleep when I'm waking well my tongue is tight I've been thinking I should leave instead
of waiting for her when the time is right
I've backed the bags under my eyes well I've seen enough to know what it's like
it's turning me upside down tell me what I've done wrong now all I can do is try
when everything's breaking me down looking at the inside out well those rules got changed somehow
maybe it's suicide to stay here and just stick around I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now
until now
I've been walking in my last sleep when I'm waking up well my legs are tight
I've been thinking I should breathe put the window up it's a mare tonight
I've been dreaming I could fly it while I'm free enough but I'm still waiting
it's turning me upside down tell me what I've done wrong now all I can do is try
when everything's breaking me down looking at the inside out well those rules got changed somehow
maybe it's suicide to stay here and just stick around I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now
until now
I've been afraid to just walk out
you know where to stop me now
it's turning me upside down tell me what I've done wrong now all I can do is try
when everything's breaking me down looking at the inside out well those rules got changed somehow
maybe it's suicide to stay here and just stick around
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now
until now
time down tell me what I've done wrong now
when all rules got changed somehow
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now
until now
that's it Charlie's done for today
that's about gentries upside down find him it's a music dot pot show dot com the pot say music network and
coming soon we'll be talking about some cool stuff that we're going to do with
serious satellite radio and with the pot safe music
and i'll be back tomorrow as i said i'm away home tonight flying the virgin's upper class
and uh hopefully that'll give me some rest so i'll be able to get the show done in some
some reasonable hour for you so looking forward to it'll be the thank god it's fried
edition of the Charlie is the daily source code daily source code dot com out of
mcroy dot com and i'll talk tomorrow bye bye