Introducing Adam Curry, here down to his butt crack and layer of field that just don't wash off.
I'm towed three, four, five, six.
Sweetheart, thank you, thank you.
With a $14 bicycle strap to his ass and a Yahoo Map of Gilbert England is front pocket.
He likes to think of himself as peddling into the future.
Adam Curry helped us Sierra Charlie 307 happy new year, everybody.
So it's an elemental, an innocent girl to get all right.
Because now we can't receive so much attention to what it exists.
We have a horn and a side horn and side side.
We'll make him a fish shake.
I'm afraid that the fish will be killed.
Leave us as dead as a kiddo.
And the fish don't seek you a kill.
And the chips you want are the other.
And the world knows the rules.
And I'm walking through inside the sunset clouds.
Every time they release the wheels.
And jealous like you can't make you spend it to me.
A list you never meant to contest for free.
It turns into a sad, annoying sight of times from the hands.
But God never match your plans in my plans.
And I'm walking through inside the sunset clouds.
And jealous like you can't make you spend it to me.
And I'm walking through outside the sunset clouds.
And I'm walking through inside the sunset clouds.
Yeah, now that's the way to start the new year.
Negative tones for Brooklyn, so my troubles begin on safe music network.
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
I'm so 307.
How did the daily source code starting off a new year?
2006, we did it.
We made it all the way through.
I hope you had a great new year, I hope you had a great celebration, and hope you are
ready and pumped for some cool stuff coming up this year.
Whew, oh my goodness, thanks Camille AC for pointing out the negative tone track to me.
Actually, I heard that on the Ultimate Mix podcast.
I was like, what, does something about that song?
I'm not really a guy who plays a lot of indie rock or punk rock, but it was almost
like, there was a piece taken from the Beatles, the, the, the, the, the, the mixed in with,
it almost sounded like hello from YouTube, I don't know, just the, it kind of worked
for me.
Learned a lot of things over the, over the, the passing of the past year and the entrance
of the new year, all kinds of lists showed up everywhere, and all kinds of information,
and the hundred things you found out this year.
That's actually something that I found in, let's see, who sent this to me?
It was, uh, Steve Page sent me this link to the BBC website.
I think what it was, it's exactly a title of this.
I think it's a hundred things.
We didn't know this time last year.
So this was published on Friday the 30th and at number 100, I think it's number 100.
And this is something I didn't know.
Um, it turns out, and I quote from this article, musical instrument shops.
So that's places where you buy guitars and drums and stuff like that.
Must pay an annual royalty to cover shoppers who perform a recognizable riff before they
buy.
Considering a public performance.
So I guess that's true in the, in the UK.
I don't know.
Is that true in the US?
I assure there's lots of people who work at, uh, at music shops who listen to,
I actually I probably should ask big, big mic, he go figure find out for me.
But I was blown away by that.
Of course, it makes sense.
You're playing music.
We've, and I told Patricia this and it's been an ongoing discussion throughout the new
years.
She said, but I don't understand why the, well, that's bullshit.
I said, well, when, you know, because she's a, um, uh, uh,
be my stem rower slash asscat BMI artist.
And, um, and she gets she collects royalties from public performances.
And I went down the list.
Well, if someone plays your music in an elevator, yeah, I want to get paid.
Well, if someone plays your music on the radio, yeah, I want to get played.
If someone plays your music on a podcast.
And then she's like, well, yeah, yeah, I guess so.
I said, well, how much?
So I basically what it boils down to every single time.
As I keep saying, look, you know, these are the problems.
And we've just stopped bothering with them.
There's plenty of talent, plenty of great music out there.
Yeah, it's a fuck.
It's a major bummer that I can't play because what we're listening to today.
Stevie Wonder story, um, and the BBC has a wonderful, um, musical journey
through Stevie's life and, um, and an interview with Stevie Wonder.
Yeah, I'd love to have that on a podcast, but obviously we can't do that.
So she said, yeah, but so that'll never happen again.
How about Glenn Miller said, nope, can't play that either.
I just went going on a list and look, you know, representatives from your community
need to step up and say, this is messed up and we need to come up with something else.
But in the meantime, we're not stopping.
We're just continuing with what we're doing.
And, um, she bought Kumar.
I think I pronounced in that right.
Sent me a link to, um, see, what site is this?
This was pretty funny.
This is, um, it's a website, but it's basically a publication for, um,
for the radio broadcast industry, radio daily news.com named Steve Jobs,
radio person of the year.
For his innovation and podcasting.
Let me see if I can read from the press release.
He was pretty funny.
Oh, there was a specific mention of, of podcasting in here.
Oh, yeah, Steve Jobs has been a champion innovator and producer of technological
products, absolutely true.
His Apple II, my iPad, I put shuffle blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
The introduction of the iPod changed the way that people listen to music
and other audio and video programming iPod spawn podcast and almost overnight.
A new distribution channel for radio entertainment program for radio program was born
with the introduction of replays of sports news information entertainment program content.
That's right.
It continues to grow measureably with more innovations expected to be introduced by
Steve Jobs and Apple in 2006, absolutely fantastic.
My goodness.
Hey, and of course, this says the first show the new year on a serious stars one
of three, the lineup is back and everyone's cracking and rearing to go.
I'm told.
So for the first half hour of this podcast, we'll be simultaneously cast on
the serious satellite radio network.
And I guess it's only what seven more days until Howard Stern arrives.
Hey, you have to think about, by the way, so the goal here is to show you the stars,
so you'll think about what I'm going to do.
Hey, Adam, this is Tokyo Dan hitting the hot clubs and recording the hot indie bands
in Tokyo.
In the background is the live version of dear friend by Diky and Little Wings,
which C.C. played on accident hash number 96 and C.C. really liked them.
Well, if you want to hear the rest of this tune, go over to the pod safe music network
where Diky and I just uploaded some clips from Diky and Little Wings recent live
performance.
Check them out.
We're catching a complete live performance on my podcast.
What's happening in Tokyo at www.whi-o-k-y-o-dot-in-for.
Hello, Adam Curry.
This is Carmen Tyler.
I just wanted to drop you a line and tell you that I hope that you and your family have
the most awesome new year and that this year has been awesome for podcasting and shout
out through the pod father himself and I know that 2006 is going to be really awesome
and podcasting and I'm very honored to be a part of it and very honored to have been
played on your show.
So just have a great awesome and happy new year.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
We are a flank.
We believe in an internet that's safe from virus hissing scammers.
We're Earthlink.
We believe your personal information should be just that personal and we believe your
internet should be a friend, not a foe.
We're Earthlink.
Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do
for you, Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
Hey, are you a professional singer and amateur dramatic screw, a school, a karaoke superstar?
What do you do when you need a professional quality backing track for your performance?
The music without vocals podcast is a regular show that features some of the most recent
backing track productions.
At www.musicwithoutvocals.com, you will find thousands of professional backing tracks available
for instant MP3 download, or you could order a custom karaoke disc containing exactly
the songs you need.
Check out the podcast now at www.musicwithoutvocals.com.
You know, I got Patricia that karaoke microphone for Christmas, so I'm totally enthralled
by the capabilities and possibilities and that was actually it was more like a commercial
than a promo, but it kind of worked both ways, which is why I played it for you.
Quite a community, this karaoke stuff is Peter Jacobs lives in Germany, and he sent me
an email titled the Senseo Conspiracy, and he's come up with something that even had
caught my attention.
Not just for those of you who knew to the show just tuning in for the first time, maybe
maybe you got an iPod for Christmas and you hooked it up and like, oh, what's this podcast
thing?
I love the Senseo Coffee machine made by Philips and Dawa Echiberts.
I love it.
I love the product.
I love the coffee, and then I figured out how to make it just right.
It gives me gastronomitis, and I love to talk about the Senseo whenever I do burp.
But now, PJ from Germany says, I've been listening to your show for a few weeks now.
There's something that keeps bugging me about it, while you seem to struggle from freedom
from the music industry.
You keep advertising the Senseo brand, as someone who really likes coffee and really dislikes
the way the world is shaped by global players.
This is a constant thorn in my ears.
Here's why.
Senseo is a brand of Sarah Lee, which I don't think is true.
I don't, I think it's, well, I could be wrong, but I thought it was Philips, and maybe
they sold it.
Anyway, just as Nestle has Nest Spresso, and craft foods has Tassimo, those brands
are closed.
Non-interoperable formats, that was a great.
We're getting down into, and today, wine a land of coffee.
Just as if Sony was to create a media device that was sold for very cheap money, but
could only play content from Sony or their licensees.
Well indeed, such a device exists.
It's the Sony PlayStation portable.
Here's how it works.
The brand owner sells licenses to the companies who produce the coffee makers, while they
may actually not sell licenses, they may sponsor them for every machine sold.
This way, cheap, system-bound coffee makers are pushed in the market.
Yeah, kind of like razor blades, I guess, which is also an uninteroperable format.
The brand owners may sell licenses for the supplies, like coffee tablets, where they may
choose to keep them monopoly on it, just like with inkjet printer cartridges.
So if you've got one of the cheap machines, this effectively gets you on the hook of a global
player, such as those named above.
Not only can they dictate what you pay for your coffee, and the system coffee is as much
as three times expensive as normal coffee, they can also push competitors out of the
market.
Podcasting is closely linked to freedom, since sale and the likes are linked to closed markets
and control, and if you like the stuff fine, but don't advertise it.
It's bad.
When I presume he means by that they're evil.
Dude, it's coffee.
It's fucking coffee, okay?
Hello Adam, this is Robin, that's Robin from InsightWorks.com, that's INS-YT-W-O-R-K-S.com.
I want to give you my thoughts on advertising and the possibilities with podcasting.
I think it's all about relationships.
Right now, relationships between the buyer and the seller with the intermediary of the advertisers.
There's not much of a relationship other than cash on an individual basis.
We send out an advertisement either over the radio, over TV, trying to induce the buyer to then
make an individual relationship with the seller.
They'll go to whatever source and then buy the product.
We have the capability of building great relationships through podcasting.
If we can aggregate those buyers through the websites, through the show notes, and create
huge numbers of buyers, slash listeners, the marketing folks, the advertising folks are absolutely
going to want to listen.
Let's use a Senseo machine for example, Senseo right now sells on Amazon for roughly $50 a
unit.
If you were to have a capability of aggregating all the listeners or the buyers that might
be interested in buying Senseo machines and say, hey, here's a sliding scale.
If you're not in a rush, sign up to buy a Senseo at either $25 a unit, $30, $35, $40, $45, $50.
All those listeners can then go click on whatever choice they want.
So, yep, I will commit to buy a Senseo machine over the next two months at $35 a unit.
Everybody picks their own price range.
By aggregating all those people together, then pot show could go to the Senseo manufacturer.
We have $10,000 people that are willing to buy Senseo at $25 a unit, or we have an additional
$8,000 to buy at $35 a unit, or we have $2,000 that are willing to do it at $40,000,
and we have three people willing to do it at $49.
If you can take those kind of numbers, go to the Senseo manufacturer.
I think they would fall over themselves to sell 10 or 20,000 units, even though it's
below their retail price.
It's about the relationship between the pot caster and the listener, and the listeners
are the buyers.
I pull in them all together, you can get some big numbers that will have a lot of power.
Love to hear your thoughts on this.
Mr. Robin at InsightWorks.com, that's IMSYTWORKS.com.
Thanks, Rob.
Thanks so long, Adam.
Hey, Owens.
Tailwinds.
Back at your buddy.
Okay, so that was very complicated.
Founded a lot like some of those internet bubble companies that would use the power of aggregating
consumer demand.
Yeah, that works to a certain degree, actually it works very well to a certain degree,
but it's a whole business by itself, and just putting my pod caster hat on here for a second,
which I do all the time, boy, do we get into some heated arguments when I put the pod
caster on at the office?
I don't want to any.
That's too complicated.
I like the idea of, excuse me, do I have to say it?
I like the idea of turning the tables around, and indeed, if we start acting like these
relationships that we have with our listeners, that they really are that special, and there
is something much bigger going on than just what you can achieve with spot advertising.
Then we have to covet it.
Then we also have to stand up for it and say, look, we're going to only advertise
what we want to advertise, we're going to, and by the way, the numbers work out so nicely
in this, you know, what I was thinking about this a lot over the holiday, I think that
was really brought us all down when it comes to the traditional broadcasts that we see
now.
Radio television, radio television predominantly, is that, you know, the only way for the, for the
media companies to make more money is to either a raise the prices on advertising, which
is, wow, you know, that's like, yeah, if, if they could, they would, but there's just,
you know, that's been hammered out, that's what these industries really drive on is that,
that price, you know, what are we paying for eyeballs or ear drums, they either, so
they can either raise the price or they can, they can broadcast more commercials, repetition
basically, and that is the fundamental difference between what we're doing in podcasts and
just an example, because it'll, it'll go to vlogging and all that other stuff is that we
have no limitation on time, you know, hey, you know, you just make more shows, more choice,
that's what, that's what I see, when I look at the directories, I said to myself, oh my God,
look at that, you know, tens of thousands of, of stations, something that's just not possible
in any radio market, any terrestrial, either based radio market, anywhere in the world, it's fantastic,
I love it. So we'll be talking a lot more about that special relationship between advertisers,
podcasters, and their audience, and how that's, how we're, yeah, we're going to try and make
it work this year, that will definitely be high on the mission statement for me. Quick update about
my parents, I spoke to my mom this morning, and I actually didn't get to speak to her,
New Year's Eve, because she went to bed early. So Friday, she starts with her chemo,
instead of the two to three sessions, they said, well, we'll start you off with six sessions,
so that was kind of a bummer, and I guess just, you know, keeping positivity up is the, is the best
we can do. I really, it sucks so fucking bad because, you know, it's, it's one thing when I'm here,
I can just pop across the channel and go help route or visit or whatever, but since I'm in San Francisco,
a lot too, that makes it a little more complicated. So I'm going to try and schedule stuff with my sister,
so that there will always be one of us around. And of course, she's got Bob, who's a fantastic,
you know, he's, he's really helping her sail through all this crap. And both my sisters went to visit
my dad in the hospital, it turns out that, oh, and I have to pronounce this properly, hold on a second,
who sent me this, I got an email about, from Neil, the acronym TIA, please, in the states,
we never call it a TIA, we call it a TIA, and I guess that Neil, what Neil, Neil is for 20 years,
has been ultrasound and vascular technologist and now a radiology computer nerd. Okay,
pronunciation correction accepted. So it's a TIA, actually it wasn't a TIA, it turned out it was
really just a small stroke. So he is still in the hospital and will be there probably for the
rest of this week and things not going too well on that front because he's lost 40% of his left,
the use of his left side. Oh my goodness. Hey, here at the cottage, we're all healthy, okay?
We're feeling good here. Say it with me now. Yodsey. Yep. I'm bringing it back. Yodsey.
There will be Yankee Alpha Delta Charlie, yet another drum cadence. We started off today with Zack
Winick. Adam sent you a request of drum cadences. Thought I'd tap into my archives. The first track
is a remix of a cadence from Valencia High School in Valencia, California home of six flags magic
mountain. It's done by a band called Lotus Fear. The band unfortunately no longer exists, but
he does have permission to hand off to me to play it. Sounds kind of fuzzy, but I'll risk it. Okay.
The name of the song is Rump Bump Bump.
All right, from the Valencia High School watching band.
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right
All right, all right, all right,
something going on over there and feel free to send me your drum cadences for the
Yatsi yet another drum cadence. Oh, that means we need another jingle for that segment totally
into the jingles for segments these days. And I'd ask all of you to send me in suggestions from
the pop music network to play on the show and I'm getting a lot of them. Thank you very much
picking out the ones that, you know, so you like them and I listen to it if I like it,
then play it on the show. It's pretty simple. And I also talked about that I thought in 2006,
we'll, we'll definitely see music videos being created for songs from the potsafe music network.
Excuse me, CC Chapman from accident hash immediately contacted me as he does and pointed me to his
random food. Now I don't know if he, if it's cool to give out the link, so he'll have to put that
or let me know or put it on his show notes or whatever. And he's done a couple of videos for some
potsafe artists and they're really good. It's really, and I was like blown away. And then to hit
me that in order to create a music video, very much, you know, the way we've been putting together
stuff like potsafe or peas, the way the Christmas carol projects that were multiple podcasts,
Christmas carol stories, how they were put together, you really only need, well, first you need
the music, then you need and believe me, this is exactly how the MTV videos are conceptualized.
So you need someone to shoot the performance footage, because you need the band either.
You need to, usually, not all videos, but usually you have some kind of performance footage.
Then you have, we call the conceptual footage. You know, this is the, the Arty Farty shit that we
make around it or whether that's done with video editing or whether that's done with, with effects
or or with some other story line that that we've through. And then of course you need editing.
So you really need to find, if you have one of those skills to find two other people, and of
course, the willingness of the band, and then we can really turn out some great shit.
Oh, before I forget, people on the satellite listening to this show right now, the Daily
Source code, it's all part of pod shows line up. And next, we have Pacific Coast Hellway for you
followed by an hour of the Angry Jewish Lesbian Madge Weinstein. I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Thanks for listening. While we continue.
Right. So now the question is, do people care? I think they would care about about music videos.
I really enjoyed looking at the three that CC had up on his feed. And I think there's something
there. So I'm just opening up the Florida suggestions. Something else I found while I was
checking out the pod safe music network. Hey, Agent, just refresh a couple of times.
Do they know the songs that show up have been played at least once? So there's some validity
to play it in. I scan them. And I really like what I heard on this one. It's from Sad Light,
from 2004. It's just another girl on D.S.C.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No
No. No. No. No.
So, none? No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
And then going along
The whole family came back
Putting aside my law
Time dies, time dies
Little and again restless
And now I see you, baby
Break the sign
They tell you why
Neither
Can't see
She's just another girl
Just another girl
She's another girl
That he's dead
Can't attract love
Can't elect ya
She's my girl
She can't get show
Can't to take love
Can't get enough viennent
Together just in all the way
So just in all the way
Just in all the way
Together Just in all the way
From satellite just another girl from using.tomutiot.com
Just wrapping up a couple of things
Before we wind up the first show the new year something that I had missed something with my Gmail filters screwed it up
Adrian peg sent me a fantastic recording of Podsay for peace if every day could work Christmas
That was played on the BBC in the context of Podsay for music and there was some interview. I was really good
I was on I think radio five
So I just wanted to make mention of that and one of my new years resolutions
I don't have a lot of them because you know, and a new year's kind of came and went
You know, yeah, we celebrated but it was your weird home. We just quiet
Christina by the way went to her first new year's party. So we picked her up around 1-15
Oh boy, um, yeah, she had a great time by the way
It was you know a little frightening from mom and dad as you can imagine
One of my new years resolutions. I'm gonna get my audio book up and rolling now
This is not a story or actually it's a series of stories that I did not write myself
But I've enjoyed I enjoyed the stories immensely when I was a kid
And it turns out there in the public domain
And I found it on that the Gutenberg project and
I will be contributing to LibriVox which we talked about last year. Oh sounds good. Doesn't last year
Which is the open source audio book collection? I guess we'd call it and I'm so loving this because I actually have a downloaded a book
That I've been listening to and there is absolutely no difference between what these guys are doing and
What um
Audible is doing and I'm a a customer of audible
But sometimes you know and facts more often than not
I'll be pretty disappointed with the quality or with not just the audio quality
They've they seem to have gotten that pretty much you know on track now
But if it's not the audio quality then it's just the the general performance quality of the of the readers or
The speaker some of course are fantastic
But you know, I listen to this stuff that is done by quote amateurs and the only reason they're quote amateurs because they're not being paid for it
There's no difference in quality in fact some of it the quality is superior and so is the performance quality
And I think it's great and
You know to be able to to enjoy these stories and to be able to pass them on and I'm very excited about doing that
So I look soon I'll keep you up the speed but that is one of my resolutions
I just have to kind of you know take the time to do it because it does take time to and I want to figure out how to do it
And am I gonna do different voices am I going to do it all from you know
I just got to figure all that stuff out one of the resolutions though and
Speaking of liberal box I was very excited as you know
I'm excited about the whole idea, but I was even more excited when I received the following audio feedback. Hey Adam
This is Tom Maris. I have talked you before
I just thought I'd drop you an audio comment about what you said in the DSC
You were talking about liberal box and
So great service
Great thing I've been trying to start up a open source audio books kind of a service for years now and nobody's been interested
But finally somebody's done it and
It's worked so and I'm gonna record something for it, which is I'm gonna do it because I'm a
I'm a university student study philosophy and one of my specialisms is in nature
So I'm gonna do I'm probably gonna do one of the public domain translations of nature and and put that up
In English of course, but most of the amount public to manage is only two I think which are
One of them has already been done by the liberal box people
So that's pretty cool. I just thought I'd say you asked about getting stuff in OPML and
You asked you receive I put together an
OPML file
I've heard about it
opened up my OPML editor
typed it up and
Before the show was even finished. I put it online
You can get it at host them to OPML.org slash Tom Maris slash Librevox dot OPML and
You can stick it in indie pot or you can
Subscribe to it whatever you want to do with it. I'll try and keep it up to date. I'm basing it on the RSS feed
So when the RSS feed is updated I'll update the OPML shortly afterwards
It may take a few hours to get around doing it, but it'll get done eventually
Anyway, I love the show. I'm looking forward to
whole years filled with a daily source code entertainment and information and
All the other good stuff. I've come to expect from from the podfather himself
Cheers. Bye. Well, all right Tom. Thank you very much. Fantastic. I immediately copied and pasted the link put it into indie potter.org
Right there on the homepage. I don't control the audio books node
So I just plopped it underneath and said audio books from Librevox
I hopefully the noted editor of audio books will
We'll add the Librevox stuff and we'll add that link until then. I'll just keep this one on the homepage
It's kind of the way it works with these open source directories or distributed directories and
By the way, in the coming weeks because this week is going to be completing code and
The week of the ninth will be testing. We're going to open up the podsafe the pod
Forget about it. We're opening up goddamn it. We're opening up our doors
We're going to start slowly, but we're getting there and of course
audio books are
totally valid
use of pod casting as
Anything that you want to do in audio essentially just match it up right there's no right or wrong way to do this stuff
Okay, everybody. So
little little secret today. I did the whole show in my in my house code stolen from the
names that hotel
The hotel that looks like a sailboat
there in as in
Saudi Arabia. Come on
Burshalar up. There you go. So it's a nice long. That's why I stole a nice long house code and then I have my bear legs
Underneath that and then my black ogs. Oh, yeah, so stylish. Maybe I should go out of your view really quick