A Domain Registration is a gift that keeps on giving for all the geeks in your life.
The newer shot hit GoDaddy.com.
Listen to this podcast for a special code that you can use to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Have your attention, please.
Do not try to remain calm.
This show is going into motion.
That is the worst code number.
Five hundred and forty.
In a world where women wear comfortable shoes and nothing else.
It's the daily source code episode five thirteen.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm on fire.
I could barely stand myself.
In it doubts I had.
I left them on the show.
I'm on a mission.
Ain't nothing going to hold me back.
Tomorrow when you hear about what I did.
You've got to follow and have a heart attack.
I found the sweet baby as pretty as you want to be.
By the end of the night.
She's gonna be a means with me.
I'm around eleven thirty.
I'm stopping by her crib.
Tomorrow when I do get a story.
You won't believe the things I did.
I'm gonna show her my old face.
Wow!
I got my best slacks.
And my shirt's looking fly.
Ain't no way she gonna say no.
With the way I look tonight.
I'm gonna love this.
I know she's gonna tell her friends.
But I get to a place I'll wait for right time.
It's time to slip in some blind slid
I'm gonna show her my old face
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
It took me a little while to figure it out, but yeah, that's what he's singing.
I'm going to show her my old face.
His name is Bo Halle, he's from Georgia.
And he's got the most piercing blue eyes I've seen in a long, long time.
If Prince had a car wreck with the Rolling Stones and Stevie Ray Vaughn, the resulting candy bar would be called...
UNAs, Bo Halle's new city, which he calls the soundtrack for mating Toronto Sorrows.
Okay.
It's on the pod save music networks where you can find it.
Show notes.
We'll lead you there at DailySourceCode.com.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
It's Thursday.
It is episode 513 of the DailySourceCode coming to you once again from Northern California, from San Francisco, the Curry condo.
So what is up with San Francisco?
San Francisco, what is up with you?
It's weather is shite.
It's been raining.
It's like Seattle.
It is literally like Seattle here.
As since we've had the company since I've had the condo, I don't think I've seen it this bad.
Maybe I just wasn't here.
This time Christmas last year, but nasty.
Thursday.
It's early once again.
I gotta tell you this is just about the time when I start feeling ready to go back home.
To be back on a...
Just a different schedule.
This early morning stuff is very difficult for me.
And we've had so many logistical challenges.
I didn't mention this for some very obvious reasons.
But yesterday, Patricia left early in the morning.
You know, that was the whole life I got my medicine thing.
Which worked out fine, by the way.
She turned out she was only a half an hour later in the studio than if she'd taken her original flight.
Go figure that.
But Christina was actually all alone in the house yesterday.
This was a big, big, big...
Well, I don't want to call it a test.
I want to call it a challenge.
When you leave your kid alone overnight, and of course the neighbors were very well aware of the situation.
But neither I could be there nor Patricia and her grandparents arrived this afternoon.
So, you know, I knew that she would be there full overnight all by herself.
And it's really one of the most frightening things for her parent.
Even though, you know, she's 16.
She can take care of herself.
She can certainly take care of herself out on the streets and in the city.
At least I think so.
She seems to be staying on a trouble.
But it was, you know, so anyway, so I stayed up extra late to call to make sure that she was up in the morning.
You K-time, and you know, she was up and about and getting ready for school and everything was okay.
And, you know, I just didn't really have a very restful night to be quite honest.
It was like, oh, my baby.
I know I'd promised you, well, promises a big word.
I said that what I'd like to do today is I'd like to go through everything that Podshow is doing.
And as I sat down this morning at 6.15 a.m.
To start writing it all down, I realized that that preparing even for an hour
would just not do anything justice.
And so I really want to take some time to map everything out because we are doing an incredible amount of stuff.
You know, we basically have four networks that we've now integrated into one.
If you look at the music flowing from the Podsate Music Network.
If you look at shows, all of the shows on the network, thousands of shows on the network.
Over 200, we produce co-produce or finance.
And they're all making money, which is fantastic.
You know, so I'd like to talk to you about that.
We, of course, have videos, which we're just adding.
We have some announcements to make, and we have some stuff to unveil in January.
In January, maybe the beginning of February, but I presume January.
So that's something that I wanted to talk about.
How about the people?
And what is it going to look like on television?
You know, all of this stuff is I really have to sit down.
In fact, I know a great time when I'll be sitting down for about, let me think, ten hours when I fly home Sunday.
Normally, fly home Saturday, but I'm flying home a day later.
So when I hope fly home Sunday, I'm going to really prepare this.
And I'll just do a real sit down.
It's not probably not going to be a show that everyone will want to listen to,
but those who are interested.
I'm sure you will enjoy it.
So I just have to get through, you know, I just have to organize my thoughts because it's so much.
I say the sale with some splendor.
Hey, wait a minute.
Aren't we, uh, there's another, uh, another hell is it?
I got another promotion starting tomorrow.
It's for a movie.
Hold on a second.
Let me just see.
I'm not supposed to talk about it until tomorrow.
What is it to stop the yard?
That's a new movie, which is coming out.
What January 12th, stop the yard.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, it's centers around, uh, a troubled youth from Los Angeles attending the historically Black
Truth University in Atlanta, Georgia.
When adapting to his new environment, it proves very difficult.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Okay, so I get it.
So we got a special podcast.
We want you to listen to.
I'll talk about that tomorrow.
So when I burp tomorrow, at least I'll know what the hell I have to promote.
Hey, it's Thursday.
You know what that usually means, don't you?
It's time once again to firm up the behind.
Because you know when you hit 40 years, where they got to work on that ass.
Amy.
Hey, baby, how you doing?
Hello.
You actually disappointed that last week was not a killer workout.
Yeah, it was kind of easy, you know?
That makes my day dump in the next two weeks.
Oh, no.
Jump and kick.
No, name me.
I didn't really mean it like that.
Today we're going to be jumping.
So get your mic situated.
You can space as plenty of room to each side.
Yeah, sure.
Take a deep breath and get ready.
Do I have to put down the spliff?
Is that the point?
Okay.
And the tea.
You're going to start with feet together.
Hands at your side.
I want to still put down the tea.
Okay.
Now leave it to your left leg and jump a couple of feet to your left.
Landing with your left knee slightly bent and your right leg lifts it just a little bit.
So it's not touching the ground.
Kind of like a leap and lizard thing like good.
Now jump a few feet to your right.
Letting the right leg land with knee bent and the left leg follow.
But keeping the left foot a couple inches off the ground.
What do I do?
Good.
Now back and forth to each side.
Eight times.
Eight jump.
Squeeze your butt.
It's squeezing the butt.
Make sure you land with your knee bent.
I hit the, I hit the bankers rack.
Breathe.
Faster.
Oh baby, faster.
I don't hear you counting.
Oh, six.
Amy, oh, faster.
Oh, that was fun.
You did a good job.
Well, I'll let you get back to your show.
I'm off to do some test runs for my video show Fit Life that will hopefully launch
in January.
Last week, I gave you a hard time about avoiding me in town.
This week, it's all my fault.
I'm getting ready to leave for home and haven't been to the office.
Well, where are you going?
I will see you at the Christmas party, which I will be attending.
Not as Amy Mac, but as podcast alley wife.
Oh.
So until next time.
I'm doing this in front of the big open window.
We're not the open window, but the, I have these floor to ceiling windows all around the
condo.
And there's the building this rink and hill tower, which is going to be the largest building
west of the Mississippi, 70 stories high.
And there's probably like 15 construction workers all looking at me going like,
look at that boy.
That boy's not right.
That's not right.
It reminds me someone sent me an awesome podcast.
Let me just see if I can find the notes on it here.
Here it is.
This is from John Hamilton.
Adam, you've got to hear the impression this podcast is doing you.
Doing a few of its funny is all hell.
I know you're always looking for fresh and different things when it comes to podcasting.
You have to hear this.
Okay.
What is it?
Oblivion.lipsin.com.
Hold on.
I just got to load this up.
Hold on a second.
Where is it?
Here we go.
It's, I don't know.
It's this show number three or four.
This, the accents are all off, but some of this shit is really funny.
Check it out.
Hello and welcome to another episode of road trip to oblivion.
Today's episode takes place in the curry condo.
Adam Curry is taking one too many hits on the curry crack rock.
And decides to do an improv show where he does two reviews on iTunes.
Both of them on the show, it fights with Don.
You know, the fact check from Don and Drew.
Anyways, the story behind this is that Jason just got on the road.
Hey, hey, hey mother fucker.
Lay off my girlfriend, okay?
Nothing to talk about because this is his first and second day out.
He doesn't even done one delivery yet.
But he wanted to do a show for you addicted mother fuckers to the show.
And we just wanted to extend our gratitude to everyone who was download the show from Lipsin.
There's a lot of downloads considering that the fucking shit doesn't even work on iTunes yet.
Fuck you.
And you stupid cock sucking pieces shit.
Run by fucking Steve Jobs and your fucking pants.
Hide up to your fucking crotch and your balls hanging down like a fucking camel's neck.
Fuck you asshole.
Fix my fucking feed shit ball.
I'm telling you, this is outrageous shit.
You're late.
Here I'm flicking the light.
Oh, that's a good shit.
Adam, put down the goddamn crack.
I'm getting ready to take your proud out.
We got dead bitch.
Can't you just fucking wait?
I can't do a goddamn thing until I'm fucking big out of my goddamn mind.
Ah, but if I'm wrong then, I have bad to find again.
And show you my base content.
Fine, what my base?
What do you say base curtains?
Oh, man, this is bad.
Okay, you know what?
You should not have a fuck of a buzz bitch.
That's wrong.
Now let's get in when it's goddamn proud out already.
I've got to go in the bathroom and shave my pussy.
You know what Patricia?
That picture that you keep continuously painting this morning.
It's getting more and more scarier.
And it doesn't even matter how much fucking curry crack rock.
I got runnin' through my veins.
Alright.
Oblivion.lipsin.com.
That's pretty funny.
That was alright.
Let me see.
That's a more stuff in the notebook here.
Ah, let me see.
What was this?
Ah, I'm like Feldebore.
I'm sure this has been asked to you more.
And once it's a possible to put Patricia's music on the pot set music network.
I made it know it's part of some record companies.
They probably start to go bonkers if you suggested blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Okay.
Now we can't do that actually.
Can't legally do it.
Anything that we've done and produced.
We can't put up anything that we own the masters to.
Ah, and I'm sure I could get permission from these record companies to put it up on the pot set music network.
But who the hell wants to go through that?
Ah, here's it.
I moved from Holland to Vancouver.
Seven years ago experienced one earthquake.
I'm in the middle of finally creating an earthquake kit.
So when an earthquake hits, I actually have food for three days in water and cash, etc.
My question is, would it not be an interesting topic to discuss or get feedback from your listeners?
I mean, your curry condo was on the 24th floor of a building situated on an earthquake central.
Have you given any thought about what you would do in case of an earthquake?
Ah, and I read that email.
I thought, you know, that is kind of interesting because no doubt the, you know,
whenever I would come to San Francisco in the past before we, you know, had headquarters here,
you'd always think about it.
Even Los Angeles.
Los Angeles or San Francisco.
You always think, oh, man, I hope the big one doesn't hit well.
I'm here.
And that goes away pretty quick.
I haven't, this is really the first time in at least a year.
I think I've thought about it.
And honestly, I don't have an earthquake kit ready.
And I really don't know what happened up here on the 24th floor.
There's a lot of big buildings that they've built in this,
and I'm in the financial district right near right near the Bay Bridge.
And I don't know.
As I said, I'm looking out the window.
I see another 70, I think it's going to be 60 or 70 story building that they're,
that they're erecting.
So I presume that these things are earthquake proof.
Is that what everyone says?
Yeah, it's famous last words, I guess, right?
But I should have an earthquake kit.
So what do I need?
Jim shoes, flashlight, water, pop tarts.
I don't like that.
Hi, I don't mean it's GD here from GD's by size bonus.
I know what I need.
Well, they're one of the organizers of podcast.
Now, unfortunately, on Wednesday 29th November,
you were unable to make it down to the purple turtling camp,
and then could you play Mr. Mum?
But never mind.
All is not lost.
Artists.
the first past life, breach of a new face of rip-bub in the form of the Union Streetrunner
as they take the stage of the Burble Turquered Camden, what is...punfest.
So if you can get to Budfest, you're not going to miss out.
You can listen to all three sets we call it live, from your listening pleasure.
Exclusively to Potsho, delivering that work.
Yes, this is Punfest Live.
Go to www.punfestlive.com
www.puncho.com
Right on fest.
We need the best live music.
On fest.
Well, plot this.
I wish it could have been there.
Sounds good, man.
I'll put it into my on-the-go channel on Pod Show.
So it'll show up on my Nokia.
And then I can use the Bluetooth headphones.
I really got a system with that.
I'm really digging that.
How I talked about that enough about the Nokia.
It's completely replaced by Blackberry.
The E61.
Which includes the Wi-Fi.
So Nokia has this awesome podcasting.
Well, it's not really awesome.
It really does the job.
There's a lot left to be desired.
But because you got Wi-Fi, essentially, you know,
I have a couple channels set up and I have one that's called on the go.
Set it up in my Pod Show Plus account.
You can actually see what's on that channel if you go to Adam.podshow.com.
And you look at channels I have.
You can see what I collected in there.
And so I just fire up the application before I leave the house.
It connects on Wi-Fi.
So it's nice to zip you fast.
And I just say, go get everything new.
And usually within like 10 minutes it'll have everything.
Depending on the bandwidth where I am.
The bandwidth at the condo is fucking rocking, by the way.
What was I gonna say?
Yeah, this is it, man.
I'm so tired that I just can't keep my thoughts straight.
I didn't get any email from John Glasscock.
And he did some analysis, which I do appreciate.
He said the, the, the jazel guy who called yesterday said the jazel has been missing for four days.
He says he ran both voices through an analyzer.
He says, well, I'm not an expert.
They appeared to be a match.
CSI, CSI podcaster.
Cool, John.
But he does say that, you know, there is some cause for concern.
You should post her picture and alert the authorities.
Uh, I don't think I can post the picture.
She sent to me.
And by the way, I don't think it really help anyone
I identify her unless you're in an interesting situation with her.
Uh, I, I'm still not convinced.
I don't know.
I'm just not convinced.
That's what I mean.
Um, so we'll see what happens.
We'll see if we hear for us.
It was his name, Nick.
We'll see if we hear back from Nick.
He did say, where is it?
Oh, shit.
I got rid of it.
Anyway, so I mean, we'll see what we hear.
I didn't even hear anything.
Nothing on the voicemail.
Since that last call.
Uh, but I, I don't know.
I don't think I should start up anything.
You know, if she's missing, then I think Nick is the guy who should
uh, who should call the authorities.
So I try that test with you by giving you some voicemail dial tones.
And if you hold up the mouthpiece of a standard telephone,
it won't work with your cell phone.
It was standard phone.
And you need an outside line.
So that would be your house phone or your office phone,
if you know, dial an outside line.
And you hold it up to the speaker while I play the,
the, the, the, the, the, the, this called the DMTF tones,
it's the touch tones and it actually dials the number.
And I'm amazed how many people find this amazing.
Yeah, we used to have phone dialers.
And in fact, this is how you, you use this basic,
uh, method of dialing as a, it was a way to hack into public
phone systems back in the day even.
You could completely circumvent all kinds of, you know,
charging mechanisms.
This has been around for a long, long time.
Of course, with cell phones,
um, you don't really use it anymore.
Except maybe you use those tones when, um,
um, you're in some kind of electronic system,
and they ask you to, you know, select a menu item.
But I don't think it's really used to dial anymore.
Because, you know, you dial the number first,
then you hit send or call or whatever on your phone,
and then it dials the number.
Until you don't even hear the DMTF tones.
Because, of course, they're not actually being transmitted.
But I did get some interesting info on this.
Uh, this is from John Kitts.
A couple of people sent me this.
Uh, they googled on the use of dial tones.
It is a US federal trade commission.
It was the US federal trade commission that issued the so-called
900 rule, which in 308 decimal 3G states,
electronic tones and advertisements.
It states that, and I quote,
the provider of pay-per-call services is prohibited from using
advertisements that emit electronic tones that can automatically
dial a pay-per-call service.
Huh.
Well, of course, it wasn't a pay-per-call,
other than your regular, you know, provider charges.
So I guess I'm okay there, but that's pretty interesting.
So you can advertise using those numbers
as long as you don't charge for the call.
Hmm.
Well, I have one for you, folks.
Uh, it's different.
I decided, what are you going to call this?
The demon dialer.
There you go.
This is the demon dialer, and today's demon dialer,
and of course, you're all going to participate.
Uh, this is someone who I haven't heard from in, uh,
in a couple of weeks, and I'm wondering why I haven't heard from him.
And so I think you should call him and ask him that.
Now, of course, what you really want to do is, is you want to record what you're,
you know, if you're going to call this person, record it,
so you can send it in and let us all, you know,
listen to how it went and when you found out who it was,
how the conversation went.
So the demon dialer today is as follows.
For the US, hold up your, the mouthpiece of your phone
to the speakers right now.
Of course, you can always put it on pause
while you get all that shit together.
Make sure you have an outside line.
And remember, you're going to say,
hi, this is the demon dialer.
When the person answers, and you'll say,
how can we have and heard from you for a while?
Now, that's only if you're in the US.
If you're outside of the US in Europe,
here's your number.
Uh,
folks on serious satellite radio,
just move on.
I hope that works.
I hope that someone records a phone call when they call this guy
and say, hey, it's the demon dialer.
Where the hell are you, asshole?
Of course, we have a regular phone numbers open,
which you don't need the demon dialer for to access.
So if you're a Brit, that is the number you want to be calling in the UK.
So you want to keep that nice little jingle-med-lea memorise.
If you're in the US, clear your brain.
Here comes your song.
One, two, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven.
Hello Adam, it's Hugh from Pharaohs,
where it is Wednesday, 13th.
Early evening, I'm not sure.
I haven't heard you haven't heard the latest source card.
I'm not sure if you're back from San Francisco.
But just to say that we are currently
is gone for the rest of the week at Pharaohs,
with our twin squirrel helicopter,
with the train modeling laser on it,
and would be delighted to see you if you happen to drop by.
And I will show you how it all works.
Also, you've got a neighbor in the hangar now.
Somebody has come to live with us at Pharaohs,
with a wakeo, which is an utterly, utterly gorgeous aircraft.
An American built open cockpit by plane.
It's smaller than the steam and that got gorgeous.
Anyway, hope to see you.
Otherwise, hope San Francisco is okay.
And if not, enjoy Christmas and speech in the new year by.
All right, Hugh.
You know, there's so many cool people in aviation.
And this will be one of my projects for 2007.
I really am going to do this.
I want to get my flying fools show up and running.
It's all about aviation and the people that make it happen.
You come to these airports, you landed airports.
All over the world, because I have flown all over the world.
And you meet the most interesting people with the most interesting stories
with the most beautiful aircraft with, you know,
obsessions, love, disappointment, sorrow.
It really, the emotions run the gamut.
And in aviation, it's, I find it a really beautiful thing to see the passion that goes
into that.
So my plan is to do a video show called flying.
I think it's a flying fool or flying fools.
Flying fools.
Flying fool.
It could be Adam Curry flying fool.
But that sounds more like I'm doing stunts or, or flying fools with Adam Curry.
Or flying fools.
Was there David?
Niven.
Or flying fools.
Was Richard Attenborough.
There you go.
Because, you know, look, look at the content that could go create.
God, I need a producer for that.
I really do.
All right.
One last song.
This is going to be something that is not on the pod safe music network.
It's sent to be by my friend.
David at Polito, known as that guitar man in New York.
Of course, he's winding down his, his park appearance.
I think he actually has wound down the park appearance,
is because now it's the winter.
Unless so we get some kind of beautiful.
Maybe an Indian summer type day, all of a sudden.
You probably won't see him in the park, but he's doing.
I love the company his podcast every single day.
It's, it's really a joy to listen to.
And let me just find the email that he sent to me because I want to set it up right.
Uh, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop.
Let's see.
So he did his year-end concert.
And I'm so bummed that, you know, I was out here.
Actually, the six, I was in,
I was back in the UK, I think.
And we would have loved to have streamed it live,
but we just couldn't get any of that together with,
with a new pod show plus launch and all that stuff.
Um, anyway, when David does a gig,
he, uh, he like, especially a big gig.
He likes to feature the, feature the men and women that, you know,
are behind him that are playing, uh, the band, essentially.
And this year gave a solo to what he says is one of the most brilliant song
writers he's ever worked with.
Uh, also one of the purest rock and roll piano players in town.
His name is George Wortsbach.
And, uh, he sent me the recording.
I think you'll like it because George has a pretty cool song for those of you who are married.
But now, I'm going to leave this stage.
We're going to leave this stage.
And I'm sorry, but you're going to have to hang out for just a little while with him.
I'm sorry, too.
Well, thank you.
I was waiting for them to turn a lights down because you people frighten me.
I've been married for a little over 23 years.
More or less to the same woman.
I say that because in the 23 years or so that we've been married, um,
she's changed, she's grown, she's evolved.
So, bye.
But mostly because she makes me.
And in that time, I've never, um, I've never written a love song.
And so, you're about to hear the first love song I've ever written.
Thank you.
You might want to save your judgment.
Most men live lives in quiet desperation, but not me.
My desperation's loud.
And so it is, I'm taking your rejection like a man, a man who's freaking out.
I admit, I have my flaws, I get drunk and with a bed.
But look beyond that, and I'm sure that you would love me.
I'm a gentle man by far, but if you break my heart, I'll shoot your puppy.
My love is real, so is this pistol in my hand.
And it's really loaded.
You love your dog, but I wonder, will you love him more than me when his heads exploded?
I am not the violent kind, I won't even swat that fly, but all this love stuff really makes my head claw.
I'm a Christian man in part, but if you break my heart, he's a dead dog.
Whoa, funny day, what can I say about the way you make me laugh when you told that dog to sick me?
You clever girl, you call the cops while I was wiping off the drops of blood from where he bit me.
What's it been? Three weeks since I've been in, and today they're going to release me.
The doctor said, all the voices in my head are in my head, and she that was easy.
And I know now I was wrong, and you won't see me no more, because I'm sedated with an order to restrain me.
Oh, but if some night by chance, in some cosmic circumstance, we should cross paths while your dog is sniffing round and finds me hiding behind your couch.
Mining my own business, and you scream so loud, you startle him, and he begins to attack me.
So I fire with three or four warning shots above his head, but I hit you instead.
No one can blame me.
George Worsbach, live with David Ecolito, you know, thank God for podcasting man.
You never, ever, ever hear this shit on the radio.
Otherwise, it would become just a lost art form, only to be performed in theaters, and we just never hear of it again.
So thank God for that.
All right, tomorrow we'll be food bar Friday. I've seen some suggestions coming for songs.
I'm looking for more twisted sisters, even sent in their ID.
So everyone, did you see him last night? They were on Leno? I think?
Yeah, Leno, or was it Letterman? No, I think was Leno.
Twisted sister doing a song that's on the Podsake Music Network, the Christmas song.
I love it. Okay, so tomorrow we're going to have a good jam. We have some good times.
And in the meantime, if you got anything to send to me, add them at podshow.com.
Or of course, if you're looking for stuff that was that appeared in today's program, daily source code.com.
And if you're looking for a great deal on domain name, well, definitely go to godaddy.com.
Use checkout code DSC3 for an awesome deal on any domain name for a year.
Take care, everybody, bye-bye.
Another Podshow Podcast. Stick it in your ear.