Potio is pleased to bring you the following killer content direct from the all new feature rich potio dot com get it play it dig it
Delta Sierra Charlie Quattro Chettano
16 million dollars worth of airplane strap to my ass
Then the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into the future
This is Delta Sierra Charlie for nine form my name is boy at
Yakshimash Adam Keri
I like you
In my country, man can go up women and eat this normal
So can I go Patricia Patricia Mr. Keri
What we feel
To me
So
Day by day free to choose a life
Putting people's heads at the top
There's no fuss in situation
Change in the heart of just one
Don't give it out
To the face
And the force around us
We
Between the end and the outside
So take a stand
In this place
Because we're the building of our own future
Just know my love
Day by day free to choose a life
It's better for more
So take a stand
In this place
Because we're the building of our own future
Just know my love
Day by day free to choose a life
It's better for more
So take a stand
In this place
Because we're the building of our own future
Just know my love
Day by day free to choose a life
It's better for more
Is it just me or does this song have that?
That very distinct holiday vibe to it
Sure sounds like it's a me
Building our own future
How this is how it sounds
And this is the daily source code
Adam Curry
That guy so smart
He knows how it works
Send out pros to everybody
And don't play the song
Absolutely
It's Friday everybody
We are completely food bar
I speak not only for myself
But about 58 other people who work at pod show
Been completely
Well, they've just been boss the wall
All the way to the wire for the past 30
I'm sorry, 56 hours
Give or take a couple
As I look now at my sky presence
Indicators still lots of engineers online
Even though they're on well
I guess they may they may live in San Francisco
But there's certainly no longer on San Francisco time
And so we're all kind of fucked up beyond repair
But things are going well
It is Friday it is the daily source code episode
Four nine or four coming to you from the Curry Cottage
And the affluent suburb of Surrey
Yesterday of course we had the lady Patricia
So yeah when I got one lady on
I can't really have another one to close by
Amy Mack
It's here too
Trim the ens
The next time the lady comes on it'll be great
Adam
Amy Mack
Hey baby
I'm sure you've heard enough of my voice this week
But again today
Never enough
Never enough Amy
I've had as much fun watching the process
I did hosting it
Real fantastic
And everyone has had an exhausting week
But that means that more than ever before
We need to ask your son
Yes
What are we doing
Rive your wireless and get ready
Oh, okay
Hold on a second
All right
All right, I'm ready
Doing side lunges
Side lunges
So you're going to start standing tall with your feet together
Okay
Now you're going to take a great big step to the left
To the left
Then the left knee and bring your arms down to the left ankle
I'm not going to do this
It's like right leg straight as you can
Okay
Now come back up to the standing position with feet together
We're going to do the right one
Now to the right
Right leg out wide
Right knee bends
Arms down for the right ankle
And up
I know you've seen your button stomach to get back up
So I'm not even going through mine
I'm sorry
Yeah, yes I am
Keep going
On the night water go on each side
Due to those long legs
I'll let you count
Squeeze that vibe
Yes
This is a good stretch for your upper body
And it's a great workout for your legs
And of course we're sculpting the booty
As abs finishes
I want to remind everyone that fitness attack
And Spanish will launch
Translated by the fabulous mark to bloom
You can find all my shows at fitness.potshow.com
Hey
Great job Adam
That bud is really coming along
I think that out for the holidays
I might be able to release you and do it once a month's check it
Oh no
But then maybe we should start working on abs
We could call it Adam's abs exercise
Hmm
Well the name might need a moment away
Yeah really
Anyway, my weekly work is done
Until next time
Thank you Amy Mack
Yeah, I remember those
I've done lots of lunges in my life
When I was fencing
I only didn't do that to the side
You didn't forward
But yep, I remember
I can get the feelings coming back
You know
Amy
I think I need to see
What
What episode was this?
12?
Let me just check
14 already, crap
I think I need at least six more
I think we need to take it to 20
That's for sure
Oh this is a nice place here
It's real spiffy
I know you guys
I don't like spiffy
Hey
So you're Adam curry
Incha
Yeah
What about you?
Well let me introduce myself
My name's Joey
And these are my associates
Many tree hands
And fat Tony
Tony he's a little too much
This is a nice place
You got here this podshow.com
It's real classy
I like classy
But for being such a nice place
Mr. Curry
It's an awfully rough neighborhood
I mean being on the internet
You know
You have to worry about hackers and viruses
And what?
Not clogging your tubes
That's why me and the boys here
We put together a little security protection agency
For just a few dollars a day
We'll make sure that
Almost nothing bad happens to you
Now you can make payment
In the alley
Next to the angry geek.com
Just leave your payment in small
Unmarked bills in a little suitcase behind the dumpster
Oh, Mr. Curry
If you decide to back out of this little financial arrangement we've entered into
Why don't I just show you why we call him many tree hands
Hey Vinnie
Show him that hand you got
No Vinnie
Not your left hand
The hand you wear around your neck
Fucking war
Yes that hand Vinnie
Please show it to Mr. Curry
Anyway Mr. Curry
As you can see he has a severed hand around his neck
That's a hand of the last podcaster that didn't
Honor our financial arrangements
You can put it away now Vinnie
Yes, I'm sure you can put it away now Vinnie
Thank you
He's a sick bastard he really is
But we keep him around anyway
You know he gets the job done
That and what we get the fire
Anyway Mr. Curry
You want our financial arrangement today
And we'll make sure nothing bad before you
You have a good day Mr. Curry
Come on boys. Let's say I'm scary
You guys are just too kind
So before I could even mention it
Already phone calls coming in
You know I'm getting into the holiday spirit
We've got the cold crisp air outside
Today not a great flying day
Hopefully tomorrow or Sunday
I am planning on crossing the channel again
But as I said it's the holiday season
That's why you know the Howard Jones tune kind of a little bit of holiday vibe
Even though I don't know if it was meant as a holiday vibe record
But it kind of gave me that vibe
And yeah, you know what I'm waiting for this time of year
Which I'm under frequent listening
Probably more frequent caller
I'm listening to that time of year
Were you going to start knocking on about
Bloody egg nog
Which is you know
American thing
Make sure you check out
The wine
Believe it's called Mama Uniformly
My Lima Echo Delta
I'll never get it the English stuff
Make sure you check that out because it's good stuff
Fight
From Bernie's world at burnewsworldcast.podshow.com
A couple of weeks ago
I sent your tune for footballer Friday
And I screwed it up
Sent you something that was footballer
And you played in any way
Then last week I sent you an intro
That goofed on you
And that whole go daddy domain name thing
That was good
You turned around and you took it
You laid it over the first song of the footballer Friday show
And you made it from some half baked
Homemade intro into something
That sounded really awesome
So I kind of owe you
I wanted to send just the right tune
For footballer Friday this week
I have an instrumental for you
And if you like hard rock and guitar solos
Funky bass and heavy metal jams
Then this instrumental is for you
All right
It's called Screaming Chicken
It's by Jobo
It's on the Podsafe music network
And it's got everything you're looking for
For footballer Friday except for one thing
It needs more cowbell
So here's Screaming Chicken by Jobo
No problem
I got to it
You
Take it all
Damn
That is excellent
You
jam that is instrumental. Don't play a lot of those on the Charlie, but yeah, like it. Dude, thank you so much.
Comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip,
CSB sent in an audio comment. I've not listened to it myself. Actually, I had lost it.
I put it in a wrong folder somewhere and if you see my desktop right now, it's just filled with
crap and I used Google Google Desktop search and bam, turns out I had thrown it into my
documents folder, but it popped up immediately. Do love that Google Desktop search.
So let's listen to this for the first time together, shall we?
Hiya, Adam Curry. You are aviation freak, so you may be know how critical, so called
Battle of Britain was. This battle took place between UK and Germany in the air only.
So here is a young-polette style question. He loves of what nationality, where second?
Did you say penis or pilots? Most effective in this battle after Englishmen?
Oh, how about a Polish? It's a battle of Britain, do you know?
Polish? Well, these were Native Americans, no scots. These were Paul. I told you my compatriots.
After EU announcement, in 2004, over 500,000 Pauls emigrated to UK. So now, birds are scared and close.
Temporarily, work market for buggerians or minions, the new EU citizens from next year.
However, the point system for emigrants, that your soil mate Patricia mentioned,
does not apply to EU citizens at all, but to people from outside of EU. Good.
So for example, people from Asia, you know. Partition was right after all, but of course, EU citizens
have no limits at all, and this point system doesn't apply to them.
So, by the way, I am launching a video blog on the domain www.smartphone.tv, and I'm pondering which video
hosting service should I use, which is the best. Do you have any suggestions? Bye-bye, Adam.
Yo. Well, yo yourself, CSB. Interesting. First of all, we look at smartphone.tv.
Coming soon, and it will be blog with videos about smartphones. Yo.
Dude, uh, you can use, um, podshow plus for that. What did you expect me to say anything different?
Podshow plus now also under videos allows you to upload a single video and create a viral video
out of it with an embed code and all that groovy stuff. So that would be one way, or you could upload
those, and you'll be able to add them to feed. I mean, there's all kinds of stuff that that we've
put in all kinds of neat little things under the hood that I'm waiting for you guys to discover.
Now, about the Polish pilots, uh, commonster blogger, I actually didn't know that. I am an aviation,
and I didn't know that the Polish pilots, pilots contributed to the battle. But actually,
they were going to help a couple more important battles during the Second World War,
but the Polish Air Force ran out of coal, unfortunately. Sorry about that, dude.
All right, you're on hard like to present Sir Jersey Todd. Now, Sir Jersey Todd is the most
badass learner in podcasting. So you can be sure he won't be saving any damsels into stress.
He'll be chasing behind the ambulance on horseback, waiting to sue the asses off the dragons that
are in jail.
Just in time, yeah, just in time, yeah, yeah
You're on a what he said, we might even win this case
Just in time, yeah, just in time, yeah
Yo, what's up, AC?
Jersey tied the official Nighted Musicologist of The Delloy Source code
And I just want to thank the great and amazing Jim Armstrong from Sonic Delloy Records
For his cover of Jeff Smith's Jersey tied theme song
I mean, how cool is that?
Anyway, Adam, listen, the elections are over here in the States
And I finally can come out and say how upset I was
About all of the negative campaigning here in Jersey
I mean, please, New Jersey get such a reputation
New Jersey gets such a reputation
of having corrupt officials and places of power.
And let me just say this.
New Jerseyans are not people who take bribes,
we are not corrupt,
and we are not otherwise easily influenced.
All right, I just had to get that off my chest.
All right, listen, I'm cool.
Today on the Cha Cha,
I'd like to bring you one of my favorite artists,
the great and amazing Jim Armstrong
from Sonic Deli Records.
Hey, how about that?
And it's song Angel in our corner,
that you're gonna like it a lot.
It's a great food bar song,
and have some fun and I'll see you around.
We all need Angel in our corner,
and we all need a good friend to warn us.
Something's just strong,
just like a supermarket man.
We love a good man,
but I don't really think it's gonna be like that.
Sometimes it's so long,
just yet a break of stuff,
and you play it about me and bring it back to you.
We all need Angel in our corner,
we all need Angel in our corner,
Baby, I can't remember if we all be
If you're in our corner
Can we all be
Friends of all of us
We all need
If you're in our corner
Can we all be
We all need
And we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are
leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving.
and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving, and we are leaving.
Well, I think that makes it official.
This is probably the longest promo ever run on the daily source code, Jersey Todd
often vacation.
I hope I'll be back for next week, and I have to say I'm a little bit envious of that
song.
It's an awesome one, dude.
Congrats.
Fubar Faday continues with something, actually, I think I should make a regular
feature.
It's a little bit on the long side, but I wouldn't mind having more of these sent in.
Maybe just once a week or once every other week.
I remember I was talking about Jennifer Yenolo from Food Philosophy.
Actually, she was racking on me, and then she did me to a cook-off, like that's really
going to work.
I can cook, but I can't cook, like anyone named Yenolo saying, but I have a secret weapon.
Hey Adam, it's Chef Mark in New York.
I heard the little slap down my friend Jennifer Yenolo gave you for mangling her name,
and the recipe thrown down she challenged you to.
I figured since she really knows her way around the kitchen, you might need a little
help in your corner.
Since the remarkable pilot podcast is now the newest show on the Potio PDN, I can step in
and help you out.
Here's a little recipe you might use with splendor flavor blends to bring to the
throwdown with Jennifer.
Okay.
I call this strawberry, French vanilla and Napoleon.
You'll need some frozen pre-made pup pastry shells, some ricotta cheese, fresh strawberries,
and a few packets of French vanilla splendor flavor blend.
Now, you know what's great about this is you can keep this show on your mobile device.
And when you're shopping, you can stop it and you can rewind it and listen to the ingredients
and then as you're preparing this wonderful dish of which I forgot in the name, we need
a snappy or name, Marks, sorry, snappy or name.
Then you can actually do the same thing.
It'll work.
Trust me.
After vanilla flavored splendor into about 3-4 cups of softened ricotta cheese, be sure
to blend it really well, make it smooth and creamy, and get it to just the sweetness
you like.
If you like it even richer and creamier, use muscarpone cheese and a hand blender to whip
it.
Slice your strawberries or whatever fresh fruit you'd like and set them aside.
Next, you're going to bake off a couple of pre-cut frozen pup pastry shells in the oven.
You can get these in the freezer case of most grocery stores.
When they've cooled, carefully divide them into two or three layers.
Spread a little of the vanilla cream over the bottom layer, line up a few slices of strawberries
so that they just peek out the edges and then top with a second layer of the pup pastry.
Repeat with more cream and strawberries and then top with the last layer of pup pastry.
You of course, you can substitute raspberries for the strawberries, but always get something
that's fresh and in-season, or you can use one of the other flavor blends as well.
If you want to get a little fancy, you can even pure some raspberries with a little splendor
and a squeeze of lemon juice.
Push it through a fine mesh sieve to get rid of the seeds and voila!
You have a sweet and bright raspberry cule to drizzle over your dessert.
And that, my friend, is how you meet a recipe throw down.
Don't tell Jennifer I help you out or she'll lock me in the root cellar with the kitchen
elves.
Ah!
We're all waiting for you, chef.
Hey, keep it down in there.
I'll make you chop more onion.
No!
Anyway, out of check out remarkablepalott.potcho.com.
On my latest show, I interviewed Chef Mingxai at an actual cranberry bog that they built
into Rockefeller Center.
Ah!
By the way, the elves crunch, but I most definitely full.
Yeah.
See you later, buddy.
You know, Chef Mark, I think we can do this as a regular feature, but we got to change
the production a little bit.
As much as I appreciate that you put this music together, we really need something more
like, let me see if there you go.
And nowadays, I'm done, man, it is time for the one and only matrimarch.
Our chef fixed, rodna, to bring you today's recipe of the week.
Chef Mark is all yours.
And then you come in and you say, today we have the vaging surprise.
Oh, good.
For something like that.
And then we could end it every single time with, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh.
But bon appetit!
Fuck me.
I didn't work the way I wanted it to.
Adam, I know you've read playboy magazine, so you've probably seen the advisor column.
And the advisor, uh, one of the best known and off-bread features of playboy magazine is also
one of the most popular advice columns in the world, with more than 10 million readers in
14 countries.
And the actual playboy advisor himself, my buddy, Chip Ro, senior editor of the magazine,
is on Pacific Coast Highway this Friday talking about the book, the column, and a whole lot
more.
In fact, Chip talks about so much great stuff on the show that I had to break the interview
up into two parts.
Well, the first part, dropping on Friday, at Pacific CoastHellway.podgeow.com.
And of course, I had to ask Chip, what was the craziest weirdest letter he ever got
as the playboy advisor?
And this is what he told me.
Well, I can have a few favorites.
The one that always comes up first is the guy who dragged the lazy boy out into the woods,
and he would go sit in it naked and spray a bug spray all over himself except his genitals.
And you can go back to people in a minute to let that digest.
And his question was basically, is this, is this normal?
And if you want to know how the playboy advisor answered that question, well, you'll just have
to check out the interview at Pacific CoastHellway.
So thanks, Adam.
And you know what?
I'm going to be sending you a copy of the Deer Playboy advisor book for Christmas along
with a box of tissues, because I know you're going to dig it.
I'll catch you later.
Yo, Mark.
Cool deal, man.
So that's today, then, I guess, that it goes up, right?
Oh, about Chef Mark, I almost forgot to say, ladies.
He's dreamy.
Hey, everyone.
This is Eugene tomorrow.
My question for you is this.
How long have you been with your internet service provider?
How many times have you switched?
My internet service provider is EarthLink, and I have been with them as a subscriber since
April 17, 1998.
Now, that's a long time before anyone had ever heard of iPods or podcasting or even cable
or DSL broadband.
For over eight years now, I have relied on EarthLink for internet connectivity and spam
for email, and they have never let me down.
If you are tired of bad service, inconsistent connectivity, constantly rising prices and email
accounts full of spam, come on over where I am, EarthLink.net, go to www.EarthLink.net, and
you can get a great deal on internet service.
I got to go double check.
I think the EarthLink campaign ends this week.
I'm not quite sure.
Oh, maybe it's till the end of the month.
I got to find out.
Of course, go Daddy continues.
It looks like we're working on some really cool with go Daddy.
I wish I could tell you.
I don't think the deal has been signed yet, but I wish I could tell you what it's going
to be.
A fucking awesome promotion.
And of course, we still have the current go Daddy promotion.
If you want a great deal on domain name, 695 for a year, go to godaddy.com and use
check out code DSC3 for all your domain name.
And now a word from our sponsor.
It's the Yanks.
This is the Brits.
We'll drive each other crazy, but everybody knows that it's apparent to see that just like
you and me, it's the Yanks.
And the Brits, the Yanks versus the Brits.
Mind the game.
I don't know.
I just had as you were talking on them in a day,
Daddy's supposed to come in because I said, and I heard you mentioned the sort of
comparison between UK, not UK, European Union, United States, and people in New Jersey.
You're going to like other states for work.
Now, I think what you mean, and I agree with you, I think it's a big deal.
But you can't quite make the comparison between European Union and United States.
They are different.
Well, they are still the independent nations, we're not going to serve the words anymore.
I mean, I don't even have to say it's probably that the states are to a point that I don't
have the right.
But they are not the same thing.
So, not quite as like, I'd like to look at your, I think, that people have won, we want
to come here.
Yeah.
You can imagine.
It'd be nice if you got it something.
Anyway, it's mentioned in recent times, come like that.
Okay, I didn't understand any of the last half of that, except that the comparison
of New York, New Jersey, UK and other European states is not equitable, not equivalent.
There you go.
Can you tell them football?
I got a green kind of disagree with you.
First of all, why do you call it a state if it isn't a state?
And as far as comparisons go, New York and New Jersey, it's like two different places.
We talk differently, we have different money and New Jersey are money is a little bit more
greysier.
Yeah, I mean, different countries, Texas, Texas is a whole different country from New York
and New Jersey.
So, there isn't all that much difference as far as I'm concerned.
And still, you can move around pretty freely.
Music by the Jim Offerman band, Russell Wolfe, and Marx says hi on the next edition of
the Pot-Safe Treasures Podcast.
I'm Eugene T. Roya Join us, download the program at potsafetreasures.potshow.com.
You know, if you haven't seen it, BTpotshow.com is launched now in the UK.
You can get to it from anywhere and you'll see the subtle differences between potshow.com
and BTpotshow.com.
One of them being some of the shows that we have running there, you have to check out
the International Sex Therapist, Dr. Cockney.
You'll find them right there in the home page.
This show is fucking awesome.
Think a white ballboard art.
Not that board art isn't white, but you know what I'm saying?
Roaming the streets of London as the International Sex Therapist and really giving us
an eye-opener and a deep probe into English culture, English sexual culture.
I think he also has a Potshow site.
What is it? International Sex Therapist.potshow.com?
Yeah, probably something like that.
And for all the talking I was doing about this thing called Goose Inc.
Goose Inc.
Which allows you to synchronize your Google calendar, which I use along with my
Gmail onto your mobile phone.
I couldn't get this thing to work.
It was supposed to send me authentication message and I didn't.
And then I said, well, just delete your profile and start it.
It just didn't work.
And then I got an email from Otto Heldemann and Otto pointed me to gcalsink.com.
Which is an open source Java application.
So it'll run on your Java phone, which the Nokia E61 handles quite nicely.
So gcalsink is golf Charlie Alpholimus Chero.
Yankee November Charlie dot com installed it, worked right off the bat, synchronized
in my calendars.
I haven't been able to get it to write up to the Google calendar only to pull down
from the Google calendar, which is kind of a drawback.
But maybe I'm not doing something right or maybe there's another version coming along.
We'll do that.
I'm sure.
But it's definitely something you want to check out if you have a Java capable
phone.
Join Dawn and Drew as the interview BT composer, songwriter, and DJ extraordinaire.
We'll talk about his new project, this binary universe.
And all sorts of other crazy things that you won't hear anywhere else.
It'll be November 13th over at DonAndrew.com.
Don't miss it.
You know, um,
check out my new album, this binary universe, and you're listening to the Don and Drew
showed check it out.
They got chicken.
Yes, they do.
I was cruising through the positive music network.
You know, as I did yesterday, when I just found my chemical romance, and I found this
outfit from, um, well, she doesn't say with her from, I wonder.
Well, their name is area phonics, and let me just read from the bio here.
Area phonics is created a totally new music style by combining elements of classical crossover
with moods close to 70s conceptual albums on this groundbreaking album.
Modern electronic sounds are combined with the lyricism of Italian aria.
And actually, I was going to play this song first.
Let me see if I can just pop this up for you, just so you can hear a little bit.
I'm playing it directly from the web browser at music.podshow.com.
And I kind of thought I was interesting because it was listed as genre was opera.
And it's titled Sposason Distresatta.
I still kick my ass, which I hear is my pronunciation.
And I thought that was, uh, that by itself was pretty cool.
But then I found this other track they have, which, to me, was just such a fantastic
mashup.
And it's actually legal, so I want to listen to this one.
The only problem with Microsoft is they just have no taste.
They have absolutely no taste.
Not only is it's common, but it's still new.
No taste, no taste, no taste, no taste, no taste, no taste, no taste, no taste, no taste, no taste.
They don't think of original ideas and they don't bring much culture into their product.
No taste, no smell, no taste, no smell, no taste, no smell, no taste, no smell, no taste.
Just killing from me.
No taste, no taste, no taste, no taste, no taste, no taste, no taste.
No taste, no taste, no taste, no taste.
Good on it's coffee, and there's still.
Are you in version?
You're still in version.
You just think you're not.
No taste, no taste, no taste.
No taste, no taste.
Better than you are.
That doesn't matter.
Excellent.
I'm not quite sure what the version thing was doing in there all of a sudden, but I liked it a lot.
I just realized that we're missing an important link.
If you haven't seen it yet, we had now have really the audience facing side of the
positive music network.
If you go to patchart.com slash music or just hit in the music tab anywhere.
You'll see that we have all these artists pages.
We've now brought it out into the forefront.
You can get an artist and put it into your collection.
It'll play in the dashboard.
You can't download it, but you can play it in the dashboard.
You can get an embeddable player of your favorite artists.
All of their tracks will then appear on the page that you put that code into.
And you can play it right from that page.
So there's just a whole bunch of things that we've done, but there's no connection from the
really the producer side, the podcast or side, which is the pod save music network.
Now I've got to go find the link on the music side of podshow.com.
So I can paste that in because that's really what you want to be.
Which you want to be looking at.
Certainly as a listener.
And then of course, so we need it the other way around.
So if you're a producer or a podcaster or anything you find on podshow.com slash music,
you should also be able to click that and add it to your play list or something like that.
That's something I still got to work on.
As we have to work on many, many things.
But we're getting there.
I think over the weekend we'll really clear up most of the big buggies.
And then we can go towards rolling out more of the video stuff.
And please, you've got to check out what we've done for the podcas producers.
You know what?
I am indeed quite footballer.
I don't get it today.
It's Friday.
Monday Tuesday Wednesday Thursday.
Food about Friday.
Add a spinal fund for the week.
Well, for the final thought of the week.
Yesterday, I did a show with the lovely lady Patricia.
And I actually listened back to it in the car.
I was running a couple of errands.
Yeah, I'd like to listen to shows once more.
Particularly Patricia's on and I can kind of see how the vibe was.
And I have to say that I'm going to try and improve myself a little bit.
It's been incredibly busy the past few weeks.
I've been sleep deprived along with all of my colleagues.
But Patricia had some very valid points.
She said, hey, you're just not in the good mood.
And I thought to myself, that really sucks.
Even though I'm really tired and even though things aren't going exactly the way I wanted to go,
I should be a lot nicer.
And so the next time you're feeling shitty, tired, food barred,
remember those who love you and who really are just doing everything they can to support you.
And the only thing you have to do is just flash them a smile.
I know.
It worked for me last night.
And Tuesday, Wednesday.
Thursday, full by Friday.
And I'm spinal thought on the reef.
On my cast, last night.
That's it for me, everybody.
Have a great weekend.
I'll be back here on Monday with a more crap.
Bye-bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this pod cast and we're great ones like it on the high performance pod cast
delivery network from Podshow and line-white networks.
I love it.