This is Soccer Girl. I just listened to the first episode of Shadow Falls and it's scared me
crapless.
This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy. Want Killer content with a badass
domain name? The show will give you a special code, get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Daily source code episode 437.
It was $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
This is Rob and with another content call, over 80-40 minutes, come on.
Time to go lose in my mind this time.
It happens to me.
I'm falling deeper into you.
We still need fun, no my name.
We are holding every bowl in this ordinary world.
I am falling now, reborn.
Extraordinary girl.
This is a button I still remember the day.
Man, come on, then you to me away.
Dream to let you know that I still do this way.
Daily, every time I still lose in my mind this time.
It happens to me.
I'm falling deeper into you.
We are holding every bowl in this ordinary world.
I am falling now, reborn.
Extraordinary girl.
This is a button I still remember the day.
Better all to sleep.
Time to go lose in my mind this time.
It happens to me.
I'm falling deeper into you.
We are holding every bowl in this ordinary world.
This is Rob and with another content call, over 80 minutes, come on.
Extraordinary girl, I'm falling now, reborn.
Jack in the pulpit, ordinary girl, from the pod save music network.
On episode number 437 of the Daily source code,
hey everybody how you doing?
Coming to you from the curry cottage.
In the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Gilford, Gilford.
And as you can tell, no Patricia on the show today.
Ah, I'm a little bit bummed about that.
I made a huge estimation error.
Now guys, if you're married or if you live with your girl,
you've always got to watch out for the signs.
You've got to think about why things are happening and not happen.
I was so stupid.
How could I think that one day before Patricia's sister comes for a visit for a week
that she would have any time for me.
Of course not.
Now I understand what's been happening for the past two days.
You know, it's like all this cleaning, all this stuff has to be fixed and worked out
and like everyone's got tasks and jobs.
And of course you give a teenager a job and teenagers won't do crap or we'll do it half
heartedly, right?
And so this morning, of course, she's doing her hair and so if I hope you understand,
I'm just going to step away from any energy there.
There's another thing I've noticed though.
Patricia has no idea how much you guys like her on the show.
Yeah, I tell her all the time and I forward her comments and stuff.
I think it's time we get on a little campaign here and let her know how much we love her on the
Charlie send an email to Patricia at curie.com and let her know what you think.
Hey, got some cool parts of music lined up.
Plenty of voice calls, promos, brand new sponsor, which is I think you'll like.
And some things that came into the email box.
Let me see, this is a couple of people passed this one on to me.
It's this awesome, awesome site called goggles, which is, um, it's kind of a mashup of the
Google, I think it's the Google Maps API and just, I don't know, as a flash, whatever funky stuff.
I have no idea how it works, but essentially you can choose a city.
I think it's New York London.
I think that's Singapore in there and you fire this webpage and you're actually flying a little
plane, a little, I mean, it's a, it's a render is a drawing of a plane, but you're flying a little
plane, um, over the city and you can, um, you can go up and altitude, go down, you can, uh,
bank left, bank right. It, it's very, it doesn't quite go up high enough for my taste.
You know, I can't, you can't really see exactly where you are and it's missing some of the
UI bits that as a pilot it would be very handy to know where the alarm flying was extremely cool.
And I put a link in today's show notes for you to check it out, uh, it's called Goggles.
See something that came in that was circulating through the potto severe yesterday, apparently
Brad Pitt, uh, makes, and I don't know if, if Brad Pitt calls it a podcast or not, but, uh,
according to the mirror, it's the mirror that, uh, the post of this, um, oh, the, the link
actually comes from China daily. You'll have to read it for yourself.
Uh, but apparently, while Brad Pitt is away from, uh, from Maddox and uh, and Angelina and,
and how many kids do they have now three? Uh, he makes, and this is the quote,
sends private internet podcast to Maddox and in turn Maddox will turn, uh, five in a few days,
sends films of his paintings and bicycle stunts. It's a personal podcast. I just wonder if they
actually call it a podcast in the paid household. And something you've got to go look at,
uh, um, Jay Donley has been working on this. It says now the fourth episode and I think he's
finally gotten it to where it's, it's, what I once talked about and he really developed a vision
around the concept of podcast doing a test drive in an automobile. And he's, um, I think it's his wife,
and she's now known as the test drive girl. They go to, uh, to new card dealerships and, uh,
they test drive and they basically film it. And, and of course, half the fun is looking at the
idiotic sales guy. I think that they were denied a couple of places, but finally, it really is a
great test drive, you know, and, and you look at all the features and you kind of get to just
hang out and drive along. Um, so I'll link to that in the show notes as well for test drive
girl episode number four out now, continuing, uh, in our contest, a new contest, which if started,
I don't even know what the prize is going to be yet, but I think we're going to have to really
up the stakes because no one has gotten it right. At the end of every single podcast on the
pod show podcast delivery network, you hear a little promo tag and the, uh, the text is, uh,
get this podcast, another one, other great ones like it, um, on the high performance podcast delivery
network, um, from pod show and limelight networks. And then there's this female voice that kind of
floats through there going, I love it. So skip to the end of the show or, or, or any other podcast,
a pod show podcast to hear the voice and you tell me who it is. I had a miss Brian on second
life on Brian's notes. I've also emailed you a bunch of times, but that's nothing. Anyway, I'm thinking
that the voice must be as a lovely Patricia. I'm, uh, 57 year old listener, um, and I'm a folder.
Yeah. No, despite your obvious higher intelligence being a folder, you're wrong. Sorry.
It is not Patricia. Uh, it is not someone who currently has a podcast per se,
although she, and I got to give you some hints to get you to get you going there. She is a member,
uh, an indirect member of the pod show family. I have to have to say a direct member of the pod show
family, and she has been discussed on, uh, certainly one, maybe two podcasts. And does, in fact,
just recently, she was discussed on a podcast that belongs to the pod show lineup. It's not Patricia.
It's not Angie B. Everyone's posting comments at dailysourcecode.com. Get your, you know,
that's the best way to register your answer, obviously. So that I have a time and date stamp
is to when you, uh, when you actually putting your answer. So dailysourcecode.com, leave a message
under today's podcast episode number 437. It's not Patricia. Oh, man. This is going to be good. I,
I think I got to come up with, uh, with a really good prize. I'm a little tired of giving away iPods.
Maybe we should just give away a different brand. You know, something, uh, a really nice one from a,
of a different brand. Give me a suggestion about that as well, if you will. Hey, Adam,
just downloaded, uh, Shane number 436 Monday, the 7th of August. Um, I don't know what's up with it.
All, um, if this problem with castblaster, that's after 25 seconds, um, it's the MP3 stops playing
nightings. Um, if you fast forward it, just after 25 seconds, places normal. So, uh, thought,
I'm just like, you know, and, uh, yeah, there you go. Bye. Folder scruncher, huh? Yeah, thanks.
Uh, you know, this is a problem we've seen in the past. Uh, something that, uh, I think probably
a couple months ago, uh, it, uh, it cropped up. I'm pretty sure it has to do with our de-gap system,
dynamically, uh, generated audio placement, which puts in the ads for shadow falls and, uh,
and go daddy and the, uh, and the promo at the end, uh, which, of course, you can win a fantastic
prize by guessing who the voices that says I love it. Um, uh, you know, so obviously we're looking
into it. We're going to get it fixed. It, it's interesting that it only happens with iTunes and
subsequently when being played on an iPod, which, of course, is a huge market. So we've got to fix
it, no doubt about it. Um, but there is something weird about iTunes that that I've noticed that
iTunes actually rewrites the MP3 file when it comes in. So, you know, if, if you have it set the
download the show or if you're downloading it through a channel and it comes into iTunes and that's how
you sync it up to your iPod. And of course, if it's housed in iTunes, they'll get housed on your iPod.
Um, so it leaves our place perfectly and if you, uh, and if you, uh, drop it into iTunes
manually. Oh, actually, that's something you could try. Please, because this worked for me, if you
download the file and then put it into iTunes manually, does it still have the same problem? I don't
think it will. Because with podcasts, iTunes does something very peculiar, which, um, I would have
expected a lot of people to be up in arms about, but I've not heard hardly anyone ever talk about it.
If you create an MP3 file and you put in your ID3 tags, you know, so that the title and the, and the
the author, et cetera, is all, is all set. If it's downloaded via iTunes from a podcast feed,
iTunes actually rewrites the ID3 tags. It takes away the information you put in there and puts in,
I think the first couple lines of the show notes of the description, which is, well, it's not the
way I sent it out. It's the way that, you know, it's what's happening on the other end. And I think
because of this rewriting, something is getting garbled with, uh, with de-gap insertions. It's
probably, it has to do with the timing issue, but um, working on it, trying to fix it, uh, but very,
amazed, actually, I should say, um, about the fact that iTunes is rewriting every single file,
rewriting the ID3 tags, which is kind of, you know, breaking my authorship there. You know,
I wanted to say something else, not what you determined it to be. Two for Tuesday, if you're
listening to us on the serious stars 102, the serious satellite radio network. Yeah, we pulled a
really old concept out of our ass, two for. So on Tuesdays, besides the lineup that we have
scheduled for you, which I'm going to pull up right now, uh, which, of course, has, uh, daily source
code kicking it off. And we've got Don and Drew actually pod show LA is, uh, is next after daily
source code. It won't be a pacific host, uh, hellway today. It will be, where's my fucking latte,
stories of personal assistance in Hollywood? You have to listen to that show if you've never heard it.
Don and Drew after that, then the rumor girls, and then in our two for Tuesday, on the, the
roaming slots, we've got, uh, pod save the queen will be on at eight to eight o'clock this evening.
East Coast time, and perfect head will be the show after that from eight thirty to nine o'clock.
Then East radio and Scott Sigler to wind it up, uh, here on serious stars 102. Let's see,
one more from the inbox. Now that's from my buddy Tom from from down under, he says he just bought
a swim P3. Have you heard of one of these? Swim P3. So W, S, W, I, M, P3. It's a small
MP3 player that sits on the back of your, uh, swimming goggles and transmits the sound into your
skull via bone conductive technology. Patricia, I tried that out just the other night.
Basically, it vibrates the sound into your temples inside of your ear. It works beautifully. The first
few tracks were songs, then the DSC came on somewhere after the first kilometer of swimming.
As I started, I thought to myself, with one hundred and forty four dollars,
with an MP3 player strapped to my head. And the next generation of radio content being
vibrated into my skull. I think I look like a dickhead in the pool. All right Tom,
Bod said music now for Kevin Reeves on the daily source code.
It's as late as the man that's a kick-ass. Throw me a line.
Is there any way out in here? Is there some way to make this clear?
Because of you, I can't sleep any more since you walked out the door and you left me.
All I do is stare at the wall and you know, bumps at all,
except for memory. While you want to try to be insane,
what you want to cause me so much pain. Throw me a line.
I don't think I can't make it on my own. Throw me a line.
I afraid that I might die even on the long way. Show me a side.
Tell me that you're still in love with me when you throw me a line.
I can't feel, so no darkness will lie,
I don't know daytime from night, haunted space in.
Yes, it's real. Oh, well, I wake up from this and the mist of your tears and embrace it.
What they're in my sports too. I don't think I can make it without you.
Throw me a line. I don't think I can't make it on my own.
Throw me a line. I afraid that I might die even on the long way.
Show me a side. Tell me that you're still in love with me when you throw me a line.
I don't think I can make it without you.
Throw me a line. I don't think I can't make it on my own.
Throw me a line. I don't think I can make it on my own.
Throw me a line. I afraid that I might die even on the long way.
Show me a side. Tell me that you're still in love with me when you throw me a line.
Throw me a line. I don't think I can't make it on my own.
I have some quality shape right there.
Kevin Reeves threw me a line from the Pods' music network,
link in the show notes today at sourcecode.com.
This is AB 50. I can't believe he's real hard to tell you what type of password he is.
AB from Conradweedil.com is a folder that's right, but I do have a question for you.
What is that with scrunchies? I just don't get that stuff.
What happened? You scrunch around your finger and you got good coverage on one part.
Under scrunch, another part. You're going to end up with like a stinky finger.
And that's got to happen. All the damn time when you're wiping, sit off your ass.
I mean, I just don't get it. I mean, I'm a folder myself, so anyway.
If anyone can tell your show and your fans with scrunchies, that would be cool.
This is AB, this is that. And just remember, if you ever want to talk about data-based it,
for RFF alone with technology. You know, sit around, talk about that stuff. Anyway,
with that fan, so please out.
Did I hear some of you? James Brown, got bucket.
You're someone said to me the other day, says, hey, man, you know, podshow,
paid James Brown to put his song up on the pods of music network.
I was like, wow, great idea. I wish he'd been that smart.
Fold of scruncher. Yeah, the controversy, controversy continues. What is better?
What is best? Is it genetics? Yesterday we gave away the iPod in the contest.
Troy needs an iPod.com. Create a better domain name, register it to make us laugh.
And announce the winner have not yet actually officially heard from the winner. Of course,
it's possible that she didn't hear that she'd won yet because not everyone's on the same
listening schedule. But we have some insight into all about the winner. Hey, Adam. It's Rebecca from
Tranny Recredo. You can find my show at TrannyRect.com. Yada-yada-fucking-yada. I'm also six-foot-one
and fat enough to play college football. Anyways, the reason I'm calling is because I wanted to
reveal the identity if you haven't already figured it out. The identity of your iPod winner.
He is actually a she, her name is Marty Abernathy. She is frequently appears on multiple shows
on the Trans-FM radio network. She's also been on my show. You can hear all about her by listening
to Tranny Rec episode 22. Anyways, since I know that she is listening to the source code,
I just wanted to say Marty, what the fuck? Quit wasting toilet paper, start folding and save the
god damn planet. So I got- What is that Trans-FM radio? Is that radio or is that a podcast?
I got to listen to that. You have something that's something interesting going on over there for sure.
Your one voice has strength. Many voices have power.
Join your fellow podcasters, bloggers and new media experts in podcamp Boston on September 9th
10th. Learn from each other, teach each other, and lend your voice to the power of many.
For more information visit www.podcamp.org.
That's kind of a cool idea. You know, there's been all these food camps and bar camps and
blog camps and camp camps and whatever the heck. And it seems to be a version of an on conference
kind of a gathering where you have some, you're usually consists of a wiki in a place to go hang out.
And it seems like a really good idea. These kind of ad hoc organist, organist, organist, organist,
organist gathering. Senior is pretty fun. So this is a podcamp which I think is taking place
September 9th and 10th. I will definitely post a link to that site in the show notes for
a quick handy and easy reference at dailysourcecode.com. But it sounds like something cool.
Now it's very interesting that they're holding this event on the east coast. In fact,
I saw someone actually bill it as, what is it, the podcast Expo east? That's very interesting
that doing that so close to the podcast Expo. Let's talk like two weeks later in Ontario,
California. So let me know. I saw that Steve Garfield is going to be there. I'm sure because it's
I think it's Boston, CC Chapman will be hanging out. It sounds like that's going to be a
pretty cool deal. Damn. Maybe I should go. That'll be, it's a shorter trip for me. That's for sure.
If you're listening to us on a serious starts one or two up next, you're going to hear where the
fuck is my latte? Stories of Hollywood personal assistance as codified by Mark Yoshimoto
name cough and joy. Meanwhile, back over here, we've got, I didn't know actually that
Angie B had participated in our earth link ad challenge where you make the advertising. And then
as it turns out today, I got to the list of finalists in. So I think there's like 10 different ads.
They could either be a song. It could be a jingle. It could be an endorsement. It could be a
straight ahead produced commercial. And my girl Angie B is one of the finalists. This is Angie B
independent musician and podcaster. So I joined Love Spirals in very late 1998, which was right around
the time when MP3s were coming into Vogue. And internet radio was getting started. Both things
I was very excited about. But with dial-up service, it was a real nightmare for me trying to upload
MP3s to the internet. I cried many evenings trying to get through to get those big files up.
So I was pretty excited to try out DSL for the first time. I mean, once again, this was right
when broadband was super cutting edge. Well, I called Earthlink to get set up with DSL because I was
lucky enough to live in LA where they were rolling out some of the services early. And boy,
did it change my life? I mean, there was absolutely no turning back for me after that.
As an independent musician, being connected to the internet at high speed 247 is a real
godsend. And Earthlink made it really simple for me to stay connected to my fans and to make
my music available worldwide. Wow. And she put her own music in it. Cool.
Alright, Angie B. Going for the big, was it two grand? Something like that. And I know Angie
reasonably well in a cyber way that is. We hung out in second life. We email a lot and
you know, I listened to her show, of course. And I have to say that she's probably a real regular
user of technology. It doesn't know a hell of a lot about it, but it's very smart. So configure
stuff out if it's reasonably well explained. So from her coming from her, I say that's a huge
endorsement. Now I just love listening to Angie B. Angie, we maybe we should do some,
maybe we should ask Pod Show LA if they can write us some kind of like a Wayne and Wanda
drama where we can just do a short little love dialogue, you know, a couple times a week.
It'll be really good. I think our voices will be perfect together. And imagine if we
recorded them separately, that could be a kind of hot actually. I'll talk to Yoshimo to Nemcoff
today about them. Hey Adam, it's Heather for movie for radio. And I was listening to DSC 436.
And what the hell playing two female artists in the same show has that ever happened before? I mean,
my show is all girls all the time, but for the most part girls get ignored. So thanks for playing
those two awesome artists. And if your listeners get tired of hearing the same boys played over
and over and over, they can check out RubyFruit Radio at RubyFruitRadio.com, where it's all girls,
all the time. Hey, all girls all the time. Told you I had a brand new sponsor on the Pod Show
podcast network. It's Akira. And Akira has a new car that they're out pimping. It's the
Akira RDX. It's an SUV. And so they came to us about advertising on the network and said, okay,
well, you know, we are trying to change advertising. So, you know, we don't think the straight ahead
32nd spots is really going to cut it. What can we do that's different? And we came up with what we
call a target cast. Those of you who have listened to some of the strategy cast, probably or a
year ago or so, heard us talk. And I think I was spoken about this before. The whole concept of a
strategy cast is where across the network, we talk about a specific podcast, which is all about the
product. So it's really, it's if you're interested, you'll go over there and you'll listen to the podcast
or podcasts as in this case, it turns out. So, you know, really, it's almost like our version of
the infomercial only is not hokey. And I'll tell you why it's not hokey because we said, look,
we'll make a target cast. And you can find this at Akira.podshow.com, Akira, ACURA, Akira.
Podshow.com. We, you know, let's make it into content. You know, you have an interesting car.
Oh, by the way, little memo to self, got to get the test drive girl to do a test drive with the
Akira without their knowledge, of course. So, if you go to akira.podshow.com, I think they have
either one or two, maybe it's the second episode isn't up yet. But it's interviews and it's
interviews done by by podcasters. So, you know, no like fake voices coming in and reading from
a script. But really just having a conversation with, in this case, okay, so here's the, the first
one is with Grammy winner, Elliott Shiner. And he's worked with, he's worked with a lot of people,
most notably probably the Eagles. He was involved in designing the Akira RDX surround sound system.
This car is basically an iPod on wheels, if you will. And then Mark Williams of, I think he's
an editor of Motor Trend magazine. Also talks about the Akira RDX competitors, features, etc.
I haven't driven this myself, but it does seem like it's got a lot of cool toys in it. But anyway,
the whole point being this advertisement that you'll hear at akira.podshow.com is content.
It's really, it's a good listen. Listen to what Williams, what's his name, winner.
Elliott Shiner, you could tell I'm reading at the same time trying to remember. My brain is so
farad. Listen to that first show and tell me that you didn't like it because if you're into a sound,
if you're into cars, if you're into sound in cars, which by the way is an as you'll hear in that
interview is a really important part of the recording process is listening to what it sounds like
on your car speakers. I think you'll like it. Accurate.podshow.com. Go check it out.
Let me know what you thought too, by the way. I really do care.
Hi, Adam. This is Peter. I'll listen from Australia. Two things I want to cover.
First up, you put out a call to get to know your listeners. Well, I'm an aircraft technical writer
who's pushing 40 listening to your show on my PDA when traveling home. I'll listen to the DSC
because you have an uncanny knacker putting a smile on my face even after a shitty day.
Just something about the way you put the show together. I don't do my own podcast,
but I will put in a word for another podcast I like. It's called The Small Room.
And you can find it at www.thesmallroom.net. The second thing is that I have a minor gripe about the
PMM. Some labels have been uploading some of their artist songs, which is great, but they put
their label name in the band name column. That means the band name and the song name are smashed
together in the song name column. That makes it a pain in the arse to read, so I just skip those songs
completely. One example is a whole series of tracks uploaded by K records. Can we get another
column put in for a label name if the track has one please? Well, that's about it.
I reckon I must owe you a beer for all the smalls you've given me on the train. When you make
it out to Oz, sing out. No, shout your one down at the pub. Cheers. Oh. Scrunch up.
Yeah, of course. You're from down under. Expect no. A lot of guys in it. A lot of aviation
guys are scrunchers. I've noticed. PMM. Yeah, absolutely. That's one of the changes that's planned.
In fact, we're even thinking about taking a little bit further. Besides having artist song,
it would make sense to maybe have an album tag in there. Of course, a label,
because you're right. That's incorrect. I mean, it's not incorrect. It's the only way we're able to
do it with the system the way it is today. How about venue? That's something that I thought would
might be interesting. If you look at Pod Show Plus and how all of that would integrate where
you can be a podcaster, but you could also be a venue if you have a big backyard or if you
haven't venue. And why wouldn't you attach artists to your venue? So people can easily navigate.
This is what the whole social media network is about, is how you connect all these different things.
Oh, man, we had a great conversation yesterday about, you know, the next, the next couple releases
that we're going to do. It's, it's, you've seen now we've put the un-bata sign up at the top,
because it is, it is still beta, but man, we are working hard and bringing in new features all the
time. And I think in the next couple weeks, we'll, I'll, I should be able to announce and list all the
things that either have changed or about to change. And, you know, we continue to fix bugs and
annoyances throughout the day. For you, interested in my aviation hobby, I have to go to the
Netherlands to visit Casplastre Mike. We have, you know, we have to sit down and chat about, well,
about, you know, the final release I would say of Casplastre. You know, we've talked a lot about
a Casplastre pro, not quite sure where we stand with that, or, you know, we've got to think about that,
also Casplastre for video. And, you know, just, you know, not just a quick Skype chat. This is,
you know, like a couple hours sit down, hang out. So, here's what I've done. I told him that I
would come visit him in the Netherlands. He lives not far from an airfield where, that I've been
too before, it's pretty accessible. But it'll be during the week. Now, I was thinking about maybe
this week, but, you know, with Patricia's sister coming and just a lot of stuff going on. And,
although the weather today actually would be pretty much perfect. I looked at the Maytars and Tafs
and it would have been great. It's going to happen next week. Sometime midweek probably,
and it will be my first solo crossing of the English channel. And, uh, it's a little daunting.
It's, you know, kind of a Lindbergh-airhardt feel that I've got there. And, and I will be recording
the whole thing. So, from start to finish, and I wanted you to know that in the event that,
that I don't make it, you know, uh, my end, my I River, I'm sure will contain the recording,
because it's solid state. So, once it's on, it can short out, but it'll still be in the memory.
So, make sure you get that, because that'll have some great fucking sound. Okay.
What was the other thing? What's something else? Okay. That was it. All right.
Couple, uh, voicemail, uh, feedbacks through our voicemail line, which you might now hopefully have
programmed into your cell phone, plus two-o plus one for the US-201-625-6357,
in the UK plus four four two zero seven six eight one three seven five three.
Two calls I want to play for you that came in about numbering the shows. I question yesterday.
You know, how long should I keep talking about which number episode it is? You know, should I go all the way up to 10,000?
Is that what I should be doing? Hey Adam, it's Jerry from anapolis, and I was up into Charlie 436.
And I, I too had that thought about the numbering scheme, which initially was really great,
because for those of us who were listening to it on an iPod and searched for the latest steps
to, that sort of thing, it was really nice to be able to see the number and kind of mentally remember,
oh yeah, I hadn't heard that one yet or whatever, and to hear it audibly at the first thing in the,
in the field, or near the first thing that you have these insertions. That's great.
Now the issue obviously is that the scales, you know, the numbering gets a little app out of
the radio just and it almost sounds a little bit, you know, as if you're bragging, you know,
hey, I want to show 10,000. So instead, you know, there are some things mainstream,
maybe media and publishing do well, and it has some good ideas, I suppose, and one of them would be
the notion of season numbers or volume numbers, that sort of thing, so you can keep the episode numbers
down to it all raw. So you can have something like, you know, season four, episode 10, that's
sort of thing, and it's still numbering and still is a one-up thing that a serial number if you
will, that people can relate to, but it's not quite too cumbersome to get around looking down
the future here. So anyway, my two cents worth, it's country.
I'm not bad there for a scruncher, some good thoughts, and there were some contrary and
views, of course. Start eight, four, seven, nine, four, five. Um, this is good doctrine from the
carcass, come to you live from beautiful sunny Seattle, Washington. Yep, for a change it is sunny
you're calling and respond to your Monday episode, and your question about whether or not we should
be using numbers that are getting a podcast, the numbering, which episode it is, and I got to tell
you, if it was good enough for John Luke's a car and Captain Kirk, it's damn well good enough
for Adam Curry. Boulder. Yeah, of course, Jamie is my friend. Yeah, you know, listening to a
couple of those comments, I finally figured it out. It's real simple. Why don't you guys
create the tags for them? You know what number I'm at, you know what number I need, send in a couple,
you know, make it a little more entertaining. I think that's probably the best thing we can do.
It can be just a voicemail. You call in. It can be a little piece you produce. I don't care.
Send it in. What are we out today? I mean, the 437 is not what I said. Yeah, we're at 437 today.
Send in the, you know, send in another 50 or something. So I have a little stack and can just pull
from it. That of course is the way we do it here on the chat. Yeah. Hey Adam and Seth,
Paul Parkinson from Pressing 12 and Paul Parkinson magazine. I just had a quick one, mate.
Thanks very much for having this voice now. I think it really works extremely well.
I'm Jennifer's kind of say I love it. I mean, absolutely awesome. And I'm just looking
forward to episode 3 and 4 on however many more you do. And just want to say that. Thanks
very much. Oh, and, um, Boulder. Yeah, of course. I figured as much.
Hey, we got some more cool shows coming out of Pod Show LA, including Flashers Universe.
You're going to crap yourself when you see that. Here's new leaf from the Pod Save Music Network.
Yeah, those amazing worlds I never thought I had. She said, yeah, just close your eyes.
Lay our hands down and let your friends feast. Hold them now because I'll take you over this
down tonight on my magic cup until all I'm done. I'll take you away from the rising light.
Oh, she said, she'll never do so. She'll better feel, that I'll swear on the dream.
I've been in a scene like red, we played, I didn't see. And she said, yeah, just close your eyes.
Lay our hands down and let your friends feast. Hold them now because I'll take you over this
down tonight on my magic cup until all I'm done. I'll take you away from the rising light.
Oh, she said, yeah, just close your eyes.
Oh, she said, yeah, just close your eyes. Lay our hands down and let your friends feast.
Take over now and I'll take you over this down tonight on my magic cup until all I'm done.
Take you over this rising light. Take you over now and I'll take you over this down tonight on my magic
cup until all I'm done. I'll take you away from the rising light. This is you never left me before.
The magic carpet by new leaf from Sweden, it's all good, as you see would say.
All right, everybody, that's it for today's source code. So tomorrow, apparently the lady Patricia will be on
remember to send her emails, okay? Adam at curie.com or adamantpodshow.com if you really want your email to get there and bypass all the spam
crap and daily source code.com for all your comments. Talk to you tomorrow, everybody. Bye bye.
Cast and more great ones like you on the high performance podcast delivery network from podshow and limelight networks.