Think Advertising sucks.
Think you can do better?
Pod Show and EarthLink are willing to put our money where your mouth is.
Listen to this podcast or go to adchelens.podshow.com to see how you can win big
in the EarthLink make advertising better challenge.
Delta Sierra Charlie 396.
Remember how much you loved your old gameboy?
Yeah, well that was on your 12th.
From the man who invented podcasting comes...
Adam Curry's Game Man.
Adam Curry's Game Man is a fully interactive unit ready to give you hours of fun and
believe you schooling with pleasure.
Just turn on Adam Curry's Game Man.
Grab the Adam Curry's Game Man joystick and you're ready for the ride of a lifetime.
Wow, check out that vibrating action!
Adam Curry's Game Man has thousands of titles to choose from including such arcade classics.
As Donkey Dog.
Shinn Ball Wizard and our special Charlie in the chocolate factory tie-in.
Fudge Man.
That one's an Adam Curry's Game Man favorite.
If you're the competitive type and like being on top.
Adam Curry's Game Man will accommodate your level of self-play by automatically adjusting
to the hardness of the action to suit what you can handle.
And every Game Man can be linked together with a special coupling harness so you can share
Adam Curry's Game Man experience with all your friends.
And with every purchase of Adam Curry's Game Man, we'll throw in a limited edition copy of
Big Nations Hairless Marvel Ball Bag, maybe a two.
Return of the dirty Sanchez.
Don't be left behind.
Call 1-198C Game Man or find us on the web at Adam Curry's Game Man Feeper.com.
Order yours today and put the sheer power of Adam Curry's Game Man and the palm of your hand tonight.
Adam Curry's Game Man, not only you're in a state of fantasy,
poppers' batteries and lubricant not included Adam Curry's Gold Fist joystick sold separately.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
Transmaders?
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need noss.
Dinking.
Transmader?
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic.
Here's Adam Curry.
I don't need to talk about it.
We've probably heard of it before.
But if you see me walking around here, please open up your door.
And when the sun comes out, you know I'm gonna shout.
I'll never feel the way I do.
Like I feel with you.
No.
It seems like here's it's been warm like this.
Deep inside my soul.
From the summer wind comes.
Knowing in there's something I really gotta show.
So let the sunshine get's gonna be fine.
I'll never feel the way I do.
Like I feel with you.
No.
Don't.
Don't be surprised if I want more.
If you need to talk about it fine, let everybody know.
Because we can't hide the way it started or how it's gonna grow.
So let the sun come out, let everybody shout,
I don't want to ever feel the way like I feel with you.
With you.
No more summer time.
I can't believe Jess Smith left out the cowbell.
No more summertime blues, it is brand new from Jeff Smith, you can find them at the
Podsight Music Network or at the JeffSmith.com, G-E-O-F-F Smith, links of course in the
show notes.
And thank you very much, Danny Boyle, was in the office in San Francisco and show
enough, lots of stuff there, waiting my arrival, no matter how short it was, dear Podfather.
Please accept this gift of a drumstick, throw my way by the drummer during the hooting
the blowfish concert at the Concord Pavilion in 1995.
Surely it won't help your rhythm, it doesn't seem to help mine, but what else should
be done with a single drumstick of the chartered list of nothing, Danny Boyle?
I just use it, Danny.
Thank you, man.
Really, really appreciated.
Very nice.
10 year old drumstick.
And then American Classic, 5B.
Everybody, welcome to the Daily Source Code, just arrived from San Francisco a couple
hours ago, Patricia and I unpacked, which usually means I unpack the studio and reinstall
it and then sit around while she unpacks the suitcases and we're both kind of floating
around a good flight and I have to say, man, it's so cold, I can't believe it.
Oh, it was like 53 degrees outside when we landed.
Oh, not good, not friendly at all, but there is some sunshine now and then and they've
had notoriously shitty weather for the past week or so, but everyone's great, really the
whole operation was success here where Christina was great to her grandparents, you know,
the 80 year olds with power tools didn't do any structural damage to the, to the, to the
cottage and the animals are all still alive, yeah, it's good.
So we're feeling pretty good and of course I promised to do a show for you and I don't
think Patricia's going to be dropping by on this one.
She was really, really just, yeah, a little bit out of it and of course everyone, you
know, there's a lot of talk in the, the house is full, so there's just a lot going on.
We're probably going to collapse a little bit later on, but I did want to get a Charlie
out to you.
There's a lot of stuff I got to catch up on so much backlog of great phone calls, great audio
comments.
So since I too am a little bit on the, on the jet laggy side, let me, yeah, just to play a couple
things for you.
This, this, what I've got lined up for you right here, I've been saving for several days.
You remember we had Malcolm Call from Abu Dhabi?
Well, Malcolm now recorded a audio comment and sent it in and this is a really interesting
guy and I'm very proud to have him as a listener of the Charlie.
Is it already too late?
Can I still resist the sirens on of the cyber collective, the pull of the podosphere?
Well I end the very near future, download castblaster and let FedEx bring me a high
LPR 40.
And if so, why?
How did I get to this decision-making moment?
For a year I've been a loyal, enthusiastic, but totally passive listener to the Adam Curry
show.
How did I discover the Charlie?
Probably through something I read on one of the media-related blogs I subscribed to,
write a business team, saffronpost on losscremote.com, a dip from Canyata Cheese on the thought
provoking unmediated.org, maybe a mention by Zeni or Cori on buying.net.
My interest in webcasting in general, video as well as audio became more focused, when
Kleiner Perkins and Sequoia Capital announced the funding of Pod Show Incorporated.
As a media professional, I'm sincerely interested in business models which break new ground.
With the less, Delta Sierra Charlie was still for me, a one-way experience, a pleasurable,
fascinating daily rendezvous with the Curry's, with comic strip blogger, with Roger
Smalls, with audio comments from Enterprising Antipedeans, from civilized, if defensive,
set the ethical and countless eloquent yanks.
I'm sure many listeners like me look juryate by proxy in virgin upper classes, add them
jets to the condo, and then back to Guilford.
I imagine myself in a cartage of my own in Sari, which would be wonderful since my daughter
will be starting at a sixth form college near Dawking as of September.
Then recently the phone lines were opened, and I entered the call in number under DSC in
the phone book of my Sony Ericsson mobile.
My contribution to the yanks versus the Brits was a spontaneous bit of time wasting at my
desk, where I prefer to remain at lunchtime, outside in Abu Dhabi the noon time temperature
is already in the sticky mid-30s, and yes, it was great fun to hear my piece included
in DSC 390.
But if I do download cast blaster, if I do commence an audio cast of my own, it will
be because of Friday's show with Patricia.
Was it the fickle finger of fate, morphic resonance, ground control to major tom, indeed,
back in 1969 I directed the video.
So I guess it was a sign, and I guess I'd better get cast blaster right now.
In the meantime, to Adam and Patricia, Bob Voyage, Guilter Reiser from Malcolm in Abu
Dhabi.
How cool is that?
So I looked it up and showed enough Malcolm was the director of the major tom video for
David Bowie, and it's hard to find Malcolm Thompson and it was hard to find any information
on him, but now I know what he's doing in Abu Dhabi, and actually there's a fantastic
picture of him on flicker, which so completely fits the voice, and I'm going to post a link
to that.
He's a consultant from music plus, which is for a satellite outfit in, I guess it's
based on, I think it is based in Abu Dhabi.
Very cool, Malcolm, and we've got to get you a DSC or my friend, there's just so many
times, you could listen to the S, so sing a ways, you know what I mean?
Greetings, I think it's the top toe here from the blood cast, the sign come garden at
the moment, like nearly all proceedings just finished in the background.
I've got three things, I want to say, number one, night.
So first of all, this is the lovely duct toe, who you probably know from the blood cast,
if you don't know or from the blood cast, you might know her from second life.
She hangs out with cars all the time in a real life as well, and she's got a special
place in the Charlie.
Well, it's probably not going to appreciate me sharing this information, but both here
and I suffer from night sweats on and off, and it is an up and night mess, and I think
it happens when we're understress or under pressure, but it's horrible, you know, and
I don't have enough sheep to keep changing them, I think you're in testing them for
water proof sheets.
You know, that's interesting, because ever since I started talking about having night sweats,
there's been an incredible, just an outpouring of people who are saying, yeah, I have that
too, even my partner, Ron, I didn't know this about him, I know a lot about Ron, I had
no idea that he also has night sweats, and he didn't really cop to it right off the
bat, but I could tell by his interest level, I was like, oh, wait a minute, something
going on here, this seems to be something that happens to a lot of people.
I have to say, and he also used to sleep naked, maybe too much information, but I have
to say ever since I started wearing box of shorts and wife beaters to bed, the night sweats
are a thing of the past, my friends.
The two, if you had your first second life dream yet, I'd have two nights in a row, and
it's quite disturbing, everything is in second life.
Number three?
I have a duck, duck toe.
This is not good, you should not be having dreams from past second life.
I also asked around, as a couple other people, and I don't know many people who have
had second life dreams, and by the way, I haven't really been on second life at all,
except for briefly in the pajama party, so now that I'm back in the time zones are all
shifted, I'll definitely check in again.
Saturday, we actually want to see if we can open up the palace, open up the palace, open
up the casino, have some fun.
Oh yeah, I really enjoyed everyone hanging around chatting around the castle, that's
a couple of nights ago, and then the pole dances came, and you know, how do we just think
this something more crazy to do in person life?
Here, anyway, enjoy the show.
Bye.
Thanks, Doc.
If you've got a voicemail comment, love to hear from you.
Two phone numbers in New Jersey, zero as in class, yeah, two zero one, six to five,
six three five seven in London, zero two zero seven six eight one three seven five three,
and of course, plenty of voicemails and messages left about Carlos 395 daily source code,
we had some technical difficulties, and I do want to get into this just a little bit.
First of all, I'm delighted so many people seem to enjoy the show, and, you know, it
does seem to be that whenever I get emotional, it doesn't matter which way the emotions
are going, people really like it, and they like it even more when Patricia laughs at me.
Hey, Adam, this is Tristan Tom, comment out of the San Francisco Bay area with regards
to daily source code number 395, and the problems that you were having with your mixer
and microphone combination.
I think one of the cardinal rules of professionalism is don't call attention to
problems, just continue on as if there's no problem, and most of the listeners probably
wouldn't even notice anyway.
Wow, so there's a lot in that statement right there.
First of all, professional, I mean, what is professional?
I thought we all agreed professional means you get paid for something instead of amateur,
root word, which comes from stems from doing something for love, and I think I'm much
more amateur than I am, professional, but isn't the whole point of podcasting is not
to Matt, well, I guess it's not the point, but isn't the beauty of podcasting often that,
you know, you get it with the warts and all the crap all bundled in it.
I have to say, even though I considered stopping that and starting the recording all over
again many times, I really enjoy the response, and I think the outcome was actually much
better than if we had stopped and started to re-record everything, particularly because
now you hear how Patricia is kept me sane for 20 years, but also please understand that
this was not just, you know, what you were hearing was not what I was hearing, and that
is partially my fault, but it was impossible to communicate because, you know, I have a
certain way of talking to the microphone, it's the same mixer, the same microphone, everything
was all the same, almost everything was the same, I have to say.
If all of a sudden you have to like step back and you can't pop your keys and you have
to be so self-conscious of stuff, it's very hard to work that way, and so yeah, it may
have sounded professional, quote, professional, but I would have been too preoccupied with
trying to keep the sound sane in my, you know, the stuff that I was hearing.
But getting flustered and frustrated and whining and just killing, it's human, it really
doesn't help, and also you come across as being a baby, but professional, no, when you
do that.
Human.
Problem with the majority of listeners didn't even notice any problem, and I can
know.
Yeah, that's not true, man.
This show, if, if I had not said anything, people would have, it would have been exactly
the opposite, it would have been, everyone's focus would have somehow gone to the popping
sounds and all the crapping, crapping out sounds that we had, so I don't think that's
it true, I think people definitely would have noticed, and that would have become a focus
of attention.
Just stand that you noticed it, because you are a perfectionist and you really pay attention
to that kind of stuff, and even if a few people, let's move, even if you listeners, even
if they did notice, I don't think it's a big deal, I mean, your show sounds great, the
majority of the time, I'm sure people will understand if one or two shows a year aren't
optimal in terms of the quality, the audio quality, but making such a big deal out of it,
getting off-flustered, yelling and screaming, getting worked up, I think that's very
unforecracked.
It's so exciting and good.
Had you just continued on with the normal show, not called attention to the problem,
I think it would have even been a big deal, nobody would have even noticed, so I mean,
just simply not calling attention to what I think would have been a solution, or I guess
you could have started the show again, you know, the problem started the show again, but
I think you did the wrong thing in terms of getting all worked up about it.
Anyway, just my comments continue on with the great work I love the show, and I will continue
listening.
This is Tristan from the San Francisco Bay area signing out.
Oh, Tristan.
And by the way, of course, I appreciate the feedback, but here's what happened, and a whole
bunch of technical guys were on to a right away, Cas Blaster Mike sent me an email, he said
that he had to dry off his keyboard from crying, he was laughing so hard, but the power
supply that I had acquired just wasn't strong enough.
In fact, after I figured out that this indeed was the problem, I felt the power supply
with my hand, it was boiling hot, so what really happened was I never, yeah, I tested it
with two microphones, and both microphones worked, but what I hadn't figured, it affected
into the equation is that Patricia's brand new headphones, because I don't, we didn't
really get to talk about that, but we went to buy headphones because probably the same
issue with the power supply, when she was using the earbuds, it didn't work at all,
she couldn't hear anything.
That's when we were in the Waldorf Astoria, and we did our show from there on Wednesday,
last Wednesday.
So, she got these beautiful, what are they Sony's?
I think they're Sony's.
Yeah.
Sony, dynamic stereo headphones, the MDRV600, it's like there's 8 million headphones.
She says, I want that one, I want that one there, and she points to it, and that's what
she wanted, and the $200 headphones, but man, are they good, but the power supply couldn't
drive the amplifier to power both her headphones and my headphones.
Whenever we really started to, whenever it was an over-modulation, when we talked into the
Mikely loudly, or whenever she laughed, which is, I love it when she laughed and to have
everything crap out, the mixer literally would start shutting down, and to add the insult
to injury, I was listening to a whole different mix, I had messed around with so many buttons
trying to figure this out, trying to be professional, trying to not let on that something
was wrong, and trying to fix it while Patricia and I were talking, multitasking, that I
hit some wrong buttons, I was listening to a completely wrong output, and it sounded like
total crap to my ears.
Hey, I just got finished listening to the podcast 395, to the whole thing, we had to listen
to you, bitching and moaning about the sound, the sound effects and everything, and you had
to wrong input into your head the whole time, so we had to suffer because you said
it up front.
Do a little show prep, you don't make us do that, or do I.
I've done so much show prep, but I thought I had it all squared away anyway, we're back
to the old sound.
Actually, now I'm using these new Patricia headphones, and I'm not sure what the, it all
sounds great.
Now, it's very hard to make it sound shitty, I hope it's not just the headphones.
So I mentioned at the end of yesterday's show that where Earthlink is putting their
money where your mouth is, and we want you to create a great Earthlink commercial that
fits within a podcast, fits within a daily source code, or the podcast if you're liking
actually.
We've called it the ad challenge, you can find that at adchallenge.podshow.com and
there's a couple of examples.
You could do a jingle, you could do a commercial, you could do an endorsement, and really
you can do anything you want, you don't necessarily have to have it fit exactly in one
of those three categories, but for all those people who moaned about the Earthlink commercial
now is your shot, and by the way, you can actually win very valuable cash prizes if you
do participate, and if you are a winner, and there will be many winners.
3rd one uses for baby wipes, welcome you to the Daddy Battle.
It's Daddy Panel number two with James B from Face the Music, the Naval Cast.
Yeah, I can go ahead and do whatever I want, and since I'm breastfeeding, it's fine.
Petey Love from the Daddy Cast, Love House Radio, Interview with the Stranger, and 17,000
other podcasts, I can't remember the name of it.
Give your kid a poker chip in the middle of the mall.
Yeah, we're playing Texas hold of it tonight, you know.
And we're joined by a new member this week, and that is Ringmaster Gregg from Dancing With
Elephants.
Welcome Gregg.
Well, as I recall, I believe I might have set my palm pilot count it off six weeks
and set my palm pilot with a day.
Okay, that's a total geek out right there.
With your host, did it's great.
On the Daddy Panel, we discuss issues like House and News 2 soon, don't I mean, there's
too much TV, really a bad thing?
How do you reward your kid for good behavior?
I think I threatened more, if I'm not happy, ain't nobody happy.
Find us on the web at 1-0-1-usesforbabywipes.com.
We're also an iTunes, the podcast, music network, and your favorite podcast director.
God.
I've got to say, man, once again, we had a great trip with Virgin Atlantic.
Those people really got it figured out.
I am now apparently a unique customer, and I found this out when I checked in.
And what happens is during the flight, even sitting in the lounge, Virgin employees
will come up to me and introduce themselves, and as to anything we can do, and of course,
I was asking for strippers and gotten none of that.
But it was great.
It was so nice once again, just that extra little attention to detail, which is paying
for crying out loud, that I didn't really even feel like bitching about the fact that
we had an older model airplane, or interior at least, so we didn't have the full on-demand
system yet to wait for all the movies to start, which kind of suck.
Oh, I saw the movie Prime.
Oh, no, I'm sorry, not Prime.
Proof with the Gueneth Paltro.
Wow, what a great movie, what a beautiful story, and if you haven't seen that movie, it's
probably on DVD.
I didn't even heard of it before, so maybe you want straight to video, but you have
to check this movie out.
If you're into a really good story, Anthony Hopkins also co-stars, it's really only
three main actors, it's all about the story in this case.
As Wednesday, which means we've got the Frank Truth coming up on serious sad light stars
102, Michael Butler, of course, with the Rock and Roll indie cast Gilmore Daily Dawn and
Drew, yeast radio, but first we've got Pacific Coast Hellway standing by for you on serious
stars 102, as our satellite window is closing.
I'll talk to all you guys on the sad light tomorrow on our Thursday show.
For those of you here on the podcast, another piece of ketchup I have to do is about
second life and the financial model about inflation.
You remember that we got a little bit of feedback about that from the financial aid podcast,
and here's a follow-up, which we, of course, placed into our 10-foil hat moment.
Hey, Adam, I'm a follow-up to your questions.
Reverseing inflation in the video game's second life is tough, but stopping it is easy.
Linden Labs just needs to stop creating more money than it takes out of circulation.
The biggest sources of inflation are the second life welfare payments every Tuesday,
$500 paid subscribers, $50 free subscribers, and the traffic bonuses where landowners
who have highly traffic sims get additional payouts.
The latter is coming to an end this month, but a second life gets more popular, the welfare
payments will either have to continue causing inflation, or Linden Labs will need to find
a different way to get new players into the game, with a reasonable amount of starting
cash while keeping the economy stable.
Incidentally, you probably don't want Alan Green's ban running the second life economy
or any economy.
Green Green spends 10 years fed chairman, U.S. currency inflated from $3.5 trillion
to $10.2 trillion, over the span of 19 years, a $7 trillion increase.
A $1,000 purchase in 1987 would today cost you $1,681.
Put another way, $1.00 at the beginning of Green's spends 10-year would today only be worth
$59 cents.
Again, some conspiracy theorists and economists believed that the extra $7 trillion he created
had to go somewhere, and that somewhere was the stock market bubble of the late 90s.
The housing bubble now.
The golden freshest metals bubble just starting, and the fossil fuel bubble on the horizon,
which hopefully Trinity will be an answer to.
This is Chris from the Financial Aid podcast with a follow-up on the tinfoil hat moment.
Check us out at financialadepodguest.com.
Thank you, man.
Appreciate it.
Okay, so for those of you who have never heard of second life, it's a virtual world where
you can basically chat, but you interact with other people, but you can build things and
create things.
Their own currency is called Linden Dollars, after the Linden Corporation who runs this
virtual world, and I got a real problem.
Now the Pod Show Palace is on a rented piece of land.
This is about all this about this inflation stuff.
And I've only paid one month's rent, and so another month's rent is due today, I believe.
But the rent was raised significantly, just with an IAM from Miss Business Week, Miss
Anci Chung, because of inflation within second life.
Now what this means is that if I were to actually put, it's like $25, not a huge deal.
So I still put the same US dollars in there, but if I'm using money that I earned within
second life, it's worth less than it was a week ago, and I actually have to pay more
for the rent.
This makes no sense.
First of all, I think I'm getting jacked by Miss Chung Enterprises.
There's no real, yeah, there's a kind of, I don't know what kind of contract there is.
I mean, it's just like, here's this piece of land painting now and you're done.
Now she's raising, raising, raising, raising, this way, if inflation continues, no one will
be able to make any money, because money you want to take out of the game, I'll just
call it a game in this instance, and turn it into US currency, you have a huge disadvantage
with these inflation rates.
So I'm very bearish on second life, and if this inflation continues, I'm out because
it's stupid, and if they really want to work something out, besides having the next
generation user interface, what's up, baby, what do you, why, what's funny, I'm, I have
to laugh.
Why?
Well, I was just actually walking by, and at could hear you talk about second life.
I explained the inflation, but I explained what it was.
Yeah.
So it's as fucked up as you know, I, there you go, thank you, thank you very much.
It is as fucked up, and I said phones, yeah, floating away, floating, floating, floating
on.
And my name is Larry, and I'm a Libra, and I get out of here, and I'm right, fuck you very
much, Mr. Adam Kerry, but stupid microphone, it's no need to worry.
The AC European correspondent is here, and I am not speaking from my rear.
I was living in six EU lens, so it's me, who EU understands.
What's up in EU nowadays, it's another EU announcement phase, Bulgaria and Romania are joining,
and all EU workers find it disappointing, Bulgaria and Romania come to EU in 2007, but
first to Germany comes soccer heaven, where at the Cup 2006 starts on 9th June, and it
could be fun, and not Danish cartoon, cheap airlines in Europe there's a lot, so come to Germany
and enjoy soccer part.
Oh, y'all, comic strip blogger everybody, oh, actually I should have done your comic strip.
Comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, if you thought inflation was a reason
to get pissed off at second life, check out this message.
Adam, I've just come to a little second life, and it's always a new version of everyone
I've got to download it, we have done, and I just want to go through the release notes,
and on the other changes, the first sentence, the ability to create joins has been removed
in the tools, man, you've always talking about the same kind of joins,
to just mean the second lungs to the visual world, as well as the SAC or the Cruisal,
no more second lungs than the potfala.
I didn't know that that was on the toolbar to start with, I still got a couple in my inventory though,
that's for sure.
Yeah, Adam, this is Mike Colin from Cali, I'm a listener slash geek who occasionally works
on install projects, and about a month ago I worked on a thousand plus blanks on install
for two of the major record labels, and so first off, when I trip to get an inside look at the
record business from top to bottom, but at the same time, I got to tell you, I've been in a
lot of different industry offices and record books or pigs, I mean, I've never seen someone
to crap in my life, and the amount of money being spent on crap, man, I was hoping to see
the word podcast somewhere, but no luck, in fact, it was kind of sad to see all the CDs and
old media, no digital players, it was kind of like it was taboo or something.
You know when it comes to these albums being leaked early, I was surprised to see these
record labels. I mean, it was ridiculous in the average office and think stack of CDs being
set to folks way before release. It's crazy, but if you were any of the crew on a little
debriefing on the other street, I saw, let me know and I'll leave my contact info on another
call on Casey Wanda, use this comment. See ya, dickier.
Yo dude, so totally would like you to call on with more intel on what's going on in the mainstream
record companies, I would be very cool.
All right, one last song before I wrap her up for today. And of course, tomorrow will be back
and I'll be awake and a Patricia will drop by in some of all kinds of songs.
Strange Day in Mexico, it's the Clintons.
Is it true that we are nothing more than about to send in that basement?
The more that we keep looking at, the harder we are, but the record keeps on spinning,
while the volume's right down. And you don't say since the end, falling in and out of life,
a strange day in Mexico, a strange day in Mexico, a strange day in Mexico, a strange day in Mexico,
a strange day in Mexico, a strange day in Mexico, a strange day in Mexico,
A strange day and next, a strange day and next
As in a strange day and next, a strange day and next
What is this stuff always happening to me?
A strange day and next, a strange day and next
As in a strange day and next, a strange day
And next, a strange day and next, a strange day and next
As in a strange day and next, a strange day and next
All that song is a little bit of cow milk
Time's day and less, you're gonna get some days on day.
Dude, that's all it needs!
Strings day in Mexico, the Clintons, you can find them on the Podsave Music Network as well, of course.
I'll put in links in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com and at curie.com, and on the Pod Castle every network, we'll get so close.
Okay, so stuff to do this week.
I'll probably be on the phone a lot with San Francisco since we got lots of stuff accomplished in a very short amount of time.
And I'm planning on going back in about a week and a half, probably about 10 days or so, and I'll be on playing back to the condo for a little bit longer stay.
I'm gonna go visit my mom this week and I'm gonna stay two days trying sneak in a discussion with the doctors, which she doesn't want me to talk to.
Oh, what else? Oh, gonna take the in-laws to see Sanatra, which is the Frank Sanatra show here in London.
I think it's at the palladium, so we'll have a full report on that as well.
And as always, I thank you for sticking with me.
I'll see you tomorrow.
We'll get this podcast and more great ones like it on the Hyperformance Podcast to Livery Network from Podshow and LineWight Networks.
I love it.