Hi, this is Ella's Death from The Eclipse podcast, and I'd just like to wish everyone
at btpodshow.com a very merry Christmas and a happy and prosperous 2007.
In a world where content is keen, we have found our queen.
You know, I had two beers last night. That's why I'm all discombobulated. Two whole beers.
You know what that does to me, right? It's the DSC 520 with your lush Adam Kerr.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying to the future.
Oh yeah.
I think you should shine on another World Cup!
If you'd told me it was the chili peppers
I would believe you wouldn't believe you in a heartbeat.
Of course it's not when the pardoncing music
now work at stereotype file with bass.
Hey everybody! How you doing?
Coming to you once again from the soon to be for cottage formerly known as curry cottage. I'm sorry
The dwelling formerly known as the curry cottage in the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Guilford
It is the daily source code episode 520 still having some some issues talking today
Yeah after the show I was I'm pretty happy I did the show before I went to the to the dentist yesterday
Until I went to visit Fiona
Had a nice little root canal done yesterday
I knew it was coming I knew it
So essentially my my cheekbone is infected
It's the pre-molar that that is died off and I'm no big hero when it comes to the dentist
Let me tell you that now in fact, I'm a big fucking pussy and there's only really two things I have a problem with
one is the actual insertion of the
Nova K needle particularly if I already have pain in my mouth. I'm not too fond of that
Although that's just you know like
It's just the thought of it once it actually happens. It's no problem
But then the really thing I'm really afraid of because I've had this happen so many times is that I won't
Have enough numbness and that the dentist will be drilling away
And then all of a sudden we'll like shoot through something like some new plateau and then you know that that drill goes into far and then the pain
She shoots throughout your head so that fucking explodes
I've had that happen so many times I really really to test that
But Fiona's great Fiona
understands me and
And she knows that what I like the most is if I heard it basically walk me through it all and just tell me every single step of the way
What you're doing I enjoyed immensely you know I love to hear about the different lengths in
Files and the drill bits and the electric one and the hydraulic one and
And I learn a lot and it keeps me occupied and she's you know, and of course she she had to swear to me that
That I wasn't going to experience any more pain
There was funny because she was trying to figure out what was wrong, you know, but so
Essentially she had to drill into the tooth which
There was a filling there from years and years ago and of course that it that had probably leaked throughout the years and that's how the
How the root
became infected and and probably died off slowly the tooth was basically dead
But before she went drilling in there
She was tapping around
So funny she's like okay, does this hurt?
I said no really it's my cheek that hurts more, but I know that's related to I thought it was my canine
But that's actually the
The infection was above the canine even though it was part of the root of the pre-mull are right behind it
We're a teeth family, you know that I love teeth
And
So she's tapping with the back of one number instruments, you know like really like like this like
You know hard, you know, it's just this that tenda and it takes it again is that tenda and I like well, you know
It's all right doesn't hurt too much, but she said hmm
Besides the guy you profanive have you taken anything else that might have numb the pain
I just want the big fat one away to the dentist like
What ever could you mean Fiona she knows she knows I smoked the holy herb
I think she was referring to any other substances was said no, but I was like I didn't hurt too much at all
Anyway, so she took care of business and I'm on massive any biotics in fact the people used to die from this
Before the invention of pelicent and a cylinder of course people used to die from all kinds of infections
But if you got an infection like a root canal and it went into your into your bone
Which is essentially where the infection has gone in my case
You know you could die and people used to
The whole thing with dentistry is just so mid-evil you know
It's like a just a leftover
thing, you know
With pliers and files and drill bits and shit. Yeah, there's this great technology involved, but
And I learned something too
She had to take an x-ray and
You know, which consists of
Putting that yucky piece of plastic film on your mouth on a holder while she leaves the room to
Desap the machine
Said you know haven't they come up with a digital variety of this yet?
I mean make so much sense
She said well, they do they do have one so you didn't so there's no more a development of
photographic film
so it is a a digital
I guess
x-ray receiver
She says but it's really impractical for two reasons
One is
It's thick so already you know these things are pretty big you've had it in your mouth
Have you had it in your mouth?
Well, if you had it in your mouth, you know what I'm talking about
But it's also in you know those are pretty thin pieces of film
But this one she she showed me it was about
Probably about three quarters of a centimeter thick and she says just almost impossible for to keep people to keep that in their mouth
In addition to that
There's a U.S.-B cable hanging out of your face where it just is not very convenient
I'm sure that they'll they'll bundle that on to one memory card pretty soon
Well, that's fun so I have to go back the second of January because now the infection has to basically
Subside so I'm on two different types of antibiotics no drinking by the way during this process
So that kind of rules out any even champagne on new years which as you know is not a big deal for me
But still so while that maintenance was taking place on the way back the jag the super v8 flashed a warning message saying
What was it air suspension
malfunction I'm like that doesn't sound good
So I had a really good experience you know I've had the outies and I've had Mercedes and the service on both of those
Mercedes being absolute by far and away the worst and outie being you know so so so so
Called up a H.A. Fox here in Guilford where I purchased the the super v8
I said all right here's what's going on. I said well come on in tomorrow that would be this morning 10 a.m
And it was great you know walk in and say how you doing up mr. Curry have a cup of coffee
Can I have your keys you know within seconds the guys driven this driven the car into the garage
20 minutes comes back well there was a technical service bulletin
And you know of course it's all under warranty will take care of everything and you bring the car back in the 15th
We'll give you replacement car it was so nice so efficient and I do understand now
Why Elton John sir Elton John has all of his maintenance done regardless of car by the way at this particular garage in in Guilford H
You know we say H and I hear the Brits say H
Not quite sure where that came from anyway H.A. Fox they have a fantastic service department
Real happy about that and and it's where Elton has all his vehicles serviced
So yeah my face is still swollen hurts. It's not a pretty site actually
Yesterday we learned that former president Gerald Ford died
H 93 nice age I have to say if you got to go
But I learned so much watching several news reports
You know I was pretty young when he was president and
All I really only knew two things about him. I've never studied him or you know
Ever really ever thought about him other than oh that's the guy who filled in when Nixon got kicked out
Then that and and that's the goofy guy
That filled in when Nixon got kicked out
He wasn't quite that goofy as it turns out
In fact, he was very athletic
Quite a scholar
But he was always portrayed I think by the press as this bumbling idiot
And I'm really happy that that I learned a little bit more about him and and I've started to look around and read up on him
And he did some pretty interesting things in fact now you're seeing posthumously people are praising him which is very nice
But you know
It's goes to show man how long shit can stick to you
Because I was convinced that he was just a goofy guy who just kind of hung in there for a
For a couple of years
Man more presidential news
Now this is very interesting let me
Let me bring up the the video for you
This is from YouTube which was shot yesterday apparently by Andrew Barron of rocket boom fame
I'm going to a YouTube page right now
Check this out. I'm John Edwards and I'm in the upper ninth ward of New Orleans where
We've been working this afternoon and I'll be along with these kids who are working behind me
I try to restore a home those that was devastated by the hurricane and tomorrow morning from this place
So what you're seeing here is John Edwards in front of it almost looks like he's in Africa
You know this dirt and and like a hut behind him and it's actually
housing in
New Orleans in Louisiana
All right to here comes
I'll announce that I'm a candidate for president United States
What I will do is ask millions of Americans including you
To join me in taking action and taking responsibility
Not sitting around waiting for somebody else to do it, but actually going out and doing it ourselves
So the first of all, I think it's very cool that he denounced the announcement of his announcement for president for running for president
On YouTube that makes a lot of sense. However, I'm a little confused now because looking through the bloggo sphere
I see that Robert Scobel
You know he was
I apparently had been invited
To be a part of the announcement which takes place today and you can follow that on the scobalyzer weblog
And you'll see that
He was very secretive about what it was going to do and and then he said oh well shit
It looks like the announcement was already made indeed. I'm going to be following or be traveling along with
with presidential hopeful
John Edwards
and then I read on
Andrew Barron
Who produces rocket boom. I read on his weblog
That he actually filmed this pre-announcement and put it up on YouTube interesting not on
Interesting enough not on his own feed or on the rocket boom feed, but on the John Edwards YouTube page
And so excuse me with some split up
So it sounds to me
Like like both these guys and perhaps more video bloggers
We're invited exclusively to cover this announcement and to to ride along with the with the Edwards campaign
But they certainly did not know that there were other quote exclusive
Reporters and
It's going to be very interesting to follow this so it seems like the Edwards campus in synonym decks has made a conscious decision to involve bloggers and
And video bloggers in the process of the campaign which I think is fantastic
But now I want to see how good we're going to be are we really going to be able to ask the and I say we as in we the peeps
Citizen journalists are we going to be able to ask the tough questions. Do we know enough about the issues at hand?
And already it seems like there's some confusion here. You know, was someone supposed to have an exclusive
Why the secrecy why couldn't anyone say anything
Speaking of Andrew Barron he's he announced they uh, I should look this up for you
He announced a new initiative
Hold on, let me just go to his page. What is it? Dembot?
I think them yet dembot.com
He's announced the new initiative called Abby Studios and
Of course this caught my eye or should I say caught my vanity filters
He did a blog post here on Christmas day. I've spent quite some time investigating pod show and pod tech. Uh-oh
Colombo on the trail. I've watched both of them form and grow. I've met the people behind the businesses and I've asked a lot of questions
Okay, well, we certainly
Met a couple times don't remember a lot of questions
uh
Anyway, so uh, there's uh, what does he call it?
Abby Studios not intended to be a brand network for shows that's a creative studio for people
So um, very interested to see what comes out of that and he's doing it with
Jeff Palmer who I know from the early internet days we certainly emailed a lot back and forth and they've really got to do anything together
So okay, we'll see
I have learned though that announcing that kind of stuff online, you know something that big and then having a
A web page up that adjusts his empty. Let me see if he's done anything with it. Abby
Uh
No, it still says Abby core. Yeah
You know people get you know you announce something like that. That's pretty lofty goal, you know
It sounds like he's got something pretty big cooking. I'm very interested to see what what his idea is
and how much it'll differ from what we're doing
But uh, you know, so far a lot of talk
So and I've learned that you can't really talk too much. You got to kind of show something after a while people get really antsy
And then they start to post negative shit
I've changed uh, yet again some stuff in the setup here
uh, p-dub
Notice that there was something distinctly out of phase about my voice and it's own it only happens when I'm hooked up to the
To the stereo valve processor here at home and not one of them in San Francisco in my other home
So I've reversed the phase on the microphone. I don't know if you can tell or not or if it makes any difference to you
But we've entered into this fascinating conversation about about microphone
Techniques and measurements and and and and really it's probably something you can't hear anyway
And the only piece I have today that I want to play for you that comes from the outside world is a bit of a shocker
um
Now maybe it's not a bit of a shocker, but it does give me a little more insight
Into the ongoing saga
Okay, I don't know who this is but stop fucking calling jizzell asshole
Well, we know who this guy is now listen to the latest
Message from jizzell hi Adam it's jizzell
I'm sorry I haven't been in touch. I've had a lot going on
Long story short. I left my husband and
It's okay. I'm in a better place now
But I just wanted to let you know that I've been thinking about you
Even though I can't listen to your show where I am
But I've really been thinking a lot about you and I miss you and I will hopefully be in touch soon
Okay, I'll be you. Bye
Wow
You know what was kind of freaking that message? She said oh, I hear listen to this. Let me just see if I try and and
It's okay. I'm an investment
Okay, let's listen to this and
It's okay. I'm in a better place now. It's okay. I'm in a better place now. That's what you say about people who are dead. That's horrible
Let me see I got some other stuff I want to talk about today
But first here's one this is a nice piece of email I got from David Manders
Who by the way had a similar experience to myself over the festive period except on his uh
Was it doesn't say which tooth put he had a root canal? He's been on antibiotics for six days really tough for a Brit
No drinking
The shakes and that's it in the next single. I want a better life
We'll be released physical release on the 12th of March
um
David is sending out
copies of the MP3 before goes on to the pod save music network, which will be on
January 8th so once again premiering on pmn before it goes into physical distribution
I love this band. I love their performance at the podcast con uk and I'm very proud to play for you the shakes with a better life
I want to bet a lie I want to bet a lie
More than these four worlds I might have been why if I want to bet a lie
I want to be your man
Because you're pretty cool and you've got sex
And I want to be your man
I want to pick a face
Oh
I want to plan you come I want to plan you come Just like the one man for the only class who allowed me to plan you come
And I want to run the show And I want to run the show
Look down from on high and check me on bail I want to run the show
And I want to plan you come I want to plan you come
And I want to plan you come
Coming to the PMN January 8 is the shakes I want a better life
Here on your daily source code thank you to Stewart Hunter who was paying attention
Here that I got Christina Nintendo DS light he says one game you should pick up is brain age
It's a great application that test your reactions to various puzzles gives you your brain age or how old your brain is
And frequent use of the app is supposed to make you more intelligent an excellent game I shall pick one up at one of those up
What it should really do is it should you know you should give that to your to your kid having played and then it should connect to the internet
And send send the information to the parents that's kind of bad isn't it?
I think about it.
Let's see another controversy or controversy Google apparently has stopped providing many of the erotic and sex blogs in their in their search results
I got a post a link from violet blue on in the show notes about that you have to take a look at it's a very interesting story
And it makes me feel even more happy that we start up this erotic a channel with pod show
Because it's going to be tough for you know when you get companies like Google who are you know deciding what is and is not good for you
And I know that violet blue tiny nipples dot com I know she's got plenty of inbound links and then her page ranks should be way up there
But apparently you got to read the whole story because it's just little it's a little too intricate to explain
Quite frankly I'm not quite sure how it works, but I know that they're not showing up in search results the way they used doing a lot of blogs are showing up
So if you're checking us out on serious satellite stars channel go to daily source code dot com download the rest of the show I guarantee you
You won't be disappointed
Finally got an invite to Facebook
I thought you couldn't get on Facebook unless you had a dot edu email address, but I got an invite so I immediately filled it out
We're shuddled right off got in no problem, but I was really disappointed
First of all I thought it was the way they you know complete your registration and then they right off the bat
They pre filled out my my Gmail email address
And they said I'll just enter your password and we'll automatically suck down your fucking address book and email it to everybody
Now I know that this is the the virality feature, but I felt the way they presented it was very very tricky
It was not clear at all that you're about to spam all of your friends and if you're
You know if you're someone who just likes to you know run get through the registration process quickly
And it almost appears like you have to fill out that that piece of the of information before you can continue
So I figured out you didn't have to as I said it wasn't very apparent and then I went searching but like okay, I'll look for classmates nothing
And maybe I'm just too fucking old
There's like nothing at all
I know I looked at Salem College, which is now known as Salem International
There's no one on there since you know before the class of 2004
Come on, you know we got to get back to the 80s with this stuff
Crap
Oh, well, how did this I was gonna play a song for you, but it looks like a cute up the wrong one, hold on a second
So anyway, so if if you went to Salem College in 1983 so if you were the class of 85 or 86
Send me a message on Facebook, I'm in there as I don't curry. I just maybe I'm not maybe I'm not using a ride or maybe I'm I haven't
Just I don't know it's like this is supposed to be the hot social network for people who want to hook up with people they really used to know and
You know the real networks of people who are connected to each other it just didn't happen for me. Maybe I need to take a little more spend a little more time and work on it
But it'll surprise
You know what it's Thursday
Did not receive an exercise
So in lieu of that give some Kelly Brock cowboy boots and Levi
He can turn you on with the way give a night in his cowboy boots and Levi
In his cowboy boots and Levi
Everything just a little more
It's one of the reasons I can't decide so
We're about to say everything without a legit thing
We're going to play this song again
When he walks on stage, he's ready to burn
Every I follows every entrance under the lights
Y'all boys are robbing his cowboy boots and Levi
In his cowboy boots and Levi
And everything just a little more
It's one of the reasons I can't talk to her
And perhaps everything without a legit thing
We're going to play this song, can't say
So in lieu of that give some Kelly Brock cowboy boots and Levi
He can turn you on with the way give a night in his cowboy boots
And everything just a little more it's one of the reasons I can't decide so
We're about to say everything without a legit thing
We're just little more
really like it cowboy boots and Levi's and before I go I just want to talk to you briefly
about the best of the Charlie's as you know we're moving house starting the first week
of January some next week we'll be packing up and moving all the way through to the second
week of January we'll be moving in moving from the east side to the west side moving on up
everybody. So I've already asked PW up to fill in for me on this serious and what I wanted
to do is have some best of Charlie's rollout and I've already got three that I've received. Here's
what I'd like to do. I need seven more. Send me an email telling me what you want to do what the idea
is that to be about 24 minutes. Actually no a preferably no longer than 24 minutes and 30 seconds
because then we can actually use those both on the on the podcast feed dedicated source code.com
and we can put them straight on to serious satellite tell me what your idea is. I'll confirm it with you
so that we don't run into any trouble where you know we have more people producing them then we
actually have airtime for although of course I could keep putting them on the feed no problem but
and you know there's some pretty creative ideas that people are coming up with so please
if you're so inclined I would I would love for you to help me out and I'm sure we can do
something like send you some fucking whack-out pod show t-shirt as thanks but know that it is really
appreciated and remember January 12th new movie coming out stomp the yard and we have a podcast
all about the movie itself. I want you to go listen to that it's at stompthepodcast.com
Tony Costas of Costas World gets us rolling with the first installment is the second installment
out yet I wonder. So I just take a look for a second stomp the hey it's not auto completing
usually and I guess I haven't looked at it in three days. How long has it taken till those
URLs those auto complete URLs expire in fire fox. Let's see stomp the podcast.
Okay now it looks like it's waiting for the poo poo studios.com which is usually an indication
of the poo poo player. That's pop a uniform pop uniform. Man how much is that suck?
So the page is not loading because I can see it right here it says waiting for poo poo studios.com
and so that's the poo poo player. You know what an exercise in branding? The poo poo player,
the fuck this is horrible. Does not even loading? Oh man. Shit. All right I want to look into that.
Well if you get to it successfully let me know what the poo poo player worked. I got to talk
to Tony about that shit man that's not right. All right everybody so tomorrow of course it
will be our food bar Friday edition. The crap is tomorrow the last one before the new year. I got to do
a special year end so I don't know if I'll be able to produce everything for tomorrow. Otherwise I'll
do it over the weekend before January 1 because I do want to do something a little different. I want
to have a you know kick and ask way to say goodbye to 2006. If you've got any songs of
suggestions any other ideas any other shit you want to send in please do it. Adam at podshow.com
and of course everything in the show notes today at dailysourceco.com I'll see you tomorrow everybody.
Bye bye.
Another podshow podcast sticking in your ear.
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT Podshow media network.
Howard by podshow and limelight network control your part in the show.
And be the podshow.com