Deltasy are a Charlie, triple three.
People of Earth, your attention please.
By playing this audio feedback in the program that you call, cast Blaster, you have unlocked
the secret subliminal message.
Oh yes, Adam has totally sold out.
We are using every trick in the book to get you to sign up to...
That link.
Over $16 million worth of airplanes trapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
Hey, once you waste a Wednesday with me.
Yes, coming to you from the Curry Cottage in the...
Affluent suburb of Surrey and Gilford.
It's a Deltasy source code.
Come along, Blaster.
The low to ever make it back on deck.
I'm a spec between the timbers up a foolish ship.
Ride a river, zulf a loss of feet.
And pour the crop out of any bomb.
Dumb enough to listen to me.
The courtroom's the place for this face.
Ticking the stand, looking my hand.
We'll never before have a bad, bad attention.
Or maybe just a one spot, the guy with some strange stare.
He never showed a long, like terror.
If he didn't want the admirer to have been made,
I went into the bench.
I guess my best defense was the sufferin' silence.
I never find the words when I'm confrontin' violence.
And anyway, do you know anyone who thinks that fast?
When they know the next words gonna be their last.
So don't consume what regret.
My beautiful face is intact yet.
I said, I need you to like me.
I like you didn't find me.
I need you to like me.
Said I need you to like me.
I like you didn't find me.
When I was the time, I was drinking in the fire.
The music on the box sent me, well, higher.
And if you need to have a song that goes along with the rhymes or the time
that it let my fires.
I don't know what I was thinking.
I was just playing on the drums when the shoot I've been drinking.
But the kit was in my head to see I'm playing on my knees.
I have fingers for sticks and I knew all the beats fit.
Well, then I went to hit my crash.
I played a perfect smash.
I accidentally punched the glass fly through the air.
Dumb's beer in the hair.
All the poor dumb soul who'd never played a role in my life before.
But he was up for one now confronting the on the floor.
I said, sorry.
All I wanted was to hit my symbol.
Big mistake.
Because I'm the Richard Kimball.
But I became a fugitive from the future temp.
Who was running after me with murder on his mind.
He looked just fine when he was away behind.
Oh, let he come and got it.
He only showed me.
I said, I need you to like me.
I like you didn't find me.
I need you to like me.
I'd like if you didn't find me.
I'm going up.
I know it's too empty.
But I'm getting so much winter.
The lady in my head just said it's nice to see her.
So many people talking with the same boy saying it's so good to be here.
It's too dark and clear.
I grabbed a pad and went again.
They urged to create.
Well, too late.
I realized that the drugs on the page dilate.
Until a big bad image is lying in big dead state.
It's too bad.
It's too frustrating.
My desire for an outside, but I don't control.
But I'm on the end.
I'm by road to patrol.
The worst kind of sign-ups.
Bring it up.
I remember I had about our relaps.
But all the people in my life were the one same control freak.
Ha ha.
Like me.
I'm each unique.
Every day of the week I sneak to the doors.
Just a barrel of fire that you like me.
Sweat it out.
Like me.
Like you didn't fire me.
I need you to like me.
I like you didn't fire me.
Oh.
I get go three.
Two f-u.
I quite sure what it was.
But that popped up on the homepage of the podcast of music network this morning.
And I checked it out and listened to it.
And I was like, yeah, something going on with that.
From Edinburgh is get go three.
Just looking at their page here on the PMN influences James Brown,
fun love and crimson and manic orchestra.
As I said from Edinburgh.
And they've been around for a while.
It's from their second EP titled Menton.
You can find that at music.podshow.com.
Of course, in the show notes on today's podcast.
Sound should be a little bit better today.
Yesterday, without me knowing it, my creative lab sound card decided to
revert back to headphones.
Why in the world headphones has to sound so shitty coming from their sound card is
behind me.
And I figured out what's happening.
There's a little check box in the.
My god.
It couldn't be a different more difficult.
There's a little check box in the control pan.
The control panel for the creative labs.
Sound blaster card, which you have to find somewhere through navigating through the start menu.
And it's a check by default, which means it's synchronized with the control panel.
I guess that's the sound control panel.
I really don't know what it is.
But I unchecked it.
Then I had to reboot and then it finally worked.
On top of all that, a cast blaster mic sent me a new version of cast blaster.
What do you have to know?
Beta 58.
My god, man.
It just keeps on coming.
So some of those issues we saw yesterday will probably this unbelievable the stuff he's got in here.
If you don't mind me just falling over this for a second.
There's a diagnostics tab under Configure and it shows it says show audio diagnostics.
And I look at it.
It shows a log of what I play.
Then it's showing my buffer size as in God knows what.
But anyway, if something goes wrong, it's supposed to send the output of that file to mic.
So hopefully everything will go good.
Go good.
Go well.
Lots to talk about today.
I'm talking feedback.
Not a lot about the cartoon controversy.
Yeah.
See, I'm trying to do a Madonna now.
The cartoon controversy.
But there's lots of stuff about advertising and some good news about for Apple, Apple owners.
And Matthew Gauer.
Complained.
So let's start off with the complaint then.
I must say the increased usage of advertising within your podcast is making me seriously
Consider dropping my subscription to Delta Sierra Charlie.
Number one reason I listen to podcasts is to avoid the overwhelming saturation of advertising
in today's radio stations.
I find it extremely frustrating to scan radio channels knowing that each channel will have a greater
chance of playing an advertisement than playing content.
Well, DSC certainly isn't yet at that level of saturation.
I finally remember your first podcast where no advertising was used.
I fully understand what a means of support is needed for podcasts.
But advertisements certainly are not the root to travel.
I find it interesting that you spend the significant amount of time within your podcast
denigrating the current commercial media institutions.
Well, actively emulating their business model via advertisements.
I believe that the satellite radio stations have a superior model, a simple subscription
and no advertising.
A flat rate subscription allowing unlimited podcast subscription will be far less offensive.
Of course, just my opinion.
Thanks for listening.
Matt.
So first of all, Matt unsubscribe if you must.
We're sorry to see you go.
The second part is, you know, the daily source code is a podcast about really about podcasting.
It always has been that's how it started more from a technology standpoint.
And this is where we get to try stuff out.
This is where we try out stuff like sound seeing.
And indeed, the sound advertising.
Do it using Vulcan mind tricks to see if we can link in a brand to a sound on the show.
We talk about user generated advertisements.
All kinds of stuff.
It's appropriate for my podcast.
I feel.
And if you don't like it, then it's not the right podcast for you.
By the way, most people check into the source code and leave after a while, you know, after hearing
hopefully after hearing a promo.
And I hope that they will replace the time to listen to this podcast with something else that is more
suited towards what they want.
And of course, the advertisements and other podcasts, if there are advertisements, should
be suitable for that audience.
So I think that the audience is listening here knows that we mess around with all kinds of
stuff and test stuff out.
And boy, I'm not afraid to let people know what the feedback is on all of that.
We've slammed me.
We've slammed pod show.
We've slammed our advertisers.
All kinds of stuff.
And by the way, on a personal level, if every single one of my subscribers would pay me a buck
a month, yeah, that would be nice.
I'd go for that.
Sadly, it also has advertising.
Make no mistake.
I believe if it's not already happening, I've been in the UK for a couple of weeks.
Stern will be running advertising on that serious.
And satellite actually satellite radio has a tremendous advantage.
And the advantage is not over content or distribution.
Well, actually it is.
It's over distribution of the player, the reception device.
So we have, let's say we have iTunes right now.
And every single new automobile in the United States that's rolling off the assembly line
has either a serious, hopefully a serious, or some others.
I'm going to mention it.
Or an XM receiver built right in.
And that's really what the whole race is about.
It's, you know, who's got GM, who's got a damler Chrysler.
And these things will be built in standard.
The subscription fee, well, if it's not already being done,
will be built right into your monthly lease or right into, you know, something or
some other form of a payment.
So you really won't notice it.
And, you know, that's really where they have a tremendous advantage.
And in podcasting, we do have a lot of work to do because make no mistake.
You're seeing iTunes is really flooding up now with all kinds of mainstream content,
particularly video content.
But, you know, just look, it's mainly public radio on that's being promoted on the home page.
Of course, the pod finder gets up there, which we're very appreciative of.
They've got to cut a new one, by the way, this week.
You know, so we, we have a lot of a lot of work to do.
And how do you do that?
Well, dude, you need money.
And you need lots of it to compete.
It's just like if you want to become a president in the United States,
you think you can do it without at least 50 and probably more like $250 million.
Well, in the future, we may be able to do it with less or maybe with nothing,
depending on how web logs and podcasts and everything start to proliferate into everybody's lives.
In order to get to get over that bridge, and I may know,
no secret of this is you need money to combat money.
It's just the way it is.
So, and by the way, I don't want my show filled up with thousands of advertisements.
And it's all, and we're not emulating the same business model.
We're trying to change it.
That's what we're doing.
And maybe you have to start at the status quo to start changing.
I told you that EarthLink has heard all the comments,
and they're coming back with something I think is going to make a lot of sense,
and there's more companies that are thinking this way,
and they are listening, and they are smart,
but big companies are usually very, very smart and very, very slow.
And in the meantime, we're just going to mess around with everything
and try and figure it out.
I hope you don't mind.
What's we do today?
Should we do Metro sexual moment or Trinity?
The so many people who were, sorry, that's a black barrier again.
There are so many people who are spoofing the Metro sexual moment now
and calling me a worse,
that I think we're actually on to something really, really big here.
So we'll do that today.
Dear Smurdy, if this is con from on Timmel,
that's the daily podcast in the Irish language.
And I'm here to tell you that this week,
we're running a competition for Valentine's Day,
with a chance to win a copy of this CD.
If the tune sounds familiar, then it should.
It's a classic love song from the 1960s,
and it's one of 10 such songs,
which feature on the new album by Hillary Bow.
The album is called Shan Nova,
and it features Irish versions of classic love songs
in a bus and over style.
And it's our prize for our Valentine's Day quiz on on table.
The answer all you need to do is tell me,
what's the original version of that song in English?
And you can send your answers via email to
immelatgmail.com.
That's ime-a-l-l-l-atgmail.com.
And you can check out the podcast on Timmel.
It's at immel.blugspot.com.
Backfall to earth.
Oh, I know that song.
It's certainly not part safe,
so I presume somehow you figured that out.
What is the name of the original?
Ah, I'm not gonna weigh in.
I'm not gonna weigh in.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
Where are flink?
We believe in an internet that's safe
from virus hidden scammers.
We're earth-link.
We believe your personal information
should be just that personal,
and we believe your internet should be a friend,
not a foe.
Where are flink?
Make this smart choice.
Visit earthlink.net
and discover what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
Okay, I want to clarify something right now.
Despite the fact that we are called
the Mike and Michelle show,
Mike and I are not a couple.
Okay.
Thank God for that.
We fight a lot, true,
but we are not romantically involved
in any way, shape, or form.
Okay.
She's kind of like an adopted sister.
I wouldn't sleep with him if you paid me.
Okay.
The Mike and Michelle show.com.
Well, how much are we talking about here?
Okay.
Nice voice, then Michelle.
Like it very much.
Today, last day for the Rocket Boom advertisement.
In fact, at the time of the recording of this podcast,
the auction on eBay has 3 hours and 48 minutes left.
Current bid.
My gosh.
What a jump since yesterday.
$30,900.
And looks like, is that a new bidder star?
Find her five?
Let's see who's in the bids here,
home on a second.
Star find her five, five percent card.com.
Looks like Texas Dave is off the list.
And then there's a new guy who came in an instant zero zero one.
Man, this is pretty interesting.
I mean, what happens?
By the way, the reserve is still not met.
I think we got to be getting pretty close, though,
about $30 grand.
At a million impressions, just an advertising speak.
That would be a $30 CPM minus all the creative that has to be done.
That's better than television, I think.
In most cases, well, depends.
Rocket Boom, of course, is a hit show.
So a hit show would probably command a lot more in television land.
But it'll be very interesting to see what happens.
Who knows what that minimum bid is, what the, what are they calling it?
The reserve.
So maybe they'll just wind up with nothing, but certainly very, very interesting.
And what happens if someone bids and doesn't want to pay?
What's the deal with that on eBay?
Will they go in a rest year?
Or what happens?
That's a lot of money.
Certainly, because these are not traditional brands.
I don't think that are bidding on this.
These seem to be eBay power sellers.
Well, five percent, was it five percent card dot com or something?
That's obviously some kind of like five percent card dot com.
No idea.
Should we take a look at that?
Hold on a second.
Let's look at, I haven't done that.
Five per, sorry.
I'm typing with left here.
Percent card dot com.
I'm typing on the Mac, which is a level higher on the podcast complex here.
Okay.
Five percent card dot com.
Like to save money.
There are two credit cards.
Okay.
Credit card company.
A credit card broker company.
I guess is what it would be.
Right, too.
I don't know if you listened to Pacific Coast Hellway.
If you do on a serious stars 103, then you probably heard Sarah the 21 year old
virgin called in with, with her fantasy about me.
I mean, it's, it's, it went so far that I won't even play it on the Stanley source code.
But it was very flattering.
And it kind of upsets me though at the same time.
Because she didn't send it to me.
She sent it to mark, you marking the minutium mud in the, in the, in the kimono
Namcov.
And a true metro sexual man.
And I'm thinking of myself, you know, that sucks, man.
I mean, I get Roger Simholzen.
He gets Sarah the 21 year old virgin.
Adam Anthony Hunt with some audio feedback regarding advertising on pod shows.
My biggest concern about advertising is the clash between trust and influence.
The movie quiz shows a dramatization of a real event in 1958 where the funders of the game show
21 have a problem with their winner.
So they rigged the show.
So his opponent wins.
And the public thinks it's a real game show.
When cigarette ads were still on TV, camel, RJ Reynolds sponsored man against crime,
starring Ralph Bellamy from 1944.
The advertiser had script approval, including don't have a heavy or
disreputable person smoking.
And arson cannot be in the plot because it reminds people of fire danger associated with smoking.
Most recently, the Department of Education was caught paying commentators to say,
positive things about the no child left behind policy.
The commentators are supposed to be free from outside influence.
That becomes public relations not commentary.
My thoughts on product placement.
I'm fine with dramas and sitcoms using actual products as props because I know that some
would not have been made without that placement.
However, rewrite a scene specifically for the right shot of the advertiser's product or
change the script to conform to that sponsor.
And you've lost me as a listener viewer.
I have a problem with all the radio payola and people who get paid to talk up the various
bands on college campuses because no one really wants to acknowledge these practices.
And yet I recently read the summary of report given that the word of mouth marketing conference
which said that people actually follow up on comments about advertisers much more when
people are above board with their sponsorship up to 70% more because they're curious.
I think of some of the stuff that happens on cover villains as an example.
The trust factor between host and listener becomes huge here.
So your comments about senseo or apple are given a completely different way to commentary rather than advertising.
I don't hate earth length because they are your sponsor.
It merely changes the reference that I place on comments you might make about them.
By the way, 30 seconds definitely is too long.
Try the public broadcasting model of 15 and don't put more than two of those together.
So anyway, I get your sponsors.
So you can quit your day job, but absolutely be honest with your listeners.
So they can continue to trust you and resonate with the things that you do say legitimately.
Thank you.
Okay, a couple things there.
First of all, I have no idea what the cover real reference was all about.
That was disturbing.
So let me know what's going on with that.
Regarding the old TV shows and historical facts that you cited,
I think it's a little bit different though when there is limited frequency and limited channels.
And of course time by definition is then limited to 24 hours per channel.
Particularly when these are sanctioned and licensed by the government.
So there are all kinds of rules that have to come into play there.
Download.acview.com.
I'm going to try not to do that too often.
A lot of people hate the burping thing.
So when it comes to the game show quizzes or changing scenes, et cetera, et cetera.
If there's no equal airtime for someone to combat that or if there's no opportunity for you to leave that and go somewhere else,
which has certainly hasn't been up until the past 20 years as channels.
I'm just expanded massively.
And of course on the internet, if you don't like what you're listening.
If you don't like what you're hearing on a podcast.
Well, you don't have to listen to it and you're not forced.
Because that's the only thing you can listen to between seven and eight in the morning or the evening or whatever you would listen to it.
So I think there's a huge difference there.
Let's just set that aside for a second.
You said so much.
Regarding the public radio model versus 30 seconds, 15 seconds do that is so unimportant.
First of all, public radio, they're so called sponsorship model.
It's just commercial.
Let's just advertise.
And there's all kinds of deals going on.
And we all know it.
There is no limit.
I don't believe we've done a single sale at Pod Show.
And we've already sold millions of dollars worth of advertising.
I don't think we've done a single sale that was based upon an amount of time.
Interestingly enough, the advertisers in some cases have given us the earthlink spot.
I've given us their standard kind of like radio based 30 second spot, which as I said, watch for that to change.
But if you talk about like the I dog or even download.acqview.com, Heather and Janelle, their show.
There's been no limit placed on me nor do I impose any limit about how long I can talk about a certain product.
And I really truly believe that people who listen to this show.
I don't want to insult them the way you did.
They really do understand the difference between a commercial message and something that's just coming from the heart.
And I think I've been very open and I've said right off the bat whenever something was a paid endorsement.
Because that's really what it is when I talk about something in the show.
It's endorsement.
But you know, I don't say standby here comes an earthlink commercial.
No, people here at they understand it.
But you know, you mentioned like Apple and since sale, I'm not getting paid by any of those companies.
And if they did, I would be very open about it.
And I would hope my listeners would be very happy for me and happy for themselves.
What I'm trying right now is I'm trying to get companies interested in stuff that we're talking about.
For example, the metro sexual moment we talk about all different types of razors.
I would certainly not mind my audience being compensated by giving them some free product to test and talk about.
And in exchange, I think I should get paid too.
Nothing wrong with that.
We already have the conversation going and I'm not calling.
You know, we, I don't give a shit.
I really, really don't.
That's going to be plenty of really interesting advertisers coming into podcasting.
And I determine, as a representative of my audience, what I think is appropriate and what is not appropriate.
And how I want to do things that are appropriate or not appropriate.
Now, what I don't determine is the amount of time we have on the serious satellite stars one or three channel.
Because our satellite window is closing in 10 seconds.
Specific host hell way is coming up.
Then Mad wine steam with yeast radio and boy is she pissed and don't enjoy after that.
And I will see you guys tomorrow and thank God it's Friday edition.
I think I went over by one second.
Oh, I'm so happy with this.
To the nanosecond precise timer that Casplaster might put together for me.
Oh, it's wonderful.
Thank you for us still giving all that feedback about timers.
So what Mike did is he basically built a really, really, really robust timer that will work for you too.
And it's built into the latest beta.
So I guess everyone else can try the same thing.
Hey, speaking of the Metro sexual moment.
Metro sexual.
It's an increased Metro sexual moment.
An increased Metro sexual moment.
Yeah.
Now, before we get started with the audio feedbacks.
Thank you very much.
I'm going for sending them in.
Let me just make you aware of the fact that pink is the color.
Does the color do you or for us, man?
It may seem really weird.
My daughter gave me a pink sweater for Christmas.
And wearing that thing, I've gotten so many compliments from so many women.
All kinds of women.
And you should try it.
I know it.
It sounds really weird and it may feel weird.
But what's going on?
So take that from your Metro sexual moment on the daily source code.
So this is Derek DeBandard from Janisburg in South Africa.
Just finished listening to Delta Sierra Charlie 331 in the Metro sexual moment.
And I had to laugh.
I could not believe it.
You have the same problem as I do.
During my hair by myself, it just does not work for me.
I have to have the help of my wife's creative hands.
I have a kind of Monday to Friday hairstyle with a bit of laurel studio line.
Kind of stuff that I was rubbing to my hair.
And that's it.
Nothing special.
Over weekends.
Then I've got to hit the clubs.
Look cool.
And I don't look cool when I do my hair.
Just like you on German TV.
Fuck you.
Thank goodness.
You've got Patricia.
My wife recently became an M-way member.
Now you know it's all about buying certain products and building your business network
and bloody bloody blah.
But the amazing thing is I am getting all these wonderful hair products to try.
So maybe someone from M-way wouldn't mind sending you some hair gel.
So I just thought I'd share that Metro sexual moment with you.
Not being able to do my own hair myself.
So I relate to you here at the bottom of Africa.
Thank you so much for what you're doing.
Love the show.
Do not miss a single episode.
It's really cool.
You are a legend, sir.
From a check out my podcast, it is www.soundrepublic.co.zate.
Thank you, sir.
You take care.
Cheers.
I use, but what is it?
Paul Mitchell.
And then I used some other like crap to put my hair.
Doesn't matter.
I can't do it.
It never looks good.
I walk around during the week like a degenerate.
And they usually don't shave until, you know, we hit a Metro sexual moment.
That's it.
Oh yeah, I should do that once in a while.
But like yesterday, Patricia was feeling a little rundown.
So I said, hey, you know what?
I'll go with you to Sainsbury and we'll go do the shopping.
Now of course, Sainsbury is exactly the spot where all these dickhead paparazzi
hang out and try to take horrible pictures of Patricia Lee.
So I was well prepared.
And Patricia prepared me and said, well, you know, let me just do your hair before we go.
I knew what you was talking about.
She didn't want to look like shit on another picture.
Yes, of course.
Hair tips and comments are welcome in our little Metro sexual corner.
You bet.
Hey Adam, this is Chef Mark with a K in New York City.
And I heard you showed today.
You were talking about wrestling and troubles.
And I tell you what, I will wrestle anyone anywhere.
If you're feeling a ring full of shave truffles.
Now mind you not chocolate truffles but the real thing.
I will wrestle anyone I have to to get at those truffles.
So for your Metro sexual moment, you had someone calling in asking about shaving the neck area and the razor burn.
And I think part of what happens why that's more irritating is because we have a tendency to shave upwards
when we get to the neck and the hair tends to grow downwards.
And they always say that you should shave in the direction of the hair growth.
And so that's probably why it's easier to get irritated.
And plus I would say, you know, put some moisturizer or something before you put shaving cream to sort of prepare the skin for that.
So anyway, that's my little Metro sexual moment tip.
And while I got you here, I will share with you another one of my kitchen quick tips, which I put on my most recent show that's going out,
which is getting greens really dry before you use them.
A lot of times, you know, you bring greens or herbs home from the store.
You need to wash them before you store them or before you even just make a salad.
Also, you know, wash them with throw them in a salad spinner and we spin it out.
Well, it doesn't always get 100% dry.
After that, crumple of a couple of paper towels, put them in the salad spinner and give it another go.
And the paper towels will absorb the remaining water that's in there and get your greens nice and dry.
So that you can store them in the fridge and they'll last longer.
You can hear more of my kitchen quick tips on my podcast, the Remarkable Palette podcast.
You can find it on iTunes or at RemarkablePalette.logspot.com.
Thanks Adam, and get that wrestling ring ready for me.
Yeah, the curry hogs are already out sniffing for the truffles from us.
And whatever you do, listeners, do not wash the herbs.
Hey Adam, I'm a bit behind, but I was listening to DSC on 2306.
And there's no way that Dr. Bronner's soap is metro sexual at all.
I've used Dr. Bronner's pure castile for a while, then originally bought it for a rafting trip down the Grand Canyon.
The soap is perfect for the outdoorsmen in your family because it's biodegradable.
You can buy it.
I love peppermint, but my barrel chested father digs the almond flavor.
The peppermint makes my chest hair tingle.
I'm an artist, can you plug my website?
Sure, Davelemortit.com.
That's Delta Alpha Victor Eco Lima Alpha.
The hell is M?
Mike Oscar Romeo Tango Echo.
Sorry, senior moment there for a second.
Ah, here's an old fan of the show, or not so old fan, but someone's been listening for a while.
Rish.
I keep messing up his name.
Rishab Kumar.
I hope I did it right now.
Hey, Mr. Curry.
Oh, that hurts.
My father purchased a Gillette fusion at Walmart.
In fact, recently, he told me that with the precision blade,
it's gotten rid of his razor burn on his neck.
Yeah, so whenever I need a razor, I'm 14, not needing one yet.
I'll be sure to be using the Gillette fusion for that precision blade.
Definitely check out the fusion.
It's a really nifty product.
My father has the battery powered one.
That's a normal motion for Gillette.
I mean, that's obvious.
You're probably going to use the same product your dad uses.
All right.
One more then.
There we go.
Ah, shit that has music in it.
How could I miss that one up?
All right.
Well, let's end the metro section.
We can get to that final comment.
Yeah.
G-I-T-M-O-S-A-P-I-N-S-G-I-Z-U-M-O-S-A-N-S-G-I-Z-U-M-O-S-A-U-S-A-N-S.
Coming to you from the heart of it all.
It's G-S-M-O-S-A-N-S.
An entertainment and technology podcast.
Hey, Adam.
This is Chris from the G-S-M-O-S-A-N-S podcast.
Listen to your show yesterday and you're talking in your metro sexual moment about razor burn.
And I have the same eye to have the same problem.
I actually don't use anything for it.
I follow an old army recommendation that is probably older than where I remember.
Getting in from.
I'm not old enough to have served in Vietnam, but I do know that from the Vietnam work till now
in soldiers who were stationed in jungle areas were told to shave and cold water.
And that's supposed to help reduce razor burn and it seems to do that pretty well for me.
The other thing that's cool about it is you warm yourself up in the shower to open those pores.
It's really refreshing to come out and come a shaving real cold water.
Just thought I would add that little bit of knowledge to you and love your show.
Good luck with it.
All right.
I'd never heard of that one.
I don't know if that.
Okay.
Army guys, check in now, William.
I know lots of you are metro sexual.
And next time, Winston in a comment, please don't put any music underneath your voice.
I'm curious, metro sexual moment.
Yeah.
All right.
Hey Adam says, uh, what's this?
Jupiter.
Everyone says that the belching and sincere were linked.
Well, I was reminded of your show because of a lighter.
I was camping in my friend tried to light a candle with his lighter and I immediately thought
about the daily source code.
I use a real player on Palm OS, PDA, XIR, 31.
The time was exact.
Okay.
I love the show.
My friend and I think about starting a podcast just waiting for the PDA end.
Oh, yeah.
I wanted to mention about the pot safe music network.
I think today is the day when we're going to, um,
now there's two things that that are going to launch and I, um,
and they're already working here for me.
So I haven't seen it yet on the public site.
One is, and this is really cool.
We got a really nice player that we're going to release that is going to be a much,
much better experience for anyone just perusing the site he wants to listen to some tunes.
Um, that's one.
The second one is the buy feature.
And, um, it's not publicly available yet.
So I'm presuming it's going to happen today.
If you're interested in testing this out, um, then you'll be able to purchase
if every day we're Christmas from Podsay for peace.
All the proceeds go to UNICEF after the nine cents is deducted for the transaction cost.
We're not taking anything.
And, you know, SLOW is on the up and up.
So if you want to test it out,
you can probably just go to that page and you just hit it a couple times.
I'd wait until, you know, kind of like midday Pacific time at least.
Um, and if, if it definitely is not happening, I'll post something at curry.com.
But I'm pretty sure everything's good to go.
And so you'll be able to, um,
by the way, if you're already a listener, um, or a, or a podcaster,
or an artist, you'll be able to use your current password to log in.
You will be asked to create a new password at your discretion for, uh,
the actual credit card piece because we can't hold any of that data.
So you will need a separate password for that.
But all the other fields are populated and everything is made very simply.
And again, we're not building a store.
This is a part of the unlabel.
And the unlabel is where artists are their own record companies.
And they're working with different parties, such as podcasts,
such as listeners, fans of their, of their music.
Um, to create their own marketing buzz, uh,
to get, uh, yeah, really to get exposure as, as, as many places as they can.
Excuse me, I'm not, I'm going to do it.
Now, what did you just say when you heard that?
Belts kind of muffled away.
What was it linked to?
So hopefully that'll be a live today.
Um, and I'm very, very excited about it.
And these are all MP3s in the clear.
Um, if you lose it, you can go back into the store.
Go download a fresh copy.
Um, and this entire system is built around faith in humankind and the opportunity
to show the world that a people like music aren't all thieves and crooks,
and that we do want to invest in talent.
And the money is going to the people who are making it happen.
You know, not to big corporation.
God, there was a, there was a fantastic article in, you know,
it's on the floor here.
Hold on one second.
Let me just, I'll open up the other mic.
Man, well, I walk over here.
There we go.
I'm sorry.
Let me just guess this.
Fantastic article in the, uh, financial times yesterday.
Uh, by Alan Levy, who is the chairman and chief executive of EMI music.
Music's revolution is not to be feared.
And he goes in to say how fantastic it's going and how incredibly modern they are.
Um, and there's some contradictions in there.
The thing that would that kind of made me chuckle.
Uh, the new music business models keep coming.
We recently licensed our music to GNAB, the first pan European legal peer to peer service.
Oh, you are so hit.
Whatever the technology from satellite radio to podcasting,
we work with companies and legislators to ensure that our artists work and the
investments we make in their work is fairly compensated.
Gee, I can't, can't seem to find the memo or the letter you sent me about that.
Here's some fantastic news.
And this is right on the spot for me.
Uh, Ryan Stevens sent me this fantastic link.
Virgin airways, man.
These guys never cease to amaze me.
You know, I'm a frequent flyer on virgin.
I've now have almost 200,000 frequent flyer miles.
And when I made my, my recent bookings to New York and to San Francisco,
I said, hey, you know, how about the space trip?
I hear that, you know, you can, you can get a spot on the,
on, on Branson space bird, um, just with, with miles within a,
you can, you can, you can cash in your miles.
And it was, I mean, so nice on the phone.
Maybe it's just the accent, but, um, she looked it up for me.
Yeah, 2 million miles.
2 million miles before you get a free space trip.
I got to fly a hell of a lot more.
Um, anyway, so for some reason this page is not loading.
I don't know what's going on.
Um, but Virgin Atlantic has introduced a blackberry clinic for upper class passengers.
At the Heathrow Clubhouse.
Um, oh my goodness.
I got a page in Spanish.
The hell is that?
Why is this happening?
Oh, I see.
You were all got messed up.
Okay.
Anyway, um, so the, the blackberry clinic helps you with tips and tricks
and, uh, and how to use your blackberry more efficiently.
And I can't wait because I hope the clinic will be open.
Um, when I, when I leave on Sunday, um, because my broken and I just want to, you know,
I have to go through this whole rigmarole on the phone calling 800 number.
I have to, you know, give out, you know, our tax ID numbers,
and all this incredible crap just to prove that this thing is broken.
So maybe they can help me on the spot.
Speaking of help, and this is a big one.
Um, I'm going to go to the Apple Insider website.
Apparently in the forthcoming update to OS 10.
Yeah, I'm going to read from Apple Insider.
Uh, or is it?
Um, according to tipsters and reports, already present on the internet's Apple.
This week, seated the fourth external build of Mac OS 10.4.5 for PowerPC Max.
That would be the one that I bought.
The build reportedly labeled Mac OS X 10.4.5.8H14.
God, that's marketing.
It's said to address issues with multi application audio support in the distribution of the operating
system update offered to Apple developer connection members.
Apple did not list any known issues.
Okay.
Well, it would be great if that was fixed, but I got to tell you one thing.
Uh, it's not going to make any difference.
I am completely sold on cast blaster.
Ah, crap.
The wrong one.
I'm sorry about that.
I had a bit of a different accent.
The elishness point.
How lame is that?
That I said I'm sold on cast blaster and then I misfires something.
I'm still sold on cast blaster.
And if you look at the cast blaster forum,
then now talking about something I'm really excited about.
About adding a MIDI control surface to cast blaster.
So you could have basically, you know, a little box with faders,
and you could control the software externally, which, of course,
would help me with exactly this problem.
It could set up buttons to fire stuff and you can fade stuff in and out.
And I think Mike is getting into the idea.
I had a bit of a different accent.
Feellessness.
And this is Jim from the UK.
Also known as the Daddy Douse.
I was wondering if you could use your influence with Apple.
They get something sorted.
Something's changed in the last version of iTunes.
I've got a smart playlist, which is podcast not listens to.
Where the play count is greater than zero.
I don't include anything from the podcast group.
It used to be that I had to listen to the whole podcast before.
It would register as a listen count.
And therefore I could pause the podcast.
There was sync.
And then go back to me podcast not listened.
And play from the last position that I was so, for instance,
this week in tech.
It's about an hour long.
Get to half an hour through it.
Sink the iPod, go back.
And then I can pick up at 35 minutes.
It now transpires that somewhere during the playback.
It's registering as a listen.
So I'll lose it from my act of playlist instantaneously.
Even on the iPods or something's changed on the ear on the phone.
Whether the pod.
I just please Apple put it back because it's so irritating.
So if anybody's listening, you know what to do.
Anyway, thanks an anticipation.
Let's see how many people can guess where I'm from just by my accent.
Thanks very much, mate.
But Birmingham.
Just a guess.
I did know that had happened.
And quite frankly, my the smart playlist I've set up doesn't do a play count.
But that's interesting that now the plays are registered even if you just listen to it a little bit.
You should be able to switch that off.
Obviously that should be an advanced setting.
One thing about the cartoon controversy.
Joseph Young says hi.
I'm just a follow up.
Yes, they the cultural editor of I'm going to screw this up.
Elon Sposten, which is the newspaper who published the the offending cartoons in Denmark.
Proposed get this publishing cartoons of Christian and Jewish themes along with other things cartoon along with other cartoons of the holocaust
in cooperation with the challenge sent out by the Iranian newspaper.
Hey, look.
This actually gets back to the previous comment about editorial and advertising and all that stuff.
I think that this is so stupid.
What does this have to do with news?
Stop making the news.
You dickhead?
Stop making the news report on the news.
This is really what's happening.
I think that mainstream media, some of them are smoking, you know, they're on dope obviously.
But I do think that they, you know, they're not dumb.
They listen around.
They always on the lookout for stuff.
And they're hearing and they're seeing.
And they're reading.
And they're saying to themselves, my God, some of this is really good.
You know, there are no secrets.
Only information you don't yet have.
So what's the differentiator?
Everybody can get to the same information.
Everybody can report on the news and do just a shitty job.
I think they really do see the writing on the wall.
And I do believe that people are smart enough.
Once they, you know, we grew up with newspapers being authority.
We grew up with television news being an authority.
My daughter's not growing up with newspapers as an authority.
She's not growing up with television being an authority.
She does question things that she reads.
She doesn't take any one single web posting as the truth either.
I really see that, you know, the next generation is going to,
It's just not going to be, there can't be bothered.
Then a bothered bothered.
Does it do it like bothered?
God, I love Katherine Tate.
And they'll, and they'll be making their own truths by, well, you could call it triangulating.
But I think it'll be a number of things.
Look at what we've learned just on this show, just by opening up a dialogue about this controversy.
Gosh, I'm getting so madonna on you.
That's today.
Just by opening up this controversy, the discussion about it,
I've learned all these things that I didn't learn from mainstream media.
Why?
They're restricted by time.
They only have 24 hours in a day for the channels that they have available for each individual channel.
We can do this for as long as we want.
You can skip around, go forward, go back to whatever you want.
It's beautiful, love it.
So obviously, that's pretty stupid.
Oh, man.
Let's see.
You know, I have like three more specific things.
I just, I've been sitting here in cast blast that I haven't been getting to for the past four shows.
Let's just run through them.
We're going to go along.
We'll probably be up to an hour today.
But if you stick with it, I hope it's worth it.
You've heard it all before.
Baby, I just want you to be sure.
Just stop and change the name.
Baby, I just want you to be safe.
I love it when you take me.
Baby, I love it.
No, just release me.
I want it to be easy.
Baby, I just need you to believe.
Hey, Adam.
This is David.
I'm a fellow podcaster out here in podcasting land or the potto sphere.
I had a comment about Delta Sierra Charlie in 325.
He had a listener of that commented that there was a lack of enhanced AAC file support
tools for the PC.
And I wholeheartedly agree with that.
Your reference to version tracker in your show was intriguing.
But you didn't mention the software application that you used.
And it wasn't in your show notes.
So I went to verse tracker.com and searched on AAC and didn't really see anything that
looked promising.
So if you remember what the name of that software was, or if any of your listeners know,
it'd be great to have that.
Also, I had a comment about podcasting production.
I'm glad to hear that.
Cast blasters going well for you.
I've tried it myself and liked it.
I'm recording my comment today with it.
I sympathized with your math problems and we're glad to hear that you've bought a PC.
I wanted to welcome you back to the good side of the force.
Last comment was, there really isn't any good podcaster modules.
For any of the major open source CMS systems content management systems.
WordPress doesn't have one, PHP.
Nuke doesn't have one.
Drupal has a basic one and the author is promising a new one, but has not released it yet.
In fact, he's demoing it on his website, but he's not sharing it, which I think just sucks.
PHP website also has a basic podcaster module that I've been using for some time and modified it.
But there's lots of features missing.
For example, you can't specify a file, an MP3 file or an audio file that's not in the website,
which is not so good.
So in summary, I just want to be able to have a good tool to produce and edit my podcast.
I want to be able to offer my listeners an easily navigable file.
And I want to have a good place to put them and manage my feeds.
So those are my comments in any information that you or your listeners could give to me.
That would be great.
I'm sure there are a lot of podcasters out there that are wondering the same thing.
Bye for now.
So regarding the enhanced podcast and creating them on windows.
Now, there's something that cast blasts from sure could do.
I know cast blasts are Mike has been messing around with that.
So I know that it's on the radar.
Now, you know, I've been podcasting for...
How long is it now?
Well over a year and a half.
But when I say podcasting, I mean, really doing this all on the computer.
Those of you who have been listening since the first show know that I've really tried to make it all work on a computer.
I just want basically a podcast studio in a box.
And cast blasts are the only thing that even comes close.
And I strayed for a while.
I have to admit there are all kinds of issues and all kinds of reasons.
I think many of them really had to do with a really, really poor shitty quality of the tablet PC.
Which, by the way, I still want to send to those medical guys.
They're doing the development for, you know, make...
Keep people alive.
Does anyone have a CD for Windows tablet edition?
Because I don't want to give the crap what as it is.
Or if you can tell me how I can wipe all the contents off of, you know, all of my documents and stuff.
So I can send it off these guys.
Please let me know.
So, but I've come back to cast blasts.
And really, what's happened is I'm realizing that, you know, with the digital mixture that is now built in with the...
Limited that is built in on the mic with all the different capabilities.
Now with the extended panel, so I can fit all the stuff in that I need to fit in there.
And, you know, with just a future smell of maybe a MIDI control surface,
it's going to be exactly what you want.
In fact, the coolest part that I think is cool about cast blasts is, you know, right now,
if you've used it, you know, when you're done, you...
The first thing you want to do is just save your file.
I mean, I'm just... I think that should stay in there.
You always want to have your local copy.
So there's really two button.
You have to two click process.
There is no step three.
So you save the file and then you click upload the server and it FTPs up to wherever you want it.
Already built into cast blasts.
And almost functional, having some issues with the...
With the transfer protocol, minor issues, but those will get fixed.
It'll be one click.
And then the show notes that you enter into cast blasts.
You know, your show name, your naming conventions, all that stuff,
will automatically be put up on the...
Potio podcast delivery network.
All in one go.
So, you'll be managing your feeds, as you call it,
directly from cast blaster.
It's going to be... It's... It's really beautiful.
In fact, I'm not a very popular guy.
I don't think around a Potio HQ...
Well, not yesterday at least, because I basically pulled the emergency break on the assembly line.
We were about to open up some data spots and get some stuff going.
But, you know, just a couple of things weren't quite right.
And this is stuff that... You know, I've been so involved...
This is what I'm trying to say.
I've been so involved in podcasting.
I know... And we've gone...
Stray in many, many, many ways.
It made it so complicated.
You know, people talking about RSS feeds.
I don't think you should have to talk about that.
It should just be done with it all.
And you should just know that it's inscribable.
You know, and the same thing... You know, you want statistics.
Yeah, you want... There's all kinds of stuff.
And so, we're almost ready to release some stuff.
And it just wasn't quite there yet.
So, I pulled the break and that'll definitely delay us by a week or so.
But it's coming.
It is definitely coming.
And it's going to be cool.
And I think it's what... Just about every single feature we could come up with for the PDN is there.
Including the opportunity to grow your audience.
And yes, to make money.
Hey Adam.
This is there and of there in the show.
I'm gonna strive home.
And I just want everyone to know that this Saturday,
February 11th is my one year anniversary in podcasting.
All your fall.
I just want to add that.
It is all your fall.
It was inspired by you.
And I thank you.
And all of my listeners thank you.
So please tune in to there in the show.
I'm gonna strive to go to the website.
D-D-D-Home.com email me.
D-D-D-Home at gmail.com and listen for the one year anniversary special.
Thank you.
Okay, I love you.
Bye-bye.
Adam.
This is Trevor Carpenter of The Scride Music Show.
SMS is a Christian music pod show.
And I've been podcasting since December of 05.
Now, as Terrace for real Christian music and radio stations have demonstrated,
the audience for Christian content is huge.
However, the Christian listener is as disenfranchised
with the big labels and radio conglomerates as anyone.
Many in the Christian community have witnessed talented artists
start a strong career with a strong message
only to see a big label suck them in and water them down.
In the very early days of the PMN,
I found some great and powerful Christian artists with a strong message.
Artists like a dream of Thorpe, whom you've played on there
over there on the DSC.
Matthew Castile, Waba, Eric Vardeman, just an image of you.
With podcasting and pod show,
and the artists to consume redistribution channels
having now been transformed,
artists won't feel the need of pressure
to water down their message or to standardise their sound
in order to fit into one of three or four categories.
I really do thank God for what you and pod show
we're doing over there.
It's really great.
One of the first podcasts I started listening to
on a regular basis was DSC.
Shortly thereafter, I added the life spring pod cast.
As a Christian, there are some things
on the DSC, I'd rather skip everyone's in a while
and sometimes I do,
but because I would have no idea what's going on
on the podcasting community,
I continue to subscribe.
Now, I have noticed that you've been adding
some great podcasters to your mix over there at pod show.
And most of these folks have either been pod casting
over a year or have rapidly built up
an incredibly large audience.
Of course, as you're beta testing so much
of this new pod show delivery network,
I understand the desire to have established podcasters
to utilize and test the systems and procedures.
However, your statistics will be slightly flawed
when you get up to speed
and advertiser starts to see
the influx of pod show pod cast related traffic.
Much of the hard work will have been on the
max of the pod show podcasters prior
to them joining the pod show.
Now, that's not an attack.
I just want to raise your awareness
to the statistical research that will be inferred
in the coming months.
Now, I suggest that you add a few more podcasters
to the mix prior to making it open to all.
Pick a few strong podcasters who are not veterans
and have a smaller audience.
This will be hard.
Just task someone over there pod show
to spend a day listening to the most
current episode of as many podcasters they can find.
They could start with the promo submissions
over at promos.podshow.com.
What you really need is a small contingent of rookies
who have something interesting to say to an existing audience.
These freshmen will give you
and the other leaders over there
a good idea of how well the pod show machine
helps yield a strong harvest.
I recommend focusing on genres
that you know already have a strong
traditional media segment.
Like sports commentary, political talk,
and oh, Christian music.
Hey, I know a great Christian music pod.
Yeah, this entire message was written
as a shameless, shameless plug
to convince you to invite me to join pod show.
Now, I'm not pulling this wisdom out of my red.
I really do believe in what I've drafted here.
I'm so confident in my future
as a member of the pod show family
that I've included several ways for you
and your cohorts at pod show there to contact me.
You can reach me at the email you received is from
or you could give me a call.
I put my phone numbers
and my Skype name right there in the email body.
Adam, don't fail me
and don't fail the pod show family.
Well, you just have to wait a little bit longer.
Everyone's going to be welcome to join in.
No worries there.
Yeah, what's interesting though is there's this assumption
that, you know, we picked and picked and chose
all these different shows.
Dude, we went to the pod cast
or the portable media expo
just to meet with anyone who was motivated
and have to come over and meet
and didn't listen to emni.
I was familiar with some of the shows obviously
but a lot of them I'd never heard before.
I had no idea.
I don't know what people's audiences
totally not interested.
I just want people who would be interested
and being, you know, a part of trying to build
something new and network and get something going.
And obviously there's some special compensation
for that.
No doubt.
So we really are building this with pod cast
so just when people just don't get invited
then they send like 3 minute and 20 second audio comments.
But all kidding aside, you will be welcome dude.
So the Grammy's Ron last night
I completely missed it and of course we can't play anything
from that side of the music business.
I wonder why Mariah Carey didn't win that many as she thought.
She looked cool and she shiver
even though the sun was shining down
life it rolled on this window
but she couldn't even hear the sound
I could tell by the recall finds
like a mappress crossing her face
she had seen what down on her
but it brought her here to this place
it's amazing what this life can put you through.
Yes it is.
There's a choice to make in all the things you do.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh
oh
Now, before you get the wrong idea, that of course is not Mariah Carey.
It's better.
It's Mariah without the attitude, it's an Adley Brown from the Podsive Music Network.
I wonder, you can find that at music.podshow.com.
Love that, it's really, it's nice.
It's something different too, it's polished yet, it's not over polished, it's beautiful, really
really like it, an Adley Brown.
Very cool.
I wish you guys, I wish we had Smello Rama on the source code because my wife just came in.
You can hear, that's tin foil, let me tell you what she just brought me.
She brought me two avocados, I've got to love her, two avocados, so sliced half avocados
with shrimp and cocktail sauce, and each package in its own individual little boat
of tin foil.
We've been married for 20 years, ladies and gentlemen, how cool is that?
Another Pod Show Pod guest, stick it in your ear!