Think Advertising sucks.
Think you can do better?
Pod Show and EarthLink are willing to put our money where your mouth is.
Listen to this podcast or go to adchelens.podshow.com to see how you can win big
in the EarthLink make advertising better challenge.
Delta Sierra Charlie 404 404
The podcast you were looking for could not be found.
Please return to the home page and try your search again.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Transmitters?
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking turns, didn't you?
I like to think I'm flying into this journey.
Autistic, it's Adam Curry.
The car is the place that comes with a sample.
Look, you sounded about 12 years old.
You sounded like you didn't even find it all right.
But you pop a beat just because.
I didn't have a car to say to God,
God, I didn't love my thing.
I thought you knew it would be this way.
I got married on my day.
Don't come up.
Instead of wanting to go,
I don't act my age.
We between the words,
everything that was good.
It's got to have a last day.
I didn't have a thought to say,
God, I didn't love my thing.
I thought you knew it would be this way.
I got married on my day.
But I have to want my understands.
When it doesn't feel wrong to me.
When you're busy making other plans.
I got married on my day.
I didn't have a thought to say,
God, I didn't love my thing.
I thought you knew it would be this way.
I got married on my day.
I didn't have a thought to say,
God, I didn't love my thing.
I thought you knew it would be this way.
I got married on my day.
I got to have to want my understands.
When it doesn't feel wrong to me.
I thought you knew it would be this way.
I got married on my day.
Gentlemen losers.
It's pot safe.
It's from the network.
No one has the pot safe.
Music network.
Everybody, how you doing?
Welcome to my humble abode in Northern California.
Beautiful day today in San Francisco.
The sun is shining.
I can see all the way up to the mountains.
Clear across the bay.
That's right.
I got a 180 degree view in the penthouse.
Which is perfect.
I just got no chicks.
Reading from their bio.
Gentlemen losers started on a drunken weekend in 1995.
And continues to this day.
Chris Cannon and Harvey Barham.
On the band after a four track weekend session at Cannon's apartment.
And now ten years eight albums later.
The two continues songwriting producing is the gentleman losers.
Yeah, like that.
Nice song to kind of kick everything off with.
Well, let me say how incredibly sorry I am.
Then I didn't get a show out to yesterday.
It was actually quite sad.
Everything all put together.
Of course Tuesday we had a show.
We had 403 and put in a full day at the office.
And Ron and Martin.
I decided to go to have some dinner.
So I driven to the office.
Ron is walking these days from knob hill.
And if you know San Francisco going from knob hill to south of
market.
It's about a 30 minute walk and going home, of course,
is a killer because it's all uphill.
And it really is the hill.
If you know what I mean.
So I said, dude, you know the restaurant's near your place.
Hop in Trinity, I brought her right here.
But of course, Tuesday morning, she had started up as normal.
And just made me feel so good.
So we hopped in and through our bags in the back.
And you got to know that we really appreciate engineering both of us.
We like engines and cars and just the beauty of it.
It doesn't have to be beautiful on the outside.
As long as it's beautiful on the inside.
And we're driving up.
And this right about the top of the hill there.
There's a 45 degree angle.
I can't believe I'm so stupid.
We actually, we did something in aviation that calls it.
That we call inviting the boogie man in.
Now he said, hey, she's running really nice, isn't she?
Yeah, well, that was the big mistake, of course.
At the stop sign, top the hill, 45 degree angle.
Coup.
Transmission drops out.
Can't go forward.
Can only go on reverse.
You can imagine that this is not good on a one way street
in San Francisco on a 45 degree inclined.
So, you know, it kind of made it fun at the same time.
And what it was, it was messed up.
And we actually contemplated driving around reverse all the way back down to the office.
And I think if we had been younger men, we probably would have done that.
But in this case, it seemed that the tow truck was a bad idea.
So we did get Trinity back to the office.
And the doctor has already come to take a look.
And it looks like she needs a complete transmission overhaul.
Which I knew was coming because she was shifting kind of rough since the day I got her.
So, oh well, it'll all be for the better, I guess.
And of course, this will actually motivate me and others around me to get Trinity completely pumped.
Or should I say pimp?
Yeah, let's say pimp.
Beautiful music in the background, by the way.
You may recognize back in the daily source code.
Used to play the rock mining off mix open.
And Luke Stanley sent me this version, which let me see.
What do you say here?
It's a PC chose to play with piano first, because he thought about me and the intro from back then.
And he plays it on the most recent episode of his video cast.
He plays in cello, but cello journey is name of the podcast.
cello journey.com.
So it's him Luke Stanley on the cello.
And in this case, pianist and friend Ross English on piano.
It's beautiful. It's beautiful.
I thought it really went well with the whole Trinity story.
Which, of course, doesn't end there because the woes have to continue.
So, after all this, it's like 1130.
And so, I get back.
I do my show prep, because I do this early in the morning.
It's just a little past 7am to hit all the satellite windows, et cetera.
Go to bed.
You know, I'm up at like 530.
536 o'clock.
And I realize I've left the power adapter to the, to Shiba laptop,
which is what I'm producing the entire show on.
Let's say, oh, let's say a moment brought to you by accident hash.
I noticed that I've left the power adapter at the office.
So, you know, we had a meeting at 9 o'clock, so it was completely hose.
No way I was going to be able to go to the office without the car, of course.
If I had had Trinity, I would have jumped in, and what do you care?
We got to show you on going on today.
Um, I'm, well, you know, it's not really bad news, but there's just all kinds of crappy stuff happened in success.
And now Patricia and I, when she was here last time, just what is it two weeks ago, two and a half weeks ago,
we went out to buy me the furniture that we're still missing from the, from the condo,
which means I have a dining table chairs, discuss that with you the other day.
The chairs are nice to have, and this baker's rack, which is going to be this set up for the studio.
And they're supposed to come on Wednesday the 14th, and there's actually, you know,
as the documentation says, we'll call you 24 hours ahead of time to schedule within a four hour window,
when we're going to drop the stuff off.
And of course, they didn't call, you know, we went through this when I just got the condo,
all the stuff that never arrived.
So, uh, I got Rosie on the case at the office, and they said, oh, well, yeah, no, um,
it's not in stock, and we'll just have to delay that until June 24th.
I saw the stuff, I asked specifically, you know, you got to drive to get to Levit,
it's like, you know, it was like a 15 minute drive from here off the highway,
and it was in stock, it was there in the store room.
They promised me time and time again.
And it's like, they don't even call, you've got to call, you've got to figure out what's going on.
Oh, well, you know, we'll just schedule that for July the 24th.
Do you, and please make sure you listen to the daily source code tomorrow.
Dorks.
So they're refunding my money.
And now, of course, that doesn't do me any good, because you can't sit on bank rolls.
Well, I guess you could.
Hey Adam, this is Bridget with the D, the latest addition to your pod show team.
I've been familiarizing myself with the site, and I came, uh, the pod sake music network,
and I came across a band that Steve and I agree would be perfect for your next show.
And this is a Steve of the Stephen Mark,
social scientists who we have working at the at HQ.
And Bridget and I actually have not been formally introduced.
I was expecting Steve and Mark to do that yesterday,
but I, uh, there's not, I think we're very male heavy at the office.
So having women walk around, you know, you do kind of notice.
So Bridget, uh, I hope we get to meet each other personally today.
And, uh, G, you know, the mood that I mean regarding Levits?
Hmm, yeah.
I think it's time to play just 30 seconds of Big Mountain Fudge Cake.
And God hates penguins.
I, you may want to be careful with those bugs in your ear.
God hates penguins, I hate you too.
You know, we got to use that every single time I'm really pissed off about something.
So Levits, God hates penguins, and he hates you.
Hi Adam, it's Gary from New Jersey.
I've left you another message previously.
I just wanted to say that I really enjoy listening to your podcast.
I listen to it every morning on the way to work.
I have about an hour of drive to work and it really did.
It's not a pleasant drive and it really does.
It does make the time go very, very nicely.
I especially encourage that I guess the diversity of the podcast.
I certainly enjoy the geeky stuff.
But I also enjoy the conversations between you and Patricia.
She sounds like a lovely woman and you both sound like you're very much a love.
That's very nice.
I really enjoy the podcast and I don't have a podcast to promote.
I just enjoy listening.
Take care.
You're happy about the good work.
Gary, thank you very much from New Jersey.
I just love it when listeners call in.
So he didn't really have much to say other than that.
He loves it, which is cool.
But I just like it when listeners call.
If you're a listener and you want to contribute because, you know,
most listeners don't have microphones and everything set up to send in feedback.
Not a problem.
We've got voicemail lines for you.
And I'm just kind of talking here covering for myself as I'm trying to find the voicemail numbers.
Here we go.
We have a number in the United States and New Jersey,
201, 65, 65, 65, 7.
Go ahead, put that in your phone right now.
And then as you store it, just put in the Charlie or just Charlie.
Or Adam, which would be the top of the list.
No, don't do that because I get so many butt phones.
My name being Adam being at the top of people's list.
I can't count the number of butt phone calls.
I get someone sits on their phone and then it just dials whatever is handy,
which is usually the top of the list, which is usually A.
Which is usually me.
In London, we have a phone number for you.
O2O76813753.
Lots of stuff going on at the office as well for Pod Show UK.
It's getting so exciting.
I guess we're going to have another whole delegation coming over in the next couple of weeks.
And it's going to go fast.
It really is.
We're going to start cranking into pretty high gear pretty soon now.
And it's all of course going to come together.
And I've told you about my stay here being really,
you know, the, how we're just, the final touches are being put on before we can go public data.
And it's still going to be fucked up and broken and full of wards and burps and nooks and crannies that are all wrong.
Yeah, it's okay.
But got a lot of people really excited about it.
And that would be the people who've been working on it for 10 months at this point.
Hey, last night, by the way, I had dinner with the Emily Morris.
I've talked about her before.
And in fact, it's funny. Emily is she turned down an offer from Pod Show to join the network.
She had a podcast called The Sex with Emily Podcast.
And I really like what she was doing.
And I thought she really had a way of connecting with her listeners.
And I think her numbers were pretty darn good as well from what I remember telling me.
But she, just around the time that we were talking to her about joining the network.
She was looking at a couple of different things that she's, I think she also an actress.
In fact, she is, she's in the movie. I'm a sex addict.
You got to see that. That's pretty funny. It's getting like critical acclaim.
I'm a sex addict the movie.com.
But she's now on, what is it?
Free FM 106 here in San Francisco.
It's owned by Infinity CBS.
So it's old media, right?
And they actually provide podcast versions of her show.
Which don't really work for me because it's a call-in show.
And it's about sex. But wow, what I realize, listening to that.
And I'll have to listen to her live on Saturday if I can find a radio.
I guess I'll have to sit in the car to listen to the radio.
If I have Trinity back by then, she actually is at a very, you know,
where this nexus of mainstream media where it's not satisfying listeners,
where we're completely, you know, going off in one direction.
And the audience is running towards podcasting and podcasting is running towards the audience.
At the same time, I think that there's a very few things that we can't compete with.
And when it comes to asynchronous media like podcasting, the live aspect,
you know, I always say if we find a song I've been loud and don't go running to your iPod
because you're going to be disappointed at that very moment.
The next day, you'll have all kinds of cool stuff to listen to.
When it comes to live, particularly people in cars with cell phones,
who just want to talk to someone, it really works.
And I think that she, it's how it's strange as it sounds.
I think that she really is the future of terrestrial radio.
It's all this other stuff that you're hearing.
It's got to simplify.
Radio has to really change their ways.
And it'll, you know, I'm following her.
But anyway, I was really nice and went to a great restaurant,
which I'm finding out that, you know, around the condo,
there is kind of, you know, there's some nice places.
What is it?
The boulevard, which is right off, it's a mission and near-embarked arrow.
Wow, great food.
She makes me, she made me laugh very much.
She's like totally out of her mind.
So anyway.
Soccer.
It's coming up.
This weekend, big, big game.
And I think a couple of pod showers are going to get together
and watch the game.
And if you want to know more about the world cup, as you know,
I don't care about soccer, except one of the world cup,
or maybe the European championship.
I don't even like the champion league.
But I do have an update for it.
Hi, I'm Mrs. Phil.
And this is Tony.
We're from the Soccer Show podcast available at SoccerShow.com.
Let's get caught up, mate.
Let's do, because we're almost at the end of the first round of group games.
Let's do a round of what we've seen so far.
The big games and the big teams.
What stood out for you so far?
I think going all the way back, I think to that very first game
to turn them at Germany against Costa Rica.
Six goals in the open and game of a World Cup finals.
You can't beat that.
Yeah, I'm just going to jump in here and say, oh, yeah.
I mean, particularly because the games are being hosted in Germany.
Yeah.
I think the Germans are real happy with what's going on there.
And then we had England on the Saturday.
They'd be Paraguay, one nail.
It wasn't a great game.
It wasn't a great performance.
But it was the result.
England needed Colin Beat, Serbian, Montenegro, one nail.
Yeah.
Even though that wasn't a fantastic score,
because it, you know, I guess it's,
depending on how many goals you score,
that's how many points you get.
I never understand any of the scoring stuff.
But man, Robin, Ryan Robin, who is the Dutcher,
what does he use as a striker?
Is he, I think, as a striker?
Wow, man.
Guy was on fire.
It was just, it was beautiful to watch him.
And if only Ruit von Nisselroy could have jumped in,
then they would probably have scored a couple more goals.
Looks like a really narrow result,
but I thought Holland would tremendous.
Yeah.
Then we had OOCH, USA, NILL,
Czech Republic.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
Yeah.
It just doesn't look good now for the USA.
That gold difference could be a killer for them.
I think it's still doing the game.
They could still do it.
And Italy got the result they needed again.
You know, none of the big teams
have really looked at dominating so far.
I'm going to fast forward to today's game,
Brazil, one nail against Croatia.
Brazil didn't look that handy for me.
Czech Republic, for me, has been the best team that I've seen.
Over the next couple of days,
we're actually going to go into the,
the first of the second round games on
way to stay.
We've got Germany against Poland.
Which match?
Absolutely huge historically.
Great match.
Germany's backline definitely looks dodgy.
So it could be an interest in one.
It's funny.
I haven't heard from comics to blogger about that game yet.
Then Thursday,
we have England versus Trinidad and Tobago.
Should be an easy one for England.
It should be the game that guarantees their passage into the next round.
Friday, there's a few good ones because it's our favorite group.
I think.
Group C, Argentina versus Serbia, Montenegro.
And then Holland versus the Ivory Coast.
So I'm really looking forward to Friday.
I think Friday.
I don't agree.
Yeah.
No secret.
The fight that I'm back in Holland for this one.
I want to see them soon too.
Well, and hopefully see a few goals in that one.
All those games we've mentioned are on ESPN 2, by the way.
The year list of them is during the week is on ESPN 2.
And all the games is coming weekend or on ABC in the United States.
A side day of course.
It's the Italy versus the United States.
That's three o'clock Eastern time in the US.
And Rudy, it's a must win.
I've been trying to work out how the USA could go through with a draw.
And I don't think with a goal difference they have.
I don't think it's going to happen.
So they really need to come out and beat Italy.
And then Sunday, I think the game of the day is going to be Brazil versus Australia.
The two teams that win their opening matches.
Okay.
I think that's God's caught up.
Check it out.
And that is your subscription list.
Wherever it's soccershout.com.
All right, guys.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to your next update.
Yeah.
Saturday.
So that's going to be fun.
I think that the US actually, I got hope.
They got clobbered in that first game.
But I really feel that the Italians are out there.
They're probably thinking how are you asking up.
And they're going to come out with their big swing index.
But do not underestimate the yank.
Do not underestimate them.
Some more UK feedback here.
Go.
Hey.
There's a question for you from the West Coast.
One thing about England.
I hear that you can't buy cider and beer in the same pine glass in England.
Is this true?
And you've said, how do you explain that?
A second question on legal subjects in Holland.
You cannot.
To a moment.
So first of all, is that what's called the snake bite?
I don't know if that's illegal or not.
I've had one.
I've had one here in San Francisco.
This by the way is a K2.
It's Kevin ready from pod show.
It's not like I didn't know he was going to call in with this question.
But he said, could you ask your listeners?
If snake bite is illegal in the UK, it's a dude.
You've got the voicemail line.
Give me a call.
I hear that they're going to be following Ireland and preventing people from smoking in public places.
How will this impact copy shops?
And if it does impact copy shops and you're forced to smoke either neat or do without.
Would you alter your smoking habit accordingly if it's supposed to?
That's it.
Good luck with Charlie.
Hope to hear it too.
Bye.
Yeah.
Well, this is going to happen worldwide.
And I think it's pretty much a good thing.
Smoking in public places.
That's just doesn't work anymore.
I get it.
And I've been a lifelong smoke, I guess.
And in the States, I really enjoy it.
You know, that's where there are places in California where you can't smoke on the beach.
And I'm all for it.
And it's good, you know, don't get mad just to get even.
And don't get mad just deal with it.
You can do whatever you want in your own home.
So now will it what'll happen in the Netherlands?
Man, the coffee shops are dying breed.
You can no longer sell a coffee shop.
A coffee shop, by the way, for those who don't know, is not where you buy coffee in Amsterdam or in the rest of Holland.
It's where you buy marijuana and it's legal or it's fuzzy.
But you don't get arrested for it.
As I said, they're dying breed.
You legally can now not sell a coffee shop, the someone who will then continue the coffee shop.
So when all the current owners die, then it's just going to be over.
And quite honestly, you know, Europe can't sell this anymore on a pan European level.
They can't be the only country who is not outlawed this particular plant.
So they're going to clamp down.
It's going to be over.
It will be.
But maybe in 50 years from now, people understand really what that plant does and what it can do.
And I'll tell you, man, my mom has me make special tea whenever I come over.
She's really starting to dig this stuff.
All right, just a couple minutes before we hit the satellite window.
I wanted to play for you.
Another entry for our EarthLink ad challenge.
I talked about this one on Tuesday's show.
Remember, this is advertising made by you, right?
So no longer is EarthLink telling you how great their service is.
The podcasts are not telling you how great their service is or what their service is about.
But actually users are telling you about it.
My name is Rachelle Kumar and I am about to tell you the one story of how I found EarthLink service
when I was 11 years old.
So here's a setting.
It's a year 2002.
I am in the sixth grade as an 11 year old kid.
Well, my family is looking for internet service and my dad completely gives up saying nothing's affordable and
giving you true high speed.
Like, dad, that is a lie.
I look around on slow, cruddy dial up and here it is.
EarthLink high speed internet.
Back then, in 2002, 49.95 a month for three megabits per second.
That was top of the line.
We ordered it and we got that email client.
We got anti virus.
We got firewall and to spy where everything, the whole package.
And I'm proud to say ever since 2002, we are proud.
EarthLink subscribers.
Come on.
If in 11 year old kid can make the right decision, I think you can too.
Fantastic.
That's great.
Go to adchallenge.podshow.com and you can enter with an endorsement.
You can enter with anything, really.
Just whatever you think will work.
But we have categories and it's what we have endorsement.
We have a commercial spot like produced and we have a song or a jingle.
And PWFenton, by the way, is indeed one of the judges.
I played something that hadn't actually been approved for the judges yet.
And he was like, hey man, don't have people send that to you directly.
I said, no, it was sent into the adchallenge site.
I just kind of felt it out there.
If you're checking us out on serious stars 102, Pacific Coast, Hellway is next.
And of course, I'll be back with you for the Friday festivities here on the Charlie,
which will be tomorrow.
Take care, everybody.
And for you still hanging out, I've got another one for you.
This is cool.
The reverse engineers, you may have heard them on this show.
You can find them on the Podsake Music Network.
Well, they checked in with their own song for Earthling.
I think what is it to hold on.
The ID3 tags aren't showing up.
Let me just see if I can find it here.
Crap, hold on.
See, this is sucks.
All right.
Oh, man.
I have to open up in a quick time window to actually see what the ID3 tags say.
That's funny.
Last blast, I think, should do the bandwidth conservation society.
Okay.
That's a reverse engineers with their throw at $2,000.
Ready, you want to go today.
I heard my computer say everywhere.
Take me there.
With every single one of you.
There's a lot of creativity out there.
I tell you, add challenge.podshow.com.
Stuff really is working.
It's so cool to see everyone putting their ideas together.
It doesn't have to be a highly technically produced piece.
It can be anything at all as long as it's done like six megabytes.
You should be able to do that.
There's more working and advertising.
We do talk about that from time to time.
This whole GoDaddy promotion has been running across the network.
We have all these codes.
If you go out and use one of those promotional codes.
For instance, you can get a domain name from GoDaddy.
If you use the code DSC3.
Now the way this works is our podcasters on the network.
Of course, they're compensated for doing that.
We call in the advertising business for every conversion.
In other words, every single fan listener, audience member who's listening to the show,
their favorite podcasters says, yeah, I'm going to go get me a piece of the internet.
And usually register something weird.
Like, what was it for CC Chapman, Mark Yoshimura Nemkov,
from PCH registered corporateradiosucks.com or something like that.
The code that's used actually money goes to the podcast.
I found out that we've converted like 5,000 domain names.
It's an unbelievable.
This is a runaway success.
And I knew that it would work.
But I had no idea that, well, I did.
What's really happening is we're leaving the messaging up to the individual producer
of the individual podcast.
Who knows how to talk to their audience.
Screw this one spot fits all thing.
And it's really working.
I got to tell you.
It's exciting because that boads well for the future podcasting.
Hi, this is Kurt Cohen from Belgium.
I was catching up with a Friday show on Monday morning.
When I was traveling to the moment, man, he did some mental programming there.
As soon as I got out of the year, I started my ice,
and keenly started stopping boobs.
I had to put my sunglasses on to get enough to the market.
I hope you caught that.
I was talking about with the warm weather in London that there's just
Wald.
I was talking with Patricia about that.
There's just Waldowall boobs everywhere.
Oh, man.
English women like showing them off.
Yep.
Sunglasses are required.
The colleagues.
Well, female colleagues.
In case you're missing London while you're in the US.
Here's a good tip.
After last year's test run, we just launched a new series of
the London-based podcast.
It's a podcast with loads of interesting tips for anybody
taking a break in London.
The second series consists of two versions, one in Dutch,
and one in French nowals.
So that's brand new.
As it's a commercial initiative for one of our
customer to see your restaurant, we had a hell of a job getting
a couple of six years again to it because of the commercial
aspect even though the branding is extremely light.
We had to get sign contracts from each group member and each
record company for those who have already had one.
Listen to this.
This is really cool.
So his client is Euro starts.
The train that runs all across France and Germany and
the Netherlands and whatever.
It's fast train.
Take your straight to Disneyland.
And so they're putting together some kind of marketing materials.
And he went to the Podsiff Music Network and contacted
each of the bands and the members to get permission.
And I presume he played them as well to license the music to
put into their marketing.
It's great dude.
I can't tell you how much I appreciate you thinking of the PMN.
I thought this might just interest you.
Because there is a demand on the commercial side for,
for about 16 years it could be used in,
and this call it the semi commercial podcast.
So anybody who understands that your French serves to
www.uristard.com slash the London dates and
subscribe to the feed.
Thanks, bye.
So if you're kind of new listening to podcasts and you're
wondering, well, what exactly are this?
There's only two questions I really get from people.
So what does Podsiff Music and what does this
and say a thing all about?
This and say a thing another time.
Podsiff Music Network though.
This is me.
God.
Since you.
The Podsiff Music Network was devised really to create a place
where artists can come together with podcasters.
That's really the main.
And there's a subpart to it, of course,
for listeners who want to find out more about the artist,
perhaps by an MP3, et cetera.
But it's all about the licensing.
And this is the thing that mainstream media and the record industry
or really the record industry has not been able to figure out
is, you know, without breaking their own rules,
how do they get this music in the hands of podcasters
because, yeah, because it's a podcasters down low,
which means people could steal it and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
It goes nowhere.
Although there are, you know, what we're seeing now
is there are many artists who own their own stuff.
You know, you have to own your own stuff.
Usually if you're with a record company,
the record company owns your material.
And they're the ones that make all the decisions.
But if you own your own stuff, you can write a license
to anybody you want.
It could be for Eurostar or could be for podcasts.
We've just made it simple where you sign up.
You put your stuff up.
The licenses in place and you're protected.
But there is some confusion.
So this guy really got it right.
You know, he went out and licensed everything.
This other piece of feedback I received really important
that you listen to what's going on here because it's not right.
And it is in violation of the pod save music network terms.
And it's good that this comes up.
Because of course, there's no malice intended.
But we do have to discuss this.
So listen to this.
How do you add them?
This is David from the Catholic Family podcast at catholicfamilypodcast.com.
And I have some questions for you today.
Recently, we created a companion feed to a regular podcast that contains
all of the pod safe music that we play sorted by episode.
Since we play mostly Christian rock, the theory is that this music
only feed makes downloading the songs into a playlist
convenient for our subscribers.
Since we're giving attribution for the songs in the feed,
including a link to the artist.
And we're using them in a non-commercial manner.
I would think that this would be an acceptable use of pod safe music.
Recently, I noticed that the pod safe music network that there was a message
at the bottom of my podcasting page that read,
we have removed XML feed due to abuse by some users.
We are currently working on other options.
I'm guessing that podcasters were using this feed to point their subscribers
to pod safe music, which would mean that the subscribers were downloading
many times the number of files that would be downloaded
in the podcasters were downloading them.
Now, I believe that we as podcasters should share the load.
So I've made copies of all of our podcasters and put them in our server
so that I'm not taking advantage of your servers.
These are the files that our music feed references.
Here are my questions.
Is it becoming a common practice for podcasters to create
companion feeds for this purpose?
Do you think it is a legitimate use of pod safe music to provide this?
And if so, should podcasters share the load,
especially considering the imminent launch of the PDN,
or is this something that you will support?
Bye for now.
All right, so let's step back.
No, not okay, not legal use of the material.
My microphone should.
Okay, so essentially, if I understand correctly what you're doing
is you're using music in the show and then as a service to your listeners,
you've created a companion feed, which if you subscribe to it,
then those songs, the actual MP3s will drop into your podcatcher.
You know, it'll come into your iTunes or whatever.
No, not allowed, go reread the terms and conditions.
You're only allowed to use these songs in a new form.
And the legalese is, it's not even that legal actually when you read it,
but it can only be in a new form of work.
So you can't actually take the file itself and in fact it says,
you may not redistribute these that way.
You can't just take the file and give it away again.
It's completely wrong.
And if you think about it, use some common sense.
No, you cannot do that.
I think about the XML link, which was actually was quite nice,
because I used that a lot.
If you add something to your playlist as a producer, as a podcaster,
then that would become automatically part of a feed.
And so I could then have all the songs that I've played come into my computer
automatically, so it have the nicely organized et cetera.
And of course, what people were either doing or finding out is they were
figuring out where these feeds were and they just subscribed to them.
And you just get free music all day.
So no, you cannot do that.
Please remove the companion feed.
I'm happy you asked.
But as nothing to do with servers or bandwidth,
it's just, it's not what the license says.
It's not what the agreement is.
Okay.
So the whole point of the podsaid music network or the way it's
supposed to function is when you play a song.
You report that to the network so the artist knows that he was played
or the band was played.
And you put a link in your show notes so that listeners can go over
find out about the artist, listen to other songs.
And if they want, they can actually purchase the MP3.
So I think you know that if you have purchasing there and you're giving away
away, that's not those two things don't go together.
So please don't be giving away the music in that manner.
It is not yours to give away.
It is yours to use within a new piece of work,
which would be a podcast or a video podcast.
Almost anything else you can think of,
but not as individual original files.
Thank you.
Hey y'all, you podcast fans out there.
This is Michael O'D.
Of most people are D days.
But do you know that this week's episode of most people are D days?
We'll be my 50th episode.
And I'll be celebrating it by giving you
a special extended mix by yours truly.
So check it out on Monday,
June 19th at www.mostpeplodejays.com
where everyone is a critic and most people are D days.
Especially Michael O'D.
Hey y'all, I don't get you out from what's outside of you
and the podcast and both the name and second life
and also the data cast.
Hey look, good to see you in second life this afternoon at the brothel.
Riding the ball, I'm still cleaning bull poop off my shoes,
but a little virtual bull poop off my virtual shoes.
But anyway, I think last time I saw you with that
the Potio Palace opening, which by the way,
episode 87 of Love House Radio,
I did do my sound scene tour of the opening.
Nothing exciting, but kind of neat to play with.
While the window is the palace,
when we were going to see some performances,
maybe some pot-tap artists or something
that nature just kind of curious.
I felt like a exciting concept to get like a
adjustment in their play and or something like that.
Didn't know if I was off the mailing list or if I was still in the works,
but just wanted to check in with you.
Again, good seeing you.
And we'll talk to you soon.
Yeah, PD, thank you man.
He's really been very helpful with the stuff
that I've been thinking about doing in second life.
This is my wife makes me say this every single time.
It's the virtual world second life.
It's a game, but then it's not really
and then it is again kind of it's a chat environment.
It's a place where people get together.
There's so many technical and technological limitations
to this that, you know,
I'm still trying to figure out what exactly to do.
I have come up with a plan with the,
well, most of you who are in second life
have probably seen Brittany Mason.
So Brittany and I've come up with a plan
and we're working with a couple of people on,
on making something happen that I think will facilitate all this.
You know, we had the palace idea.
But the technical limitations, oh sorry.
The technical limitations just really don't make it possible.
More than like 30 people hanging around at one time.
So this is some stuff that we're doing to up that number
and to really make a community place
where we have a lot more control over what's happening
because I get so sick and tired of, you know,
shit appearing and stuff blowing up
and they're definitely, you know,
my castle has been destroyed several times.
Like, no one knows mysteriously how it happened.
So I just had no patience for that.
I'm all for trying to make something happen there,
but not if all this crap goes down
and if it just doesn't work right.
So I'll keep you up to speed on that,
but it'll probably be,
it'll probably be another week or two before anything
really worth mentioning is,
it's going to take place.
And of course, as always, when it rains,
it pours, it all comes together because
the Podgeau Plus, Podsafe,
the Podcast delivery network,
everything coming together.
The nexus are intertwining.
Hey Adam, this is Tom from the Buckeye Drive Time Podcast.
Since you have some audio comments,
you've played me a couple times on the air.
I appreciate that.
And I have sent you a ton of mail
and have just begged until I can beg no more.
Oh, dude.
I ignore all that shit for a Podgeau contract.
I'm coming up on 100 shows.
I'm getting ready to record.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What is that?
Begging for a Podgeau contract?
Oh, no.
Let me just put that piece again.
I'm coming up on 100 shows.
I'm getting ready to record show number 80.
And have just begged until I can beg no more
for a Podgeau contract.
I'm coming up on 100 shows.
I'm getting ready to record show number 80.
And it would be great to have this done before I hit my centennial.
That will mean that I have spun over 3,000 songs
from the Podsafe music network
and played over 3,000 promos for other podcasts.
One of the things that's kind of
concerning is how many of the podcasts that I have spun
the first promo for on Buckeye Drive Time
and they've going on to have Podgeau contracts.
What do I have to do here?
Let me know.
I definitely would like to see if being on Podgeau
can up the listenership.
Thanks, talk to you later.
Well, I should certainly hope so.
Well, there's a couple of things we can do.
The first of all, just I think I should reiterate
when we launch very soon.
It's going to be free for any podcast.
Anyone who wants to do any type of podcast
and you'll be able to use the infrastructure,
the network, the delivery network.
We've got fantastic place for your audience members
to interact with you, interact with each other,
connect, share, a lot of the aisle, the stuff.
It's a social media network.
And you'll be able to use all that for free.
Maybe you want to check that out first
and see, because it's like, yeah,
I just want to get the contract done real quick.
It doesn't work that way.
Everyone always has questions and it's a process.
And the process is ongoing.
Your name of course has been submitted
to the official submission committee
who his name is Richard.
I did that probably a couple of weeks ago.
Yeah, man.
I like what you're doing.
Definitely.
Okay, I'm going to wind it up.
I've got to head off to the office.
Lots of stuff still to do.
It's going to be another fun day.
Breaking some technology,
dreaming, coming up with cool stuff.
And as always around the four or five PM,
we all break out our laptops and
speakers and start cranking up music
because we're all just so giddy and stupid by that time.
The Adams is at Roberts,
from the looking out the window podcast
and the Kansas City Weather Podcast.
I was just wondering if you have gotten a chance
to hear more of a class brand new song.
You just put it out on the podcast music network.
A few days ago,
I don't know, maybe in the weeks ago.
I heard C.C. Chapman talking about
he couldn't play it because of computer problems and stuff.
It's called not for me,
just absolutely made tender,
emotionally gripping,
you know,
it really showcases your voice.
It's going to lead you crazy for more at the end.
And I think you'll just be horrible.
If you didn't get a chance to at least hear it
or even play it on the B.S.C.
Saturday, email,
we're going to be interviewing here
for looking out the window.
You're probably this week.
I don't know if it would be good
in this week's show or not,
but we'll get the story behind what that song is all about.
I'm looking out the window.
And you're listening,
there's that would be a very cool thing to hear.
I want to be sure to be able to hook up
and do the interview.
And keep it going.
I'm going to have you back in the stage, bro.
Bye.
Shouldn't life be easy now.
Now I'm over you.
But why do I care?
And why can't I laugh?
And why do I fall to pieces?
Every time I see your photograph,
is it because
it's because
you're older because
you're younger.
you're older.
it's because
You're older
you're older.
Too high, but it hurts so much in sight
And I know, I know, you're not for me
I know, you're not for me
I tried to tell you
Time and time again
But love is blind and you decided not to see
What I told you, what I needed
And I know, it's not for me
But I can't be there
So I tried to hide
But it hurts so much in sight
And I know, I know, you're not for me
I know, you're not for me
Shouldn't life be easy now
Now that I'm over you
Wow, is that prettier?
Laura Clap, not for me
I totally agree, it does leave you
Just wanting for more at the end of that
It is chilling
And you can find Laura Clap on the Podsake Music Network
You know, it's really nice
You know, all the Podsake Music
You can really get involved in an artist's career
What they're doing
Because it's all still so small
I guess it's very much reminiscent of the 60s
And coffee houses and stuff like that
And the FM radio in the early early early days
And what's so nice is that
And so often when I play a song
The artist will send me an email
Because when you report that into the network
Automatically notification is sent to the artist
And they'll send me an email
Thanking me
Oh, terrible
Excuse me
Damn, sorry
But they'll do it every single time
And my response is almost automatic now
Please don't thank me
I thank you so much for putting your music up there
For taking a risk and hopefully it's paying off for every single artist who is
Joining up with PMN
And also when we come out with Podsco plus in the PDM
There's all kinds of stuff for artists there as well
I mean it's like
I wish I had a hundred more people
So we'd go a hundred times faster
It's just it's so much work and so much to be done
But it's it's going to be great
Anyway
Laura Clap has sent these emails to me several times
And you know and she keeps thanking me
And I say don't thank me
Just send naked pictures
All right everybody tomorrow
We're going to do the thank God us fried edition of the daily source code to feedback
Adamaccurry.com
You've got the voicemail numbers everything is in the show notes
A daily source code dot com where you can find the latest episodes and the podcast feed
Take care everybody. I'll see you tomorrow
I can't
I did that
Peter help me out
So Podsco podcast
Stick it in your ear
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from Podsco
And limelight networks
I love it