The town of Shadow Falls holds a secret so much kill to protect, and others will die to expose.
Who's here to my dad, didn't you?
Swordle.
I'm the one that killed him.
Hey!
Be monks to choose an initiative for alls.potshow.com.
This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 442.
It's on Muscle.
About $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I need such a sweet sweet thing to lay.
Gotta hold on me.
I hope and dose for little ladies.
I have the plan to see.
I've got a friend who's written the papers.
Thinkin' there's daylight with me.
I feelin' real shut down in my heart.
Feelin' there's daylight with me.
I see it no more.
It's a nice guy.
No more.
That's it.
I'm sick.
I won't see you before.
I got a friend who goes and written the papers.
Thinkin' there's daylight with me.
I feelin' real shut down in my heart.
I'm feeling insane, I'm saying no more
It's a nice guy, no more
It's a nice guy, they said, I'm saying
I want to be with you
I don't feel me on the legs today
I can't close my eyes
It's a nice guy, I want to be thrown out of the soul
It's always a circle, and then has the heart
I went to church, looking at coffee too
When everybody rules
The river's living, yeah good night's me
The punishment in the nose, they said no more
It's a nice guy, no more
No more, it's a nice guy, they said
I said, I'm saying, no more
It's a nice guy, no more
It's a nice guy, they said, I'm saying, I'm saying
I'm saying, no more
Yeah, yeah
Alice Cooper, no more, it's a nice guy
Live in Montrose, Montrose, which is a lamb
In 2005 from Brand New
DVD, CD, and it's on the pod safe music network.
This is so phenomenal.
This is exactly what we had hoped,
that's a nice fade out, by the way.
This is exactly what we had hoped for
when we started building the pod safe music network.
Wouldn't it be great if these huge artists
could put some of their back catalog up
and have podcasters share that with their audience?
Maybe educate some people about older songs
that we just can't play.
And of course, it's a loophole,
and this is when I'm loving so much.
The master recording, I'm sure that the original
no more Mr. Nice guy is probably owned by
Warner Chapel or some publishing company,
more than likely not owned by Alice Cooper himself.
But the words, and the music he owns, he wrote those,
and he can license that any way he wants.
So apparently, he owns, or I guess,
was this eagle rock entertainment.
He was releasing this DVD, and so this live recording,
he has a whole separate deal, and as a part of the promotion,
yes indeed, it's up on the Ponset Music Network.
So that's really, I mean, think about how phenomenal this can be.
All you have to do as a mainstream artist
is to re-record.
That's all that it takes.
Then of course, I can already hear people going,
oh, what about all the other cool bands
of the Pods of Music Network?
Yeah, I have not forgotten about them,
but I'm just so pleased to see.
Let's see, what do we have?
We had, so first we had Deep Purple come in.
George Thurra Good, Alice Cooper, rainbow,
also now in the Pods of Music Network,
and I'll be playing some Gary Moore at the end of today's Daily
Source Code, which is kind of a weird one,
because you almost didn't have a source code today.
The plan was for me, actually, to go fly
to see Cas Blaster Mike in the Netherlands.
Now, the weather today in Holland is very nice.
Actually, the sun is just starting to break
through a little bit here.
However, this would be my first solo crossing
of the English channel.
You know, I'm a little bit wary of that, particularly,
because I didn't have the practice that I wanted to do
over the past weekend.
And they are expecting about 35 knots of wind near the end
of the afternoon and thunderstorms and rain.
And that's pretty much the spot where I would cross
Ostenda, which is the shortest route
across the English channel.
So it's from basically in Belgium,
so from Belgium, I'd fly up.
But coming back, the only alternative would be to take
the long route, which, of course, I've done many, many times,
but with a safety pilot, and I just don't really
feel confident enough to do it.
And I think that that's really what aviation is about
is when you know your limits and when you know
that you cannot do something or you shouldn't
probably be doing something.
It's much safer for me and for the environment.
So maybe Sunday, I don't know, it's so much to do.
Yesterday, of course, there was no daily source code,
my apologies for that.
I fully intended to do one.
I had a whole day of meetings in the city in London
with Neil Dixon, who was working
with this pod show UK, meeting some extremely talented people.
Just spent the whole day outside.
It wasn't really that sunny, but it was just really nice.
It wasn't chilly or windy.
And we just hung out and drank habachinos
and talked about all kinds of cool stuff.
And how wonderful it could be.
If all the talent that people in the world could have
all the distribution they wanted.
And it was just, it was fantastic.
And how, man, there was a, was it pod fest
was last night in London that's feel coin?
Is it a bit job for the masses?
You can find it, I think it's a podfest.com.
And so a lot of people from the pod casting
seem we're going there last night and unfortunately
I couldn't attend because, oh, you know,
we still have you gone here and there's just lots to do.
And it was so warm last night.
I woke up at least five times.
So anyway, so the reason was no show on Mondays
because I'd set the alarm for seven o'clock.
You know, Christina still doesn't have to go to school.
So we're getting up about an hour later, typically.
But in order for me to make my one o'clock meetings,
I had to really set the alarm.
And somewhere in the middle of the night,
the alarm clock fell off the nightstand, the battery popped out.
And so we woke up around 9.39, 45.
And I'm like, okay, I guess we won't have time
to do a show because it takes some time.
And now that I'm catching up,
I asked Patricia today, I said,
would you mind doing a show?
And whenever she answers, well, what time do you want to do it?
And she knows that I have to have this done by like 130
in the afternoon in order to hit the satellite window
for Peter.
So she knows that.
And that's kind of her secret way of saying,
I have other stuff to do today.
No.
And the other stuff is her sister Ivana's leaving today.
So I kind of understand, they wanted it.
I think go into town one more time
walk on the high street and do whatever.
And it's sisters, you can't come between them.
So tomorrow, Patricia will definitely be on the show.
I promise you that.
And I've got lots of stuff to do.
The visual communicator, studio software package
came in today is huge.
And I didn't, this is cool.
They actually sent me a green screen.
It's a part of the package.
You can hang it behind you if you want to do virtual sets
and stuff.
So I'm sure I'll be playing around with that a little bit today.
And lots of communication with San Francisco.
You may have noticed, if you checked out podshow.com,
that all that work we did over the weekend up until all the way
through yesterday is starting to pay off.
We've added extra freedom to the system.
All kinds of server configurations and stuff.
And man, the site is just flying.
So that means that once we have this all cordoned off
and we're happy with the performance,
now we can really start to build out some features.
Because I have to say, you guys
came in in a little bit stronger numbers
than we anticipated initially.
And we'd set up, obviously, what is it?
Load balance stuff and all that.
But still, we definitely had to configure
a few of their servers to keep up with the demand.
So show-wise today, I had about 50 different voice
mill messages.
And I thought, I'll play a couple of things
that I just have laying around that I've been
meaning to share with you.
And then maybe we just go through a couple of these voice
metals and just see what people are saying
because it's just a shame not to do anything with them
and just to let them go.
And by the way, it's your contribution to the share.
Hi there Adam.
And this.
Yeah.
This is Eric and Andrea from Let's Get Nautie.
The next time you're in a steamy, a soldier
and let's face a naughty mood, you need to tune into our
show.
We're fine.
We're insightful and we're downright provocative.
So if you are all about pleasure and pleasing others,
give us a listen.
And Adam, we know you like pleasure.
You can find us at www.let'sgetnautiepodcast.com
or subscribe to us in iTunes.
That just started my weekend off just fine.
The app's so loosely.
I use a show that I've been working with
Jay Donnelly on this.
I mean, I'm not really working on it,
but I've been giving him feedback and giving some suggestions.
And this is something that we talked about on the daily source
code a long time ago about doing test drives of cars.
Just going up and saying, hey, can I do a test drive?
And recording it, of course.
Now he's taken it one step further with his girlfriend Holly.
And they're actually recording this on video.
And I think some of the sales people are now
cluing or tuning into the fact that they might actually not
be there to buy.
But the episode five of Test Drive Girl is out.
Hey, everybody, Jay Donnelly with you.
And on today's show, the Test Drive Girl,
what's the latest episode of this week?
Yeah, we're test driving the Kia Sorrento this week.
And how did that go?
Well, you have to watch the show on Friday.
I'm not going to tell you all my details.
Yeah, okay.
So, uh, all right, did you enjoy the ride?
Was it a good ride?
Oh, I enjoyed the sales guy.
That was a good ride.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I heard you called him a honey.
Oh, yes.
So go to test drivegirl.com.
Check out the latest episode of the Test Drive Girl.
Right on.
I like it, man.
It's cool.
Because it's a real test drive.
And you can see these sales guys bullshit in their way through.
It's fantastic.
Okay, hitting the voice mill numbers.
Of course, the number, if you don't have a pre-programmed
and you're mobile phone cell phone yet, uh,
do the plus thing.
Now, we went through this, um,
want to go there Friday.
So, plus is usually accessed by hitting zero twice or whatever.
And then, uh, one for the country code two zero one for Jersey 65 65 65 seven
or London 020 76813753.
Hey, Adam, it's Paul Parkinson.
Uh, thanks for the shout out on, uh, yesterday's show.
But, uh, man, um, Patecast Paul isn't Paul Parkinson on Paul Parkinson.
And Paulcast Paul is a lawyer from Birmingham and does the
Paul Parkinson podcast Paul podcast.
He's also on podcast using magazine.
I'm Paul Parkinson.
And I'm known as Parkinson.
I do the flashing tall podcast in the weird nylon podcast and I do podcast using magazine.
Paul Pinfield is Paul Pinfield.
And he does the calm cast and podcast using magazine.
He said your confused can you imagine what it's like for us?
Um, Paul Parkinson, I may take it.
Oh, one more thing.
I hope you're wordless the other day.
Have you seen the V's website?
www.vz.co.uk.
I have check out the perfanysaurus section.
Um, I'm sure some of those won't make you onto the list.
But, uh, have a look.
Tell me what you think.
I'm like, cheers.
Fuck.
This is so moment brought to you by all the Pauls in the UK.
Yeah, it's too confusing for me, man.
I can't keep you guys apart.
You know, I got a drumstick from from Paul one or Paul two and
Paul three and
You're right, it is confusing.
It's way too much for me.
Let's see, uh, a lot of feedback on, uh,
on my mini rant about that story on MPR, uh, about, uh,
flying business or first class and and how that actually
subsidizes, um, a economy cast, a class travel.
Boy, you guys respond to pretty strongly to that.
I wish you would send in more audio comments because, you know,
just reading stuff off comments isn't all that compelling.
So you can call in the voicemail line anytime.
No one really yelling at me on the voicemail line as much as they were in the comments.
Uh, but there was some feedback on it.
Hey, Adam, it's been from Southern California.
Um, just listening to the DSC 4401, we'll see the guy from MPR.
It's like, doesn't he get it?
Communism's dying.
Capitalism is getting.
He's got the money.
Get to do things.
If you want to do things with those guys you're doing,
you work your butt off.
It's kind of like the pressure complaining about you having no butt.
It's because you worked it off and you're reading the benefits.
That's what it's about.
So if you're accepting your standing in line, hey,
then you get out of the line, go back to work.
See you later.
Holder?
Huh, I bet you that was a folder.
And there was a lot of talk about, uh, about these about the foil terror attacks.
And I, I got to tell you, I'm, I'm growing a little bit skeptical.
I really am, uh, you know, main reason being where is the follow-up?
You know, so okay.
So we, we got all these dangerous guys.
We rounded them up.
I guess in the UK, they can hold them for up to 28 days.
But where's the proof?
You know, I should, now I think when you need some follow-up, we really need the follow-up.
And, and if I'm going to hear the message, well, we can't tell you about these guys
because that's not in the interest of national security,
then I'm going to be probably a non-believer in what's going on.
And you know my standpoint on this.
I'm just not going to be scared into anything.
I'm going to fly.
I'm going to do whatever I can in life legally, obviously.
Something's maybe borderline.
But I'm not going to let me, I'm just not going to be scared away by anything.
And I'd like some proof.
I'd like some proof as to what the plot was.
Okay.
So what do we know?
It was like liquid.
It could have been in liquid explosives.
In perfume bottles or lipstick in casings or in baby formula.
Okay, that's all fine.
You know, and they arrested a couple who had a baby who the woman was nursing.
I'd like a little bit of proof on this, guys.
I don't change from the U.K.
I'm just listening to the, it's not even something like what's in the screen.
And it's the call, the call about that conspiracy theory,
the very quiet blogger running.
Just something, it said, run with me or he said that he's giving you no proof.
Neither of the American government given anybody any proof.
It's all, everything that they've come up with so far speculation.
We've got no video evidence.
We've got no call evidence that there was anything on anybody on those planes online.
Yeah, that's really interesting.
You say that.
I just wanted to jump in here because in the United Kingdom,
there are hundreds of thousands of security cameras everywhere.
They're known as CCTV closed circuit television.
And I think the statistic is, if you walk around or if you're any,
if you're outside anywhere in the United Kingdom,
you're caught on camera at least 30 times a day.
And with every other crime that takes place in the United Kingdom,
immediately on the news, you see the CCTV footage.
You know, they show you what's happening.
They show you who's involved and the picture quality is fantastic.
Not a single piece of video about any of these guys.
These alleged terrorists.
Not a single piece.
So, yeah, it's a very fuel level uneasy.
11, and I think somebody, I'm one of these videos,
had some kind of proof, maybe not as much proof as we think about success.
Six or seven of these people are still actually alive.
That was supposed to be on the planes and we're in a normal jobs in America.
So, you know, it's fair enough to make a comment like you've got no proof,
do you learn government that's given you more proof either?
Yeah.
It is a bit strange, however you think turned out.
But there you go.
See you there on that fire.
All right.
I agree.
I haven't seen much proof anywhere.
It's really hard.
I'm tired of it.
I don't want to talk about it anymore.
You know, I'll wrap this up with Matt from
Matt's today in history podcast.
He actually had some pretty good to say that I liked a lot.
Check this out.
Hey, Adam.
This is Matt Bittil of the Matt's today in history podcast.
I was listening to episode 441 of the Charlie and you had a call from
a gentleman, I believe from Austin, Texas, who was talking about the fact that, you know,
supposedly you and I and a lot of other people don't know what's going on with regard to 911.
What really happened with the volunteers really about and that we need to sort of wake up and
you know, find out that we're all being fooled and all that.
And I will say, I'm sure there are things done by governments around the world every day
that are pretty terrible that you and I will never, ever find out about.
However, I think and you probably know this that there is a huge industry that is a
risen out of 911 conspiracies and the problem is that the people who write these books and put
up these websites and that you hear on late night terrestrial radio, they take advantage of people
who, they need that, they need a conspiracy to somehow explain the fact that there are people
in the world who hate them just because of who they are.
The problem with this is that it's dangerous. History is full of sort of, you know, propaganda
that was created out of thin air that drove entire populations to dangerous activity.
If you look at the protocols of the elders of Zion, which was published in the early 20th century,
that basically claimed that the, everyone of the Jewish race was out to dominate the world,
you know, even Hitler and the Nazis used it as an excuse to put Jews and camps.
And so, you know, you have to be very careful when all logic points in one direction,
then that's probably the direction we need to look. I mean, you can certainly look at,
you know, the Bush administration or the Blair administration and say that there are things you
don't like and certainly there are things that I don't like. However, that doesn't mean
there's a worldwide conspiracy to pull the wool over our eyes. So anyway, that's today in history.com
and scruncher. Thanks. Wait a minute, he said it, he's a scruncher!
There's I'm a weapon, weapon, weapon, weapon, weapon, weapon.
You know what I received in my email box this morning?
I received the third episode, the rough mix of Shadow Falls, which I believe we're going to release
on Monday. If you have not heard this originally produced audio drama from Pod Show,
listen to it at ShadowFalls.podshow.com. It will scare the pants off of you.
Mark Yoshimaru, an improv, probably pissed off about you. Let me just, uh, let me uh, let me
play the opening for you. You'll immediately be wanting to hear the episode. There's a story that
people tell in Shadow Falls, a story about a well. Back in the 1700s, the town elders decided to
dig a new well because the old one had gone bad. I leave it up to you to decide what that means.
Every able body male took part in the digging and hauling a birth for the new site. After five
days of back breaking work, the new well was finished and the town elders went to close up the old
well wasn't for all. One old man who claimed to know such things said the old well had been
cursed because the people of Shadow Falls had not pleased the spirits. He told them of an old
tradition after the harvest festival when, along with condemned prisoners. One thing is until
I'll put it all so we sacrifice to it. For every light that shines, a Shadow Falls.
I love it. I have not listened to, uh, uh, I've not listened to the, uh, entire episode. Yeah,
but I'll report back on it tomorrow and it should be dropping on Monday. Shadow Falls.podshow.com.
You know, there was a, I cannot, where was this? I had a comment somewhere.
Someone had met one of the, uh, one of the actors on Shadow Falls. Crap, what was that?
Hold on a second. Let me see if I, hmm. I guess I lost it.
Oh, I'm sorry about that. You just have to go and listen to it on Monday and I'll look for that
for that comment. I'm a little bit discombobulated today. I would say, and I think I had to do
with bad sleep. If you're listening to us on, uh, Syria stars 102, here's what's coming up tonight.
It's Wednesday, uh, right after this show Pacific Coast Hall, hell, hallway Pacific Coast
Hellway, uh, Dawn and Drew, then a great show that, uh, it's called American cliche is also on
the podshow podcast network. Then Michael Butler with a rock and roll geek show and then a non-pod
safe program, which you can only hear on series, which is the Frank truth, Brian No brings you
the world that is Frank's. We just live in it. East radio after that and we wind it up with another
fine audio drama Scott's signal that'll be between 930 and 10 o'clock eastern time. On Syria stars 102,
uh, I'll talk to you guys tomorrow. Um, and if you want to hear more of this show, go to dailysourceco.com
or check out podshow.com for a whole bunch of cool podcasts. And for those of you still hanging around here,
we got the other's ramblings in a crap horse. Like, and that's Troy. I want to play the whole thing.
Hey, and it's Troy from Rutgers ramblings. You know, the iPod guy. Well, it hasn't arrived yet,
but you'll be one of the first to know when it does get here. Anyway, I wanted to drop you a note
for something that I saw on podshow plus over the weekend. Well, you know how Google and Yahoo and
even I think my space has their own start page for their users set up to be my dot
whatever, you know, my dot google dot com or my dot yahoo dot com or, you know, something of that nature. Well,
someone has actually registered the name my on podshow plus. So whenever you go to my dot podshow.com,
it goes to their homepage. And there's a few of us who have been digging the so-called my
in an effort. I don't know to see if people are actually going there. Like, I tried to.
And I could have sworn that that used to go to your your homepage if you had cookies enabled. But
maybe I'm just, uh, remembering it wrong. But whoever my is definitely, uh, definitely gets
a not a my book because that's pretty ingenious. So anyway, like they always say, keep up the good work.
And I'll be listening. Ew. Thanks, Troy. That's kind of interesting. I haven't received the iPod yet.
I thought I'd already want to. Let me know if you don't receive it this week. Okay, and I'll check with
jocelyn. A lot of rumblings in second. Let me just respond to that for a second. So, you know,
having a my dot your company named dot com is, uh, is very 1990 my book. That's what's cool about
podshow plus is you get to make your own URL. So it can be anything you want dot podshow dot com.
And you can also map a domain name to it. If you have something else, and then the site will
understand that and we'll actually pick it up and respond as if it's a I actually haven't even
done that myself. But it's a capability we've built in that I'll go back and do that for the daily
source code dot com. So you can check it out. Um, lots of rumblings in second life.
It's about me saying that if Duran Duran is coming in, it's, uh, it's officially unhip.
And I don't want to be a part of it. There are still plenty of reasons to check out second life.
Adam, this is a hippie geek book from second life. The newest resident of podshow island. I
wanted to remind everybody about the podbong that you can only pick up on podshow island.
Place all the podcasts and podcasters or every day adding new shows to it.
It's aggregating the RSS feeds and it's absolutely free. So come on down to podshow island and
pick up the podbong. Adios, man.
There's nothing like lurking on a virtual bomb, my friends.
Hey, Adam, I'm pretty up to Rob Kerns from the Navy Reserve podcast. Find that at
NavyReserves.navy.mil. Just want to call lunch and know that we're on our fifth podcast now and things
are growing great over here. We're getting in some actual web stats from around the, uh, the Navy and
are from around the world and it's going great. What's a particularly amazing is that since we launched
our podcast, we've been starting to get calls here from other entities in the Navy wanting to know
how they can get a podcast going. And now big Navy has even launched the podcast, much of period
to ours because we're actually trying to make it a real show where a lot of these other elements
are just putting out new stories. But about once a week now, I'm getting one of two calls,
people ask me in the Navy about podcasting, how we developed it and how it's growing and how
what our feedback has been. So it's growing and it's growing exponentially. So I'm sure
not getting as many hits as the DSC, but we're growing out there. So thanks a lot, Adam, for all
your kind of words about us and here continue to support other Navy Reserve podcast. So anchors
away. Take care, man. Bye bye. Oh, that's a good one. Anchors are way. I'd like to know if you're
folder or scruncher. Yeah, that's it's good. I like it for our service men and women in the Navy.
I'm wondering when everyone else is going to join our board and gee, want to be nice if we could
really get some podcasts that we could send overseas for our boys and girls over there,
not just Americans but Brits, Japanese, Dutch, you name it, they're all over the place.
Would you please remind me to play Carmen Tyler tomorrow? She sent me just a beautiful,
beautiful, yeah should I play that for you? Hold on a second. Don't tell me I lost it.
What's up with that? Oh, man, this is so lame. Well, anyway,
hold on a second. Oh, this is making me angry. I think I lost them a whole bunch of files or something.
This is really weird. Well, Karen Tyler sent me this this really wonderful voice feedback.
I'm still searching my desktop as you can tell. Yeah, shoot. Okay. Did you know that she's a
former Miss Louisiana? And now that I'm looking at her picture again on the podcast, music now,
we're going to go like, uh-huh, but she is. So remind me to play that tomorrow and I'll get out of
you here now with one last song from PMN. It's Gary Moore. Remember here? If you're talking about
great guitarists in the world, now you'd probably say maybe Jeff Beck, Eric Clapton. Some might say
be king. But when I think about what we have over here in the UK,
without a doubt, Gary Moore springs to mind. Listen to that sound of gunna reign today.
Yeah?
Outside.
LosЕder is shiny.
It's feeling like we're both the way
But inside
My heart is planned
And I find it's going to rain
Two days
Everybody
I see a smile
As they watch the children play
But for me
No reconciling
And I find it's going to rain
Two days
All the clouds have come
Everybody sees the sun
But for me
No reconciling
The clouds have come
And I find it's going to rain
The sun is shining
But never see
She went away
Inside
My heart keeps planned
And I find it's going to rain
Two days
Yes, I'm free
It's going to rain
Two
Oh, man, how beautiful is that?
Chuh!
Listen to that guitar
Now I know I couldn't find Carmen Tyler
Because the comment she sent
was actually a tag
Which I've been asking you to do
I think it was Suzanne from InsideWorks
Who did the tag for today
And there was another one in there
I love it when you just please send me tags for the source code
You know, I have 4, 4, 2, 4, 4, 3
I don't have a 4, 4, 4, 4 or a 5 or a 6 or a 7
But what Carmen did is she sent me 4, 5, 0
Hey, this is recording artist in former Miss Luziana Carmen Tyler
And you're listening to Delta Sierra Charlie Show number 450
With the pod father himself
Adam Curry
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Can't wait until 450
Send me a picture to put in 450 Carmen Luziana
All right, everybody
I'm going to keep my eye on the weather
But I really don't think it's going to happen
That'll be flying today at least not
The risk is just a bit on the high side for me
And I'll be back tomorrow
More than likely with the lady Patricia
She has promised mind you
Take care Adam at podshow.com
DailySourceCo.com
Talk to you tomorrow
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
Get this podcast and more great ones like it
On the high performance podcast delivery network
From podshow and lime light networks
I love it