This podcast is brought to you by Potcho and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie.
More 3-0.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just in peace, Adam Curry.
Let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it.
We can't hear it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's
take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take
take it, let's take that move back, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's do it, let's take it, well, all of it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it,, let's take it, let's take it, let it take it, do it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, let's take it, we
Can't stop all the rudders when it's really flowing
Break the sales something down in percent increase down low sales
You can't prevent satellite radio and video games
Change the terrain it will never be the same
Did you know in 10 years labels won't exist if I DVDs and compactists?
Hey Mr. Record man, what's wrong with you?
Still living up your cattle up from 1982
Hey Mr. Record man, your system tech compete
It's the new artist model, wild transfer
Break the sales
Down low the sales
You know, we just wanted to level playing fields
You've overcharged us from music for years
And now we're just trying to find a fair balance
I hate to say it, but
Welcome to the future
Down low the sales
Hey Mr. Record man, what's wrong with you?
And your label like it was 1990
Down low the sales
Mr. Record man, your system tech compete
And that's a lyric if I've heard one
It's the new artist model
A wild transfer complete
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
It's Friday, welcome to the last show for this trip
Coming to you from the Curry condo
Hey foggy San Francisco, yes we are back to normal
Time to go back to Blighty
Where it is still well into the 90s
Oh man, thank you so much everybody
For sending the music and that was from Josh English
Who's from Australia
You heard MC Lars
Download this song
Apparently
Been a pretty big hit
Down under
And he said we were going to set this to me
I think probably a week or two weeks ago
And I've just been holding on to it
And I was like yes, the perfect Friday for it
So last night this was going to be the big night out
It's me and our database
Dominatorics Aaron O'Neill
And as it turns out
They were more pod showers
We were going to go to the minks stole show
So yesterday after work
I think like 730 or something I left the office
I wanted to bring my stuff home
I had the car with me
Trinity of course cruise
I want to drop all my stuff off
I figured okay I'll call the cab
To take me over to the venue
And I'll just sit here and just
Just chill out for a couple of seconds
And so I didn't hear the cab call
That they had arrived downstairs
I didn't hear
At least four phone calls
From Aaron I think Chris Rockwell was there
And no in fact somewhere around 11 o'clock
I awoke because I do have some alarm set up
On some of the computers here
If there's something wrong with the pod show site
That shit did wake me up
I was dead
I was out
I was completely gone
Didn't hear anything
Except of course
The one thing my ears trained to
It's like something wrong with the site
Top row and said we gotta go check it out
So I don't have any cool stories about last night
If you like such a dick and wait until I get to the office
I'm going to be ridiculed all day
And I'm sure about it
So no good stories to report I guess
Then from our evening out
Maybe I can tell you all about what
Everyone what kind of trouble everybody got into
When I'm back home with the cottage
And bring you the Monday show
Yes, they did hear Mark Yoshimoto
Nemkoff on Pacific Coast LW
I was insanely jealous
I mean talk about songs
You'd love to play on a Friday
He rolled out Andrew Gold's lonely boy
Which of course is not pod safe
But oh Andrew Gold is a personal friend of his
So it was completely okay
I'm like oh man
Ah
That's I mean lonely boy is such a beautiful
Actually that's a song you want to kick a Friday off with
But since I don't I can't count Andrew Gold is one of my personal friends
You know that Patricia and I we have a couple of songs
That are you know how you have a song that is your song
Or yeah, it's our song one of them
Is a never let her slip away another fantastic Andrew Gold track
It would be cool to play that on Monday hand hint
Even cooler if if the lyric would be
Instead of a talk to my baby on the telephone long distance
You can see why this is our song right?
Because we do a lot of talking long distance
Wouldn't it be cool if
I should I pay for this if I could get Andrew Gold to re-cut that just that
For first opening line and say
I talked to Patricia on the telephone long distance
Oh man, oh man, would I have some super sex if I made that happen
Ha ha
Speaking of Mark Yoshimo to Nemko have you heard of this?
I didn't even know he was doing this show
I'd heard about it. I'd heard about that he'd written
He'd written the show or written parts of it or I don't know if he was supposed to be a book
Or what it was
It's a podcast called Where's my fucking latte?
And it's about public personal assistance and Hollywood and the stories that they've shared
You've got to check this show out of course
I'll put a link into the show notes on that daily source code.com
I think he's up to episode nine
I couldn't believe it tonight
I've I've synced that up into a channel
I've put all of them onto my iPod for the trip home
I cannot I cannot wait to hear every single episode of where the fuck is my latte?
You're on her, I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out
You're on her, please don't bang that gavel
You can try this cowbell out
Let's all give a nod
To the hardest work in law here
It's just inside the bag
You're on her, what do you say?
He might even live in this case
Characters inside
Yeah, yeah, it was Characters inside
Oh, it was Characters inside
Show of now
It was Characters inside
Oh, yeah, I don't hate it
It's the toughest
Yo, what's up, Adam?
It's Characters inside
Hey, and between trying case all week and preparing my debut on serious stars
One or two for this Monday night
It has been a hell of a week
And on her voice, I've read down the Jersey Todd Show dot com
And Jersey Todd Show dot pot show dot com websites
May not have earned a simple lawyer like me a 10-4-0 hat
But man, after this week
I have definitely got my 10-4-0 being on
Look, the quote James Brown, ain't no pain killer
It's a body thriller
I gotta tell you, I am really pumped up
The pot show is chosen to include the Jersey Todd Show in its lineup
I look forward to doing your proud
And I really thank you for the opportunity
But hey, look, it's Friday
And I don't know what you want to kick off the weekend right
So, I'm bringing you to the band lines in the street from Vancouver Canada
They've been called by Magnet Magazine
What the stones were and what the Dandy Warhol should have been
So from the PMN, this is the band lines in the street
With mine ain't yours
Rock on
Rock on Jersey Todd official musicologist of the Charlie
Cranking it out
Now
I'll feel free to turn it off for some
Can't know as much people in here here
Rock it
It's a last chance to rain
Take all down on me
Let us know, take it
My yours, take it
Now you're late
Who's going on with me, though
Your life's much better
My name's yours, take it
And we're now making it right
But how long can you grow
Don't try to sing
Same old song
Never try to make it right
Still without long until you go
Never try to see it out of my head
I was looking for a place to hide
Let us know, take it
My yours, take it
Let us chance to rain
Take all down on me
Let us know, take it
My yours, take it
Now you're late
Who's going on with me, though
Your life's much better
My yours, take it
Never try to make it right
But how long can you grow
Don't try to sing
Same old song
Never try to make it right
Still without long until you go
Never try to see it out of my head
You're always looking for a place to hide
Let us know, take it
My yours, take it
Never try to make it right
Making it right for them out of getting me wrong
Don't try to sing the same old song
Every time making advice to me how long till you go
Never try to sing it out of mind
I always love you more to play tonight
That is how we make it
Mind your taking
Minds of the street, thanks to the official music colleges of the Charlie jersey Todd
Podsafe music on the daily source code
You know if you're listening to the show in an MP3 player that recognizes album art
So for instance iTunes does that or your iPod will do that
You'll see today we have a nice picture of a naked monkey
And the reason I bring this up is twofold one is because
Bridget at the office
I don't know what she's listening to the show in
But she came to me yesterday and said oh you know that picture you put in there
That's a I could put in some picture on yesterday's show of some project or working on just like a little teaser thing
And she said oh that's the wrong version
And I said well I can't go change it now
Everyone already has the show you know just leave it be
You know send me something different you know send me a certain you different picture to put in there. It's fun
I like it when people see it's another part of the mashup that I make is the picture that goes along in the album art
And she said well what's that same to you and of course the standard answer is well naked pictures obviously
So she sent me the picture of the naked monkey
But I was thinking you know we have this new system at pod show. It's not rolled out. Yeah, but if you look across podshow dot com you'll see
Art work for almost every single podcast of the podcast doesn't have art
Then I think it gets a default like headphone head logo
But that album art is pretty much what everyone displays and it's taken from your feed from your podcast feed
And it really doesn't change that much, but I know a lot of people I do it. I know Donna Drew does it. You know they change the album art
Which is cool because when you're actually listening to the song
You know you can there's some context there
So Andrew Grummit has come up with some fabulous system
That will enable us to actually rotate the art along with what is the current picture that's in the most recent MP3 file
So what an opportunity right there
If I put a picture in then anywhere daily source code is displayed on podshow dot com
Not just when you're playing it, but anywhere it's displayed that picture will pop up as well
So I'm thinking
Yeah, you got it
Make a picture
Hi Adam is Carl again
Look I know the topic of scrunching and coding is well and true over. I just thought like you know you've actually missed out a section of people
I don't know if I'm any plastic on the planet that does this which I'm not but I represent this third party
Adam
I'm a shower
Since I was a small boy, I've never actually used toilet paper after doing my business
I simply hop off the toilet
Jumping the shower
Apply some shampoo to the hand and rub it through the bottle
This gets rid of all the mess with my thoughts
And there's just a hell of a lot easier
I don't know if I'm any person that does this, I don't care if I am
And that's kind of hygienic kind of nasty
But I just thought like you know, so I'll finish this
This will come into with shower
Do thank you
Thank you so much for the information really appreciate that
Yeah, that works but not when you live in multiple times don't you know you're not always on the same schedule
This is
Something sent to me Jeff, Jeff Hins, it's for the summer
Little D on the chart
We'll go back with her legs and tits out
Some roof down, some shades and shits on
So make them off because by November we've got them back to the windows
No, the sun will wait for
Stop with the shit to the end of April
So not complain when it's cold or too hot
Just be grateful for what you've done
Because there's nothing you can do about the weather my friends
So make the most of an unexpected hot weekend
We've been summertime, blazing, blazing, blazing
You know this is the summer of the summer
You know that we will go away
This is summer time and it's the way it goes
You know this is the summer time, summer time, summer time
Summer time, summer time
This is summer time, summer having a lot
I'm smoking weed when it's heaping over the park
I'm not leaving until the sun goes down
Or until the sun goes down
You decide to stay around, I could drown
In the amount of cider I've drawn today
He's don't matter because it's a lazy Sunday
I've got bedtime to waste and the sun's a blaze
We decided to move the party over to a late place
On the way, over there grab a couple more
Great ton of girlfriends and a few with inmates
So look you fine, two don't hire in the central page
Time we decided to get in date
And it's time to die, keep the girls occupied with
What was a wine ignite the pub
The tuning to eat something
Been drinkings in two in the afternoon
So that the sun is going down and up and see the moon
Pities over soon
But there's lots to come, every weekend
In the summer sunday sun
To the summer time, ladies and ladies
Don't praise me, you know
This is the summer time
You know that we will go
To the way and fall
This is summer time, and this is the way
It goes, you know
This is summer time, summer time
Summer time, summer time, summer time
Summer time, summer time
Go walk a first thing on the sunday
I've been loon' cause the sun's short
From a curtain to lit up my room
I roll down my pit to view the world from my window
Who's giving me inspiration for my personally single
Cleared blue skies in the mid 20s
Still on the rise, the pub began to meet my clicking
Get high, we drag slow to the park
To smoke somebody kick a moor about
Check out the fibbons, cause that's what summer's all about
Ladies walk around the town
In next nothing, showing off their plans
Cause, yeah, rules are lovely
Not as much as I love my own garden
In the summer, cause my neighbors don't stop
Isn't that too loose?
Stunner, and she's some makes toilet
Super void wet masks
To mess the only time
Over-shops like to cut the grass
When the sun shines down
Bleed your head and then relax
And make sure the volume on your get to blast
A little max, so enjoy your while you can
And open another big
Cause you only come a first and pretty summer one
See you in summer time
Ladies and days in crazy
In the summer summer time
You know that we will go
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
This is summer time
And this is the way it goes
In the summer summer time
Summer time
Well, those yellow ones
We don't know who Jeff Hintz
He doesn't know who Jeff Hintz is
He does the friday night dance party party party party party
I think his name is
He does the Friday night dance party podcast. So it was actually emails have given all the talk of the DSC about the British Summer World
The ladies show off their stuff. He just got to play summertime by little D
He's been playing it since May it was voted the theme song for summer 2006 by listeners of the Friday night dance party
I gotta say I'm chairman on very cool and I like the way it ends nice a abrupt fade out there
Did I miss something? Oh, whatever
Hey, let's time to check in with the the Troy needs an iPod dot com contest
Remember, this is an unofficial contest void wear print of a buy by law and of course
I'm the final judge and I don't give a care. I don't give rats ass what you say
I determined who's going to win the video iPod and
And I've asked you to put entries for this into the comments at daily source code dot com. Thank you
Finally people are getting it. Let me just bring up the
Oh wait a minute for this be the satellite repair man coming in with a message. I just sent an SMS text message to
To PW Fenton saying hey man, can I make a 49er for the satellite window today? I'd love to because we got like two and a half minutes left on on the satellite window
And I got so many more cool tunes to play and so much more fun stuff
I want the serious one or two listeners to be able to
participate
Let's take a look at the
Troy needs an iPod dot com. Do you remember this started out with
Troy needing an iPod trying to raise money through Troy needs an iPod dot com and then
Other one start other don't here we go. This is Peter. Let's see what he says. Oh my second
You can hear the buzz and then we get the
Yep, that would mean
crap
Okay, sorry satellite folks
You're not getting a 49er today. You're getting another minute and 41 seconds
So anyway, so this contest just started to spin out of control. I thought since we have this go daddy
Campaign running where you can get a domain name for $6.95
Sance by using checkout code dsc3
I said you know what the hey that's a that's a pretty good investment
You know why don't you register a domain name it doesn't even have to be with go daddy quite honestly
I really don't care where you register it
And let's see what the most original entries are so I'm just gonna run down the list here
This is from the buckets
What you really need is a job dot com which will soon be pointing to monster dot com. That's pretty good
This is St. Maz
Patricia support of Spammer's means she means I have Patricia's support of Spammer's means I have to use
comments to win an iPod dot com
Which points to junk email filter dot com good one I like that one
Let's see ed ed x
My dude new domain name for the contest is edwood dot com ED wUD dot com nice shorts wheat simple like it indeed
Denny 24 hours. I don't need no stink and iPod dot com okay
See the other one that he put in was I don't need no stink and iPod but Troy does dot
Com nice very very collegiate there very very friendly
Let's see oh man he got a whole bunch of dope. Who's who's this this is
Audio attitude
sent in for pod show dot com iPod for pod show plus dot com
iPod I pod show plus dot com need iPod for pod show dot com and I win an iPod atom doesn't suck dot com
Okay, okay
The iPod that launched 1000 shows dot com and that points to pod show dot com as Bob Evans
Pretty interesting how about this one this whole competition is just a desperate try to sell more domains with go daddy to please our advertisers dot com very good one
Very very very very awesome
I want Adam credit to give me an iPod, but I will accept donations from anyone dot com
He just gets better and Troy actually pipes back in with I got digged at the show and all I got was this lousy iPod dot com
How come no one's registered scruncher dot com I can't I don't understand was that taken
I know we had scruncher a folder, but okay keep sending them in sometime next week. I promise you
At this point I'm not even sure that you know one prize will
We'll do it because crap man. There's so many good entries
Enter yours at daily source code dot com. I guess sometime next week we'll we'll announce the winner and
There's certainly will be at least one prize which is the the video iPod crap crap
I was talking so much about the domains and miss the entire satellite window
ah
Yesterday I was talking about how weird it is to buy a house in the UK you know Patricia's been trying to to purchase a cottage for us
And and we have to go through this whole closed seal envelope bidding process
Which I've never never witnessed before my life and I like is this the way it works in the UK
And of course I gave out the daily source code voicemail numbers in New Jersey plus one for the US
2016256357 or our London number plus four four two zero seven six eight one three seven five three
And then I get some responses. Yes, sure. I did are they consistent? Hell no
Hi, I'm long time listener James here. I was just walking back from the under motor show
Listening to the DSC and I hear you're having problems with the UK property market
As it happens, it's by coincidence my family are buying a house on the Epsom Road moment
Which I think is just around the corner for me
Continue with the trick is research
We haven't to know that the house has been on the market for four months
Which is a long time for a property in this
After and sorry suburb and we also know that the current owners have a property. They already can move into
So because of this
All offer is 800 rather than a 50 or a 60
Which is what they're asking
But our chance is a further increase by being able to say that our house is under off and now
So the whole thing can be done and dusted if they accept
Yeah, you know actually we did try that
Patricia did say hey look we don't have anything to sell
You know we're just we can move right out of that rental and we can hand you money whenever
Told you she was there with a checkbook, so but that didn't seem to impress the vendors
Which isn't the second century because that's the thing you're selling
The old thing are these kind of values
The asking prices never the price you pay for
If it's on the market and there's lots of interest
Then you can pay out a 50,000 pounds more or if there's not been much interest and it's been on the market for a while
The same amount to be taken off
If you need any more help, I'll drop any mail. See you have my address
Thing is I'm in the area. I love the show keep up the good work. Bye all right
So it sounds like it's a pretty normal procedure. I thank you for the lesson economics
Yes, I know if there's a lot of demand then the price goes up and if there's not a lot of demand then the price probably goes down a little bit
But it sounded like they're you were talking in the age in the in the in the price range of
850,000 pounds which is like 1.7 million dollars if you can believe that
And that you could expect to pay 50,000 pounds over that price. So that is what that's like
4% am I saying that right
No
It's more than it's like
Crap six percent
Okay, so be prepared to pay that if there's a hope. I mean, how do you know if there's a whole bunch of interest
How do you know when these guys say well, you know we already have several offers in
But you know are the offers lower or higher?
This is confused. I just want to buy the house just tell me what the damn price is
I Adam it's the Adrian Pack here a lot of listener since April 2005 now
From the UK. I'm just a comment about your cottageing
Firstly the
That's not the normal way to buy a house in UK. I mean the way you describe it with a
An asking price and then making an offer which is probably the same in pretty much
Every other country is the usual way to buy most properties, but there are other ways in the UK
And I'm sure there's a
State agent's listening it can explain this better than I can but
I suppose in the end it's up to the personal selling the property. How they want to do it and how they think they're going to make the most money out of it
And the way that that's the one you're looking at
It's being sold looks like
It doesn't mean you're going to have to decide how much you're prepared to pay for it and put that video in those for the best
And you know that's the way they're going to make most money. I guess and I don't you do the same when you sell it on
That's it really from me just to say that I don't have my own podcast so I've got nothing to promote
So I'm going to promote one of the one I'm releasing to this comment is sponsored by
Let's see
clever little pod
little pod calm
Nice work. Thanks a lot. Bye
Almost perfect if I were to say what is the what is a perfect comment when you send it into the daily source code?
It is by saying who you are where you're from?
referencing what you're calling about
putting your comment in and then yes indeed
indeed promoting a
Promoting a show that you listen to
Not your own show promoting a show that you listen to he doesn't have a show which I'd like that much more
I'd love it when listeners call in the only thing you could have done to make it perfect was to wind up with
the folder scruncher
I had a big full
full of them
from one
Well, I'm a pressing lawyer
20 odd years
You know, this is why you need to write down those voicemail numbers because this is exactly what happens
You're in the car, you're on your bike, you're walking, you're in the bus, the train, whatever it is
You're listening to the show and then you hear something and you want to respond immediately and that's why
You know the mobile phone is such a fantastic device for it
So pre-program those numbers in your phone, please you can find them
Write in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
What a level nonsense
And that's actually not the way that things are usually done at all
They just don't even much more orders fashion
It's nonsense to sell bits and they've got somebody who's got the head sticking with their bears
But I don't know if something I don't know I do want to remind you
And it's a bar's market at the moment Adam unless this is something really special
I can't honestly I would hold on a second, Paul
A buyer's market. I don't think it's a buyer's market in guilt for dude
I mean houses are being snapped up left and right
I think it's definitely still a seller's market witness all the interest for this particular house and
Unfortunately, of course it's something special
You can get some great bargains at the moment you really can
Anyway, I'm a proper lawyer. I'm not one of those
Pongers, but not like Jersey Todd, you mean
South Hades is a cool conveyance
I'm a bloke that actually goes to court and gets you hamster thing
So I'm one of the real real lawyers
But if you think the
The purchase is silly you wait and see that's gets with the process you've got
Search is that you're going to do you got to work at the lamps for a whole lease hole those
Registres to tackle and register time alarm
It really is it's like some weird odd game of clues that
There we are anyway
Hope you spot too painful. See you night. Bye bye. No, everybody. Thank you very much. I appreciate it
I'm Jersey Todd. I'm just kidding man. I know you're for real. In fact, I might actually need you
I'm looking at this piece of paper here
From the building important notice dear owner slash resident
The Metropolitan Association has received numerous complaints regarding smoke slash cooking odors permanent permeating from unit to unit
Attempts by Howard S. Wright to diagnose this problem have been unsuccessful
The association is keeping a running log of all smoke slash odor related incidents
We hope to identify all affected units and possibly and possible causes of this problem
to report an incident police in the near mail to smoke smell reporting at yahoo.com
Oh shit. I shouldn't have told you that
I wonder if it's really just are they smelling cooking smells or you don't you don't think it could be
It could be anything else now. Do you
I have a question for you about biodiesel a couple of weeks ago. I discovered a biodiesel gas station
Just three miles from my house. I'm so excited
We drive a diesel VW. So of course I wanted to check it out. I've been filling up there ever since
It bucks me though that it's only be 20 20 percent bio and 80 percent petroleum
20 percent is better than nothing of course, but why is it at a hundred percent? I know you've done the research
So I'm hoping you could explain it. Thank you, pod father. Oh, Kelly. Oh, I love it when you say pod father. Thank you, pod father
She says that in my dreams, too
Cali normally I would have rolled out the Trinity theme tune, but I forgot
So a good question. Yeah, there is a difference between what Trinity is running on and what you're putting into your brand new diesel by the way
I commend you. That's fantastic
And of course B20 is a good start and an exactly what it is. It's 20 percent vegetable oil and 80 percent petroleum-based diesel oil
And the reason for that is really just the production
It's you know, we don't have huge facilities cranking out gallons and gallons of the shit by the second so
You know, it's really the I think that there's also the supply may be you know that the raw materials because you know
Basically the stuff that that I get here in San Francisco, you know, it's literally collected from restaurants and it's all you know
It's vegetable oil is being thrown out that was you know cooking oil essentially it goes through a fairly simple process before you can put it into your tank
And the bio fuel OASIS does that in in was they in in Berkeley and
You know, so the best thing to do would be to set something up
With some of the other diesel drivers in the neighborhood and you know set up a little community
I think this is you know, it's so hard to create massive quantities of anything and that's why refineries
You know there are refineries now being built around the world that will cost anywhere from four to eight billion dollars
I mean this refinery business is not trivial for to eight billion dollars and it's usually not owned by
By you know by one oil company, but multiple oil companies because of the expense it's so incredibly large
Now of course they're making so much profit. What did what was the profit
Announcement yesterday ten billion dollars for one company the second highest every in the history of oil companies
You know, so that's that's that's pretty astounding
So I would recommend that you know if you're really into it and and you really want to mess around with it
You get one of these kits, you know for like a thousand bucks or fifteen hundred bucks and you can go around to the
You know your local Chinese restaurant twice a week and you could fill up a
You could drive for a month
With five cars on that amount depending on how big the Chinese restaurant is of course
So that's really the difference Cali and and that is the groupy thing about biodiesel is even if you're running on 100% biodiesel and you're running to a jam
You can pretty much throw anything in there and it'll work and this is what the diesel engine was designed for wasn't designed for patrolling and base stuff
hey wait a minute um Cali was on
MSNBC yesterday wasn't she yeah hold on a second let me
Shoot let me see if I can bring up she said she was gonna put it on the show
Let me bring up geek brief for a second let's see if we can see how she did on MSNBC
I know that the show she was on was going to be with Allison Stewart which is really fun because Allison Stewart used to be a
Associate producer at MTV which basically means you have a producer and the producer would stand next to the VJ
While you were doing segments and would make sure of course that everything is you know that you're announcing the right video and
With my producers we'd always go through what I was gonna say and we'd prep it a day ahead of time and the Associate producer is
Kind of well at MTV in the day you were certainly more a go for than anything else
But then she slowly moved over into the news department where I think she was very well suited and before you knew it
She was on air and she was doing MTV news
I did a couple of a couple of shows with her the weekend rock. I did that a few times with a lovely girl
And very very proud of what she's done her careers just moved into well
G the big leagues
Doesn't mean that she completely understands what we're doing
But hopefully canlly did a good job of explaining. Let's let's check in. Let's see. Oh shoot hold on
I'm not hearing this
Something must be wrong hold on
crap. Why is this not working?
Oh, man
Play
Shoot hold on a second. Oh, you know what happened fire fight. This is the new fire fox
Just crashed. Let's see if I can get rid of this all right you know what I'll do I'll wait for that to
I'll wait for fire fox to restart and I'll play this in the meantime
Hi, this is Lockjaw host of the podcast junkie show
If you're as tired as I am of all the crap to corporate media giants are trying to force me to you on the radio
Head on over to the podcast junkie.com
Were you here music come independent artists over view of other podcasts and whatever else I feel like throwing your way
Join the revolution today with Lockjaw the podcast junkie
Music by all my fault so they're available on the podcast music network
Okay, so I think I figured it out what happened was fire foxed one of those automatic updates
Which I really don't like it. I'm sure there's a setting forward, but it's I feel it's so wrong
When when software does that, you know because there's so many things that you know that can happen in the background
Why is my computer slow? Why is it not running you know why did I see the disc light going on?
It turns out that fire fox is saying they're downloading everything in the background and and then you know halfway through
Well, I had everything all queued up everything all teed up then it wants to restart fire fox. You know this is not this is not the this is not good
Okay, so I've fired it back up. I got into my channels. I went to my
My tech video channel which you can also access by the way if you go to atom.podshow.com and
Let's see there we go. Okay, so we got Callie. So this is from yesterday's MSNBC
And I had not looked at this so well hopefully it'll be fun to kind of listen to it together and see if that works. Here we go
It is one of the most popular forms of new media and it's called podcasting think of it as
Portable entertainment and information on demand and podcast well they can be created by anyone
honest Callie Lewis gets more than six million hits per month on her program
Geek brief TV hit the video podcast download all about technology so who better to ask about the basics of
podcasting and Callie just for the record there there are two types of podcasts, right?
Yeah, there's good ones in bad ones audio or you can do video just like radio or TV
All right, you say you can just do them
How do you just do them?
So for a simple it really is and it's very inexpensive
For audio all you need is a computer a microphone some headphones and some
Recording software for audio what I would suggest is to use cast-blaths
Callie go Callie
And has everything you need to be able to publish a show and Geek brief TV is actually a video podcast
Oh, you got to look at this. She looks so cute. She's a via via remote
Looks like she's coming in from is that the Dallas studio
And so the the caption on the screen read podcasting offers portable news and entertainment on demand and we use an application called video Q Pro
Again, it's super simple. It has everything we need it has a teleprompter we can do green screen effects
We can put title graphics. I think you fancy TV people call it what?
Cairon, there you go
And they're doing a split screen
Well, we started December 23rd which was what six months ago seven months ago and we the first time we heard a podcast
We knew we had to do one because it was so addictive and so compelling
So we just started and we had no video production experience at all. We don't know what the heck we were doing
So we just started to see what we could do and
Within three months or three weeks. You know, it's interesting because that is true when they first started out
They really were just trying to do whatever they could do
Cali and and the invisible kneel
And now that they've actually quit their day job and are doing it full time the quality
Predominantly forget this the quality of of the video and the editing and the green screen and and all the stuff they're doing
But the editorial is great and and they're getting all kinds of great gadgets. I mean really I think
This is you know that between the stories they're doing they have a great mix between
Yeah, I'd have to say between a gadget and rocket boom and of course Holly beat
Cali be much hotter than
Anybody on either of those shows
Actually we had 3,000 viewers we were getting shut down by our hosting company because
We exceeded our bandwidth limit and then we saved you. I pleaded to a company called pods
Yes, help me back from running and this is my big question to you
This is my big question
Is Adam Curry really a big-haired fag?
Right after I make my podcast my audio or video one how do I get it out to the world?
Oh, well, I is a
Website called pod showed up
And they made very easy to
To do it without understanding any of the technology behind it which has been the hardest part for the past two years
Because you had to understand the technology but now you don't all you have to do is sign up
All right, so go to geek brief
Geek brief TV. I'll put a link in the show notes and go check out the entire interview
That's pretty cool the the funniest thing about all this is you know here. I am playing all this for you this
This stuff from MSNBC and in in all reality. I think more people are
Listening or more people are watching Cali show around the globe then actually will ever see
For see that interview. I had a miss pool park incident from podcast user magazine in the flashing 12 podcast
Adam I'm running an ask on the reverse engineers this month in the August edition which comes out on the first of August
But I'm also trying to run one on black lab and I'm catching up on some DSCs
I've been away for a couple of weeks on business and I heard that you're meeting up with a guy some black lab on Friday in the office
And could you ask them to get in touch with me? I've left them a number of messages at
Contacts at blacklabworld.com
But I've not heard anything back from them. So if you give them a nods. I'd really appreciate it love what you're doing on the
DSC I've got a ton of things about
Brits the anchors is the great so I'll do a proper all year coming on that
So look forward to seeing you sometime. Thanks a lot keep up the good work. Cheers night. Bye bye. Sure Paul
Well in that interesting so yeah, I actually had I almost forgotten that today we
During our food bar Friday, which is a tradition at Pod Show around
Was it four o'clock five o'clock and you have to knew we just stopped work and and then there's always a presentation or something fun going on and today indeed
We will
We'll have an acoustic set. I'm not sure if if I'm not exactly sure who's coming but let's just say an acoustic black lab set
And yeah, of course, I'll put it in a nudge for you there Paul
But if you left contact numbers everywhere and it's about an interview you know and someone ignores you
Maybe it's because they don't want to be interviewed. Hey Adam. This is Neil from the pod safe revolution podcast
Now Jersey Todd's the official musicologist of your show. I'm sticking my claim right now is the official pod safe
Revolutionary of the Charlie
There's a band coming at a new jersey called the new London fire
Their debut albums currently only available for pre-order. It's not actually hitting the streets until the 8th of August
But I haven't talking with their label now for over two months and yeah, you guessed it these guys are part of our revolution
These guys are now officially pod safe
And not only a pod guest who's getting the single before the albums released we're getting it before radio gets it
Yeah, it's gonna be up on the pod safe music network tomorrow
But I just wanted to make sure that when these guys blow up people are gonna be able to save
They hurt at first on a daily source code
Cheers man have a good Friday and a folder scruncher. No, okay. I do thank you so much
It's interesting because
Mark Yoshimoto Namcoff also gave me a link to this song saying this was you know the new black lab part project
Shit man. This shows recorded way too early for me to understand everything
But it does kick ass
On the podcast before the radio
Was she can't confess
The dogs are left to mind
Sometimes
Never find their way
She just
Time to save
There's a way for me today
Things will not be dead for now
They will not leave the way
To some other space
Things will not be dead for now
She's just the god of the lack of ghost
No worse thing
She could have her hair
Yes, I think I love you
Let's just take in love for clothes
Someday you have to find her home
She just time to save
There's a way for me today
Things will not be dead for now
They will not leave the way
To some other space
Things will not be dead for now
What's come? It's awfully touch your smile
They make it there
Way into the space
Where the dead out of place
Don't believe me, I've tried
I'm resting for a while
I will look for you again
Someday you have to find the home
Where you go
She just starts to save
There's a way for me today
Things will not be dead for now
They will not leave the way
To some other space
Things will not be dead for now
I don't care whether it's Black Lab, New London Fire
And Som is great
Different
Winding up
Thank god it's fried edition of the daily source code
Last show from
The curry condo cannot wait to get back home
I miss my girl so much and
Sometime in the next two weeks when we're back home
We're going to go to Disneyland, the Euro Disney
We had of course to
Postpone our plans because now in the middle of this auction for a home
You know, I don't want to have to leave town when you're in the middle of the auction
Okay, I before I go one more I want to come out. I want to play for you because I thought I was a really good question
I did manage to I actually I don't know if I did all this I hope they are didn't
I have a quick question
Really regarding
e-business
How does how does someone like
YouTube with there knows it's quote you from DSC whichever one I'm listening to from many Monday
YouTube 100 million video views a day 100 million that's one hell of a lot of anguish that the hell of a lot of information being passed back and forth
So about it you know what candle is a shit hole and it's all very noisy
100 million at day and a hell of a night money. I mean seriously. It can't be banner ads
How does that work?
Tell me
You are the parts are that you've got an ugly face anyway
Thank you and yes, Camden is a shit hole. Let me just take a take note of that. Let me just write that down
Memo to self do not be as a Camden
Okay, so I thought that was a really good question to take us into the weekend
First of all, uh, YouTube runs on the same physical network infrastructure at the podcast delivery network runs on so I
Know what what the theoretical cost would be and I and I know that is a kick ass network
So yeah, and you know obviously if the number of a hundred million videos per day is true
That is a huge amount but I don't think so these guys have investors behind them
In fact, uh one of their investors also invested in pod show so not that I know anything more about them than I do now, but
Or than I wouldn't that I would know if I if they weren't investors because
Shit, I have to go beat the information out of him, but it's not so much about
You know how they're gonna make money because there's all kinds of issues
You know, there's all the copyrighted material which of course what YouTube is used for a lot
They're not really providing
They're not providing 100 million
unique visits to their website because these videos are viral so it is all coming off their server
So they have some limited ways that they can monetize by putting an ad into the actual video itself
Of course is one way and you they like revert as you could click on it and then you could play it on a click through
Basis, but that's still no way you're gonna get anywhere near Google numbers for a long time because there's just you know
There's billions of web pages that are being accessed today with Google Adsense or something comparable
And a hundred million just really does not cut it when it comes to that type of advertising on the other hand
If you look at how podcasts are done, they're serialized and and people
Have an audience, you know, it's it's not just one video that gets passed around but there's an audience around a show
And that show could consist of videos being passed around in fact be on a lookout for video junky
But it's very hard to build up a relationship with you know or or even look at the relationship between the producer of that video
And the audience because it's pretty much you know the the producer is the person who sent it to you
That's almost the way it feels like
But that's not what YouTube is that's not why YouTube is so exciting what YouTube is doing is they are proving that
People are willing to
Get their video entertainment elsewhere. They are taking their eyes away from traditional television from the box and even though it may be the same stuff
That they're looking at YouTube
It is a different venue and that's what so
I can't last
All right everybody. I am on my way home next time you hear from me. I'll be back with the lady Patricia and the pod princess
Pod save the queen which of course will have a new episode out on Monday or on Tuesday since vacation
We should be able to do it the minute I get back home
Thanks so much for pulling me through and I will talk to you on Monday. Bye everybody
Get this pod cast and more great ones like you on the high performance pod cast delivery network from pod show and lime light networks