In just days, Podshow will unleash the all-new Podshow-plus network with all new features and functionality designed from feedback provided directly from you.
From you, the audience, the audience, Podshow.com.
Change the world, win valuable prizes.
I'm getting ready for my addition on the new Podshow video show, Port City PD.
A pop show?
You want to be on a pop show?
Yep.
Have you seen a pearl?
The story?
The acting?
The sound effects?
It's amazing!
I'm trying out to be on the new show for as you know Pearl.
I'm the wave of go-for destruction.
You think it's appropriate for a go-for from bedtime stories?
My kids love to want to be on Port City PD.
Pearl?
If it offended, then don't watch.
But for right now, check out my Judo Kick.
Yeah!
Happy, just introduce the show.
Sure.
Delta's Sierra Charlie.
Four.
Nine.
Three.
With fifteen bags, the spring has stuck in our pants.
Sugar?
And fifteen bags of toilet paper hanging from our cracks?
We don't need no speaking sugar.
I'd like to think I'm right.
For the future.
Podshow is scary.
Sometimes an atom's all alone.
He needs his love right there on the microphone.
So here she is, yes, the lady Patricia.
The same two heads are better than one.
And with this angel from above,
There's nothing that they both can't do.
A make you wild as dreams come true.
So grab your earbuds and jam them in.
And let the fabulous show begin.
It's Adam and Patricia.
Yes, Adam and Patricia.
Adam and the lady Patricia.
She slept a car and she said she's caught and played in.
To make them move from here.
This time it wasn't as if she was complaining.
This time it wasn't for me.
He tried to come and save her down.
He tried to convince her she was wrong.
She said I think you'll never understand.
Let it go.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry now.
Let it get to go.
I'm not out.
She screamed at him that she so tired of breathing.
For anything in life.
I'm not having fun there.
I'm barely frustrated.
It comes just like a nap.
She had it up and she felt that things were changing.
Comments that she was right.
She thought no question no doubt.
And now I'm sure.
Let it get to go.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry now.
Let it get to go.
I'm not out.
I'm sorry now.
Let it get to go.
I'm not out.
Girl stuff.
You didn't like it?
I don't like it.
You think of that girl with the glasses on Lisa.
Lisa Lopez.
You're not a real podcaster man.
You're not a singer anymore.
You don't want to sing anymore.
It's a baby source code for nine or three coming to you from the current curry cottage.
Soon to be the former curry cottage.
I'm going to call the new place the curry cottage.
I have no idea.
It's a little too big maybe to be qualified as a.
It's your perfect it is.
Yeah.
That's what everybody says.
Picture perfect.
What?
I don't know.
Anyway.
To guess where they're from.
Breakhouse.
Guess where the girl that you just heard is from.
That's what I want to ask.
Okay.
Where's she from?
Yeah.
You'll never guess.
Germany.
Well, I'll close actually.
Switzerland.
Oh.
Yeah.
This is this is a bunch of producers out there called ninety nine productions.
Ninety nine ninety nine red balloons.
Four doxions.
Yeah.
Inc.
And.
What they do is they have their own studio.
And then if they find someone who's talented, then they just do a do a record with them.
And then try and try and make it.
Make it happen.
Yeah.
So they got a whole bunch of stuff on the fun.
I like it.
And I kind of like that song.
A little bit of the.
Very good.
I don't know.
It sounded already like a hit.
Like do I know this song?
I think I already know this song.
And that's good.
That's what they did with her home.
Will that work?
Fuck.
I don't know.
How exciting is that?
Yes.
I don't know why isn't it working.
And you know why it's Adam?
Yes Patricia.
They want to know in England.
People will come into the country.
Yes.
It's not work.
They want to know the skills that people would bring to this country.
Oh.
This.
This is.
I'm not working here.
I'm just living here.
I get I get paid in America.
Okay.
I don't do any work here.
The only thing I've done here is I speed.
Yeah.
I speed too much with.
But in the future, they're going to see, you know, who immigrates to this country.
They're going to be very strict with that.
And see if they can can bring a new skill.
Now, you know, you're just see, I don't think it's for anybody.
I think it's only for Romania and Bulgaria.
That's what I just said.
I'm new.
Who's they?
The news.
What news?
Oh, and to BBC owned by the government.
Well, I think it's very good to look.
You know, I do.
I'm just saying, I don't know how to bring.
I don't know how true that is is what I'm saying.
I don't think it's a correct.
Uh, report.
It's really correct.
They can't do that.
You can't be part of the European Union and then say,
But no one else can come in here.
You can't do that.
That's like, that's like New Jersey saying,
If you're New York, I'm sorry.
You can't come in.
Well, that's not what they're saying.
To just say, can you bring something?
Is it something?
Can you add something to this country?
Well, you're just going to.
Just leech off of the system like you and I.
Absolutely not.
We we spend the money.
Look, they may make a tougher.
That's true.
Yeah, that's good.
But they can't stop anyone from coming in.
They just can't.
That's not what they're saying.
Anyone who wants to come here and has no job.
You're fucking crazy.
It's so expensive here.
Yeah.
You will die.
You will die of starvation.
It is very, very, very expensive here.
Yeah.
Don't do it.
I think that's, you know, keep the pound in.
Keep the prices high.
Keep all the riff rap out.
Yeah.
If you're not here for shopping.
That's what I was saying.
Are you working here, sir?
No.
I'm spending.
We're just shopping.
That's all we're doing.
Did you see their faces?
It's always okay.
Well, yeah.
Welcome.
How are you doing?
Oh, that's good.
Then welcome.
Good morning.
How are you?
Tata.
Yeah.
All right.
So we've missed you on the show, huh?
Oh, did you?
Yeah.
So busy.
No.
Every single time I've done a show, you were too busy.
And I was busy too without a staff.
Sure.
Because you are so busy.
I have to do the other stuff.
In fact, just before we started the show, I got a phone call.
Which delayed the start of the, you want to know what that was?
We launched BT Pod Show.com.
So yesterday, we, or we unleashed, we unleashed the new Pod Show Plus.
Yeah.
And now we have the English version, the UK version, English, the UK version at BT Pod Show.com.
And so this morning, the chairman of BT, the Dutch guy, Ben Provine, was on the BBC
Breakfast.
Which, of course, I missed.
I didn't see it.
I didn't know.
And it was talking about it.
If anyone recorded that, I'd love to see it.
I went to the BBC, he's like, what is it?
They have a podcast service, but they don't actually.
They're not using it very much.
They show you the highlights of the news.
I want to see the whole program, you know?
Like, let me just scroll through that.
So they're freaking out because they found some questionable content on the show at BT Headquarters.
Really?
Yeah.
And so, you know, I'm not in the censorship at all.
It's, you know, I think everything goes.
Within, you know, within some, like, we don't want pornography on our site as an example.
That's, you know, we don't want, and forget about whether it's legal, illegal.
I'm just not interested, you know, go somewhere else for that.
I'll send you some good links if you want, so.
So then there's this show.
It's, it was a called sneeze wart.
And I'm like, oh, this is a, you know, it's a very questionable podcast.
And I'm looking through all these episodes.
Like, there's some, some girl, you know, dancing sexy.
What a close-on, even.
I can't believe this.
Yeah.
What is, this can't really be true.
I don't understand that.
Come over here, because I found the episode they're talking about.
You remember Leah from Big Brother?
Yeah.
You're going to have to come over here, huh?
Because I can't turn them on over.
Do you have your glasses?
Yeah.
Let me see if I can see it.
Oh, I can see it.
Okay.
There you go.
You can see it.
So the show, by the time you hear this podcast, this episode will be gone.
So you don't, don't, don't go looking for it.
Yeah.
This is Leah from Big Brother.
Oh, I'm going to give you some audio here.
Do I have sound with this?
Sneeze word.
Let's see.
I hope I have audio.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, but that's what she was talking about.
She didn't do any more, and she was actually a shame doll.
Dude, she has to do it.
I don't know if it's new, but after seeing this.
Looks very new.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Well, yeah.
Hello.
Oh, my God.
But now, but you're saying it's a hot porno.
I have to say it's a porno.
Yeah, it's hot.
The day before yesterday.
Yes.
I was upstairs, you know, cleaning my face.
And I always do, you know, put just like Leah got her face clean right there.
She needs.
I was in my bedroom, and I always switch a TV on, you know, for, you know, just to get in the mood for sleeping.
Yeah.
So, and I had it switch on BBC 4.
Mm-hmm.
Well, they had sort of a sex show there, but it was telling people, you know,
yeah, it was more teaching people about sex, about what happens, you know, because
Well, then it's educational, then it's okay.
It's educational.
Yeah.
You have no idea.
It was beyond porno.
But wait a minute.
Were they, was horrible?
Were they really?
Yes.
Were they showing fully erecting?
Everything.
Full erecting.
Close up.
Yeah.
Because that's actually illegal.
What do you think is?
Where the, the combos.
Oh, God.
It was seemingly.
He was coming out.
The guy was coming.
So, he was, but close up ejaculating.
Yes.
Thank you.
There you go.
My dear.
And he was close up.
Because that's, hold on a second.
That's the point out of it.
That's the difference.
If you say coming versus ejaculating, that's the difference.
That's the difference right there.
Well, you know.
Yeah.
So, did it turn you on?
No.
Well, I mean, you know, then it's, it's okay.
Hmm.
Well, all I know is, there's two things.
It was.
Let me answer.
Gosh, you never let me answer the question.
I wasn't done.
Educational.
Yes.
That's what it was.
There are two things.
In the UK as far as I know, you're not allowed to show a fully erect penis on television.
Yeah.
I don't know why.
I don't know the problem is, but that's not loud.
I don't care about that.
The problem here is that's, that's a stolen video.
That's someone.
That's a, that's a, that's a part of a movie.
That's copyright.
So, that has to come off.
That's the real problem.
Yeah, that's the problem.
So, but, but I don't think it's the, I think we've, we've all seen it now.
You know, we've all seen it by.
Are we still surprised?
I think so.
We are.
Yeah.
I've seen so much.
Especially on the internet.
I mean.
Are you really?
Is that what you're doing on your computer these days?
Show me.
You're showing me.
This is awesome.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, what we're going to talk about.
We had so many things that we've ever since I got back.
We said, yeah, we'll talk about this.
We'll talk.
Oh, um.
Well, first of all.
Yes.
You're not in a good mood.
What do you mean?
I'm not in a good mood.
Well, I know to the, you are very tense.
Well, downstairs.
You just accused me of fucking up five years of our life.
Huh?
Just before the show.
Oh, in Holland.
Yeah.
You, you, you tagged me.
You always tagged me because I'm Dutch.
No.
I just said.
Yes, I do.
You're right.
Yeah.
So, that's why you say, why do you want to be there then?
You know, I didn't want, I don't want to be there.
Oh, but then you wanted to be there because you, you thought you had something going there.
And you wanted to stay there for what?
Right.
But you attacked me.
So, and so that's why I'm not in a good mood.
Yeah.
So, don't attack the Dutch, okay?
No.
I am attacking the Dutch.
I'm not talking about that you are in a bad mood now.
You are in a bad mood the last couple of days.
Not in a bad mood.
I'm busy.
Yeah.
You're very busy.
Right now, you're putting me in a bad mood by saying this.
Why?
Well, because I'm not in a bad mood.
Throw it out.
Come on.
I'm busy.
I'm fucking busy.
That's what I mean.
And when you are busy, you are so focused.
Yeah.
Because that's what you always are.
You're very focused on what you're doing.
There's no space for anything.
But listen, I'm 42, which I consider to be pretty old.
You know, compared, I remember when my dad was 40.
I'm like, dude, you're fucking old.
Yeah.
And we're really trying to build something here.
And now is the time to make it happen.
I know.
And I'm tired.
I travel around the globe.
But what?
It's amazing what you guys are doing.
I think it's wonderful.
Yeah.
We haven't even had time to enjoy it.
We've been working.
Yeah.
So.
I'm very proud of you.
And you know, Christine and I do understand it.
And it mean, well, we shop.
Yeah.
You never hear me about that, dude.
You never hear me.
I'm never grumpy.
I'm just joking.
Never ever.
No, no.
There you are.
Yeah.
I knew Luke.
What do you mean?
That's cheap.
So, do you know how many people can afford new look either?
Oh.
You know, you guys are fortunate.
I know.
Just to you.
So, you got complaints?
Uh, sex.
You've had sex for me.
I've given you sex.
As by the time I go to bed, you're already asleep.
True.
Yeah.
Or see, here's something.
You know, Patricia doesn't like to have sex when the teenagers awake.
No.
Turns me off.
Yeah.
Okay.
But I know that she's still, you know, with a door open and everything.
I don't like that.
Okay. Well, so does that limit your choices?
When do you, you can have sex or not?
I always with children.
So, but so, please don't say that it's my fault.
Yeah.
But she's sleeping over sometimes.
But let me tell you.
She knows exactly what's going on.
The minute you close that door, click the big fucking lock goes on.
You think she doesn't know?
Are you really kidding yourself?
Do you think that she isn't having sex?
Oh, I don't want to know that.
Yeah.
Exactly.
She doesn't want to know it.
I don't want to know it.
Yeah, but of course I know it.
Yeah.
Well, there you go.
Okay.
So, what's going on with all these people?
Well, excuse me, before you move on.
Are you sexually satisfied in our relationship or not?
Because people are wondering about this now.
No.
Yes, I am, my darling.
Be honest, if you're not, you know, just let me, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, lots of people would,
would happy to come by and help you out.
I'm sure.
Well, talking about that.
Uh-oh.
I'm going to do.
Do you tell them yet?
No, I was sworn to secrecy.
All right.
All right. All right.
Well, I'm busy changing the world, winning valuable prizes.
You know, don't have time to sexually satisfy my partner.
You decide to make it even busier and go do something yourself.
Well, I do have a crazy guy in my arms in the future.
Because I'm going to do a strictly condensing in Holland.
Yeah, in Holland.
In Holland.
And that is dancing with this.
This is the stars.
So, let me ask you, Miss Pai.
Yeah.
Since you won't change your last name to mine.
Why did you decide to do this?
Why are you going to go to Holland?
Well, you know it.
To do a television program.
I'm not doing for the attention, because I don't like that, actually.
And I don't need it.
Then why are you doing it?
Well, I had sort of going from summer to the winter,
and having a lot of things on my mind,
and being busy with trying to find a house and all these things,
and disappointments and days, and that, and falling through.
I was...
Your life is so horrible, isn't it?
Oh, no, no.
I was a little bit in a dip.
I didn't feel well.
My body didn't feel good.
There was no energy left,
and you went to America.
My parents were here, which was a lot of fun.
And the people of that program were calling me.
And my mom was in the standing next to me,
who heard the conversation.
This is when I was in the San Francisco.
Yes, and you were in San Francisco,
and they were asked me if I was interested to do that.
And I said, well, I have to think about it,
and I'll call you back.
And my mom starts to jump up and down.
Oh, you have to do it.
It's such good.
We enjoy it.
And everybody's watching it in Holland.
And they think you can do it.
And it's good for you.
And I said, well, you know,
I love dancing, though.
You know, I don't want to sing,
but dancing, I always wanted to dance.
Although I've never did it before.
Well, dance, ballroom dancing, nothing.
You know, not with a partner.
So I thought, you know, maybe it's good.
Maybe it's good to challenge my body.
You know, because I'm not a very healthy woman.
And see what I can do.
And give me a boost.
You're very healthy woman.
What are you talking about?
Well, my heart is not.
You know, and sometimes you're afraid of your heart.
Because you don't know what you can do.
How far you can, you know, push it.
You're always, it's always hanging above your head.
You know, and for this, I'm very healthy.
And my muscles are okay.
And I thought, maybe I'll do it for myself.
And see what I can do.
And maybe it gives me a boost.
And then, um, I think it gives you a boost.
Then why?
After that.
No, well, after that.
You think, wow, you know, I can do that too.
And it gives me good feeling.
Yes.
But that's why I'm doing it.
I totally.
So I had one rehearsal this week.
And I heard that was a couple of very good guys.
Well, hold on.
First tell me.
So yeah, tell me about your dance partner.
Because don't you get a professional, though.
Yeah.
So my, I told my sister, Ivan, who was, was always watching that.
Who was a professional tango dancer herself?
Not at all.
But she said, oh, that two guys were really good looking.
Very, very good.
They're sensational.
They've got a lot of passion in them.
You should have one of them.
So I had a request.
And I said, you know, my, my family says it.
I have to choose this one.
You were about to say, my husband has given me enough sex.
So could I have that Remco guy?
That's, that's what I thought you were going to say.
No.
And so, and I got the one that I want.
I got the one that I want.
And I had to make my arms this week.
Yeah.
My got 28 years old.
Mm-hmm.
And how do you go?
It went very well.
I try to make me jealous, because I'm not bothered.
I'm not bothered.
Face, I'm not bothered.
Face is not.
Pain is not bothered.
Pain is, look, pain is, my pain is face.
I'm not bothered.
Oh, God.
Walling out of your crook.
Yeah.
Of my crook.
It's a stool.
Yeah, I know.
No, that.
So, um, no, I'm not making it.
Because we're not jealous.
We're not jealous.
You like it.
You always say it's good for you.
I haven't seen it.
Good for you.
Yeah, good for you.
No, I'm very happy.
Yeah.
It's just that it adds so much planning, planning,
dimension, because you want me to do it.
Yeah, right now.
To stop everything and start flying you around.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
I'll just like you when you're going.
You know, there's so many things.
Yeah.
But that's me going.
It's a go on.
That's a big difference between me going.
And you really.
And I know when mommy is going.
Yeah.
And the hardest thing is that, you know, you want.
You want to have another pilot with you.
And that's the hardest thing is to find another pilot during the week,
because most of them work.
Yeah.
So, I think if you just take your chances with me.
I didn't do it.
Yeah.
So, now it's going to be fun.
It's harder than I thought, actually.
Now, what dances do you have to do?
I have to do a waltz.
That's a waltz, isn't it?
It's for Christmas show and a new year show.
So, it's not as long as it's.
Well, no, no, it's silent night.
Yeah.
They're making a waltz.
It sounds like a bit disappointed about it.
It's very old fashioned.
Well, why don't you tell me when I'm going to the song?
I think I'm going to talk about it.
Well, it's Christmas.
So, I know that maybe that that show will be a little bit more Christmasy.
But I have to talk about that other show.
And the other one is sort of...
Here's what you do.
You say, I've got a great idea for a song.
I'd like to do a waltz, too.
I have a pot safer piece.
One, two, three.
Yeah, it is.
You can do a waltz.
One, two, three.
Yeah, it is.
You can do a waltz.
One, two, three.
No, no, no.
Okay.
All right.
So, I hope that finds me something else because it's a bit...
Silent night sounds dreary.
Well, Silent night, okay.
But then the other one is South American.
It's very nice.
It's...
But still, it's...
How about your...
My mum...
You love it?
And I think I forgot that.
Can't you do mumbo eetleano?
That's a mumbo.
This is...
I think this is a zember.
Who gives a shit?
My mumbo's zember.
Who cares?
You think the audience care?
You don't even know the difference between a mumbo...
A mumbo, a mumbo...
But do you know what I mean?
I mean, this is crazy.
Do I have...
Do I have mumbo?
I don't have mumbo.
You think...
Hmm...
Not here.
Yeah.
But you know what I'm saying?
It's like...
Who gives a shit?
Whether it's a mumbo or a somber?
And they'll be your song.
They'll be kind of cool.
No, they don't do that.
Because there's a big orchestra there.
It's playing live.
Yeah.
Just...
I mean, exactly the way they do it here.
They have to do it.
Do it.
Yeah.
I have no idea what it is.
That's right.
You're talking about it.
Your pass I do it was really lovely.
I said do it.
Well, I told them that you want to do it too.
You want to try it.
No, that's not true.
That's...
You always say when you're sitting on the couch.
No.
I can do that.
I can.
But I'm only going to do it for Bruce Forsyte.
I'm not going to do it for a Roman Brown stator.
I'm sorry.
I'm not going to invite you here.
Not yet.
That's right.
I'm not going to accept the invitation.
I will not.
Nothing.
I will...
I will have nothing more to do with Dutch media.
Done.
Especially those fuckers.
I don't...
I haven't forgotten RTL4 cock suckers.
Yeah.
Enjoy your show.
But...
That guy's already gone.
Yeah.
There are already other people sitting there.
Yeah, but you know what I mean.
Yeah.
You know what I mean.
It's just the whole general thing.
I know.
I know how you think.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm not angry.
It's done.
Mm-hmm.
Do you want to mean?
Yeah.
Well, I will probably...
We'll never be done because I'm Dutch.
Yeah.
And you...
Never be Dutch.
But you know, you will...
You want to become English.
I'm getting your British passport.
Uh-huh.
When you were British passport, then you're done.
Then they probably want to ask me for...
For strictly condensing.
Well, let me do a commercial.
I'm going to go on a second.
Ten lessons.
I've learned a lot surfing internet.
Number one.
Entering your email address on some websites is an open invitation to spam.
Number two.
Before forwarding an email about the ghost of a dead boy appearing in the theatrical film.
Three men in a baby.
Check Snopes.com.
First.
Number three.
Spyware.
Then forms you that you have spyware.
There's not very helpful.
Number four.
The FBI will never send you an email warning about your visiting 40 illegal websites.
They'll simply bust down your door.
Never, ever, Google the Toronto-based quartet.
The Bare Nicoladies on a computer at work.
Number six.
And Microsoft are not tracking this email.
And forwarding it to 15 other people will not get Walt Disney signed to send you free passes to Walt Disney World.
There is no such thing as a national do not email registry.
Number eight.
There is no ousted prints in Bangladesh willing to share $15 million with you.
Closing one porn pop-up window opens 15 more.
And number ten.
I think as your service provider will solve most of these problems.
Unfortunately, the remaining few will take some common sense.
I've got to get your EarthLink email service.
So you actually were interested in the pills that were you got spam with like, what was that again?
Like some...
The Xanx.
It's a fucking drug.
They're sending me those.
Yeah, it's called spam.
Yeah.
You would actually save one.
You're like, oh, that's interesting.
That's cheap.
It's nice for drugs.
Yeah, but that's not good, man.
You don't know what you know.
No, that's what they say.
Of course.
You never know who makes them.
Yeah.
Or if it's even what it says it is.
Maybe it's not.
Give me an update on Paul McCartney.
Because while I was gone, shit really hit the fan, didn't it?
Oh my god.
It's nasty.
And why...
How does it come that people when they divorce?
It's such a mess.
Can they just divorce?
No, that's the press, huh?
It's the press.
Of course they can.
This is the press is having the game.
Remember, Heather?
Yeah, but if there's nothing going on there,
and they're not angry with each other.
And they can do anything depressed, you know?
Well, first of all, they're in a divorce.
So they're not happy with each other.
There's just no two ways.
I don't care who's breaking up for what reason.
Yeah.
That's just a fact.
So you're never going to get someone smiling.
Oh, I'm so happy because they're just not.
Okay.
Sometimes who's ever so happy.
You want to do it.
No.
Give me one example.
Thank you.
You don't have one.
Very, very quiet.
Dude, do I have to go get the fucking magazines about that?
No.
Do you want me to get the magazines?
I don't have them, but it sounds good threatening that.
Well, because you were there.
Well, of course.
No, no, no.
You made it worse.
There you go.
That's where all the problems started.
20 years ago, I was there.
Yeah, but the divorce went very quickly.
Very good.
Yeah.
Nobody wanted anything.
And Baba.
Yeah, but you also didn't divorce a guy who's a billionaire.
Okay.
It doesn't matter.
That's not the same.
That's calm.
That happens.
That's nothing.
And by the way, Paul McCartney is like royalty.
I know.
Sir Paul is, you don't mess with Sir Paul.
We'll see.
So it is the press that is make.
This is what the press does, huh?
Whether it's about you or me or poor.
But you know that Paul McCartney and Heather that a while ago, I was looking at them.
And I said, this is not good.
The two of them.
I know that.
But not give me the update on where we at first.
Well, I don't know.
She's asking a lot of money.
And well, actually, we don't know because it's all speculation, of course.
What was the thing about her leg?
Her leg?
Oh, he was smacking her around.
With her own leg?
Yeah.
No, I don't know with her leg.
That's what you told me.
I was a champion.
He hid the leg.
I hid the leg.
He hid her artificial limb.
Oh, really?
I'm not allowed to do that.
That's fucking hilarious.
That is very funny.
No, but, you know, outside, if she has a...
Who knew?
What am I going to do?
Who didn't leg or not?
Yo, bitch.
He found your goddamn leg.
She...
Sugibane.
He's just not.
And she doesn't look like a very nice person.
You know?
And I've seen her couple of times.
I've seen interviews.
I've read interviews.
I still don't like it.
And you know what I think is the problem.
And where it begins, where it all begins.
Before you get to that, can I just say one thing?
She may not come across as a nice person.
But you really don't know her.
Let's not forget she did lose a leg.
I mean, and she did try to make something of herself.
So I give her some props for that.
You know, you lose...
You lose like most people say fuck it.
I'm going to sit inside in my wheelchair all day and be unhappy.
And by the way, maybe she's still just a little bit unhappy about it.
Like getting fucking chopped off by a police motorcycle, no less?
Of course.
But...
I get for a little bit of leeway there.
Just a little bit.
And we don't know about it.
I don't think it's an excuse for not being a very nice person.
Dude, you think I'm grumpy now?
Take off a fucking leg and then see how happy I am.
You'll be so happy.
So this is what I'm saying, you know?
People are a little brave.
But what I said to you is I think that the whole problem with the two of them...
You put your left leg.
You left leg.
That's where it started.
No.
You know, that wasn't even a problem for Sir Poma Cardney.
Not at all.
But what I think he's older.
Okay.
You are older than I am.
You are now analyzing the problem between these two.
Yes.
What is the age difference between Paul McCartney and Heather Mills?
I don't know.
He is 64.
It's more than we have.
And she is what? 40?
Not even, I think.
Oh, come on.
She's got it.
You have to look it up.
Google.
Hold on.
Can't spell it anymore.
No.
Sir Paul McCartney.
Yeah.
Keep calling.
It's like royalty.
Exactly what you're saying.
You know.
1968, dude.
She's younger than I am.
She's 38.
Exactly.
38.
Yeah.
Shit.
That's a big difference.
It's like 28 years.
But listen.
So before you start, I think people like Paul McCartney.
They have a whole history.
I think he's very important.
He was a very important person, especially in a music history.
Everything started with the Beatles.
Everybody in the whole world is still copying the Beatles.
All the new groups are still copying.
You can hear something.
The Beatles in everything.
It was so important.
I think that somebody like Heather is absolutely not interested.
Doesn't understand it.
Although he's maybe not talking about it.
He's not, I think he's not a person that keeps on talking about the Beatles.
He looks ahead.
But still having that.
He's a stone or dude.
He's sitting there all day going.
Yeah.
He knows a lot about music.
His life is music.
Every memory is music for him.
She doesn't understand it.
And that's where the problem also starts.
What you're saying is, whereas it is his life.
Yeah.
And if you have a part the next to you that has nothing.
Nothing.
I guess he kind of, because I still, I caught the Beatles at the very tail end where they had the blue album and the red album.
Remember the collectors albums, like compilation albums.
And I played those over and over and over again.
Yeah.
But I'm four years older.
And right after that came disco.
That's, you know, I remember having my Beatles,
Blue, double album and red, double album.
And on top of that was Greece.
Yeah.
And on top.
And then the inside of the night fever.
And then after that I was, I don't think she witnessed.
I don't think she did.
No.
I don't think it's really an age thing.
I think she just doesn't give a shit about music.
No.
She doesn't give a shit about that.
It was a bad match.
The only thing that she thinks of is, oh, thank God.
He's born with God.
That's why he can help me.
I can see that.
Well, that's me.
You don't know that.
I agree with what.
I heard that in something I saw on TV.
You should write it.
It looks at his face.
And I thought that is wrong.
You should write for the son.
You'd be a great corner.
If I look at myself.
I absolutely can't compare myself to Paul McCartney.
But I am from a musical family.
My, my dad is a musician.
Everything was music.
Now I say, I'm medium.
You the only thing you know is Google.
And sitting on your ass and looking at your laptop.
Excuse me.
The thing of me.
You think of Google.
Sitting on my ass?
No.
That's what I'm saying.
What if you were just somebody who was always busy with, you know,
Internet.
I am not God.
You don't know anything about music.
You don't know about the history of music.
You don't know where it's coming from.
You don't know shit.
So every time I say something, he's like,
I don't know.
I've never listened to it.
I would be a very unhappy person.
I wouldn't marry you.
And here I was.
I would not have married you.
This time thinking was about my cock.
Here's some guys who are influenced by the Beatles.
Yeah, it is the band.
You know who these guys are?
One of your daughter's favorites.
Who is it?
Come on.
They just joined the podcast music network.
I don't have a name, but I know.
My chemical romance.
Yeah.
Ah.
Don't.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm like that, that's not the end
Never, never, never
Never, never, never, never
Never, never, never, never, never
Never, never, never, never, never, never, never
Never, never, ever, never, never, never, never really
Never, never, never, never, never, ever
The new musical sensation known as chemical Michael Roman's from New Jersey and they just put this song up on the pot set of music that work
I do think that's pretty cool. Well, we did some exercise on it. That was nice. Yeah, I saw it on my butt in front of the Google
I heard you bought it. Okay, bitch. What else from? Well, I read that
Brittany looks really good. She was getting divorced. They've let him in show for two seconds.
Yeah, for two seconds. She just stopped. I saw it on YouTube. Yeah, I think she woke up now. Yeah. She finally got it. Dude, how about all those videos of you on YouTube?
What was that? That's pretty cool. Yeah, that's you know, and this is what I like about YouTube is all that
You know, all the the television stuff that you can't find anymore. Yeah, there's just no way to go and get it back. That's fantastic
Yeah, it really is because it's some good stuff and a lot of your video clips are up there and
Yeah, even a producer I think who did one of the we had a sort of a top of the pops in Holland and he produced it and we've been there many many times
And he put the mom the you think he did that. Yeah, I think he did it totally it's sort of a strange name
But I recognize totally legal, but yeah, you don't care. I don't care. I don't care at all
Yeah, then why do other people care? I don't know. Thank you. I don't know why it's wonderful
I think I think that it's wonderful. Yes, since those videos that know to do it, you know since those videos been up I get emails saying hey, I'm
You know sometimes we don't know what to answer because I don't know where they are. I don't know now we know there's like one song on iTunes
I think wonderful. I think well you should call your record company tell them didn't to EMI release a box set of your older work
Yes, they did. Yeah, but my last record company wanted to release a DVD. Yeah, I think they're they're all in trouble
They're not they're not doing it. I don't know now. They're all in trouble
They they have no money to spend anymore. No, that's the business is gone. It's just it's you know
Remember we used to have guys who would ride horse carriages and with horses and that they had no cabs
No, where are those guys? Yeah, they're gone. You know sometimes things just have to go
Yeah, gross restores and supermarkets. Yeah, that's sort of things. Yeah, that's that's a shame actually
Anyway, Brittany. Yeah, Brittany. So I think she finally woke up
That Kevin Fettaline was feeding her hamburgers
So that she was really looking
A shitty as possible and as fast as we really think that guy was doing that on purpose
I don't know, but if you are Brittany Spears husband
You have to be a little bit responsible say darling don't do that
It's a pity because you've got a talent. You have to come back and you have to look but he probably didn't do that because he saw it
If you hamburger and all the money's going to be mad
You're just making that shit out
You don't know that's horrible
That's that's what that's what all the newspapers and entertainment tonight do
No, but he looked like a loser
Okay, agree with you there. That's that's what she's the worst. She gets the two kids
Yeah, oh no, and he's asking now he's going to
I know what he's going to try to get the kids. Oh, please
Yeah, please. I don't I don't believe that for sure
He's not going to get the money
What the money?
I heard money. He did if they married and he deserves money
Well, he probably gets a little bit, but
I think he should get a lot
You know, I think if Heather Mills can get
She's going to get 50 million pounds
So about to preen up
Yeah, but they didn't have it preen up and I don't think Brittany Spears and Kevin federal
I never preen up
You don't care
I really just don't care
No, we don't care about Brittany
Well, but it was set to see her like that and it's what people feel
And you know who's coming back
We talked about this
Whitney Houston
Yes
And guess who's producing her record
So happy
Guess who's producing her record
No, I do
Quincy Jones
Oh, that's good
There you go. And so Quincy
If Quincy Jones is producing the record
Then this could she could really do it. She can stay off the drugs
She'll I think she could make a huge huge comeback
Absolutely
Exactly what I said get rid of Bobby Brown
You know, do a killer record
Oh, everybody said that
Everybody said that
Yeah, but I want to take credit for it. It was my idea
And on you're going to say maybe Bobby Brown is a very nice guy
Because you always do that
No, he's an asshole
Oh, he is
But I knew that from day one
This one is free
I've told you the story about Bobby Brown
I knew he was an asshole because I've met him
So I think I have an unproper and thought
He had an attitude problem
That's what you see
I met him
Backstage
Remember the Z100 jingle ball
Remember you see the metal ends
Be concert and we have a whole bunch of artists
This is graphic and nasty
What I'm going to tell you
But Whitney Houston was there
I mean, this is in the days of
You know, I want to dance with somebody
So this is actually just
Yeah, yeah
It's around
80 days
Well, he was doing more than that
Because he ran out of a dressing room
Saying everyone
Him and Emma just fuck Whitney smell my fingers
Oh
And I thought you aren't asshole
Good
So I hate that
Right
So you see I have an unproper authority
That he's an asshole
I didn't defend him
Okay
Because I know him
That's shocking
Yeah
Or at least I know him
I know him enough
From that one encounter
Did you smell it?
Well, of course
Of course
I said can I look that finger above
I know you did
Oh, I did not
Do you really do
Honestly not
I don't know
Yeah, it was like one of those guy things
Where it's not actually
You're not actually meant to smell the finger
No
It was just like so wrong
Yeah
So wrong
And that's the woman he wanted to marry
No, he was sitting
He was really sitting there thinking of the money
Believe me
That's a guy who was really calculating it
Do you think she has anything left
Of a voice you mean
Of anything she had
Of a voice her money
I don't know about the life
I think she still has the house
The big house in New Jersey
You know no
I mean you just don't know
I don't care
I do I do hope
I mean
I could hear her voice going
It was just you know
She couldn't go
Yeah, you can destroy your voice
With that shit
I know
But
If Quincy Jones is producing
Then he he wouldn't do it
If he didn't think something was there
He really wouldn't
No, yeah, he's just he's such a pro
Very happy
Yeah, yeah, I think that's good
Very happy for him
That's good
All right baby
It's 47 minutes
I think we should stop
Yeah
Okay
Do you want it?
Gossiping
Wanna accuse me of anything before we go
We need a little
We need a little jingle
What is Adam's fault this week?
What is Adam fucked up this time
Lady Patricia lays it out
No
Everything else good?
Not everything is good
No, not everything is good
But what do you mean?
What's not good?
Well, you know that you're what is it?
You're thingy
Oh, yeah, this is a big problem
Yeah
Well, it's not gonna end up won't be here's problem
The podcast console is so big
Console
Yeah, we don't think it'll actually fit
Up the stairs
On to the third floor
Well, you're you're hiding me
Yeah, I'm gonna hide
This is beautiful
Look at this beautiful third floor
Where I can lock it down and shut you up
Lock you up
Yeah, and just slide pizza through the door
You can you can you can let your hair down
Yeah, I don't worry about but this chair is gonna be a problem
No, it's not
You think that I don't think that'll go up
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
We've got to measure it
Because we're gonna you know put it flat
Are the workers there today?
You want to go and measure it?
Yeah, let's do that
Yeah, that's a good idea
Okay
I need to measure it
I think we should definitely take some measurements
So we have to you have to call the
Call anyone
Let them know we're coming
But I'm gonna put you in the tower all the way up there
Yeah, in the tower
The curry tower
Curry tower
All the way from the curry tower
Yeah, I need something to do
Yeah, not yet
We'll come up
Yeah, we'll think about it
Okay, but thank you for dropping by
Okay
Will you come by again soon?
Of course
Your fans miss you
I mean the building anyway
Yeah, you're in the building
You're working in the other room
Yeah
All right, thank you very much
Are you welcome
I love you
I love you too
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
Get this podcast and more great ones like it
On the high performance podcast delivery network
From podshow and limelight networks
I love it