Delta Sierra Charlie 3-2-6
60 million dollars worth of airplane strapped my ass
Than the next generation radio content in my ears
We don't need lost thinking crazy
I like to think I'm flying into this genre
Oh, fantastic
It's a brand new week, are you ready for a whole new round new chances?
It's a Monday from the cottage, it's the source code
I like to think I'm flying into this genre
Good road action
rated up for me also
but see you seeking as fast as billions of thousands
wow, that bad god
from between our demons
Turn up on the background, come from the north side of the town, come out of my nose, but they have nothing else you do.
Who could've been a rat, I'm covered a little time there for you to excuse.
Yeah, I thought it could've been a rat, I'm covered a little time there for you to reduce.
When I think of you who came earlier, I think of you joking out of me tonight.
The only one who came and failed love, they tell me what you've written This brown spy was behaving harshly hurts a little for you.
You said you come round by five dirt ass, so I will wait for you, you, you, yeah, yeah, we can sit around, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, tutй o, winning our match, our prizes, our prize.
All of the robots have been manned together, but still tears
Then you would never come, got me in
Could be the right time, could be the little time that for you to excuse
Yeah, could be the right time that for you to be used
No use in iron, the things will be made never, and all of a sudden
Just won't tell me, tell me what you're doing
I still have left, a little for you
No use in iron, the things will be made never, and all of a sudden
Hey, no use in iron, the things will be made never, and all of a sudden
Just won't tell me, tell me what you're doing
I still have left, a little for you
No use in iron, the things will be made never, and all of a sudden
Just won't tell me, tell me what you're doing
I still have left, a little for you
No, no, it's me
Nothing like taking all the source code with a song and a bit of a mind sound
Go water's bad, no use driving
Whoops, sounds like we missed a bit of the ending there on the download, makes no matter
How you doing everybody, it's the daily source code Monday coming to you from Curry Cottage
And it's been a very busy morning, I just got back from Ferrox Airfield, Echo Golf Tango
To pick up my lovely bride who was delivered
Nicely, neat little package, the wind commander and Nick flew in in the moony to bring her back
As you know, my own playing the sessina is awaiting his new engine waiting for parts
It's all going to be put together and we chose the interior colors and everything's going to be great
By the way, let's just call it the Delta Sierra if we're talking about the plane because that's actually the call sign is November 277 Delta Sierra
So we'll just call it Delta Sierra from now on
So of course, you know, that takes good two hours to get out there on time, hang out
We had a cup of tea, had a bite to eat and then to Patricia back and so we're back and I'm on the microphones on the cast blast that
Getting you some daily source code interesting
Yesterday I spent a lot of time searching round for stuff and this may be a new thread that we just opened up Patricia said Friday night
She she slept in in Rotterdam at her sister's house and so she told me Saturday
Was it Saturday or Sunday? Maybe it was yesterday. She said, wow, I've slept so well here. You know, she has a little bit of arthritis in her hands and a little bit in her back and she said, I don't feel anything at all
And the immediate conclusion she drew was
That it's due to cell phone towers, which are actually very near by the house. It's funny when you see the house
Patricia, of course, as you know, she found the place she got everything together. She decided this was the place that we're going to stay for a while
Just a rental
She never actually saw the building next door, which is DEFRA
DEFRA is the what is the stand for department of
I should have looked that up shouldn't I I'll look it up when I'm talking about it
DEFRA are the same guys who who not only take care of agriculture, but I guess they
They make sure you don't bring your dogs in illegally, so we definitely dealt with them in the
The time that we've been here. Let me see. I'm just going to go to DEFRA.gov.uk
I'll give you exactly what it stands for department for environment food and rural affairs
So this all kind of came together because Patricia mentioned that to me. I just seen a neighborhood kind of like a neighborhood
What is it committee type thing?
They send around they want you to donate 10 bucks and they take care of all the parking problems and all that stuff and here at the back I read
It was mentioned that all mobile phone masks at DEFRA will be removed by the time employees vacate the site in 2007
So like wow how coincidental is that that she's talking about cell phone towers may be bothering her arthritis
And at the same time I read that so I immediately set off to look for two things one is the effects of cell phone towers and I'd have to say these are
These are micro transmitters not macro, but
No macro transmitters not micro these are pretty big puppies and I'd say that they are close enough to definitely have an effect
On something at least just reading through the literature, but I can't find anything related to arthritis although Patricia is very very sensitive to
RF radio frequency and to electricity
I mean we've actually moved beds in houses because she said I can hear the electricity in the wall and like okay
That's cool
Meanwhile the
Why guess because it's DC current her
Her heated bed she likes to have her feet heated while she sleeps that doesn't seem to bother her at all
But you know who knows what's going on now the course the second thing I went looking for is to see if the department
For the environment food and rural affairs if they indeed are leaving in 2007 and what's going to happen to this monumental space next door
Because you know my next the next house we we will live in will I hope will be one that we that we build ourselves and
Patricia it's really bothering her. I then we have to move. I mean, that's clear
So I also spend some time looking to real estate market and
I'm not really ready for it
But anyway, if you have any information on that
On either differ leaving Gilford in 2007 or on the effective cell phone tower specifically on arthritis. I'd love to hear about it quote of the day
This comes from Scott Adams from the Gilbert principle
Creativity is allowing yourself to make mistakes art is knowing which ones to keep and I really like that quote
Because I think that is indeed exactly what podcasting is showing us and many other forms of
Of stuff will create ourselves you know web logs are raw and and so are podcasts and I agree that the mistakes that you know if they're the right ones to leave in that is true
Really art
It's a beautiful thing
We're talking on I don't know if it's Thursday or Friday about Google in China, which of course is what everybody seems to be talking about these days
First thing I noticed
And I think I have a couple of actually have a couple of emails about this. Let's listen to this audio comment because
If you're not awake after that cool waters bands song you will be after this
And this is rubber head from the rubber room radio show available at rubber room radio.net
I got audio feedback comment here for you from something you were talking about on DSC 324 talking about Google censoring content in their web searches in China
I just got a message for all of those who've been bashing Google for trying to provide China with some sort of means to access information in their
Horrible starving country you know you're all bunch of hypocrites. I want you all to go look in your closets
Now your proverbial closets where your skeletons are but your actual physical closets where you keep your clothes go get your clothes
Go on take them out of the closet there and look at the tags how many of them say made in China
Is it doing business with Chinese sweatshops more heinous than blocking search results or how about those of you who don't have a nice Trinity poop mobile
Do you realize that China owns the second largest oil company in the world are you about to stop driving to help your brothers and sisters in China
Think about it a communist country owns a giant private oil company
I don't remember which one could look it up cheese what about the furniture you plant your fat ass on each day
You were looking under the sofa and see if it was stamped with a made in a communist oppressive abortion mandating evil Google censoring country
Trying to say is that it's real easy to start bashing a search engine
But it's a hell of a lot harder to live 100%
Socially conscious all the time and bashing Google doesn't get you off the hook
All right
Okay, I feel much better Adam. Thank you for letting me get that off my chest and my show the rubber room radio show
I don't spew a lot of political rants like this one
But I do play some really weird twisted music and you could check it out at rubber room radio.net
And Adam be sure to give those paparazzi but holes hell you've lived in America long enough to know how to sue the bastards
All right have a good next lot. All right, dude. Rubber room. Rubber hit. Love it. Yeah, I think this is maybe a classic case of projection
I think that the reason why mainstream media and journalists in particular are really jumping into this and also a lot of bloggers
Maybe there's projection that we feel that maybe some of our civil rights such as freedom of speech are being squelched a little bit or well, maybe maybe
Maybe there's so much freedom of speech that no one can hear it anymore. That's also possible
JT from ciopodcast.com is scutops.com. Rob mean emails has been a while since we communicated, but
I'm sitting here listening to daily source code 324 and yes, I'm in China, but look what the world needs to understand about this Google thing is rather simple
English reading Chinese simply use the English version of Google and can basically get whatever they want
They can get prawn or basically you know anything the desire there are more details that I won't get into here
But in general when I'm in China, I can get to most of the new sites all of the podcasting sites I desire
And I listen to stuff like distorted view and other stuff that would be considered questionable here
Now the Google stuff and censored Microsoft stuff really applies to the Chinese versions of these three sites of these sites
What also needs to be realized is that most people in China speak English English is taught to all Chinese growing up for those who really want the information it is there
And he says tailwinds all right JTK
presuming your an arman. Yes tailwinds absolutely back at you. Who's guys all that stuff
So this is interesting first of all because I said if you're in China and you can hear this out of my voice, please let me know so maybe it's not
Such a big deal. Yes, I understand that the connectivity to the Google.com is rather spotty and you know, I don't know
Maybe the banging keys against the ethernet connector or something to try and make it you know to discourage people from using it
But apparently they don't have the technology to close. You know this great firewall of China sounds like it's not that great as it's
Perhaps portrayed and then anyone can reach the regular Google but the Chinese Google is a customized version. Okay
That to me is almost like an enterprise sales. That's where they they should list that on there on the 10Qs enterprise sales to the
People's Republic of China incorporated they created a special version of Google. I wonder. I wonder if they got paid
Little Scottish last
Is now
Trying to teach me gaelic which of course is a perfect
A perfect way to code
Transmissions to the people's Republic of China as we teach them gaelic we learn gaelic and we're set
And I got some
Like a big panic
Message from PW Fenton who produces all the
The pod shows on serious of course if you're listening to stars one or three on serious then here you go
PW is responsible for it
What's interesting is that I'm ending at exactly when the when the sound blows
But he's saying I'm consistently 10 seconds late so it's very possible that this clock just doesn't run on time
So we're keeping our eye on it for today as I get down to the last 30 seconds
When the before the satellite window closes all of double check with you
And then Sean Rife said I heard you're talking about the countdown clock sound being owned by
Oh, gag
Sony
Want to let you know that you're not the only one using it Kim commando who was a nationally syndicated radio
Who has a nationally syndicated radio show about computers and technology uses the exact same sound in a weekly radio show
In fact, she seems to use it in every episode
I don't know what this means but wanted to pass this little bit of info on it seems that if you're going to incur the wrath of Sony she would too
No, that's not necessarily true if this song of this sound which you'll hear in seven minutes and 45 seconds from now
Approximately if this sound has been, well, interesting if they
Most people make jingle sounds and convert and music for commercial submit that to ask cap or BMI what is it it's not
I don't know if they submitted to ask have BMI I guess they do I yeah, that would make sense
And then so every single time it's used and then there's the so called sync fee
But this to me sounds like it's something that someone put out there and it's just been used all over the place if you're the originator of it, please let me know
I'd love to get permission to continue using it and I'm sure that the folks at countdown clock would like that as well as would
What is that the show in
I forget was a TV show that uses it was that in Canada for some reason I'm thinking that and Kim Kamando is interesting how stuff like that travels around the world
It's probably the same as a couple of the drops that come in cast blaster
I'm not sure if if we created them or if they were taken off of royalty free stuff
I mean we're not charging money for him. We just kind of throw him in as an extra diddy like this
Or the yeah, of course, and then we have the
Right
Which of course is just how it provides for hours of fun when the first time you download cast blaster
So keeping our eye on it for for Peter make sure we don't mess up the timing today
From the thousands of podcasts available today
Why should you choose us the most?
We can host things about this
The mouthpiece podcast is going for podcasting with the arme page bid to the daily newspaper
It's giving the voice to the people who consume the media
Send your emails and audio to Mr. mouthpiece at gmail.com
The greatest thing about the mouthpiece podcast is it's almost entirely listener submitted
Again, Mr. mouthpiece at gmail.com
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do. We are a flank
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers
We're Earthlink
We believe your personal information should be just that personal
And we believe your internet should be a friend not a fo
We're Earthlink
Make this smart choice visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you
Earthlink
We revolve around you
Do you have the talent to write your own lyrics and melodies
But don't have the ability to create your own tracks to complete your visions
A rap or pop artist
Then contact our cadian reading
Based out of Austin and Houston's exes or cadian reigns
A collection of musicians interested in creating wide reaching rap
Hip hop and pop beats for hinderpinter artists and record labels to purchase
Along with offering a wide array of pre-produced beats such as the ones you are hearing
We're also available to sit down and create tracks with you to fit your own personal style as an artist
For more information and contact us, please visit our website at ArcadianRain.com
While you were there, you can also listen to more of our beats
That's www.ARCATIANREIGN.com
Stop dreaming of making a record and start today
I'm sure that that stuff is going to happen
I just want to make sure everyone hears about these places we can go and collaborate
Like, was it myvirtualband.com is another one of those
I really love that
This is the stuff we dreamed of 10, 15 years ago that you could actually
We're dreaming of it in real time at the time where latency would all be figured out
Of course, we haven't figured out latency for real-time musical collaboration
Since you need to be kind of on the beat and even a couple of milliseconds makes a difference
And we haven't been able to get that working with the freaking USB microphones
Let me see, Peter
Is that Peter?
Yeah, from Ultimate Mix podcast, Peter Long
Peter Long, every ball day
Adam, you said clear channel took over the airways in the US
So the world tuned to podcasting
What's happening now in the free media that's podcasting has to be paid for
Huh?
Okay, he has a link here
To podcast-audio.crystallist.com
Crystallist is a big owner of radio stations
Particularly in the UK
And they are selling their podcasts
By subscription
So you can get, let's say they do have a free offering
You can get 15 minutes best of podcasts
But for two pounds a month, so five bucks a month
You'll get extended best of additions of your favorite shows
Full length downloads of some programs
Presumably not those with music or only ones that have been cleared as such
Exclusive online only programs, searchable archive of LBC
That's the LBC FM is this offering by the way, I'm sorry
It is a Christmas property
You can get the podcast played that you listen online without downloading
That's a contradiction in terms for full listings of what's on click here
So you can sign up it's two pounds 50 for one month, seven pounds for three months and ten pounds for six months
You know what?
That's fine
I'm sure many people will sign up to that
And by the way, if you're going to pay me two pounds a month like five bucks a month
Done
I'll take it
Absolutely
I'll give you a commercial free version
You bet you
Maybe that's what we have to do, maybe we just have to
Inundate these podcasts with so much commercial messaging
The people just say screw it, I'd rather pay for it
Let me know what you'd rather do
Geek brief is back, Callie
She had a bandwidth issue
Apparently this video podcast she does is it got really successful
Very, very fast, he's never done any camera work
She's cute, she does this
I just have to say it, she's cute and she talks about gadgets
duh, no wonder it's popular
So you can find that at geekbrief.podshow.com
And we're happy to have her
Suckin' off the pipes here
As it were
Let's see, we got some stuff about iTunes New Zealand
As if that really existed
Hi Adam, just listening to DSC323
And in the spirit of sticking it to the man
I thought I'd share this with you
My name is Gada, and I've recently started the New Zealand podcast
I Heart and Z
With my husband
You can find out more about it at ourheart and Z.com
It's about all things New Zealand for my Canadian perspective
And from his cute perspective
Apple has decided for whatever reason
I can't open up an iTunes music store in New Zealand
I have no problem with this as Apple has enough of my money
In our software company Zodel
We have two-time exercerers
Four times parable of laptops
One-eye cloud video, one-eye cloud shop
Thank you
You know what?
I'm just gonna stop for a second
Because I told you that we'd check the times
20 seconds left
And I'm telling you
The clock has already off by four seconds
As we're counting down
I'm comparing castblaster
Which is saying the satellite window closes in two seconds
So goodbye y'all
And now that's 243031-32
My gosh
The countdown clock is actually off
I'm just going to presume that castblaster is right on the money with its recording times
So that's kind
That's not good
The only thing you would expect
The countdown clock to absolutely do right is run on time
So man
Oh that's horrible
So what was it like a full four seconds that would that it was off?
This is not good
I got to write back to the guy who wrote it
I don't know how he's doing this timing
But you presume that at least that part would be on
All right
Just us podcasts freaks here
Let me continue with this thing about iTunes and New Zealand
Because that does blow me away that Apple
Has no iTunes store that you can actually use
You know in New Zealand
It's an outrage
Outless other Apple stuff
I was surprised to see that I had to sign into the music store in order to submit my podcast
Of course
This is impossible because I'm sitting in New Zealand with no iTunes store
And no iTunes account
Well, well, well, well, well that is interesting
Of course
I didn't think about that because you can't sign up with a New Zealand based credit card
That's how they
Segregate your purchases
You know the billing address of your credit card
So I have a Dutch account
And I have a US account
And what you see when you log in is significantly different
You know the top 100 different as well
That's all based by region
Not overall as a global status
And
You need to have an iTunes music store account
To submit your podcast
But of course there's the catch 22
Can't open an account
Can't list your podcast
New Zealand
We are on the way
I decided to email the friendly people at Apple
And this is the response I got
Thank you for your interest in the iTunes music store
At this time customers who reside in New Zealand can use the iTunes music store to browse music
Listen to previews and watch videos
However, purchasing music or submitting podcasts is not yet available in your country
While we cannot comment on future availability of iTunes music store
Please be sure that we are committed to bringing the iTunes music store to music lovers around the world
Since early the iTunes music store team
I couldn't believe that they've knownly turned away free content
Not very community minded if you ask me
I guess that brings me to what I love about DSC
Podsac music network podcast alley
Countless of their shows like The Dawn and Drew Show
Basically it's community
So in the time between deciding to record this and actually recording it
I've such data work around and I'm happy to report that iHeart NZ is now listed at iTunes
In the meantime if you're ever looking for a podcast from the land of the Long Want Cloud New Zealand
Remember to keep iHeart NZ in mind
Check us out iHeart NZ.com
Thanks Adam
No, thank you. I appreciate it. Okay
We'll figure out something we can do for New Zealand
I wonder I wonder wonder wonder
Perhaps
Can I do it through my account?
Do you mean you can submit as many podcasts as you want under one account can't you?
So why don't we do it one big clearing account and just start listing all the podcasts for you?
Be happy to set that up
I'm sure there's quite a number of podcasts podcasters that would like to get listed
That would be no problem
I'll look into it if you know by the way
Let me know if you can list more than one podcast and of course it's never guaranteed because you know sometimes just don't get listed
It's apparently the way it seems to go
So while we have women talking on the show and thank you very much
I appreciate it
And GB checks it
It's Angie again, you know, I was talking to an indie band about podsiff music network and mentioned
Adam Curry's involvement
And the first thing they thought of is hey, is that that guy with the big hair
So that reminds me that you said you just got in a cool new haircut
But I haven't seen any pictures of it surface online yet, so you're going to put some up
Now to do is buy Dutch gossip magazines Angie
That's where you can see all my cool pictures
Should be hearing today when we're going to court
It should be, you know, this month sometime
I can't go next week because in New York and that does have precedence over this
But it's the same style Angie, it's just a little bit shorter, you know
Nothing, nothing too radical, nothing, nothing too fancy
But if you send me a picture of you, I might consider
Let me see
People really digging the bill album that was available for download
That bill made available
Here's a hotel wins drew, Drew Domkas from the Don and Drew Show
Can I say tail wins since I'm a remote control pilot
He flies RC helicopters
No, no, Drew, of course not
You're not a real man when you fly those
So I think we're going to hook up in San Francisco one of these days
I think they march as something like that
And they're going to do some big, you know, we'll set something up
We'll do a big Don and Drew
Sheen Day against San Francisco
It'll be fun, I'm really looking forward to it, I'll be great
Thought some more feedback on today's show
About four more and then we got another great pod save song
Which is from a very very well known artist who is just joined
The pod save for a revolution
So stay tuned for it
Hey Adam, and data c324
Utah does have my pod show
What allow us to combine multiple subscriptions
Into a single RSS feed
I think that's pretty cool
But is only one half of the ultimate solution
What we also need is an option to manage which episodes have been downloaded
As the pod show end
This would mean I can download episodes first thing in the morning for my commute to work
And then again before I leave work for the commute home
For this to work
I think what is needed is a thin client on the user end
Which knows how to do two things
First how to talk to my pod show
And second what to do with the downloaded episodes
In my case I'd want them sent to my iPod
My iPod would never get duplicate episodes
Because my pod show is the one keeping track of what I've already downloaded
Extending the concept
Such a client could even be run directly from my iPod
Much as share pod does now for copying tracks on and off to any computer I plug it into
Given that such a client would have to operate with my pod show
It would be easy enough for developers to create new clients
To address different platforms i.e. Mac versus Windows
And different devices such as iPod versus iRiver etc
Anyway, that's my ultimate solution
What do you think?
Oh yeah, I almost forgot
Thanks, dude
Yeah, very good idea
I like that a lot
And I know that Kevin and Sue and the whole gang are listening
So I know that they'll take those ideas to hard
You know we've got a lot of great stuff that we can do
When Andrew Grummit came on board
We also acquired gigadile.net
If you haven't checked that out
Definitely look at gigadile
You can create an entire
Podcast feed made up of other
Individual episodes or any piece of audio
Basically so really
Really
You know, puts a whole new metaphor
On to the idea of
Of what a podcast is and how you can create one
Without actually ever recording something yourself
So
Definitely stuff like that in the works
We just want to, you know, the stuff that we have now
We just want to get out get it into bait
Already so people can start playing around with it
And start breaking it
I'm doing a fine job by the way of breaking most of that
Okay, let me see Nick Jaffey has a few words as well
Let's see what he's got going on
Hey Adam, this is the podson from the zoo
Of course, and I just want to say a little
Feedback thing on my podshow
Why don't you have, as it mostly is woven together
Why don't you have the PMN
Linking up with your show notes
So whenever you play a song
It would write the song
And maybe the
The creators link
In the show notes or something like that
Because then of course, that would link up with the
Royalty thing for
The podcast is referring to you
If they click on the show notes link
It's really complicated but it could work
It's going to of course work with other things like
Promise etc
Do you see listeners please check out my website
Zov.com
Absolutely
Yeah, so of course we'd love to have that automated
Which would just be fantastic
We have a module now for your show sites
That you'll see on your
When you're able to sign up for the podcast delivery network
And you can actually have that display
The last five songs you played
From the pod save music network
The next obvious step is to have that
You know just kind of magically appear
Here's the songs in this in this episode
I don't take a little bit more work
But I have faith in George the Russian scientists
Hey Adam
This is God in from KTSP
God in St. Song's podcasts
Remember last year when you and Patricia
We're enjoying Valentine's Day
Under romantic tunes
I played in KTSP 18
Well it's now time to announce the second
You'll KTSP Valentine's Day edition
And this year
I'm taking requests
So if you or your listeners would like to dedicate
The romantic love song to their loved one
Please drop a comment
On www.ktsp.net
Thanks Adam for playing this promo
Bye bye
I love that Karen is hung in there so long
What is this now over a year that she's been doing
Karen think it's Karen's
God in steam scene
It's a tongue twister
Cadence themed song podcast
It's usually shows up in my
In my iTunes actually is where I'm subscribed to
It usually shows up on Sunday
And I just love playing the songs
You know nice and loud throughout the whole house
Well you know just doing my thing hanging out
Usually walk around on my bathroom
Very nice
I'll think about it
I'll come up with something since I'm not going to be home for
Shiza and be in New York
If you haven't checked them out yet
I know I've talked about it
There's a
Oh my gosh
There's a podcast you might want to check out
It's
Heather and Johnnell
And basically their entire show
Just to enable them to podcast
I'll give you a step in
And so they're sponsoring that show
And it's a Christina's listen to it a couple of times actually
It's for you know like a teen teenage girls 15 to
I'd say easily 19 because you know
You're never too old to talk about guys I guess
I have limited listening experience with the show
But you can check it out at download.aciveyou.com
And here's something very mysterious
Something fresh is coming
You
It's all about a brand new network
Sure everyone in their pod father has a network
But this one is different
This one is fresh
Fresh media works but you
The podcast are in charge
Go to freshmediaworks.com to sign up for more information
Fresh media works
We're reinventing media together
Fresh media works.com
You're almost swear young palette did that
Not quite sure what it is
But lots of people are excited about freshmediaworks.com
Kind of a drab website right for right now
But apparently something cool going on
So keep my eye on it for you
Two more things
Okay, Alex Ross is an ex English professor
And I want to correct me on the use of my language
The English language
Alex says you frequently use the term prolific when
Thank you me profound
Whether it be about something your father or
Mad Weinstein said and by the way they often say the same thing
The same profound things
I noticed you tend to transpose the words
prolific denotes quantity length and number
The amount of podcasts you've created is therefore prolific
Your music library may be prolific
The Rolling Stones or Charles Bukowski are prolific
But people don't make prolific statements
They make profound ones
Thank you very much Alex. I appreciate that
Yeah, I know I get that messed up
And there's also profound and profane
I'll know and that's probably why I get freaked out about it
And neither use profound or profane just use prolific
Seems like it's easier
A safer bet every time
Because I remember one time in college
For all three months that I was there
I meant to say profound but I said profane and
The professor freaked out on me
I don't remember exactly what the context was
But I remember don't want to get those messed up anymore
Hey Adam greetings from Jerusalem
I'm a BBC journalist and have sent
The last few spent the last few days in the West Bank covering the Palestinian elections
I've just uploaded a post-election podcast
And ipodcast.lipsin.com
That's Bravo November India podcast
All-one word.lipsin.com
Is this the first spot news podcast recorded on the ground
From a developing story in the Middle East
Kind regards from Stewart
I don't know if it's the first I certainly love it
I don't know if you're a freelancer Stewart
Or what the deal is
But I'm subscribed to your feed
That's fantastic. I really enjoyed this stuff
I could hear people around you
You know and even though it's
Some of it was very similar to what you might see on CNN on the BBC world news
It had a whole different vibe to it really really enjoyed it
So keep it rocking
And then finally
I told you I told you something like this was going to happen
The Dutch Ask Cap BMI the Buma
Who are responsible for collecting fees from
Basically any performance
So if you have a radio on in the workplace or if you have a restaurant or a bar
If you have a restaurant or a bar
Now there's a
An organization
The Dutch Hotel and restaurant organization
And they had set up hospitality music.nl
Which you probably can't get to
If you're trying it right now in front of your computer
The reason what they've done is they put up
What they considered to be pod safe music
They don't call it pod safe
But they call royalty free music
That all these restaurants
Were happily downloading and playing because they felt that the
The Buma fees were just too high
And they were cutting in too much into their profit margin
Now
The Buma says
That they have the right to collect from every
Place of business
Regardless of whether you're playing all royalty free music
Or not in fact they'd even clubs they'd do it by CD player
And furthermore they
I guess they served an injunction against the site
Because they said there were some infringements of copyright
So the site is currently down
But wow
That's messed up
This is exactly what I predicted
They're basically saying
We have the right to collect
Money from you whether you're using
Our music or not
And I think that
Definitely
They're trying to protect their turf here
And this is something that someone should take all the way
I'm not going to spend any time
Any more time that I have to
Helping out Dutch causes
Certainly not when it comes to
Stuff with the government and
Going for the
For the justice of it all
Because I don't think I owe
The country that
I would certainly do it in the states
But come on
This is this is messed up
And I think you should be able to play
Completely royalty free music without having to pay for anything
Or maybe you can choose to pay a different organization
If there's a different kind of deal
That should be a competitive thing
And it's not
The Buma says they have the
God-given right almost
The legal right to be the only ones who collect those types of fees
And they're going after them
Whether their music is being used or not
And these establishments
So I'd say that's pretty messed up
Meanwhile on the pod safe music scene
Things are going very well
We have
A major major artists sign up
And has dropped three songs onto the PMN
And one of those is titled Ever since
I'm going to play it right now
This is Leslie Gour
I dreamt you
I drew you
Long before I thought that I might never find you
I chased you
I traced you
And held your picture up
Into the light
All the way to light
Today is too long to miss
All the parties I've been to
You were missed
I've waited ever since
I met you
I tried to forget you
You know I felt somehow
Someone had sent you
To me
And as if you knew me
We picked up where we left off
In another life
The times I tried to settle out
For so much less than this one
I'll say it all
But all in every
I left
I waited ever since
I met you
All the way to light
Today is too long to miss
All parties I've been to
You were missed
I waited ever since
I met you
Ever since
From
Leslie Gore
First album of new material
In 30 years
And of course it's her own
Project role in label
So she owns it
She wouldn't be saying you don't own me
Well actually she does say you don't own me screw it
Nobody owns her
Welcome
Fantastic that she looks great
Great to have you in the pod save music scene
I'm sure lots of pod castes will pick up
And it's great to see that there's even a
Remake if you don't own me that she's
She's also made available
Fantastic
All right
Full new week of shows
Coming your way
I think Thursday will be the day I'm going to the
Netherlands the win command to just told me he would
He would happily arrange the moony
For me since Delta Sierra is still in pieces
But there will definitely be a show
Then I'll just upload it from the hotel
Do a quickie
I'll talk to you tomorrow
Take care everybody and thank you very much for listening
Subscribing daily source code dot com
Adam at curie dot com
Bye bye
Another pod show pod cast
Stick it in your ear