This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 3 9 or 0.
A $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm a representative of her majesty's British government.
The Empire need you.
What the question is, do I need the Empire?
Oh, you just can't mind?
I'll make it come and make you all awake.
My story might make you laugh.
I might make it come and make you laugh.
What a thing, dude.
I'm not a governor.
I'm a manager for you.
And I'm a paler from making a good thing.
Dealing it out on your own.
Do you like it?
I want some more
I might not get it never before
I never wonder
You never stop
I never still never get too hard
I just don't know
I want my dead end to that
I'm on my bed
I'm on bed
I'm on bed every year
I'm on my dead end to that
I'm on my bed
I'm on bed every year
I'm on my
I don't want any
I lost it
I'm on my weapon
It's never a day
Oh I'm on my dead end to
I'm on my dead end
I'm on my death
I'm on my dead
I'm on my dead end
i'm not gonna freaking out
life it's just so hot
i'm not gonna
stop it
so I'm gonnaю
oo, hey everybody how about that one how Bob-al
recommended by Coty BROMLEE
thank you very much Coty from the Pots head music homework
uh Deadpool
YO
I love bands like this
and look just look at the pictures
kind of like that 60's MOT-TIpe vibe
Q-GROAL
wah
DIGIN cock
hey
It's Thursday coming to you from Curry Cottage in the affluent suburb of Surrey.
It's Gilford where the sun is just cracking through.
It's been kind of a mixed weather day, sunshine rain.
You know what it's all like.
And I got lots to talk about today.
We're going to go a little bit longer than usual.
So probably actually the the satellite repairman.
P-Dub, he said, I'd like to have a 49er from you today.
That's our code for can you do a longer show?
So yeah, absolutely. Lots of stuff to talk about.
Some stuff that happened this morning with an interview that I did on the BBC,
for BBC Scotland. Got to tell you about that one.
And let's get this one out of the way right away.
Well, we're from our spine here.
It's the Yanks versus the Brits.
We'll drive each other crazy, but everybody knows that it's a parent to see.
They're just like you and me. It's the Yanks and the Brits.
The Yanks versus the Brits.
Mind the gap.
Very special episode of the or addition of the Yanks versus the Brits today.
I think that this is the guy who called in a couple weeks ago on the on the brand new voice mail phone lines,
which in New Jersey you're 2016256357 or in London,
02076813753.
And you might remember it. All that all he said was,
this is a test to test communications from Abu Dhabi.
And the guy's name is Malcolm.
And he sent in a segment for the Yanks versus the Brits and his voice.
It just blew me. He could he could be talking crap for all I care.
I'd still listen to what this guy has to say.
The Yanks versus the Brits is proving a great feature on the Johnny regularly,
making me smile when I remember the misunderstandings of my high school and college years in the states.
I think I'm beyond being phased by pronunciation issues.
When I write my spelling is British, I reckon my punctuation is probably America.
There is one area in which an American peculiarity in rages need mightily several times every single day.
This happens whenever I want to print out a document on my printer.
And I'm someone who takes pride in the way my correspondence and manuscripts look.
I try to lay them out in a way which pleases the eye.
But how often do I hit the print button and then realize that I've forgotten to override the default 8x10 and the half inch US letter format?
Most of the world uses internationally standardized stationery sciences.
A letter or a page of a script is most often A4, roughly 21x30 centimeters.
But a few printers I have been able to find offer A4 as the default format.
It remains only an option which has to be selected each and every time.
This may for many people seeing a trivial matter if the document can be read, what the hell?
But even if I can easily accept that you say tomato and I say tomato,
I like my margins, page breaks and blocks of type to look the way I want them to look.
And so I curse Mrs. Hulet and Packard with great regularity.
And thank the Lord that for at least an hour or so of the day I have the Charlie running in the background to keep me from taking all of this part of seriously.
The only problem is the Saturdays and Sundays without the SC.
Here in the United Arab Emirates these are office days.
High risk days.
Defenderation of HP printer entirely possible one of these fine days.
Well, that's my take on the youngsters with the bridge at them from Malcolm in Abu Dhabi.
Malcolm, thank you so much.
Peter Day from the BBC has nothing on you, my friend.
Listen to those pipes.
And I was thinking, I could pull so many great drops from that.
How much was it on Saturdays with the Charlie?
Man, can you get a microphone and download cast blaster cast blasts at our calm and just record some shit for me?
Just anything.
I love it.
It's a phenomenal.
Did you hear about this?
It's circulated the internet a little bit.
A mix up that happened at BBC's 24 hour news channel.
BBC, BBC world or BBC 24 BBC news, whatever the heck it is.
It's really, really funny.
I just love what happened.
I'm going to paraphrase the whole thing.
It's not really important who's who and who's what.
But apparently, they were looking for a guy, an IT expert, to discuss, what was it?
I think was the future of, oh yeah, this was surrounding the Apple records or Apple publishing for the Beatles music versus Apple computer.
And so they had an expert on.
You know, and then he was really participating about the, you know,
he was answering some questions and talking about the future of music online and what was going to happen to,
to broadcast and he was really going all out there.
Unfortunately, I didn't see the piece.
It'd be great if anyone recorded it or if there was a link somewhere online to see this interview.
What happened is, and I can see this still happening.
Well, at any broadcast facility, particularly a 24 hour news channel.
So there were a couple of people waiting in the lobby.
One of them was the, the guests for this interview, the, the IT journalist actually is,
what he is, Mr. Cuney with the K.
And there was another gentleman there, Mr. Goma, who was there for an interview,
but it was for a job interview to work at BBC News.
And so apparently, you know, and you know how this goes, like, hey, you know,
got to get the next guest and the producer runs out of the hallways, like,
yeah, who's he for the interview? Oh, yes, he, okay. And so the guy's like, all right.
And whatever the confusion was there, they got the wrong guy.
And they, and they rush him through the studio, they plop him in the chair,
they're live on air. And, you know, so the question start and this,
and it first the guy's like, you know, he's apparently he's kind of, you know,
bewildered, but then he gets into it.
And then he, as I said, he starts to pontificate about the future.
Meanwhile, the person who was supposed to be interviewed, the IT journalist,
they're watching some other dude on the screen with his name.
And now it's like, you know, everyone's upset and there's all kinds of,
you know, possible litigation because it's hurt this guy's reputation.
And this goma guy who's there for the job in a year's like, hey,
I'll be happy to come on your show again.
That's the next bird witness. Oh, fantastic.
Now this morning, right after I dropped Christina off at school,
I went to the BBC Southern Counties studio facilities,
which are at Guilford University, where they have an ISDN hookup,
so you can basically be connected to any BBC studio.
I guess around the world, it's kind of a dusty closet with some really old antiquated gear.
And, you know, the old, you know, those old senheiser head sets that we all
craved at one point because you could barely feel them on your ears,
which, of course, totally unsuitable for radio broadcasts.
And because, you know, there's immediate feedback leakage through these things,
because they sit so snugly on your ears, but don't close any sound off.
So that, you know, that kind of gear, old gray metal stuff.
So the interview was for BBC Scotland.
And it's for the midday show, they're hosted by a woman named Muriel Gray.
And although I've never heard her show that she's been in broadcasting for 20 years.
So she's been around.
So, you know, I, of course, at 930 exact right on the button,
you know, BBC Glasgow calling Hilfoden and all connects and, you know,
get the engineers and then they set up and add nice little preamble chat with Muriel.
And of course, it was, to be about podcasting, a pre-recorded segment.
So I guess she does like 10 minutes, 10 minutes, three guests in a half hour or something like that.
And it's, it's for air on the 29th.
And so I had a really nice little chat up front, which I'll tell you more about in a second.
And then the interview starts.
You know, within, within just a few seconds, I realized that we have fucked up.
We, we being myself, and also the PR marketing department of Podshow.
We presume the BBC does their homework and their research and, you know, these extremely well-funded organizations,
really know what they're talking about when they approach anything from a journalistic viewpoint.
Well, what I realized very quickly is that the only podcast Muriel had ever listened to was one to be exact,
mine, and that would be yesterday's show.
So I'm kicking myself, because yesterday, I just threw out a show there, which was very much, you know, two songs,
to talk about my day at BT, because everyone wanted to hear about that.
And no promo is or anything.
So I immediately kick myself for, you know, for the response she had, because of course,
I can understand where she said, well, really, it's just, you're talking about having a big Mac and,
top meeting some guy at BT, and I said, well, excuse me, first of all,
it was a wopper, second of all, it was the CEO of British Telecom, but she said it was boring,
and she thought, and it was, it was like, just mainstream.
The fact that I'm even going to charge advertisers money for it.
So I don't like to immediately go on the defensive, because I don't feel I have to defend,
podcasting at all, but I was really pissed off at myself for not making sure that, you know,
she's never heard of the tartan podcast.
You know, I mean, what a disservice to her listeners.
And I just could not really, I could not move her left or right to be honest,
and she was extremely arrogant about the position of mainstream media,
and professional, and that's all the people want to hear.
So I felt that personally, I did, I did my best, but I did poorly in the overall,
you know, the results that I got from this interview, I'm sure,
and they will send me a CD, so I'll be able to listen to it at home.
Although I'm pretty sure that maybe I can get it on sky on the satellite receiver system here.
And it's stupid, you know, we should have, we have to, we can't forget that people just don't do their homework.
And then just following on the gang's versus the bridge, she wound up the segment,
and this really is getting to me.
You know, there's not much you can say to me as a Brit that'll rub me the wrong way,
but I hear this all the time, and I don't like it.
So she winds up by saying, you know, final question,
can podcasting topple governments, and I thought for a second, I said,
well, you know, we're already seeing web logs bring down political people,
particularly in the United States, so yeah, of course it could.
She said, well, because you do something about Bush then, you know,
and that was the end of the interview, before I had a chance to actually say,
well, you know, maybe if you paid attention to your guy Blair,
and got his nose out of Bush's ass, maybe Bush would have some more attention to look at some stuff.
But this is very, very consistent with Brit saying to me, well, you know,
hopefully you could do something about George Bush.
Like you're fucking powerless, come on.
Get someone in your government who will speak up for what you're really saying.
It's not all that bad.
I mean, it hurt me, it really hurt me.
Now, so she says this mural grace says there's no difference between what you're doing and what we do,
we're more professional.
And I said, no, because there is a lot about the freedom of speech and expression,
which you don't have either based on.
Primarily time constraints, you can't say everything you want,
because you only have half an hour as an example,
or political reasons for your company, or your broadcast organizations,
or for legal reasons of commercialism, which would not be possible on the BBC.
All these different things.
And to give you a great example, Muriel, and I hope that you're listening.
I hope you listen to at least one more episode of the Daily Source Code.
Here's a fine example.
We were talking before the interview about something which you would never talk about on the air.
Now, you did not disclaim it to me as being off the record or not being able to talk about it.
So I'm going to tell my audience exactly what we discussed.
She said, and this is before we actually started taping,
and have you ever been to Scotland?
I said, no, but I finally had my aircraft here, and I can't wait,
because one of the guys at the field, Jason, who actually works in the towers from Scotland,
and we're going to go, and we're going to do a tour of Scotland, one of these days,
one of the weather's a little bit nicer.
And she said, well, what is this aircraft?
Is it like a John Travolta Boeing, or is it a sess nice?
I said, well, it's a little bit in between, more on the sessness side.
I said, you know, but I wouldn't mind having one of those Travolta 737s,
or I can park next to my house.
And then she starts laughing, she says, oh, yes, well, there you go.
It's the homosexual, Scientologist.
And I said, what are you talking about?
You're talking about Tom Cruise and talking about John Travolta.
Oh, no, no, John Travolta's gay too.
I said, what?
She said, oh, yeah, oh, definitely.
I said, well, you're really easy saying that.
I mean, what are you saying?
On what authority do you have this?
And she said, I have it on firsthand authority from a man who's had sex with John Travolta.
And so I'm like, whoa, this is a major scoop.
And then she said, okay, but now my producer is saying we have to stop this and we have to start the interview.
So there's the difference.
You have a producer who won't let you talk about something that I think I was actually really interested in that for a moment.
It's like, wow, I mean, this is a pretty big claim.
Not that I care.
Not that it makes any difference.
Not that I love John Travolta more or less for it.
But wow, you know, you're so flippin' to pass on that kind of news,
gossip or otherwise, but you're too pussy to put it on the air.
Now that would be a conversation to have.
God, I feel good when I do that.
I know the tin foil hat moment presented by the financial aid podcast.
Yeah, I mean, if you or anybody you know is considering trying to make a real life living on second life,
you should know that inflation in the second life world is devastatingly high.
In the last 45 days, according to second life's own website, there's been approximately 10% inflation in the currency.
That works out to 81% per year.
Check it out for yourself on the second life website.
Just go to secondlife.com, look under commerce, economic statistics.
What does this explosive inflation mean for you?
Well, if you're just playing the game where fun, it's actually a great thing,
because it means that one US dollar will buy them that much more currency in second life.
However, if you're looking to make a business out of it, it means that your second life dollars are depreciating rapidly every single day.
If you bought a dollars worth of linden currency today, in a year, you'd only be able to redeem that same amount of currency for 19 cents.
Definitely think carefully before making a real life business out of second life.
Now for your tin foil hat moment, wouldn't it be great if the US government had a page just like second life did detailing inflation?
They used you, but the government has taken away that information from the public as of March 26 of this year.
Some conspiracy theorists believe that the recent run-up in gold prices has less to do with oil,
and more to do with the US government running the printing presses at full speed to try and make up some of the deficit by printing more money.
Just like it takes more linden's second life dollars to buy a dollar with hyperinflation in the game,
it takes more dollars to buy a gold in first life.
This is Chris from the Financial Aid podcast with your tin foil hat moment.
Stop by for more at Financial Aid podcast.com.
Dude, Chris, thank you so much, man.
I love it when you send stuff.
If Chris does the perfect type of, has perfect contributions to the Charlie, he really does.
He gives you some information, something that you wouldn't know about, and then he plugs us on shirt when he's out.
And that's, I love it that way. It's fantastic. Thank you.
For those of you who don't understand what he was talking about when he's talking about second life.
For those of you in Scotland hosting a radio show on the BBC, your first man may might be Muriel,
and your last name would rhyme with John Travolta, his gay.
We're talking about the virtual world known as second life, which is garnering great interest from the BBC,
from Harvard University, from Creative Commons, now also about to host an event in second life.
And that is very interesting, Chris. I'm not liking that at all, this inflation thing.
But if second life is true to first life and they do have a lot of financial models set there,
how can we reverse that? How can we reverse the economics and reduce inflation?
Is there a Fed that we, is there an Allen Green Span, he's gone?
Can we get Allen Green Span as you available? Can we get him as the Fed for second life?
I'd like to know about it. And I'd like to say just a little bit more about second life.
Actually, let me play this comment for you, and then I'll give you my viewpoint on it.
I had a much of their caution in San Francisco, and I thought I'd give you a call because I heard you talking about second life,
and how you like it so much. Now, I'm in second life too, but I gotta tell you, it is an evil game.
Not just gaming is bad. You know, that's not bad, but second life is bad.
When you've been in it for a while, you'll start noticing that there are people who are married,
that are breaking up because of second life,
there are people who are becoming psychologically disturbed because of second life.
They take it too seriously. It's called second life.
And a lot of people, a lot of people are using it to try and replace their first life,
and you can't do that. And I know I've seen that happen with the ton of people
that are on my friends list there. It gets nuts.
So I thought I'd have to add my team San Francisco, and don't live your life on a computer.
Get up and take a walk once in a while. Trust me, you'll thank me for it one day.
Right. So here's what I want to say about this.
We're dealing with the next generation user interface right now.
The three most common ones we have in our lives are Windows XP at this moment.
Macintosh, of course, that's a much smaller percentage.
Very similar type of user interfaces.
And then there's Linux, which has KDE and all kinds of all folder-based hierarchical, hierarchical,
desktop systems, filing systems, really.
And second life is some powerful ass mojo, because it is, in my mind, I see it as an interface.
An interface which you can do, you have tremendous power over.
Really, you can do all kinds of amazing things, particularly if you want to do something collaborative.
To me, no different than fire.
Fire was invented. Fire is very powerful ass mojo.
You can draw your clothes to it. You can stay just a warm through the winter.
You can cook food on it, but you can also get your ass burnt to a crisp.
And that's the part that you're missing.
And I truly believe that the powerful mojo part of this is because we are so used to watching television screens.
And seeing little tiny figures in the box do stuff to actually have control over that.
The virtual reality, your brain parses that as reality.
And guess what? The people are actually having very human-like responses in reaction.
So it's definitely something that you have to be very, very careful with.
And for those of you who are adults, and of course second life, I think the only interesting part of second life is the main grid.
We're no teenagers or kids are allowed.
You know, now just for a second think about what your kids have been doing and what's been happening with their minds as they're playing grand theft auto or any other of the Murriad of Xbox 360 games.
Okay? Powerful mojo ladies and gentlemen.
Hello there, Mr. correct. Just a quick comment.
A bit of our second life and a bit of our second life and a bit of our second life.
And life is allowed to crap when you first start talking about it, but I've been on a bottle look.
I quite like it. And he's right. This thing about, you know, it's not real life, obviously.
But it's a, it adds that extra dimension because you know, I'm sort of the top of your castle.
There were a few of the people there. I thought, I should have been there.
Then I saw you sat down in a chair chilling out and thought, this is a bit weird.
I've just liked London on someone's roof and it did feel awkward.
So I didn't say anything to you.
And I just bugged off, I was somewhere else.
But not before, funny enough, a chat by the name of comic senior added me to his friends list.
You all guess as good as mine.
But anyway, I've got a great idea.
Now, I don't know if you can have an audio stream in the air in second life.
I presume not because I've not heard any.
But when you can, this is a brilliant opportunity for pod save music.
What about?
Now, you're talking about a pod save concerts.
Like the being in the same style as the BBC thing.
But what about pod save live music jams?
You could even have second life virtual bands,
where people sat down playing their instruments into the computer.
What do the users here?
And you can basically have a full band live jump without leaving the house.
Without paying any rehearsal fees or anything.
You could even make it.
So you have a virtual pod save music band.
Now, come on, let's go to the earth doing it.
Anyway, keep it up to see you later.
Yeah.
I was not funny about it in south of England.
Coops in the earth, where the young man live.
Oh, come to the north with a real man live.
You sound like that guy and you stenders.
What's the guy's name?
Who's the friend, the jailbird friend?
Up at the north.
We know how to drink.
Won't work.
Second life is only as good.
It's just an interface sitting on top of the internet.
So everything that can be done underneath can be done in second life.
Just in a very easy to manage collaborative fashion.
This is not really even possible today.
And in fact, a lot of this jamming and stuff is very overrated for second life.
You know, it's just an audio stream or a video stream.
And you can have some avatars coordinated, you know, bang and away.
It's great.
But I think, you know, maybe just have that as a visual.
But then you have an opportunity to go chat with the artist later.
That is what's going to be exciting.
I forgot what you said before that about second life.
Yeah.
Okay.
Powerful stuff.
But in fact, the linden corporation should actually have a disclaimer when you log in.
They really should.
They should be smart about that.
Just put the disclaimer up now because it's true.
And I'd love to hear from any of the psychologists or doctors who work with the
brain and with the human mind.
If you could weigh in on this topic, because I think it's it's totally dangerous.
If not, if not handled with care by professionals, dammit.
And please don't send in the comment that says, yeah, everyone's getting sucked in.
I just, I'd like to hear from a real from a scientific perspective if possible at all.
Hey, we got to take a short break for the sad light folks.
As I said, we're doing a 49er today.
So you'll hear some commercials, which serious is lined up for you.
And shoot.
We'll do something else.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
Where are flink?
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers.
We believe your personal information should be just that personal.
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a fo.
Where are flink?
To make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
Tired of that commercial?
Good.
Because we're going to let you create your own commercial, coming soon.
The pod show edge challenge.
Sponsored by Earthlink.
I got a big sense of standing by.
Hey Adam, Neil here from the pod safe revolution podcast.
You know, show that I've really become addicted to lately.
Apart from the Charlie, of course, is Steve runner in his
for depudations.
I thought I'd let you know that I made the 28th.
I'll be running in the ING National Capital Marathon in Ottawa, Ontario, Canada.
And over the last 20 weeks, running more than 1,000 kilometers in training.
I've really become sick and tired of the music on my iPod.
So I had an idea.
To do my show, I've created what I'd like to call the open source playlist.
And the goal of this, of course, is to create the first truly pod safe music marathon.
That's 26.2 miles, 42 kilometers, or roughly 3 hours and 20 minutes of amazing pod safe music.
So what do you do?
Email us at the show.
PodsafeRevolution.com with any artist bands or songs.
Of course, that are pod safe that you think I would like to hear while I run.
Words of encouragement are encouraged.
So, you know, maybe some words of wisdom from the Lady Patricia around
Mile 23, or maybe even Adam Curry Cowbell Remix of his favorite pod safe song around
Mile 24.
Oh, man.
Wouldn't it be great if you had Patricia in your ear buds and she'll describe it that she's
OK, I'm touching the guys now.
I'm motivating you.
Wouldn't that be cool?
Anything like that.
Just talk to her about that tomorrow.
For an example, the first song that was added to the playlist this week was Black
Labs learned to crawl.
Anything in that vein, anything that you think would help you get through a marathon
yourself.
Email us.
PodsafeRevolution.atgmail.com.
Also, check out the show in iTunes to search for pod safe revolution.
Now, it can't say tailwinds, but I'm going to say heelwinds.
Thanks, Adam.
Cheers, man.
Yeah, great idea.
And I'm going to have Richard Brewer hey from Pod Show.
Give you a call because we started a running channel.
And we got a lot of the same ideas.
It would be great if we could work together like the very much.
Yes, dear.
I will leave with my mom now and go shopping a little bit.
Okay.
I wasn't allowed to go earlier because she said I had to do my bed first.
Yeah, to make it your mom made you make up your bed first.
I couldn't leave the house.
57 years old.
She's telling me what to do.
Right.
And your dad standing behind her with a fucking power tool.
Yeah.
Make your bed.
Can you imagine I'm sweating?
No, no, you're perspiring.
You don't sweat, my dear.
She said, I said, mom, let's go.
I'm going to call taxi.
No, you didn't do your bed.
Yeah, that's good.
Hey, so tomorrow will you come on the show?
Yeah, okay.
And then I want to talk about the Eurovision song contest.
All right.
I want to talk about Paul McCartney.
And I don't want to talk about your breasts as usual.
If you don't mind, that'd be okay.
All right.
All righty.
Are you leaving now?
You're calling the cabinet.
See you later.
Bye.
Adios.
Muchachas.
Bye-bye.
Hi, Adam.
This is Jen from bucketpodcast.com or Madison Carnell and Second Life.
One of the call to tell you that I met you in Second Life last night.
And I told you that I've left you a voicemail from work, which I did.
And Adam, your reaction was not to say that school or great to hear from you.
Your exact quote was, was it naughty?
So Adam, a promise I would call you and leave you a naughty voice no message.
And I guess it's going to have to wait for another time.
I just had to tell you.
Was it naughty?
Seriously.
Did you have anything else, man?
And I'll leave you the naughty one later.
Bye, Adam.
Jen.
Listen.
I'll tell you why.
And you know, because I come up onto the roof of the castle in the virtual world
known as Second Life, which I call a very powerful Asmojo user interface.
And you know, you say it's Jen.
And I heard your comment.
And you know what?
It was boring because you call up.
You say, hi, I'm calling you from the office.
And you just go on.
All you do is you plug your show.
You know, do something fun or entertaining.
You know, just do something different, except hey, it's great.
I'm here in your show and here's a plug from my show.
I'm not interested in that.
That's all.
I was just giving you some guidelines.
You could do something funny.
You could do anything that's just more entertaining.
I'm just going to use a suggestion because I thought you had a great voice for saying
naughty things.
Just have some fun.
That's all.
I apologize.
Don't take it out.
I'll be personally now.
Coming May 27th.
The Ed's Mixed Bag Podcast presents the country music marathon.
And just in time for the Memorial Day weekend, why not put the entire episode
on your iPod and let the folks at your barbecue here at.
Don't own an iPod?
No problem.
Burn it to a CDR.
Take it along.
12 of the best country pod safe music network artists will each perform one of their exciting songs.
No promos, no chitchat, three sets of four songs.
Back to back.
After each set, a brief bio from the PMN profile page and the artist's name and song title.
So join me your host Ed Ovet.
For a Memorial Day weekend filled with the sounds of a country song on Saturday, May 27th.
Download it at idzmixbag.com.
Thanks for listening.
I love the country music on the pod set music network.
In fact, a lot is happening with the most driving pleasure.
Drive at sensible speed.
Be courteous.
And obey traffic regulation.
It may save a life.
Possibly.
Get lots of great feedback.
And I really had no.
I've played a couple songs.
Particularly yesterday.
Yes, they kept cutie.
And getting some awesome feedback on it.
And when I say awesome, I'm talking about a hundred different emails.
Hey, Adam, I'm listening to Wednesday's Charlie.
And I know that you're playing a song by Death Cat for Cutie, which is a very, very, you know,
a popular band.
And so I'm a little surprised.
But the fact they're on the PMT and then I'm so just excited.
But the fact that labels are actually jumping on board now.
So I just artists and labels are putting artists.
I think I'd never find the pot to pot to take me to network on there.
I'm like, wow.
So this whole pod says thing man.
It's really working.
So you have to go right.
Right.
Yeah.
That's the work of CC Chapman and Michael Butler.
And of course, the smart record labels are on to this.
They're like, okay, we get it.
And they're doing it.
And it's a working.
And I said this morning to Christine.
And I said, you know, I got a lot of comments about this deathcat
for Cutie.
She says, yeah, that's great.
I've known them.
And she rattled off five more names.
I said, where?
Come on.
Man, I'll engineer it.
Let's do your podcast.
I'm so ready for it.
By the way, every single song that we play from the podcast,
music network on the daily source code.
We ramp up towards our full release.
We'll be made available for purchase free and clear MP3s.
No digital rights management.
It stays in your accounts.
So you can always go back and download it again.
You could copy it for a friend.
And of course, you'd hope that that friend would buy it if they liked it.
To support the artist.
99 cents of which 90 cents goes to the artist.
9 cents goes to the the processing company that does the transaction.
Potio takes nothing proud to help with the pod safe music revolution.
And it's really kicking some ass.
Hey, Adam.
This is Chris from the randomly wired podcast in beautiful El Paso, Texas.
I was listening to your Monday edition of DSC and heard your intro with the new release for
Bank of Jones.
And I thought that was pretty cool because I had just gotten in touch with Stephanie from their American
Record label.
And had just told her how it was Jones.
And for a new track on the pot safe music network because I had gotten some good response
from some friends here in El Paso and actually heard first day on Kaylee Q and just not
man, that's awesome.
I hope we put a new track out.
So I sent her an email and she responded with the new track online on the 12th of May.
So when I heard it on DSC, I just thought, man, that's so cool.
I just got in touch with the record label.
Ask them for a new track to be put on the pot safe music network and learn the whole
run your show on Monday.
I hear the song.
I love podcasting.
I love this.
Keep up the good work and if anybody else wants to check out my podcast, check us out at randomly
wired.logspot.com.
I have a good one and we'll talk to you soon.
And dude, don't think that didn't do it.
That's very possible.
You're called, made that happen.
Everyone should do that.
If you hear of a band that you love, you want to get them in.
If the record label needs to talk into.
If you need any help, contact CC Chapman or Michael Butler would be happy to hook you up
and do whatever it takes to get you in.
And I made a mistake that I want to apologize for.
I said, hey, this idea of best of Charlie's or the DSC rewind.
I like best of Charlie is maybe the best title to be run over the weekend.
So I said, hey, what a great idea.
And of course, there's now three people who have produced best of Charlie's.
And the mistake I made is I don't have any of the infrastructure in place to do what
I should do.
And that's put this on a different podcast feed.
Because when I put it into the regular DSC, a lot of people didn't like that.
So I'd like you to not create any more DSCs or best rewines or best of Charlie's.
Until we get the PDN up and running fully in the open.
Which only be, you know, it's coming.
It's coming very soon.
Because the wise had to start up a new WordPress blog and just become.
It becomes very complicated.
Whereas you can really just manage that thing.
You can have the best of feed.
And we could have three of them if you want.
And I also said it to the Jeff Smith.com who is so wonderful at always.
Always working on something to help me out in the show.
So once we do actually get it running, get ready to snip this out of the show.
So you can use it for your best of Charlie or your rewind.
Because Jeff, of course, has made jingle all about it.
That's why everyone gather around and head into a party.
Get your buzz and jam a man is the best.
On the Charlie talking to the best on the Charlie.
Yeah, that's the DSC.
That's the best on the Charlie with Adam Curry.
Come on, now's the best on the Charlie.
Better than the rest.
The best on the Charlie.
Come on, now hit, now come on.
I'm on that talking man here now.
Here now what you see.
Here now.
That's the best of the Charlie.
Best of the Charlie.
Charlie.
Hello.
Okay.
You could snip it out.
I left a little bit of white space before and after that.
Thank you very much, Jeff.
For those of you that sent me feedback and emails,
Gmail's about a virgins plea.com.
Yeah, it was a hoax.
If you go to the website now, if you're only just hearing that episode,
if you only just heard that episode of the Daily source code,
you know that it was a hoax.
Okay.
So I fell for it.
I thought it was pretty convincing.
It was done pretty well.
It was an experiment in viral marketing.
Okay.
It worked.
Hey, Adam.
This is Robert head.
Leave me a message.
You don't have to put this on the air in there or anything.
This isn't for.
I don't need to plug my show or anything.
That's always the wrong thing to say to me as you don't need to put it on the show.
You know it's going on the show when you say that.
Before my golden ticket that I heard a week or so go on the dead cast,
number three.
And I'm checking out the beta pod show site.
And it's great.
And I just want to leave a message and say thanks to all the folks at
Pod Show and Kevin and that other lovely lady that was on your last
Devcast show.
Oh, Aaron.
Looking forward to the next Devcast.
And I'm joining Pod Show.
All right.
Next one.
Bye.
Thank you.
And I believe we'll do another Devcast tonight as I got email from Andrew and Kevin
K.O.
K1 that the SDK, the software developers kit is now complete and ready.
So I think that's really good news.
Adam.
This is Tom from Michigan.
I'm a regular listener of the Charlie.
I just had to send you some feedback on this all this talk of Neural and
The Negligistic Programming lately.
Mason, come on.
Mister, ego here.
So I'm quite familiar with NLP or Neural & Guistic Programming.
In fact, San SAU.
The San SAU on the burp is a textbook example of Neural & Guistic Programming and
it's worked on, well, let me just say conservatively, tens of thousands of
daily source code listeners hold on a minute, tens of thousands.
Me, you've got a great show in all.
But come on, even the pod father doesn't wield that kind of power.
I mean, no matter how far in, I stick my earbuds when I'm listening to your show.
I just don't see that. Oh, sense sale.
Oh, man.
I don't see.
You're supposed to stick it in your ear.
Not in your rear.
I'm sticking stick it in your ear.
I don't know, you know, I lost my transplant.
Anyways.
You know what, I think I made my point.
No.
Great work, man.
Great show.
Later.
I don't know what your point is, man.
Definitely 10.
Sticks in here.
Definitely.
Please, light a match.
Definitely 10s of thousands.
Hey, Adam, this is Thomas Carolina.
I just got to say, you got this in sale.
Think down to an art.
Now when you belt.
I think it's in sale and say it's in sale.
I look to see who belts.
So I guess the psychology things work and give up good show.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Not only is it working, but I'm investigating something very peculiar.
There was an advertising industry magazine that interviewed an advertising executive who claimed
claimed that it was his idea to come up with a sense say a burp neural linguistic programming.
And I've gotten a lot of email and we've actually reached out to this company a couple times and not getting any response.
And said, hey, what's the deal?
You know, if anything, you know that this is not paid.
It's my reputation at stake.
Me, Adam Curry's reputation.
I'm not getting paid to do this and say crap at all.
So those of you who keep emailing me about that and asking what's going on were working on it.
I just, you know, I want to be a little journalistic about this because it could be that the person who wrote the article is just full of crap and made it up.
That's very possible.
I'm not put it past any any publication to, you know, it could be an honest mistake or an assumption or whatever, but it's certainly not true.
It could also be that someone is trying to claim that.
So we'll get you the bottom of it.
I promise you.
If not, I'm going to send a matchup.
I don't think he's done me any harm at all.
If anything, it's probably told me as few manners.
By for now, I'm not going to do this.
I don't think he's done me any harm at all.
If anything, it's probably told me as few manners.
It's fine for now.
Roger, it seems like you're catching up on all the old episodes.
Don't worry about it, man.
Don't want you not to respond to all that episode.
It's catch up.
Get current, William.
And comic strip blogger just briefly yesterday he, I mentioned,
who I played a piece from comic strip blogger.
He'd called up LBC London Radio Station and was mentioning my name and getting the host to talk about me.
And it was funny.
And I said, I'd pay him 500 second life Linden Dollars, which is the virtual currency use there, which is,
will probably be worth about 50 Linden Dollars by the end of the year.
According to Chris Ben from the Financial Aid podcast.
And I said, you know, I'll pay you every single time you mention my name on a show.
And here's his response, which you posted at curry.com.
He said, regarding your, I should do the voice.
Regarding your offer for $500,000.
No.
You know that you can't get me through money real or virtual.
I have a feeling, by the way, that CSB is independently wealthy, but I could be wrong.
However, if Brittany, that's my partner, my sexy girlfriend in the second life,
if Brittany from second life would agree to do one hour naked dancing at the CSB labs for myself and other visitors watching pleasure
for each mention of Adam Curry on British radio, then I can go for that deal.
Ask Brittany if she agrees.
Let me know by email.
Dude, you are so off base, man.
Brittany will kick your ass just for seeing that dang.
Hello Adam Curry.
This is comic strip blogger's penis.
Yes, I also call the balls that hang out with me dudes.
The one on the left, I also call him Kurt Loder.
Because he is gray and wrinkly.
And the one on the right, I sometimes call Adam Curry.
And sometimes I just call him Bill, just for fun.
But anyway, Adam Curry, I hope someday that I can meet you in person.
And maybe I can kiss you.
Or you will kiss me.
Yes, yes, Adam Curry.
This is comic strip blogger's penis.
I'm afraid I have to go.
I think we thank too much coffee.
Bye bye.
The voice mail lines in New Jersey 201 6563 57 in London 020 76813753.
Derek J. Steen says yo Adam.
I'm hosting pod tea for cancer during May.
And I've got an audio comment about it for you.
I would love if you could play it on the DSC Jeff Smith made an awesome song for the event too.
I believe he even sang you an email about it.
Well, yes, he did.
In some letterly water, the search is gone out for the soldier's seat.
Is the world's biggest morning scene.
You have a cup with me.
Good morning.
Howdy Adam, this is Derek from Senior Australia.
I'm hosting the Ponte for cancer, which denies my inter the world's biggest morning tea.
And not for profit foundation, which raises money for the cancer council of Australia.
and cancer research of course is shared worldwide so this is an event that everyone
can benefit from. The official day to have a morning tea is the 25th of May but you
can donate till the end of May from now to the end of May and on the 25th of
May I am going to have a very very special morning tea which anyone in the world
can be included on live through Skype and if you are having a morning tea at the same
time between 8 a.m. and 10 30 a.m. Australian Eastern Standard Time you can be included
in the Guinness Book of Records as being included in the world's biggest simultaneous morning
tea which last year this cause got the award like the Guinness World Record for that.
So this year we're going to get it again and it's going to be more worldwide because
PODT for Cancer Man you can also donate by buying the official PODT for Cancer
which you can get links to from my website nothing pod showed at bugspot.com
and the five dollar profit from that goes to PODT for Cancer and so do all the other
profits from the other mercenesses my shop. There's a great cause and I'm very excited about it.
You can find out more from my website nothing pod showed at bugspot.com
so you take care now peace out.
Excellent. It's like full Collins man. Jeff Smith is so talented. I hate you.
Hey I'm totally in. So 8 a.m. Australian time would be last night 7 p.m. UK time. I think
you gotta give me more times. I can't figure it up on myself anymore. To wind it up for
today and remember tomorrow the lovely lady Patricia will be on the show. An email from
Michael Applant. I think it's Laplante or Laplante. Here from Windsor on Terry or Canada where I
listen to the Charlie every day will on the assembly line at Dameler Chrysler's Windsor assembly
plant. We've built minivans and Pacificas. I listen to DSC number 387 where you played another
tune by Canadian Danko Jones. Great job. They really deserve all the success that comes
their way. I've been listening to them for the past eight years. Anyway you ask your listeners
for more suggestions of pod save music to play. You may have heard of the band The Famous because
they're out of Sam Fran. I know you got a pad there. I first heard them on the Roots Rock
radio podcast which by the way was recently favorably reviewed and Rolling Stone magazine.
The tunes I'd recommend you play on the Charlie would be get you back lost or mid-white.
You can find these songs of the pod save music network. And it goes on to say I originally
purchased the CD Light Sweet Crewed on the iTunes Music Store and I've been playing it regularly.
I love it as I'm sure your listeners will do as well. Mike, thank you very much. I appreciate
actually I had put this song in my playlist for a future spin. And the reason why I
recognized immediately after I played this song a preview to before starting the show. It's the first
line of the lyrics.
It's now magic. It's just a fool. The developer here is just a ring toss away.
I'm a mid-white, I'm a mid-white, I'm a mid-white, I'm a mid-white, I'm a mid-white, I'm a mid-white,
I've never left high and get a senior world's wallet oversteer. What were anything
perr ustedes saying?
And it's going to take me home before ten o'clock. I will wash my face I'll never do my homework.
Can you call this fear mark? What will it sound so fairリ?
I was in lost, I met you at the boots just all you said to do Big Texas like what?
Seven stories tall? What did you expect?
Fill off the ride, home the midway Fill off the ride, home the midway
I nearly died, home the midway Fill off the ride, home the midway
I had one of those, I had a ZZ Top key chain, the guys gave to me when I interviewed them a thousand years ago, fantastic, the famous and midway winding up the Charlie for Thursday
I'll be back tomorrow everybody, at amaccurry.com and dailysourcecode.com for 20
Another pod show podcast, stick it in your ear
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from podshow and line-light networks