This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want to hear content with us at Ask domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 3-8-0
The following is an actual pod star conversation.
May 1st 2006.
Pod star emergency.
This is Adam.
I'm still going to stop late.
And the guy we're currently coming next to me is listening to corporate radio
So loud.
I can't hear my favorite pod cast.
Okay sir, try not to panic.
I've just called in an air strike from the pod father.
Bad things happen to people who listen to bad radio.
Is everything all right now sir?
Yes, yes.
Thank you.
Oh, bless you.
Pod star.
Tell us where bad radio lives.
And we'll make sure it's gone.
This name is Adam Curry.
He's always in a very moving wheel.
Right up.
Right through Ask domain.
Straight top.
Sorry.
His name is Adam Curry.
And go ahead.
Vision.
Glory.
The old song.
Dog there.
And keep free.
And hang home for his name is Adam Curry.
His name is Adam Curry.
And Adam Curry.
He was 16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic.
It's Adam Curry.
I'm flying into the future.
I didn't have a way to say
Been attached to a hole
From all we have a surprise
It's ready to settle down
Maybe get some kids in the wild
And it's a lie
When it wins, can we rise?
There's a way to write
What's in this life?
When it wins, can we rise?
There's a way to write
What's in this life?
When it wins, can we rise?
There's a way to write
What's in this life?
When it wins, can we rise?
There's a way to write
I'll be the one, I'll be the one
It's time to miss me
There's a way to write
When it wins, can we rise?
What's in this life?
There's a way to write
When it wins, can we rise?
Good
It's a way to write
It's important
I want to give you a review of last night
John Collins
And evening with John Collins
I've got to tell you, thoroughly and press
We had a great time
It was about an hour south, an hour's drive south of here in lots of them
Which is very famous, very nice acquaintance
historic. Look really good. And we didn't mind driving for an hour and we had, you know,
it's always fun, just the two of us. And oh, man, isn't nice that our daughter can now kind of
hold down the fort alone. For those of you who are parents who have reached that stage where
you trust your kid to stay home and not let, you know, murderers and rapists in and not burn
down the house. You know what I'm talking about. We had forgotten. Now, first of all, this theater,
the Guild Hall, it probably holds about, I don't know, maybe four or five hundred people.
I don't think there were more than 200 people there. So it was nice and cozy, nice, small
intimate atmosphere. We had forgotten to mention yesterday that opening up for Joan Collins was the
infamous quartet who perform every Friday night on Jonathan Ross's talk show here in the UK,
which is, uh, I think a great show and it's a, it's a big hit. It sends sail, everybody.
Um, they're called forpuffs in a piano. And it's exactly what it sounds like forpuffs in a piano.
And I hope we don't have to get into explaining what the word puff means in the UK.
And they always have these great comedic skits and they have little jingle-like songs kind of,
I'd have to say, uh, in a way they're kind of like Jeff Smith, uh, although I think Jeff is
musically better and certainly sings better. Uh, but they have, you know, cool little lyrics and
little, uh, little fun things for every guest that comes on. And they opened up and it was
fantastic. We laughed our ass off. You know, if you're, if you're, if you're no that kind of, uh, a gay comedic review
type stuff, then you would have really loved it. Um, and it was, these guys were really sweet, you know,
after they're done like 45 minutes set. They said, okay, we'll be in the foyer. You can buy our CD,
which, uh, we still have 15,000 copies of, no one ever bought it. And I understand why, because of course
he went into the foyer. We bought their CD. They were, you know, handling the money themselves.
It's just amazing. It goes to show, you know, you think these guys are on TV every single week
on a huge show and, and they're really grovelin to make ends meet. Um, uh, and Patricia immediately
jumped. Oh, I want to picture with these guys. So snap to pick you. Probably have already seen that
on curry.com. If not, check it out. It's, uh, four poofs in a Patricia is what I, uh, titled the
picture. We listened to the CD on the way home. Oh, so disappointing. Actually, I bought both
their CDs at a Christmas CD and whatever their other CD was. None of it was any of the comedic
skits. It was all like, you know, real gay party songs. You know, YMCA, I will survive and really
poorly produced and just the crap, total crap, which is unfortunate because there's so funny
on stage. And then it was time. The diva herself came out, Joan Collins. Now, um, let me set the stage
foyer. So we're only like four rows of weight. It was almost like a high school play. This is how
this, this, this, this, this theater was, it was situated built. And, you know, probably if I spit
hard enough, like I could have reached her, her shoes, mine I add, by the way, Joan Collins has
I mean, awesome, awesome looking shoes, really nice shoes, just something I wanted to say. The whole
outfit, the whole woman is, she does have a nice, a very nice persona. Oh, or I, I've always enjoyed.
And she's 70 by now. She never gives reveals her age, but she's about 70 Patricia has, uh, it
on reliable information. These old broads, you know. So what it was is essentially kind of a
multi-media walk through her career. Huge screen of three different sets on stage. So a classic
chair, a telephone set, you know, just little props that she could walk to to complete the story.
And start soft, of course, with, you know, with dynasty. And then she walks on stage and,
uh, big needle scratch, stop the dynasty. There's a lot more. And it's really interesting because
this is something that you see with celebrities a lot. People who've become famous for, or really
super ultra famous for one thing, uh, but have really have a huge body of work behind them.
And actually after that, the stuff that they became famous for. So of course, we all know
Joan Collins from Dynasty, but man, she, she's done a lot of stuff. She's been in some super
huge movies, theatrical productions, television shows, and some really crap stuff. And she made
a great fun of herself. Now, the thing that really pissed me off. Within 30 seconds of her walking
on stage, I leaned over to Patricia and I said, her wireless mic is going to crap out. I can hear it
right now. It's an antenna positioning. I don't know what it is. And sure enough, within like a minute,
every single time she sat on the chair, the audio would cut out. Now, here's what's on
forts. So first of all, that really breaks your concentration when you're listening to someone
under into the story. But she is approaching this very much from an actress point of view. It's all
scripted. Um, the everything she says is consistent. I'm sure, uh, the, uh, the pictures and videos
are triggered by someone offstage, clearly, uh, to go along with the story. So whenever, you know,
if the mic cut out and, and I was happening to me, I would have broken the script and I would have
done something and made sure that that got fixed. So throughout the entire hour and 15 hour and
20 minutes, there were at least five or six moments where you could just, you cringe because all
sudden, then all you hear is her voice. And by the way, she still projects very well, but it just
sucks, sucks, sucks. I would, I want to kill the audio guy. That was such a bummer. Um, but good,
it was really entertaining and it was fun to learn about. She had some great stories about
Elizabeth Taylor, uh, about, uh, you know, the Swiftie Lazar, her longtime agent, uh, just about the
Hollywood days of old and his fantastic to listen to. And I thoroughly, thoroughly enjoyed myself.
I had a great time. And I know Patricia did too. And on the way home, it was, uh, we had a great
drive back, uh, except for, you know, when I skimmed through all 13 of the gay disco tracks from the
four post of the piano, I was just sucked. And then I threw out my 145 classics. And we just kind
of cruise on still with the, uh, with the vibe in the memory of, of Joan Collins's story. It was really,
it was cool. I have, I have to say. It's nothing that I don't think, uh, it's something that could
make it to, uh, to a London stage, or to, uh, you know, or Broadway. It's definitely not that quality.
And also, she should be triggering the, the, the events herself, kind of like the weatherman that
would have made it much easier. If, if I were producing it, uh, but it was good. So we enjoyed it.
And it was funny because when I got home, we were home around 1130. Uh, I, I teleported into the, uh,
into the, uh, into the castle. Um, now when I teleport into the castle, people can't see me, but I can
still hear them. And I was literally hearing the campground out front people saying, yeah,
I wonder how Joan Collins was. So it was a little too late for me to get into the whole, uh,
whole review last night. So I teleported out. And, uh, yeah, good times, good times. If, if you have a
chance, I think they have 10 more dates if you're in the UK. And by the way, Portsmouth nice,
very nice. I think we should go back there during the day and see what Portsmouth has to offer.
Lots of, uh, voicemail coming in responses, uh, appreciate your use of the phone lines in Jersey 2016256357
in the UK in London, O2O76813753. And then just pour it in.
Hey, Adam, this is George Ramchino, man. Hey, there are these two guys who are working
in the prison laundry. And they say your hair wasn't as cool as Ricky Rackman. So I stabbed
them in the exercise yard with a knife by me from a spoon handle. Hey, just one man,
there were a couple of new guys on a said block. And one of them kind of looks like you.
And from behind, if you know what I mean, he lets me stroke his hair, which is nice because
it reminds me of the chop chop. And man, you know what's crazy? No, he's thinker.
Look, he's just like her loader. Uh-oh. Oh, man, I got to go. I think one of those very
innation guys just bought me for a carton of lucky strikes. I'd better go do my stretchy so
I don't pull a hammy. I'll catch you later, man. Mr. chop chop. Peace out.
Oh, yes, our friends from prison. Glad that we're making a difference for you guys
on the inside. Incoming subs-based. We have to.
Hey, everyone. Hey, Adam. This is Rev Tim from the Rev Tim podcast.
My second annual Mother's Day Special is coming out right around the corner. And I
wanted to give a shout out to all the source code listeners because I believe that the source code
has one of the largest audiences, as well as some of the most diverse people around the world.
What a great audience that you have. I love to hear all your comments all the time. But the
second annual Mother's Day Special, I need your audience, Adam, if you could ask them to put together
a very special show that will actually go on the Rev Tim podcast. And here's what I need.
I need people to email me audio comments to Rev Tim podcast at jmail.com. That's Rev Tim podcast all
one word at jmail.com or just pick up a telephone and call area code 815 301-8600. That's the
godcast.org audio comment line. And we're going to put together a very, very special Mother's Day
program at the Rev Tim podcast. Hey, you guys have a wonderful day. Adam, say hi to the family,
yo Patricia, yo Christina, and yo to the back garden. Hey, you guys have a good time. And Adam,
one of these days when you're in the Bay Area, hey, look me up. I'll buy you a cup of coffee and we'll
hang for a while. Take care and God bless. Rev Tim, everybody. Of course, celebrations for Mother's Day,
only US, only I believe, as we've already had Mother's Day here in the UK. I celebrated on US
time for my mom. I'm going to go see your Saturday again, by the way. She's doing much better. She
actually went to my sister's son's birthday party, which meant like a 45-minute car trip. Of course,
Bob drove her. And she's feeling good. Her buddy Gloria came over for she lives in Pennsylvania.
And she stayed for a couple days. And so the spirit is there. And that's what that's what really
really counts and makes a difference. And so I'll see if I can whip something up. She's, you know,
my mom doesn't really listen to podcasts. I got her the, you know, the groovy laptop,
which she uses all the time. But I don't know, she, I don't think she wants to make time to listen
to podcasts. By the way, you know, fantastic comments for Patricia. People really loved yesterday's show.
What was interesting? Well, two points really. One is that just about every single comment that
came in about second life was on Patricia's side, which is interesting because I still see it a
little bit differently. I even got friends of mine saying, hey, man, you've got to watch yourself.
You know, you're going to get sucked in and we don't want to lose you. I think it makes a difference
if you have a purpose. You know, if you're just in there to either fight or have sex or walk around
and stuff, yeah, you can get lost. But still, you know, what difference, if you're giving up your
television time, if you'd normally watch TV for an hour and a half or two hours, this is totally
better than that. You know, you write your own script. The script goes as it goes along as you do.
You just have to be able to unplug people get addicted to TV, too. So I'm with you on that. And too
much of anything, obviously, is never going to be good. But now I got to tell you, I've been sending
these, you know, Patricia has never been into computers or the internet until I set up the the
I, the G5, I'm back in the kitchen. And now I catch her all the time, man. She's like reading
comments. She's doing email. And yesterday, she actually let, uh, she actually let a piece of
chicken burn because she was preoccupied with stuff other than what she normally would do. So we
got to keep our eye on her, too. You know what I'm saying? I add them. This is Susie calling from
Dublin in Ireland. I just wanted to say how great it was to hear Patricia on the show today. When I
first heard that she was going to be on the show and I went, oh, thanks. There will be no talk
about second life then. And wrong I was. But then. Oh, I got to, I love that. You were just
like the lucky charm, Leprechaun when you said it. Oh, goody. They'll be no talk about second life then.
But we know talk about second life then. And wrong I was. But then I agreed with most of us
Patricia was saying. So that's it. We off no end. And I really enjoyed listening to the show
that I look forward to the other information about podcasts and things like that. And I really
get me into listening to why it's for I see a podcast. Anyway, keep Patricia coming on the show
was a guest and really enjoy it. And I have information as I try some stuff which I was sent to
Patricia by email. That's okay. All right, then take care. Bye. Thank you very much, last love it very
much. Yeah, lots of people sending in arthritis information. That's cool Patricia just said,
if I took everyone's advice said, I wouldn't have to eat food anymore. Just be in pills and
other stuff and remedies. But she's going to try it. You know, as I said, she's in touch with
herself and touch with nature. She is a white witch. So she'll evaluate it. You know, my mom
actually said that she should carry two chestnuts in her pocket. Apparently that works too. But
there is no sure fire remedy. That's one thing that is definitely for sure. So I do have to hit you
with a little bit of second life talk because it is a part of my first life no matter what you say.
Michelle Bellasky sent a Gmail to me. He says, you know, I don't know if there were others who
bumbleed upon your neighbor's yards and a quest to find yours. But I know that at least I did and
I want to apologize. It was certainly nothing malicious intended. It was simply a matter of not
being able to fly very well yet and also not very clear on how to get my bearings in the world.
Quite simply, I got lost. I ended up on your neighbor's patio. Someone came out, asked me what I was
looking for. They told me how to get there and I was on my way after perfuse apologies. The problem
came in by the fact that they were having sex at the time I popped in. I really feel bad.
Initially, I thought it was quite brilliant of you that people had to fly to your place for the
landmark where they get deposited, quite fitting. But then you have people like me who don't know
how to fly so well, I want to say all I know is that for any future parties you may have there,
I remarked the landmark to indicate the front door spots. So I'll never again appear on any
neighbor's doorsteps. Well, we're going to move any future parties which are going to be
structured. It's great to be hanging out and I really like it. It's cool to just drop in. It's a
way for me to communicate with people who listen to the show. Listeners podcasts, there's a
like, but it's bad for the neighborhood. What is the podcast? Is that building next to me
really from the podcast pickle guys? How obnoxious is that thing, man? Don't.
So the pod show palace coming along quite nicely, quite nicely. In fact, I'm looking for
scriptures and animators. So this is real life stuff. I'm looking for scriptures and animators
who can help out with this project that I'm working on, which I think will fit seamlessly
into what we're doing in real life and podcast. And it'll just give us an extra dimension.
You know, not trying to hook you on crack or anything, but it could happen. So if you're
and you know, think, what is it to machine him up? Is that what they call it? You know,
where you create videos from second life? Think that. Think about, you know, great animations.
Think about, you know, scriptures who, and I've looked at the scripting language for second life.
It seems, it doesn't actually seem all that rich. You know, there's some, there's some good
stuff in there, but could do with a lot more. But if you're interested, fire off an email to pod show
palace at gmail.com. So scriptures and animators experience in second life, please, only, and send
it off to pod show palace at gmail.com. Yeah, I'm sorry. I haven't been by the castle, but then
too busy between my two pod cast and the show I have coming up to really hang out in the old
SL, but I did drop by really briefly the other day. And two guys were in there wearing their
matching pod show shirts and jeans and put tops in the same hairdo. And one of them asked me,
oh, are you Adam's mistress? The one who doesn't play the cello? So I don't know,
I'm weird. I was like, yeah, I guess it looks like I am. Anyway, hopefully I don't know next week.
Angie, what are you saying? Are you my mistress now all of a sudden?
I didn't know you played the cello, secretly. So there you'll be able to see you again, but I
did want to mention that I found out about how to get audio into the game. I can use my nice
cast to bring a stream in. So I could either DJ or sing or whatever else. And you could
DJ too over at the castle. So just have something to do with using nice cast or whatever else to
get into your little audio service in the doodle. So I'm sure you can ask around and find out very
quickly how to do that. Well, have a good rest of the week. Thanks, Angie.
Sidelight listeners on serious 102 daily source code.com to hear the rest of this show. You've got
Pacifico's Tell My Next and Digital Flotsom later on as we continue here on the Charlie.
See, was it something else? I didn't want to say anything else about second life I was done.
I'm trying to keep it to a minimum. You know, just based upon the feedback that I got,
a lot of you just really don't care. That's cool. You don't have to. I guess I can treat it just
like flying. You know, a lot of you don't care about me flying either. I did receive some interesting
videos, though. And there's just just stuff there. The stuff that we can do. The stuff that
will totally carry over into into our real life that I think will be extremely cool as we
start to connect all these pieces together. I was made aware of the fact just two days ago,
right here on the daily source code that it is national may is national masturbation month
and go figure. Wouldn't our buddy Jess Smith just love to hook into that?
Here we go.
Thank you, if you haven't been so naughty, I'd never want to thank you, but naughty naughty
one day. I really have to say we've been so bloody naughty. Thank you, sweet today, boy.
Here we go. A naughty naughty monkey. I really have to thank you. If you haven't been so naughty,
I'd never have to thank you. A naughty naughty monkey. I really have to say,
if there's a naughty naughty monkey. Yes, the fabulous Jess Smith available for wedding
smart mix was and a spankin. And actually for some good-ass tunes, the Jeff Smith dot com,
that's G-E-O-F-F, the Jeff Smith dot com. He can also do all kinds of stuff for your show
if you're a podcast or if you're interested. Here's something interesting that I got. This came
through on, not sure if this came through on the voice mail line or not, but first time a candidate
has actually called into the judge. Hello Adam Curry. This is David Martin and team of Texas.
And listen to the podcast for a long time. Work it on a good audio comment for you.
It might be kind of lengthy. I don't know if you'll play it or not. There were a whole bunch of topics
that you could talk about. You want to know a little bit about me, go to votes for the number four
David Martin dot org and learn about my campaign. Take over says, they're old.
I kind of want to be like the comic strip blogger who makes me laugh every time I hear it. Thanks
Adam. Wow. Now that would be a candidate I would vote for. If comic strip blogger were to run.
For European Parliament, no less. Oh, wouldn't that shake things up? Wouldn't it be fantastic?
Yeah, I should think about endorsing a candidate for elections for any elections anywhere.
You know, everything makes so much difference. Anything that, in one sneeze anywhere in the world
is felt everywhere else. Hey, where's Roger Smalls by the way? I haven't heard from him in weeks.
I'm a little bit worried. He didn't show up at the draft in darts. I haven't heard anything from him.
I hope he's okay. Roger, if you're listening, not just myself, but lots of people miss you, my friend.
For sure. I was going to say, oh, yeah. I was I was actually contemplating getting into the
discussion about Iran. I was listening to the BBC this morning. I just switched back and forth
between radio four and BBC London, actually, which I think I like better, which is more local
and has kind of more real people on it. At least that's my opinion. And so there's a lot of
rumbling now in the UN about Iran, not complying with the, uh, what is it? Is it a resolution they
have to comply with regarding, uh, using nuclear energy for safe purposes and not for weapons
of mass destruction? Of course, the Iranian government or the, uh, is it the Ayatola?
Has said some pretty funky things in the past. So it's stuff is heating up and it does concern me
a little bit when I listen to it because I think the UN is totally useless. I don't think it makes any,
I don't think they can do anything for anybody, uh, but the IAEA is at the International, uh, atomic,
something, association, you know, the guys who check on nuclear stuff, they have some checklist that
Iran has to comply to and apparently they don't. So now you hear all this stuff about you
a new, you know, security council resolution and that force could be used. And it's just like,
am I just dreaming or is this deja vu or what the hell is going on? If you haven't
opinion about it, I would like to hear, um, because sometimes it's important to talk about that
stuff as well. You hear so much of it that you become almost immune and numb and then you can,
you think you just, and you don't know what's true or it's not true. It's being spun or isn't
being spun. I guess I'm going to have to go and delve deep into some web logs. He's
I can find some truth in those, but it's, it's, it's complicated and I have to be honest. It really
does worry me. And now we're from Ashfinter. It's the Yanks versus the Brits. We'll drive each other crazy,
but everybody knows that it's a parent to see. They're just like you and me. It's the Yanks.
And the Brits. The Yanks versus the Brits. Mind the gap.
Hi Adam. This is Kristen from Metropolitan Detroit, Michigan. And I'm also known as your neighbor,
Gabrielle Reo in second life. I own a lot next year, currently vacant lot, and comics and
yours lot, also known as comics your blogger. Anyway, I've been a loyal DSC listener for about
seven months, and I'd honestly never considered contributing feedback of any kind until
your Yanks versus the Brits segment of DSC number 378. I just have to respond to Glenn from the
Zed A show's comments about Americans. Not all of us are ignorant about the world outside of our
borders. Nor are we all running around wildly in a nationalist observer with the belief that
if it is an American, then it's not good enough. Just as Glenn feels annoyed by the stereotype
that he's encountered being a South African, I'm just as bothered by the American stereotypes
that he mentioned. It sounds like Glenn has encountered Americans to display qualities such as
ignorance or intense nationalism, so I don't want to invalidate his experiences. I just want to
state that these are qualities that you can find everywhere and in every culture. Yes, every culture
has its quirks and idiocying crises, and we Americans certainly have quite a few, and so
to the Brits. There are many of us that have lived outside of the United States or who have
family outside of the United States, and therefore we have a wider world view. I just felt the need
to speak up for this segment of Americans. So thanks for giving me this opportunity for feedback
and thanks to you and all the podcasters out there. I believe that you're all pioneers in
something amazing and I'm glad to be a part of it as a listener. So cheers to both the Americans
from the Brits and I'll see you in second life, neighbor. Yeah, neighbor. Open up your parcel to
me neighbor so I can drop by unexpectedly when you're having sex. I'm loving this. Yanks versus
the Brits stuff because this is, we got tons of stuff coming in. Peter had this enormous story which
I really want to set up properly, so I'll do that maybe tomorrow on next week's show. Keep
them coming in though. And if you have the opportunity to send them in as an audio comment,
pre-recorded, please do because obviously it sounds a lot better than these phone calls,
but at least we're getting listeners like Gabrielle and I'm really appreciative of it.
And there is some learning to be done here about why these differences exist and where they come from
and I'm always interested in the in the history of things such as why do Brits say Z and Z? I'm sorry,
crap, I set it up wrong. Why do Brits say Z when Americans say, when yanks say Z? Well,
pay attention kids. Hey, Adam and Bruce Murray from the Z cast as Z cast dot com. As you can tell
from the name of my show, I have a particular interest in the last letter of the alphabet.
You know what's one of the wonderful things about being Canadian is that we enjoy the best of
both worlds when it comes to the yanks and the Brits. I mean, we have close ties with our common
wealth brothers in the UK, but we still enjoy many of the wonderful traits of our friends and
neighbors to the south. But as to the alphabetical dilemma of why does the rest of the English
speaking world say Z and only the American say Z? Well, that's simple. They changed it to rhyme in the song.
Get your cowbell out. A B C B E F G H I J K L M N O P Q R S T U V W X Y Z. It just doesn't rhyme. So they
changed it to rhyme in the song. But the rest of the world still uses the original Z. I mean,
you would drive a Jaguar ZX, right? And of course, in Canada, we listen to ZZ Talk. Oh,
well, not really. I mean, most people think that Canadians say A, but but we don't. We say Z.
Anyway, you can check out the Z cast at ZEDCST dot com or in the United States ZEDCST.
I haven't quite got into a second life yet, Adam. I'm still trying to figure out the first one.
But I always listen to the Charlie. Take care, Adam. All right, Matt. Thank you.
See, it's working. I like this stuff. If you if you're in the car right now and think,
I got to talk about this. You can call me 201-625-6357 or 02076813753 in the UK.
And I only say that because I figured that it's just easier if you write it down.
I know you can pause it and go back, but I just want to put that in there.
Playing the cowbell, by the way, is it's kind of hard because I don't have the podcast
Paul gave me this wonderful cowbell off of his own drum kit, which is highly appreciated. I actually
should have asked him to sign up to put his signature on it or something. But I treasure it dearly.
What I don't have is a drum stick. I'm currently using a pencil. Adam, chip from top of the
pod, saves here. And by the way, I bought the top of the podsafe.com domain for $6.95.
So daddy, thank you. Yeah. I'm excited that you have props like the cowbell at your disposal.
And don't take this personally, but you truly do have the rhythm and cadence of a
Jersey white boy. I got to have a cowbell, baby. Now, commenting on a recurring thing from the
last few shot shots. I think if you're going to cremate yourself, you should then use one of
those leftover cheats and chong papers. And then maybe your friends can light up some curry,
but in memorial. You know, they say that THCD stays in one system for a long time, so maybe it
will hold out through the cremation process as well. I know it sounds weird. Hey, but it's better
than the use wet socks that chong used, right? Well, that's all I got to say. Loving the show,
keep it up, and one more for you. And then I got to go. I got a fever. And the only prescription is
more cowbell. Yeah, baby. I try, man. I try sometimes I get it, right? Sometimes they're one of
this podsafe music is just off beat. That's also possible. Yeah. Yeah. We were talking about that.
When I die, I definitely want to be cremated. That makes a lot of sense. It don't take up any space
for me. And the original suggestion was to put me into tattooing, and tattoo me on the
Madge's ass. But I like this better. You know, just have a whole bunch of friends come over and
smoke me. Yeah, I think that would work. Hey, Adam, it's Matthew Ebel. You're going to be turned into a
tattoo on Madge Weinstein's ass? No. I don't think so. To quote Dennis Larry, we're going to have
to wait till you die, and then smoke your ashes. Okay? Because considering how, well, most of us,
you know, pretty much know by now how you end every show. And probably begin every morning,
and maybe a little bit lunch too. I'm pretty sure we'll be getting a good buzz off of that.
So yeah, no. Save it, please. Don't, don't, don't waste it by, you know,
by turning into a tattoo on somebody's ass. Because that's just, you know, that's really an unpleasant
thought to begin with. So this one's for you. Well, I can't bring my lighter to the day job.
So just imagine a clicking sound. Tutal. Matt Tutal. Matthew is so sweet. He sent me a lovely email.
He posted something similar on curry.com regarding the second life conversation the
Patricia and I had yesterday. He said, you know, dude, I really don't want to lose you as a friend.
Don't get sucked in. The stuff is bad. Mojo, he's lost friends that way. He used to hang out with
and doing important things like eat pizza, barbecue, and smoked up. I lost a lot there, Matthew.
But it would not be cool. Of course, we don't know what's happened. What comes out in the
afterlife, but it would be interesting to just see all my buddies sitting around smoking me.
That would be kind of cool. Let's see. What else did I have? Oh, I wanted to roll this out for you.
Since he's been doing such tremendous work and always is there to help me out
and comes up with all these fantastic creative ideas. A little bit of props for Jeff Smith, who is
being propped all over the place these days. And rightly so. Hey Adam, this is Russell from the Raising
Giants podcast. My latest show is up number 25 and it's an interview with Jeff Smith. That's
right. Lee Jeff Smith, who created the Metro section moment, Trinity. And most recently, the Raising
Giants podcast theme. You can check out the show over at Raising Giants.com. That's
a Raising with an RAZ and hope you enjoy it. Take easy out of this guy. Jeff Smith has such
hokey stuff. I like it. And could you believe that accent that he does on the Yanks versus the Brits?
I think it's really good. I mean, I'm no expert. I thought it was really really good. Okay,
two geeky items before I get out of your hair for today. Of course, I want you to send in your
kick-ass music for tomorrow's Friday festivities. The thank God it's Friday edition of the
Daily Source Colors. We wrap up another week. And of course, I'll try and get the Lady Patricia on the
show. This comes from our time, Crop, a Dutch listener. And here's a, he sent a link. I don't think
he sent a link. Crap. Well, anyway, open street map project is going to free the Isle of White.
Now, the Isle of White is to the south of of Gilford, almost straight down south. Actually,
very near Portsmouth, as I said earlier in the show. Only takes about 20 minutes, 25 minutes to
fly to be over the island itself. This coming weekend, the open street map project is gathering on
the Isle of White off the south of the UK armed with their GPS devices. This band of some 30
plus enthusiastic amateurs planned to map the whole of the island, demonstrating how easy it is to
create copyright-free maps and not have to be at the mercy of commercial organizations like the
ordinance survey with their insanely high fees, not familiar with that, by the way. All collected
data will be available on a creative comments. Clearly, the more people turn up, the better the
results will be. So one last push for getting more to come along is going on. Usually excited about
this. This is from Simon says, I guess. So I'd love to help. If I can, you know, I could certainly
take the Delta share up Sunday. I don't know exactly what you want me to do. I could do some
aerial photography. I have a GPS. I could save my track. I mean, I don't know how to help. I'm just
not sure what is needed, but if you need air coverage, I'm here for you guys, for sure. Okay,
one last geeky bit. Hi, Adam. I got my golden ticket today and I've been playing our own
pod show plus. I didn't see any links on the site for feedback. Okay, so let me just tell you that
we have the devcast.devcast.podshow.com. Another episode coming up. And if you subscribe to that
show, you have a large relatively large chance of getting a golden ticket, which gets you in now,
where we're helping the developers help us essentially. And so that's what he's referring to.
So we finally got his goal to take it and his end and is looking for place to provide feedback.
The developers want beta feedback and bug reports. If so, where should we send them?
One other thing, what have you done with the commester blogger? Hold on one second.
We had started a source forage project to do just that. And source forage says that within
two business days, it'll approve your project and turn it around. And it's been like five or six days.
But K1 is on that and Andrew Grummer on that and just keep your eye on the devcast
show site as well as developer.podshow.com. Okay, now what was your question about
commester blogger? Recently he's been so nice and I sort of missed the abrasive old CSV.
This is where I call you Mr. Adam fucking curry. But I don't think I get pulled off of the same
gusto as a commester blogger. So thanks Adam. This is Jeff Bear from Craft Beer Radio.
You can find the show at www.craftbeerradio.com. Yeah, you know it's interesting you say that because
you know people like commester blogger. I really like that when people push back and particularly
the way he has done in the past. And it I like getting inside people's heads and trying to
see if I can tool with them and turn it into something positive. And actually I think commester blogger
has delivered a lot of you know a lot has contributed quite a bit to the show. I also miss a bit
of the abrasiveness. He sent in an audio comment for Patricia about second life which sees
me I'm not going to use because I don't want to subject my the lady Patricia to you that in
that manner specifically. But feel free to abuse me a little bit more. And if you don't want to
then you don't and actually you know how shit he's going to get all pumped off now because I said
that he was abusing me you don't know whatever whatever I got it I understand okay Jeff one more
thing there hi out of that shit did I miss it all what was the last thing you said. Anyway
I guess it's time for me to go what are we at 43 minutes perfect okay so if you want your
domain name for only $6.95 as you heard earlier just go to godaddy.com and upon check out
use the promotional code dsc3 and you get that domain name for $6.95. Ports of the show brought to
you by earthlink and of course we have the pod show challenge coming up very soon where you can
win valuable cash and prizes and have a hell of a lot of fun creating stuff as we are working
with earthlink on that and and that'll start off in the next few weeks and of course you're
really responsible for this because of the outcry of protest almost against the earthlink commercials
that have been running across the pod show network so you're going to get your chance to change
that help us change advertising because that's really the next phase of where we have to go.
I'm I'm that's it I'm done I'm empty I've nothing left I'll see you right here for the
fight of festivities send those links into songs from the pod safe music networks please another
pod show podcast stick it in your ear get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high
performance podcast delivery network from pod show and limelight networks. I love it