Delta Sierra Charlie 347.
Hey Craig, what's up?
I wonder what it would be like if Technorama was picked up by Pod Show.
Hmm, I wonder.
Corporate accounts payable means speaking just a moment.
And internet error occurred.
What the fuck does that mean?
I don't know Craig.
It's Craig.
Not Craig.
It's Craig with a K.
It's not that difficult.
Well, at least your name is in George Michael.
There is nothing wrong with that name.
There wasn't until that no talent asked clown started getting arrested everywhere.
Uh-oh, here comes Curry.
I need to get back to work.
I just know I had him curry's gonna make me come in on Saturday and do a podcast.
And I'll do it because I'm a big was.
It sounds like somebody's got a curse for the more news.
You are not a worse and well, I too am not a worse.
Hello, Chuck Craig.
Hi, it's Adam.
How's it going?
Uh, did you guys get the memo about putting cover tags on your podcast?
Yeah, I got the memo right.
Yeah.
If you could do that, that would be great.
Oh, and I'm going to need you to do a podcast on Saturday.
Yeah.
That would be great.
Uh, that was a little weird.
Yeah, but you're still a woodman.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Do the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky drinks, man.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Fantastic.
It's Adam Curry.
Hello, Adam.
This is the new love of your life, Laura Clav.
Come and do your life from Kansas City's Barnetasha.
Wish you were here.
Switching.
Hey, the morning vanity.
Come over half the sleep.
Just sent a bad decision.
Come home.
Quick to anticipate.
Which part of our jeans?
While she puts the fake eyelashes on.
Every morning same reaction.
Have some room Saturday's fashion.
Hey, hey, sister, you can let your head down.
You ain't done nothing bad and nothing up to feel so good.
You're just the pilot of the world and the rush.
This crazy life we live in is all a part of the world.
She's under self attack.
Can't do this, can't do that.
Or she might lose her precious hands.
Watch your figure, watch your weight.
Clean out that empty blade.
Throw you know that ain't no way to live.
Time for social intervention.
Listen girl, pay close attention.
Hey, hey, sister, you can let your head down.
You ain't done nothing bad and nothing up to feel so good.
You're just the pilot of the world and the rush.
This crazy life we live in is all a part of the world.
You ain't done nothing bad and nothing up to feel so good.
You're just the pilot of the world and the rush.
This crazy life we live in is all a part of the world.
You're this crazy life we live in is all a part of the world.
Or a clap.
No, no, no.
Hey, hey sister, everybody.
How you doing?
It is Monday.
Here at Curricanage, a beautiful day.
Blue skies.
No wind.
About four or five degrees centigrade.
It is just fantastic.
And of course, I spent the weekend here at home.
It was really, really nice.
But if I had a choice and I wasn't at home,
that doesn't mean I'd choose it over here.
If I wasn't San Francisco in the other home,
I think I would have been in Kansas City.
Hey, Adam.
This is at Roberts from the Kansas City weather podcast.
Hey brother, I was driving home from the Matthew evil Laura Clapshow here in Kansas City on Friday night.
Actually turned on a daily source code right after that, which I was halfway through.
And heard the announcement about the show.
And the fact that you said if you were in the States, you would have come and mad.
Brother, you missed a show.
Holy smokes.
Now, because of his popularity, you probably would have thought that Matthew evil would have
gone ahead and closed out the show and Laura would have opened for him.
Well, I was not the case.
And, you know, Matthew evil isn't absolutely phenomenal guy and phenomenal artist.
But Laura, holy smokes, dude.
You have got to wonder why some big,
recording label hasn't picked her up.
Oh, no.
That's the quote of the night.
We're sitting at the table talking to Matthew evil.
One of the girls were sitting with leans over and says, you know,
she would be a perfect open for Cheryl Crow.
Matthew evil turns around and says,
No, she could close for Cheryl Crow.
I couldn't agree more.
Sorry, you couldn't be there, brother.
I know they're going to be doing some more stuff in Nashville.
So if you go to Kansas, go see him there.
And Laura is actually originally from Kansas City.
And Matthew evil sounded like he was all for coming back to town and playing at this place.
So if you get a chance when they're over here or over there, whatever,
you got to check him out.
In any case, have a great weekend at him and we'll talk to you later.
So that came, you know, like in the middle of the weekend.
I was like, I really wish I could have been there.
But it was nice being home.
Let me make that very, very clear.
Oh, man.
I was expecting some more pot-sake music videos to pop up,
particularly after that show.
It's someone must have videotaped it.
I guess not.
Got a couple cool pictures.
And it looks like that was a great, great show.
Congratulations to Laura and to Matthew evil.
And yeah, what a nice guy, Matthew.
You need to say something like that.
By the way, let me just say, I would really be sad
if a major record label picked her up.
I've been talking a couple of pot-sake music artists
over the past week or so.
You know, some email conversations.
And, you know, many of them have been very, very close to being signed by a major.
You know, only to be dropped later on or the timing was wrong.
It's like, it's crap.
You can be putting out tons of stuff.
You can put out a new song every single day if you want.
Every single day.
Another thing that doesn't quite work yet is being able to get your music into a purchasing situation,
such as, well, such as iTunes.
You know, it takes many weeks.
In some cases, many, many months.
In fact, I think that's actually what this price-fixing thing is about.
You know, they're looking at price-fixing within the music business for online downloads.
I think that part of the issue here is that independent labels don't get the same courtesy
that the three or four majors do in getting their stuff up in a timely fashion,
which I think still is either, you know, every Tuesday, I think is a possibility.
That makes sense.
So once a week.
But really, if you want to get up there, I think it takes at least six weeks if you're independent.
So, along with the pot-sake music network.
We're just waiting for our, was it sure mail?
Subscription.
Lots of people sent in comments about that, about the whitelist.
Sorry.
The blackberry.
I kind of remember to do that before the show.
The whitelist, blacklist, stuff.
We'll be talking a bit about that later on today.
Oh, regarding, uh, pot-sake music videos.
Hmm.
Oh, boy.
I keep following her show.
She had it.
I'm talking about Calli.
Calli Lewis of Geek Brief TV.
God damn it.
Our fearless leader.
She had the sexiest t-shirt on and it was a Geek Brief six.
I think or something like that.
I can't remember which one it was.
Now, can't be six.
Must be more than that.
Um, it was like nerds or hot or something like that.
I was like, yeah.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Hey, Adam.
Calli Lewis from Geek Brief TV.
Hmm.
So, I'm sitting here watching the Academy Awards.
And all I can think about is your first video podcast.
Really?
Come here on the Jeff Smith video.
So, so cute.
It was adorable.
But you.
You're holding back on us.
And I'm very upset at you.
You're lips.
Hot.
Yes.
sexy.
But you have more to offer than that.
And I'm not asking you for a glimpse behind the Terry Cloth.
I already googled that.
But just show us the whole face next time.
Okay.
Now, on to the next thing after my rant.
Don't worry about the production time.
You're busy, man.
Send it to me and we'll take care of everything else for you.
Okay.
Ah, that's really sweet, Calli.
That's very, very sweet.
You know, I chose specifically for that format.
And I'm going to do another one this week.
I'm just waiting for the right video to come along.
Which is always the hardest thing.
If I'm going to do this.
Show of.
Podsake music videos.
Then I want to make sure that I've got the, you know, got something that's good.
You know, it can't be just a song.
In fact, I was looking at a couple of music video channels over the weekend.
And, you know, it really does make a difference.
What the video, what's in the video.
It's a whole other piece of art, which doesn't necessarily have to come from the artists themselves.
You know, so I think there's enough creative people that we're going to, I'm going to try and help connect.
To see if we can come up with some, you know, cool new ways to promote pod safe music and pod safe music artists.
What else?
Oh, the reason why I chose that format of just the mouth is, you know, I started thinking,
you know, I travel a lot.
And I can do my podcast basically from wherever I am, even if I'm on an airplane and I've done that several times.
In the car, wherever, you know, it's pretty simple.
Cast Blaster Travels now on the lightest notebook I've ever owned, the, the, the Shiba Porter J.
In a pinch, I can just pop in the, the wireless mic and that's it.
You know, I'm good to go.
But I don't always have the hair, you know, and this is, and we've talked about this.
You know, it gives me great confidence to have good hair, but I can do it.
I'm very, I'm very, I'm very poor at getting my hair cropped.
Oh, it's almost a metro sexual moment.
So I figured, you know, what is the one thing I can show at all times, which, you know, will be worth watching.
And I figured, that's just about the only piece of me that can, you know, make pieces of me the counts.
This podcasting thing, if you're listening to us on serious satellite stars, stars on the satellite.
This podcasting thing is really happening.
You know, who else has an iPod and is listening to podcasts, not just music.
In fact, probably not even any music off the iTunes music store, but solely listening to podcasts.
Oh, yes, it's holiness.
The Pope.
And here's Father Roderick.
Tell us all about it.
Yeah.
Father Roderick here from the daily breakfast that daily breakfast.com.
Remember, I went to Vatican Radio almost exactly a year ago to tell them about podcasting.
Well, they immediately understood the importance of this new medium.
And in two days time, they had started to podcast themselves.
Well, check this out.
This weekend, the Pope himself has started to listen to podcasts.
When Pope Benedict XVI visited the headquarters of Vatican Radio last Friday for their 75th birthday,
the people that work over there offered him an iPod Nano, preloaded with podcasts and music.
The back was engraved through the words to his holiness Benedict XVI in Italian.
Since Vatican Radio offers podcasts in eight different languages,
the Pope now has the technological capability himself to plug in and listen to these podcasts.
But what is the Pope has finished listening to the two gigabyte of audio on his iPod Nano?
Since he's a pretty busy guy, he perhaps could use some suggestions about what to listen to next.
So this week at the daily breakfast, I'm launching a contest.
In order to find the most original, most interesting,
funniest or most surprising top three of podcast or pot-save music for the Pope to listen to.
The winner will receive a special gift from Vatican City.
So visit dailyBrexas.com and mail me an audio clip with your favorite political top three
to dailyBrexas at sqpn.com.
Let's help Pope Benedict discover this great world of podcasts and pot-save music.
Yes, you're holding this, this is podcasting.
Oh, Roder, great idea.
And if anyone can get podcasts onto the Pope's iPod, you know what's going to be?
Father Roderick, you know, he can do that.
Dude, that would be so cool. There's lots of inspirational podcasts that we're qualified.
That's for sure.
But, you know, if you really want to show the Pope what's going on, you've got to slip a little yeast radio on there.
Oh, man.
I wonder if he would declare this podcasting, the devil's work or not.
Ah, very cool.
Yeah, that's nice.
And he's definitely keeping up with the times.
Our Pope.
But of course, you know, what I'd really like is for him to go through the whole experience
of subscribing to podcasts through the iTunes Music Store
and see if he can bless that somehow I doubt it.
Lots of, actually, you know, today is going to be a mix of feedback
in audio form and email form.
Dave Christensen says, Adam, on Friday show you mentioned that you believe your case
against MTV was important and could have set precedent.
I quickly took a break from studying to run a citation check on your case.
It turns out that the MTV V curry case is referenced by a number of courts
and all the opinions are positive, meaning that they do not overrule any points in the opinion written for your case.
Specifically, MTV versus Curry mentioned 34 court opinions three of which discuss my case.
Specifically, MTV versus Curry is mentioned inside it in 58 law review articles.
Oh, then Dave says these aren't huge numbers.
But it isn't really bad considering its opinion from a district court case.
That's right, the pellet court case provides more presidential weights and therefore
are cited more often.
See, I told you, I told you that it was a precedent setting.
I guess that's what you're trying to tell me.
Michael Barry says, Adam, I think you're missing a big reason why the Iraq war
doesn't draw the same attention or protest as the Vietnam war.
Now, I said that this is because the mainstream media has done something very different
than the Vietnam war where we saw actual news reels.
And there were reels that was filmed, I think, at the time, mostly film.
Of dead American boys, well, predominantly American boys, you know, being brought home
and on the battlefield.
And what Michael says is the real reason that there's not that much attention is the lack of a draft.
A mix as I do not, Michael is making them.
I do not support a draft, but if there ever was one, the shit would hit the fan.
Self-interest is one of the biggest factors driving the protests against the Vietnam war.
Ooh, I don't know about that.
I'm not old enough to know.
But, oh, man, can you imagine a draft being instituted?
Yeah, you're right.
It definitely would stir up some majors.
Hey, I didn't want you here.
Actually, you know, I hope you win your court case and everything goes well for you.
I know that there's such that if they don't understand the meaning of the English word, public,
then they shouldn't be using an English website now, should they?
Yeah, right.
For example, the public part, just because it's called public.
It doesn't mean I'm allowed to go there and pick flowers or follicles again.
I don't think they're going to like the stand-on in court.
And I think you'll do just fine, I always do.
So just this said, all folks says on the internet.
Just the adventures.com's going to have to read some of my French three dollars.
So, bye for now, and may the win be with you.
So, that's right, Roger.
Just because the park says it's a public park does not mean you're allowed to pick flowers.
There are follicles around, like goodness.
So Roger and I are definitely going to try and meet.
But it's not going to be at the Guardian Conference.
There's something about, you know, a little confused about all the different words.
You know, whereas when I talk about a lawyer here in the UK,
that's known as a solicitor.
And he has some other word, which to me sounded a lot like parole.
I'm not going to share what that was, off the look of the email.
So that was not a day that he was free to travel.
But we are definitely working on the hookup.
Lots of controversy on the curry.com message boards.
Comic strip blogger is all over the place.
And he keeps saying kind of the same things.
And, you know, I asked him if he would just do me a favor
and participate in the show and not just ramble on the comments
and really give me something that I can work for.
Comic strip.
So it is time.
To hear.
Comic strip.
From our favorite poster.
Jeff, you're not to come.
Comic strip.
Okay, here we come.
This comic strip blogger.
I just wanted to comment about all this stupid lawsuit
against the poor Dutch journalist.
So Adam Curry.
Stop kidding us.
You started this whole fucking lawsuit against the Dutch employee
just to get publicity for yourself.
I am sorry, but I am not digging this whole
defending my family, my copyrighted photos, staff.
Which people like you, with middle life crisis,
have such late life hobbies where they pretend
to fight good causes, but in your reality.
It is just subconscious need from a publicity.
And why the fuck you care at all about
Netherlands and about what Dutch press rights.
Do you have Dutch citizenship?
For fuck's sake.
I ask you this stuff for many, many times.
Many times it didn't answer.
So, fuck you.
That's sort of a disclaimer that the comic strip blogger
is in no way family's safe.
You know, I actually worked on a whole ran to whole
replied to comic strip blogger.
With Christine, a listener who said,
let me help you work on some long ass rants.
And we came up with something that was pretty good,
but I'm actually going to go hold that back if you don't mind.
Because this Thursday is when the judge will
give the verdict and tell us all what the decision is.
And that will really answer a lot of your questions there
or a comic strip blogger.
And of course, I do care.
You know, if you look at the Netherlands,
look at their track record for wealthy people
who have been killed famous or wealthy people
in the last five years, several of whom I know
and have known personally.
So, the protection of my child goes above all.
And then, secondarily, in this comes back to the MTV vs. Curry suit,
I believe that this is important for creative commons.
And when a mainstream publication says that the value
of something on the internet is nihil as in zero
because it's out there and it's published.
You know, I think that that's a travesty
if they would get away with that.
And it basically breaks creative commons.
And so, all I want is some sort of precedent,
some sort of signal from the judge that will say this is not okay
and we're not just going to let you pay someone off with a fee
and go and do it again the next time.
That's really what that's what all it comes down to.
So, any rants on that, I reserve until hopefully Thursday show,
hopefully I'll know before you guys get up in the US.
Excuse me.
Oh, my goodness.
Hold on, maybe I should play this.
Hey, happy, what's up?
Well, the world seemed to be better again.
I know change is inevitable.
And you know, I've tried hard to stay up with the times.
I even call the Daily Source Code the Charlie.
But Adam is up to his old tricks again.
Just listen to Daily Source Code 342.
Excuse me, since I'm drinking one right now.
So good to be drinking one.
The burp is back and things seem right in the world.
And then this happened on Daily Source Code 344.
Did you just burp?
No.
On this show, you know what happens.
What do you have to say?
Did I burp?
Yeah, what do you have to say?
What do you have to say?
Excuse me?
No.
Since I owe.
Oh, since I owe.
Thanks for listening.
Oh, for the past year and a half.
Oh, I'm confused.
Not even Patricia knows what to do.
And I'm trying to figure things out.
We may not even have birth, wanker, trinity, or even...
I got to get that.
Hey, Roger.
Yeah, Roger.
You can find bedtime stories.
My kids love at www.psml.com.
Yeah, I know that comic-strik blogger is a pain.
Hey, Roger.
Let me turn up the boom box so you can hear the cool mash-up.
Happy pulled from the pod safe music network.
You're pointing out me is freaking me out.
What?
What are you talking about?
Lucky luck.
You're pointing out me is freaking me out.
Let's go for his or on crack, man.
To wind that up a comic-strik blogger, I have the US nationality.
I have a permanent work permit and if I wish to use it residency permit for the
Netherlands have had that for many, many years.
I work in the United States.
I pay federal taxes in the United States.
I pay local and council taxes here in the UK.
Yeah.
Is there a problem with that?
Actually, there is a problem.
It sounds to me like you're upset CSB that you don't have the opportunity to go to the United
States, which of course is a shame because it is rather difficult.
But I have to say you might need a serious attitude adjustment if you want the US to let you in.
But really, I'd like to delve into your history.
I know lots of people that I shouldn't spend any time at all on a comic-strik blogger.
But as you read around, I believe that comic-strik blogger is really Jacek Routowski.
And you're a Nokia, a former Nokia employee who got fired and was so pissed off that you started to promote
very heavily and very aggressively the competition, which would be Microsoft.
I'd be really bummed out if I were listening to this story on serious stars because you're about to hit
a specific host Hellway East Radio, Donna Drew, Gilmore Daily, DVD Weekly and CC Chapman.
Talk to you tomorrow.
So we'll just continue here.
Peter, thanks by the way for finally sending you a printable rundown and yelling at me.
So now I know exactly what's going on serious.
So if you're really that pissed off at Nokia, tell us about it.
What happened?
Why did you get fired?
Give me some details on that.
We could have a very interesting conversation.
The way you've carried on about MS mobiles and have put up your own money to, in fact,
the comic-strik blogger was one of the first people advertising on podcasts by sponsoring
the Donna Drew Show even before they were at Pod Show.
And I just want to know more about you.
So please feel free to send in some more background on yourself, CSP.
Hey, Adam.
It's Dan Schmidt from the Kidcast podcasting in the classroom show.
And we are educational podcast that's focused on teachers and students and how to integrate
podcasting into an educational space, how to manage it, how to be creative about how
you integrated into the curriculum.
We play lots of examples.
Give lots of tips and we sponsor a contest.
And this month's contest is pretty exciting.
What we're giving away an iPod shovel, a hundred dollar gift certificate to FTC publishing.
And we're giving away five copies of my book, Kidcast podcasting in the classroom.
So that's pretty cool.
But here's the deal.
We're focusing on podcast dramas.
So if you think back to the goal-nage of radio and all the theater of sound and theater of the
mind stuff, it was really powerful stuff.
And we want to use that medium for learning.
So we're challenging teachers to, and students to create their own podcast dramas or
skids and share them with us.
So they just need to write an original skit that contains at least two characters.
And it needs to be educationally appropriate.
And they should try to teach the listener something new, preferably in the curriculum within
their storyline.
And we're looking for things that are short.
Maybe three to four minutes.
They just have to record and edit their skit.
Add some cool sound effects and maybe some music.
And then put it up on their server as an MP3 and then just send us the link.
Then they can find out more information by going to my website at Intelligenic.com slash
KidCast.
Or they can find us in the iTunes podcast directory or in podcast alley.
Just look for KidCast podcasting in the classroom.
Thanks Adam.
Stay creative and keep mom learning.
The voting is now open on slam idle contest number nine.
The contestants are Cynthia French.
I could kiss you in public.
Like the fluency and the jacuzzi was removed.
Like finding your favorite part of a really bad gift.
A Rachel can.
Whether you are here as a queen or a whore.
When you think things can't get any worse.
And it seems like you're coming apart at the seams.
Just remember that you're the one who scheme these schemes.
Patricia Evah.
You know, as I do, we sing the same tune.
Why couldn't I stay and share the mood?
Seems Stuart.
As a cell for moon rises.
Growing taller over.
Over.
The song and trees that have grown in the fields that.
G-S-Bast.
And I paint you new cities where walls are clean with people are there.
And welcome you in.
No, it's not like that.
But take one step.
It can be.
Maybe.
And Andrew Taylor.
Do you still feel shy around women?
And don't know what to say.
Do you get on nervous and clammy and just wish it would go away?
To cast your vote.
Go to slam idol.tripoet.com.
Hey Adam.
Marcus Couch here.
And I'm here to remind everyone of a few things.
First and foremost, the new episode of Pod Show Music Rewind is out.
That's episode 23.
And you can find the show at podshowmusicrewind.com.
Now this week we've got Pod Show Music Podcast, like the Rock and Roll geek indie cast,
accident, hash, mad pod, and the scenes scene.
But in addition, we'll head over to the UK and check in with Evan Crawford and the reaching
for lucidity podcast.
We'll get jacked with Jack Elias on the get jacked podcast from Washington D.C.
We also check in with Rich Palmer and the Miami Valley music cast.
And I'm excited to announce our first Japanese based podcast into Rewind.
What's happening in Tokyo hosted by Tokyo Dan?
So what did all these music podcasts have to do to get on Pod Show Music Rewind?
And ultimately be heard on serious stars?
Well, it doesn't take special VIP status selling your soul or
mounds of cash.
All you have to do is edit a song.
And then you click of your music podcast that features a song from the pod
safe music network.
And then email that clip to me at podshowmusicrewind at gmail.com.
That's it.
It's really just that easy.
Thanks everyone and be sure to check out the new episode at podshowmusicrewind.com.
This is Marcus Couch.
Take care everybody.
All right, everybody.
I think a little monkey markers.
It's funny.
How people want to be on the serious satellite.
But it is actually, see, when does it put on?
It's on Tuesdays between nine and 10 Eastern time is when the podshow music
rewind airs and its entirety and it's been opened up to, as you heard,
anyone who has a pod save music podcast wants to send, you know,
just caught up a little segment of it where you play a song.
Send it off to Marcus.
He'll take care of you.
Tony Blair, the British Prime Minister was on television.
I think it was Friday night, I believe.
On this talk show called Parkinson.
Now Parkinson is, is really, it's not just a talk show.
Parkinson or Pauki.
As you know, and here is an institution, really.
But, you know, to have the Prime Minister come on and sit down and just chat
and his, you know, Parkinson's format is, you know, himself, two chairs,
and a backdrop and an audience.
And that's it.
It was really nice.
It was, you know, he came across very personal, personal,
and very personal as well.
I didn't think he answered every question, you know,
to the best of his ability.
But he did have a couple of really funny stories.
And one that I like the most.
He was talking about after his marriage to Shari Blair.
And he hadn't really met, well, he had met his father-in-law,
her dad.
Well, they hadn't really had any serious conversation.
So after the wedding, everyone goes back to the house,
and they're in the, I guess, the drawing room,
or the sitting room.
And, you know, Tony's like, well,
and I'm going to really have a chat with this guy.
And he says, well, have a chat.
And Tony says, sure.
And he says, do you mind if I light a split first?
Oh, I think he said joint.
And then Tony went, yeah, okay, no problem.
I was like, wow, that's pretty heavy.
That's much better than I didn't inhale stuff.
It was just really nice.
I wonder what would be like if George Bush would go on Oprah,
something like that.
Well, maybe not Oprah.
I guess, I didn't, didn't just recently do like a walk.
I mean, I don't like the walking tour stuff.
I don't like the edited stuff.
Just do a sit down, don't edit conversation.
You know, that would be, that would be good.
Let people see who you are.
You know, if there's anything wrong with this president
and there's a hell of a lot wrong.
It's this PR, man.
Stupid.
It's just an idiot when it comes to PR.
Does everything exactly their wrong way?
Speaking of wanting to be on serious satellite.
Hey, Adam, this is Tyler Jersey,
Todd Show, great talk with you on Friday.
You know, I was all psyched up when I saw on the show notes that
we're going to play my comment.
I was just about to run out to best buy it to buy a serious satellite receiver
when I realized something.
You see, there's developing case law here at the Delhi source code.
Two wits, sir.
The landmark holding in the recent case of quasi-toli
V. Curry stands for the proposition that a guest of the
Delhi source code is not required to buy a satellite receiver
if their prom was played after the satellite window expires.
This is exactly what happened to me.
Of course, the remedy is for you to let me tell people
to check out the Jersey Todd Show at www.jurzytodshow.com.
There you go.
After they're done listening to the Chacha.
So let's be a big man.
Nice try.
Or off the best buy.
Ah, shoot dude.
I missed it again.
I'm sorry.
I'll have to remember to do better next time.
All right.
In this portion of the source code,
we're going to be talking about a whole bunch of different things
that are definitely related to podcasting, internet,
freedom in general.
You know, all the stuff that we want to keep off of the satellite.
One other thing that this conversation keeps going on.
Thank you all very much for sending in so many different ideas about being
blacklisted at ISPs.
For those of you who are just tuning into the Charlie,
this is about large ISPs.
And the biggest defender is Microsoft with Hotmail and MSN,
who will flag different types of email is spam.
And the whole issue is you have to go to these intermediaries
to have it solve.
You know, if you go as an individual or even as a company and go to Hotmail
or Microsoft and say, hey, can you take me off your blacklist
put me on the whitelist?
They basically say, you go talk to those guys.
And those guys happen to charge money.
So lots of comments come in about running my own mail servers.
And there's a whole bunch of things that can be done.
But I'm quite sure at the end of the day,
we've done some cost analysis.
It's much, much cheaper to have an intermediary do it.
At the same time, by the way, I have to say in that $80,000 fee,
there's also hardware that can really handle strong email by itself
has become such a science.
You know, you have engineers who are dedicated specifically
to fine tuning email delivery performance.
Well, I guess the spam guy is really fine tune that stuff.
But in general, I think it's just the bad thing.
It's part of this, we're seeing AT&T now saying that they want to charge
people who are providing content.
So they kind of make money on both ends of the stick.
And we'll talk about that in a bit.
Also, lots of talk about the music industry.
But first, this blacklist is...
Hey Adam, it's Matt Snydgrass.
And as you know, our company and your company
have been doing a lot of business lately.
And the communications of which has been the email.
But just last week, an email that I think came from Ron
to me that you and Greg and Chris were copied on.
Got blocked in our company, spam filter through Lotus Notes,
which troubles me because we've since successfully been able
to email each other.
But just this email got put in a possible blacklist section.
So in a world that two businesses are trying to conduct business,
this blacklist problem could hurt business, literally.
So I just wanted to let you know that that problem
and throw that onto the fire as well.
Take care, buddy.
Thanks, Matt.
God, this is me off.
See, this is exactly what happens.
You have a company.
And then you start to say any emails.
And Matt, of course, works for some offshore gambling company.
Just kidding, dude.
I don't know if you want me to mention who you work for.
But I check that you guys have four email servers.
And it's very possible that either one of them somehow automatically
flagged.
In fact, you have two email servers in San Francisco.
So it could have been, which are third and fourth in the list.
So the first, you have a main email server, which doesn't appear to be in San Francisco.
I'm sorry.
I want to San Francisco.
I want to San Jose.
There you go.
Or at least I can make that up by the naming convention.
So if the first two ones are busy, then it'll fall over to the third of the fourth one.
And now the discouraging thing here is that it's very possible.
And also highly likely that your notes installation,
check some kind of database somewhere periodically to see if there's any spam,
addresses that should be added to it.
And it wouldn't surprise me if they got this from,
like the short mail people, you know?
Or maybe someone else.
I don't know.
Gabrielle Lowe says,
if it's so hard to get email through hotmail without being white listed,
why do I receive five times as much spam in my hotmail inbox
than any other web mail system?
Well Gabrielle, because this is not about spam.
It's being sold as an anti spam issue, but it's not.
And in fact, what's happening is people, the companies that are sending you that spam,
in likelihood, may even be paying to have a delivered.
You know, this is, AOL is not saying they're going to trap spam.
They're saying they're going to charge people for it.
That's, that's a very, that's something very different.
So, you know, you're only seen as legitimate if you can come with this huge
water of cash.
This is very bad.
Believe me.
If you ever think of starting, you know, your own business on the internet.
You're going to run into this problem and it really does suck.
There's also a clearing house.
Someone, a couple of people sent me email about about a clearing house,
where you can basically have them deliver your email,
but it's very hard then to have your, you know,
any identifying marks of your own company in there.
It just sucks all wrong.
It's bad.
It's really bad for the internet.
Let's talk about AOL for a second.
Now, I mentioned that I haven't done it yet, a while back,
was it last week.
I listened to this session, the artist's round table at podcast hotel.
And I'm really sorry I wasn't there.
And it was just impossible for me to make it.
It's coming to San Francisco.
So I do plan on attending there because I think we have a lot
of confusing issues.
And what I had suggested is I would comment on that session
and re-record it.
But okay, you know, that would be like three hours long.
So I just want to address some issues here.
Because now, also after, you know, after having listened to it,
there were two people talking.
One was, I think Tim is his name.
I'm not sure who was, who was the representative for Iota.
And Iota, maybe I should take a look and see what they call themselves
exactly as far as I understand it.
They are an organization of independent record labels.
Let me see.
I owed, which would be dot com.
I hope not dot org.
I wouldn't make any sense.
Well, that's Iota national international training and consultancy.
So maybe it is dot org.
That's interesting.
Welcome to Iota.
No, that's a shoot.
I can't even find Iota.
Let me just punch in Iota.
Let me see what comes up and trust the old Google tracks and relevance
for me people.
Iota on low.
It's the independent online distribution alliance.
Ah, okay.
Let me just read with their charter is so I don't miss quote anything.
Iota alliance dot com.
There you go.
Iota is the industry leading digital distribution company for the global independent
music community run by an experienced team of digital music experts with a passion for independent music.
Iota distributes thousands of releases from independent labels to digital music outlets around the world.
Okay.
Now, they are a service essentially.
So they sell their service to I presume to independent record companies not directly to artists.
I'll just look into the clients tab here.
Let me see.
Find labels.
Oh, they do artists as well.
Okay.
So they've got.
Oh, they've got tons of them tons of them.
All right.
So as I was listening, I kept hearing the guy from myota say things.
You know, like, oh, it's the same podcasting is the same old thing.
It's promotion from music.
I was a woman.
I think Jennifer was a name who was both a podcaster and a musician.
And she really wanted payment from podcasters if they make money.
And if they use music in their podcast.
Now, this, of course, is not what the podcast music network does.
And I'll just explain that briefly because most of you probably understand.
The podcast music network is a very small and very simple license, which basically says
any tracks and artists makes available here on the podcast music network can be used by podcasters under the following conditions.
Well, there's actually a couple of conditions there that have to do with collective works, etc.
And so there are limitations to what you can do with it commercially.
But you can pretty much, you know, just use it on your podcast as long as you attribute it.
I put a link in your show notes and report it back to the network.
That's really the biggest piece.
And we're doing our best to automate that part, actually.
And that's pretty much it. And this is part of our unlabel concept.
And the unlabel concept really means that every independent artist is their own company.
Is their own record label.
And it's, you know, the record labels essentially have been disintermediated out of the equation.
You don't need tons of money to record something.
You don't need tons of money to create a video.
And you can market very well online, particularly working with podcasters.
And, you know, here, here am I, here am I.
I'm a old DJ, ex-Broadcaster, my partner, Ron Bloom, together we conceive the pod save music network.
He's a musician of blues guitars from Atlanta.
So, you know, it kind of worked out.
And we had some real discussion about this, you know, about how to make money.
And there was also something else interesting that came up in the artist's roundtable.
You almost unanimously, what I heard was, you know, don't give anything to the performing rights organizations.
That money doesn't get to us anyway.
Oh boy, I just have to say very briefly.
Oh shit, I'll say that for tomorrow.
So, so all of that didn't quite sit well with me.
And that's why I really wish I had been there.
And that actually asked me to send off a, you know, a quote or something in audio.
And I'm glad I didn't do that because it would have been completely out of context for the conversation.
But over the weekend, maybe it was Friday.
A news release came out.
I think I saw it on podcast or new, no podcastingnews.com.
And now everything has started to fall into place.
And now I'm starting to understand what I owe to is trying to do.
So, I'll just read this release to you.
Tower records to start free download service from music mashups within podcasts.
Actually, the story comes via a tector.
Talk about reinventing tower records, which is in the throes of offline troubles.
It's trying to do something new online.
It plans to open a new online service this summer called Tower pod.
God.
That lets consumers create their own podcasts using a catalog of some 6,000 songs, which tower will provide free.
None of the major labels want to be part of this, mainly because of copyright concerns.
But Tower has signed up independent online distribution alliance and indie music trade group and distributor.
It's in the IODA, acts in the IODA, include hip hop group, black allicious, and rock flashback Peter Frampton.
Tower intends to generate revenue from the podcast by selling ads on the most popular ones.
Any money generated will be split up amongst a large group that includes the user who created the podcast, the artist, the label, and the publishers who created or own the music as well as tower itself.
So now I get it. Now I understand why that conversation was driving the way it was.
The thought here is to make a pool of music available where I presume podcasters will be able to go to.
They say consumers, I guess maybe they're going to allow consumers to create playlists of stuff or something like that.
But let's just take, let's just assume that any podcaster can go in there and use that music.
And then I don't know if there's, you know, what the real terms of the license are.
So sometimes there's, I've heard different things like, well, maybe you have to talk over the intro.
We're basically all the stuff we went through radio.
But they're going to be selling ads.
And then that's the way that the money is going to be, I presume they're also going to be selling tracks.
I mean, that's probably why you have tower records involved for Tower pod.
But I think there's a, there's a thought mistake here.
First of all, you're divving up the money amongst, was it five parties?
That doesn't make a lot of sense.
Particularly, and look, you guys probably know music better than I do.
But when it comes to advertising on podcast, I think we have some experience.
And I don't know how many podcasters are going to want to take a small portion.
At the end of the day, let's just fast forward five years.
Let's say that prices for advertising on podcast have been set and recognized.
You're still going to be chopping it up into more pieces with your proposal than any other one.
So, you know, that feels to me like there's just too many hands in the pot there.
And then, you know, and who determines what music can be sold there.
And, you know, let's just say advertisers don't want, you know, some rock song with the word fuck in it.
And does that mean that song is excluded?
I think there's just too many questions that have to be addressed.
And obviously, I wish them luck.
No doubt about that.
I mean, we're not competing with any store or any store-type format.
The sales and the pod sake music network are there just, you know, as an almost, as a service.
You know, if you want to, you don't have to.
You don't have to be listed on PMN only.
If you want to sell, you don't have to make anything available.
You can take stuff off, you know, it's very, very flexible.
But I'm keeping a close eye on this one.
And I guess they'll be announcing that all the plans hopefully will be able to see some of the terms.
But it just seems like, you know, just seems like that might be a tough nut to crack.
And if anyone from Iota has any thoughts about it and would like to spin it back, please record a comment and let me know.
I'm very, very curious.
It was listening to hood hype, hood hype.com.
Jay Mac over the weekend.
And boy, that blew me away there with those guys who were talking.
I can't forget who we had on.
I think it's one of his guys from New York.
And they were talking about payola in the music business and how it's still rampant.
And there's some DJ.
I think at Hot 97 in New York City, who's been accused of accepting $1,500.
You listen to the latest hood hype, the podcast to get all the details.
But he was accused of taking $1,500 for playing a record.
And I thought to myself, man, just look at what's happening on hip hop.
And look how many stations are playing hip hop.
And look how many video music channels are playing hip hop.
And then look at the currency that hip hop deals with.
You know, lots and lots of bling, lots and lots of cash.
You know, it seems like the artist.
And even if you listen to how artists and DJs, you know,
there's a lot of respect going on and everyone loves everybody.
Oh, maybe because they're all on the take.
You know, I've never been offered money ever, ever, ever, ever, ever.
In fact, when I was on the radio, my boss Lex Harding would tell me,
he said, you know, if someone from the record industry ever wants to buy you a drink
or takes you out for dinner, you can go ahead and accept.
But you must buy them the next round or buy or pay for the dinner.
And you can always submit the bill to me, which never happened
because I was never offered that interestingly enough.
I think it happens probably with with the DJs or kind of like, you know,
the not the morning or afternoon drive, you know, it's probably somewhere in hours
that still still count for BDS, you know, for the tracking system.
So it counts plays, maybe maybe the midday person or something like that.
It's going to be someone who's not a high profile, not a high profile person
on the station.
But apparently it's just, it's completely rampant.
So, you know, the music business is really falling apart at the seams here.
And now all this talk about, you know,
anti-competition that the pay, all the scandals,
spitsers doing a pretty interesting job.
And we'll pay attention to him.
Nick.
Guitietta's, I think, one ear,
thought I had of ladies in the way in which the unlabel is forming in a very,
in a way very similar to that of political revolution.
Theoretically, the transition from a dictatorship to a demographic,
democratic or Republic style of governance happens when one,
the central government loses exclusive control of information,
meaning the ability to control distribution and thus the ideas of the public.
Ooh, that's definitely up there.
And two, the middle class begins to emerge and turn against
said central government.
Very astute there, Nick.
I think you're on to something.
Definitely do.
Uh, what the hell was this?
This was an audio comment.
I don't remember why I wanted to play.
Sure, mech sense of second.
Hey, I'm, my name is Byron Barman.
I was just listening to the Charlie number 346,
and Stewart Devonport seems to have a problem with some missing files from the iTunes
music store.
All right.
About a year ago, I also lost quite a few downloaded songs,
but after a quick email to the iTunes music store.
Dude, you're freaking me out with a left-to-right thing.
The port, I was able to read download everything.
No extra money, no extra hassle, no problems.
All I have to say, to Stewart is try emailing tech support before you
publish on somebody else's show.
Adam, thanks for the show.
I look forward to it every day.
I don't have my own show yet, but you can check out my website at www.busticated.net.
Also, be sure to check out my little brother's music on the pod save music network.
You can search for him under Andrew Bowerman.
Thanks a lot.
All right, okay.
Now, I just want to make sure you heard that because of opposing views.
Uh, I just have to wonder, I have a feeling that more people have been told
sorry you're out of luck than not.
So, you know, I haven't been able to find any type of policy that says you can get your music back.
And of course, with the sales on the unlabel, you have a little cubby hole area
through PMN where you can always go and read download your stuff,
so you can play it wherever you are.
Let's see, just a couple things, yeah.
I wanted to mention this thing about, where is it now?
About this congressman.
I think he's a congressman.
Let me just double check.
It's a good, uh, this is about that AT&T trying to own the net, uh,
Preston Garala posted this on, uh, I think on the curry.com comments.
AT&T Verizon and other telcos have been warning that they're going to demand money from Google
and other sites if those sites want adequate bandwidth.
But now a senator is proposing that to ban the practice and is standing up to the telcos
who are acting more like a cyber mafia than legitimate businesses.
Senator Ron Wyden of Oregon, Ron Wyden of Oregon today introduced legislation that would
ban network operators from charging sites for extra bandwidth.
The law would also ban the practice of favoring some content providers over others.
I think that's more important, actually, that according to the New York Times.
Other congressmen are, uh, uh, co-tiling to the telcos because the telcos are big campaign contributors.
They'd let the telcos do what they want and turn the internet into their own private network.
Okay, uh, the widen bill called the internet non-dense discrimination act of 2006.
Not a sexy name, but the Inda.
The Inda, everybody.
They, they, the faces tough sledding money talks and the telcos are doing a lot of talking.
Again, these are all comments from curry.com.
In addition, the FCC has made it clear, they won't take any action on the matter,
so we can look, we can't look to them for help.
So I say, um, could somebody please, you know, point out a link, you know,
how do you, how do you support this bill? Is that by, uh, emailing your congressmen or, uh, or emailing, uh,
Ron Wyden, what, what is the, what is the, what is the correct action?
And maybe collectively, if we all, uh, hand over some money is,
let's just, let's just fight money with funny, with funny with money.
Money with funny, baby, honey.
Let's just, uh, you know, collectively send a whole bunch of money to this guy, so we, you know,
and, and to other, uh, other people who support the bill, so they won't have to take money from the telcos.
And let, let your voices be heard. Let's see if, uh, this stuff actually works.
Now that we have voices, not just written voices, but real voices that can be heard.
Uh, thanks, uh, to everyone for all the vacation suggestions.
I guess you guys think I should take off, huh?
And I shouldn't podcast that all, I don't know if I can do that.
Uh, I definitely need, you know, internet wherever I am, just to keep up.
I had to empty out my Gmail inbox once in a while, so, you know, email doesn't start bouncing.
Um, but we're really going to go somewhere where virgin flies, and I think it's going to be either Antigua or Barbados.
So, uh, I'll, uh, let you know, but it is going to be the first week of April.
That's for sure, Patricia's birthday. It's going to be nice, Christina has vacation, very much looking forward to it.
Ken Wells has Adam your observation about stone people not getting arrested on cops was interesting.
I have noticed that the typical guy arrested on cops is not wearing a shirt.
In fact, in my home, as soon as the police interact with the guy with no shirt, we all say, he's going to jail.
That is kind of interesting.
No shirts. No shirt was definitely a way to get your ass lung in jail if you appear on cops.
All right, um, that's it. There's nothing really.
I can save all this stuff for more, more pots and music network stuff.
All right. Let's see. We did about 53 minutes, uh, overwhelmingly 99% of, uh, of all comments that came in said that, uh, you guys like the longer podcasts.
So, uh, there you go. 54 minutes today.
Tomorrow, we'll be back, uh, it's going to be a week home at the cottage on Friday evening.
We're going to go, uh, uh, on a little trip. I'll talk more about that later this week.
It's going to be the three of us. And, uh, oh, cheese. I can't believe I forgot the most important thing.
I wanted it. Well, not the most important. I forgot something really important today.
Shit. I want to do that at the beginning of the show. Well, this will show how many people listen to the whole thing.
On Monday, um, the wind commander and I are flying back with a Delta Sierra, which has been completely refurbished, is completely ready, completely done and ready to rock.
And this will be its final fairy flight, which means it's going to be, uh, stationed at Ferrox Echo Golf Tango Fox Trot here, uh, in the UK, not far from the house.
And, um, I'm going to need a safety pilot while the plane is here. And a safety pilot is someone who's an experienced pilot, um, who flies with you.
Um, you know, sometimes we'll take over part of the duties, but it's just kind of theirs and extra set of hands ears and predominantly eyes.
While I build up my, uh, my hours in, uh, you know, really someone who also knows the landscape knows the airways, everything.
And it just has some local knowledge of where I'll be doing most of my flying.
Um, so I'm looking for a safety pilot. And I thought, you know, there's so many people who are wishing me tailwinds has gone to be someone who knows somebody,
or maybe someone who's actually listening to this podcast directly, who, um, has the time available and, uh, obviously you're going to be a pilot.
I, you're going to have, uh, experience, um, it will be great if you had experience in the Cessna 182 RG, um, but it is, you know, complex aircraft.
It'll be great if you're a flight instructor and it'll be great if you have no job and are retired and just want to fly a lot and make some extra money on the side.
Uh, so, uh, send off, uh, and, you know, any contacts or anything, uh, or anybody you would know to animecurry.com.
Uh, and I, you know, I'd love to start on Monday if you're available.
So, uh, Monday or we could possibly make a Tuesday, but there's gotta be some pilot around here who was just, you know, just loves to fly.
And, uh, and has the time, you know, I'm pretty flexible. There'll be some overnight stays.
Basically, we would take everything, we'd pay some money, um, and, uh, and we'd have some fun as well. So, looking for the safety pilot.
Pass it on, everybody.
Goodbye, everybody. I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Another pod show pod guest. Stick it in your ear.