For the first time ever, the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr. in one action-packed DVD collection,
own all 27 episodes, the cult hit, including all new interviews with Carlton Koo.
First thing that Brisco did that impressed us was, we're not only to come in and really read the dialogue well as an actor,
but he also did a standing flip in our office.
You flipped too for Brisco County!
If you like the kind of TV you can't get on TV, get your copy of the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr.
Available now on DVD.
Pop on Microsoft, I'm burn for Marshall, 4-6-9 or...
Daily source code, 4-6-9.
I mean the DLC, 4-6-9.
The worst time at this, every time on the high, I'm head to where you're place.
The world that goes through the base is running through my mind.
I think of the day I leave all of the time.
This solution's up for myself, all running through my head.
You know where to go, but back from here, you know where to go, the way you take.
I can be now accountable for things of on your rise.
I can expect to win with you, and you want things to last.
Yeah, I know, it's more safe.
You will be the best one I've ever been.
Right, they say...
I tell I fight in action.
The fight inside my head, I'm twisted with no respect for future wishes.
The days go by up, come too fast.
You're a part of my future, like you're far from my path.
If you don't lose time, I'll bet they won't be alright.
It's a blessing count, and I've gone for the night.
This solution's up for myself, all running through my head.
You know where to go, but back from here, you know where to go, the way you take.
I can be now accountable for things of on your rise.
I can expect to win with you, and you want things to last.
Yeah, I know, it's more safe.
You will be the best one I've ever been.
Right, they say...
I tell I fight in action.
You know where to go, but back from here, you know where to go, the way you take.
You know where to go, the way you take.
I tell I fight in action.
It's a blessing count, and I've gone for the night.
You know where to go, the way you take.
Yeah, I know, it's more safe.
You will be the best one I've been.
Right, they say...
I tell I fight in action.
Step behind.
Back in action from the pods, safe music network.
Why that song, you're asking, well, I'm in an emo mood, my friends.
Yes, an emo mood indeed.
We were so happy.
You know, the house that we finally agreed to sail on the curry colosseum, got a phone call yesterday.
You're not going to believe this.
It's like, what kind of luck are we having with this lately?
There's a covenant on the house.
The house was built in 1976.
This covenant dates back to then, so that's 30 years.
A covenant that says that the garage, as you and I would say, may not be converted for use for anything other than a garage.
This unfortunately was exactly where we planned to have the new kitchen.
Since the existing kitchen was going to become my office and studio, it actually has a built-in studio compartment.
You know, soundproof and everything.
Of course, the door opens so we can still hear the trash collectors.
But now it's gotten all complicated and we have to go to the council and figure out what this covenant can be removed.
What was the intent of the covenant?
It's really, really, it's all this appointing.
So now we have to do two things.
Go through that process and also try to reconfigure the work that we wanted to have done to see if we can still fit in.
I am that may require planning permission.
You see why I'm emo.
You see?
Maybe this will cheer me up.
Hi Adam and Patricia.
This is Ali from Swingercast.
Oh, man, she's not here.
But it's okay.
I'll pass the message.
I mean, pass your message.
I've been thinking, you know, 69 has always been my favorite number, but 469.
Hmm, that's even better.
That's my new favorite number.
That's a hot combo.
469.
John tells me you like to have people send you naked pictures.
Check your mailbox.
Folder or scruncher?
I guess I'm by.
I do them both.
I fold and scrunch.
How about that?
Delta Sierra Charlie number 469.
All right.
Feel much better now.
Everybody.
It's episode 469 coming to you from Curry Cottage in the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Gilford.
The pod show SF crew coming in over the next two days.
So it's going to be real busy.
Should be able to squeak out a Friday Charlie for you.
Although I'll have to do it from the hotel room.
I think I'm going to stay Thursday night.
London in order to get a fresh start Friday.
Because we have the digital musical words coming up on Tuesday.
It's just busy and busy back in San Francisco as well as we have yet another fantastic podcast
Joining our pod show lineup.
Adam, this is Chris Christensen.
I thought I'd give your listeners a little taste.
With the amateur traveler podcast, it's like sometimes it goes to exotic locations.
If you're not sure you've seen Star Wars on that's land and they don't ever bar.
It was exactly like that.
Where we hear wonderful things.
Sometimes we inform.
There's a smaller museum up a little way.
It's not a bad walk.
Called Lorojiri.
Or just a muse.
The monastery of the royal bath with the nuns.
Adam.
Of course.
I did it.
And sometimes both.
And in my plate there was kind of this gloppy looking thing with a little bit of meat.
Turns out I got the penis and test.
Oh, the amateur traveler podcast.
Amateurtraveler.com.
All right.
Congratulations.
Welcome to the family.
I've been listening to the amateur traveler podcast for a while.
I like it.
I love all kinds of travel podcasts, especially if they include kind of like the sound
seeing sound, seeing tours.
Where you're actually on location talking to people.
I love stuff about different food.
Not too sure about the testicle.
I think's really catchy.
It's the one that everyone rebelled against.
And then Jeff Smith Smith even sent in a new one and a new voice mail comment line number
Jingle.
But this one is catchy, man.
You can just remember it as I plus one.
6256357.
And for the UK plus four four two zero seven six eight one three seven five three.
Mess just coming in from around the globe.
Hey, Adam.
My name is Christopher.
I'm a podcast from Germany.
I've said this before.
There's something about German speaking English that I love.
It's just I can listen to it all day long.
There's not enough German podcasters doing English podcast.
Please do more of that because I can listen to it all day long.
Okay, continue.
I got a solution for the problems with the PMN and the Blossom Germany.
I found an article at Heizet.de where you can read in that the
Gemma and Germany got a partnership with the American Associations.
I think they are called Ask Open PMI.
So what it basically means is that the Gemma can only provide the rights.
They got from the Ask Open PMI and Ask Open PMI.
Don't have the rights for the songs on the potsafe music network.
What it means is that we in Germany are allowed to play all the songs from the potsafe music network.
But that wasn't the only reason for sending this audio comment.
I don't know if your logic holds water there.
Be it.
I don't know.
You know what?
It's hard.
I don't want the show to turn into like a legal show.
The daily legal stores code.
I just.
You know, I got nothing against lawyers personally, but just a whole process.
You know, now I'm going to have to go through all this legal crap with it.
Forget about it.
What's the other reason you call my friend?
I also want to ask you if there would be maybe a German Potion network.
My podcast is on the American Potion network, but a German Potion network
maybe would be better for us in Germany than putting our stuff on the American one.
So my podcast is now on dailypot.potion.com.
Check it out.
Thanks, Adam.
I'm a folder.
Ah, yeah.
I want to choose who's got.
Yeah.
Well, I wouldn't mind doing a country for a specific version of Potion.
That would be cool.
But, you know, we have to find some partners as what we did here in the UK.
And I'm just, you know, we don't have anyone in Germany right now.
But we could put together some kind of something cool.
Well, it would be feasible.
It cost a lot of money.
You know, it just doesn't mean these things happen.
It really does.
BTpodshow.com is coming along quite nicely.
I've seen on the internal network and cost us some amazing content that's being sent in.
Hi there, Adam.
It's Mike Cooper here.
He's calling regarding some charity events coming up.
I thought you'd be interested in.
And this I'm Mike Reciple C has actually access for free screenings of the devil
where's Prada, the film starring Merrill Streep, and half the way.
And your listeners have got the chance to see it before it goes on general release.
It's all part of raising money for breakthrough breast cancer.
There'll be volunteers on the evening collecting money.
And so hopefully listeners can go along and participate in this.
The screenings are completely free.
We're taking place across the UK in Gateshead, Edinburgh, Manchester, Belfast and Bristol.
And if anyone's interested, they can go along to the website to register for tickets.
The address is www.nessan.co.uk.
And just click the devil words prior to link.
Thanks a lot.
Bye bye.
Was that a commercial?
Was that a commercial for Nissan?
What the hell was that?
Let me just check the sound for a second.
Let me see what that...
I thought he said Nissan.co.uk.
What are they doing?
How are they sponsoring this?
Hold on a second.
Nissan.co.
Not getting paid for this one by the way.
But it sounds like a pretty cool, pretty cool deal for each hit.
Hmm.
Maybe I misunderstood it.
It's server not found.
How was that?
Nissan.co.uk.
Didn't he?
Hold on a second.
I'll rewind it.
Nissan.co.uk.
Sounds like it is www.nessan.co.
You can.
And just click the devil words prior to link.
Thanks a lot.
Bye bye.
Maybe after www, which is very old fashioned.
Oh, shit.
It's working.
Nissan.
Get your shit together guys.
Nissan.co.uk should work as well.
Okay.
The devil words prior to where is it?
I don't see that.
Hmm.
Services, vehicles, inside Nissan.
Special offers.
Maybe it's under special offers.
I don't know.
Surfing.
So you don't have to.
Not mind.
I'll check it later.
If I find the actual link to what he's talking about.
Of course, I'll put that into the show notes.
A daily source code.com.
Anyway, good deal.
Nissan's doing that.
I gave it his Nissan if they're doing it for.
For breast cancer.
And you can get a free screening out of it.
And actually as a movie, I do want to see.
I'd love to take Patricia, but it didn't sound like they were doing anything in London.
Mr. Curry.
I was out taking my dog for a walk today.
And I realized there's a particular area that we walk through.
That is very affluent.
There is generally three or four cars on the.
Big driveways.
And these are, you know, not, not the cheap cars.
These are big expensive cars.
Several of these houses.
If you look at them from the Google Earth, you'll see.
Swimming pools in the back garden.
I don't think any one of them that's got a helipad.
But I wouldn't be surprised if they had.
And then I realized that that's where name of this lane.
Explains it all, really.
It's called Folders Lane.
Exactly.
I thank you so much for taking a picture of it.
I put it in as the album march for today's show.
If you're listening to this on, uh,
we know's media player or real player or, um,
or even quick time and an iPod or, uh,
the pod show player you'll see.
Folders Lane.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
An affluent suburb indeed.
Are you tired of trying to go through the 30 plus songs that they are
to upload to the five safe music network?
Do you want to know when your favorite artists are both in the track?
Let me do the work for you.
You need today.
Only plays the newest pod safe music from the pod safe music network.
This six-minute podcast will play one song from the pod safe music network
most weekdays.
Come check us out today at newmusic today.net
or newmusic today.possil.com.
I'll take that.
I got the show.
I got it.
I thought that was good.
Yeah.
I love getting the new music.
So if you're going to put one together every single day now,
make sure that you don't just put the music out there.
But you actually make a show because you can't just redistribute it.
But I know what you're doing.
So that's cool man.
Very good idea.
I wouldn't mind if you played a couple more.
Give me.
It seems like every day there's between.
I think on average it must be about 20 new tracks that are uploaded to the pod safe music.
Now we're going to play another one at the end of the show, obviously.
And I have, uh, yes.
The official musicologist slash ambulance,
Chaser of the Charlie Jersey Todd will be coming up in just moments to weigh in
about the Apple trying to trademark podcast controversy.
But first, information about urine.
Hey, this is Bubba at the, uh,
a lot of punk podcast at a lot of punk.
Uh, podshow.com.
Listen, the reason you're pissed now is because the spirit has a,
in time in it called, uh,
lots of silver based things on called Mark Captain.
And if you have a special jean in your body that breaks it down even further,
makes it smell like, uh, I don't know, like, scump this.
That says because you've got that jean.
Hey, onions, garlics.
Uh, I didn't say it smell like scump this.
Scunks aren't very nice smelling.
Uh, I can't, I told you I was on the border where they're like this.
Oh, no, but I don't think it's scump this.
All those, they'll do the same thing.
Uh, plus hey, the service has got lots of fiber,
vitamins, good stuff like that.
One of them telling you one thing that's kind of disappointed about with the
digital music awards.
Go hold on a second. Okay.
So that's kind of solved.
I guess it's a jean.
That's very interesting.
A jean.
So it's the sulfur.
I did read this.
A lot of people sent me information about it.
And not everybody has this smell.
And I'm wondering, of course, you know how my mind works.
I'm immediately wondering.
Is there a correlation, perhaps,
between this jean that makes your urine smell like scunk piss.
And scrunchers or folders.
Or not at all.
And I appreciate you playing country music on the show.
There aren't so wild.
Listen, you want some good work in the country.
Come do at wallpongs. podshow.com.
Any time, listen.
And above us, thanks for the show.
I'm older.
No, I'm above, but thank you, man.
Yeah.
Um, that's interesting.
You say that about the digital musical awards.
I, um, it's an English award as far as I know.
It's, or it's very, uh, Anglo-centric.
And it's sponsored by British telecom.
And you know what?
Country music.
It just does not go over very well in the UK.
Hey, Adam.
This is Murphy from Murphy's Salute podcast.
Home of the Blues.
Um, I'm calling about the comment you just made on, uh,
the SC468 about, um,
what I call a Sparigus P.
It's an enzymatic, as I understand it.
It's an enzymatic reaction of the body that, uh,
only 15% of the population have.
They don't know exactly what causes it,
except it's an enzymatic reaction.
And, uh, that's it.
I, uh, you imagine you'll probably hear from some doctors,
but that's the simplest explanation that I know.
Yeah.
Take care.
Love the show.
Um, former smudger.
Oh, very good.
A convert.
Fantastic.
Welcome to the club.
Yeah.
It's weird.
I didn't know that it was only 15% of the people.
And, uh, and now that I think back it, you know,
that it could very well be possible.
But it's something genetic.
So that's interesting.
Uh, again, uh, I post to you the test.
Is this something that might even fit into our scrunchers and folders?
Okay.
The iPod podcast trademarking debate.
Yesterday I weighed in, gave you my comments.
You can occur with Rob Walsh of podcast war on one podcast.
He had the, uh, the similar analysis.
And he really called out a lot of the journalists.
You know, I went back and read some of the, uh, some of the reports.
He sums them up quite nicely in his podcast.
Uh, and everyone's talking about season to cyst letters.
And you know, they'd never even seen the letter.
Hadn't it all?
And of course, the only way to really find out what is going on with this.
And who stands to gain or lose what and who's right and who's wrong.
Is to ask a lawyer.
Of course.
You're on her.
I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out.
Please don't bang that gavel.
You can try this cowbell out.
Let's all give a nod.
To the hardest work and lawyer.
He's charging time.
And then he's charging time.
Yo, what's up, Adam?
It's Jersey Todd.
The host of the Jersey Todd show.
The official musicologist of the Cha Cha.
But listen.
I'm not here today to talk about food bar Friday or any of the good stuff happening over
the podcast.
Music network.
Note today, I'm here in my official capacity as the pod show pro bono attorney.
And while I've been listening to this wonderful discussion.
We've been having regarding the iPod trademark debate.
And listen, I got to thank you for your referral.
And I got to thank you for the bill.
I got to remind you of one really, really important thing.
Dude, I'm a worker's compensation attorney.
I chase ambulance this all day.
I mean, the last time that I messed around with copyright.
I was getting like a C plus on my final exam.
I mean, I have as much practical and working knowledge of copyright law as downtown Julie Brown.
So with a big wobble, wobble, wobble, wobble.
Let me give you my thoughts on the matter.
The first.
Oh, nice is that.
A lawyer who tells the truth that he doesn't know shit about what he's talking about.
Oh, it's so refreshing.
This thing is clearly Apple has filed a trademark on this.
It's enforceable and there's laws regarding it.
I mean, that's the stupid answer.
But when I, in hearing yesterday, sounded like you were saying that this was, you know,
not a cease and desist letter.
And this was actually kind of sort of nice of Apple to send a letter like this out.
I don't know how nice a letter it was.
Look, I don't think it was a letter that they sent out in preparation of suing somebody.
I think it's something that they want having their files down the road.
It's a letter that they send out to prevent something called a generic side.
You see, if a trademark holder fails to actively enforce their trademark, then the trademark could
fall into public domain and then anybody could use it.
Yeah, that's a great headline, isn't it?
That's a really good one.
Apple computer practices generic side.
Or do we practice generic side on Apple computer?
That's, yeah, that's the way it is.
Podcasting community exercises right of generic side on Apple computers.
For example, bear.
They originally copyrighted aspirin.
Uh, but the courts of ruled the United States that that trademark fell into public domain.
So other companies may use that name.
Uh, zerox for copiers and bandage for it.
He's a bandages.
Well, they're both trademarks, which are at risk of subcoming to a generic side.
So when it comes down to it, not necessarily a friendly letter, but not necessarily an unfriendly letter either.
It was a letter written by a corporation to make a hundred percent sure that they can control their trademarks
and their branding and protect themselves in the future.
And the folks with iPod want to make sure that the term pod doesn't entirely fall even more so into public domain.
And in some respects from what I can tell Apple is being extremely aggressive in maintaining this trademark.
So there you have it.
That's my two cents on it.
This is Jersey Todd of the Jersey Todd Show.
Oh crap.
Todd Show.
Oh, man.
I got to go.
Hey, listen, take it easy pod father with the podcast on the pod show with podcast delivery network.
Oh, man.
I freaking hate lawyers.
I love you, man.
Except for the part about the billable hours.
Everything else is cool.
Yeah, I agree.
Genericide.
Very good.
Yeah, that's true.
That's exactly what it's about.
And I agree with you.
Total consensus they're confer on the fact that Apple is using, you know, is doing this now because they have to.
To combat genericide.
And I don't foresee too many too many problems.
I don't.
It's just about doing stuff with actual mobile media devices and calling something pod around that.
That's going to be an issue.
And at the end of the day, whoever has the biggest lawyers is bound to win.
You know how that works.
But then again, can we just close this chapter?
I think we should.
I think I'm kind of done with it.
Those you're listening to us on serious stars.
One, two great line up for you today.
I'll tell you about that in a second.
And what you're not going to hear is another great pod safe.
A music track, which the guys will actually, they've been nominated for a digital music award.
Too bad.
Because you guys will be able to hear it.
Wait a minute.
Let me just, I got one more thing about the, the iPod.
Just because it's a buddy.
I want to play Kevin Reeves, everybody.
Hey, animal candidates, Kevin Reeves.
And I've got a way in on this pod issue.
Because there's, there's some certain things about it that are completely ridiculous.
First of all, you said in the letter that Apple started using the term iPod.
And I told her of 2001.
And since then, they have been the first to blend a portable electronic device as being called pod.
Any musician listening?
Anybody else on a little kidney bean shape device from a company called Line 6 called Brace yourself?
The pod, which was outweighed before iPod ever came onto the scene.
I think I bought my pod used in string of 2000.
And it had been out for a couple months before that.
So come on, Apple, get real.
This is like the, the techno Gestapo here.
I mean, I love Apple.
I love my G4.
I love what they've been able to do for technology and for special musicians.
But, but come on, Apple, this is, this is, just get real.
The other problem is that they say that you can't use the word pod in any kind of electronic device.
They're going to pick off M audio.
Anyone own an M audio, fire pod.
Which is a sound card flash audio interface.
Sure, a lot of pod cache is a part of it, and use it.
So anyway, just, just thought I would put my 20 cents in.
And, uh, keep up the good work, dude.
And check me out at Kevin Reeves.net and the scourron shower.
Yeah, Kevin. Now, and you know what I like, you man.
I appreciate what you do.
And I love, I love your, your music.
I love your art.
Your work is fantastic.
But I think this is the kind of stuff we can do without.
I mean, this whole Apple thing, which started off unfairly with a really bad report from
Wired Magazine, talking about a cease and desist letter, which was not the case.
They had not even seen the letter in, in my regard otherwise.
Why would they even use those words?
It just creates this storm in a, in a, in a cup of tea, you know, a storm in a glass of water.
Is that the expression?
It's just, it just gives everyone a reason to fucking blog.
It's dumb.
And hopefully it'll stop now, but I have a feeling that the conversation will continue.
And it'll eventually, here's what's going to happen.
In a few weeks from now, you'll be able to see in Wikipedia under podcasting, because this is how it always goes.
Some version of the story that Apple computer is vehemently trying to register a podcast as a trademark.
Yeah, and it's just not the entire story.
And it's unfortunate, but that's the way it goes.
That's Apple's problem on my problem.
I've had that myself, those several times.
That's why bigger small, like the stick up for someone who's being falsely accused, particularly when the emotions run high.
All right, fucking.
Let's play some music, shall we?
nominated for a digital musical award.
It's drug mu.
I'll play a digital musical award.
I'll play a digital award.
You know, yes, ma'am could have used some cowbell definitely.
I would have liked to have explored the studio space with the cowbell nominated for a digital
music award.
The ceremony is taking place this Tuesday.
There will be plenty of podcasting video casting associated with the event.
We're doing a whole bunch of stuff there and it's going to be fun.
I hope we'll be able to bring some of it to you around the globe.
As always, I want to thank sponsors of the Daily Source Code.
Well, I actually want to tell you to go over to bgblast.podshow.com, Christina Martinez
Me doing a show over there.
Go Daddy for a 495 if you use a checkout code DSC3 for ordering a domain name.
Anything you like.
And of course, there's the accurate target cast.
If you want to know more about the accurate RDX SUV, accurate dot that's ACURA.podshow.com.
I've got a hurry up.
Although what are we going to do now?
30, 31, 32 minutes.
I have a call with David Epilito, that guitar man from New York.
I'm going to talk about doing some stuff together.
So by the way, he's one of the check this link.
He's one of the finalists of the Earthlink ad challenge.
At you can hear actually all the finalists are at earthlink.podshow.com.
That how easy is it, everybody?
DailySourceCode.com for all of the links.
Particularly if you want to know more about a Sparagus P.
Adam at podshow.com for everything else.
We'll talk tomorrow, everybody. Bye-bye.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.