This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and Go Daddy.
Want killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
This is Delta Sierra Charlie 457.
My name is Matt Weinstein, the Jewish Lesbian, I am a little free ski, and I hate George W.
But I love Adam Carey, and I am funny.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, and the next generation
radio content in my ears.
Carey, this is not Antonio Panteras, but this is the judge, all 57.
Until we add him, his wife will mainly be greeted on your list, because Patricia is on mine.
Why is marijuana not legal?
It's a natural plant that grows in the dirt.
You know, it's not natural, 80-year-old dudes with hard-ons.
That's not natural, but we got pills for that.
We're dedicating all our medical resources to keeping the old guys erect, but we're
putting people in jail for smoking something that grows in the dirt.
You know, we have more prescription drugs now, that every commercial out TV is a prescription
drug add.
I can't watch TV for four minutes without the guy who has five serious diseases.
Like, you have a wake up tired in the morning, I'm like, God, I have this right to
down whenever it is I have it.
At the time, you don't even know what the commercial is, if people run it through fields
or fly kites or swim in the ocean like that is the greatest disease ever, how to get
that.
That disease comes with a hot chick and a puppy.
Schools and how it's all about self-esteem and a school, build a kid self-esteem, make
them feel good about themselves.
If everybody grows up with high self-esteem, who's going to dance in our strip clubs?
What's going to happen?
Our 4-0 industry.
These women don't just grow on trees and takes lots of drunk datties, missing a lot of
dance recitals before you decide to blow a goat on the internet for 50 bucks.
And if that disappears, where does that lead me on a Friday with my new high-speed
connection?
Mastermind's another word that comes up all the time, do you keep hearing about these
terrorists?
Mastermind's are being killed up in the middle of these terrorists.
Mastermind's sort of a lofty area to describe what these guys do, don't you think they're
not mastermind's?
Okay, you'll take farm, right?
And you'll put it back back and you'll get on the bus and you'll blow yourself up.
Why do I have to blow myself up?
Who's the king mastermind here, real you?
Americans, let's face it.
We've been a spoiled country for a long time, you know what the number one health risk in
America is?
Obesity, obesity.
They say we're in the middle of an obesity epidemic.
And epidemic, like it's polio, like we'll be telling our grandkids about it one day,
the great obesity epidemic of 2004, had to get through a grand pie.
Oh, it was horrible, Charney, there was cheese, cake, and pork chops everywhere.
Nobody knows why we're getting fat, or look at our lifestyle, and I'll sit in a drive
to us at different.
I'll sit there, be on 15 other cars, instead of getting up and making a paper walk to the
totally empty counter, everything's a mega meal, super size, won't biggie fries with
that one, a jumbo fried one, a collage, one, a biggie fries, one, a 30-puggest
for a niggly, a prime on the floor, there's room in the back, take it.
One, a 55 gallon drum, a coke with that, it's only three more cents.
Sometimes you've got to suffer a little in your youth, the motor may use to see later
in life.
You think if Bill Gates got laid in high school, you think there'd be a Microsoft?
Of course not, you've got to spend a lot of time, stuff in your own locker with your
underwear, wedge stuff, you're asked before you start thinking, and I want to take
all the world with computers, you'll see, I'll show them.
We're in one of the richest countries in the world, and the minimum wages is lower now
than it was 35 years ago.
They're homeless people everywhere.
This homeless guy asked me for money the other day, I was about to give it to him, and I
thought he's just going to use it on drugs or alcohol.
And then I thought, that's what I'm going to use it on.
Why am I judging this poor bastard?
People love to judge homeless guys like you get in the money, he's just going to waste
it, he's going to waste the money.
Well, he lives in a box, what do you want him to do with it, save it up by a wall, you
want to take a little run of the store for a throw rug and a CD rack, he's homeless.
I walk behind this guy the other day, a homeless guy asked him for money, he looked
right at the homeless guy, he was much better, I'm going to get a job of him, people always
saying that to homeless guys, get a job, like it's always that easy, this homeless guy
would learn his underwear outside his pants, I'm guessing his resume ain't all up
to date.
I'm predicting some problem during the interview process, I'm pretty sure even
McDonald's has an underwear go inside the pants policy, not the day important, very strictly,
but technically I'm sure it's on the books.
Now the suggestion was, smoke some of the only herb, then listen to the song, but I don't
think that's even necessary.
Thank you very much Sam Green for suggesting that, let me give you all the details,
it's not on the pod save music network, you can find it's lazy boy and you can find it
on, what is it on my space?
Yeah, so I'll put a link to that in the show notes, wow that was awesome, like all
the bomb is going to do is spend the money on drugs now alcohol, wait a minute, that's
what I do with the money, everybody welcome to the daily store's code episode number 457
coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey, it's known as Gilford in the United Kingdom,
my name is Adam Curry, and not it's another beautiful day, I don't care where you are,
what time it is, what you're where there's like, I'm just happy about what we're seeing
outside today and we've got a great show, a lot of response about half of the interview
Ron and I did, being held hostage by Joseph Jaffey, so your comments on that coming
up in this program, program, and of course some other nice little late bits and it's
Thursday and I almost, it's almost a regular feature now and I'm just loving it, get my
ass back in shape, it is, what do I do today, Amy?
It is day six of the Save Adam's ass camp, and I'm Amy Mack, right on, I got to tell
you, I'll be instructing you, I'm Clea Squat, Clea Squat, how you doing, I'm doing good
bathing fantastic, all right, let's get started, you're going to remain standing and your
legs are going to be wide apart, okay, wide apart, wide enough to squat, yet not wide enough
to fall over, okay, now this is a new one, so listen carefully, I want your toes to point
out to the side, and now you're going to squat making sure that you keep your chest, shoulders
and head straight up, okay, so, you want to go as far as you can or until you're even
with your knee, and then come back up, even with my knee, okay, okay, again you have
seven more, he's in the butt, his knees are in the same line as your legs, six, he's in the
butt, of course the knees don't come over the toes, five, he's in the butt, good, keep
breathing, four, he's in the butt, three, she's the tall, he's in the butt, two, I
want you to hold the last one down in the squat, all the way down, all the way down, 20 seconds
to go, watch, this is a great leg and butt exercise, it also focuses on balance and stability
too, right Adam, yes, yes, right up, 10 seconds, as always you can find me at fitness.potshow.com
okay Adam, you can come out, feeling pretty good, like crap, the answer is supposed to be great,
I can do more sets, oh well, next time, hey me back, he was so mean, hey me back,
I was prepared for it, I have something ready to go, well I catch a breath here,
this the hands of me, greetings, open more hands, I am Valquire, I can do, I'm in the god box,
a place you can linger before you make your way home, put down your swords, park your trusty
state, and leave your troubles here, one problem at a time, tonight, here's your cup of
meat, drink tea, three, then ask me any questions, brush to shortage, they will be answered as well,
oh man, see I was prepared this time, I had a promo standing by so I catch my breath,
you know Amy Mag does it to me every single time, is that last set and then she makes you hold this
for 20 seconds, did you try that, did you actually try that squat that she suggested for and hold
it for 20 seconds after you already done seven, it really hurt my thighs though, it was burning in my
thighs in my knees and wait a minute, no there is a little bit of burning sensation in my ass,
thank you Amy Mag, yesterday I told you the story about an interview that Ron Blumen I did,
it was about an hour and a half, we scheduled multiple time zones with this new marketing podcast
from Joseph Jeffy called across the sound and so he split it up into two parts and I told him
you know you shouldn't edit it at all, just do the whole thing, and so he decided to split that
interview into two parts over two episodes, which is not his choice, I don't like it at all,
I just don't like that personally as a listener, as a user, but then he went on this whole thing
about I hadn't sent him any love, no link, love, no traffic and so he was holding
part two of the interview hostage and so I kind of went off on that yesterday and of course immediately
revoked his permission to use any other part of as of yet un-aird part of our interview, forget about it,
I kind of made it my bitch, hey Adam it's Kevin Crossman from the Frappac podcast,
man you laid down the smack, that was awesome, when you told off Joseph and he held your interview
hostage and now you're holding his podcast hostage, I love it, I mean what did the guy expect?
Did he send you a promo, three to play, no did he talk to you about it, you know that you
needed to show him some love before you do your interview, no, if he did then that might be
sure, but I'm sure he didn't, you are the man Adam Curry, Boulder, thank you, well a lot of people
checked in including someone who always has advice and can tell you what to do when you're in trouble,
it's a little bit different though unfortunately, Peter I'm a satellite repair man coming after
you, satellite repair man watching on a new hill that you're missing,
and answer questions too, learn nothing in the universe and you can't do for you, a satellite repair man,
whew, satellite repair man, here it goes, I need money, Adam you owe me brother,
in your effort to put a snotty podcast or in his place, and the moral of that story is
not to give interviews to shows that nobody listens to anyway, in that effort you insulted
two of my favorite people, first, I didn't hear, I don't know if he added a lot, it didn't sound
like it in the first half, maybe some bits, maybe his own stumbles that he took out, that's that's
pretty typical, that's what Rob does, a forward podcast four on one, is he takes out all the
ohms in the stumbles that he does, it's just so, it's so contrary to what I like, I made an appearance
on Rob's podcast four one one show and let me tell you, the majority of the editing was done on me,
if Rob had chosen to leave that show on edited, it would have been, it would have been actually
entertaining is what you're trying to say, I hate it when you're editing, why? We don't have
any network news to hit, there's no penalty, who cares if you're stumbling and bump, you're
human, that's what it's about, I love it, that was, you know, I keep reminding myself, that's the
first thing I loved about independently produced audio entertainment, it was raw and it was like,
it wasn't those can things that were so used to, I love the rawness, it would have sounded
actually entertaining, Peter, at least an hour longer and people would have had no doubt as to why
I don't do digital flats in life and second, you will, I guarantee you that you have a very different
image of what Joseph Jaffee looks like, because actually he's a good looking guy, as, you know,
as guys go, but he sounds like, you know, Roger Smalls territory, that was just rude, without Roger,
Uncle Jesse, the satellite repairman wouldn't even exist, he wait, that's right, screw him that
little twitch, oh we haven't heard from Roger in a while, I'm sure this will evoke some sort of
response, Peter, thank you. Oh yeah, there's more where that came from. Hi, this message is for Adam
Curry, my name is John Carman, I'm calling from the G-spotted division of G-mix.com, we are a queer
podcast and we're putting together a conference on Metro Sexual Identities and I wanted to invite you to
sit your Metro Sexual Ask Down on my panel, you could reach me at 412, oh fuck shit, okay, I've got to
redo that, all right, take it, take it, oh crap, shit, fuck, you didn't want us to, um, you didn't want us
to, um, edit, so all right, I'll try to be as wrong as possible, I just had a spare moment and figured
I'd give you a call on a second, hold it. Yeah, I just had a question about something you said on your show,
um, no, if we bend over, you'll not only give us love, but an interview, you know, I, uh,
like, by personally, I'm tempted, but I can't bend over, Sam, I'm already game married to another
big head, that's in the 80s, so, uh, what I can offer you is, uh, some of the drag queens and maybe
a trans-secret, we're two from our show, the G-spotted, give me a call, let me know.
Right. I was when I made Joseph Jaffee bend over and told him he was my bitch, I didn't say what was
happening, of course. Now Joseph Jaffee sent back a very lengthy MP3 file with an apology, but it wasn't
sincere. And, you know, and I'm only partially kind of, you know, making fun of this situation,
because, well, shit, something to talk about, right? Uh, but it, to me, if he thinks that, okay,
so now he sends me the apology and now we've created a little bit of buzz and, uh, and now everyone's
talking about it, now they're going to go listen, that's like, no, no, yeah, the, uh, the band is
still on Joseph, um, so there's no, what you sent me, I'm not even going to play it. That's how
pathetic it was as an apology. And, you know what, I'm doing it for your protection. If people
actually heard what you said, you know, they think that you're a douche because you, you know,
you clearly, you're trying to get some traffic to your show, which I think, uh, you know,
you're, you're, you're the new marketing podcast guru. This is it. This is how you do new marketing.
I don't think so. I'm not playing that game. Home, we don't play that game.
And others agree totally.
Hi, Mr. Curry. It's column was all here and I was just listening to show four, five, six.
And, uh, I've started that you haven't been playing enough of my audio comments. And, uh,
I'm holding your show hostage. Um, if this audio comments not played on the net show,
I actually refused to listen to podcast anymore.
Um, it seems that the revolution has begun. And, uh, I hope you understand my terms. Thanks. Bye.
So, unlike, uh, unlike George W. Bush, we do talk to terrorists here on the Charlie.
And, uh, that was an easy one. Good. So, we saved one listener there, fantastic. But, Joseph,
you're not other words, man. In fact, uh, since you have not been capable of coming up with
some kind of fantastic, uh, penalty or punishment for your horrible horrific deed,
I'm going to open that up to the listeners of the Charlie. And, uh, they're going to decide what
your punishment should be for this clearly, clearly way off base action that you've bestowed upon me.
So, you know how to do it? Call into the voice mail.
One, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven.
Now so many people hate that, that jingle. I just keep playing it until you send me a better one.
Voice mail number, if you're entering it into your mobile phone, put the plus in it for, in, in,
in front of the number, plus one, two, zero, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven,
in London, 0207, six, eight, one, three, seven, five, three. Let me know what you think the
punishment should be for Joseph Jaffee's heinous crime. Hey Adam, this is Christopher Penn from
the Financial Aid podcast with a tinfoil hat moment about scrunching, folding, and what it says about
you. Use my conspiracy theory. You, Adam, career, are the party committing the conspiracy here.
Using the scruncher of folder survey to assess the socioeconomic background of the audience members.
What am I talking about? Scrunching and folding is largely a function of the quality of toilet
they we use. Good quality, higher cost toilet paper can be folded easily. Poor quality,
commercial grade toilet paper, like you find in fast food restaurants and rest areas and,
you know, highways, folds poorly because of its lack of quality. Mix it nearly impossible to fold.
Most of us learned our bathroom habits when we were young. Our homes growing up had a level of
toilet paper quality that dictated that our parents and therefore us, scrunched or folded when we
learned how to first use the bathroom. To where the papers are commodity, if you're cutting
gossip home, it's one of the first areas to be cut. And therefore it could be used as a
predictor of your socioeconomic background. The habits you learned then are still likely with you today.
Scruncher of folder tells the tale of your background and it's Adam Curry's secret waves
assessing your socioeconomic status. It's not 100% reliable by any means, but I would bet a whole
role of Sherman that the correlation is there. This is Christopher Penn from the financial aid podcast
with another tinfoil hat moment. See you all at Pod Camp this weekend. Yeah, that's really interesting.
Interesting analysis there, Chris, and I really do appreciate it, of course, with your tinfoil hat
moment. I should have done tinfoil tinfoil at moments.
But as I've said before, that doesn't really hold true because the richest guy I know who is
worth more than $100 million has his own aircraft and is a very nice guy is a scruncher.
So it doesn't really hold water. Now, of course, I'm sure there's got to be some kind of adjustment
for you and your calculations there. But that's not really why I said it up. The only reason I want to
know if someone is a scruncher of folder is, well, I can play the song, of course.
Hey, this is Sharon and tampon and just giving you a little bit of birthday wish and
listener profile female 41 widow mother of two boys. I'm an architect though. I haven't played
a net game for a while. I'm an online retailer and I'm a scruncher by nature, but I'm trying to
learn to fold. I have to say I like it better, but don't always think about it. Don't always remember
and, you know, frankly, just doesn't matter. But love the show. Thank you, bye.
Oh, thank you. I appreciate that so much. Single mom of two, everybody.
A milk sent me naked pictures. Please. Hello, Adam. This is Terry. Let me start off by saying I'm sorry.
I missed your birthday, but here's a belated birthday greeting. I'm creeping up on the same age.
So don't let anybody give you out hard time. It's really not worth it. You were looking for some
feedback on how your listeners are. Well, you know, the one area that you haven't touched
as far as your listeners and the spectrum is poetry or writing. You do excellent work with music
and pod show and the pod safe music network are awesome. I use them all the time. You've also
turned me on to several new podcasts. And I thank you very much, by the way, shuttle falls. Oh,
please, gotta keep it coming. Excellent. The drama. Anyway, happy birthday, belated, and
keep doing what you do because you make a lot of people very, very happy. This is Terry Witterdorf,
better known as the little red from Little Red's writing hood. Let me read.
Find the podcast. It's somewhere. Anyway, have a great day and keep Patricia on the phone.
You guys are awesome together. Bye for now. Bye. Love you. Me and it.
Yes. No, I was going to say something. I can't remember what I was going to say about that.
Anyway, thank you very much. I appreciate it daily source code.com or adamantpodshow.com.
And don't forget to keep your promos coming in through promos.podshow.com. We're going to start
something new on our serious satellite window. We've got four hours a day on the serious satellite
stars network channel 102. And we now and besides the shows that we have a rotation and we're
rotating more and more shows since we have, I was like a thousand shows on the network now.
Since we have so many of them, we're just trying to get as many people exposed as possible.
Those you're listening to serious stars want to know that by now every week they have to
new between six and ten you hear it all. But we also want to, since we, you know, there's no way
to feature everybody. You want to put in promos. So get your 60 second promos. Can be 30 seconds
but no longer than 60 seconds. I know it's counterintuitive to what pod castings all about, but
in the linear satellite world, we have, we do have top of the hours and commercial breaks to hit
and stuff like that. So put that at promos.podshow.com and we're going to set it up so
when you are featured, you'll know all about it. And of course, that happens every single day.
Monday through Friday from six in the afternoon to 10 in the evening, Eastern time on
serious stars 102. I'm going to do one more thing here for you and then we'll play a song.
I won't check this out. Hey, I don't make long time listener first time caller, not really
calling the first time. I know three or how long I second. Why is it mono?
I hate this. Can I make it mono like that? It was Mike. I was on the one channel. The hell was that?
It didn't sound like one channel when I set it up. Wait a minute. Maybe I can, uh,
oh man. There's no way to make a mono. Let me see if it gets better. Let me check.
Be sure of. It doesn't. Okay. Crap. I'm sorry about that. I'll play it tomorrow. I'll go
modify it. That sucks. All right. He's another song. Again, not from the pod save music network,
but I liked it so much. I was sent this to me. Howie. Howie. I put together a project called
ROTFLMAO, which I guess would be rolling on the floor laughing my ass off, which features
check this out. Ricky Lee Jones with Tom Maxwell and Ken Mosher of the squirrel nut zippers.
And I listened to the song, and you heard the song that I started off with today,
which was definitely a song to think about. Well, this is an, and of course, the name Ricky
Lee Jones caught my eye because, uh, man, Chuck Eason love has got to be one of my most favorite songs
of all time. You know what? Can we actually, uh, hear something? Let's try a little test.
Well, we're messing around, shall we? Let me open up Windows Media Player. This will be cool of this work.
Uh, let me see. I go to music. And I, uh, what the hell? Okay. I'm, uh, I subscribed to Napster.
You know, you know, the Napsters, you know, that illegal thing that turned kind of legal?
Well, the thing they've still got kind of right is the search function because, you know,
well, how cool was that back in the Napster days when you just go search for your favorite song?
It'll kind of show up. So now it does the same thing. Only, um, you couldn't, the, when you download
something and actually downloads. Let me see. Search. Ricky Lee Jones, tell me they have Chuck Eason love.
I can't believe it. They don't. Oh, no. Oh, that's horrible.
Wait, let me try the track. Uh, Chuck Eason love. Don't tell me they don't have that.
I hear it is. Uh, live. We don't want live. Uh, the LP version.
Thank goodness. Okay. Let's, let's see if I can play this for you. Play. Come on. Do it. Do it.
You, you love, I'll just play a little bit of the song because of course that's not pod safe either.
But when you hear this tune, I guarantee it's going to, it's going to just freak you out.
Connecting to media buffering 37% of the lead. Oh, yeah. Listen to that. Listen to that. Listen to that. Listen to that.
The quality of this recording is so good. You can actually hear the microphone come on.
You listen to this here. Be real quiet and out of the point out where it comes. Here comes.
Listen. Here comes.
I'll just get to the chorus for a second.
Cut out the code out the code. Yeah, sure. Okay. Listen to that.
Come on. Get to the chorus.
Well, it's getting so new. It's going to be the whole song before I get to the chorus.
I hear it. All right. It's the longer part of the tune.
Thinking back, Chuckies love, Chuckies love, Chuckies love, Chuckies love,
Chuckies love, Chuckies love,
I don't believe. How good is that?
Oh, man. I wish I could share the whole song with you guys, but let's listen. There we go.
Okay. Yeah. Okay. Stop that. Let me just really make it really make it horrible and say that
that song was brought to you by the accurate target cast for the accurate new RDX SUV.
Find that it's accurate.podshow.com and by Earthlink, the ad challenge. We're about to announce
the winners. You can listen to all the finalists at earthlink.podshow.com.
And they have another one. Oh, yeah. If you want to say send that big-haired
tag from the 80s to jail for playing RIA Music on his podcast.com, use Chuck out code DSC3.
It'd go daddy.com. So anyway, back to the email that how he climbed sent. So he's put this
project together with Ricky Lee Jones and that's why it immediately caught my eye and he said the
play it. So how are we? I'm going to play it. Would you please be so kind to support this on the
pod save music network? Could you? It's it's it's really funky but the lyrics of course really
kick ass particularly because it's Ricky Lee Jones. And you can be a Lindy Hopper. Have you had
enough? Or do you still let me in?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, don't embarrass yourself,
network. Would you please? And that's it for today. Short, sweet, simple. I'm feeling good. Lots
of stuff happening. Next week, big announcement in the United Kingdom. So I'm going to say,
and after that, I hope to go back to San Francisco for a little bit and hang out with the crew
there. There's like five new people I haven't met yet, at least virtually I've met them, but not through
not in interpersonal contact. Yesterday, those of you in the UK probably have heard of
Dr. Cockney. Well, he was in San Francisco. And he dropped by the pod show offices, doing his
Dr. Cockney sex talk thing. And it was like 1130 here, 1130 midnight. And we had the video conference
going and there was a bizarre, I'm sure it'll show up in his show somewhere. DailySourceco.com for all
the links, et cetera, for things discussed on today's show in the show notes. And of course,
ad about podshow.com is where you can send your stuff and promo.podshow.com. Don't forget,
talk to you, my everybody, for football, Friday, sending your suggestions. Bye, bye.