Hey, this is Don Miselli.
And this is Drew Domkin's.
From The Dawn and Drew Show.
Check out ShadowFalls.podshow.com.
It's so spooky, you might pee your pants.
This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Deltess Yara Charlie, 43-4.
Sometimes an atom's on a loan and he needs his love right there on the microphone.
So here she is, yes, the Lady Patricia.
The say to handsome, bad, I've been one and with his angel from above.
There's nothing that they both can't do.
The make you wildest dreams come true.
So grab your earbuds and jam them in.
And let the fabulous show begin.
It's atom and Patricia.
Yes, atom and Patricia.
I talk to my baby on the telephone all this time.
I never would have guessed back when there's someone so bad.
Yeah, I really only met about a week ago, but he doesn't seem to matter to my heart.
I know that I love her, I'm hoping that I'll never recover, because she's good for me.
It would make me happy to never let us live away.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The like to give you the teenage crush, always cool day.
All the school day, I feel like the leader won't be on you again.
Yeah, I'm a little bit dizzy, I'm a little bit scared.
I guess I never met this much away that I love her.
I'm hoping that I'll never recover, because she's good for me.
I really only make me happy to never let us live away.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I really only met about a week ago, but she doesn't seem to matter to my heart.
I know that I love her, I'm hoping that I'll never recover, because she's good for me.
I really really make me happy to never let us live away.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And Rugold never let us slip away.
Uh...
For you baby.
Yeah.
Now...
One of my favorite songs.
I know. What do we know about this song?
What do we know about this song?
One thing it's not.
Well, we're never gonna slip away.
But it's not a pod safe.
No, it's not. It's right.
But guess how come I can play it?
I don't know.
I got permission from Andrew Gold himself.
You're kidding.
Yep.
You bet you.
Really?
Yep. So I could play it for my baby.
I know.
So how did you do it?
Um...
Mark Yoshimone and M.Coff.
From my pod show L.A.
Yeah.
Uh... he knows him.
And he played...
Uh... what do you play?
He played another song.
And uh...
And I complained about it.
So what the fuck is that?
Yeah.
And uh... and turns out he's...
Uh... he's good friends with him.
So I said, could you please have him...
Recut this song...
To start with...
I talked to Patricia...
Oh, the...
Oh no!
He wouldn't do that.
He didn't want to do that.
Oh.
I understand.
You don't want to mess with you.
That would have been a wonderful gift.
Yeah, that would have been even better.
That's what I figured out.
Better than a bunch of roses or anything.
Oh.
Shall I throw those out then?
Ha ha ha.
Hello, baby.
Hello, hi.
It's the Daily Source Code coming to you from Curie Cottage.
I'm back just arrived this morning.
Uh...
A couple hours ago?
Yeah.
On my favorite airline?
It's the Virgin Atlantic.
Yeah, I slept for...
I think five hours at least.
Yeah.
I really, really slept.
One thing I failed to understand.
If you're flying at 39, 40,000 feet.
Yeah.
And, you know, it's going to be a sleeper flight.
Right.
Why do they serve broccoli?
Ah!
This is so dumb.
Ah.
This is like such a no-no.
You do not serve people broccoli, particularly not when they're flying.
Like beans, broccoli.
You smell like ass.
The whole time is over.
Yeah, right now.
And...
It comes out of your ass.
Yeah.
So not only that.
Really?
But people have gone a pass.
Wind.
That's my whole point.
Yeah.
Well, that was kind of the point.
Is that though?
Yeah.
It just stinks because people just stink.
But they never think about it.
Because sometimes you have beans.
Lots of beans.
Beans is okay.
Broccoli?
This is okay.
Same problem.
Broccoli farts are worse than being farts.
I'm telling you.
God, he's home.
I finally have someone to talk to about all that nasty shit.
Yeah.
I missed you, baby.
I missed you too.
Yeah.
I missed our daughter.
Who immediately came to me with three questions.
One.
My cell phone was broken.
The light stays on too.
The laptop hasn't been working for two weeks.
And what was the third one?
Oh, um.
What?
Should I talk to a birthday?
No.
There was something else.
Oh, yeah.
About her.
The money.
Yeah.
Something about money.
Oh, yeah.
What do I get my money?
Yeah.
When do I get paid for my downloads?
Welcome home, Dad.
How you doing?
Yeah.
That's exactly what happened.
Was to have your home.
So that was long.
Yeah.
Three weeks.
I think I was going for three weeks.
Was now or two and a half.
Almost three weeks.
Yeah.
Three weeks.
That's a bit too long.
That's too long.
I mean, nothing to compare, you know, to people who are.
Who have gone sea on the sea or.
Right.
They're gone.
Well, they're gone probably for three weeks at a time.
Sailors.
Sailor.
I'm like your sailor.
Yeah.
I'm your sailor boy.
I've come home.
Yeah.
And I spent all that extra time.
I didn't spend with you.
I spent with the nerds and geeks.
Yeah.
The engineers.
It was cool.
It was good.
Yeah.
It was very good.
Yeah, I was definitely good.
Well, you were very busy.
Oh, man.
Here with it.
But that's kind of what's great about it is.
You know, all I do is get up at six in the morning.
Do the show.
Go to the office.
Come home around eight.
Eat.
Sleep.
No.
Wank.
Eat.
Wankers.
Exactly.
You had food in the house?
Yeah, man.
Yeah.
No, I'm set up.
No, I know how to do it.
Yeah.
No, I know how to be a bachelor.
20 years too late.
Yeah.
I'm not totally set up.
Well.
You know that women love bachelor's when they come in their bachelor pad.
And it's clean.
And they say that they have everything on the control.
Yeah.
I should try that test.
It's so good.
I should bring some buries up.
What?
I had the other way around.
I looked at your bachelor pad.
Yeah.
It was a stinking mass.
Hold on a second.
First of all.
Help.
I'll never forget.
Patricia takes one look at my bed and goes, don't think I'm laying in that.
And I said, don't think you were invited.
Yes.
See, that's good.
Good one.
Yeah.
When I was still back in the day when I was fresh.
And I had snappy answers.
Yeah.
But we can always lay on the floor.
Did I say that?
I didn't say that.
You said that.
Yeah.
Exactly.
So I haven't updated everybody on the house.
Oh, yeah.
So yesterday, after I'd already done the show Patricia, I got a frantic
SMS from Patricia that we didn't get the house.
Yeah.
Didn't get it.
I thought that the whole system with the envelopes was a bad idea anyway from the beginning.
Maybe you should explain what happened because the guy called up a day early.
He was supposed to call today.
Yeah.
They called a day early and says, I'm sorry.
Then I expected an incident once.
This is the agent.
Yeah.
Miss, this is Michael.
Hello, Michael.
So in so agency, I'm afraid to have a very bad.
That's a bad news.
That's a good thing.
And it just started.
What?
Everything.
Your boobs.
No.
Everything was falling.
Your boobs.
You had to pick him up off the floor, boy.
No.
Everything.
And you said, well, you don't have the house.
Somebody else.
And I said, oh, what happened?
Because I thought he was enough.
But that's the envelope.
What he explained actually ahead of everything.
We offered like 12 or 13% over the asking price.
Yeah.
Now first the asking price.
That's how you start.
Then you're here late.
Well, there is already somebody over the asking price.
Uh-huh.
But we have so many people interested.
So what we're probably going to do at the end is make a couple of envelopes.
Put their best offer and the situation you're in.
Put it in there and give it to the vendors.
Yeah.
The vendors.
The people who sell the house.
That's the vendor.
Never knew that.
Vendor.
What's a vendor, you know?
It sounds like ice creams.
That's what a vendor is.
Exactly.
At an Albert Square.
They're all vendors.
I know.
So.
And then they will decide.
And sometimes it's not even the highest.
But if the situation is better.
It goes faster than they will choose.
Yeah.
I thought it was a bad idea from the beginning.
I said, yeah, but ask the vendors.
You know?
The vendors.
What they would like to have.
Yeah.
To take it off the freaking market.
And they said, well, I will ask them.
Mrs. Curry.
But the very decent and very old fashioned people.
Yeah.
And they thought it was not a very good idea because it's not nice for the other people.
And I said, this is business with focus.
And they went.
They want the money that they actually want for the, you know?
Did you say the line?
You said it just like that.
Yeah.
But you did.
To American probably.
Uh-huh.
And it's a pardon.
Pardon.
I didn't mean to be so proud.
Yeah.
It's very emotional.
But I said, can you could you please ask them that?
So he came back after a couple of hours.
Because I noticed that English people take their time.
If they say, I'll call you back.
That means three, four hours late.
Yeah.
In America means like.
I'll call you back.
Exactly.
Sometimes they don't call back at all.
Uh, that's cool.
They have, you have to call them again.
Yeah.
I don't have very good business.
Sorry, Mrs. Curry.
I was very, very, I was very busy.
I had a couple of meetings.
Yes.
I'm so sorry.
And then when they say the, the way they say it, I'm so sorry.
You believe in right away.
I've noticed with some of the business.
They're doing here that they kind of appreciate the straightforward American way of doing it.
Oh, they do.
They do.
They actually do.
And they knew that I was serious about it.
Yeah.
And so they did ask.
And, you know, they did.
But now they end up actually with less.
Then I said, they could have asked me.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
So it is stupid idea.
Don't ever do this again.
No, I mean not that, but with envelope.
Oh, thank you.
It disappointed about that.
And who knows?
It might fall through.
Yeah.
This is the crazy thing.
Because it means absolutely nothing.
In fact, we already went back and bit more than the, than the winning bit.
So Michael said, yeah.
Well, you know you never knew that.
You never knew that.
But you just has no.
Yeah.
You never know what happens, Mrs. Curry.
It might be a little bit wobbly.
And I said, well, one thing.
We're not wobbly.
You want to come back to us.
We're not wobbly at all.
We're not wobbly.
So what do you know what?
We learned something here.
Yeah.
We learned that the system sucks.
Exactly.
I was very frustrated.
You know, and if we find a house that is,
there has none of these problems.
That means nobody wants a house.
Exactly.
But this was very popular.
It was a nice house.
It was a very nice house.
It was in three weeks' time.
If I were here, I might have been able to have a different,
I just, I feel guilty that I wasn't here to help you.
Yeah, you left me here.
No, it doesn't matter.
Oh, you're telling me I couldn't, I've done,
I'm not doing a right job.
No, no, that's not what I'm saying.
I guess what I'm saying is,
I'm always going to wonder if I was here,
could I have changed the outcome?
With a voice like that, you might.
Hello.
Because you didn't.
Yeah, you.
I'd like to.
Could have, I'd like to take a look at your house.
The Mrs.
Yeah, maybe she was very sensitive for that.
You know, you don't know.
She's a sensitive Mrs.
She's very sensitive.
She's very nice.
I met her, both of them are very nice.
Hmm.
So what else happened?
Yeah, I have to just breathe out, exhale.
Yeah, there'll be another house.
I'm a bit disappointed.
There will be another house.
You know there will be another house.
I know.
Remember, it was, it was the horny castle.
It was the bomb diggy, and then it was the foamshizzle.
It doesn't matter.
Every time, I just, you know how I was just.
You know how I was just.
I know.
Yes, you do.
And the moment I move on, then I, you know, I think, okay.
Oh, I could do this.
I'm happy you know.
We'll get the rundown of what's coming up on the pod show on serious stars one
or two, which this show is a simultaneously cast on.
Pacific Coast, Hellway next.
Then after that dawn and drew.
And then soccer girl will be on tonight at, what is that eight o'clock?
You've heard soccer girl how much you?
Yeah.
We have, sod, our, our search specialist is like, he has dreams about soccer girl.
Really?
Yeah.
I promise them, like, a mud wrestle between Dawn from Dawn and Drew and soccer girl.
Oh, Dawn is going to win this.
I think Dawn will kick her ass here.
Don't want her to stop of you.
No.
Dude.
She's strong.
Peed up, show.
You'll like this episode.
This is about, do you know that there are people who are immune to weed?
Yeah.
Turns out he's one of them.
Oh, whatever you do.
Aspirant and weed.
Aspirant doesn't work.
And the smoking weed just does not get stoned.
Oh, he misses maybe something in his brain.
Oh, well.
I don't.
I don't need to know about the weed to know that.
He's working for us.
Isn't that saying enough?
Email girl tell her to come on after digital floods and then imagine why
I'm seeing with East Radio followed by the Frank Truth, your favorite show.
Brian, no.
Yeah.
That's a cool last show.
That's tonight on the pod show.
Up until 10 Eastern time.
Hmm.
Yeah, so I really don't have much else to say because I told you,
I mean, you know, the things will pop up as as a home and we're around each
other.
Well, yeah.
Yeah.
I don't forget that you just came home.
So you're still a little bit kind of a shot off.
Oh, the ball ball.
Well, I was actually looking.
You brought me some magazines.
Yes.
And I was looking.
Did I bring good ones?
Yeah.
Do you know that don't sell pilot or flying magazine anymore?
Any of the key asks at San Francisco Airport that pisses me off?
I'm very interesting about flying.
What I've read about John F. Kennedy.
Do you think it sounds like bullshit?
Yeah.
Well, you know, maybe.
Yes.
That could have happened.
Yeah.
So many things.
So the story is that he was, but they said he was still over New York,
over White Plains, and that they couldn't reach him on the radio.
Yeah.
And that he was in the flight path of an American Airlines jetliner.
Which, you know, he must have been pretty high.
I had, I'd have to look at the map and see what the,
Yeah.
What the altitude rules are on that region.
But that's not where he crashed.
No.
But the thing that he crashed over Mars.
Nobody heard him.
That could be something.
That is possible.
Yeah.
But you know, you've flown with me.
And how many times I said this cock suckers in the air and no,
you know, and the tower will literally say, you know,
you've got traffic coming away.
What are from whatever direction?
Hello.
Unknown.
We don't, we don't have monfrequency.
Yeah.
Because, you know, these people just flying around and just not.
It's fucking crazy.
So more people are doing that, actually.
Oh, well, maybe he was so busy.
No, but he could be on a different frequency.
Although, I think they try, I mean, this is the, they look.
It's national inquire.
So how, uh,
No, that's true.
Or it's worse.
It's the exam.
Or it's heard something.
Yeah.
So they say there's a cover up to the FAA and the NTSB,
that they covered that up.
For what?
Why would they cover that up?
That's what that would make no sense.
Makes no sense.
It was reading about, um, and I've read it already in English paper,
which is, you can trust.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you for prefacing that.
Scary spies and Eddie Murphy.
That blew me away.
He just got divorced from the beautiful wife.
gorgeous.
And now he's getting married to scary spies.
He's got five kids with her.
Five, uh, I think.
No, I think three and he had two from his first marriage.
He's been married for a time.
Okay.
And now.
I was going to get married to scary spies.
No, Mel B's.
I don't know.
It was a lot younger than he is, but that doesn't mean anything.
But I don't think she's that.
You know, no, no, no.
No, I think she's.
Well, she's 38, 39.
And he's maybe 45.
It's not that.
Yeah, yeah, it's not that big a difference.
Not at all.
No, no, no, no.
Okay.
But she has never really been very deep.
Well, it might give him a little bit, sort of a,
a young injection.
Something that he maybe needs because we're easy.
I wouldn't inject that.
But I wouldn't inject Mel B with your penis.
I do not.
She does not turn me on at all.
No, but maybe for either but no, but nobody.
I always thought of her like, she's a very sexy woman.
Really?
Oh, no.
No.
I don't know.
Scary spies.
Does that ring a bell?
Does that make you think of anything?
Scary spies.
She was the scary spies.
She reminds me of downtown Julie Brown and that really pisses me off.
No, maybe I thought she was, she had guts or something.
That's why she was scary.
Yeah, the gut hang out all the way.
Yeah.
So that, then I saw that Pamela Anderson is back with David Spade.
No, that's had a locklear.
Oh, that's right.
That was funny too.
David.
David Spade and Heather Locklear.
That's a good combination.
You know, that is very nice because it gives hope to nerds like me.
I think he's a lovely nerd.
I like him.
Yeah, that's I know, but she sees that.
Yeah, I see something very sexy there.
I see something sexy in her too.
Well, her.
Yeah, I don't know.
Sure.
I think she's sexy.
She needs some humor.
Is David Spade on the list now all of a sudden?
There is no list.
Yeah, there is a list.
Come on.
Well, let's start a list.
I think he's so funny.
So he's on the list.
People who are so funny are on the list.
I love that.
You know, I love that.
If we ever hook up with Heather and David, we're all the list.
They're on the list.
Wow.
Okay.
What I said is a nay.
A nay.
No, no, no.
Pamela Anderson, you said that already.
And kids.
Kid rock.
Do you know that you know Aaron.
Tell us that.
You know Aaron Brcell, the podpimp.
Do you know?
Yeah, you do.
You've met him.
He does our promotions marketing.
Big guy.
Really big guy.
Yeah.
He flew.
Because, you know, where everyone's going back and forth between the San Francisco and London
for podcha, you guys.
He flew from San Francisco to London.
And he sat next to Pamela Anderson.
The entire trip.
I wanted to beat him senseless.
How unfair is that?
I fly with the hip airline.
Yeah, with like virgin.
I never, what I get like pussy cat dolls.
Yeah.
Imagine sitting next to Pamela Anderson for 10 hours.
Oh, man.
She's sweet.
I've heard.
And the way she.
That's exactly what he says.
Yeah, she's very sweet.
I think she was alone.
She wasn't with her kids.
Yeah.
She's always with the boys.
Always.
Oh, playing with them.
Going everywhere.
She's a great mom.
That's not everywhere.
Not always because she was on the flight with Aaron.
She was.
Yeah.
That's right.
How come I don't get to say, huh?
I get like, I don't get any celebrities on virgin.
Where are the celebrities?
On virgin.
I never see them.
Yeah.
Never.
You're right.
Except for the pussy cat dolls.
No, we had that John, you know.
Johnny Vegas.
No.
Don't you Vegas who was a named.
Yeah.
No.
No, no, no, no.
Don't rub it in.
Didn't he?
Yeah.
Don't say like you're happy.
You know, because we tried to be nice to him.
But he had an attitude.
So now.
He gets it back.
He flopped.
She put a curse on him.
Yeah.
You have to be nice to me.
Yes.
If you're not nice to the lady Patricia.
Yeah.
Then you, then you will flop.
Oh, yeah.
You will flop.
Ha.
Okay.
So that was the only one that I ever actually saw.
Have you ever been sat next to a celebrity on an airplane?
No.
Not in airplane.
Where did you sit next to a celebrity on a boat?
Well, we're in couple of shows.
Yeah.
And I mean, it has to be like a happenstance.
You know, like a real cool incident.
No more.
Yeah.
I flew with a, there's a point.
I slept with her.
Yeah.
I know.
We had a red eye from Los Angeles.
Yeah.
She slept together.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
She's beautiful.
Is she still with a, was she?
Waga mama.
What does that supposed to be?
She looks like a waga mama.
Those of you listening to us on serious.
You're not going to hear the rest of my story about Daisy Fuentes.
Unless you go to daily source code.com and download the show.
Pacific Coast Hellway.
Next for you guys.
You always had a thing for her.
I love Daisy.
Yeah.
I didn't.
She had thick ankles.
You always said mama.
Mama.
Yeah.
Cheetah with her.
But she was nice.
Very nice.
One of the few people that I really got along well with that MTV.
Yeah.
Very, very nice.
But she was also like me.
She was kind of an outsider.
Yet fully entrenched.
You know, MTV celebrated the 25th birthday on Monday.
I think Monday or two.
I bet they didn't tell you.
No.
Well, approached you.
No, no, but MTV did nothing.
They did celebrate it all.
Oh.
Yeah.
It was not worth celebrating.
I think it makes kind of sense.
You know, the kids who were watching MTV now, they weren't alive.
When MTV started, you know, it's like, why?
And, you know, VH1 did some stuff.
You know, VH1 member VH1 used to be the Kenny G channel.
Yeah.
The history of Metallica is not TV.
Right.
But now the history of Metallica is on VH1.
Oh, that's a change.
Right.
So VH1 is, but it's, it feels, it makes me, it makes me feel old, really.
Yeah.
It's just silly.
It's not the same.
No.
Of course, it's not the same.
And the last top of the pops.
You saw that?
How was it?
How was the last top of the pops?
Well, it was actually old.
Top of the pops, which started in 40, almost 42 years ago, in 1964, which is the
longest running pop show in history, as far as I know.
Well, did you know that it was a time?
Yeah.
I knew that.
That it wasn't hip to be on the top of the pops.
Did they say that?
Yeah.
They said that.
Really?
Yeah.
There was a time to say that.
During, uh, well, I'll be doing this.
It started when they had too many, uh, wumbles and plumbles.
Yeah.
They do have a lot of that stupid shit on.
That's typical BBC because then the BBC wants to promote something from another show.
Exactly.
And they changed every time they had another producer with other ideas who had to make, you know,
with this last guy, I forget his name, who was doing the production.
You know, top of the pops is in like 20 countries.
Yeah.
They sold it.
That was a good idea.
Yeah.
And I did it very well.
He brought it back to basic.
Yeah.
You know, just music.
And if you cannot sing it, uh, live, which is understandable.
Well, you used to understand the rule.
If you have a routine, you're dancing.
But the rule used to be with top of the pops.
I remember this very, very clearly.
Um, because of a union rule, some weird union rule.
You had to sing live or had to do that.
So, so either you had to sing live on the show or you had to record a new vocal.
Yeah.
Only the vocal.
I don't think it was the instruments.
Well, no.
There was a time that, uh, the also you had to use English musicians.
English musicians.
Right.
Yeah.
And you're thinking like, my God, we worked on this so long.
And now we have to do it in one afternoon, you know.
And that was the end of the series.
Because the producer, um, that was, yeah, it was the stars.
And we didn't do it.
Because it was too hard.
And the producer, yeah.
Everyone said, well, no, that's not that easy.
No.
We're not going to get that sound.
We're not going to do it.
Wow.
So you didn't perform on top of the pops for your artistic integrity.
Yes.
Actually, yes.
Actually, um, one of the couple of producers came, uh, this week.
And told, um, uh, told, I don't know, in the show.
In the last show.
Yeah.
No.
It was nothing to show.
It was, it was about top of the pops.
And they said that, uh, well, a lot of X were right.
Not to do it.
Because it is a hard work.
You're looking for a great sound.
Yeah.
Really, really working harder than that.
And then you got to go and walk it all up to the TV.
Right.
And that TV sound is always so good.
Anyway, isn't it?
Not at all.
So, uh, I was right.
And so I was, uh, I produced a sound.
We didn't do it.
I picked up a book at the airport.
And, uh, something was, it's like the 10 homeless second.
Is it really good?
Not for you.
You wouldn't give a shit.
Oh.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Well, I had this reason of saying this.
Oh.
It's the little blue book of advertising.
52 small ideas that can make a big difference.
Oh.
Um, forward written by a guy.
I know Jerry Delafimina, who is a legendary advertising.
Yeah.
And it's not, it's not really about advertising per se.
It's about, um,
Customers in general.
Just what, what customers want.
Oh, and what they want to see.
Well, and, and most of the, you know what it is with, with all this.
Micro marketing and viral marketing and, and internet and cell phones.
Advertising hasn't changed.
People still want the basic things.
Yeah.
They still want a good feeling when they, when they see it,
Oh, see, you're here and advertising.
Right.
That's really true.
And so a lot of it is just going back to the basics and one thing,
I had 10 hours.
So, uh, one thing that, um, they keep coming back on on the book.
These two guys, these writers is,
know your customer and I thought to myself,
I really don't know my customer because, you know,
the customer that we have right now is people listening to this.
I don't, I have no idea who these people,
and yeah, some of them I do, but I really don't know.
No.
So I thought why not ask the audience to call in.
Uh, the voice mail numbers.
Get your phone out so you can pre-program the number.
In a second.
Um, I just want to know your name, how old you are,
where you're from, what you do,
and then if you're a folder or scruncher,
of course, that's.
Of course.
Every single phone call I get now is,
Oh, and uh.
Now you get some information from them.
Well, yes, I think that information is pretty interesting.
Yeah.
You know, the richest guy I know,
who's probably,
a hundred million area,
if not close to a billionaire,
God knows how much money he has.
You know him too.
Ray.
Hmm.
He's a scruncher.
So that's interesting.
I'm a folder.
Am I destined to fail?
If I mission towards incredible wealth.
I think it's about people who are in a hurry
or take their time.
Hmm.
Interesting.
Well, so I want to build a hypothesis on that.
So I just want,
I just want to know it's listening.
What they do.
Hmm.
And it'd be great if we had people who don't have podcasts,
but I'm interested in the podcasters too.
Yeah.
You are they.
What are they?
Yeah.
And why do they listen?
Why do they listen?
You know?
We're kind of job.
And what do they like?
What is there?
Yeah.
Because then we can determine what we can do.
That'll be better.
I think, you know,
I think our audience is older than I thought.
Well, I think so too.
I think it starts around.
God.
I hope there's some really hot girls that listen to the show.
Look at people we meet in the train here.
When we go by train to London.
And you see people with iPods?
Yeah.
They're not young either.
No.
You're right.
They've got money.
Sitting there, relaxing, listening to it.
And I think, what are they listening to?
Yeah.
Well, so I arrived at Heathrow.
And it was very, very quiet.
And so you go through the fast track.
I love fast track.
You get this little purple card.
I know.
Hi.
I just walked right up.
And so there were two girls, two immigration agents.
We were really, you know, young women.
Yeah.
And one was dark hair and one was blonde.
It was really funny because I walked right.
There's no one there.
I walked right up.
And I'm like.
Which one?
The go.
I don't want to insult anybody.
Which one did you choose?
Well, it's interesting because the dark hair girl who was definitely less attractive.
Because you know, I'd like blondes anyway.
Yeah.
She said, well, she was anyone you want.
And she almost apologetically said, okay.
You can go see her.
I said, no.
You spoke to me first.
I want to hang out with you.
Oh, you made her day.
Oh, totally.
Yeah.
The fuck was I talking about?
Well, about the choice.
Which one you choose?
No.
The reason I said it was for some reason.
Well, it was a wonderful that you went through the short term memories going.
Been through what?
Before that.
I brought up the story for a reason.
What were you saying before that?
Quickly wind it.
The hell are we talking about?
I'm so fried.
What were we just talking about before I started in the story?
Well, about your customers.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah.
No.
The listeners.
The writers.
No, you're.
So she says, what are you coming to do?
Because, you know, of course, the paper.
Even though we've done our paperwork, I still don't have the official visa.
It's a small thing, but it, you know, I'm fucking lazy.
And so I said, you know, I'll be here for 10 days.
Which is true because within 10 days, all have gone to Holland, you know, which all of it makes sense.
It don't really care.
Yeah.
Oh, what kind of business are you doing?
Well, you know, and I mentioned the name of the company that we're doing business with.
And she says, well, well, tell me about it.
She was, yeah, you know, sometimes I do this.
If whether they're interested or they want to see if I'm smuggling.
Well, they're bored.
They're bored, probably.
They'll be heard of podcasting.
Then the, the blonde says, oh, yes.
Oh, yeah.
For the podcasting.
And so we got into this whole thing.
Yeah, you know, they were, they were young.
Yeah.
Between, I'd say they were on 25.
Oh, yeah.
That's you.
And so she heard of podcasting.
Mm-hmm.
That was cool.
Yeah.
I think that's why I told the story.
I have no idea.
I don't like to pay off as much as I went.
I'm pretty sure I messed it up.
Okay.
So voicemail.
Yes, really.
Voicemail number for just to introduce yourself to us.
Yeah.
Right?
That's, I'm Adam.
Almost 42.
And Patricia.
Good job.
Plus 1, 201, 625, 635, 7 or 4 or plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3.
Well, I only play a song.
I got a really cool song here.
And then, and then we'll wrap it up.
Okay?
Listen to the lyrics of this song.
I think you like it.
I like it.
We're up now.
Chocolate cake makes my poor stomach ape.
And all those pills are too much for me to take.
Don't like cocaine, because it makes me all up tight.
We're coffee and reefer makes me feel alright.
First of all, method, make you hide.
That's too much.
But I've never liked going five days without a sniff.
As it makes you say stupid things like.
We're coffee and reefer makes you feel alright.
We're gonna take you high.
We're gonna take you low.
The beans are making fly.
All the bug will make you slow.
Shoes, feet, balls will make you snow your stereo.
But you've never heard of going in hawk.
For a cup of Joe.
You know the crank will end you ride in a crank.
Smoke that nasty crack and you want to rob a bank.
Forget the nicotine and cannot be.
Ben's a dream.
Try golfing and reef before a real mellow scene.
We're gonna take you high.
Don't draw my car.
Don't answer the phone.
Just try to spend them coming out.
When I want them to stay 2003,
Press your hand on a pedal.
We're caught to channel, hey, how's everything you need?
X to C, we'll cause a man to love a wall
Love you, we'll whiskey make you love a girl
You never touch it all
Nestling, we're turned you into a little pinky racer
We're caught cappuccino with a mellow gauge taste
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah
Wait, thinkin about that.
I heard that on here's that podcast going on the jazz hey
The jazz suite podcast dedicated to jails
It's played by independent and indie artists
The music that major labels just miss
and I heard that song was like
Yeah, it says it all so you can find it on the iTunes actually for sale on iTunes
Some songs you just you know you're here to me. You say thank you. Yeah, let me tell you who that was by the way
Otherwise you have no fucking clue you can go to iTunes all you want that was
Come on, why doesn't it work now?
Who was it?
Who was it now we want to know?
Yeah, I want to know too. You know the old fashioned way when you write it down
Oh, I got it. Hold on. It's always works
Ron sunshine shut off
Ron sunshine coffee and refer is the time. Oh, Ron
Ron sunshine. That was well not awesome. Whoa yeah, and it's so true
Every single thing saying he wrote in that. I don't know about crystal meth. Yeah, you're like
Yes, you're like coffee and reefer. I'm like. Yeah. Yeah. That's why I heard I was like
Thank you, man. It's speaking my language here
I've already heard it, but episode two of Shadow Falls drops today. It's really good. Yeah, yeah
Good boy enjoy it. Yes. Yeah, everyone has heard it. Everyone has heard it loves it. Yeah, we're not stupid. I mean, no
If we didn't like it, we would have said it. It's like 20 people that work on the show
20 people. Wow. Yeah, well, I mean if you listen to the credits all those actors and sound engineer
A lot of a lot of great actors without any work
Some of them have work, but but that's kind of the whole point of pod show LA. You know, there's all these people who
Who have the talent they just didn't get the slot, you know, just not your turn or whatever the however it works there
You know, and here's like come on in, you know, you got an idea bring it on in. We'll do something with it
Fantastic. Yeah. Yeah. All right, baby. I think we've done quite enough for like 40 minutes. That's enough
Don't you think? It's okay. Yeah
No, I want you for myself. Yes. I'm going to go flying this weekend. That's for sure. Oh
Definitely I need to fly. Oh, make sure everybody hears you
Yes, I will circle the cottage
All right, uh, get your music suggestions in for tomorrow because of course it's Friday
TGIF. We want to crank it up. If I do a real Friday music show you want to come on. Sure. Yeah. I missed you so much. Oh
I really did really yeah
I missed you do really yeah really really, but you know what it was hot in the cottage
I was actually kind of happy that I wasn't there in my bed. Yes, so I'm in because men are already a little bit
Smelly sweaty sweaty. Smelly acts then women but you actually said to me yes
They also have you're coming home because I actually kind of missed the irritation
You say that or no? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you know that's love to
Uh-huh, that's love to how long can you take the irritation though? Yeah, could belong to the whole thing go packets
That was the whole package. Yeah, okay, all right then so well, uh, maybe I'll meet you back here tomorrow
I'll be here okay Adam at podshow.com, please if you're going to send me email the query.com is also posed again
I don't understand email is breaking all over the place
I know and David source code.com for comments on the show and anything else all right all right
I love you baby. I love you too. Okay, bye bye
Another podshow podcast stick it in your ear
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from podshow and lime light networks
Um