This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 359er.
This podcast is explicit in nature as we start with the word from Brother Mark from Pod Show
LA.
You big looking like a friend spin-off sucking lame ass reality show cloning, Sarah
Jessica Parker looking like sea biscuit non-romantic comedy filming, stupid plot, stupid
story, stupid casting, waste of money, basic instinct too.
You got to be freaking kidding me producing, big dumb waste of two hours of my life.
Where the hell are your freaking balls?
Where the hell is the next pulp fiction?
Clark's Taxi Driver or Seinfeld, or even anything worth the voting.
One freaking Iota of my time, too.
Worthless junk you're crapping out because you're so out of touch.
You can't see that Tom Cruise has jumped the shark of life.
You my epic cantor's leeches.
With no integrity, always every stupid suit with an MBA and no creative experience has
got to spray on the hydrant with their worthless infantile and insulting ass-enine ideas that
just don't work.
And don't screw everything up because the only chances you ever take are ordering the
chef salad and not the Caesar at Spagos.
Hey, power launch on this, you self-important tinsel town pod knockers, you're out of
date, you're out of touch, you're out of ideas, guts, and vision, and I'm out of
any ability to give a flying fuck in a rolling donut about what you do anymore.
So kiss my ass Hollywood, I got something better, I got Pod Show LA.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio
content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I lost my young, my house and my wife misplaced my edge, my keys and my life, I can't
begin to begin again, I have to find out, just wherever I've been, but I'm happy.
Singing the blues, got the clothes on my back, ain't got nothing to lose, still got my friends.
We're sharing some booze, guess I'll let it be, and sing, yeah, the blues, yeah, the blues, yeah,
ain't got no guard, no hope on no gas, just one wedding ring, and I kick in my house, I'll
fall, no I don't need anything, just some good friends, and this bottle of dreams, and I'm happy,
singing the blues, got the clothes on my back, ain't got nothing to lose, still got my friends.
We're sharing some booze, guess I'll let it be, and sing, yeah, the blues, yeah, the blues,
yeah, the blues, yeah, the blues, yeah, the blues, yeah, the blues, yeah, the blues, yeah, the blues, yeah,
ain't got nothing to lose, still got my friends, yeah, the blues, yeah, the blues, yeah,
ain't got no guard, no hope on no gas, just one wedding ring, and I kick in my house,
I'll fall, no I don't need anything, just some good friends, sharing some booze, guess I'll let it be, and sing, yeah,
sing, yeah, the blues, got the clothes on my back, ain't got nothing to lose, still got my friends,
sing, yeah, the blues, yeah, the blues, yeah, the blues, yeah,
yeah, the blues, yeah, the blues, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, the blues, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh man,
I just keep hearing more from these guys, I can't stop playing and coming ground from Texas,
straight from the pod safe using network and music.vaachow.com. That's three bottles of
Bottles of dreams. Bottles of dreams. Bottles of dreams. Bottles of dreams. Bottles of dreams.
Bottles of dreams. That's it. Common ground. I've played a couple other
of their songs. I keep hearing these songs on different podcasts that I
listened to and I'm like, oh yeah, I got to listen to that and I look at the
show notes. It's just common ground. Yeah, I think I heard them. I added to my
playlist and then I'm like, I have already played like three or four of these
guys songs. Excellent stuff. Hey, everybody. I got a semi. Yeah, semi sunny
today. It's the sun has just come up over the bay. It's a little bit before
7 a.m. here in the Curry condo in Northern California. So it'll be kind of a
nice day. The end of yesterday was okay. I guess that I'm just expecting too
much from San Francisco weather. You know, it is still kind of a mix between Seattle
and Los Angeles with much more on the Seattle side. Last night I actually went
home. You know, you guys know, I really don't drink. Went out for a couple of
beers. This played a couple of places called Zeitgeist on Debose and Valencia
in the city and it was really, really cool. It was a beer bar, but you kind of
walk in and you go out the back and then it was all you could have been an
Arkansas for all I know. It was kind of like a, you know, the sun was just
kind of setting. It wasn't warm, but, you know, it was a nice atmosphere,
picnic tables, old jalapies and all kinds of junk out and back. And then this
incredible mixture of beer known as the Zeitgeist, which actually I video
recorded what is in it. So maybe I'll put that on one of my, my video podcast
in the near future. But it was great. You know, had a nice little bit of Indian
after that, some nice chat, nice conversation. And it just kind of completed
out my perfect San Francisco day yesterday. Yesterday, by the way, we started
with our advertising 2.0 campaign, one brand many voices. That's right. We have
about 50 podcasts on the network now. We have this humongous promotion with
GoDaddy. And it's, it's really cool because every single podcast is now
enabled to give their listeners a discount on several of the GoDaddy products.
Now, you also may have heard that the podcasts now start with an automatically
inserted promo tag, specifically for the GoDaddy promotion, which I'm very
excited about because now we have all these pieces of moving pieces of technology
working. And it's kind of interesting because I think what does it go as you
do? What is the slogan that we came up with? You want a badass domain name,
something that, in fact, it was the word badass. And I hadn't really thought
this one through because Steve Webb of life spring podcast, I immediately
hopped on on the internet and said, oh, wait a minute, this is not what I want in
front of my show, which of course is totally understandable. So the cool thing
about the, the de-gap system, which we have, our dynamically generated audio
placement, is that we can put something else in to automatically run in front
of Steve's show. So we're going to take care of that. And then, oh, man, just
wait until the podcasters have control over that and you can start to move
stuff around. And then, hopefully, we'll give listeners the opportunity to
mess around with the order of different pieces of the show. So, and of course, if
you, if you go to GoDaddy, we have three deals for you for source code
listeners, for straight up 10% discount, additional discount to any order you
already have. When you order at godaddy.com, use DSC one as your promo
code. If you use DS2, when you check out, you'll save an additional $5
off any order of $30 or more. And if you just want, you know, and this is
actually this is fun to do. I've done this many times. If you just want to get
a friend of yours, a cool domain name, it's only 695 for an entire year if you
use the code DS3. And that is actually fun. People have purchased domain names
for me as gifts all the time and they just map them to curry.com. It's kind of
funny. You know, and so on. Hey, look what I got you for your birthday
present. So, and of course, you don't have to use my codes. Use any of the
pod show podcast network codes because you actually directly contribute to
helping that podcaster because the more the more domains they are able to
to help sell the more money they make. So, it kind of works all around very
excited about it. Particularly about the technology piece though, it's kind of
cool to be able to be able to see the network kind of come together. More
about that tomorrow. I'm sure on the thank God. It's Friday edition, which will
be the last show in San Francisco for this trip after that. It's back home or
back to the other home. And see, what's the next Monday? I've got a, I'm on a
panel at the Guardian Media Conference. That should be pretty cool. I'm
thoroughly expecting Roger Smalls to show up somewhere, which would be our first
meeting. And then, uh, end of the week, end of next week, wrong vacation. Oh,
cannot wait. Hi Adam, this is Steven Schleicher. And this is Charlie, not the
penis, reocconced, Richard British, Kirkfield, Oregon, the Tona, Charlie White.
From the coolest roundup podcast, we are super excited to be one of the newest
members of the pod show family. We listen to a lot of quality podcast each day
and we really want to thank you and pod show for inviting us to join.
Coolness roundup is a weekly podcast aimed at answering questions about that
complicated world of consumer technology.
Branch, you need some help keeping your computer healthy or you're looking for a new
camera for your next vacation. Maybe you're looking to buy a new television and
you don't know whether you should get an LCD or a plasma screen. Each week,
Steven and I talk about the best and worst gadgets and devices we've seen during the
week. We answer listener email, dive deep into a topic of the week, and often have
spirited discussions on technologies that are changing our world. And Adam, we
want everyone to know that we also give away free prizes every week and some of them
are worth a lot of money. The coolest roundup, the tech show for everyone, are in a circle.
Are in a circle. Coolness roundup, welcome to the network guys. Congratulations. Great to
help you on board. Thanks for the promo. I was going to say something. Oh yeah,
about you mentioned prizes on the coolest roundup. We have something really cool that we're
going to do. I'm hoping sometime mid next week. I'm calling it the golden ticket.
Matt, this is going to be so much fun. We now have the technology. I'm really, I'm really
psyched about this. We now have the technology to, let's say, you know, of the, the hundreds of
thousands of downloads that the daily source code receives. We can actually now take one
downloaded random. So, you know, let's imagine the 6,000th or the 60,000th person to download
the Charlie on any particular day would actually receive a different show. And it would be different
because the show would say congratulations. You've just won the golden ticket. And it would be the
only winner chosen at random. And of course, you know, it's kind of like a, uh, in a way it's a bit
like a lottery because if you don't listen, then you can't claim your prize. So you have to listen.
And, uh, and there's only going to be, whether it could be multiple, we're just going to start off
with one. So I want to start testing this. It's a part of the gap that I just talked about. We'll
test that that next week. I already talked to Sam Levin at Pod Show HQ. Let me just see,
he sent me an email about we had a prize to do this one on a second. Let me see. I'm just
popping the Gmail real quick here. Gmail has been kind of funky the past few days. I get a lot of the
put you head between your knees, pray, and try again in a few minutes. Don't like that very much.
Makes me a little bit nervous. You know, scenes have got four full gigs of my stuff on their servers.
Let me see where Sam, here we go. A key span audio video dock for the iPod, excuse me,
plus the, since how audio video RF remote. Oh, cool. Yeah, that's like a some super power remote.
So you can, so you have a dock and then you have a power remote that you can use in any other room.
Cool. Okay, Sam. So we'll be giving both of those away. Details on it next week. I just wanted
to let you know that that's coming because it's just, you know, the network is starting to happen. I'm
loving it. Also, the email situation we're now getting through to hotmail. We're not getting through
to all service providers, but we're getting through the hotmail now. So something starting.
Someone's doing something somewhere. Hey, Adam, regarding Wednesday showed DSE. You
did it to me again. I'm driving right now. And I'm listening to some feedback about the,
the pod safe music network. And I just got to tell you. Okay. Now, I'm, I don't have a podcast right
now. Okay. I, but I am something very important out there. I'm a listener. And I appreciate this new
medium. More than probably your average person out there. But this is my point. You already got
streaming music out there. Okay. Pod safe obviously means a whole lot more than streaming.
Music. And this is my point. And I do have one. I don't buy much it from iTunes because I really
don't care about a most of the music that's there. If I want some music, I'll just go to
Rhapsody and I'll stream it and I'll play it and play it again. And the way Wi-Fi is working,
you know, you can always get the stuff out there. It's always going to be available. Okay. And you
can record it if you want. Damn it. There's so many different ways to get in the music. But what's
cool is as a listener who appreciates this medium, podcasting and pod safe music and all the stuff
that comes with it. It's the artist, baby. I'm appreciating the artist. And I want to give the
artist money. Let me give you money. Just like a lot of other people out there that are waiting
to hear the challenge. I have mentioned this before, but it's going to work because if I know that
my nine, nine cents can help somebody out there. Okay. Somebody out there. It's going to mean
that it's something that I appreciate doing. And I want to do. So, all right. I'm a listener.
I love your show. Adam, keep it up. But you make me go crazy sometimes. I stop pull around,
get the damn microphone and all the best you do for peace. Yeah, baby. Thank you so much. I love
it when listeners send an audio comments. God, that's so nice. And identify yourself as a listener,
please. That's nice, you know. Because we love doing this stuff for you. And definitely,
you know what Ron and I were talking to a couple of analysts the other day. We get calls all the
time from like the gardener group or forest or the Pew study or whatever. And they want to pick
our brain about what's going on. And the state of the industry, all that stuff. And it's amazing,
how little, well, it's not even that they don't do the research, but they're so skewed towards
existing models of music and entertainment and the recommendation and it's all based upon technologies.
And you know, we take a lot of effort. We make, we put in a lot of effort to explain that this
is something different. And this comment from a listener, not a podcast from a listener, is exactly
right. People are not, it's not just about buying a song, okay. It's about the involvement that you
have with these artists. Yeah, okay. So the universe may be a little bit smaller. And by the way,
artists are very, getting very good at how to communicate with their fan base and with people who
are their customers. I would, I would basically have to say whether they look at them as, there's,
there's their wares as art or commerce or whatever. You know, they have a fan base. And it's about
that involvement. That is what's taking place in pod safe music. You buy a song. At this point,
you're 99% likely to receive a thank you note from the artist. If you buy a CD, you may get a
t-shirt thrown in or something like that. You know, this is, this is what's happening. And I have to
believe that that is a very important part of what's going on. I see it with Christina as well.
You know, she loves the fact that there's all these independent bands that she can, she can email
with and, you know, comment on their site and they're active in their forum or, you know,
whatever other type of platform they use to communicate with their fans. And oftentimes,
you know, I have also seen the incredible disappointment when they get picked up by label,
which more and more artists are seeing is not really that beneficial. And a lot of them do come
back after the fact, but they get picked up by label than you never hear from them again,
which is disappointing. But I'm pretty sure this going to be plenty of artists who will never
sign up to a mainstream label, because, you know, the profit margins on selling
15,000 units in the pod safe arena is probably going to be more for the artist than selling,
you know, 150,000 through a mainstream record company. It's just that simple. It's math,
ladies and gentlemen. But for people who enjoy music like myself, you know, I used to buy albums
and I'd spend hours looking at the pictures on the liner notes, particularly if it was a double
album member of those when it just opened up in the middle and then nice smell of vinyl and
cardboard and maybe to had a poster slipped inside the sleeve. You know, this is the new version of that.
It's real direct contact with the artist. It's just exciting. And I really appreciate
listener comments like that. Thank you. Hey, Adam. Peter Klythero and Suffolk in the UK.
This business about taking names in vain happens all the time to me. Every time anybody sees a
great bit of technology. Here's a great bit of music. They invert my show's name.
What's that you say? The name of the show. It's Suffolk and Cool. Suffolk and Cool.
Ah, just search under Suffolk on iTunes and credit where it's due. This is Lane Duck and chaos
from the Ponceau music network.
Excellent. Good name, man. Suffolk and Cool. Love it.
And we have a celebrity metrosexual moment today. Special guests checking in via audio
comment. Don and Drew. Speaking of bullshit, we're listening to Adam Kray's daily source code.
Your teeth all talking about him put snare on his junks and I told him he had a visual.
Because as you've seen him, I have seen his penis.
Yeah, but he's not talking about nearing his penis at all. He was talking about nearing his
another region. So what do you think he's talking about, Craig? Well, there's the balls.
Those get a little hair here, but I don't think you're going to put nearing your balls.
We're also going to put another region. Right over here, like above.
I think he's talking about the whole deal, not just like the bikini area. Well, you know what?
Clip this out right here. It's like this to him. This is a metrosexual moment.
Do you add a boyfriend? Were you talking about your balls with the snare?
I'm just curious. Maybe it was his uh, maybe it was the butt. He talked about uh, he must be
trombone. Maybe Patricia doesn't like the hair. Oh, maybe you're right.
To your Adam Curry. Was it the butt? Was it the ball? See, I was thinking he was talking about
like above the bikini. That's not very nether than is it? That's pretty nether. Yeah.
That's what I was thinking. What were you envisioning? I imagine just the whole thing.
Smooth. The whole thing. The whole thing. From friends to backs. That's the backs.
Might as well lather up down there. It's like chemicals. You don't want to really
lather. You had a specific time for him. No more than eight minutes? That's what it says in the
model. No, it says no more than 10. Hair removal scientists. How do you know?
Cause I accidentally put the feet on me once. And I said, oh, I know.
She works good. Okay, so yeah, that was my question. Yeah, for Adam. Okay, well, I'll submit that to his
Metro sexual moment for you. Thank you. Excellent. All right, well glad you guys did that because
maybe it's because you guys are been in Wisconsin too long, you know, but we all get all
geekly and funky when we talk about that stuff. I think that kind of pertains to Americans in
particular Europeans don't seem to be so hung up on it. Then again, you know, you go to a beach in
Europe. The women are topless just like the man and it doesn't seem to be a big deal, but yeah,
that's for a different source code another time. Look, your appearance is not for yourself.
You make your hair look pretty, or you put makeup on, or you do other things for other people.
That's to make them feel good about you, at least that's my theory. Now, the only other person who's
going to see my nether regions done, besides you, of course, is my wife. Now, you know, I'm a big fan
of porn, right? And a good porn, you know, stuff with a story, of course. And I watch it whenever
I can, whenever I have the opportunity. And let me tell you, you know, take a look at the guys there.
Do you see any hair? No, of course you don't. And believe me, you've just forgotten.
Or take a good look at Drew's crotch right now. I mean, I compare to any porn movie you've
seen done, please. Front to back, baby, all the way. Hey, folks listening to this show on
that serious stars 102, I'm about, oh, shit man, and Pdub sent me the whole rundown. I, uh,
uh, I'll see you tomorrow for Friday. God damn it. He's going to be so pissed at me. Shit. Oh,
I only want, I even put it in my line up. Oh, I wish I could turn, but if I could turn back,
time. So I'll tell you what, what I was supposed to say is specific to tell
why next, then match Weinstein for a full-hour dawn and Drew, the Gilmore Daily podcast,
followed by PW offense, digital flat sums. He's got a new one out. Uh, was that the beer show that
I heard the, the, the second beer show? Oh, no, the beer shoot. That's what I was. It was kind of cool.
And then the rock and roll geek show to wind it up. Crap. I need a producer.
Someone who's here early in the morning who can help me with my nair and stuff.
Hey, newbies. This is happy from bedtime stories. My kids love with another frequently asked
questions from the Charlie. Today we talk about Trinity. Trinity is Adam's Mercedes Ben station wagon
that runs on biodiesel fuel, but Trinity did not start as a Mercedes Benz, but rather as an idea
for a promo with Volkswagen during Adam's ongoing conversation about biodiesel fuels. Volkswagen has
been very interested in advertising on podcast. And I kept, I had to test that, you know,
we're on a way to Apple with Chris and I'm saying Chris, dude, get me a Volkswagen and we'll do a
couple things with it, you know, we'll broadcast from it, but also we'll do my biodiesel experiments on it.
That was the part that he had kind of a reason. I don't know how I'm going to pitch that.
But alas, no Volkswagen. Then on daily source code 297, Adam takes us on a sound scene tour and
introduces us to Trinity. I told you about this car that I saw parked right near our brand new office
and that I put a note underneath the windshield wipers saying, will you sell me this car? And today
I got a call this morning from Isabel and she said, Adam, I said, yeah, she said, well,
you left this note on my car. I just want you to know that I've actually had it up on Craigslist
for a couple of weeks. And yeah, it's for sale. And ladies and gentlemen, I present you with Trinity.
And Trinity was so popular. It didn't take long till Trinity had its own thing song,
which appeared on Danny's source code 300. All right, everybody,
feel free to sing along. You're going to be here in this tune. I love the future.
I can give you likely 1.25 times, feel like it's me out. Trinity, Trinity,
quintessential luxury home. Trinity, Trinity,
have a buy-home, diesel, industry. But she could talk, you hear her thank, Adam for pooping in her
tango, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, it's so good,
everybody. So that's almost perfect. Jeffrey Smith, thank you very much. I love the Trinity theme song.
That, of course, will for the foreseeable future mark a small discussion about biodiesel,
now Trinity and the biodiesel conversation on ongoing part of the daily source code. As Trinity,
now has a slogan, 3 My Machine. Well, newbies, now you know just about everything about Trinity.
This is happy from bedtime stories, my kids love and I'll see you next time at daily source code
frequently asked questions. Oh, happy. I love it. You know when I get my new show
side up on the the pod show podcast delivery network, which I already kind of have half built
behind the password protected area and all that stuff. I'm going to make a special little module
that has all these Charlie facts. Charlie facts. There you go. Now this is cool. I love it.
Because that is great. You know, people come in. So what the hell is this show about? Very often,
people saying, you know, I listened like 10 back episodes to understand what was going on.
This really is quite helpful and I appreciate it. You know, Earthling is still a sponsor of
the pod show podcast network. And yesterday, it knows it wasn't yesterday. It was early in the
week. See what this Monday or Tuesday on Steve Gilmore's Gilmore daily. And Earthling also sponsors
his show. He read a letter a piece of feedback about the about the advertising. And I just wanted
to share that with you. Let me see if I got it hooked up here. I think I do. They have shown that
they can be respected. Okay. You can love this. This is a listener feedback sent to Steve Gilmore
about the Earthling advertising in the same way that they are respecting us. And I'd like to
read you some email. I got it. Actually, it was a blog post from the blog post. Somebody who
Robert Lanko's perhaps, I'm not sure, but the site is planet SA best A.B. No to Steve Gilmore, I do believe.
Today, I went to Earthling.net and looked at their services. Of course, I have few uses for their
service since I live in Europe, but in case I moved to the US tomorrow, I need to be able to
make an informed choice. And he has a little smiley there. I learned all about everything through
the commercial and Steve Gilmore's podcast on the Pachon network. For example, the Gilmore gang.
And the first 10 listens, I thought, what a bad ad for a podcast. Then I started getting interested
in the different accents of the speakers. I studied North American literature and language. He says,
and finally, at about the 50th time I heard the ad, I thought, oh well, I'll give them the
respect they deserve and pay their sight of is it. There you have it, advertising even with
lame spots works. Often the frequency is key. Tung out of cheek, though. It is a great decision on
their part to put themselves out here in the blogosphere with all the coverage on better bad news
and other pages ripping them apart. Apparently, they care and I am willing to give them the benefit of
the doubt. Do you believe anything that's possible? I just thought that was, and yeah,
I said to these guys, boys, not you heard of it. We believe in an internet that's safe from virus.
This is a virus. Where's he from? Voiruses? Is he released? He's always not from my earloom.
So, that was another take on it, which I thought was pretty interesting. And this is, you know,
what you're hearing right now, this is what we're doubting advertising 2.0. Fuck web 2.0. Let's go
to advertising 2.0. That's a little more exciting to be. And you'll see that EarthLink, well,
we've talked about this. You know that the something's coming very, very soon, that's going to be
extremely, extremely fun for all. Speaking of fun for all, ladies and gentlemen, comic strip,
comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip,
comic strip, he is back. I think we've got everything kind of cooled off now with the
comic strip blogger. The board has calmed down a little bit and he started to make some sense again,
and he sent me another audio comment. Hey, I'm Kerry. See you, satellite radio is like a marriage.
You came for sex, but you stay for love. See you's just achieved 4 million subscribers
because they came for her outstanding, but people stay for other reasons. For matters too,
at living, for roadok, or for Baba the Lost Ponds. Let me tell you something. My favorite
on series is Jay Thomas Show. This is on the same channel as Pot Show, by the way. Adam Kerry,
I have kind request. Please contact outcs who is booking guests for Jay Thomas Show and get
interviewed by phone on Jay Thomas Show to it for me. Thank you. You know what, why don't we get you
interviewed by by phone on the Jay Thomas Show? That would be cool, blogger. And I'll talk to the
satellite guy. That's so unfair. I'll talk to PW. Oh man, he's hate me right now. PW is
uh, yeah, I PW has all the incident. I'll be cool. We'll get in touch with the guy, but I think you should
be interviewed, man. You're the one that is, you're the fan. You're, you know, promote our stuff,
will you? That would be really helpful. Would appreciate it. Love the comment as always. Now this
next and actually the final bit I'm going to play for you today is uh, it's a promo that typically
would be too long. I would, you know, I just think I'm not going to play that because it's just drawn
out, but it's uh, someone who's doing something that uh, that I really want to encourage and I think
is a very brave, uh, any from the UK. So there you go, buy a saw around. Hi Adam. This is Don McAllister
from the Screencasts Online and your oMac podcasts. I have some news that may be of interest to you
and the Charlie listeners, as I know a good proportion of them are podcasts as themselves.
We'll have to over 20 years in corporate IT. I've taken the life-changing decision to become a full-time
indie podcaster and do podcasting for a living. I have two podcasts, Screencasts Online, which is a free
video podcast delivering weekly Mac based tutorials for the desktop and iPod. I got to tell you,
I actually already heard about, uh, because I think you the on the most, I'm subscribed to your
Screencasts coincidentally, um, and I was just looking at you at the Screencast version of this audio
promo last night and then this, this, this, this showed up this morning. So it was, it's interesting
how the internet works in strange and mysterious ways. It's been running since August 2005 and
built up quite an audience. There are now over 40 tutorials to download, covering also to topics
from Mac OS 10 to application reviews to podcasting. And the show has quite a unique approach
in that it uses Screencasts to deliver the tutorials and I managed to keep my ugly mug off the screen.
The Euro Mac podcast is a weekly audio podcast covering Mac news, but with a European spin.
It's only just been launched in the past three weeks, so it's still building an audience,
although the feedback's been great.
All right, that's the one. I haven't got any sponsorship or advertising as
yet. It comes to people. But hopefully that will come now that I've time to promote the podcast
properly. However, what I have introduced to see me through the initial period is a new subscription
scheme called Screencast Online Extra. Now the main show remains completely free and you can just
subscribe via iTunes as normal. But the six month extra subscription includes a free DVD of all the past
shows in all sorts of formats, access to high definition and high resolution versions of the shows,
and you special show every month just for subscribers, a monthly newsletter and lots of other
good stuff. The full six month subscription actually works out less than a price of a decent
coffee from Starbucks each month. And it includes all the extras including the DVD.
If people want to drop over to the site at www.screencast online.com, then they can pick up this
week show which explains the background to why I've taken the decision and how I've gone about
setting it all up. There are also free downloads of the show in high definition and in hands
desktop format to try out. And as soon as the podcast show delivery network and the podcast
music network come out of beta, I'll be doing some free screencasts on how to use them and to demonstrate
their functionality. Ah man, that'll be so cool. Notice by the way, it's not beta. It's beta.
A new one for me to start using. Oh, we have the beta beta controversy. So I hope that the
Charlie listeners will support me in this new venture. If only to show that it's not just
Ricky Javece and the other mainstream podcastes that can make a living out of podcasting.
Thanks for playing this audio comment at them. It's really appreciated. Thanks again.
No dude, my pleasure totally. So three things hit me when I listened to that one.
Actually when I saw it last night as I was going to bed, I saw your screencast.
And so a couple things hit me first of all. Wow, what a great format for video.
It's not going to work that well on iPods because the screen is just too small. But actually I got a screen
recorder last night. While I was in bed, you know, you really inspired me.
And I was trying to record my desktop, which by the way, I deem is the most personal piece of real estate
I have the applications that are on there, the files, the folders. And I think that would be
interesting for other people to be able to look at that. And I was actually experimenting with
opening up a video window on the desktop. So what you would see as a viewer was my desktop with
my mug. It kind of often the corner. Now, you know, it's with an eyesight camera. So the quality is
minimum or minimal. Let's put it that way. And, you know, then I could actually take you through
stuff. And I could, I don't know. I just think that there's interesting stuff to do. The issue
I'm having, of course, is performance because the screen recorders get pretty bogged down when
you're, you know, pop in web pages and this video playing. And, of course, what I'd like to do
then is open up another quick time window and play some more video. So I have some experimentation
to do. And specifically, getting it out to MPH4. Man, this is, I do not know enough about this.
There's so many fucking options. Is it H.264 that I should be using? Is it the, the,
the, you know, a quick time, you can export directly to, to M4V, which they say is Apple's version
of, of MP4. Now, if you export to MP4, it plays like shit on the Mac, which I don't understand.
Or maybe it's just my Mac. I don't know. I just, I need something that'll work.
And I need to be able to record. And I think my Mac should be powerful enough. But it might not be.
I might not need some kind of dual. It would be a shame if I can't do it on the power book,
because it's so easy to do it anywhere. God, it would be so cool to show it. Just share you my,
my desktop world, my laptop. Oh, that would be fun. So that you really inspired me with that,
and I appreciate it. So I'm, I'm working on that. And then, uh, and of course, I really, uh,
was a shaft to hear that you, uh, are considering doing some screencasts of the pdn. That
will be great. In fact, um, maybe in a week or so, we should talk, and then, you know, we can get you
in early, as you know, it's going to be, uh, we're delayed by about 10 days. So somewhere around mid-April,
just around tax day, cleverly timed. We'll be, uh, we'll be unleashing everything. And maybe you can
have some screencasts in there before that time. Uh, and we should definitely talk business about that.
And, and also, as I was viewing your screencasts, I'm like, wow, what a great opportunity for
branding and advertising, writing the screencast. It, you know, for a whole bunch of reasons,
a whole bunch of types of advertisers that make so much sense. But you may not want to do that
in sounds like you're, you're down the pay route. And I think that in your case, that is probably
a very smart idea. And I love the, the packaging that you're putting together. So congratulations.
I mean it. Congratulations. And, uh, I, I wish you lots of success. Okay, everybody, I'm going
to hit the shower, get dressed off to HQ another full day of fun stuff. Uh, oh, today I'm being
interviewed by the LA Times. That should be, I think it's today. That should be fun. Yes,
they run and I were interviewed by the, the chronicle. Um, and it just seems like the press is coming
through on another wave, you know, and, and of course, podpimp coordinates all that at HQ. Um,
so we're pretty stacked up this week. And, um, so maybe I'll get a video out tonight. I'll
mess around with some of that screencast technology. See if I can pull it together. Uh,
I'll check on, I got a lot to do. I'll check on the emails getting through to every single
ISP. So we can finally open up commerce on the pod safe music network. And, uh, last shoot, you know,
it'll just be busy. I'm ready to go home folks. I'm very, I miss my girls. I really do.
Uh, I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye, I can't last.
DailySourceco.com for the feeds. And add a Maccurry.com for the feedback.
Another pod show pod cast. Stick it in your ear.