Delta Sierra Charlie 3-4-1, this podcast is not family safe.
Well, Adam, since you appeared to be clueless in this regard, I've compiled a list of why
you are so despised.
I now give you the top 10 reasons why we hate Adam Curry.
Number 10, he used to work at MTV when MTV was still cool.
And as host of Headbangers Ball, arguably, he had the coolest job in MTV also.
Number 9, he is married to a beautiful former pop star.
Who drives a Jaguar and has her own cosmetic company.
Number 8, he is gorgeous.
Over six feet tall with roguish, good looks and a full head of thick blonde.
You know, fuck the list, I'll tell you what I hate you, Adam Curry.
You're always prancing about, look at me, I'm Adam Curry.
I can speak five languages, I fly planes and helicopters.
Look at me, I'm Adam Curry.
I've partyed at the MTV Beach House and the Playboy Mansion.
I'm Adam Curry, I co-invented podcasting.
I was in a movie with Sean Penn and Elizabeth Herley.
And I was also in Truth or Dare with Mandala.
I had my own TV series.
I'm so rich and bloody fucking successful in popular.
I've got my own stalker.
And, and if that wasn't enough, my last house, my last house was a fucking castle.
You've got some sort of magnet of vacuum that sucks away all the good fortune that
was intended for the rest of us regular guys.
You're taking more than your fair share.
Well, fuck you, Adam.
Fuck you in the plane, you flew in on.
Headwind, headwinds, Adam.
I want my hair back.
I want my hair back, you selfish bastard.
Oh, I swear I wouldn't do this.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Turn me this.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Oh, I guess it is Adam Curry.
If I feel it's feeling, if I let myself go deep again, we'd stay by my side.
If I feel it's feeling, then don't ever be the same again.
Let's cut our own love, don't I'll be flying.
Cause I can't sleep inside of you.
I can't feel your undermore.
I can't sleep inside of you.
But I don't mind if I'm inside of you.
You're my rally show Are you the answer to my question?
Have I wasted my time now?
Cause if I feel this feeling,
Call all of your first year next year
I'm calling the rally show
Will you be my light?
Cause I can't see someone
I can't feel someone
I can't see someone
But I don't run
You're by my side, I feel fine
I'll be fine
Can you show it to you to me?
Hey, show it to me
Hey, baby, I'm calling
Give me call
Cause I can't see someone
I can't feel someone
I can't see someone
But I don't mind
I go blind
I can't see someone
I can't feel someone
But I don't mind
You're by my side, I feel fine
I'll be fine
I'll have from Montana
They call themselves Black Lab
See the sun
And boy, do I ever
Sun just coming up here in Northern California
The Curricando Hey everybody, how you doing?
Time once again for the Daily Source Code
It is a little bit later than normal
It's a 7 a.m. I got up at 6
And of course, this is time to late
For those of you sitting on Syria saying, wait a minute
It's not 7 a.m.
No, this is the podcast
A synchronous entertainment in your ears
People ask me yesterday
Why I sounded like shit
And the only thing I can think of
Is that I just have this incredible cold
I don't know if it's the air conditioning
Or if it's just the, I could be the avian flu
Of course
If it's just the stuff that's going around
And around and around
Will we ever get out of this cycle of
Drippy noses
So I got up this morning 6 o'clock
I'm ready to put the charted together for you
And you always love to check my email
Because you know Patricia's completely email
Savvy now that she has her G5
I'm back
And so the first thing she says is
Hey, you're
Just get my, my cub here
So the first thing she said is hey
You're official
Your new license came
That'll be my pilot's license
I've been waiting for
Christ and it's almost six months
Six months to get a new
An actual piece of plastic that says
That I am both certified for
Rotaries
For helicopters and for fixed wing
And it finally came
I must say though
Your government at work man
If you go to the FAA website
And you send them an email
Or you click on their feedback form
They do get in touch with you pretty quick
Because they sent it to the wrong address
Or something like that
Anyway
It's snowing
In it
It's snowing in the United Kingdom
Today, at least in
In Guildford
So it's so weird man
And so now we've had this beautiful
Weather out here in San Francisco
Not that it's really warm
But the sun is shining right now
It's once again
It's coming up over the bay
It's just flooding the entire condo
It's
It's great
And there was another email that came in
I was from my, from my attorneys
As you know, next week
Excuse me for a second
Next week
On was it, I think Tuesday the 28th
Going to court in Amsterdam
Against this gossip magazine
Who did two things wrong in my mind
One is they followed my daughter
Took pictures
I'm sorry
They didn't publish pictures
They followed my daughter
And they published
The name of her school
And how she is transported
Or was I might say
Two in from school
Which of course in my mind
Is definitely in danger of my child
Now that of course is going to be subject
To a judge saying, well, you know, you've had her in the public eye
And maybe, you know, maybe it's okay for 15 year olds
To be followed around by men with large lenses
Which I don't think so
So that's very subjective
That that'll just depend upon the judge
Remember no jury system in the Netherlands
It's a professional judge system
And if they run out of judges
Then they revert back to a pool of backup judges
Who of course are lawyers
In their during their day job
So it's a kind of interesting court situation
Not at all likely might be used to in the states
And here's the interesting thing
Because I just saw they had to produce all the documents
They're going to enter into the lawsuit
Whatever
And what they're claiming
This is great
They're claiming that the
For those of you who don't know what happened here
They took pictures off of my flicker site
Which of all every single picture I put up has a creative comment
Either it's public or private
And of course I do have some pictures that are private
Just because I store all my pictures on flicker
But I don't want everything to be seen
And every single picture has a creative comments
License attached to it
Which is the share like non-commercial attribution
Which means, well, go look it up
It's creative comments
It's real simple
But you understand the point about non-commercial
So you can't use these pictures for commercial purposes
And of course a gossip magazine
Unless they're truly going to claim that it's news
That would be interesting
But I don't think that's the direction they're taking
So they basically stole my pictures
And published them across three pages
I mean, I'm not talking like little snapshot
I mean, I'm talking like full page stuff
For my trip to San Francisco
The three of us in Central Park
Just it was our personal pictures
Which if I ever wanted to sell those
Believe me, I could actually make some real money
From selling those for publication
So here's the argument
Underneath each picture or next to each picture on flicker
It'll say if the picture is privateer public
And then it has a little creative comments logo
Which is typified by the circle
With two seas inside of it
What they're saying, this is their argument
Is that the words this photo is public
Means that that photo is public
And you can go and take that photo and do with it as you wish
I can't believe they're actually going to enter this as their defense
But apparently they are
This is exactly what they're saying
And like well, you know
It just boggles the mind
And if this could actually happen
Because if they could get away with this
Because of those words this photo is public
Then Yahoo has a lot of explaining to do
Because Yahoo owns flicker
And man they got a lot of changes to make
And it just doesn't seem like that is possible
I think these guys are just trying to wheeze around
Someone didn't really look
And the arrogance of it
I just can't believe the arrogance of it
You know if I'm caught file sharing
One fucking MP3 of a ripped off song
You know then I get a call from the settlement agency
From the RIA
And only although probably started around 50,000
In my case probably more
But they can would let down to about five
And that's what I'd have to pay
If I didn't want to get my ass sued off
And these guys just come on to the net
Just come into any place they want
Take a picture and just pop not just one
Three they just publish them full page
It's unbelievable
So that of course boggles my mind
I had to spend a couple minutes just
Replying to my attorneys
Three me through email I'll call them later
But I'm sure that they have the same opinion about that
It's just nuts
Let's see, yesterday great day in the office
Here at Pod Show and at the headquarters
Dawn and Drew were in town
So there's a lot of a lot of hub up
We had a lunch forum which is great
Because everyone is working so incredibly hard
I think around the fifth or seventh of March I think
Maybe something like that is we're going to start
Bringing listeners
And we'll probably do a very small beta for listeners
To come into the into Pod Show
Plus and check out some of the stuff that we've been building
So everyone's really really working very hard
It was nice to just get get out
I'll have a lunch
For some reason we serve Margaritas at this lunch
Which I thought was fascinating
I had one I was like
Okay, I think that's it
But it was great to see Dawn and Drew
And I wish I could have gone to the podcaster meet-up last night
I was really planning on it
But I got kind of hung up at the office
Working on some stuff with K2
And before you know it's like nine o'clock
And so I forget about it
Let's see a couple of pieces of feedback
I want to share with you today as well
Here's one from a buddy of ours
I'm just Kevin Reeves
I'm not even going to try and apologize for the
Weird audio quality here
I'm laying in bed
It's 6 a.m
And I'm checking my email
And I'm completely pissed off about something
And DSC 139
You were talking about
People in Australia not being able to purchase
The song from the PMN
Because of some credit card issue
I wake up this morning and I got an email
From another Australian listener
Who cannot purchase my album
My website with the little PayPal buttons that I've put up there
The credit card itself is being denied
Not an insufficient funds kind of denied
But you can't use this credit card denied
And I've heard about this
A ton of times on the Maccast
I've heard about it
A lot of times just kind of
Surfing around the podosphere and the net
That people in Australia
For some reason
Can't seem to get music
Now my site is a dumbass PayPal button
That is generated just from the, you know, merchant tools thing
It just says click, you know,
PayPal, fast free and secure or whatever
So what is up with our
Supposed global infrastructure
Not being able to support our friends down under
I'm just completely pissed off with the fact that
You know, somebody had a desire to buy some of my music
It's nine bucks
I don't give a shit about the money
That's not the issue that I'm trying to raise here
But if somebody liked my music
Wanted to support me as an artist
Wanted to wanted the music
And can't get to it
Because somehow they're locked out
Because of their region
That is just completely ass of mine
We live in this global market
And here we are
People can't buy something
From a website
Just because they live somewhere else
This is completely retarded
And I'm sure that there's more
Incidences than you can count with PayPal
And iTunes
And whatever else that takes a credit card that's saying
Oh, you can't purchase this
Because you're from, the fuck kind of world do we live in here
I'm just completely I rate
So if anybody in Australia wants to buy my record
Preorder it whatever
Fuck it
Send me a receipt that says you can't get it
And I will send you a free download
That's just how we're going to do it
I feel like people should have access to my music
And if you can't get it
I will make sure you get it
So that's it for today
Adam, I just thought I would throw that out there
I'm sorry for the long feedback
But I just wanted to open dialogue
No, I got it
I totally get it, you're pissed
Of course you are
And so now I have some backup here
On some of the problems we saw
Some folks from Australia trying to purchase
Podsafe or piece off of the Podsafe music network
And they were having trouble with their credit card
So I guess it's not just
It's just in general for some reason
The clearing houses or the credit card
Processing companies
I don't know what it is
But that is major discrimination
And why?
And let me, I'm just trying to think back
Because I talked to Chris Rockwell about it
I know we saw a purchase from New Zealand
I think we had at least one or two purchases from Australia
But we have gotten feedback that some folks have had problems
Using their credit card
So it does seem like some kind of discrimination
I guess
Moving forward
With the unlabeled concept
Making MP3s available
Free and clear for you to purchase
Through the Podsafe music network
I think we're going to add a couple more songs to the data test
So we can really
We want to test out the podcaster links
There's all kinds of reporting
Stuff remember now if you're participating in the data test
You'll see that
Just every single track on the Podsafe music network
Has a kind of grayed out by button
Which means you can't buy it yet
But if you look for podsafe
For peace you can actually sign up and see the process
And send us some feedback on that
If you will please and for night
You know put your credit card in you've opened an account
And of course
Except for the transaction fee which is nine cents
Everything else is going to podsafe
For peace which of course is going directly to unice
So for the data test
No one's making money
It's up the damn credit card guys
In this case that would be clicking by
But hey, you know what they're doing it
And then yeah, okay
So we're just going to continue to test that
And I think that we'll have a couple more songs that will make available
And then we'll just open it up
So any artists can go in
Click a button and make any tracks available
That they wish
What else was I gonna say
My goodness
Oh you know who's in town today
Ponsi
If you don't know Ponsi she is a Chris Parillo's better half
Then I really mean the better half
She's going to be in San Francisco
You know nom dex is coming up
So maybe maybe I can drag her on the podcast
That would be cool
Yeah, maybe we do that for tomorrow
We'll do a thank god it's Friday with Ponsi that could be yeah that could be interesting
All right, so I'll ask her if she'll do that
So she's going to be in the office
And around San Francisco that'll be fun
Oh man oh yesterday
We had we finally had our earth link conversation
You know what I want to talk about the earth link conversation
But I'm going to do that outside of the satellite window
So folks on the serious stars 103
If you want to hear that you have to go to dailysourceco.com
And download the entire podcast
And you may want to listen to this
Six foot five
265 pounds of angry ex-loinbacker
His daddy toughened him up with a strap
The law called it child abuse and assault
His daddy called it discipline
That discipline
Help make Perry Dawsey
Oh pilot wrecking ball of a linebacker
A football legend and a pain-dealing machine
What would the football stop
The violence didn't Perry has spent his whole life
Trying to break the cycle of violence
Do we come a better man than his father
He told himself to control his anger
His paranoia and his powerful rage
But the voices are telling him something else
When the infection hits Perry has only one week to live
The question is
How many people is he taking
With him
Infection is the horrifying new podcast novel by me Scott Siggler
Author of Ancestor and Earth Corps
Infection drops March 11th
So sign up now at ScottSiggler.potcho.com
Or subscribe directly at feeds.feedburner.com slash Scott Siggler
The infection kills you slowly
If the cure doesn't kill you
First
Scott Siggler man your out of your mind
This guy is just bopping all over the place
We're so proud to have him on the
On the pod show podcast network
So it drops March 11th
You know the success of Earth Corps
Scott has got so many items in the fire
There's so much cool stuff going on
And I'm really looking forward to this new novel
Which of course will be released
As a podcast as well
So stay tuned for that
Let me see
Okay, what we're going to do here
You know it seems like this infections
Of course infectious infection
Flues
We talked about the bird flu yesterday on the podcast
Oh of course
You think that I would be the only one talking about bird flu in podcast
No, I don't think so
The world of the 21st century
The planet is in a state of terror
Helped to rent some by international terrorist groups
Abel to trust constants on their own
Unstoppable by the government
Unreasonable to impress
So hard core a speaking sheep's and whistles
With a weapon so strong
So powerful
They can demand all the stealing grain they want
Tweety pie stars in
Bird flu
Over the coos nest
The sea geek
Until there's a cure to bird flu
There's something to listen to
Double WWE dot
And the sneaky key dot next
Go ahead take advantage of it
Well yeah, and there's also a
There's a bird flu
Uh weblog that I've been
Has been brought to my attention
Influenza pandemic.blogspot.com
Those of you checking us out now on
Serious stars 103
Bear in mind very soon if you hear
Something completely different which I think will be
The blue collar comedy channel on 103
That means we moved up one notch
To 102
That should be coming any day now
Coming up right after the source code
In just a second from now we kick it off
Or continue with Pacific Coast
Hel way Mark Yoshimura and M.Coff today
It's he this is Kid Rock
This is the lead singer of Creed
This is Dignation all of Christian rock
And anyone with an ounce of decor
After that yeast radio
Madge Weinstein back at home in Chicago
Dawn and Drew after that discussing
Let's proceed in leprechauns
And after that PWF and himself
Introduces his new listener calling line after
An episode of digital flots
And we'll see you back here tomorrow on the bird
On stars 103
Kick it off at 6 p.m. Eastern
At its three p.m. Pacific
Okay, they're gone
Speak in of Madge Weinstein
Hello Adam
It's Madge here
Listen I heard that you listen to your
Asking why I haven't been
I'm
Leaving new messages anymore
Clever messages
Well because evidently you found Roger Smalls
Who you like more than me
And
Plus my girlfriend because he is good
It's just died of cancer in case you didn't notice
First of all
I am not the least bit offended by somebody
Making a joke about cancer
That's idiotic
Why the fuck would I make care about
Somebody making a joke about cancer
As if it just started to exist
When my gutsy isco
It's got cancer inside of it
Listen remember a long time ago
When I said that I think breast cancer is worse
I'm sorry when I thought vaginal yeast
It's worse than breast cancer
Well listen
I meant it
Because my gutsy
Really Christ I got up
It just stayed hard
It's anyway enough
So I don't know what are all you walking on egg shells
Plus I didn't even have time to listen to your gut
Fuck I'm starving so now
Listen that's not the real reason I'm complaining
And you better listen to this Adam
Because you may not want to play it on your show
But how come
You want it bitchy you're going to get bitchy
Why Adam
Does it take since September
To get way into wisdom
And rate it fox
Signed up with advertising agreements with pod show
I've had a call Brian longest a hundred thousand times
And nothing happens
And I called Richard Bruhae and he promised
Everything's going to work
And then he tells me no it's not going to work
Because they're rearranging something
So that was some from September
To now now how the fuck am I supposed to make you got
Damn money and me got damn money
If I can't even forget any of this
Fucking fucking goddamn fucking paperwork
So get the shit together over there
Already I don't know who's fucking fault it is
But just fucking take care of it
I'm doing my part
I call every five seconds and you're like
Mads take initiative take initiative
Well I'm taking goddamn initiative
I got a popular show that I work with Wanda
And Reagan with it's called Eat This Hot Show
It's been on it
It's actually featured on the iTunes
And how the fuck am I going to put sponsorship on it
Take your goddamn assholes together
So do it
I'm in mourning
Take care of me
Mads my dear
Well I went to the I went to the mat for you yesterday
To figure it all out
You remember when we helped you
Set up your own production company
Which owns your own podcasts
Remember that dear match
Remember when we did that and why did we do that
So that you could produce more shows
Well
Remember all the paperwork that had to be made up
Which we paid for by the way
So that we could set up your production company
Well now we have on our dime
We've gotten more lawyers more of my favorite people
Mads working on agreements
So you can actually have the direct agreement
With Wanda and with Reagan
So give me a break
Okay
I love you anyway baby
You know that
Hello Adam this is Chris Skinner
From the podcast
Simulacrum
It was a pleasure to hear you playing my advert
I think it was yesterday
For McWilco turbo sword 94
Which is a brand that I'm sure will be available very soon
You had problems with the name
Simulacrum
It basically means a vague
Or unreal resemblance to something
And the shows called that because I interview very very very famous people
But they're not real
Well they are real but they're not really there
But they kind of are
I think I think I'll probably be the best way to celebrate
And I have adverts on it as well
Which are kind of real
But because they're really adverts
But they're not always
Selling things that are there
And that are real
You should listen
It's really good and we should have you on
Because you're your real really famous now
And you have a nice neck tie
So thank you very much
Chris Skinner from Simulacrum
I keep up the good work
Dude
What are you talking about?
Maybe you're confused with Tim Curry
Who know is not related to me
Let me point that out
Speaking of being on shows
I'd like to be on Simulacrum
Now that I know how to pronounce it
If you haven't heard it today in podcasting
Episode number
Was it three or four I think
Yeah, I'm not sure
I thought it was three
Interviewed by the guys from today in podcasting
Who build themselves kind of as a
A twit for podcasting
Love it
We had a really nice conversation
Haven't listened back to the show
But I know they posted it
And we had a really good chat
About just all kinds of stuff
And podcasting
And really enjoyable
So if you want to check that out
You can look for it
It's at today in podcasting.com
I'm sure it is
I'm sure this guy did that
Okay, so briefly about earthling
Because this is
First of all
I wish that I had recorded this
But you know when you have a phone call
It was me, Ron, KJ from the office
We had the folks at Jess and her team at MediaVest
Who are their agency
And we had the marketing department in Atlanta
From earthling on the phone
And you know
If we'd all known each other really well before
And it would have said can I please record this
But actually
One or more I think Scott from earthling
I said that he would be happy to come on the show
And talk about
About our conversation
Because he said it so eloquently
And so beautifully
You know what they had learned
From the earthling commercials
And all the feedback that they received
Not only from us
But these guys are out there
They live on the internet
And they really do care about their customers
And they even said that they were laughing
At times about
You know about
Basically the
The thought process that we'd all gone through
About these commercials
And I think that I'm also realizing now
That it just doesn't make sense
At least to have the same commercial
Playing every single time
And
And it was it was it was it said
You know we really liked a lot of these alternative
Commercials
You know what was the one they said
From I think it was was that
Derek Kay Miller who sent that one in
How shoot now I'm forgetting
The one that said you know earthling
It's like a laxative for your inbox
And it was so great he said
You know it's true that we really are
We really are laxative for your inbox
And we really like that kind of stuff
So we were coming up with a plan
That will involve everybody
And there is reward for this
There's obviously
You know I talk about a lot
Social and for winners
Yes economic reward
To participate in this
And we should be announcing
I hope sometime next week
We have sign off on the idea
And everything
We've kind of talked a hint a little bit about
What that would be
But it was so nice to hear
Talking about
New ways of advertising
And they're so into it
They are so completely into trying it
They understand it's a risk
But they said screw it
We just want to do this
Let's go and figure this out
So I'm looking
I'm looking forward to a lot of you
Folks helping us out
And indeed figuring out what works
What doesn't work
And you know maybe we'll learn something
In the process
I sure hope so
So anyway
I should be able to get Scott from earthling
I'll shoot for that next week
If I can get him on
To talk about their thoughts about advertising
In
You know really
When I think about it
I haven't seen or heard
Many interviews with advertisers
With big name brands
I'm not talking about agencies
I'm talking about big name brands
And their thoughts about advertising
In podcasting
So that may be a first
Certainly
I know that these guys are
We'll do a good job
But explaining their position
And what we're going to do
And I'm very excited about it
Okay
I'll tell you what
I'm going to get ready
You know I've been standing here
Once again in my
In my white bathrobe
With my black ugly boots on
Which is the way we do it here in podcasts
Alright Michael Butler
This one's for you
I think you love this song so much
But you got to do it
You don't like this
You got to do it
One, four, three
Stingray
Right around
All our world down here
Been alive
Falling down on a patio
Making plans
Moaning to care
People go
Can't happy face
It's sad I don't need you again
Piles
No, one, four, three
That's where we're
Get it all
Now you'll never find it
You can feel it
One that's far
It's far
You'll never find it
One time
One from the corner
We've been by our time
Take our right and right
But we got nothing to hide
Make a start
Just one right
To our right
Never say that
Good boy
With your heart
What do I do
You got to do it
One, four, three
That's where we're
Get it all
Now you'll never find it
You can feel it
One that's far
It's far
You'll never find it
You got to do it
There's all that brought us
Ask a place
What do I do
W Trying to find you
When I find you
Everybody want me to spell it
When all I need is sudden
To begin one
And one is falling for you
One, four, three, from the Bodhisattva Music Network, music.bodshow.com.
I just realized I made an incredibly huge mistake.
Last Blaster Mike has created a new version, or the Beta 060 of Cast Blaster, find it at
castblaster.com, has removed the war bowl that everyone has been talking about.
And I'm such a dick.
I forgot to install it.
So apologies for the war bowl.
The minute I'm done with this show, I will go and install the new version.
I'm so sorry about that.
Adam at curry.com, dailysourcecode.com is where you can find all the information about
this show.
Be back if you feel like it tomorrow, right here on the Charley, it will be the thank
Goddots Friday edition.
Take care now.