This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want to hear content with AdAS domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie, three, six, five.
$16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jar.
365 episodes, it's a full year of the Charlie.
$16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
$17 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
$20 million worth oft per flight.
$20 million worth of planes strap to your ass.
Don't you know, there's a reason to show
You'll feel good
Turn on your gun, move
You'll never know, if you're right
Come on, come on, come on
Where are you going?
To me, to you know, touch me
No, no, no, no, no, no
Everything's not for me
Call it never, never, never always be
No, never, never, never, never
To me, never, never be
You're holding so much, what a place
Why the wind is right?
No, never, never, never, never, never
No, never, never, never, never
You're holding so much, what a place
Why the wind is right?
No, never, never, never, never, never
No, never, never, never, never
No, never, never, never, never, never, never
No, never, never, never, never, never
No, never, ever!
No, never, never, never, never, never, be
I won't do do do I
I'm never gonna be
You said I'm supposed to beg you please
You know what I mean
Turn out the lights to turn on the sun
I don't mind me
When I finish from my side
I'll tell you I need you
I'm never gonna be me
It's all I've forgotten
Yeah, not like a bunch of racket that kick off another Charlie, huh?
I'm coming home, it's the red bendies, and I am home, back at the Cottage.
Yes, you guys look beautiful.
This is the Daily Source Code, episode number 365.
We've had a little bit of a numbering issue with the best of Charlie's, but this is the
official, the first year of the Daily Source Code.
That is, if you were to start on one day and play a Charlie every single day, you'd
take an entire year, 365 episodes.
And that, of course, is excluding the wonderful best of Charlie's that were created
by the Daily Source Code audience over the past, almost a week and a half fantastic.
I can't tell you how cool it was to listen to those every single day.
And so thanks to the bedtime stories, go first, thanks to Marcus Couch, thanks to Angie B.
Oh, Angie, oh, Angie, your best of Charlie was my favorite without a doubt.
So we've got to pick up our little love messages again, you know?
But it's denying that you sent me panties, puppies.
Also thanks, of course, to PW Fenton, who did the yesterday's best of Charlie was it to
mash up.
Oh my goodness, that was great, PW, I really appreciated that.
And as I was listening to it, home, I just have it here, I have it cut up on the Mac,
because I was listening to it.
This particular piece got Patricia laughing in a whole different part of the college.
Anyway, the, the, um, the, um, the, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, um, uh,
and so I fired off an email, I said, um, uh, uh, um, uh, um, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, um,
he dove.
Thanks for making yourself conscious, man.
Really appreciated.
But it was a great experiment.
It really, really worked.
And I'll make sure that, uh, we get t-shirts.
Oh, man, my mixer is a little cruddy.
I'll make sure that we get t-shirts sent out to everyone to send to the best of Charlie.
Again, really appreciated.
Thank you very much.
It was so nice on vacation.
I was almost completely unplugged and you'd expect me to have all kinds of stories to tell
you, but really, it was 100% uneventful exactly the way we planned and we haven't had
in the sun lay down, just read some books vacation in a long time, um, one where there
wasn't a television production attached to it or, um, in the US when we went on vacation
to New York and San Francisco last time, um, we were all sick.
So that wasn't a real vacation.
We were also looking for apartments and stuff like that.
So that was, that was kind of a working vacation.
But just lay down in your ass.
It was great.
So now I can tell you what we were.
Pine cliffs, Sheraton resort in the Algarve, um, right to the east, yeah, to the east of Albufera.
And it was fantastic.
It was exactly what we wanted.
Right down to the buffet dinner, which is the kind of dinner we like the best because you
can kind of decide right there what you want to have.
And they had theme nights for the buffet dinner.
Oh, yes, we're very common like that.
I love it.
And the buffet breakfast, and it was fantastic.
It really was.
We hadn't been in Portugal for 23 years.
And boy, has a lot changed.
You know, of course, they'd become a new member of the European Union.
They spent billions of euros on infrastructure.
There's now actual roads.
You can, you can really drive from from the airport to the Algarve on on a highway.
And the people are just so incredibly nice.
And if I were to compare them to Spaniards,
because it'd been to Spain on vacation a lot, I have to say,
like the Portuguese better, really, really nice.
And they, of course, they have almost no industry in Portugal.
They have oranges, I believe.
They have obviously some fruits, but oranges really big.
And they have some textiles, like shoes and stuff that come from Portugal.
And the rest is pretty much tourism and golf.
And Patricia and I have now definitely decided
after having spent an entire vacation in a golf resort.
Hey, we should try that sometime.
And we will, our next door neighbors, or across the street,
actually, Jimmy and Marion, I think they run the golf club here near by the cottage.
So we'll definitely hook up with them.
And we're going to start trying some golf.
How incredibly lame is that?
But a lot of people seem to be into it.
A lot of people like it.
And Tiger Woods is a pretty cool dude.
So I guess we're going to get started on it.
Of course, the one thing that I'm kicking myself over
is that I forgot, I can't believe this.
I forgot my video camera.
So we're on vacation and I had this beautiful,
and I actually almost purchased it specifically to take it on vacation,
to mess around with it and do some fun stuff.
I left it the exacte C5.
I left it here at the cottage.
I'm such a dork.
God.
So just a bit about the trip.
What was really nice is, well, it wasn't nice that we couldn't get any flights
from the UK direct to Farrow Airport.
We could get them from Rotterdam.
And so we did something kind of different.
We took the channel tunnel.
So we drove to Folkston.
Thank you for the correction on the pronunciation.
Couple people emailed me about that.
Folkston.
And you drive right onto the train.
And it's about 25, 30 minutes underneath the North Sea channel.
And then you pop right out and all of a sudden, you're in France.
And of course, you're also driving on the right hand side of the road again.
And the speed limit is significantly higher than the UK,
at least in the French portion of the drive.
And you drive through France, drive through Belgium, pass the castle, pass right on the road
where we used to get off the exit to go to the castle up to Rotterdam.
It took a little detour, a quick stop off at Purple Rain in Brida, which is my old coffee shop
haunting grounds where I'd go and chill out with my Muslim brothers who have been running the shop
for about 20, 25 years now.
So it was great to see them.
And then we stayed at the Rotterdam Airport hotel and left the next morning, 7 AM.
I think would really, really early flight off to Fato.
It was perfect.
I just can't say anything else, but it was absolutely perfect.
And it was great with Christina.
We had a really good time because she, of course, is now a young woman and an adult.
And they're almost adult.
And the brains are in adult mode.
Let's put it that way.
And she's funny.
It was great to be with her in the same quarters without my space.
Because you see a lot more of your kids.
If there's no space around.
Boy, it was she Jones and hard.
Oh, and it's all about it.
That's my space has now become her email.
This is how these kids are using it.
It's fantastic.
It's almost like a subscription to people.
In fact, it is opting email almost.
And, you know, like, I keep saying, yeah, I, I send you an email.
She's like, I don't really email.
So why?
Because every time I go to email, there's spam.
I don't want to go through all the spam.
So I guess that that's how stuff is moving.
Email got so messed up that kids aren't using it anymore.
So she was Jones in big time.
Luckily, now we had a townhouse, two bedroom townhouse.
So there was no Wi-Fi there.
No hard-wired connection.
So you had to go into the hotel lobby and they had a vote of phone.
Wi-Fi hotspot, which Christina, what I did is I gave her the Mac every single day.
It was charged up.
Damn those new batteries.
Damn it, Apple used to have like an hour and a half charge.
You know, you knew your kid would be back in an hour and a half.
And I was like three hours until the battery runs out.
Pretty cool the way vote of phone has that set up.
By the way, you log in.
You get one of those splash screen pages that says, you know, you've got to pay.
And the way you do it is you just send a text message to a vote of phone phone number.
And then they text you back a code and then you use your username as your phone number.
And you use that code as the password.
And you can buy an hour or 24 hours or 72 hours.
And it really easy.
You know, no credit cards just straight to the phone bill.
I was using my U.S. singular cell phone.
So it did a straight to that number.
The building is all transparent and fantastic.
Excuse me, Sensei.
Yeah.
And I'm drinking one right now.
Let me tell you.
Portuguese, okay?
Great, great, great people.
But they got no sensei.
Hey, Adam, this is Travis Goss.
One of the hosts of the odd radio show.
Looks like you had a pretty good vacation.
It's soaking up the sod, catching some rays.
You know, doing all that really cool stuff.
While some of us had to work our asses off just to make a living.
Now, just plain what you're mad.
But seriously, how was your vacation?
Yeah, as I said, vacation was just dandy.
And I got a tan, except for that one part where, you know, if I'm sitting down,
then my stomach starts to kind of like bunch up into multiple packs.
I have a one pack.
You know, most guys have a six pack.
And so I've got a nice white crease there.
I'm the kind of guy that, he's what happens with me on vacation,
a gone vacation and everything starts to just release.
And please don't get the wrong idea.
But I get, my sinuses get blocked up.
I'm dead the first 48 hours.
I'm pretty much dead to the world.
I'm just, you know, complete exhaustion.
I just let everything go.
It's hard to get me out of bed.
And, and, you know, and then so around day three is when I start to emerge
and then I'll sit in the sun, only in an hour, even if it's overcast,
I'm the guy that's fried, you know, I get completely, completely red,
and then I have to be real careful for the next two days.
So that's about half the vacation.
And then I can really start to get to enjoy it.
Although the sinuses still are blocked up.
I've got a, I've got a cough, which is just kind of a lingerie.
It's probably been there for months and months.
And just as it was starting to really loosen up and, and everything was,
I was getting rid of everything.
It was time to leave.
And so we flew back, oh, that was cool.
On the way back home.
Patricia, let me see, no, we were in, so it's Transavia,
which, it does, you know, daily flights to Faro and Rotterdam,
which is, you know, on my favorite airport, even to take our own plane, too.
But they can land 737s on that runway.
And so we're sitting there and the stewardess comes back and she says,
to Patricia says, you know, you're, you're, you're dentist's son.
Now this is her first dentist from 30 years ago.
So he's about 80 now, but her son who is his son, who, whoops, who knows.
His son, who is now 41, I think, a 42.
He was first officer on the flight.
And so she had mentioned that to the, to the captain, the first officer.
And he said, oh, well, you know, have him come up front.
And so Patricia went up and was talking to him.
And of course, he wasn't flying the plane, the captain was.
And then Christina and I were both invited to go up front.
This is about 200 miles away from Rotterdam, somewhere over Leal in France.
And we're invited to go up front and sit in the jump seats.
And for the rest of the journey, all the way down up to the gate,
it was, I have to say, and I've been in a cockpit of large aircraft before.
You know, you can get to take a look, but actually to sit there and to witness the entire landing.
Whoa, that was awesome.
And of course, what you see is that it's exactly the same as with the Delta Shara.
There's literally no difference.
Yeah, the instruments are a little flashier looking.
You know, they've got glass cockpit and all that.
But it's the same thing.
And I could actually, you know, it's understand very well was happening.
It's like, oh, well, and actually, they told me not to tell you how easy it was,
because they didn't want anyone else catching up.
And then the next day, as we stated, the Rotterdam Hilton again,
we met Patricia's family came over, not the Hilton, the airport hotel,
but Patricia's family came over yesterday morning.
And then we drove off to Fox and it was, once again, it was great.
The, that whole channel, tunnel experiences is actually pretty damn good.
And I think if you were to go to Paris, it would probably be a pretty good train ride.
You don't have to take the car, but you can take the train ride,
the train, I think, from Waterloo Station.
That, whoops, the hell was that?
Oh, Skype, yes.
Did everyone look down at your computer thinking that you just received a Skype message?
Best pieces of your podcast.
They sucked, so you stupid fucking stop doing some interesting content,
or you really be fucked up.
For those of you who knew to the Charlie,
comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip,
comic strip,
on, come in, come in for a second, Patricia just walked in.
You want to put on your headphones?
Actually, no, but okay.
Yeah, put him on for a second.
I think it's, I think it's all working.
Hey, baby.
Hi, honey.
Oh, what happened?
Is this higher?
That's weird.
Hey.
Yeah, turn over to that way.
Somebody used the studio here.
Some, I think so.
Our house sitter.
She's like, oh, no, they're gone.
I can finally use the studio.
Yeah, right.
So I was just telling everyone how much fun the vacation was.
Yeah, there was a lot of fun.
Yeah.
It was. I said there's nothing to report really because...
No, we just been very lazy.
Enjoyed the sun.
Yeah.
Which was, oh, what was not nice on your body, yeah.
I like that, because it's so cold here.
It's well, it's not bad today.
It's been a big day.
Actually, we brought the sun.
Yes, we did.
Yeah.
Yeah, so now it's nice here, but it was nice to feel the warmth on your skin.
And that was not just me laying on top of you.
And that was not you.
Which is sweaty butt against me.
Okay, well, thanks for joining the show.
And so how do you feel?
How do I feel?
I feel good.
I feel rested.
I feel energized.
Empower is ready to rock and roll.
You were so tired.
Yeah, I was just telling them that, you know, the first two days.
I'm like in coma.
Yeah.
And then I saw my sinus.
Every time you had fell backwards.
It's like, would you mouth open?
Is that frightening?
Yeah.
It's like I just died.
I thought my God, he's exhausted.
Yeah.
Well, I am.
Well, all that flying back and forth.
Yeah.
Oh, there was an article.
Hold on a second.
You'll like this.
Mm-hmm.
Tom Schoobling sent this.
That's the guy that that archives all of the Korean van in
goals, and all my radio shows on the internet.
The guys in Australia.
Oh, yeah.
He sent an article from the BBC that the researchers have now
discovered, let me see where it is here.
If you wear sunglasses when you're flying westwards for jet lag.
If you wear sunglasses, then you're buying.
Oh, yeah.
Your brain.
Yeah, thanks.
Thanks.
Tonight, and then it will basically say the lower level, and you won't be as tired.
Good idea.
Yeah.
Of course, you look like an asshole on the planet.
Well, I find the whole thing.
Once on TV about dark and about when it's getting dark outside, how you
body just shuts down and.
Well, my wake up when it starts to get dark.
Ha ha ha.
Yeah.
Yes.
So does my daughters, actually?
Well, what do you expect?
You guys don't want to sleep.
There's too much going on in the world, huh?
Yeah, it's just too much happening.
I know.
Okay.
But anyway, so it looks like I'll be around the cottage for.
Yeah, but there's no food in the house.
So that sucks.
You say you walk in, you say, hey, you have an eating yet.
No, because I've been down stairs.
Because there's no food.
Well, of course, a mom always can find something in the house,
and prepare you something.
You know, there's some bacon, some eggs.
Yeah.
I know you would like that.
But first, do you show?
Yes.
And when you're done.
And then I get a reward.
A little gold star.
Is that your reward?
Oh, that's pretty nice.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
So it's good to be back.
Yeah, definitely.
And I'm going to be around for a while.
Yeah.
And then the two of us will come to.
Uh, then the two of us are going to go San Francisco.
We're going to Pebble Beach.
Yeah.
You know, maybe we should hook up with Jimmy and Mary and before that,
and start golfing.
Because Pebble Beach is the golf.
I told him we're going to start golfing.
Yeah, we were actually vacationing.
Um,
Yeah, a great golfer.
Yeah, golf resort.
Yeah.
And we're looking at going like, oh, you know, maybe we should do that.
I mean, it's good cardio vascular exercise for you.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, of course it is.
Why do you think all those guys with heart attacks to golf?
You think so?
Yeah.
It's supposed to be fantastic for your heart.
Yeah, I mean, you see.
They didn't look very hip, did they?
I don't know.
Wait, if you know how I always, it's so funny.
Because every time I see sort of people of my age,
I always say, oh, there's a lot of old people here.
And I think, oh my god, I'm actually the same age.
And I forget all the time.
And Mary, I can grow.
Because I don't feel that way.
And Mary, I congratulate you on your birthday.
Because we only celebrated it privately.
It has to be on your birthday.
Yes, we have to.
When you get that, it's true.
April 7th, Patricia had a birthday.
Yeah.
I guess we don't say how old you are anymore.
That's we don't talk about that now.
Yeah.
It comes to a point in a woman's life.
It's so disappointing.
You know, so many things I have to do.
Disappointing.
Yeah, I just, I remember when I was 18, 19,
I always love my birthdays.
Yeah.
I was like, oh my god, it's my birthday.
But now you think, oh shit.
Yeah, what was that we heard yesterday?
When up until you're 40, you're living.
What was that?
I can't remember it.
It was actually very good.
It was so good.
I can't remember it.
Is you're living away from death?
And after you're 40,
you're living towards death?
It was something like that.
Yeah, something like that.
Yeah.
God, we're stupid.
Can't remember that.
No, it was good.
We both, yeah, it's true.
Yeah.
Oh, hold on.
It's like, hold on.
Oh my gosh.
You know what this means, don't you?
You can't hear it?
Well, anyway.
I think that this is me.
Yeah.
No, he's not.
That's not you.
That means P-Dob was going to close the satellite window.
And we'll check you guys out on serious tomorrow here
on the daily source code.
Can't believe you couldn't hear any of that.
No.
I didn't even know, did I thought, do you hear yourself?
Did the headphones?
Then why do you, why are you wearing that?
Why don't you tell the engineer that your headphones
aren't working, baby?
You're not.
That's all I said.
It's professional.
I'm not going to mention.
Put them on.
Let's do it.
So work.
You hear anything at all?
No, no, no.
It doesn't matter.
Yeah, it does.
Of course, you turn around here.
My, my wire's not long enough.
Okay, let's see.
Does that work?
No.
You're kidding me.
No, I'm just not plugged in somewhere.
You are plugged in.
It doesn't matter.
It's not interesting.
No, it's not interesting, but it's annoying,
because then you can't react to all the...
Yeah, that's the next time.
It's all right.
Okay.
I'm going to have to go downstairs anyway.
I understand.
I've alienated you.
Okay.
Okay, baby.
You want to?
Yes.
Uh-huh.
Oh, yes, please.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, please.
Okay.
Bye.
Bye, baby.
Love you.
Bye.
All right, see you later.
Okay.
The lovely intelligence and misputure-share-py, everybody.
Okay, so one more thing I'm really excited about.
This Saturday, the 15th.
And that kind of ties into comic strip blogger,
because he was going to be in the UK on the 15th.
And he said, he sent me an email saying he wanted to interview me
on some neutral ground, but he's only here for one day.
And unfortunately, the 15th, this has been planned for a couple of weeks.
Wing Commander William is bringing the plane over from Antwerp Airport,
the November 277 Delta Sierra.
He'll be arriving 9 a.m.
I think at Fair Oaks.
And then from there, Captain Dan and I,
and the Wing Commander, fly back to Antwerp.
So we're basically shuddling the Wing Commander back.
And then Captain Dan and I will fly back to the UK again.
So it's going to be a full day of flying.
The point is, though, I have a safety pilot.
And I had a long chat with Captain Dan last night on the phone.
First time we actually spoken on the phone.
Sounds like a great guy's little bit older than I am,
but very experienced pilot.
And knows a shit load about what's going on in aviation in these neck
of the woods.
He even turned me on to another airport,
which is just 15 minutes from the house.
And it's an X-R-A-F testing center
where they actually built the Harrier Jet.
It's called Dunsfold, Dunsfold Park Airfield.
It's a private airfield, but I can get a hanger there immediately.
And you can even land a Gulfstream G5,
because it has the most, you know, an incredibly long and wide runway.
So it's, I'm very jazzed about all that.
And the fact that I'm going to be around for a couple of weeks,
means I might actually get some flying in.
How cool would that be?
Meanwhile, back at the ranch, and I'm just catching up on everything.
All, you know, there's so much to catch up on
of what's been happening at Pod Show headquarters,
Pod Show LA, and even Pod Show UK.
Let me let you know.
And I've shadowed four walls,
all two secrets some will kill to protect.
And others will die to expose,
because it is on this ground that the very first battle of Armageddon
has been waged for over 300 years.
A battle that will finally be decided once.
I should have prefaced that by saying this is just a voice test
from our voice for Shadow Falls, which is coming very soon.
Shadow Falls, coming this spring to the Pod Show podcast network.
Pod Show LA is rocking, man.
There's so much talent that is waiting on tables in California.
And they're just like, everyone's showing up with great ideas.
And, you know, they all want to just everyone wants to work.
You know, it's so, it's so unbelievable how many people are just trying to get
shit done, really is, you know, whatever it is.
And to be able to do stuff with no rules, no boundaries,
and come up with your own ideas, it's really working in Pod Show LA.
Pod Show UK, we'll tell you about that.
At the, let me see, the end of this month, Ron's coming over.
And he actually is also bringing his wife, Marta,
and I think KJ is coming over.
So it's going to be a good fun, week in London.
As we're meeting with a number of different companies, partners, clients,
customers, advertisers, podcasters, et cetera.
And actually, I think we should try and set up a couple of a couple of,
I don't know if we could do a, like a podcaster, a UK podcaster,
meet and greet, hang out, chill, drink some pints, you know, throw some
darts, get together.
That actually might be a good idea.
I'll, I'll see if I can get on the agenda on the schedule.
As soon as possible, because it's going to fill up really, really fast.
But it looks like stuff's getting pretty serious.
And of course, then, I'll have to change on my tax status and stuff,
because it'll actually be working here as well.
And that does kind of suck, but hey, anyway.
So that's what's coming up in the future of cheesemen.
We know, I haven't even had a chance to look at all the work that's been done
on Pod Show Plus, the MASH board, the PDN, Pod Save Music Network,
all that stuff coming together in the next days, slash weeks.
Not quite sure.
I don't even know what the unleash schedule is now.
I mean, there's so much to talk about.
But to my tomorrow, I'll be much better educated.
I promise you, I'll know exactly what's going on.
A nice welcome home gift from Jeff Smith, the legendary Jeff Smith.
You know, he said, you know, I've got a song for you.
You should check it out at some of my, uh, my, uh, dot Mac, I disk.
So you're going to do his public folder.
And, you know, so I pulled the song out.
And they're like, wow, you know, there's a whole bunch of stuff here for other podcasters.
And just so you know, when I commissioned Jeff to do something,
I, you know, Pod Show Paism, I do plan to do that work.
Like the evil Pod Show song and stuff like that.
And Jeff is so unbelievable.
He, in real life, he, uh, he does a lot of gigs.
He's a, he's a real working musician, plays a crazy piano bar.
So that's how it's so easy for him to just shake all this stuff out.
You know, and it sounds so catchy and hokey and it's great.
But it really does seem like he's getting his act together.
He's got some ringtone sales going on.
It looks like he's producing stuff for other podcasts.
I think he even did something for for gig brief TV.
So, you know, maybe part of the dream is becoming reality for this guy, you know.
Anyway, it's song about it.
Except I got my dream.
I'm gonna quit my day job too, just like you.
Okay, okay.
I got a punch at clock.
I got to pay my dues.
Oh, yes, it's true.
I'm gonna quit my day job too, just like you.
I was made for more than just being someone's too.
I can make my own show.
Hey, I'm gonna quit my day job too, just like you.
I'm gonna make it in my little room.
You're gonna all download it soon.
Yes, it's true.
I'm gonna quit my day job too, just like you.
Oh, yes, I'm gonna quit my day job.
Oh, yes, I'm gonna quit my day job too, just like you.
I'm now my bandwidth is not enough.
My server blew out in above.
My RSS feed might be lost forever.
How did ever come to this rate?
Did we get so big?
Suscriptions go in through the roof.
And overnight without a clue.
Looks like our dreams are comming.
Oh, yes, I'm gonna quit my day job too, just like you.
I'm gonna quit my day job too, just like you.
Okay, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on
hold on, hold on, be honest, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold onto, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold back on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on over, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on open, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on
We have friend, not a foe.
We are everything.
Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net
and discover what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
Warning, consumption of this program,
make me foot down the headbag,
you know, control the latch
for business or hanging over onions
into the pouring the two audience.
I never saw anything.
Internet is for before.
And work daily one in the museum and in the editing.
Oh, my favorite part.
It makes sense.
I get it.
Nowadays,
it's already a free item.
I'll give you an end to shoot.
It's a good job.
Today is a great week, man.
That's my official job here.
Proxpress and mail driver
Painters, we need to be done need not.
They need mail service.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my word.
That was nice.
Let me freaking tell ya.
If you can't stay with the heat.
Stay on the net.
Oh, that's nice.
You trust.
Proxpress.
There you are.
Thank you.
Buddy, open the door.
Open the door.
That chair.
Hello.
Hey.
Okay.
My name is 14th of this podcast brought to you by Acveut.
Check out heather and janella.ow.hicive.com.
This is great.
It's talking about my space and the I have to reiterate one more time.
Parents, if you Werew about what's going on in my space land and what your kids do in there, open in account.
kids do in there, open an account, you know, find out what your kids' profile is on my
space and keep tabs on them.
It's completely honest and legal and open.
You can do that and lay them up the place if you don't like it.
You know, post lots of really lame pictures and bulletins on on your kids' my space
like time to come to dinner, you know, it'll really work.
Trust me on that.
But it doesn't seem a lot of people trust me because myspace.com has now hired the very
first.
This is great.
Chief Security Officer from the New York Times, and I love the way the New York Times
of Maria Newman wrote this.
Here's how the New York Times tells you what myspace is.
Myspace.com, the social network and internet site popular with young people that has
alarmed some parents and law enforcement officials concerned about sexual predators, announced
yesterday.
It was hiring a former federal prosecutor to be its first security chief officer.
Yahoo, now the guy's name is great.
He man's shoe, knee gum.
He man's shoe is here to protect your children.
Dudes, dudes, dudes, dudes.
So, they're so doing that to cover Fox's ass, you know, and it's all about the stock price.
Believe me, this entire acquisition of my space by Fox, and it helped look at their share
price.
That's what it was done for, and it was funny because I was listening to the Guardian
on one of the Guardian newspaper podcasts here, and they were talking about that the whole
plan behind the Myspace acquisition was to connect that audience with the Sun newspaper,
which of course is a Murdoch property here in the UK, because the Sun's circulation
is dropped significantly, and apparently that's the flagship publication is really important.
So, who knows?
I think it's still all just about stock price.
I hope that don't mess it up though, because Myspace is definitely cool.
And I love just looking at how excited Christina gets now that she's understanding how to
paced in codes.
I mean, that's the beauty of this thing.
It's so, so feature poor, really, that, but they've let all these little pieces open,
that, you know, you can create different backgrounds and put other modules and stuff onto it.
Lots of good ideas there.
Of course, we've taken some of those thoughts and put them into Pod Show Plus, which, well,
it's coming very soon.
Very, very soon.
I love to launch it along with Shadow Falls and our bone game show and stuff.
We'll be cool if we could kind of bring that all together at the same time.
Anyway, he managed you now looking after the safety of your children on Myspace.
Hey Adam, this is Steve Runner from the podcast, Fidipidations at SteveRunner.com.
Fidipidations is a tough name to pronounce, but it's to show about running any title pays
homage to the first marathoner of ancient Greece fame, Fidipidies, a messenger that
legends says ran all the way from the plains of Marathon to proclaim Athens victory over
the Spartans.
Upon entering the city, Fidipidies was said to have shouted, rejoice, we conquer him and he died
of a heart attack.
This year, I'll be podcasting as I run the 110th Boston marathon on Patriots Day, April
17th from the plains of Hopkins in Massachusetts to downtown Boston.
I've been training for this thing since December and I feel pretty confident that I'm
going to win it this year.
Well, okay, I might not win it.
But I'm fairly certain that I will drop dead about heart attack when I finish.
One thing that I'm absolutely certain of is that I'll win the England podcaster's division
of the race.
This is the first time that anyone will be actually podcasting as they run the Boston
marathon and I promise that it won't be boring.
See, I'm just an average guy, a 44 year old, slightly as manic, middle of the pack, runner
who offers a non-elete perspective on running.
So you never know what's going to happen.
I'll even be wearing a computer chip that will email listeners in real time as I'm running
of course.
So everybody can be there with me through the internet as I, runner number 23116, runs the
26.2 miles to Boston.
If you've ever thought about running a marathon and figured it would be impossible, check
out my weekly show, Fit Dependations at SteveRunter.com, thoughts, opinions, observations, and
rambling dietrads about running, composed during distance long runs.
In an April as I run the Boston marathon, thanks Adam, and it's we runners like to say
run long and taper.
Steve, you're an animal dude and I don't know how you're going to do it, running the
Boston marathon is one thing, but then talking and doing a podcast at the same time, dude,
I want to sponsor you.
I don't know if you can, if it's a sponsorable event, I presume it is, I'd love for you
to be wearing a pod show T-shirt.
Just let me know, shoot me an email.
I'd love to sponsor this.
This is a great idea.
And I'm not going to go to this whole thing is with the chip you're wearing that emails
people in real time, but I want in, man, that's great.
I really do.
And I've listened to this Steve runner podcast and it's unbelievable how you can, you know,
keep up that, that physique of running and talking and, hey, so doing that on the marathon
will be great.
Please, let me know if we can sponsor, I want in.
Oh, this is nice.
This is a podcast Patricia's going to get really turned on by when I, when I, when I
subscriber to it, I'll watch you a plus.
Hi, Adam.
Luke Stanley here, longtime listener of the Charlie.
That is me playing Chalo in the background.
I really liked your comment a few weeks ago about being a tour, rather than a
talker.
So, I was thinking, classical music avoids so many copyright issues and so it is great
for podcasting.
So, I made a video podcast of me playing the Chalo live.
The feedback has been great and I'm absolutely amazed by having a chance to communicate
with an audience.
Podcasting is amazing in that way.
Please visit my video podcast called Chalo Journey that's C-E-L-O-O-O-D.
You can listen and see what Chalo playing is all about.
Thanks, Adam.
You know, I got to say, um, Chalo playing is hot, man.
It really is.
It's hot.
I mean, not when guys do it, but when women play the Chalo, oh, God, that's so, that's so
sexual.
If you know what I mean.
Angie B. Do you play the Chalo by any chance?
I once met Paula's on back in the MTV days when she was still cool, before she, I don't
like, you know, she's, she's gotten to Mary Hart like kind of, I don't know what it is.
Got an uncool in my book and I'm going to talk, right?
Being the uncool is bastard of the blogs.
But when she was still cool, I met her and she told me she plays Chalo and then she sent
me an autograph picture of her playing Chalo.
You know, black dress.
Hey, the French, gosh, man, you know, you go on vacation and then the French protests
actually worked in that something.
And yesterday, Tuesday, there was another protest.
So they got the labor law dropped or cut from the new law package.
And this was about employers being able to fire new hires at whim within two years, like
a two year trial period, excuse me, since sale again, which, of course, you know my
opinion on that.
So it got dropped, got cut from the package and then they celebrated with another protest
on Tuesday and said, hey, we got a couple more things that were pissed off about.
It's not, man.
I read a great, it was in the financial times, I think, I read over the holiday about
the French.
And this was a very anti French article, I bet I think it was.
And the article said, well, you know, it's here's how it works in France.
On Monday, just about everything's closed anyway, they have a 35 hour work week in France,
35 or 36 hour work week.
So Monday, just about everything's closed Tuesday, Wednesdays, all the kids are, you know,
have half a day at school, so everything is, you know, so do a lot of offices apparently.
And on Friday, it's, you know, Friday is weekend, man.
That's not for work.
And so that leaves Tuesdays and Thursdays and getting anything done.
And guess which days, all the protests are held on.
Yep, Tuesday.
So it really leaves Thursday with the last day to work.
Man, man, man, I don't know if you've been to Paris recently, but Patricia came back
and she said, man, it's dirty and it's skunky and people are, don't look very happy.
And so, uh, and of course, there's no real homecoming without our friend from the UK.
Yeah, I just wanted to explain, that the, the, actually on your lawn was a genuine mistake.
I had the little accident with a candle on Thursday, but the manage to stop things spreading
towards the house.
There's no need to worry while you're on your holiday, so it'll probably grow
you know, you're just lucky I was there really.
Anyway, I just wanted to just send you a little message
so that you know that I'm thinking of you
and also I'm keeping a safe eye on the house.
I'm just picturing you in Portugal
and you look at the speed,
those eating a chocache,
while you galloping on your little donkey
along the beach and slow motion.
You must look like a modern day Jesus
on that down K,
whereas Jesus turned water into wine
you can turn shit into petrol,
which probably has more commercial value
in today's society.
Anyway, enough about that.
I actually wanted to warn you,
that I've just looked at Portugal on the internet
and you might be in danger
of a very nasty jellyfish called
the Portuguese Man of War.
I'll attach a picture of it with this email
so you know not to poke it with the stick
if you see the little fella.
Just cross the road.
Now, you can try one of two things
if you get stern.
The first is to pee on yourself
because the chemicals help neutralize the poison
and the second is to call the doctor.
So, take a take there.
Sure, they can say not mine.
Maybe you can get your little donkey
to pee on your swallowing.
I don't know.
Actually, when I was really young,
I went to a seaside
and don't keep pee on me.
I thought it was a little cow
that needed milking.
Ursula can child food story
as mine.
Personally, I prefer to get stern by jellyfish
and have the horrible stinging sensation in my eyes again.
But one thing I do know
that thing is good for is putting our fires on someone's lawn.
Just because we don't get birds.
Anyway, how do you get back safely?
Yes, I'm missing hearing your lovely warm voice.
So, bye for now.
Roger, thank you so much
and of course, I heard this before the show today.
So, I went out and I walked around the house
to see if I could find the dark patch
and I think I found what you're talking about, Roger.
Now, we had about half a foot of snow here
while we were gone.
So, I probably got rid of any dark patches,
but there's a couple dark patches in dude.
Don't do that.
Thank you for watching the house, Roger.
Really appreciate it.
Oh, yes, good to be back.
Also, notice by the way,
Roger has completed a Google bomb
for Mark Fondalinda.
That's the editor of that rag that stole my pictures flicker.
Go ahead, type it in Google Mark Fondalinda.
You might have a laugh.
It's Future Street.
From the pot saved music never.
It's not long to be.
We're all sweet.
Never need to worry.
We're everything.
It's not defined by what we see.
There are almost things.
It's never meant to worry.
Never meant to be.
Don't mean to be.
We're bound to be late.
And I'd rather be.
Totally committed to the dream.
And I'll tell you.
Till it's right.
The way where it's going to be.
Don't let me go.
Some head touches the way they speak.
And I'll tell you just what you love is in my mind.
Baby me.
Down on future street.
And baby by then I'll know.
About the plans for you and me.
Oh, baby me.
Down on future street.
And baby by then I'll know.
About the plans for you and me.
Yeah, I'll those things.
I want some days.
Hey, now.
Strolling Brooklyn from the name of the team.
And all the rest.
Show me the way.
But it's me.
Because I've been down this way before.
Don't ask me.
Because I think it's just the way it makes me.
And I know when I'm still loving him.
Oh, baby me.
Down on future street.
And baby by then I'll know.
About the plans for you and me.
Oh, baby me.
Down on future street.
And baby by then I'll know.
About the plans for you and me.
Oh, baby me.
Down on future street.
Don't ask me.
Because I think it's just the way it makes me.
And I know when I'm still loving him.
Oh, baby me.
Down on future street.
And baby by then I'll know.
About the plans for you and me.
Oh, baby me.
Down on future street.
And baby by then I'll know.
About the plans for you and me.
Oh, baby me.
Down on future street.
And baby by then I'll know.
About the plans for you and me.
Oh, baby me.
Down on future street.
And baby by then I'll know.
You know, when you listen to song like this from the pod say music network,
think yourself.
Man, how poor is American idol?
You know, how lame is the talent there that is being
loaded and applauded.
It's just not to be compared.
That's Martha Redbone, New York based American Indian singer.
On the pod say music network future street.
You can find that a music dot pod showed our comment.
Of course, I'll put a link in the show notes.
You can find it.
Hey, that's it for today.
Going to close down.
Got lots of stuff to do.
San Francisco wakes up in a couple hours.
So as I said, I still got a dive head first and everything.
Find out where are what we're at.
What we're doing.
And of course.
I'll tell you all about it once I know.
So I don't know what's going to be happening this week.
Good Friday, of course, on the way.
So we may.
I don't know.
I guess, you know, folks at pod show, man.
They don't like to go home for anything.
So I don't know if they're working on a Friday.
But lots of lots of good stuff coming up in the next couple of weeks.
Going to be here at the cottage.
Plan is to have Patricia on the podcast a couple more times.
And hello, dear.
Can you tell how many I'm going on the taxi here?
Oh, you're going to go into town.
You look pretty.
Give me kiss.
On the podcast.
Yeah.
Did you like the occasion?
You coming to the microphone?
Oh, the taxi's waiting for you.
Okay.
So you had fun?
Yes.
Portuguese scam people at the internet though.
Yeah.
It was pretty expensive, wasn't it?
Okay, baby.
Caps waiting.
I love you.
What time are you home?
630.
Okay.
Bye.
And I'll be back here tomorrow.
Adam at curry.com.
Start filling up the Gmail again.
Happy to hear from you.
And of course.
For the latest episodes and the podcast feed.
Go to dailysourceco.com.
And I'll see all you guys tomorrow.
Another pod show pod guest.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this pod guest.
And more great ones like it.
On the high performance pod cast.
Delivery network.
From pod show.
And line line.
On the high performance pod cast.
Delivery network.
From pod show.
And line line networks.
I love it.