Delta Chericharly 315
Delta Chericharly, saints of Seedini
Hey!
Sunday!
Friday!
La la la la!
And then comes it's Saturday!
Saturday!
La la la la!
It's Sunday!
Sunday!
La la la la!
And then it's Monday!
Me!
I've never sleep anymore.
And I can't be with you anymore.
And I can see in the darkness.
Since you left me in the dark.
I replicines from our intention.
But on the streets I'm not here yet.
And I've got a torn screen on the brakes.
It's rising right above the end.
I've never been the same again.
Not since I had the operation.
The surgeons ripped down my heart.
But they left me with a brain.
Yeah, but they left me with a brain.
So I watch movies in the darkness.
They will recognize me.
But they're all sub-titling.
They're all sub-titling.
But I don't speak Chinese.
So I'll just never understand.
Why you don't have any more?
And why your boyfriend wants to kill me?
Can't I watch this film?
For in the morning.
For when I have to kill her.
So I can't earn me a living.
So I can have a place to see.
Or not depending.
I'm always playing at the multiplex.
And what is playing at the movies?
I need a Chinese phrase book.
Free-caxant and Chinese phrase book.
Good morning, everybody.
Or good afternoon.
Good evening.
This is the Daily Source Code.
Sorry, microphone movement there.
It's a Friday.
And I saw that band perform last night.
Free-caxant.
Uh-huh.
And around midnight, they showed up on the podcast music network.
How beautiful is that?
I don't know.
Yeah.
Remove the blackberry.
So are you just starting here?
Yeah.
Yesterday we had a little celebration at the pod show offices here in San Francisco.
It was in honor of my partner, Ron Bloom's birthday.
I won't disclose his actual age.
Well, let's just say he's old enough to receive the PlayStation portable from me.
So he's at that ripe old age.
And part of the celebrations was having a band perform.
And the band that was chosen.
I'm not quite sure who the committee was.
But I was real happy.
This is actually the band that big mic from extra super-action show just joined.
He's on drugs, man.
Mic is great on drums.
He kind of reminded the way he drums, although not necessarily in this song.
Reminds me a bit of the way I just watching him actually.
Reminds me a bit of the way that Mick Fleet would place the drums.
And it was great.
And what was amazing is that even though this song wasn't on the pod safe music network,
I'm pretty sure the big mic played it on the extra super-action show within the past couple of weeks.
And I'm sitting down.
I'm sitting at the band and all of a sudden the song comes down like, I know this song.
And once again, it was just, you know, it hit me.
So hard that, you know, the concept that you need mainstream music to be, you know,
to create a show that people will enjoy is just not true.
It's just about the recognition.
Once you've heard it, you know, and if it hits your DNA the right way, you're going to love it.
You're going to recognize it and you're going to want to hear more of it,
and you're probably going to want to buy something I would hope.
And that is a piece of news from yesterday that really I'm really excited about.
The very first, of course, is not publicly available yet, but the very first transaction of a track
from the pod safe music network purchased all the way through with a credit card
with a free and clear MP3 download was executed yesterday by Chris Rockwell.
I think he and Michael Butler are doing the testing now.
And so it works.
So now it's just, you know, a matter of getting all the nuts and bolts and pieces together.
And of course, we have to come up with the right, you know, well, with the right offering.
And this is going to be really, really interesting for the pricing of songs
of the pod safe music network.
And obviously, this is something that we're discussing with artists,
we're discussing with just people who love music.
And also looking at the industry, the word on the street without a doubt,
is that Apple is being squeezed very, very, very tightly by the record industry
because they want flexible pricing.
And their whole thing is, hey, look, if a song is really popular,
we should be able to charge more for it.
That's fine.
But it's definitely going to break the 99 cent model.
And I don't think Apple is going to be able to hold out.
I think in the in Japan, it's already happened.
And it will more than likely happen in the rest of the world.
So that'll be pretty fun to see, you know, if you can, what people are going to do.
Here's something on the radio and then maybe buy the track on iTunes,
or which could be a buck 99, or here's something on a podcast
and be able to purchase that much, much cheaper.
And of course, artists will always have the option I presume
to cut the price down to zero if they just want to give it away,
very much like iTunes does now.
Anyway, my head is just buzzing.
So it was a long day yesterday.
I'm sorry I didn't have a chance to bring you a show.
And that was just a million different factors,
including the fact that I started the morning off with a daily download
I've rekindled the show for Chris Rockwell.
I'm not going to play you any pieces from it,
because I'm not particularly proud of what I did,
but I did take one for the team to make sure.
I took one for the team to make sure that we could actually have
the continuation of that fabulous podcast.
Another podcast I, oh shoot, I didn't queue up a piece for you.
Let me see, maybe I can get one of their promos, one of their snippets.
Found out that there's two other guys who are doing podcasts
who work at the Pod Show HQ.
Hold on, I think it's stuck on the bridge.com.
This is Brian and Matt who drive in,
who cross the Bay Bridge every day to come into work.
They decided to do a podcast together.
Let me see.
And so they basically do a stereo podcast in the car
while they're stuck on the bridge.
Okay, they got a couple of clips up here
on stuck on the bridge.com.
Let's check this one out for a second.
You farted!
Damn it, man!
Trying to tell us what to do.
Shit!
Son of a bitch!
Damn that's bad!
Woo!
Smells like baby food and fraud!
I can't tell you how much better I feel right now.
It's kind of clean in myself out here, apparently.
Woo!
Let it all go!
Wow!
Okay, glad you guys are doing that in your vehicle
and not in the office if you know what I'm saying.
Plenty of comments about the new Apple announcements
and the hardware and the software that Apple has come out with
and Michael Black was kind enough to email me and say that
there's a very little reason you should be bummed out about the Mac world
announcements.
Your eye Mac and power book are no less cool
because the new machines are faster.
That kind of mentality is probably cost you a lot of money.
And as one big-haired fag to another,
I totally understand.
So quick math reveals that the top MacBook is approximately
the same speed as my dual two gigahertz power Mac.
And the new 20-inch eye Mac is probably even a wee bit faster.
Didn't you find the, oh, this is a good one.
Did you find the inclusion of an FM receiver
in the wired remote for the new iPods a little insulting
or at least pointless?
Well, Michael, let me tell you.
It's very logical when you think about it.
Now Apple made a decision early on with their fair play DRM
that they were going to work with Hollywood
and big, big, big props to Apple for really being able to create
the iPod, which of course without a doubt is the device that
most people aspire to have even though there's plenty of people
buying other MP3 players.
And of course there was the connection with the iTunes music store.
So it really made a lot of sense and it really kickstarted the mobile audio
revolution without a doubt, certainly from the music side.
And so I told you about the squeeze that's coming in
from the record companies.
So it's very obvious that the, and just go look at iTunes.
Look at the podcasting section iTunes and you'll see that there's probably
80 to 85% is all mainstream media content that is being
repurposed as a podcast.
So these are, you know, the relationships that Apple has.
It's okay, you know, that's what they, so they talk to the mainstream media
both on the music side as well as on the broadcast side.
And so it makes sense that the radio partners were saying,
hey, why don't you put a radio into that iPod?
You know, and what what penalty is there to Apple?
No, and I think, you know, every other MP3 player on the planet
almost has an FM radio built in.
Most cell phones have FM radios built in.
So there's no penalty to them.
I don't find it insulting at all.
I won't use it.
I have a, I have an FM receiver on my eye river,
which I think I've used once just to see how well it worked.
And, you know, that was about it.
So I don't feel insulted at all.
I'm just very happy that we're able to route around
the pre-existing relationships and do our own that thing,
if you know what I'm saying.
So instead of building an FM receiver into some device,
well, we do stuff like this.
This is Lori.
And this is Joe.
He's a guy.
She's a girl.
And we're on the pod show.
We are two novice wine drinkers who have been podcasting on location
from wineries in Northern California reviewing the wineries
and their wines.
A guy, a girl at a bottle podcast,
or thrilled to join the pod show family
and have taken the first steps down the path
to eventually quitting our day jobs.
Be sure to look for a guy, a girl
and a bottle on the pod show network at podshow.com.
So Adam, now that it's official,
when are you in the pod show folks going to join us
for wine tasting to celebrate?
Lori, pass the wine.
No, it's mine.
No, you had too much.
No, no.
It is mine.
All right.
Joe and Lori, a guy growing a bottle.
Congratulations guys.
And welcome to the family.
Very happy to have you on board.
As I've mentioned on this show a couple of times
in the next few weeks,
we're bringing in a whole bunch of new podcasts
into the network.
These are predominantly people
that I meant at the pod cast,
or the portable media expo
that are known as the podcast expo.
And they're also going to be using our new system,
the new system, which in time,
and we're moving pretty fast,
will become available to anyone
who wants to create a podcast
and let me reiterate anyone.
Okay, for free.
And what that for free means is you come into the network,
you get all the network services.
And that guy goes beyond hosting
and bandwidth,
which of course is not to be underestimated,
because bandwidth is not free.
It may seem free.
We'll give you tools.
Oh man,
cast blasters.
Now,
I believe it's,
it's now completely connected
with the latest version of cast blaster,
where you record your podcast,
and then you just hit a button,
and it uploads everything automatically
up to the,
to the pod show podcast delivery network.
It makes your entry on your show site.
It just does the whole thing for you.
One click and you're done.
To,
you know,
I can't wait to the sum of the stuff to come out.
That should be ready about the same time
that we're ready to open up to anyone
who wants to come in in podcast.
And guys,
absolutely.
I'd love to polish off a bottle.
Hey, I'm in San Francisco
until next Saturday,
so come on by the office.
We should start around noon.
Let's see.
I picked up another piece of audio from,
is this the head of green,
you know,
I keep listening,
this head of green podcast.
And I really,
you know,
I've been listening to it.
It's the business week podcast.
Now,
she's had,
I think,
yeah,
I've been on the show,
runs been on the show,
but also CEO from,
no way,
that was different show.
What I hear recently,
the guy was responsible for podcast at CBS.
Just all kinds of movers and shakers
that she,
that she gets in this podcast.
And I really enjoy listening to it.
And on the,
I'd miss this one on the December 21,
she did an interview with,
a pair of very successful podcast.
There's the mommy casters,
who are,
well,
mommy casters,
of course,
can never quit their day job,
because,
well,
you know,
the job of a mom,
just is not equitable,
but they are doing extremely well.
They got a great sponsorship from,
Dixie,
paper,
products.
And of course,
they're a member of the pod show network.
And I just want to play a little bit,
of this interview,
which I hadn't heard yet.
It's a pretty interesting where Heather talks a little bit about,
about the network itself,
and the mommy casters,
actually get into the pod safe music network.
So, let me play a little bit of this,
because usually it's meat pontificating about this shit.
And I'll hear it from someone else.
I talked to Ron Bloom from pod show last week,
and,
you know, it was really interesting.
I got a wide variety of reactions about him and pod show,
and some people still don't quite understand,
you know,
what pod show is about.
So, I was wondering,
can you,
you know, you guys work closely with them?
Can you describe,
you know,
what their, what your take on what they're doing?
Well,
I think that they are really,
truly developing the concept.
I mean,
they're definitely at the forefront,
you know,
the pioneer.
They're pioneers,
you know,
and I think they're really,
trading new territory.
No, wait a minute.
This is the two,
your own horn segment,
boiling.
I think there will be copycat groups
that try to go and do the same thing with different.
The pod show has gathered together shows
that are a vastly different group.
And I think that in the future,
they'll probably be more,
little groups like pod show,
but they'll have a family friendly,
you know.
Right.
But we're a Christian network.
For, you know,
gay and lesbian network, you know,
that kind of thing.
Right.
In reality,
I mean, I think what are the major things
that pod show is doing right now,
aside from putting together this network,
they're actually out there educating.
They're educating all the advertisers.
They're educating all of the advertisers
and corporations,
and stuff about what pod casting is
and about how powerful this medium can be,
and actually is.
And I think that,
there's,
there's a huge learning curve that's going on right now,
and pod show is that the very forefront is that.
There are also the big reason why pod casting
is becoming so well known,
because they're out there in the right venues,
talking about it,
and getting the necessary media attention
that it means in order for it to grow.
The other thing I love about pod show
is that they developed their own music network
that is groups of unsigned musicians
that are able to get their music out there
through pod casting now.
So that's the pod say.
Yeah.
Right.
And that's actually kind of a,
kind of a secondary revolution going on,
which, first pod casting is being very revolutionary
and challenging, you know,
conventional media.
But now you've got this pod say,
music network,
which is challenging the record industry.
Yeah, exactly.
And I love it.
And now we're having small music labels
sign up all of their artists
on to the pod say,
music network.
Oh, I'll make it even better.
There's actually,
I believe some big major labels
who are now silently releasing
some of their material onto the pod
safe music network.
You'd have to go investigate for yourself,
see if you can find it in there.
I've only heard it haven't,
haven't actually found it myself.
We're not challenging the record industry though.
We're rooting around it.
That's exactly what we're doing.
We're just recreating a whole new infrastructure
outside of the traditional way of doing things.
It is, you know,
I got an email from SLOW.
Of course,
responsible for the writing or the co-writing.
Excuse me,
co-writing and production of the pod say
for peace of everyday were Christmas.
Within,
I guess it was done.
What is it?
The first week of December is when
that song was completed after a very short
production and turnaround time
with help from all these fantastic pod
safe music artists.
Got it up and running.
Obviously in time for Christmas,
but it was very, you know, a very timely piece of music.
So it only had a lifespan for this year.
And it'll come back every year,
at least it will on my show.
You know, a very short lifespan
because after Christmas,
you know, you're just not going to play
many Christmas tunes.
Over 300 pod cast played that song,
Worldwide.
That's astounding.
It's absolutely phenomenal.
And, of course, sales
are all go to UNICEF.
And I believe SLOW was working on the tally of the sales.
You know, any track that was sold,
even if it was just one is,
is of course, fantastic.
And we raised awareness.
And we also had a good time while doing all this.
So,
was anything else I was going to say about the pod
safe music?
Oh, yeah.
Yesterday,
I talked to my buddy Steve Leeds at Sirius.
And you may be listening to this on your brand new
serious radio receiver.
You got for Christmas.
And there's some ideas about what we can do
with pod safe music and serious satellite.
And in February,
I'll be in New York,
and I'm going to meet with the head hunchos there
and see if we can get something going.
So, yeah.
Hmm.
Ah, Friday.
Let's see.
Tomorrow's going to be just a chillout day here.
Actually, I'm going to do some cleaning
because it's, again,
I've only been here for a short week
and it's amazing what a mess one guy can make.
And that's the bummer about the, about this whole situation.
You know, I've got,
I've really got it all set up perfectly.
You know,
I've been married for 20 years and all of a sudden,
my wife says,
Hey, you know, once you go,
go build your own little oil rig there
and you can have your bachelor pad
and you can work real hard
and then come back after a couple of weeks
and then play real hard with us
with her,
and of course with our daughter Christina.
So, that's a,
that's just a beautiful thing,
a beautiful position to be in.
Of course,
the downside is,
I have this great bachelor pad
and I can't have any girlfriends
to cook and clean for me.
Hey, Adam, one will let you know
that no,
you do not need a dot mac account
for you to the eyewab or for the garage band.
I finally gave up on the PC laptop.
It failed several times
and ended up missing a couple of shows.
So, I've moved everything over to the mac.
I'm on a power book,
just like yours,
outdated a couple of months after it bought it.
Yeah, I did it all in Garage Band last night
and pretty slick, not bad.
He worked in the same interface all the way across
and let's you do a lot of things
that are specific to podcasting
and they didn't include quite a few loops
so you can have some fun with it.
Check it out, number 28
at www.buckidrivetime.com
the most recent episode
if you want to hear one
that was put out with a grudman.
Hi, buddy.
Tom, thank you very much.
We'll definitely check it out.
Talk to Drew last night, Don Andrew.
I hadn't spoken to them in a while
just gave them a call
and they're still producing on Garage Band
and Drew's very excited about
giving this podcast studio a try.
Although we did get them some equipment
because they're still basically working
on their original setup,
which is the USB microphone
and Garage Band
and have not changed anything.
So wait until they get some equipment
that they can play around
with and do some other things.
Quite honestly,
I definitely want to try it out.
I will of course buy
I-Life 2006 or I-Life06,
whatever it is.
But just looking at the demo
that Steve Jobs did,
I don't know.
I think that I'm just not a big fan
of having to look at tracks
while you're recording.
I'm-I have a plan actually
that's kind of stuffed away
in my head.
I want to create a piece of hardware.
And of course,
you know, my father-in-law
not only is a very talented musician
but he can build anything
that he sets his mind to.
He built the whole podcast complex
at the cottage.
My entire studio set up.
But he's also really good
at putting together mixers.
And I have an idea for this,
you know,
the perfect podcast
mixing console
that will work in conjunction
with software.
Or it could work
completely independent of software.
And next time I visit,
I think I'm just going to sit down
where then we're going to
spec it out.
And I know in him,
he'll put it together.
And then if we have something
to put it into production,
that's usually the way these things are built.
Because it really is not one mixer
or one piece of external gear
that really covers the entire gamut
of what I think you'd need,
or at least what I want
in order to create a podcast.
Hey, those of you checking us out
on serious stars 103.
My satellite window is a closing.
We're going to continue here
on the podcast.
If you want to continue to listen,
we actually have a
Trinity segment coming up
in just a couple of minutes.
You'll have to go to dailysourceco.com
and, well,
gee, download the podcast.
But no worries,
just stay right where you are
because Pacific Coast
hellways up next,
followed by yeast radio
with Madge Weinstein
and Dawn Andrew
and all the rest
of the Friday festivities
here on Syria.
So I'll see you guys
on Monday,
have yourself a great weekend
and enjoy
riding the hellway.
And for those of you
hanging out here,
let's see.
As I said,
Trinity coming up.
And that is one of
my projects
that I'm working here
on here.
Actually, so I was able to tell
big mic yesterday
that I kind of
come up with a deal
with just two.
And the deal is
if I can get Mike to move
his drum kit out of their
garage, so Sue can park
her car.
She'll let me set up
my little biodiesel
refinery.
Mike was not happy
with this.
Hi Adam.
This is Len from the Flying Pilot
podcast.
And I wanted to put
to rest this idea of
small computer-based
flight simulators.
First,
in whatever flavor you have,
X plane,
Microsoft Flight Simulator
or others,
these programs are
great for instrument
practice and instrument
proficiency.
You can practice
procedures for holding
patterns,
missed approaches,
and route navigation,
and your instrument
cross-check
while you're doing vertical
losses, and both
shallow and steep bank
terms.
Sort of a homework study tool.
Since I did most
of my training
well before these
personal computer-based
programs were available,
I pretty much had
to resort to
chair flying.
I don't know if you
ever did this, but
I did it sitting
at home on a toilet
with a toilet
plunger acting as my
control stick,
mentally going through
the next day's lessons.
Now,
about logging time
in the simulator,
the FAA
has addressed this
frequent question
in their advisory
circular AC
61-126 entitled
qualification
and approval
of personal computer-based
aviation training devices.
The circular was
published on May 12, 1997.
It's 11 pages long
with the last
seven pages detailing
the device qualifications
and the PDF is available
on the web.
Basically,
as far as logging
the flight time,
it says
yes,
but
you can log up
to 10 hours
of dual instrument time
with a qualified instructor
if the simulator
meets the criteria
in the circular.
Since all modern
flight simulation programs
meet or exceed
the 1997 software
and display requirements
in the circular,
your focus
should be on the hardware requirements,
which include about
15 different physical
control inputs,
and these
specifically can't be
substituted
with the keyboard or the mouse.
The whole package
must be approved
by the FAA
with your request
submitted a minimum of 60 days
before it scheduled use.
I hope that this
finally clears up
anything having to do
with these
PC-based
simulators.
And of course,
here's my plugin.
You can visit
my website
at flyingpilot.com.
Thanks, Adam,
and keep up
the instrument training
and practice.
Yeah,
thank you very much, Len.
Yeah, I think that
so besides the oil
refined,
the biodiesel refinery,
I really want to
create a beautiful
flight sim
for the condo here
because the time
out here in San Francisco
of course cuts into
any flying time
because I'm
four and a half thousand
miles away
from my aircraft.
And I think that
what I'm going to go with
is definitely
with X plane
and going to hook up
you know,
the 12 required
devices.
Of course,
I'm not going to
submit and try and get
FAA approval.
I don't think that's going to be
worth it.
It'll just give me,
you know,
I don't need to log the
simulator time.
I really just want to
be practicing and practicing
as much as possible.
And there's always
an hour to every single day.
Just want to plan it
so I can spend one hour
a day
at the refinery,
one hour day
in the gym here
at the condo,
which I have yet to do
this week.
And then one hour
on the flight sim.
Now is
that a life
or what?
Isn't that just perfect?
When
I was going to say
something about that
I can't remember.
I'm a little fuzzy.
You know,
I'm still having to
get up really early to do
these shows out here
on the west coast
because I'm so behind
you know,
let's hit it anyway.
And I come on everybody
sing along.
You know the words
by now.
All about that
bio diesel industry.
Trinity.
The quintessential luxury.
Oh.
Trinity.
From the bio diesel industry.
Yep.
Oh.
So yesterday,
I took Trinity
to the gas station,
nearby.
Because she's been shifting a little bit
rough.
Now,
I had a Rolls Royce silver shadow
too
in the early 90s,
which I drove to New York.
In fact, I drove that car
for 90,000 miles
drove to New York City every day.
And it had,
interestingly enough,
it had a GM transmission,
which was kind of funny.
But sometimes it would
display the same type of
shifting behavior
that the Trinity is doing now.
And usually
it would mean it just
would be a bit of transmission fluid.
I'd say this thing is
topped up all fluids
or in place.
So it must be something.
It's probably the,
I think it works
with like some kind of
banding system or
definitely need to
check her into a garage
one of these days to
make sure that that
doesn't get worse.
And maybe a wash.
I'm looking for a
a car detailer.
And then
midweek.
I'm thinking around
Wednesday,
we're going to head off to
the bio diesel,
the Berkeley bio diesel
oasis to do our first
fill up.
And that, of course,
will be a sound seeing
to our
and it got some audio
feedback today.
Hey, Adam,
it's Peter Jarros from
Jesus on the radio.
I'm sending you this note
to explain a very
important point
once and for all.
There is
no such thing
as a bio diesel
engine.
They just
isn't.
Bio diesel is a diesel fuel.
It'll run
in any diesel engine.
The sole difference
between a bio diesel car
and a petro diesel car
is what's in the tank.
Nice.
Here's the deal.
Burning a fuel
made from petroleum oil
works.
But as you know,
the scarcity of oil
means that any
dependence on petroleum
makes the plot of mad
max seem
not so far fetched.
Too bad
into
one man leaves.
Plus,
it's just plain dirty.
So
wouldn't it be
great to burn vegetable oil
instead?
Much cleaner
and you can grow it
in your own backyard.
Now,
a diesel engine can burn
just about anything
combustible.
But there's a problem with
straight vegetable oil
or SBO.
It's too thick.
They can burn
in a diesel engine
but it has to get hot
first.
That means
tricking out your engine
to heat up the oil
and that's in SBO conversion.
That'll work.
But surely
there's a better way.
Well,
of course you know
there is.
Bio diesel.
The trouble with SBO
is that it's full of glycerol.
You know how glycerinous thick?
Well, it's the glycerol
in vegetable oil
that makes it so viscous.
And the viscosity
clogs up a normal diesel engine.
So, what do we do?
We take it out.
See,
Veggie oil is basically
triglycerides,
which are glycerol molecules
each sporting
three fatty acids.
And then make a great name
for a rapper.
Wouldn't it?
Fatty acid.
Yeah, I'd have to be one of those guys
who doesn't really have his own career.
So as always,
rhapsody featuring fatty acids.
Kind of think of it.
Rhapsody is a much better rapper today.
Yeah.
Anyhow, where was I?
Right.
The fatty acids are still stuck to the glycerols.
So,
we do a little boonoo
or, as a scientist,
call it,
transesterification.
Which means,
we throw in some alcohols and lie.
The lie
breaks the triglycerides up,
giving us glycerol
and free fatty acids.
Then, the free fatty acids
bind to the alcohol instead.
The glycerol is a thick,
goopy mess,
but the alcohol fatty acid combo
is a nice thin fuel,
that we know,
as bio diesel.
So, what did I explain all that?
To get across one simple point out of
it takes some work to make SBO into bio diesel.
And the whole point of that process
is to get it to run in an ordinary, unmodified engine,
which is why,
say,
with me now,
there is no such thing as a bio diesel engine.
I don't know what Trinity's previous owner did,
but I assure you,
she does not have a bio diesel conversion.
She is a great car, though.
Take us for another ride sometime.
I'd love to hear a sound saying
door the place where you fill her up.
There's another reason for this note too,
and that's Tom Loyat.
Tom is one of the biggest names
in American bio diesel,
especially on the East Coast.
He also happens to be my girlfriend's father.
For a long time,
he ran his own bio diesel shop
and grabbed size building out back,
until he hit two problems.
First, his fuel was declared
non-street legal until he had come up
with some obscene amount of money
to get it tested,
and then his shop burned down.
And to make things worse,
the government declared it an oil spill,
even though it was just vegetable oil.
Figures.
These days,
he's a bio diesel distributor up here in the Northeast,
but he's also a major bio diesel consultant.
He would love nothing more
than to help people set up their own little refineries.
If you'd like me to put you in touch,
I'd be more than happy to do so.
His website is over at yellowbioidiesill.com.
Hey, by the way,
I should mention that my show
uses on the radio.
He is a music show
that has nothing to do with Jesus.
He can find me,
my co-host Sarah Cat.
It's a great tune to go for it.
Jesus on the radio.com.
Tailwinds my friend.
And free fatty acid.
He didn't shoot nobody.
Bye.
Van, that's fantastic.
Well, okay,
this is going to be a seminal audio comment.
This is something that we're going to bring back once in a while,
because what a fantastic explanation.
Now, I do know, indeed,
that there is no such thing as a biodiesel engine.
The only conversion that took place on Trinity
because she's pre-1985 is the hoses,
because that glisterole content,
or the glisterole content of the biodiesel,
can actually corrode or erode your rubber housing.
And so those have to be replaced
if you have an older model car with older hoses.
And if you lift the hood on Trinity,
and that's actually what I did take a picture of
is, well, you see some nice, new spank and hoses.
And that's just so the biodiesel doesn't rot the hoses away.
And that's really cool.
You know, I know that Ray Lane,
one of our board of directors,
you know, one of the big wheels
at one of our investors,
Clienter Perkins,
eat lissons at the show.
I think,
oh, regularly,
and sometimes I think he listens every single one.
He has sent me some information about biodiesel before,
and I have a feeling that they may have an investment
or they may be considering an investment in some type of biodiesel.
So I'm hoping that there be some way
that we can bring our experiences
and Trinity into their decision-making process.
And maybe we can do something really good
with someone else's money.
You know, that's always a lot of fun.
So yes, as I said next week,
we will be doing that sound seeing tour
or be heading off to the Berkeley biodiesel oasis
to fill her up.
And once I have a spot,
in order to my kit, my official biodiesel refinery.
She could talk.
You didn't have a thing.
I don't forget being in her tent.
We're Trinity.
Trinity.
Yeah.
Yeah, how's it?
And to wind it up for today,
lots of emails from people who are having problems
with iTunes,
retrieving their podcasts.
Two emails and some theories here.
I just want to briefly stop and talk about this.
James Prevay says this issue
with how poorly iTunes downloads large files
has been a problem for me
since I registered my first RSS.
I used iPod 11 for the longest time
and enjoyed the download recovery feature
for some of the larger cast.
Yeah, that's if you like mess it up
and then it doesn't go download the whole show again.
I had a number of Apple scripting issues
between iPod and iTunes,
but they were workable.
When iTunes came out with the RSS feed manager,
I switched wholeheartedly.
When I did that,
I should have sent out a mass apology
to all the podcasts I was subscribed to
because the amount of bandwidth
and other people's money
he says that was wasted during that time
that I was using iTunes for subscriptions
was embarrassing.
I would see DSC attempts to download
up to 10 times a day,
sometimes reaching close to completion
only to start from the beginning of the file
when a lost connection error would appear.
I have to admit that even though I was fully aware
the bandwidth was not free,
I continued to use iTunes for feeds
until the latest version of juice appeared.
I think the ISPs are doing something
with large data transfers,
but I don't think we can blame iTunes for it.
We can, however, blame iTunes for not using
download recovery for such large transfers.
I concur 100%.
Thing will be wise for podshow
or any large file content.
Distributor to get a very good handle
and how much bandwidth is wasted.
Oh, we know.
Believe me.
Until the last bits get to the client,
every bit before has potentially been squandered,
but still paid for it.
Yep.
We're aware of those problems.
We can see it in the log files
because you get these partial downloads
in your access and actually in your error log.
Pete Shannon, I think it is.
I add them the most likely
reason that people are getting broken downloads
within the same network segment.
And this is indeed something that we've detected.
It's probably some of the transparent
caching hardware that's in place on the network.
I did an interview for one company
or based in the UK.
What their hardware does is redirect requests
for files to the cache machine,
which then makes the request to the outside world.
It's the ISP's attempt to reduce external peer-to-peer traffic.
For some of the statistics the company built up,
they determine that 60% of all internet traffic
is peer-to-peer.
As far as I know,
there's no way of bypassing this cache of its in place.
Information about the ISPs will go
a long way towards figuring out if this is the case or not,
but it seems to be the most likely reason.
The problem is that it's the first retrieval of data.
The problem is that if the first retrieval of the data is incorrect,
then everyone is messed up on the near side of the cache.
Ah, yes, of course.
Yeah, that is a problem.
And it's a problem that we're going to have to figure out
network wide.
But really, the only way to do that is
is to complain to your ISP, I guess.
But it's funny because I just,
offhandedly mentioned it,
and it seems that planning people really are having problems
with the automatic download of their podcast.
And I also believe that most of it has to do with their,
with the local ISP issues.
So keeping our eye on it for sure.
What are we at now?
We're at almost 40 minutes.
Let's play one more song.
Something I got off the Podsake Music Network, of course.
And let me just see if I can go to the page
because I've actually, I think I've played them before.
But it was a whole different genre.
So this is a Chrissy.
Yeah, that's right.
Chrissy.
I'm looking at a picture now.
Let's go to the, you know what?
I'm going to go to website.
She looks really cute.
Let me see.
What's your website?
BostonFashionA Music.com.
Is that what's going to?
Oh, page underscore8.html.
Okay.
So I think I played more of like a kind of a rock song
from her last time.
But this one showed up on the homepage of a
PM and this morning while I was scouting for songs.
And it's completely different.
Yet completely enjoyable.
He's the one that I love.
The one that I need.
The one that I love.
He's the one that I love.
The one that I need.
The one that I love.
Come on.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I don't think I have to tell you how pissed I up.
How pissed off I am right now.
This is the same Apple audio problem that is not being acknowledged by the company.
This is why I have a Mac
because it works well in Audio.
I demand at least an acknowledgement and if possible, an explanation.
It'sl,
and why I should buy anything else from Apple
until you do that. That's just, that's the truth, okay? Just tell me that you're looking
into it. Just telling me that would make me happy, okay? Because otherwise I'm gonna keep
bitching about it.
I just can't tell you how I know for you. My everything, me everything, my
inspiration for every song I sing and what no one knows in life.
I'm gonna give it to the world and that's just the way it is.
I'm beautiful was that, huh? Chris Jones as in Chrissy and he is.
He's the one with a little bit of extra effects there. That hell was that.
Stop. Stop. Stop already. One final thing before I go, I just read on my Gmail.
An announcement that Blackberry is now going to be offering the Pocket Mac program for free.
When you buy a new Blackberry, that's the program that allows you to sync up your Blackberry to your iCal
and your address book and everything on your Macintosh, which is very cool.
And I'm trying to set something up here, there we go.
And there was also, they're putting together an agreement with Google.
The first thing they'll be doing is, well actually they've already released the Google local, which if you haven't used that on your new Blackberry yet,
my god man, you get Google maps and the satellite images and you get directions.
I mean, I've actually used this thing for directions when I didn't have the Tom Tom going to the car.
It's great. So a real Blackberry client for synchronizing your Blackberry with Gmail cannot be far off.
It can't be far off. We're supposed to have a meeting with the Google team today, but I don't think I don't think that happened.
So and the Google talk guys are going to be there.
And I think the Gmail people as well. So if that, if it doesn't happen today, it'll happen next week and I'll definitely let you know about it.
All right, everybody. Hey, listen, I had a good time this week.
I believe that we're going to Atlanta Sunday afternoon.
There's a couple companies in Atlanta.
You can just think about that for a second and you'll figure out which ones they might be.
We're meeting them on Monday, which is kind of weird because Monday I think is Martin Luther King day, but and particularly in Atlanta.
They're not taking the day off at these companies.
So I'll talk to you probably Monday night or Tuesday morning, one of the two.
And you have yourself a fantastic weekend.
Happyness and health, my friends. Bye-bye.
Pot show the other white meat.