It's the Daily Source Code, with the multinational, Adam Curry.
Good job, Cindy.
Good waiting, Cass.
Thank you, buddy.
I am from Holland.
Isn't that beer?
Bringing the show to the US.
They said I might want to get a bit of American in me.
I hope you're the first time.
Delta's Yeracharling.
489.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Did the next generation radio content in my ears?
We don't need no sticky and dirty.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic.
It's Adam Curry.
Charlie, what are you doing with daddy's computer?
I don't know.
Danny, Josh, Scott.
Hey, we train hotcasters.
Seriously early in the day.
Hey, it's DSE for a line.
I'm telling you now.
I quit.
The situation where you shit's there in my face.
Ain't gonna go on no more.
I got my hands dirty while you roll on mine.
With one eye on the time.
I've done my hardest diving.
For I can't take that hotify.
You can't roll me around your tongue no more.
Baby, it's time to clear up your emotion.
I say, baby.
You'll never fall and overboard.
Please don't say, baby.
But I'm telling you now.
I quit.
Because loving you is a job I don't need
Ain't gotta gotta work no more
I quit, I quit
The situation's making for me
Ain't gotta gotta work no more
Ain't gotta gotta work
I hate you, I hate you
Too late to say your story
You're just like every other
Love them, a shot brings out in you
You're gonna run and forth
Come back, and I'm so sorry
That I can't be your mother
And I'm telling you now
I quit, I quit
Because loving you is a job I don't need
Ain't gotta gotta work no more
I quit, I quit
The situation's making for me
Ain't gotta gotta Work no more
Ain't gotta gotta work no more
I quit, I quit
Ain't gotta work
Ila Brown, I quit, brand new on the pod save music network, and you probably know her.
A C, she was season five American Idol Finalist, place number 13, and of course perform
for 35 million viewers. She's put all of her CDs tracks up on the pod save music
that were really like this stuff. Apparently she did the CD in just under two weeks,
right after American Idol Contract expired. She also went to the NCAA to play for
Boston College Eagles. I mean, why not? She's also easy on the eyes. Influences,
Celine Dion, Natasha Beningfield, Disney songs, Mariah Carey, and so many more. No idea
if she's single. She's probably Sagittarius. Everybody, oh, thank you Jersey Todd
for pointing that one out to me, man. Always right on dude. Coming to you from the curry
cottage in the affluent suburb of Suri known as Gilford. It's the daily source code episode
for 89 beautiful, beautiful crisp sunny day today where we've definitely just, you know,
November 1st, I played pod save for piece boom. We're into winter all of a sudden. It's cold.
First sub zero temperature. I'll be sending rate, of course. I think we had one or two degrees below
zero last night, some frost on the ground this morning. But it really is that nice.
You know, as long as there's no clouds in this sunshine, it's great for two reasons.
One, it makes you feel really good with that crisp air outside. And two, there's a much less
or almost zero risk of icing when you're flying in sub zero temperature. You don't want clouds
when it's freezing. Or even when it's, I mean, even if it's nine or 10 degrees on the ground up at
altitude, it could be freezing and could get your icing, could make your fly really, really bad.
No, I'm saying, yes, it's Thursday. Amy Mac. Here to save my ass. Amy.
Hey, baby. That's right. It's time to exercise with Amy Mac.
I'm ready. All right. I think you're going to be pleased with today's exercise.
Oh, yeah, I always have Amy, you know that. It requires some stability, but not a great deal of movement like last week.
Hold on, hold on.
Did you feel those kicks the next day? Wait a minute, wait a minute. Hold on, Amy.
Hold on. I got to take off my bathroom. I just want to be prepared, you know, before you get me doing stuff.
Let me open it the out. The second microphone here.
Let me just check the second. Oh, hey, hold on. Why isn't no working? What the hell?
Oh, oh, sorry. Didn't mean to hurt you like that. Yeah. Testing one two.
Yes. Okay. Had to turn on the Phantom Power. Okay. Back to Amy Mac.
That's what I thought. All right. Let's do it.
Okay. Let's get started. Okay. I'm ready.
Stand tall. Stand shoulder with a part.
Feet shoulder with. Now lift your right leg up and straighten it out in front of you.
Okay. Good. Now balance and hold. Okay. I'm balancing and holding. Great.
You probably feel this in your leg. Yeah, my thigh. Yeah. Now take that leg and make eight small circles to the left.
While holding your balance. Okay. One two. Head tall, stomach squeeze, three, two, and eight.
And put it down. Now eight small circles to the right.
I'm sorry.
Please, that's that. Keep it from to be over.
Excellent. Bring that right leg down.
Shake it out. Okay. Shake it out. Good.
And take your left leg up and straighten it out in front of you.
Okay. It doesn't go all the way out in front of you. Really?
Now balance. Okay. I'm balancing.
Breathing and being small circles to the left.
One two. Squeeze everything.
Yeah. Yeah. Woo.
Full circles. Don't just wiggle in play.
Okay. Okay. Okay. I did it. And now circle to the right leg.
Oh, I've heard enough. One two.
Stand up tall. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
You know exactly. I'm sorry.
Bring it. Well, that seemed pointless.
It really works all those stability muscles and pills and endurance for the legs and butt.
As you practice, you'll be able to balance longer and do more circles.
Well, that's it for me. Visit me over at fitness.patchow.com
And until next time.
Okay. Okay. I can turn off the second microphone.
There we go. It's better. Okay. Thanks, Amy.
Did that show launch officially?
I think this now officially on pod show plus the exercise.
So you can all do all 12 episodes of exercise.
Back to it's a 12 step program that we have here.
Also fitness attack, Amy Max regular podcast is now also available on Espanol.
With pod show diva Marta.
Catching my breath here for a second. Let me just check my notes.
Let me see what I got going on today.
Oh, yeah. This was pretty important.
I was aware of this, but I kind of forgotten about it.
The strip podcast. I've played bits from the strip before.
They always get all the mega celebrities in Vegas.
Who do we listen to? Who do we listen to?
Oh, Chubby Chakra. That's right. That was a really good one.
But they've always got some kind of celebrity hanging out of the strip podcast.
And they're running a sweepstakes, which I think is coming to an end pretty soon.
It's a,
Oh, that was an all expenses.
It was a trip to Vietnam on a second. Let me just go to his page for a sec.
Oh, the deadline's been extended. Excellent. Let's see.
Help us pick a new theme song when a prize. Click here.
Is that it?
Somehow I don't think that's the one. Wait a minute.
Here's the Vegas trip sweepstakes deadline.
Okay. Let's see what we got here.
Oh, it's from Southwest Vacations. Excellent.
Okay. Where do they have?
Just like you. We love Las Vegas.
Oops.
And the strip podcast. Take advantage of our vacation deal.
The week and experience it throws those Vegas.
Enter to win a trip to the strip. There you go.
That's what it is. Okay. Go check it out.
At, of course, I'll put a link in the, in the show notes.
Oops. Oh, my words.
It's SteveFrice.com slash podcast.
I'm pretty sure they have the strip.podshow.com.
I'll put a link in the show notes so you can find it easily.
Now, what the heck happened to my notes here?
I've been using that Google notebook.
That's pretty cool.
Because, you know, it can synchronize across any browser.
So you kind of have your notes nearby.
And at your fingertips, regardless of what computer you're on.
So it's definitely very cool.
Ah, remember this?
Remember this is a November jump out.
A trace and a plot.
I've seen a reason why I jumped out of trace and should never be forgot.
So that's the nursery rhyme.
I was hoping you guys would come up with a good rhyme for me.
So then 400 years people still know about the daily source code.
But I think I kind of received a challenge from a lot of the different listeners when we start talking about flying.
And I checked it out with Captain Dan.
And it is actually possible for us to fly at night on bonfire night.
And get some footage of us flying over the fireworks and bonfires.
Or as Chris Rockwell says, who will be doing camera from the back seat.
Go up in a plane and if people shoot fireworks at me, fuck yeah, count me in.
And this is actually, and the reason why I want to do this, besides the fact that it's just cool.
I haven't done any night flying in a while, is I've been thinking about doing a video show called Flying Fools.
And it's since I'm flying anyway.
I meet so many interesting people at airfields, well, certainly all across the UK and different parts of Europe.
But I do hook up with some interesting folks.
I think maybe it would be a cool show to show aviation from a little different side.
And the people that make aviation happen.
It might be kind of specialist, but I think what better way to start off with the first episode is me being the flying full number one.
Attempting to go film fireworks and bonfires from the air in the dark.
And so of course, Captain Dan is working on making that happen.
I think we have to actually pay to have the airport stay open longer or open up, especially for us.
It's going to be interesting.
Actually, I think we're going to pull a bunch of guys who want to do some night flying and they'll all chip in.
Now I got to figure out when and where the bonfires are.
The final member of the fifth, which is Sunday, right?
But then I get this message.
I had him, it's John from Gielford here again, just following up on yesterday's call about bonfire night seeing Gielford.
Just be filling up with text from there by things, please.
And I've just noticed that the sign-up side, the department.
They're only up in the same three, bonfire and fireworks.
That's the night 7 p.m.
So, wrap up.
We'll get to family down there.
And I got all of them.
He's called sign-up down here, we're up on that.
I've looked rough that.
Here's what I'm flying.
Yeah, so I totally want to do that.
But I got to know, is it Saturday night?
You said Saturday night.
Are you sure you were right about Saturday?
What is Sunday then?
Is Guy Fark, I mean, is bonfire night?
Like the night before Christmas?
Is that the night before the fifth?
And someone's going to help me out here.
Come on.
The Brits help the yank out because I want to do this.
But if it's Saturday, I have to know.
And I kind of planned it all for Sunday.
So is it Sunday night or Saturday night?
Please help me.
I love the company.
Hey Adam, it's a, it's a friend in New York City.
David, a polito, that guitar man from Central Park.
Listen, if you careful what you wish for, brother,
I know you've been saying that you'd like I love the company
to become part of the Potio Plus family.
Well, if you go to iltc.potio.com, we hooked up.
And we're bringing you a new show every day Monday through Friday
to show about music, the people that make music.
Once a week, my buddy said Bernstein's coming along.
You know, the guy that brought the Beatles to America.
He really wants to meet you, by the way.
And then, you know, once a week.
Now we're not even quiet.
We do something called the Wednesday wake-up call.
It's all about music's place in politics and social
conscience.
This phone numbers that everybody can call in and kind of mix it up with everybody else.
It's really very cool.
Just tell people to show up.
I love the company.
Good.
Welcome aboard.
David at polito is buddy James and sit Bernstein.
I mean, is that spectacular or what?
I love the company.
ILTC.potio.com.
Great to have you guys on the networking.
I, I so want to hang out with you guys.
And of course there will be a New York trip in the near future.
I was so sick the last time I couldn't go and hang out with him.
But I definitely want to chill with these dudes.
That's a cool, it's cool company.
Our friend David I polito keeps in New York.
Very, very excited about it.
So we've been producing, man, we've been doing so much.
We've been producing shows for our launch.
We've been signing all kinds of new podcasts, pod shows, independent
video producers doing some amazing, just amazing shit.
And I'm really proud about this about an acquisition.
I guess we'd call an acquisition.
We won't own anything.
But we've got none other than Pete Townsend.
And Rachel Fuller, who will be joining pod show with in the attic.
Which is, I've talked about this before.
And of course I've played a piece of audio of Pete and flaming lips doing
Bobo Riley.
Essentially, as the who are on their on their world tour,
they're now in Los Angeles.
Every single gig, either just before or after the show,
it kind of depends on what's going on.
Rachel, who is Pete's girlfriend.
And Pete's son, who does a lot of the production of the show.
They sit down with one or multiple of the bands who opened up for them,
depending on if it's a festival or a straight ahead who gig.
And they have this air stream trailer, which is completely outfitted
as a production studio audio and video.
They interview them.
It's just really like a sit down chill out, have a cup of tea,
play some songs, talk some shit about the good old days.
And we'll be doing an episode a week.
I'm really excited about this.
There's also a contest, a sweepstakes for charity,
that Pete and Rachel have put together with Pete's,
with the last guitar.
He's promised not never to smash another guitar,
though the one he smashed in Tokyo in 2004.
That's been made into a table.
And they'll be, I guess the sweepstakes,
there's promotion that they'll be giving that away for charity.
So details on that coming very soon,
but I just got to play this one little bit of,
I'm looking at the video here,
so you're only gonna hear the audio of,
see it's Rachel Pete and the flaming lips.
And Pete, Pete goes into the story about a time he dropped acid
with Keith Moon on an airplane.
You just kind of listen to a little bit of it, okay?
This is in the attic, in the trailer, Pete Downson, Rachel Fuller,
and flaming lips.
I love to become that.
No, I mean, when I took LSD, I never liked it.
I'd always freaked me out.
I mean, I never could do the blissful, you know,
see things and be happy and all that sort of.
So you want to go into a place where all the lost socks were,
didn't you?
Yeah.
One.
No, I mean, quite seriously, as I remember it,
the big mistake I made was trying to explain this trip that I had
to Ricky Javez, you know, who he is.
David, my friend, Dad, I don't know.
Genius.
He sat there like this, and I took him,
and then I went up and I went in the plane,
and I go, oh, she's turning to a pig,
and I was hearing, you know,
and suddenly, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I was always in that place where all the fountain pens
get lost at a bullet point pens, I'm sticking glasses,
and socks are going at the back of the hand,
right there.
And I was in this weird place,
and I had a voice telling me, go back, go back, go back.
Just looking at me like that, and I said,
anyway, that's really how I began, you know,
my spiritual thing,
because when I got back in my body and, you know,
accepted the fact that I'd actually been out of it.
I wanted, well, where did I go?
And he said, oh, but that doesn't,
that doesn't convince me that doesn't convince me.
That doesn't convince me.
You wait until you see this show.
He goes way into this whole trip,
into this old experience, he had.
But there you have it.
Pete Townsend visiting the place where all the lost socks go,
and where the lost pens turn up.
I love it.
Fantastic.
I'd be kind of avoiding talking about this next topic,
because I've been following along with the Bob Gentry,
who's been participating in this NBC show called
Star Tomorrow.
You can find a start.
Star, no, star tomorrow.
It's start tomorrow.
Star Tomorrow.com.
I'm not quite sure what the, what the prize is.
And I have a feeling it's web only.
I'm not quite sure, however.
I'll have you know that he is through to the final round,
the top five, so it's the final five,
and he'll be, he'll be vying for,
for winning this, this competition,
which, of course, is, you know,
somewhat like an American idol or whatever,
but just to remind you, who Bob Gentry is,
I'm a big fan of the stuff he's doing.
This has been up on the networks since 2005.
It's upside down.
Back in time on the source code, everybody.
I've been talking in my last sleep,
when I'm waking up.
Well, my tongue is tight.
I've been thinking I should leave
instead of waiting for her when the time is right.
I've backed the bags under my eyes.
Well, I've seen enough to know what it's like.
It's turning me upside down.
Tell me what I've done wrong now.
All I can do is try it.
When everything's breaking me down,
looking at me down side out,
well, all rules got changed somehow,
maybe it's suicide,
to stay here and just stick around.
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now,
till now.
I've been walking in my last sleep,
when I'm waking up.
Well, my legs are tight.
I've been thinking I should leave
but though in the world,
it's a matter tonight.
Well, I've been thinking I should leave
but though in the world,
it's a matter tonight.
I've been dreaming I could fly it.
Well, I'm free enough,
but I'm still way down.
It's turning me upside down.
Tell me what I've done wrong now.
All I can do is try it.
When everything's breaking me down,
looking at me down side out,
well, all rules got changed somehow,
maybe it's suicide,
to stay here and just stick around.
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now,
till now.
I've been a friend to just walk out.
You know where to stop me down.
It's turning me upside down.
Tell me what I've done wrong now.
All I can do is try it.
When everything's breaking me down,
looking at me down side out,
well, all rules got changed somehow,
maybe it's suicide.
Well, I'm free enough,
but though in the world,
it's a matter tonight.
Well, all rules got changed somehow,
maybe it's suicide.
To stay here and just stick around.
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now,
till now.
Tell me what I've done wrong now.
All I can do is try it.
When all rules got changed somehow,
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now,
until now.
Oh yeah.
So good to hear that again.
Bob Gentry, upside down,
you could find him at the pod state of music network.
And hopefully the winner of NBC's Star Tomorrow.
I see, I didn't even realize this.
He's just, he put up a new song on October 6.
What does that sound like?
I'm playing this directly from the web,
by the way, from the pod team music network.
Oh, you know, it's going to be another
gentry classic for sure.
Listen to that.
Oh, I got to listen that whole song.
Maybe I'll play it for you on tomorrow's Who Bar Friday.
Okay, let me see.
Oh, you'll love this.
Trucker Tom here. Hey, guess what?
My 81 year old mom is podcasting.
I want you all to join us in RVing and knowing the good,
the ends and the outs, the good and the bad and the ugly.
It was her idea. She wanted to start a podcast.
I just wanted to tell you that we're not young people anymore,
but we still have a taste for adventure.
And thanks to cast blaster and pod show working together,
it was easy to set her up with the podcast.
Happy to share my mom with the world at RViddits.podshow.com.
Be good to yourselves and I'll let you know when we start our adventure.
Bye, bye.
I'm waiting to hear that first show is fantastic.
What's your 81 RViddits.podshow.com?
Fantastic. Thank you so much, Trucker Tom.
And I'm glad that I worked out with cast blaster.
Once you kind of figured out,
it's really simple because all you do is you record the show.
You fill out the information, they show notes and some other data.
They'll help people identify what the show is,
what it's about, even your album art and you click upload.
And that's it. There is no step three, essentially.
I'd love to hear from you guys on the voice mail lines.
Lots of Brits calling in these days.
Even though I'm giving out the US number pretty much exclusively these days.
But in case you forgot.
I had a meal for three days.
I've just been listening to four eight nights.
And your comments regarding the audio quality of the report from Jera and Martin Upper in the city.
And it's what I'm going to say.
I don't know if it's been for somebody else.
That was produced at my first podcast of the quarter.
Next that idea makes a product out of it.
You know, something with bright colors and big buttons.
For the album coming, you just know the tomorrow to record their content on.
So I'd like me chuckle that one.
That's just a photo of that.
And yeah, thank you so much.
Thanks, Neil.
Yeah, I don't know what was up with that.
That was I still got to get to the bottom of that.
What they were using up there in Manchester.
I think Spotlight.podshow.com is where they've uploaded more stuff.
I'll check for you and put a link in the show notes.
Because it definitely was a lot going on.
I'd up in Manchester in the city.
And I'm sure that Jill and GD got GM and GD.
I should say.
They got plenty of new artists on the podcast music network.
And hopefully it turned a lot of artists there on to the whole pod safe music movement
and to pod casting in general, et cetera.
But the idea of my first podcast, or actually Katja, who does Katja's cast,
the Kat's cast.
I should say KAT, C-A-S-C-A-S-T dot podshow.com.
She actually did a design of my first podcast recorder.
She never really finished the technological bit,
and we were kind of halfway through cast blaster.
But now that I think about it, this is very much what cast blaster
might always envision for cast blaster.
Find that at castblaster.com, by the way.
You can use it for free for anything under 10 minutes,
and then there's $50 for a lifetime license.
Five, actually, should you change computers five times in the meantime?
And I think it would be as simple as creating a new skin.
I'm not quite sure how it works, and when it does applications,
but I'm pretty sure there's a lot of people who know how it works.
And I guess if you can create a photo shop file that can be cut into bits
or pieces, it can be done.
But Mike is on vacation currently until,
well, until, remember, remember the fifth of November.
When he gets back, I'll see if I can have a chat with him about it.
And also want to tell you that, you know, we're all very excited about the launch of
BTPodShow.com, which is on the 7th of November.
Remember, remember, the 7th of November.
When we'll be bringing you lots of flavour from Splenda.
But we're also launching the new version of PodShow Plus,
to be found at podShow.com.
And I think we've really nailed it this time.
You know, it's only been, was it four months since our first unleash,
and we've learned quite a bit, and we've figured out,
I think what it really takes to have a social media network,
so we've really divided it up into four pieces.
You're going to love this when it comes out.
Which will be November, I'm sorry, November 9th.
The second week of November, whatever.
Somewhere around there, I don't want to have everyone sitting around waiting.
We've divided it into people, which, of course,
is the Plus part, PodShow Plus music, which, of course,
is the PodSet Music Network.
Shows, which, of course, encompasses all things,
podcasting, anything that's serialized.
And then a new addition, videos, which I think we really got
a cool video system that you'll be able to upload single videos
to that you know, you may not want to actually have a show
within RSS feed, or you may want to take advantage of our online
editing system, which will just fucking knock your socks off.
Imagine that upload some music, which you can get from the PodSet Music
Network, upload some graphics, some pictures.
You could get that somewhere from your gallery at PodShow Plus,
upload pieces of video, and then you can, you know,
put it all in a timeline, and put transitions in, and, and,
and out the back end, poop, say, a full edited video.
It's really fucking amazing.
It's, it's exactly the stuff that I've been begging for.
So I think you'll really, really like it.
Also, a way to monetize that if you don't want to use advertising
based monetization, or just to let people embed that
on other pages, you know, very much the YouTube Google
video concept.
But the nice thing is that you can easily then put it
into a show at PodShow Plus, you know, single click stuff.
We've changed how collections work.
Now you can actually create, um, I'm just going to
ramble on for a second.
What the hell is that outside?
Mail truck.
Uh, you'll be able to create a feed of individual items.
So, you know, already you can say, well, let me just put a feed
together of, of shows.
So I have my new show, and, you know, whenever there's a new episode
of any of the shows that I have in that channel in my
collection, it'll, you know, it'll essentially drop out
into my iPod, or I have it on my Nokia,
and 91 cell phone.
So I'm still liking for the, for the podcast portion of it.
Uh, but now you could also put together a feed very much like
gigadile, as you know, Andrew Grummit created gigadile.
You can see gigadile.net.
Um, so now you can say, well, I'm just going to put together a feed
and that feed will only consist of singular items that I put in
there. So you could even make it private.
So I could set up a feed for Patricia.
And whenever I found a, you know, a great show, not not a,
I'm really an individual episode, or, or a great, um,
a great video that I wanted to see, or even just a picture.
Then I can put it into that feed, and it will automatically update
on, uh, on that private channel we have on podgeo
plus or on her iPod or on, well,
G, her set top box or any of the other myriad of distribution
devices. We've been working on with people.
So I'm, I'm really getting excited about this.
Look for that to launch second week of November.
Oh, sorry. Hey, Adam, my name is Logan,
and I'm a broadcast journalism student, CSU Fresno.
I'm also working on filmmaking, screenwriting,
which brings me to my question.
Online video has finally been taken up by major broadcasters.
The big four TV networks are now supplying back episodes for free.
Cable shows. You can now buy on iTunes,
and even shows like Battlestar Galactica,
producing quote unquote webisodes
that are intended exclusively for an online audience.
Right now our independent video podcasts are predominantly
nonfiction,
Dignation Room of Rules, Gaper TV,
or the other variety show type.
Tiki Bar TV or Askin Ninja easily come to mind.
So finally, my question.
Has podcasting matured enough to lure professional
if not union talent for dramatic and genre shows.
And our advertisers and podgeo
ready to begin work with show creators and producers
on making shows with a good production value.
Thanks, Adam. I love the source code,
and I'm always glad to see a new one up here on my iPod.
Yeah, buddy. Well, let me answer this question for you.
First of all, I take slight offense to the
quote good production values.
That's horseshit.
You can create good production values
if you're in an attic somewhere,
or let's anywhere in the world
that you have a computer.
You can create something with great production values.
I mean, that's just horseshit.
There's nothing to do with someone who's quote professional or not.
Is the industry ready?
Yeah, what are you talking about?
I mean, I've been doing this for almost two years.
No, I've been doing it for two years.
I'm a code professional.
Lots of people are in it.
Now, what are we doing about that?
Yeah, absolutely.
We're opening up a studio in Los Angeles.
We have a studio now in London.
You know, it's office studio.
So, you know, there's work going on.
That's cool. That's kind of in the background.
We're working on licensing
with ASCAP BMI to expand that if it all possible.
But, you know, forget about whether that's possible or not.
There's plenty, plenty of professional talent on the pod save music.
Now, work, look at what's coming on board.
Look at the fantastic artists who we have.
There are definitely mainstream names.
Yeah, we've been working with people here in the UK with the OJ
and Olivia.
They're quote unquote professional talent.
The only thing that will be problematic is the concept of union.
This is the one thing that really has to change across the board.
We've changed it in music licensing with the pod save music network license.
We'll have to do something similar with the talent
because it's just not going to play out.
You know, the audiences aren't going to be large enough
and it's just not going to make any sense
with the free distribution model that, you know, that's the path
that we seem to be going down.
There's no way you can tell anymore where something's been played or repropagated.
So it's pretty much going to be buy out for everybody when they do something.
Or a share in revenue, either one, but not like a union where you have unionized rates.
I just don't see that happening.
There's too many variables.
We've ready for it.
Dude, we're deep into it, right in the middle of it.
And it's very, very exciting to me.
And we're getting lots of refugees from the broadcast industry.
One last song for you today from British Columbia.
I've played her before on the show.
And I like her.
Yeah, and when she's got the Levi's on,
and she's got,
oh, that's second.
Do I have the right, I'm thinking, do I,
is this the right, I don't think I have the right song queueed up.
Crap, how do I do that?
Oh, I see what I did.
I queueed up the same song twice.
Hold on.
Here it is.
It was right underneath it.
Yeah, cowboy hat and Levi's cowboy boots and Levi's.
That's what it is.
It's a little bit of country on the DSC,
and it's coming from something that ain't hard on the eyes.
Kelly Brock.
I wonder,
this cowboy wearing a country?
Yeah.
I love to watch and walk.
That boy could put in a healthy girl in shock.
He makes some of the ladies say.
In his cowboy boots and Levi's.
But boy's got style is number one of the shots.
I wouldn't forget,
but I'll make a break your heart.
Making turn you warm.
We give a night in his cowboy boots and Levi's.
In his cowboy boots and Levi's.
That's what it is.
It's just a little more.
It's one of the modern nights.
That keeps on short.
That's everything we've got to let you play.
But boy can't play.
It's so good.
We give a night in his cowboy boots and Levi's.
But ever since he was just a little boy
It was my my body, like it's on your head
We're at semi deep down on that chick
The boy can't lay and he should get set
In his cowboy boots, Levi
In his cowboy boots
Damn
Like that, Kelly Brock, cowboy boots and Levi
I've learned while surfing the internet
Number one, entering your email address on some websites
Is an open invitation to spam
Number two, before forwarding an email about the ghost
Of a dead boy appearing in the theatrical film
Three men and a baby
Check Snopes.com first
Number three
Spyware, then forms you that you have spyware
Is not very helpful
Number four
The FBI will never send you an email
The warning about your visiting 40 illegal websites
They'll simply bust down your door
Never, ever, Google the Toronto-based quartet
The barricade ladies on a computer at work
Number six, Bill Gates and Microsoft are not tracking this email
And fording it to 15 other people
Will not get Walt Disney signed to send you free passes
To Walt Disney World
There is no such thing as a national do not email registry
Number eight, there is no ousted prints in Bangladesh
Willing to share $15 million with you
Closing one porn pop-up window opens 15 more
And number 10, everything as your service provider
Will solve most of these problems
Unfortunately, the remaining few will take some common sense
If you want a great deal on domain name, go to godaddy.com
Use checkout code dsc3
For domain name for entire year for $695
To Maro, Fubar Friday, fucked up beyond dollar pair
We'll have great music, I'm sure the music college is jersey
Todd will check in more promos, more shit to talk about
And please let me know, bonfire night, Gilfuck, Gilfuck's
Guy Fox, when am I supposed to be flying?
When can I actually see something?
When can you shoot a rocket up my ass?
Let me know, Adam at podshow.com
And show notes for today's episode daily source code.com
Take care everybody, talk to you tomorrow, bye
Another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear
Yet this podcast and we're great ones like it
On the hyperformance podcast, delivery network from podshow
And line-white networks
I love it