Already a hit state side now you can check out the following podcast and good old
blighty btpotjo.com single-handedly making a men's for the Boston Tea Party one show at a time
I got it a 5-5-5m
was $60m worth of air planes strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio content
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Keep it hit me, I don't know where it's just when I thought I had everything.
Did it recognize a feeling feel like a rush coming through me?
Yeah, you were shining like a downward second girl from a baby.
Your mystery is made to be my surprise.
And not a day, don't mind, don't mind, don't mind, don't mind.
I'll take my time, just think you're fine.
Not a day, don't mind, don't mind.
I don't mind when I think I'm flying into the future.
Keep it hit me, I don't know where it's just when I thought I had everything.
You're always looking at me, I don't know where it's just when I thought I had everything.
Yeah, you were just like a bitch, you're always so bright that you love me.
You're the world girl, and I'm feeling I never believed I would have me.
Tell you not to leave, and that wasn't changed my life.
And not a day, don't mind, don't mind, don't mind.
I'll take my time, just think you're fine.
Not a day, don't mind, don't mind.
I don't know where it's just when I think I'm flying into the future.
Keep it hit me, I don't know where it's just when I thought I had everything.
You're always looking at me, I don't know where it's just when I thought I had everything.
Ah, nothing like a little bit of cowbell.
You get to go on on a Tuesday.
Everybody how you doing?
So that a source code coming to you from Curry Cottage in the affluent suburb of Surrey
known as Gulford.
That's Cherry Swade from Ontario, Canada, and not a day goes by.
Thank you very much to Brian, no for suggesting that a no secret there, the influences
has listed on the on the pontsive music network.
Of course, links to that in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com influences Brian Adams,
Bon Jovi, Deflopper, and the Beatles, Bibles.
You know what's so cool?
Every single time I do the cowbell because of the the microphone set up and the compression
and everything.
You know, if I hit the cowbell really hard, then it'll, you know, I got to find the right
mix for the music.
And so I take the the cowbell and my drumstick and I turn away from the microphone.
But when I do that, I'm looking straight at my mom, picture of my mom here on my desk
and she's looking back and she's always smiling at me and I can just hear her almost
thinking, he's so idiot.
Okay.
Mr. Mom for the next couple of days Patricia's off again to Rotterdam to go and practice rehearsal
for her.
I think she's doing two different dances, I don't know if it's two or three, two for
sure for dancing with the stars, which will be the year and episodes in the Netherlands
and she's very excited and of course she's out to win too and I think she's going to do
it.
She's really, she's so good at this stuff even though she's not trained at dancing.
She's just, she's got the rhythm, you know what I'm saying?
Hey, portions of this podcast are definitely not family friendly to me tell you right
now that even though you may find portions of today's show extremely humorous, some
of the topics discussed in the daily source code may not be appropriate for young ears
and may be very difficult to explain but since we're kind of in a, won't we do this?
We're, we're getting, here we go, we're this work, we're getting kind of into a, into a holiday
group here.
This is horrible, it's like, don't we have a better Christmas, Christmas music?
What's this Christmas Eve at the club, maybe this will sound better, let's try this.
We're getting into the holiday vibe here, everybody, there really is a lot of love going
around in the Pod Show family, of course we have thousands of shows now who are podcasting
out to the universe and sending you all kinds of good cheer for the holidays and well,
you know, you can always count on my fellow podcast network producers to make me feel really
nice and warm and, and just a part of their family and some people love this time of year.
Here's an example for a good tidings and holiday cheer from our Los Angeles chapter.
One thing, I never want to miss is Adam Curry's, Mary Mary Fistmus, oh yeah.
When Adam gets back to San Francisco, I'm gonna buy some stock in Chrisco,
there's big Christmas grin and holiday chuck goes ill tear up your o-ring with his
greased up knuckles from Thanksgiving, right to the new year he's got one hand right up your rear
and while you're celebrating holiday masses, he's ramming his fist right in the air asses it's
Adam Curry's, Mary Mary Fistmus, oh yeah.
When he gets started it's hard to make him stop. He'll treat you like Sherry Lewis,
treated lamb chop because he's bringing joy to all the girls and boys with a rubber ball gag and
the bag of sex toys. On his belt you'll see some missile toe and he's got his hand inside your
Cheerio and maybe while you let him deck your halls he'll give you a reach around and tickle your balls
it's oh yeah. Adam Curry's, Mary Mary Fistmus, insert cowbell here.
He's making a fist and greasing it twice and when he's all done you'll probably need ice.
He knows if you've been folding, he knows if you might scrunch and if you're really lucky he'll
give you a don't get bunch. Oh yeah. Adam Curry's, Mary Mary Fistmus.
That's a real sing along. Mary Mary Fistmus, Mary Mary Fistmus.
Happy Fistmus everybody. Mark I think we need to find some more things for you to do there.
Mary Fistmus Adam in the shock. Adventist Beach. Hey it's not like I didn't warn you okay?
Let's see what's going on some things that haven't seen a lot of post on around the net,
not yet at least. The first one is something happening here in the UK as reported by BBC,
the Everettrustworthy BBC. There was a lobby. I believe led by Sir Cliff Richard
to extend copyright in the United Kingdom to 95 years instead of the present 50 years.
And so now an independent review is going to recommend that these terms are not extended.
What this means and I understand where Sir Cliff is coming from by the way because he did
songs when he was 15, 16 years old. It probably even could even be older than that. Maybe even
when he was 17 or 18 and that was 50 years ago. In fact, it was at 2008 and back in the day
and we're talking like late 50s, Cliff Richard was without a doubt the British Elvis Presley.
I mean he was the shit and chicks loved him and guys loved everyone loved Sir Cliff. He wasn't a
certain. Everyone loved Cliff Richard. And so understandably he's saying hey what the fuck!
So when these things, when the copyright expires 50 years after their creation,
what that means that anyone can do anything they want with those songs in the public domain.
These were those songs we'll go. So automatically they could be played on podcasts. I wouldn't
mind playing summer holiday. That'd be kind of fun. Of course Sir Cliff will make no money on these
anymore. And so I understand his gripe about that. I don't know if he's making a shitload of money
off of summer holiday anymore. But I can understand certainly if someone were to do a remake.
I remember the young ones did a remake of summer holiday. It went to number one in many countries
around the world. So if that were to happen again then he'd obviously he would miss out and I
can understand where that's a farmer. But at the same time think about the wealth that he'll be adding
to the public domain literally by his songs coming into into that realm and being able to be
used and passed on and shared with the younger generation. I have no idea who Cliff Richard is
besides that old queen that keeps popping up. So I haven't seen a lot of news about that. And by the
way I think we'll see a lot more of these songs coming to the public domain over the next couple
years. I'm not quite sure what it is in the States now because that got so convoluted.
Sonny Bono was of course one of the people who passed legislation to extend copyrights. It's
basically a way for hollywood to have an edge. And that's okay. Don't mind. We don't really
need your shit necessarily but it'll be fun to be able to share. And this caught my attention yesterday
as a story on MacanN.com that Apple is apparently has filed for a patent on the concept
of a podcatcher. And if you read it, it literally describes what iPod or lemon did, what iPod or
did. In fact, I think we could even argue the case that radio user land, the day-winer created,
that that even supersedes any patent attempts. And I looked at that and I said to myself, you know,
I think we should stop this. I mean, it wouldn't be fucking horrible if all the work that all
these developers spent on making this work and integrating it with Apple's product, if the
the patents were given to Apple, which of course is ludicrous because there's so much prior art
of this technology synchronizing. You know, iPod literally says, down automatically,
downloading podcasts, synchronizing it to a portable device. And we were doing all of that every single bit
of it. So I have asked our attorneys to form an opinion on how to block this because I think we should.
And well, of course, there's always one guy who can always trust in the case like this to weigh in
with his explicit commentaries.
Comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, all right,
hitting C.S.B. Hi Adam Carey. When you woke up today, can you notice this each in your
ennus? Oh, yo, yo, some utterness wrote you a bad damn when you were sleeping. Who could it be?
Yes, it was Steve Jobs from Apple Corporation. He tickled your ego by inviting you to creation
of potfinder and hands podcast. And in meantime, Apple's lawyers were busy screwing up secretly
you personally Adam and whole pod of fear. Adam, I kindly ask you to stop sucking cock of
Steve Jobs and to oppose Apple's evil actions like patenting of iPoder. Recently,
I noticed on Wikipedia entry about Jeremy's effort and that he is one of inventors of podcasting.
If it will go on, then soon nobody will even know that you had something to do with invention
of podcasting and a stood as fetching MP3s from RSS automatically to media player. Adam,
just listen to me. You're genuine friend. Yo. Yo. Well, let me just say,
first of all, I don't believe that I think this is just an automatic process, which of course is
exactly what Apple should be doing. Everything they create needs to go through a process and if it can
be trademarked, if it can be a registered trademark, if it can be a patent, that I think that's pretty
much automatic. So I don't fault the corporation for doing that, but I'm not going to let it happen.
And by the way, add Kevin Marx to the list as well. All these people who created prior art,
what I commit today is that Pod Show will put up resources and funds to keep the entire concept
of a pod catcher in the public domain. I'm not quite sure if we have to make it. I mean,
the script I created iPoder was always open source from day one very clear. So, this patent
fuck you. It's not going to happen. Pod Show is going to put their money where their mouth is and
stop that. That will not take place.
I'm in that used to suck so bad and the pleasure. And I went into the bathroom and got myself off,
biting my lips the whole time because nobody would hear me. As the pod bother saves the world,
as only a former MTVVJ can with extreme prejudice. You are such a dickweed. Get the fuck out of my office.
Deep in the bowels of the curry cottage, plans are set. Splendid consumed and soon humanity will
experience a reckoning. That usually fucks companies up. For the next year there's going to be a
lot of turmoil and radio, trim everything down, get rid of the quote, excess fat, which is usually
comes in the form of chop people up into bits. So, I think this is the time we need to strike
drunk. Don't miss this daily event because if you do fuck you, Adam Curry and the daily source code.
This show is fucking awesome. This podcast is rated gigas.
All right, it's episode 505 of your daily source code of course. I say it's your daily source code
because you completely contribute to it and it does one way for you to do it if you live in an
UK pay attention, sing along and put this in yourself. So while we're here talking about the UK,
David, who sent in that David Graham, who sent in that six minute long comment. Yes,
today about Chris Moiles, the BBC, what they can and can't do with podcasts. Here at the call,
he edited it down to three minutes. Okay, let's listen. Hi, Adam. Listen to the feedback you
received from your listeners about the mention you got from Radio 1 DJ Chris Moiles. I have to
apply and make some corrections. Our response from one of your listeners called James made out
the Chris Moiles was against podcasting and saw no future in it. This is incorrect. Chris
actively promotes his podcast which in turn educates the public about podcasting. Chris would love
to do a original content for his podcast, but BBC rules restrict him from doing so and the following
explains this. It's the new and improved podcast this week and I'll tell you what how this works
and I'm going to explain to you exactly the truth, right? Who dug his currently loading it on
to the website as we speak? Here's how it works. The podcast through somebody's bizarre BBC rule
states that we can't have any new material on the podcast. It's all going to be stuff that we put
out on the radio. So to get around this this morning, so what do you got this morning,
the new show? It's between half three and four. We played out what will be today's podcast.
So technically what? No, it has been broken out. So therefore we can put it on. Yeah, so every week
half three to four in the morning on a Friday morning, we'll put the podcast out on the air.
Another lesson I call Chris Moiles Home of Public, which I also think is untrue.
Listening to Chris for over five years now, I cannot understand where these comments have come from.
Probably the tabloid media. Chris has a gay day producer who often picks on him for show entertainment.
The producer. Oh, please. This is the song my best friends are gay excuse.
There's no problem with this as it's normal show banter, but listeners who don't listen that often
may think it's because he is gay who knows. Thank you. I do like it. And you know,
cause it's cool to have a human being on the show. Oh, well, but it is because I'm hated by
that's why I'm a homophobic brother. Yeah, I know, I hear that. Yeah, I hear that. I hate all the
gays. But you want to meet Ali? No, to be fair, let's just clear the song. I don't give him. I don't have
care what your anybody's sexual orientation is. I really don't care. I do hate Alan, though.
Nothing to do with his gay. He was bisexual, stray, acesial. What bother me? The slide
is I still find them irritated with a huge ego. My final question is the statement that Chris
wears a little there. Again, which I think is untrue. The majority of time, it's Chris's guess
who swear on air not actually him. But again, the media headlines it so it sounds like he was a
one with the foul mouth. Well, there you have it Adam. You can make your mind up what you really think
Chris is like. I find it interesting that listeners who obviously don't listen to Chris's show
find it acceptable to comments on something that they don't listen to. I find that odd. Anyway,
this has been David Graham from Dorset England, who some of say has been corrupted by Chris
Mose. Grunge. Yeah, of course you're a scruncher. Not you're absolutely right. I don't know Chris
Mose. I've not listened to his show enough. So you've certainly given me a different perspective and I
appreciate it. And I'm still watching. I'm a celebrity get me out of here, which I think is
four more nights. And David guessed lies in manellies of former husband is still in there. Boy,
what was I wrong about this guy? This guy is fucking funny. He's really funny and he's endearing
and he's very American at the same time. Not at all the liquid I thought he was. And you know,
and even through the lens of, even through the television camera, you know, you still end the
way. It's edited. You still don't really know what someone's like, but I certainly have a much better
idea. Well, here you go. Throw Chris Mose in the jungle. That's an idea. Hey, Minks, Genevieve
and I wanted to call you up and tell you the good news. Really? What's the world cast? Just cut
sign up at the pod show network. Yep. Just cut the contract in the mail today. Going to be at
a rope.potcho.com. Awesome. Did this be what I think it means? No, no, we're not changing anything.
Still covering all kinds of rope bondage. Thank you so much. I think she needs interviews with the
experts. Talk about politics and performance art and, of course, I'll still ask you both as the
official rope sluts to be my assistance. Thanks. I mean, yes, sir. But are we care about
if Adam Curry? Wait, Minks, you should see great answers. Thanks. No, don't tell me you signed
it without making it. But both of you, I couldn't very well demand exclusive bondage rights
to Adam Curry. Now, could I? Why not? Was it not what I've done? It's can't believe
let you talk to me to that where my, and then you, hey, you, you enjoyed that. Well, yeah, but
you promised me Adam Curry. You promised me Adam would. Hey, hey, we're not even really sure
he's actually kinky. Okay. That's just rumors. I don't care. Me either. You either get us
Adam Curry or you can take a rope cast and shove it up. All right. All right. Well, Adam,
you know where to find me. Great answer. And the rope cast at rope dot podshow dot com. No,
Adam Curry. Yes. Welcome to the network rope cast. Uh-huh. Now, I'm not, I'm kinky, but not
it. I'm not into rope at all, but I saw some of the pictures at rope dot podshow dot com.
I also found your hidden video cast. I wouldn't mind hanging out with you guys.
I can tie in or I pretty mean not a chic shank.
It's, you know, it's interesting. I said to the to Richard Brueh and Joe and our talent
department. I said, you know, I, I want an erotic a channel. I want, especially since it gets
no play on iTunes, I want a proper erotic a channel. Can I just say, I think the guys are
really, really delivering this time. Good job, boys. Good job. Okay.
Sadly, Windows now officially closed. It's just you and I, my friends and the juries.
Now I question anything. I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not,
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not,
He didn't buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car
He wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy
the car, he wanted to have the car, he liked the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the other car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, small, small car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted get the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the car, he wanted to buy the
You know, this kind of sounds like one of those songs that's running out of copywriting.
Yeah, the Jerry's and change your mind from the pod save music network.
I don't know what it is about those guys.
I played a different song by then earlier.
Was it Friday, maybe?
Remember what day?
Previous show.
I like him.
I really like the way they sound.
Uh, what was it going to say?
Oh, yeah.
I got a nice note and my checks back.
I tell you that from from the camera, the camera police who who snapped me,
speeding, they're saying that I have to get a UK equivalent license.
And then when I get the license, then I send the license in with my,
what is it?
120 pound fine with my check because it's two fines each, 60 pounds each.
Then they'll take off six points off of my license and pack to me.
So I'm like, and now, of course, since, you know, this has to happen within some,
I guess some agreeable amount of time, I'm already getting all kinds of, you know, legal
notices that I'm going to, basically going to jail is what's going to happen.
So I'm going to see if I can, if I can, I got a, I feel like shit today.
I got, I've been running a fever for two days, but sometimes this week I have to
have to take care of this, I have to get it done along with all the services that
have to be changed as we move to the new cottage.
I've got to get to bandwidth set up.
I've got to get to the sky, satellite TV set up.
Oh, man, this is just so much, it has to be done.
But that's just my personal life.
There's stuff to be done professionally as well.
Some good news regarding accessibility of podshow plus I'm so happy that someone
called in with this information.
Adam listening to 504 and just one thing that if we use in your text, this drawing or
your beautiful flash content, there is an accessibility panel where you can put
like shortcuts and tab in that description so that screen readers can actually interact
with a content, just sort of getting my sense of the show holder.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Okay, I'm all over this.
I had no idea I bet you the developers didn't know or weren't thinking about it.
This is great news.
And quite honestly, I could hardly imagine that Adobe, with its 98 or 99% penetration
of flash on all computers in the known universe, that they wouldn't have baked in some
accessibility stuff.
So apparently it's in there.
I will have the boys and girls look at it.
I promise you, let's get this done already, let's get this stuff working for people.
And this is where this was supposed to queue up, but there we go.
Yeah, what's up AC is, Jersey Todd, the official musicologist of the Chacha.
Hey listen, coming off the ton of blues of 35th birthday party last Friday, I had to bring
you a special midweek song to the Daily Source code, and I just had to get this song up
to you today.
I couldn't wait till Friday, the artist is Peter Mulvey out of Wisconsin.
His new album, The Nuckleball Sweet, well it's out on signature sounds.
And this is an artist that's been getting a lot of national press.
The songs are absolutely wonderful and I'm telling you, you got to check them out.
The song that I'm going to give you today, growing the high tops, is going to give
you a good kick in the ass for the middle of the week.
So go over to signature sounds website at www.signaturesounds.com, tell them to post more
of their artists of the Podsate music network, because they have got some absolutely amazing
people on their roster.
Hey, I'll see you guys on Friday, but right now this is Peter Mulvey on The Daily Source
Code.
Pretty young girl in my arms, is speaking of shelling to me.
I'm drinking beer, wine, I feel fine, I still may lose all the best I can to see.
I will lose all the best I can to see here.
I'll show you super places almost empty, barbed in this put-up of chairs, never been
song that was signed, it's gone on its way into the air, has gone on its way to the
air, gone, gone all the way, gone, every one on the way, gone to light on the air.
So go over to signature sounds website at www.signaturesounds.com, tell them to post more of
their artists of the Podsate music network.
So go over to signature sounds website at www.signaturesounds.com, tell them to post
more of their artists of the Podsate music network.
So go over to signature sounds website at www.signaturesounds.com.
So go over to signature sounds website at www.signaturesounds.com
website at www.signaturesounds.com