This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want to hear our content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Well, hello, everybody.
Welcome to the very first Devcast.
Which you can find and hopefully,
Did find at developers.podshow.com.
With me, I'm in Gilford in the Curry Cottage with me today.
Joining us via Skype is Andrew Grommett,
who is at Pod Show HQ in San Francisco,
Morning Andrew.
Good morning, Adam.
So, here we go, bro.
We're getting real close now.
Getting real.
So, excuse me, I'm eating a cheese and grapes.
Which is a rocket fuel for developers in England.
It's not a diet coke.
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't drink diet coke.
Okay, so here's the concept.
We want to allow the first audience members to come into Pod Show
Plus and, you know, snoop around and see what's going on
and work with the podcast delivery network as well.
And since we have lots of cool stuff that we already planning for developers,
we thought it was a logical,
yeah, really a logical step to say,
well, why don't we let the developers in first?
Who, of course, are fantastic listeners.
Andrew is you and I, or as I know, having worked with you.
I mean, those early days of, of podcasting when,
literally, you know, I'd create a show and then you guys would adapt your code.
You know, what was it like from your end,
back in the day, developing with, with users who were creating podcasts?
It was pretty amazing.
The thing, it's, it's, uh,
when you can build your own code and then,
have that, you know, influence your daily life, build the tools that are,
you know, improving your, your data day experience.
That's, that's one of the best things you can do,
I think, uh, as an engineer.
Maybe just short of building stuff for other people,
which, of course, we were doing it the same time.
But, uh, I do have a great memory of the first.
I don't know if you remember this,
you remember the first.
I think you played a clip from a coverville of the Abba.
Um, do you remember this?
They did Abba covers in the early days.
Trying to think, I don't know.
I just have this incredible memory of, of walking down the street,
and listening to this cover of an Abba song,
uh, and thinking, wow, okay, we're really onto something here.
Um, yeah.
Covers of Abba, we've really improved the universe.
Haven't we, Andrew?
That's great.
Okay.
Now, we've had, um,
developer.podshow.com up for a while.
Um, we actually haven't really been able to add much to it.
Since we haven't really opened up yet,
and I guess, uh, we're working to happen here.
We'll eventually flow over into, uh, into that site.
Yeah, right on.
That's, uh, where we're collecting all of the, uh, ideas.
Right now, of course, it's heavy on ideas.
But, uh, as we release SDKs,
we will have, um, you know, downloads and web visible,
the HTML documentation for everything that we release,
uh, trying to make it really easy.
Collect code examples, um,
uh, pointers to, uh,
people who might have put things up on their own sites.
Just try to make it, uh,
you know, the place to get started,
if you're a developer and want to build something around the PDN.
Right.
Now, there's, there's really two sides.
There is the PDN.
The podcast will be network and actually, uh,
there isn't API for that now, which, uh,
is pretty standard.
I don't think we've published it yet,
and so we can get to it.
But, uh, we're going to publish that
for these developers as well, who will be playing with that?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
So, um, I've actually, uh,
there's a couple of the recent posts sort of hint at where we're going,
and, um, actually, I made you,
maybe that maybe I should do a dev cast to actually talk
through some of the stuff we, uh,
you know, figure it out, uh,
doing some of that implementation, um,
uh, as a, you know, a way to,
test the water and see what people's reactions are.
Uh, before, you know, what happens when you commit things,
too, uh, writing on the web suddenly,
they become stack.
Yeah.
Before, you know, even if you say,
even if you say, this is not stack,
so maybe a podcast is the way to, uh,
uh, you know, put some ideas out there for feedback.
Excellent.
Well, yeah, that would be good,
and then we'll just include it in this feed as well.
And then we have a pod show plus.
And this is where I think there's a lot of exciting stuff
to be done as well.
This is really the, the experience side.
This is what we built for the audience.
This is what really is taking the most time.
To really get it right.
And we have a concept of modules.
You want to get into that a little bit and explain what that is and,
and how they work and how the developers are mess around with them.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Modules are segments of every user and show on the on pod show plus
will have a page.
We're calling it a profile page where you can, you know,
sort of like a homepage, uh,
where you can, uh,
uh, view information, uh,
about a person or a show.
And the person or the, you know,
if it's a show maintainer,
they arrange content on that page,
sort of like a blog page,
um, or a sort of a my,
you know,
Yahoo type page.
And what we'll be doing with modules is,
um,
modules just our name for different areas on the page,
that you can fill with flicker feeds or,
you know, any RSS feed or,
yeah,
who weather or, um,
you know,
recent shows from the,
uh,
I'm sorry,
recent, uh,
additions to the pod safe music network.
So we've come up with a handful of modules,
uh, for people to put on their pages.
And what we'll be doing is opening an up,
up in SDK that lets developers create,
uh, new modules that people can put on their pages.
So, uh,
that, you know,
within kind of reasonable limits of security and,
and machine, you know,
resource use,
you'll be able to put pretty much anything on your page that you want.
So, uh,
we'll make it, uh,
you know,
let a thousand flowers bloom,
as they say,
you know,
let's see what people come up with.
Yeah, we will actually have,
uh,
almost a user version of that,
which, of course,
a module that eats HTML.
You can, you know,
jam any HTML in there,
which users have gotten pretty good at.
And you'll be able to put that on your page as well.
So, it's,
it's kind of hard to explain.
So, that's why, you know,
I'm happy that now people are going to be able to come in and take a look at it.
Um,
how are we actually going to manage the,
uh, this development process,
Andrew, I mean,
who do people talk to,
uh,
I know we don't,
we don't have everything set up yet with URLs,
etc.
Obviously,
um,
we're not going to give them out on the public podcast.
How,
how will the feedback loop work,
is it going to be a CVS,
or what,
what have you set up for all that?
Yeah,
we're looking at,
actually right now,
uh,
using a source forage project.
Um,
we've talked internally about,
uh,
you know,
managing the CVS ourselves,
but, um,
I think,
there's sort of,
this is a well understood,
you know,
problem set as long as people are developing open source stuff.
We,
there's plenty of tools out there,
uh,
that we can,
you know,
so we can use for,
uh,
saving people's code.
I mean,
the key thing is just that,
you know,
and there's a place to point to it,
and stuff doesn't fall through the cracks.
Um,
but,
K1 and myself,
Kevin Strausky,
will be,
in the points of contact.
We actually have a,
a little used currently,
uh,
Gmail address,
podshow developer at Gmail.com.
So we'll either use that or,
or whatever tools are available on,
say source forage,
or,
you know,
wherever we host it.
So now it,
it being on source force.
That means we can keep it close.
We can keep it password protected.
Well,
that's a good point.
Uh,
source forage is,
is for open source,
um,
you know,
code,
which I don't actually,
that's a good question.
I don't think we've,
um,
technically if it's running on our servers,
we could keep it closed.
But if you mean,
you know,
we need a password,
in order to commit code,
sure that's how source forage works.
Um,
but the code itself up there would be out in the open.
Okay.
Well,
that's,
that's not,
that's not an issue.
Well,
and I think probably,
um,
and so we're going to issue golden tickets on these dev cast.
So it could be that you'd hear in this show,
could be in the next show,
could be the one after that.
But really,
the intention is to get all the developer's in,
but instead of having,
you know,
a couple hundred show up in,
in one day,
we're going to stagger it.
So you'll hear in one of these dev cast,
you'll hear instructions on where to go.
And I'm thinking that that makes sense,
that we give instructions,
or maybe there's a pre registered,
um,
that's a good,
that's an interesting one.
We can give more.
We're also going to have a wiki else that I mentioned,
as a place for information,
and putting up code samples.
Yeah, my favorite technology.
Okay.
So instructions,
how to get into this particular developer program,
we'll be included in the golden ticket.
And of course,
over the course of the next,
I don't know,
we'll probably do five of these,
and then as they go along as you and Kevin and other people have stuff to say,
we'll just do more,
which I think is kind of cool
if we have the audio feedback portion
to what's going on,
then eventually everyone will get in.
Just so everyone is clear on the intent there.
Oh, I see.
Okay, right.
And Andrew,
by the way,
is the guy behind D-gap?
We can actually do this, right?
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
So, well,
do you want me to talk about that?
Yeah, absolutely.
This is my favorite,
favorite stuff that we built.
This is cool.
Okay, so with D-gap,
we basically have a system where you can set up a flag that says,
you know,
the next episode that comes through on show X,
should be flagged to get an insertion.
And then there's a pointer to,
you know,
the file that will be inserted.
And as you recall,
we'd come up with a convention for passing the information into the system about,
where in the middle of the cast,
the insertion should be made and with what probability, right?
This was the coin toss idea with each downloader.
We pick a random number and,
you know, subject to some probability,
decide whether that user will get a goal to take it.
And then if they do,
we bump the counter and,
and, you know,
check to make sure that we're only serving these golden tickets up to a certain point.
And after that,
we don't serve anymore.
So we're eventually going to open up an API for that as well.
I would presume.
We definitely can, right?
It, uh,
excuse me,
but all I'm saying all,
yeah,
I had my own,
you know,
I was thinking about that.
You know,
we're not,
we need to get this in sale.
Love here over HQ.
Really.
Um,
uh,
so we can APIize that absolutely.
Um,
I think the sky's the limit, really.
Cool.
We have to,
you know,
figure out what people like and,
okay.
Um,
just,
oh, yeah,
I wanted to touch briefly on,
because I,
in the source code,
I said that,
really,
the only skills you need are knowledge of HTML,
PHP.
Am I correct in that assumption?
It doesn't seem like there's much more there, is there?
Yeah.
It's, uh,
there's actually,
a sort of build-up function that will set up a skeleton for you as well.
So you don't even have to know the file structure,
all that deeply.
Um,
but you give it a name for your module.
And, uh,
it's sort of what the,
you know, a gentle slope.
You can just put in some,
some static text and you're often running,
uh,
but what we'll do is we'll provide docs on,
you know,
how to get deeper and create custom variables and so forth.
Excellent.
So yeah,
I don't think we,
we're not going to require any sequel programming or anything like that.
Okay.
Good, because then I can't participate.
I want to get in there and mess around and screw some shit up.
I know just enough to be really dangerous.
I was going to say,
can you, you know,
tunnel out your,
your second life identity somehow.
Dude,
that stuff is outrageous.
Have you been,
but tried second life?
I haven't.
I'm scared of it.
If I do it,
that'll be it.
It'll eat your time.
It takes away your life.
It, it,
it becomes first life almost.
It's amazing.
I've already,
um,
someone already gave me a,
um, a penis.
So I can use that now and all the,
you know,
the sex area is,
it's crazy.
It's like,
it's really nice.
What did I hear that they're,
they're prostitutes now?
Oh, yeah.
Excuse me.
Escorts Andrew.
Escorts.
Oh, sorry.
All right.
Good man.
So let's leave it at this.
And tomorrow,
I think I'll connect with,
uh,
with Kevin and, uh,
who walk us through,
uh,
some more of the module stuff.
And as of tomorrow,
um,
hopefully we'll have it all set up so that we can,
uh,
and so this is this first one.
I'll just make sure that,
uh,
everyone is receiving it that,
we've got,
uh,
everyone is hooked up and subscribed.
I think this probably going to be about,
30 to 40 people who will,
who are subscribed already.
I mean,
it's, uh,
excellent.
Yeah.
Now I'm looking forward to this.
Because there's a lot of excitement on,
on the,
on the first post,
mainly because people are just waiting and waiting
and waiting for me to get my ass in care and get this stuff up.
All right,
um,
what's up for you today at HQ?
And well,
uh,
I've just about got the,
the wiki set up.
I think I was mentioning that the,
um,
so this will be uh,
tied in with the pdn,
so that the login will carry over and,
um,
uh,
got a call with a big,
unnamed company coming up here in about a half an hour
to talk about some joint projects.
And,
uh,
yeah.
So we'll keep,
better as well.
Keep em busy.
All right, man,
fantastic.
Um,
well,
that's it for dev cast number one.
Be on the lookout for dev cast number two by tomorrow.
And of course,
uh,
be on the lookout for your golden ticket.
Andrew,
thank you very much,
man.
I'll talk to you later in the week.
All righty.
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it.
On the high performance podcast,
delivery network from podjo and line white networks.
I love it.