This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charley 420.
Oh, man.
420.
Hey, what's up, Adam?
This is Buck Thompson.
I'm a listener.
I don't have a podcast.
It's not yet.
Sounds of listening here to the Charlie number 400.
Congrats on that milestone.
But I was thinking, I was like, what's the next milestone?
And it hit me.
It hit me.
It kind of breaks.
I'm driving home from work.
I'm like, holy shit.
It's 420.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking trees in.
I like to think I'm flying with you to the future.
podcasting.
It's a very...
2.
1.
3.
2.
420.
I think I heard a noise.
Hey, man.
You got the Doritos?
I can't.
Where are you going?
I'm going to give you something to drink.
Hey, isn't that Kurt Loader?
420.
On the Charlie.
You just don't hear enough Reggae on the radio.
1.
2.
The destruction time to start up a new restoration time to live together in animation when we've gotten in the way
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I
can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it,
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't think of this, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't of what I meant, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't for it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it
That's your bed
And she got on against Hawaii
No, I can't do it
I can't do it
Go ahead, I defy you
Turn on any radio station
Turn on the radio in general
Listen for 24 hours, tell me if you hear one reggae song
You're the body of music network
From Ontario
You're the believers
If you want to know more about
The reference for 20
Put a link into
Of course, I don't know if it's the most reputable source
But it seems to gel with what I know about
422 Wikipedia article
You can check that out
So everybody, how you doing?
Were chill, relaxed
420 beliefs started for me
Oh man
I'm going to say about 15 years ago
I just did a documentary of Jamaica
That was actually of the Caribbean
But spent about 10 days in Jamaica
Doing a full blown documentary
I believe actually
That documentary is available now as a show
I'm pod show plus I'm going to go take a look
Because my body from Australia
Had digitized that so I did see it somewhere
It's in a very small, quick time format
You can see us actually
Cutting a record and then taking
The master tape to tough going records
And they actually press the vinyl for us
And I went to a
I went to a couple of parties
Checked out the sound system
And I kind of fell into the belief in the religion
If you know what I mean
And I still even don't understand everything about this
420 business
Hi Adam, this is Jennifer Navadate
And this is a comment for show 420
You know, if I were to talk about
You're from Sayo Coffee
And I've heard you talk about your screaves
What I haven't heard you talk about
Is the WB the weight and the weight
To elaborate a little bit more
And how that works in your life
Oh wait a minute
And have a great show 420
Okay, no no no now I get it
I even had it in my show notes
This is pretty funny
I listened to that comment
Just through the speakers of the
Toshiba laptop
Let me just I'm changing in the show notes right now
And I actually thought she said
Weight and weight
I don't know what that is
So I'll play that comment
But now that I hear it and I hear her saying
Wake and bake, yeah got it
Well, I'm not recommended
That's not a good way to start off your day
It really isn't but there are some days
You know, when it's appropriate
Like Saturday morning, Sunday morning
Coming to you from Curry Cottage
This is the daily source code
It's episode 420
A lot of exciting stuff going on
I feel real good about podshow
Plus and the podcast delivery network
Which we've now put into public beta
There's still there's such a world of
Difference between beta testing stuff
And and using it in a closed environment
Actually seeing it come alive with people
Digging each other
Getting shows, putting links in
Pimpin out there their pages
It's and and so much response
And I'm telling you
I what I'd really like
If even if you don't like
What you're seeing, please send me a comment
You know, booth
Commonster bloggers already accusing me of only playing positive
Positive comments about podshow
Plus. I'm just not getting any any criticism
Or very little criticism through audio comments
So you should definitely give us a call
Hold on a second, let me uh
Let me get the phone number for you
I don't know it by heart
Can you believe that? I still don't know the phone numbers by heart
Hold on, where is it?
Uh, crap
I'm believable
Where the heck did I save it?
Oh dude
I'm so host
Hold on a second, I'm messing everything up here
All of a sudden like yesterday show
I think I started off by saying
Uh three nineteen instead of four nineteen
So you can tell that I was definitely lost
Ah shit
Ah come on, give me the
Don't here we go
In New Jersey
So that would be plus one two zero one six two five six three five seven
Or if you prefer in London
Plus four four two zero seven six eight one three seven five three
And then we go let me just put this into the uh into your show notes there
Boom perfect
I'm loving it now I can put everything into cast blaster
And it all goes straight up to the
To the to the servers as show notes
It's freaking amazing. I love it. Okay. Wow. We back to today's show
Um
Speaking of comic strip blogger. Oh, it's doing
I don't where's this jingo?
Yeah, I'll have to go look for the jingo here. Check them out
Yeah, I don't carry yes. You still are screwing your beloved blackberry
Well
I see that you have launched the pot show
Plus at last I am not taking these features of pot show
Plus that are a clone of my space that come
But I like this free podcast hosting feature
How about ability to use once on the main for pot castle hosted for free on pot show
Plus is it coming in and time soon? Is it coming?
Whatever
We got a meet to drink some beer made. How about cash?
Yeah
A good question coming strip blogger. Yes, in fact
That is a major part of well first of all you can always
Um web forward a domain name obviously to your pot show
Plus domain so in your case it's csb dot pot show dot com
But yes, in fact we're going to be integrating that with the with the whole
Purchase of a domain name. Doesn't that make a lot of sense?
Now does the whole go daddy stuff start to come together?
Uh, so obviously the the concept would be you
Yeah, here's how it would really work if I were doing a my show
It's okay. Think up a name so it's
Um
The Polish podcast
dot com it might even be available go to go daddy dot com you get the pot
You get the domain name you check out using code dsc3 so you get it for $695
Sanson right there would be configured to my pot show plus account wouldn't that be beautiful if that worked
Well, that's exactly what we're planning
Hi Adam this is Slotsky. I saw a lot of the s.k. y
From Oxford England and just call it a say that I've been listening to the s.c.
Uh, about to the shows and you've been going on about the podcast with
We get what the long time have been also curious to see what it's like
And now that we've got it
I love it
Thank you, bye
No, thank you
Yeah, I see a lot of people confused about what what it is we're doing and yeah for hundreds of episodes
I've been talking about this and we've been building this for listeners and
We truly believe that this is what listeners
We will use and I'm shoot. I'm using it and I'm well
Um, has audience members and listeners basically we build it for what we want
It ourselves and what we believe in is the right way and a fun way and an easy way
Um
To discover podcasts to share them to create them to create channels of podcasts, you know
It's uh
We really worked on that a lot through our own experience
Um, something very prolific I was going to say or was it profound?
I never can remember
Well, we'll get to it. There's more feedback. Check this one out
Hi Adam, my name's Darren, long time listener and pro-crastinating podcast
I've only done about four shows in the last 12 months
But I'll get round to do another one
Eventually I've been having a look around pod show plus
And I have to say I'm a little bit confused
I'm trying to get um, the RSS feed for the
Bond show that's coming up
I do like the idea of a
Um, a quiz show on a podcast
But knowing how I am I'm unless I've got an RSS feed set up now
Then I'm going to forget about looking back and signing up with it
Other later date
Is there a um, a feed for it already or has the owner of the pod?
Cast just not put one up yet
Um, if you just point me in the direction of of what I'm supposed to be doing here
Okay, yeah, great question
And I've seen other people and this is what my microphone potential meter is
Pring it
This is a question I've seen come up time and time again
Um, people who have been enjoying pod cast
Um, for a while now understand the orange and white XML button
Love to copy that link and then put it into their favorite pod catcher
Which in many cases is iTunes or juice
Um, if you click on an episode you'll see a little box right at the top appear
And it'll allow you to play the episode and we know as media player or real player
Um, there's a button there to automatically subscribe yourself to that pod cast with iTunes
Uh, there's a XML button there so you can copy it and paste it into something else
It's just one click further than um, then the homepage
And you know, I'm I'm kind of evaluating that as well
Uh, I don't I don't think that's I think that box should surface or at least be optional
To surface on the homepage and it may actually be available
I just haven't figured out how the modules work
This is the big thing is we have my page and you can go and edit your profile
It's all drag and drop and add modules and dude
We need more modules and I'll talk about that in a second
We'll just finish up your audio comment here
Um, and of course to end this voice mail
I'm a scruncher, but I kind of like scrunch it to get the volume
And then neatly wrap it around the outside to get the smooth surface against the um
Butx
I don't believe I'm saying no, I said it for you
Thanks for the great shirt
I'm like a scruncher, okay, so we have one for the UK scrunchers
And we are keeping track are you a folder of your toilet paper or are you a scruncher?
What else, or something else I was going to say about podshow plus is this is you know
When you when you build something regardless of what it is
If it's dependent upon other things in this case podcasting of course is
Very dependent upon bandwidth and the speed of delivery
In fact, probably still 70%
Actually, I think it's like you know, if 27% of all podcasts that we see in our network
That run through our servers are being picked up by podcatchers
By automatic download programs such as iTunes
And the rest is all direct links
And when you build something you want to build for the future
So if you build an application a program to run on a computer
And if you know that oh, if only we had more memory or faster processors
Then we could do this in this and this you're definitely going to build that in
Because of how quickly computer processing changes
So too with bandwidth
So my true belief and a lot of other people are with me on this
And some people may or may not be with me. I'd love to hear from you
But my true belief is that we will eventually
Maybe in five years live in a truly 100% connected world
And RSS is a great distribution format
It helps you
Basically syndicate your content
But you know the whole idea of downloading and pre-caching and having stuff
Ready for you when you pick up your iPod
Was really developed because of the limitations of
The current state of the network
And if you trace it all the way back to the conversations they
Why and I had about the enclosure element in RSS in 2001 actually
You'll see that it was all about the last yard and about getting it onto your device
So it'll be ready for you when you want to play it
So you wouldn't have such a crap the experience
Well now you know we're five years five years on
And we've got fiber rolling out and certainly in other parts of the world
There's plenty of bandwidth
And of course there eventually will be an iPod or an iPod like device
That understands well in fact the Nokia and 91 that I demoed for you
Was already you know already getting there
You'll just be connected and you just say give me that podcast
And you'll click on the equivalent of a web link
And it'll start coming in and there'll be so much bandwidth available
So it'll come in really fast and start playing
So there will be no degradation in the experience of click and weight
Which is why this whole time-shifting part was put into place
Now of course there are still many valid reasons for downloading it to a device first
But I think that we'll see you know if we can actually afford it on airplanes as well
Ah excuse me sense it here
This sense say a moment
Brought to you by crap willow.podshow.com
That's right my sister called
And actually I called her just to say hi
She's an Italy and she said you know now you got this damn pod show thing going
I decided to sign up and I did my first podcast and it's fantastic
Now she tried to use cast blaster
But her microphone wasn't working on her PC
So she used her MP3 players internal microphone to record
I think she then loaded that file up into cast blaster
And then another pod safe song and she used one of the electronics effects
It was really cool to hear it
And I guess she used the you know the upload to the pod show servers
Because it seemed to work her podcast is at Italy.podshow.com
And it's fun it's a man the whole family's getting into this
What is going on with the curries should we be
We be
worried
Hey, Adam this is zero mother and don't care a lot
I'll listen to the source code
May not be the right voice now for this, but we're signing up for a cocktail
Plus get money account click down the read terms and conditions when I was signing up
Send me to a page I went back had a similar level of registration
Uh, might be good to have a little pop up window there instead
Just want to let you know thanks that side, but it's awesome. It's going to be a blast
Keep it up
Look for the expanding model
What what was that? What do you say at the end?
Yeah, the last
Keep it up
Look for the expanding model
Well, Brad we would have flopped too
Fantastic
That's a bug. We got to fix that. Dolly noted. Thank you
It's seven it's no I
Why did I congratulate you on your launch of
I show plus
I've recently come to the conclusion that there's really two types of people
In life and there's uh, there's the ones who want and desire things
And and then there's the ones who go get
And with what you've done is obviously with what you've done for podcasting
And what you've done now for creating this this delicious blend of social network
Combined with audcasters and podcasting
It's really inspiring and I just wanted to congratulate you
And being a person that to me is inspiring to really go out there and get it
And get something done rather than sitting on a couch
And saying wouldn't it be cool if you know that
That's just really someone I wanted to
So personally in the phone say thank you for what you've done
So have a great time. Keep up the podcasting
I listen all the time and talk to you soon
Dude, you gave me a semi. Thank you
Dude, speaking of that
What's this this whole thing this this bone thing going on between CC Chapman and
Peter
Which of course is a blatant promotion to try and get you to go and pre-register for our game show
Bone.podshow.com
And as I discussed just earlier click on an episode
Or from that front page you can get it you can get the podcast just click on
Get it if you're registered and signed in log bin
And you can get the feeds from any of the episode pages now
After
CC and PW did their little WrestleMania throw down
Someone else is added to the mix
Okay boys
I have had enough
I just got two more emails about you as a first
PW
CC stop it and stop it now
I know there's a problem on a quantity is
You can see that they're talking about a fight and the one and the other
And saying bad things about one and the other
Then the bone and one and the other what is that about
Don't beat Bowling one and the other
Stop it
I mean it
It just hurts me. We go fishing every summer
We've done it for 14 years
He's always get a lot as a matter of fact
You both can't up on me and make fun of me
I don't tear
I don't die
You hear me bad talking about y'all
No
Cause I love you
And it's love one another
Now you stop it
Now you know what I'll do
And don't you make me
Come over and take my belt off
Because you know what you see
Remember two summers ago
When Adam Curry was a fussing with that man
That they were a gas place where he gets gas for the boat
I took my belt off and looked here
Let me taste them
How we are dead
Stop it
Stop it now
We'll see it
Is that Biodneasle son?
Boom.potshow.com
It's PotShow's brand new game show
Kicking off very soon
I think there's a promo up there now
Think you'll like it in the first round
The first episode of Bond
It's a CC Chapman
Throwing down against peda
The sad light repair man
And I believe that we'll also
Well, I'm pretty sure
We're going to get one of those shows on to serious stars
If you're listening to the daily source code there
This is the pod show block
Bringing you the best in pod casting
Taking up to 10 o'clock this evening
Pacific Coast Hellway is coming up next
If you want to join in the fun
Come on over to podshow.com
Or if you just want to
Listen to the rest of this podcast
Which we simply don't have time for
Because of the satellite medium
The linear way in which it operates
Go to daily source code.com
And download the rest of the show there
Let's see
What's else I was talking about
Oh yeah about developers
This is why we had developers
We were handing out golden tickets
We wanted them to come into podshow
I'll be done in a second with the podshow talk
We wanted to get them in early
So they could start creating these modules
And I'm thinking now
I know tons of different ideas
For modules that I just love to see
That I wanted an module
You know is one of these elements you can put on
Your on your page at podshow.com
And before I talk about the two that I want
Put your right hand in the air
Not take the split file
Okay, and wave goodbye to all our friends
On serious stars 102
PCH is next for you
So I'd love to have a
What I'm listening to right now
That would be so cool
If you could go to my page
You could see what show I was listening to at that
Very moment that could be a module
Or something else I thought of
If I'm if I'm listening to a show
And I want to you know put a message about that
I want to promote it on my page
I'd love to have some kind of module for that as well
You know where you click something
And then you can type in a little bit of text
And then it goes straight into a predesignated spot
But there's just tons of things we can come up with
And apparently it's fairly simple
If you go to developer.podshow.com
There's an SDK available
Excuse me
This and say a moment
Brought to you by bone
The new game show from podshow
Bone.podshow.com
And then finally
And this is something that's
That has just been kind of
Slipping through the cracks
If you've created a channel
Which means when you get a podcast
You can select a place to put it
A channel as what we call it
On the left hand side
I'm just going to go to my collection right now
So I can represent it properly
On the left hand side of
Each channel on the
There's a little bar there that has the channel name
There's a little white down arrow
And it's clearly it's not obvious enough
But if you click that it expands the entire channel
And gives you a whole bunch of different options
Just like when clicking on an episode of the podcast
From there
You can subscribe to it in iTunes
You can actually manage it
Put it into other channels
But you can also hit the play channel button
Now when you hit the play channel button
Guess what?
Exactly
It plays all of the podcast in that channel
With the most recent one being first
Back to back in the dashboard
And of course you can do the same
With Windows Media Player
Of course it's not going to download
Play all of those podcasts as fast as they can come
Barely into you
So that's something you might want to check out
It's a R.A. Potshoe plus tip of the day
So I told you my sister called me and she told me about her podcast
And about her page on Potshoe
And then she said by the way
Just so you know
I'm a scruncher
Hey Adam
This is Shui from
It was a telephone amp
I wanted to tell you about the youngsters
I am a scruncher
I take three or four
I don't know the blue
Kind of squares that are preferring
I take off their scrunches
Gather and light my ass
And make sure I'm squeaky clean
Yeah
That also might be the fact
That I'm an unruly teenager
I don't know
Yep
Just calling it to let you know that I'm a scruncher
Thanks
Thank you
That's good information
So we've got two American scrunchers now
And we've got one European scruncher
Where are the folders?
I'm Chris from Nashville
Just been listening to your
D.S.C.
The gang spurs is the Brits
Yeah, I'm a scruncher
I just want to let you know
That's such an intimate detail to fill me in on
But I'm so appreciative of it
And Leo Vagoda sent me a fantastic link
And this is of course this is truly what we needed
There is a website and I'll put a link into the show notes
Of course
Scruncher or folder.com
And we're tallying it up
Who's a folder?
Who's a scruncher?
Go to scroo to scruncher.no scruncher or folder.com
How do a couple of the
extraneous things here?
Oh yeah, once I've been using Google
Reader for probably half a year
Now at least that imported my
My opml subscription list into it a long time ago
And they went through a lot of interface
Crap
But they've changed a lot of stuff now
And now you don't have to dig down 15 levels
To actually add a subscription
Or to manage them or to delete them
And you can easily find all postings within one subscription
And it's got a lot of really good Ajax stuff
So even your scroll wheel works in the scroll
In the scroll area of the stories
And it's kind of like a river of news concept
So you know, and it has some kind of relevancy
Magic behind it
I'm really enjoying it
It is definitely getting me the stuff that I'm
Most interested in reading
I do want to mention that
And yes, I got a call from our sales department
From Greg
The Sales Weasel
And he said, yeah, man
We've got this promotion running for a little man
The movie and actually I'm going to go take a look at
Let me go look at a little man right now
And he says they have a podcast
Hold on
Littlemanpodcast.com
Let me just go there
I think something actually plays when you hit the page
Let me see
I remember
Yeah, what is it?
Oh, it's the way in brothers
Marlin Wayne, Sean Wands
And it's a new movie called Littleman
And it starts on
It's in theaters July 14th
And so they have this podcast
Let's just see, well here's the show
This is the trailer, I think
The trailer of the movie
Let's watch it together, shall we?
I'll see what he has that
Let's see, maybe the audience will be good
The audio will be good enough for you
In the world of crime
There is no one
Where lesbians, where comfortable shoe
Spopee
You've got to put on the card
And you'll bout to get one in your butt
Sorry, cow
Now he's back in action
And going for the score of a lifetime
That's what I'm talking about
But something is about to go
The queen's diamond is gone
Terribly
And to finish the job
This is very silly
The digital
Now what?
We go get it
They got silly
You'll have to, I like the music
I've got a plan, yo
You're good
In someone else's crib
Honey
Look, I'm like God
It's a big thing
Go, go, go, go
From director, King and Ivory Wands
You know what?
This is so silly
I bet you this is going to be the summer blockbuster
The National Geographic sort of way
The guys who brought you white chicks
Another fine movie
Have a good night's sleep
Creamy
Oh, it's buttermilk
Yeah, right
There's a special bundle of joy
I'm going to show you how great it is to have a day
I'm you're going to show me what it's like to be a day
Okay
So anyway, so they want me to talk about the
Talk about the movie
And I said I can't talk about the movie
Because I haven't seen the movie
And I can't recommend the movie
If I haven't seen it
So they're going to try and get me a copy of it
As soon as possible
Probably one of those that like sent to the Academy of
Motion pictures, arts and sciences
So you can vote on it
Some hide doubt this is going to win in the Academy Award
Oh, by seeing
Buying
Oh, yeah
Come way in
Who were me
You were an animal last night
You've never done that before
The little guy
Little man
Okay
You know what? On a day like today
When it's episode 420
Yeah, I think that would be the perfect movie
To go and see
Alright, littlemanpodcast.com
And show
As soon as I've seen the movie
I'll let you know
Uh, see what else we're going to talk about
Rocket Boob
Yeah, that's next
New host for the Rocket Boomb podcast
Yeah, play the intensity
Listen, I was just listening to your comments about Rocket Boomb
And uh, you know what?
It's supposed to happen in Rocket Boomb
I think it's going to go down
Uh, I mean an X
MTV DJ
He's doing a podcast
Come on
No way that can work
Anyway, give up a good work
Fuck you soon
I agree
XMTVVJ's doing podcast
We'll never fly
It's a stupid idea
It just can't happen
Yeah, show was good
You know, she's she's the interim host
Is now what she's being built as
She's a co-owner named Joanne
I've never seen her on an MTV
Hold on a second
Let me just go to Rocket Boomb.com
That's the great name
Rocket Boomb three syllables
Always good
What's her name again?
Joanne Colon
Colon
How does she say?
Does she say Colon or Colon?
Uh, who cares?
Uh, she's cute
She's good
You know, she's professional
Uh, this is, you know, MTV
People who work at MTV
Or have worked at MTV
The MTV truly is
The purest form of gorilla television
The budgets are so incredibly low
It's not the MTV video musical words of course
But, you know, this is the segments
You know, these are taped in sequence
One after another
The videos are inserted later
So you're kind of pretending that you just saw the video
Some of the live shows, of course, is different
Obviously
Um, so there's a lot of pretending that you just saw something
The vibe is really what you create
On the studio floor itself
Because it's pretty dead stuff to do
Um, and particularly stuff on the road
You know, you know, the whole
What we used to call the wookie cam
It's like the tilting left
And then tilting right
And then moving in and moving back
That was developed because
MTV couldn't afford
Or wouldn't provide steady cams
And so it's, it's much easier
Um, you know, what we say
In the, in the music business
Actually, if you can't cover it up
Turn it up
So, you know, it's very hard to keep a steady shot
Um, when someone's doing a stand-up
Somewhere on location
Um, and that's why steady cams are so beautiful
And particularly the type of locations
MTV goes to the lot of shaking going on
Um, so camera men just started doing this thing
You know, the in and out zoom
And the left and right tilt
I have a feeling that maybe it was Warren
Who was one of our camera men
He may have started that in the studio
I'm not too sure
I think I, I think member Warren doing it first
And then all the freelance guys got into it
Because it also made it much easier for them
You know, hey man, why should I have to have a really steady hand
When I can do all this wookie cam stuff
Same with the jump cut
Um, MTV, you know, I think that they either didn't have the equipment
To make great transitions
Um, and probably didn't have the, I got a sneeze
Hold on
Ah, excuse me
Ah, I was looking at the light
And I heard you saying bless you
Don't do that when someone asked the sneeze
Oh, I'm sorry
That was, perhaps disgusting
I mean it that way
The jump cut
Um, developed an MTV, you know, just lack of knowledge
And lack of tools I think
And it turned into an art form
And people said all sudden like, well, that jump cut thing
We were taught in film school that we weren't supposed to do
It actually, well, it actually turns out
It's pretty cool
Um, it's anyway back to Joanne Colon
Colon, Colon just doesn't sound right
Um, she's a great job
And, but I think kind of the appeal
The, the underground
Um, non-professionalism of a man
I think that team, you know, that
To me was more appealing than any, any other part of her, or her, her appearance
Although that's nice too
Um, but, you know, it was a combination of things
Combination
So, we'll see, we'll see where it goes
So far so good, I would say
And, you know, I'm really waiting to see when a man is going to do
She can totally, um, go on to do great things
Uh, I do think she should start going
Because I do know that
It's all about the timing
And it's all about the talent
And the right talent put together
You've got to have the right team
And you've got to tiger your way through
Uh, and I think that the news is getting old
And she better start capitalizing on it pretty quickly
Uh, then just briefly something that, uh,
A number of people sent to me
Uh, it's a BBC story
And of course, I will link to that in the show notes
Opening it up right now
The, uh, UK's independent music labels
Now want to charge
Um, so they want, they want the law changed
So internet service providers become liable
For illegal file sharing by their users
This is the association of independent music
Uh, and they've outlined an entire plan
Um, about copyright reform
And they call this actually an innovative answer
An innovative answer
So the whole idea is
They want the your internet service provider
To pay them a licensing fee
And somehow apparently track what we're sharing
Even if it's illegal and to have them pay for it
It's a stupid
That's fucking stupid
Jesus Christ, you're open
It'll never happen first of all
We are opening yourself up
Because the law clearly states that they're, uh,
Conduit, you know, they're just a pass through provider
There's not their responsibility
But, you know, you do this
And you actually push that law through somehow
And in the UK it appears that you can pretty much, you know,
Buy your seat in government these days
Just by providing a loan to one of the parties
Um, you want to push that through
I mean, then everyone who has any type of copyright
Is going to turn right to the ISPs
And you'll shut it down
This is worse than any so-called net neutrality
Debacle, uh,
A annihilation of the internet
This will totally bring it down
And it's stupid
And the things that I'm reading in this article
He had the innovative answer
Uh, let me just find some of these quotes here
Just really bug me
Mmm
David Ferguson, chairman of the British Academy of Composers
And songwriters said quote
Professional composers and songwriters
Are only able to produce new music
If they are paid for their work
That's such bullshit
Cry-key
That is, you, all of a sudden you take a whole group of people
Who are just as talented
But certainly no more talented than podcasters for instance
Who also create a product
In fact, we create a lot more product
And saying, you know, if you don't get paid
Then you can't, you can't make your art
And it's bull crap
You know it is
Oh, it's so, uh,
Ignorant
You know, even from a technological standpoint
There's no way to document it
And police it
And, uh, but to say, you know, this is an innovative answer
To the problem
And these, and this is the independent music labels
Please
Get a grip on reality
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Ah, then one final thing for today
This is really nice
A Nielsen study came out
Which is, I have a PDF of it here
Podcasting gains an important foothold amongst
U.S. adult online population
Now Nielsen are the guys that, uh,
That really are the benchmark for billions of
Dollars worth of advertising money
Around the globe
So, uh, I'll just read the first paragraph here
Nielsen that ratings a global leader
And internet media and market research
By the way, owned by VNU, a Dutch company
An ounce today, and this is nice, that 6.6% of the U.S. adult online population
Or 9.2 million web users
Have recently downloaded an audio podcast
4% or 5.6 million web users
Have recently downloaded a video podcast
And then they have a whole table here
And they've got all kinds of breakout stats
Uh, these figures put the podcasting population on par
With those who publish blogs
Uh, 4.8% and online data is 3.9%
Interesting
How we're podcasting is not yet nearly as popular
As viewing and paying bills online
Which is, uh, one of the most popular activities on the internet
51.6% online job hunting 24.6%
So, they go through, um, they go through a lot of stuff here
And, uh, there's already, uh, people are picking up
Some of the statistics and saying, well, it turns out that
People who listen to audio podcasts
Most of them use Safari
Uh, as the number one browser
That would automatically make a lot of audio listeners
Mac users
That's interesting
But I'd like to know where they got their data from
Uh, number two is Firefox
And, uh, really trailing way behind is, uh, internet explorer
Now for video podcasts
Um, the numbers even a little bit higher
But still the same ranking Safari Firefox internet explorer
I really, I should figure out where they
Where they got their data from
Um, okay, and then they, you know, then they say, you know, here
The sites that these people go to
And, uh, and that's pretty funny here
It is, um, here, top content and e-commerce sites
Visited by podcasters
This is the US home and work
Um, people who listen to, well, it says audio podcasters
Hmm
Oh, this is podcasters, okay
Well, this, I think that's what they're saying
So if I understand the verb, it's correctly
The top content and e-commerce sites
Visited by podcasters
That means people who create podcasters
Uh, on the audio side
Their top site is Mac world
Then it's a wired news slash dot
Multiple e-commerce sites
Niketown.com
Apple and iTunes
And video podcasters
This is the astounding number
Video podcasters
All seem to go to startrek.com
Follow by live thricks365.com
That makes a lot of sense
Because, uh, that's a streaming
Uh, a streaming content provider
Fark.com, because of course, a lot of these
Video podcasters, humorous and cynical
And, uh, and based on the topical
News of the day
Then the e-commerce sites e-music
And also Niketown.com
What the hell is going on at Niketown
Won't you take me to Niketown
Let's see, what the hell is it
Why is Niketown so popular
Oh, on Niketown.com
Oh, this is going to be something really good here
What the hell happens at Niketown
Oh, you know what?
So you hit Niketown and there you see
I think this data is bogus
I don't know
Oh, I sound a Canadian there, didn't I?
So that's the iPod that connects to your shoes
I don't know, man
They're me, you know, when you put it all together
And you see that it's
Mac people going to
Macworld.com using the Safari browser
And going to Niketown
But it does appear from the data provided
It does appear that Mac people
seem to be doing more podcasting than windows people
Which I really like as a statistic
And you know why?
Exactly
Because that means when the windows people catch on
Those numbers are really good
Super hot, late com
One more song for today
Some about it, you know, sexism reverse
Let me say yeah, perfect Charlie material
Oh, it's a super hot, late com
From the podcast using that work on your daily source
Don't want to take it
I can't pay the fine
Don't want to go to coma
I ain't got the time
But there's a late com
It driving me driving me
Out of my mind
Won't you stop writing that ticket
Won't this hundred?
Help you change your mind
What to do with them now?
Handcuffs, you're pretty late
I thought that you and me could reach a compromise
Super hot, late com
One more song for today
Let me say yeah, perfect
Super hot, late com
You can't pay the fine
So you got my license
And I'm a registration
So you got me going
Close to 69
That might be illegal
And for the seventh day
I can't help myself
Not my york, don't mind
Super hot, late com
Mama york, don't mind
Late com
Wow, super hot, late com
You can't pay the fine
She had a nice set of guns
30,80 least
And as we talked
I got into trouble when I tried to steal my piece
See how I was sticking to myself if I
I played my car grind
I hope you get sprung
By the end of the night
I worked my way out of this situation
And now I'm thinking I shouldn't pay the fine
As a stepped in the van
I heard a telepartner
If the party wagons rocking
No, come on, now get us
You can't pay the fine
I love the super hat made in Calvary
You said I fell super hot made in Calvary
The tone is super hot made in Calvary
I can't hear myself made in the super hot made in Calvary
You got me now made the super hot made in Calvary
Well not super hot made in Calvary
I got there the super hot made in Calvary
One more style super hot made in Calvary
Found me you are so super hot
Super hot made in Calvary
You super hot lady Cobb Bow Hall winding up another episode of the Charlie
Which I hope to get up online as soon as possible
I just noticed all of our servers are down
So I guess the wonders of beta and so it goes
Tomorrow the thank god it's Friday edition of the daily source code
Hope to see you here. Thank you very much for listening
Check out daily source code dot com or addem dot pod show dot com or curry dot com or
Or whatever, you know just send it to me addem at curry dot com
Bye bye
Another pod show podcast
Stick it in your ear
Or twenty
Get this pod cast and more great ones like it on the high performance pod cast delivery network from pod show and lime light networks
I love it