Potcho is pleased to bring you the following killer content direct from the all new feature-richpotcho.com
Get it, play it, dig it
Adam Curry and the daily source code is on the air. Delta Sierra Charlie 510.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
You criticize the way I talk, you can't know how I feel, yeah yeah
I'll sit for the best with your dark nature, you don't know what that takes, no, no
It's a matter of time now, get it to see, for a turn in your dark enemy, hear a voice that keeps on telling me
I'm free, free of the drama, free from the drama, free of the peace, free of the pain
You can't face a title, demons, a world cup is a rain, but not now
You suck the light fire of every room, how much can I take, I don't know
Not a flower that merges into the touch, so beautiful but it takes so much of the light the light inside of me
I'm free, free of the drama, free from the drama, free of the peace, free of the pain
I'm free of the drama, free of the pain, the moment we miss, I was free
free, free of the drama, free from the drama, free of the peace, free of the pain
I was free, free of the drama, free from the drama, free of the peace, free of the pain
I'm free of the drama, free of the pain, the moment the moment we miss, I was free of the pain
I'm free of the drama, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain
I'm trying to make my microphone louder, but I'm not succeed, I'll work on that during the next
day, I'm free of the drama, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain
I'm free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain
I'm free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain
I'm free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain
free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free, of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the loss, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain, free of the pain,
To keep a car on the road even the Department of Motor Vehicles not a place you want to go necessarily, but you know
It's automated it's systemated it's hydromated and you can get your shit done if you want to
So we've had the the Jaguar in the UK for a year now and
You know the I've renewed the the insurance and they have this thing which is the license tax
And you know the car comes well when I bought it they just got an a license a tax disc
Which is basically the sticker that you put on your on your windshield and it expired
It expired in November
So I have to get a new tax disc and you get a thing in the mail
That what does it cost like soren or tax or what I basically you can choose by
Between paying the tax and getting a new tax disc for the next 12 months
So you can drive legally on the road or you can declare it off road and you have to fill out certain papers
And this will any can't be on the street if it's in your garage or whatever
So you know I took the car to the dealer. I got the MOT tests. You know a test that I guess is for the
I don't know MOT was a stand for
Ministry of transportation
So you know it the car complies I have this certificate. I have my inch and I read the instructions on the letter
They sent me which was filled with all kinds of yellow and blue colors and lots of tiny letters and I really
Concentrated on it and it's that you know here's what you need you need to send off the originals the original
Certificate of insurance the original MOT certificate and your check for I don't know what is it?
It's something like 100
100 pounds whatever it is and then they'll send you back a tax disc
So I did this before I left and I just got an email from Patricia when I got up this morning
They sent it back. They're really good at sending shit back to me including my money
You know, please refer to the conversation about me trying to pay for the for the speeding ticket
Which they also sent back and you know, they won't do it until I have an official
UK license so that they can then subsequently deduct points from my license
They sent it back saying that I had to supply the the car log book
What the hell is that car log? I don't keep a log on my car. What are I gonna do? What is the official car log book?
You know, I don't even have to do that for my aircraft
So please help me, Brits tell me what to do
I don't want to get a thousand pound fine for driving around with the wrong tax disc
It's frustrating very frustrating. I just don't understand the system. Please help sign your your buddy
Adam
Time to get the ass back in shape been sitting on an a lot of course on the airplane, so I got to firm it up
Adam, how are you? I'm good. They've got a firm up the acid bit today. I know you've been traveling this week
So I thought we'd take this opportunity to stretch your glute muscles. Oh my glutes. Yes, okay
Betching is very important part of working out. You know, okay
What are we gonna do? Okay, grab your wireless. We're gonna be on the floor. Okay. I don't have the wireless. I'm gonna I'll use the
This one on on the floor
Okay, now lay down on your back. All right, I'm on my back. Knees back be flat on the ground. Yes, ready
Now take the left leg and cross it over the right leg put in your left cap on the thigh of the right leg
I'm glad you sent me a picture
That's your arms and grab the underneath side of the right thigh and pull it towards your stomach
Oh, oh take deep breaths. I see what this is now take your left leg down and bring the right leg up to the left
Switch the left cap is over the right back. I got it. Okay, grab underneath the left thigh and bring it towards your stomach
Okay, forget to breathe. Yes, I'm breathing and bring the right leg down
Don't you feel refreshed? Yeah, oh, yeah, it's a great way to improve your blood flow
Feel so refreshed
Have a good stay in San Francisco. That's it. We're not to avoid me the whole trip this time. Oh, Amy
Have a great weekend everybody and don't forget to check out my shows
Fitness stuff podshow dot com. That's a side until next time
Amy well first of all that was that was kind of easy. I only had to do one on each side that's all
I feel you know like I didn't really have a good workout and of course
I'm not trying to ignore you Amy
In fact this morning the first thing I do when I walk in is I'm gonna come in there and I'm gonna plant a big one right on your sugar
Whatever that is
We've talked about the the strip podcast
It's a fine podshow podcast emanating from Las Vegas Nevada and because the guys are in Las Vegas and they are very
You know, keyed into into the industry there. I should say the entertainment business
They get a lot of superstars appearing on their show usually via phone in you know call, but it's
It's exactly how it's supposed to work. You know, it's such a stealth show. I love it because I don't think the people
Who who are interviewed often realize the reach of this show and these guys are getting press all the time for the outrageous things these
See leberties
Say on their show
Who do we remember we did a whole thing about Chubby checker, but
Dennis Miller
Everyone who comes in the Vegas they all the oh, yeah, well we'll do this little the some kind of internet thing here
That's what I could just hear the press agent right? Yeah, there's some kind of internet show
I just want you to call in and it'll be really nice and you know, it's just a local in Vegas
Well, of course, it's not and they had the half on David Hasselhoff on the strip the strip dot podshow dot com
And
He is he's Mr. Cyberhoff
He's coming to take over
He's getting ready to do some podcast then right now
I'm thinking about doing my own television series on the internet really why not
If I've got P if I you got a Google me and sometimes there's anywhere from one million to 15 million people
That are hitting me daily if I've got that audience
Then why shouldn't I do my own television series but not doing an hour? I'm not gonna do an hour
I'll do it like a five-minute series
You want to have people and then get the financing like I did for Baywatch through
A major company like
Whatever Coca-Cola master quote would it be about and and get these people to finance it and I can do like you know
Secret agent man or or not so secret agent man or something funny or travels with behalf and then just do a five-minute TV series and get it advertised why not
Now, let me tell you something that's fucking cool. Let's get the half on the podshow
Oh
Man, let me just I got to turn up the volume a little bit on the the output device there for some reason that was a really soft bit
So wait a minute, so you know
Just like he did with I don't did he do that with Baywatch? I know that the Baywatch basically failed and then it made it big in the overseas market
I I didn't I thought that there was another producer there
I could be I think
The way the way it worked and I've made hassle half a couple times. I just can't remember the entire store
I know he told it he told to me. I think what happened was
On Baywatch I wasn't going anywhere and they basically could barely pay
Salary for the actors and he said I just give me a piece of the show
I believe in it and he probably didn't have anything else to do with the time and
And then of course it took off became one of the
Indicates and international syndication successes of the 80s and I had made everybody very wealthy who was involved
So it sounds to me like what he's saying is he wants to do a five-minute show every single day or week or who cares
And he wants an advertiser to underwrite it half
half on the podshow
Oh, totally gonna make it happen strip strip guys get me his number get me in touch with the half god dammit
Listen, you've been talking a while now for how the media changes things
To make certain things look a certain way
And well great news you roll over the news yet today after at least the show there's news yet today
The things that happened to Patricia the fall from the chair and
What they did on CZ is actually they cut out the piece of the bell for Charlie
Daily source call the least and
They they made a comment about about about the husband flying with his private jet
And I didn't know it's just now what I had had a jet
But still that proves again that they
Always make things worse or make shoes or make bigger than you normally should sound the diff day
When you listen to the the data source code a lot you know about
About your plan, you know what kind of airplane it is and that's it's a regular turbo prop thing
We have a lot of problems with it. We actually have to blow in your holes and tubes and stuff
To get things you could get things going
But according to Dutch national show business news TV you have a you have a private jet
They well, they didn't mention the word near jet yet, but they made it sound like a hat one
Just letting you know
Oh, dude, thank you so much. Okay. Yeah, this is great. I appreciate the the report
So this was on the was it on Friday show where Patricia and I maybe was Monday show Monday show
Patricia and I talked about about her fall during her rehearsals for dancing with the star
So apparently the Dutch show business new like kind of like some of the entertainment tonight. I guess
On television they they picked up arm the podcast and and they played a piece of it and and they said that
Now I take a little bit of a fence to what you're saying about about the Delta Sierra the Delta Sierra being my lovely
Sess no one a two retractable
Argy
Yes, sometimes you got to blow into its tubes to make sure she's function improperly
But it isn't that some monkey plane is a proper aircraft, you know
It's uh, it's got autopilot IFR all that stuff. It's it's a real airplane
It ain't no jet
But that is kind of interesting how they pumped that up a misdemeanor flew himself in his private jet
By the way, Sess no makes fantastic jet aircraft the Sess no citation series
You might want to take a look at those not bad at all
But yeah, I guess I guess they just wanted to make it sound better. There you go
And by the way, you made a mistake, too. It is not a turbo prop. It is a
constant speed propeller
Which is a little different than a turbo prop
Turbo prop actually would be a jet engine with a propeller
But that's okay. We all make mistakes, you know, even the show business guys aren't perfect
Keep our eye on the situation though for them damn liars
I guess the the only thing I'd like to say about that is uh throughout the years I've learned the only thing that is really truthful
On television and in the newspaper are the advertisements
Really like me and I just want to think the academy
But there's no
Okay, well, I just want to thank the foreign press
No foreign press what the
Who chose these k*** awards
Well, that's f*** great
What the f*** is going all around this f*** place
Well, at least I get a trophy
This what oh
This whole bloody thing this whole tally thing is just a bunch of sh*** isn't it
Oh, he did me I've been knighted by Adam curry. Oh, and that criminally in 17th song
Yeah, what do you freaking do? Yeah, now I've gotten a white show. I mean who the f*** has jersey time think he is
Oh, alright, this is my favorite stand on
That's the first annual jersey touch your award subscribe at jerseyton dot poncho dot com
JT from jersey doing that wacky thing again. All right. How do I get in how do I get on these awards? I did I have I won nothing this year
Absolute I was not nominated. I won nothing
The sounds to me like this is the Kanye or what kind of award show where I might be able to get in on the ground floor and actually have a shot at winning something
So let me know if you nominate
to
Gary Alexander and I am Colin from Las Vegas have a question for you. I
Host the podcast called the ultimate podcast, which is a podcast based on mixed martial arts
UFC the ultimate fighting competition
Actually the ultimate fighting championship
To be exact, but the question is this is that I have had some people go to my iTunes site and leave some negative comments
But it's kind of suspicious because the comments are not just negative
They actually promo another show
Like this guy sucks
You should listen to this show and then they give the name of the other show
So I didn't know if this is some way that I might be able to remove that from iTunes
granted the other the other podcast directories and listings
Do not have that
I do not have that problem there
But just want to find out from you first of all, it's actually commenting and it's obviously shitty and
Really don't appreciate it, but
So I'm trying to find out anyone else has had that issue. Thanks a lot, and
Thanks for the garlic mate. Yeah, you know
I think that's a strategic mistake on Apple's part
They open that up so that anyone can comment on the show and and I've seen this happen all over the place
I'm sure that it's happened to more people it's happened. It's go look at daily source code at
On iTunes. Oh, there's some real nice stuff there. Yeah, people using that to basically promote
Their show and we'll do that on any any podcast in the category so you're in the ultimate fighting
Championship the UFC that that's your bag and
People are trying to promote their own show probably off of your back. I think that's a big mistake
And we've had this conversation about pod show plus and pod show plus people can indeed review
Your show
But you are allowed it's your site. You are allowed to remove the review. You know, it just doesn't you know
It doesn't make any sense because you can't control that kind of stuff and it really sucks ass
So I don't think it's a way you can take it off, but I want to say I believe
100% in in what you're doing in the the ultimate fighting championship and I and I really want to invite you to join the the pod show
Network so
I'll have Richard Brewer hey give you a call
That is if he's listening to the show
Of course, that'll be a great test. Yeah, wouldn't it if you've got a call from him or not? I'm wondering if Richard will listen
So I can't help you with iTunes, but I may be able to help you with a couple other things looking forward to talking to you
Hey, I'm Jason from Tennessee
Just listen to the
2006 buzz out loud from seeing that pod test
Need to check it out. I think a good friend college blogger is had left a message for them
Concerning the new apple phone and he's not
Discusses a voice so you might want to check it out
You can totally tell it's a comic strip blogger, but it's not the yeah
Discuss voice
Okay, I'll bite he sent a longer clip of
of the show and and a sound clip of the the so called the guy who should be
Comics strip blogger who called it
Let's have a listen. Oh, we talked yesterday about the idea that people could hack into a cell phone turn on the mic and listen to your conversations without your knowledge
We talked about taking a battery out as a way to prevent that and then suppose that the only way around that would be to hide a second battery in there
That's pretty interesting actually
I've got to go listen to the show. I want to find out how I can listen other people's calls. This next color points out is that we missed something
A clue to that whole situation in our very own podcast. Okay
Hi guys, I can't believe how you felt to connect the dots on Monday's podcast. No, that's not comic strip blogger
I yeah sure he he made disguise as voice on this show, but that doesn't sound like him at all. Let's listen again
You were mentioning how we're rogue intelligence agency could manage no no no that's not CSV and besides
I think if he made it onto another show he'd be the first one to point it out
In here on your trust the UK listeners just wants to leave you a comments response. So your commitment
So have pod show protect the
Patent of podcasting
pod specifically pod catching
I applaud your sentiments really good to hear that the hero pod show are fully behind that. Let me just bring up to speed on this
apparently
Apple
file day a patent
on the concept of automatically downloading audio programs and synchronizing them to a mobile player
Basically you know how pod casting started out and so they they filed a patent for this saying that they invented it and we all know
Because it was done out in the open that they did not invent it
So just bringing up to speed on what the sky's talking about
Through the you know getting podcasts into our chains and
Who's setting up pod five on all of that
course
You know reach out through that relationship and see we can get get it discussed and maybe just not so we're in Apple without going through the blood sucking lawyers
You know everyone always seems to want to reach for the lawyers
And put up a legal challenge and obviously I understand why you have to do that but
I will be nice to hear that maybe you try at least try to get to an alternate channel as well and avoid getting a lawyer involved and maybe you're some sort of
Gentleman's agreement in place
That would be good to hear so just one of what your comment on that was
Thanks a lot catch you later. Well, I have a way forward. Thank you. Of course you're a folder
I've I've two comments to make on that number one
This is the United States of America and once someone starts with a legal procedure
Which is exactly what filing a patent or patent is all about it's it's a legal document
The only way to you know ensure that you can stop that is by filing against it and and starting legal proceedings
I like Apple as a company. I don't want to have to go and and do all that
But here's here's the thing that really bugs me go to fucking wiki pedia
Right and look up pod casting and look at all the people who have added their names to the list as the
influencers and and and and and co
Discoverers and inventors of podcasting. Please go do that
And then tell me where are all these cox suckers right now? You know if you really invented podcast thing
Then how come you aren't all over this? I feel that I definitely contributed so I'm gonna stop that as bullshit
You know, and I don't want a patent at all on on on podcast, but I certainly don't want someone else
Who really did not contribute to the process of
The invention of this wonderful system that we have
I don't want them running away with it and then being able to charge anyone who wants to take this idea and and bake it into their own
software and get that bullshit
So where's the outrage?
I think the only the only way to do it is is is to file a legal document
You can basically hold up a patent for a long long time when you do that. I think it's
Probably just the path of least resistance. That's what it is
But again, where's the outrage? I'm looking for that
I'm looking for all these people who claim and had to have co-invented this stuff and been doing it forever
And it was their idea in 1920 go look at Wikipedia go write all those people
Ask them what they're gonna do about this taking place
Very curious to see what happens
Yeah, I'm how you doing this is Chuck from a candy pack cast in the cold city of Chicago, man
So you're in San San that this week that's so cool and you know, I hit you with a few AM emails
I was wondering if man if there's any possibility we've got
John Lennon's anniversary coming up Friday for food bar Friday on the 8th of December John Lennon's
26th anniversary of his death and me and my buddy Jay Gapner who's up on the up on the PMN and I'm actually looking man
It's what a great job you guys is on these I'm pod so
Come on the holiday list here and damn
The song is great is called a soldier's Christmas and it's in John Lennon style man and his glory and
If there's any way you can play fest Friday's touch
Man that would be so great
Would so appreciate we cranked it up last year when when you gave us the call for pod safe music then your feed broke and you know never got played, but
And picked it up over at
Pod safe
Christmas and
I was so happy about that, but man if there's any way you could play it Friday for John Lennon's anniversary that would be smoking
Adam, thank you so much, man
Hey, I'm also to Merrick Airlines too, so I've said you see emails from there
Tellings to you. I'm a folder and I got blessed man peace and wealth. Thank you.
Tailwinds tailwinds back at you. I presume your pots I saw the emails coming
I haven't read them. I saw the subject line because it said Friday food bar so
I figured I'd take a look at that tomorrow within this voice mail came in. Yeah, you know, I've listened that song
Some reason it just doesn't do it for me. I don't know. I'll listen to it again tomorrow, but I think tomorrow being the anniversary of
Was it what was it his birthday? I forgot what you said
Let me see it's probably my email was it was his birthday or was it the anniversary of his death?
No, it's got it
26 anniversary. Okay, here it is. I got your email Fridays DSC content John Lennon's 26 anniversary
Okay, hey, I'll listen to it again, but I think John Lennon would appreciate it more if we just
Told the man to go fuck himself and played some of his music, you know
Think that would make a head of a lot more sense
Feels a lot more right to me if you know what I'm saying
Is everybody box entry to wind up today is Charlie
He's in love with Goldie. Oh, I was technically a virgin back when I was 21. I had a pocket full of rubbers and a pack of
Bubblegum. I could spit in seven colors hit the ceiling with each one
I thought I'd be a million there by the age of 25 then it came to whistle fast before I even blinked and I thought I'd marry me a model
And I'd live a happy life
Born
Here's a come-and-go
I'm still holding on. I want to always let this go
Just like Goldie home
So now I'm biting with the mirror and I'm losing never match
I was suck a bunch of seconds that I tried to turn my back the years are going faster
And they're never gonna last
Go
Here's a come-and-go
I'm still holding on. I want to always let this go
Just like Goldie home
Here's a come-and-go
Well, I'm still holding on. I want to always let this go
Just like Goldie home
I don't need another new year because it's just another day
I don't want another candle on my happy birthday cake
I don't need to be reminded that it's gonna end someday
I'm still holding on. I want to always let this go
Just like Goldie home
If you're out, you just about as pretty as they come
She's done enough to be my girl and all the nuts to be my mom
Just like Goldie home
Here's a come-and-go
Well, I'm still holding on. I want to always let this go
Just like Goldie home
Here's a come-and-go
Well, I'm still holding on. I want to always let this go
Just like Goldie
Bob Gentries Goldie Han from the pod save music network
You can find links to that in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
Okay, so tomorrow will be football Friday fucked up beyond all repair or as some would say recognition
But I think repair works a little bit better
It'll be the end of a twisted week for me. So
Yeah, we'll celebrate and style get your song
Get your songs suggestions in now get them in early and you know
I wouldn't mind a couple more new openers. I don't have anything
Until like a 577 or something like that so I'm you know you can start with 511 starting tomorrow
I would really appreciate it all right out. I'm at podshow.com dailysourcecode.com
I'll talk to you tomorrow everybody take care of yourself
Another podshow podcast stick it in your ear
Yet this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from podshow and line-white networks