Delta Sierra Charli 350.
Georgia!
Hi, this is William Nelson.
Alcohol, prohibition didn't work in the 1920s, and marijuana prohibition isn't working
today.
It's time we stopped arresting responsible marijuana smokers.
It's the fair thing to do.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky in prison.
I'd like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Fantastic, it's battle courage.
Judgment Day 2006.
It's the fair thing to do.
Perfect.
Is.
...
And then then only then will I know and I had to hit the satellite window so I really had to get going on the show.
For those of you who are listening to this on serious satellite and stars, it's the stars cast everybody.
This is the daily source code is just the start of our four hour block of time that we've got here.
We're all not some awesome podcasts after this show.
You will hear Pacific Coast, Hellway.
After that Madge Weinstein with East Radio, Dawn and Drew.
Steve Gilmore checks and I think he's at the E-Tech Conference with the Gilmore Daily.
And then digital flotsome, I believe a new episode today as a PW has been threatening.
And we wind up between, was at 930 in 10 o'clock Eastern Time tonight with Michael Butler with a rock and roll geek show.
I don't know if it's the indie cast or probably the straight up rock and roll geek show.
So you can stay tuned for all of that.
Gosh, man, it's so weird, you know, just not having people are calling the whole day.
Have you heard anything? Have you heard anything? I haven't heard anything.
I don't know. I don't know what to say.
But this morning, I woke up and it was the first thing on my mind to have to say.
So, hey, some, some other, oh, it's okay. So here's the real bummer news.
The real bummer news about today's show.
No audio feedback from comic strip blogger.
Damn, that bums me.
I wish I wish.
He says he's not going to send me any for a while. That's a bummer, man.
I love you. People are finally getting into your CSB seriously.
People want to hear your opinion in that, in that different voice that you have and your accent.
And there's, in general, most people like it.
And then another bummer, I just follow bummers today.
The vacation isn't parallel, my friends.
So there's a half-term vacation period, which really we didn't know about.
This is the first full year that Christina's in school because we, actually, I guess we did know it last year.
But I don't know, maybe we, who knows what happened.
Last year was so close to us moving in that we didn't really pay attention to it.
But it seems like all of Europe has hit the lottery and is traveling to every destination,
Virgin Airlines flies.
I can't buy a ticket, not even to New York, Las Vegas, San Francisco, Los Angeles,
Barbados, Antigua, Dubai.
I mean, God, we've been there and didn't like it very much.
But we just want some sun.
Forget about it.
And then hotel rooms.
Well, sure, Mr. Curry, we found something in Antigua.
The only availability left for two hotel rooms.
Only $5,000 a night.
And of course, I said, does that include a brojo?
Jesus Christ.
So that sucks.
So now we're kind of looking at what we can do in Europe.
Maybe Portugal, maybe, see what else is there.
Portugal is probably the best bet we have.
But still, it's very, very difficult just to find a place to stay at all.
And I said, how is this possible?
And so first of all, I guess this is the British.
The UK has their half-term all at the same time.
In other countries, by the way, they kind of stagger that, which is interesting.
So all of the UK is just flying out.
They're just leaving the island like a mass exodus.
So that's one problem.
But the hotels.
Now, this is very interesting.
So this is what the prices are now for two hotel rooms.
$5,000 a night.
And that's just regular.
That's not a suite.
It's just two hotel rooms.
There are hotel rooms that are going for about $17 or $18,000 a night.
And they're fully booked.
And so I started online, of course.
And I got so frustrated.
I called Carl.
I told you my girl who fixed everything for me and has done many vacations for us.
And she says, well, what's happened is you have mainly Russians.
She said, there's just so many incredibly rich people coming out of the East block.
And of course, you have to wonder how they became rich.
And they don't give a shit.
They're just buying up everything, taking their whole family.
So it's really, it's a capacity problem if you can believe it.
Just unbelievable to me.
So don't know what we're going to do.
I think Patricia, the world record company boss.
I don't want to say he's old, but he's a, he's a X record.
Well, I guess still currently.
She's never really signed with any other record company.
If you don't from co to he owns some hotels in Portugal.
And she's going to give him a call and see if he can fix anything out.
Because I can get a flight arranged down there.
We can work that out.
And even if we, if we had to go, economy class is not all that far.
So it's not such a big deal.
But I think I could probably get an aircraft worked out for us to take down and back up again.
Now some good news.
Although it doesn't work here in the UK yet.
Ryan sent me an email.
There is now a Google chat or Google.
What do they call it?
Is it, let me just see how to take my blackberry out of my pocket.
Actually, it's Google talk, but it's the same thing as a Google chat.
There's an application for the blackberry.
So that you can actually maintain your, your Google chats on your blackberry.
I'm very excited about it.
Unfortunately, it doesn't work on non-US networks.
That's to be either a US or a Canadian network.
So I'll have to try that next week when I'm in San Francisco.
Looks like I'm going out on Tuesday.
And we'll be there for, let's see, a good work week.
So about 10 days, that'll be out on the west coast.
And we've, of course, we've got lots of cool things planned.
Cali's coming out.
Cali's coming out to Cali.
We're going to do something together.
Yeah, I was just listening to the penis episode 349.
Oh, excuse me, I mean the Charlie episode 349.
And I just want to have one comment.
As far as I'm concerned, you could call it what my mother called my penis,
which was the jingle bell.
This is Mike signing off from Oakland, California.
Hey, parents, please tell your kids what it's called, okay?
This is ridiculous.
This is really stupid.
What's wrong with the actual words, huh?
The actual name of the pieces of the anatomy, penis, vagina, breasts, nipple.
Oh, in other words, you can hardly say on television in the US.
Yesterday, one of my ego filters trapped a posting from a reporter
from the OC, the Orange County Register, who had heard rumors that I would be
showing up at the meetup last night.
The Orange County podcast is meetup.
And, yeah, I was like, whoa, so I posted a comment on the web
log and said, hey, I don't know where you're getting the information
from, but I'm in the UK, and I'm definitely not showing up.
And it was very confusing.
And finally, we boil it all down, we figured it out,
how the information stream got mangled onto the web,
and I got some feedback about it today.
Hey, Adam, Corey, scriptener here from the buddy group
and the Orange County podcasters meetup group.
And just wanted to say thank you for being understanding, patient,
and responding to the Orange County Register reporter
that contacted you regarding the claims they made
that you were coming here, even though you're in the UK,
to the United States meeting.
It's, we learned a valuable lesson tonight.
What we learned was that no matter what you say about
Pod Show, and then a lot of other things that you talk about
that are great that are happening in the world,
the only thing they hear is Pod Show.
Adam, Corey, big hair, blonde, flowing locks.
So anyhow, thanks for being cool.
And of course, you're always welcome at the Orange County podcasters
meetup group if you're ever in the area.
Make sure you bring Mark, your Shemotor Nemkov down to
because he's a cool dude, and we'd like to see him here.
He's a dead man.
Keep up the good work.
We'll talk to you later.
He's a dick.
I got to bring Mark, your Shemotor Nemkov.
He's a guy who's trying to set up Pod Show LA.
He's got like some, you know, he has some cockamamey plan
about setting up some kind of production thing
in Los Angeles.
He's got a shack on Venice Beach and, you know,
in a laptop.
And he's playing Mr. Big Shot.
He's got a three series BMW.
But no problem buddy about the rumor mill.
That's alright.
I'm happy to help.
I just didn't want people to think I was a dick
for not showing up.
That's all.
And believe me, that happens a lot.
Aloha.
If you remember, I left you a comment.
First comment.
Show it in fact.
On episode 348 of the Charlie.
And after my friends hearing it,
they were a bit surprised.
And some of them, one of them,
instead of congratulating me on, you know,
going forward and being individual,
one of the rest of it independent.
I could say was, I can't believe you said
that's hard at the end.
Which was a bit deflating.
I thought, what can you do?
Anyway, the news story.
I submitted it on Newsvine.
And it's also mean first of us on another day
and delicious.
And it's nice and healthy.
So, it's great.
Timberd.org is great.
And also, I suggest everyone goes on
www.tibberd.org.
And, you know, come on.
Get to the point dude.
Which is that there's a link.
Okay.
To the point.
Anyway.
I wasn't actually going to be talking about my post.
I was going to be talking about them.
A guy a few comments after mine.
Talked about something about being superior.
And, you know, knowing how to podcast,
because he's a podcaster.
And, as a regular listen,
also to Twitter, this week in tech,
I'm Leo Leport,
also said a few tweets back.
That podcast,
and podcast listeners.
There's always a one-to-one ratio.
And, you, as the pod father,
I could understand why you're a bit confused about that.
Why is it the mainstream,
or maybe the Wikipedia show?
Why is it the mainstream audience listening to podcasts?
Well, before you go on,
let me say, have you looked at iTunes recently?
Have you seen what's being promoted?
Have you looked at Yahoo?
Seeing what's being promoted?
Please.
That's pretty obvious.
You know, we're being shoved down.
But this has been happening for a long, long time.
So, that's one of the reasons.
You see,
I, as someone who likes to introduce people
to new things, such as video gaming,
and, you know, blogging,
and read all web 2.0 services,
like flicker, and rapper,
and or blogger, and so on and so forth.
I like to introduce people to podcasts,
as well.
What I found is that podcasting
is kind of like a evolution from blogging.
Therefore, for people for some people
to be able to understand what podcasting is,
they need to be able to understand what blogging is.
And I find that I need to explain to them
what blogging is before I can explain
to them what podcasting is.
And this is generally a problem.
And so, as you can probably see,
that's why,
because of all the RSS fees and XML fees,
that there's usually one to one ratio
of podcasts and podcasts.
This is, obviously, very simple,
but, to the mainstream audience,
it just looks too difficult to be able to access.
And that's why I'm about to say,
and by the time you've played this,
you probably know what results
to your core case.
And that's what I have of course.
What results your core case is,
and hope is a good one.
Oh, yes, one more thing.
And I was just thinking,
because podcasts are so addictive,
and so great.
I was just thinking that,
maybe once people listen to podcasts,
I know for myself,
this definitely is my case.
In my case.
Well, it's a lifting list in two podcasts.
They'll start podcasting themselves,
which is why there is a one to one ratio.
But anyway, it is very complicated,
especially for people that are slightly less literate
in a computer-wise.
So that's why I have to say,
add a goodbye.
Not to tell this side, but goodbye.
Okay, not to talk.
All right.
To the people, chap.
Okay.
I don't think it's a one to one ratio.
That makes no sense.
There's plenty of reports that say,
there's millions of listeners,
and we have our own reports.
I think that there's definitely
between 10 and 15 million listeners out there,
a worldwide mind,
which is a very, very small percentage.
So two things I think that you're doing the right thing,
if you're enjoying it,
then you want to turn other people on to it.
The easiest way is probably just send them a link and say,
click on the frickin' link and listen.
Now, what you send them is of great importance.
This is another thing.
You know, people,
this is the sending thing that happened with weblogs.
Now, weblogs for years were seen as,
oh, well, that's just someone writing about their cats
or sitting in their pajamas, kids.
You've heard all the bullshit about it.
So it'll take a while.
It may even take as much as four more years.
Maybe three years.
I've been out for almost two years,
so I always go in five of your cycles.
So it could easily take three more years
before it really, really is widely known what podcasts are.
So I definitely want to put some of the burden
on the promotional activities there on the listeners.
And when you get your pod show plus,
it'll be much easier.
Much easier to just enjoy pod casting.
Whether you want to subscribe or not,
and we make that very easy as well.
So look for that to come out.
I think yesterday,
they showed up just about everything.
I've been following along.
I'm now running everything on the podcast delivery network.
And I'm subscribed through everything on my pod show plus.
And there's a pretty cool player.
It's really nice.
So you can, you can,
you can compile your own playlist of your favorite podcast.
So let's just call those a subscription.
But in the player, you pop open the player.
And it's, it's its own window.
And you can select.
You can really do drill down and move back and forth
between what you're subscribed to.
So you can say, alright,
I have a list of stuff that I,
that I want to listen to in the morning.
If there's new podcasts,
I pop up the player,
select the playlist that I want to hear.
Immediately it shows you all the new episodes.
Audio, video, AVI,
Windows, media,
doesn't matter what it is at all plays.
It's very cool.
And I think that will probably make a big difference.
Also, it does show notes.
And oh, this is very cool.
It does enhance podcasts.
So it understands how to play those and give you the pictures
and the links that are associated with it.
So yeah, you're going to look out.
They're coming very, very soon.
Lots of people sent me the link to spamcube.com.
Talking about yesterday's,
or the ongoing talk about the email tax.
That AOL amongst others are threatening,
or I guess they're already planning to put into place.
And I said, wouldn't it be great if you had a device
that you just jacked into your modem
and it kind of took care of everything?
So spamcube.com, there you go.
The world's first anti-spam gadget for your home.
All you do is, let me see,
let me see if they have the tell you how it does it.
Yeah, say hi to spamcube.
Just plug this plug in this powerful little tool
and you'll completely protect up to four computers
in your home from spam.
Typical marketing.
Makes no sense to technical people.
Our proprietary built-in anti-spam technology
stops spam, so there's no subscription fee
and it's easy to install.
Also works with all operating systems
and virtually every email program.
So I guess what these guys do is they have a service
where your email, you'll see your DSL was down.
And this is how email was meant to work by the way.
Let's say your server at home is down.
You won't lose your email.
It'll just be stored on their service.
And when your connection comes back up,
the email will be delivered.
And you just get it from your spamcube.
And you can then determine what is spam and what is not spam.
But of course, they can communicate with all the list, et cetera.
But it really gives you a lot more control.
Does it say, what is it cost?
150 bucks, man.
It should be offering some sex favors for 150 bucks.
But the idea is right.
We're getting very close to some consumer-based solutions on that.
Hi Adam.
This is Christian from Sweden,
without the podcast as yet.
I just think that one way to solve this thing
with registration mail getting lost
would be to require people to do things
the other way around.
Instead of sending registration messages to people,
you would have an email
that they send to you and have things on your mail service
that have those emails trigger their registration.
Thank you and goodbye.
Right.
Yes.
I appreciate the thought, but that of course is not going to work.
The whole point of using email is really for a confirmation
that you are the person who you say you are,
or at least you are the email address
who says they are the email address.
It's so easy to spoof things the other way around.
Basically, I could go register you,
I could look up the code,
and then I would email the code coming from someone else's email address.
That's pretty simple to spoof,
and then you still have to build all kinds of stuff
on the other end to stop the spoofing.
It's not that trivial.
It's just, and people are really misunderstanding
that this is about spam.
It's not about spam.
It's about guaranteeing delivery of messages
to you from outsiders,
whether you want it or not.
Now, of course,
I would presume that with the AOL email tax,
if you receive something that has guaranteed delivery
and you say I don't want to receive this anymore,
then you won't receive it anymore.
And presumably those folks won't be
charged for the privilege of not being delivered.
But in essence, it's just wrong.
It's just wrong.
Strong mail actually is the company
that we're talking to now about helping pod show,
and it's not because I agree with what's happening.
It's just because we have to get moving.
We have to fix this problem now,
and we can't wait,
because we can't even open up sales
on the pod sick music network
without these registrations.
Hey, everybody, raise your right hand for a second.
Go from left to right, say goodbye.
The satellite listeners, Windows closed.
It's just us now.
I mean, that would be just us.
It would be me and you and PW Fenton.
Okay, it's time to send an audio comment to the boss.
Now I know that the boss doesn't really like
being criticized by the hired help,
but you should also know that if you say anything bad about me,
nobody on serious will ever hear it.
But here's the thing.
You are an American.
You are not a Brit.
I love Brits.
Don't get me wrong.
But Brits are odd people
who drop syllables from somewhere
it's like turning military into military.
And then they add syllables to other words,
like turning aluminum into aluminium.
They don't need letters or any actual syllables.
They just say a syllable.
This is a fact.
And more importantly,
it is not a controversy.
I love seeing that word.
As Brits has told you over and over,
it's a...
That's right.
Controversy.
Hey.
Tell all your listeners that there are two new digital
flotsome episodes in the shoot.
First one may be a little weird and different,
but the second one,
which should be out a few days later,
will be more likely shows that they are used to.
Who?
Sorry.
Tailwind.
Oh, Peter.
You fired.
You're in so much trouble now, man.
I can just hear all the Brits going.
What?
Feel free to send in your audio comments for Peter.
Make it creative.
Do some work on it,
so we can start a real controversy around this.
By the way,
aluminium is actually the correct...
It's not just the pronunciation.
It is the correct word for the element.
Is that an element?
Well, for that metal.
Aluminium, not aluminum.
I believe aluminum is absolutely incorrect.
I could be wrong.
Unless it's some kind of derivative of aluminium,
then we're just talking about two separate things.
The most talking about ayoda,
the independent online distribution alliance.
This is an organization I'm learning more about.
They essentially distribute music online.
That would be sales.
And they sit in between record companies,
mainly independent record companies.
I believe some artists who have their own record companies.
And services like Napster or iTunes, etc.
We've been talking about their tower records,
alliance that they've kind of announced.
I think the news got out a little bit before they were ready
to really talk about it.
Towerpod.com.
There's not much there right now.
So the idea there is they're going to take their catalog,
which is six or seven thousand songs.
And any podcast that signs up with them
will be able to play the songs.
Royalty free.
I presume I haven't seen a license yet.
So I'm not sure if there's any other caveats about
playing songs in their entirety or talking over intros or anything like that.
And they will be they have a financial model,
which is advertising.
So advertising.
And this is where I think it kind of breaks down.
Advertising will be split up between the record company,
who of course splits with the artist,
with ayoda and with tower records.
And then obviously any affiliate, if they're going to do an affiliate program.
So it seems like it's going to get really, really thin down.
And of course transaction fees,
with maybe tower stake and care of that.
So it seems like it's going to get really thin.
Now Tim Mitchell,
who I heard talking at the artist roundtable at podcast hotel
and Seattle recently,
we discussed that on the Charlie.
He promised me an audio comment.
And he sent in 15 minutes worth of audio comment.
A lot of background about himself,
and about ayoda, which is very helpful.
But very little to nothing about what they're actually going to be coming out with.
So I didn't really feel like it was appropriate to roll anything out.
But I will post his 15 minute comments.
So you can have a listen to it.
But he didn't really,
and I don't think he can probably didn't really explain anything about
about what's coming up with tower records.
So hopefully when he can, he'll let us on the Charlie here.
No, because obviously I'm excited about anything independent happening.
I'm also very curious to see how this model's going to work out
because it's a whole different way of monetizing.
And let me just say one thing.
As I start to abstract myself a little bit above all that.
Now if you have a podcast, right?
And the podcast consists of audio feedback,
songs from independent musicians,
and anything that other people create that you put on your podcast.
Just on the pure spec of it,
you see this, you know, there's two files.
One could be a file from Matthew Ebel,
and one could be a file from comic strip blogger.
Both of them, creative works of art.
Both of them, MP3 files.
No difference.
Inter exchangeable.
We'll play on the same devices.
But for some reason, and this is where I think we have to start adjusting
our thinking.
For some reason, more value is attached to the song.
And I think that this is artificial.
It's an artificial value, which I have no problem with,
because I like to buy my music.
And I like to support artists.
And it's, you know, people who, you know,
who make music full time.
It's very admirable.
And, you know, I wish everybody could,
I really wish everybody could make money with whatever the hell they're doing.
But there is no difference.
And then again, I don't think there's any difference with a podcast file.
In fact, I put out more MP3 files than any pod-safe music artist
that I know.
I put out on a five a week, almost, usually five a week.
There, gosh, there's sometimes 10 times as large as other files.
Yet, they are deemed worthless on a transaction basis.
Although Ricky Jervais, of course, is trying to show that that's not entirely true.
And even he's getting ripped off and put on a bit torrent.
And on some of the peer-to-peer networks.
So if you really just extract yourself a little bit,
you know, I think we have to be realistic about, you know,
about trying to shoehorn old models into,
into the digital world that we live in.
Now, I think that everyone has a right to monetize.
But that doesn't mean that it's a God-given right
and that that value is automatic in my mind.
So my way of monetizing is through advertising.
Most musicians weigh of monetizing is either through sales,
or I think which is probably even bigger through merchandising
and through concerts and gigs.
And people who send feedback into the daily source code,
well, you know, I don't think many people are looking to make any money.
You know, some people really do a lot of work,
and some people do less work.
But take Jeff Smith, as an example,
is not a published musician.
Actually, I'm sorry.
Let me take that back.
He doesn't have an album out,
but he has plenty of songs on the pot-save music network.
But I know him, not through his pot-save music songs.
I know him through the stuff that he sent into the show,
you know, stuff like...
I'll stop it now because you get excited.
Don't have anything from Roger today either.
So, you know, I want to help him too.
And when people say, hey, you know, who made those great jingles?
Where do I get the ringtone?
I'll pass them right on to Jeff.
You know, so that's kind of how we work stuff out.
But I think we just have to be very careful about
carrying over a lot of these old models.
What else was I going to say about that?
Oh, yeah, one more time about the Dutch Azkab BMI,
the Buma STEM era.
So I was looking at the articles again.
You know, these are the guys that collect the money
from everybody and everything that could ever play
a radio or a CD player or anything in their place of business.
And they're supposed to distribute that to the artists.
And what they've done consistently is they've invested that money.
And they usually have a two to three-year delay
before they start paying out funds, of course,
it's on a rolling.
So if you start today as an artist
and those public performance rights organizations
are collecting money for you,
they don't start to give you money until two or three years.
But then, of course, it continues after that
if you continue to put out more music.
But in that interim period, they invest your money.
They've invested in almost 300 different
investments.
They don't list what they are in their annual report.
They had 330 million euros invested
and lost 46 million.
46 million of other people's money of artists money.
And I want to make mention of this
because what I don't think people realize is that
this is, yeah, sure, it's Dutch artists money too.
But this, you know, we're just what's going to happen.
This is going to be huge lawsuits, huge organizations
and from the US, you know, all the big companies
they're going to come in and they're going to kick these guys
ass for doing that stuff.
It's just unbelievable.
No regard for intellectual property right there.
I wanted to read you this quote again
as we talk about the tiered internet.
I'm not going to make it too long today.
I just have a couple more things I want to play.
This was from the CEO of SBC, who of course,
purchased AT&T.
I don't know.
I just got a banner ad here.
An SAP on business business week.
Okay.
Let me just find this.
What's his name?
His name is Ed Something.
Of course, I probably,
here we go.
November 7th interview with Business Week online,
AT&T CEO Edward Whitaker,
Jr. declared,
quote,
what Google,
Vonage,
and others would like to do is to use my pipes free,
but I ain't going to let him do that.
Whitaker and AT&T argue that they need flexibility
to exact a toll from web services that hog bandwidth.
As broadband use grows,
the bells and cable companies say that intensive users
aren't paying their fair share.
File shares swapping user can movies account for 60%
of North American residential broadband use estimates
David Caputo CEO of Sandvine in Waterloo, Ontario,
which sells technology to manage network traffic.
Yet over eaters get preferential treatment
over weaker ones.
So the main thing here is that this guy,
Edward Whitaker, Jr. said,
Google, Vonage, and others.
And I'm really looking at Google more than Vonage.
Vonage is voice over IP.
That's a whole different thing about who's packets
to get delivered and all the shit that's all.
It's frightening is really what it is.
Got some feedback on it.
Aloha, Adam,
this is the digital slot curve brando
from the digital slot pod podcast at digitalslob.com.
I've been listening intently lately
to the DSC or the Charlie or the Cha Cha
or the Chimachanga lately,
especially episodes in the upper 340s,
about the so-called tiered internet.
I'm glad you're shedding light on this complex,
but important topic.
I'm writing about it this week in my syndicated humor column.
I just wanted to bounce this metaphor off you and you're
maybe your listeners and the hopes of boiling it all down
into a nice little edible bond mall.
You can tell me how on the market might be.
As it stands right now,
the birthday party photos I forwarded to my sister
bounce around in the same sandbox at amazon.com
uses to ship us whatever Oprah tells us to read,
but cable companies want a higher profile piece of the action.
It seems to me even though they're basically just a utility.
It's too bad because rich people can already
buy huge TVs, expensive clothes and nonstop flights
to Europe and seats that were flying all the way back.
But even then there are limits.
I mean, even they can't write a check,
so big it would allow them to flush a pot roast
down the toilet.
A rising digital age tide should raise all ships in my opinion.
And that means raising the bar not only for excellence,
but for mediocrity as well.
Let me give you an example.
Weeks ago I created a song called Digital Slop Pod Fever
and uploaded it to the Pod Safe Music Network.
Thanks to royalty-free music loops,
drag and drop functionality in my wife's voice.
She owed me a favor for making me sit through a mat
and they have chicken little.
Anyway, I made a song.
It was rancid and a bismal by every measure,
but a song anyway.
It's still free for the taking on the PMN.
I guess a little bit like the way a tire fire would be free
for the taking for anyone who wanted to cart it away.
But even as bad as it is,
if I took it back in time,
I'm pretty sure I could get a record deal
and airtime on MTV between Mickey
by Tony Bazel and I ran by Flocke Seagulls.
It even ended up, as it turns out,
as an intro to music on the mic,
Marka Barshow out of Amsterdam a while back.
The point, however,
is that the song was made and is available,
thanks in part to the universally available web
that's fast enough and cheap enough to move it around.
And to an ego big enough to insist I wasted an entire day
making it.
But if I'm ever to take my musical career to the next level
from awful 80s,
one hit wonder to awful 21st century Mozart,
you can bet I would need a smarter application
bigger memory and a faster internet
and it's got to be roughly the same price
for else it won't happen.
Any more investment on the front end would require
some initial talent,
not to mention a divorce.
I suspect the next would be Google
or it would be Amazon.com would be in a similar predicament.
But given the same tools,
imagine what someone with true abilities
would be able to accomplish.
So, let's not organize the web
like the Titanic,
stifling the best and brightest way back in the series.
Let's push all our pipe dreams
through the same pipe.
That's the bond model there.
Okay, sure.
Wondering.
Mahalo Adam and let me know
when I can join the PD and party
because I know there's a line forming
that's longer than the one to get into the Don
who showed down at the Waikiki Beach Comer.
Just a bit of feedback from your friendly
neighborhood digital slob.
Aloha.
Mahalo Aloha.
Okay.
All right.
So, I have a whole bunch of different comments
about that which I'm going to save until tomorrow
at towards the end of the show.
We'll do a thank God it's Friday edition.
Hopefully, a celebratory edition.
That would be very cool.
Of course, I'll be posting something
on curry.com later today
if I have anything to report
and I surely hope I do
sometimes as I stated before,
you know, the courts will just say,
oh, you know, we actually put the judgment
and envelope sent it off.
You'll have it by Monday.
It's happened to me before.
Believe me.
One final piece of information
which pertains to podcasters.
This comes from duck from the rock cast
Italia from Italy.
Of course.
Adam, you were right.
It's dangerous to put our podcasters
in the hands of others.
I'm not quite sure what that was about.
Oh, I see.
Right now feed burner is unreachable
from the most important ADSL provider in Italy.
And it's been like this since Saturday.
It looks like other parts of Europe are affected too.
Feed burner is aware of the problem,
but can't do much.
And here's what they said.
And I'll quote from the email.
We've received a report from our hosting provider
stating that there is a routing
slash peering problem
between global crossing and sea bone.
Unfortunately, this problem is outside
of the control of both feed burner
and the providers that feed burner is connected to.
There's currently no estimated time of arrival on
when this problem will be resolved.
We will continue to communicate with our providers
and pass on any additional information
as it becomes available.
So that's a huge problem.
That can happen to any ISP.
So the way it works.
And this is exactly what could happen
with teared internet.
Remember we talked about peering the other day.
So global crossing and sea bone,
both are backbone providers.
And the agreements that these huge backbone providers
like AT&T have is,
look, you hand off X amount of traffic,
all hand off X amount of traffic to you.
And since it's kind of the same,
we call it a wash,
no money changes hands,
and they call that peering.
Which comes from the telco world in general,
where there's a settlement at the end of the month.
You know, if I make a call from you through
two here in the UK to your phone,
which is through AT&T in the States.
At the end of the month,
there's a settlement in the two companies.
You know, say, okay,
you know, I sent these calls to you.
That'll be you know,
$3 million.
And they say, okay,
well, we had $2.7 million.
And so they figure all of that stuff out.
This huge systems that calculate that.
But on internet traffic,
it's almost impossible to count it.
So the or at least down to,
you know, some particular levels.
That's what IPv6 is supposed to solve.
Look, I'm not a technologist in that, in that regard.
But here it is.
So there's, I think I've looked for it.
Any border gateway protocol
geeks out there who want to help us out with
what the dispute is between global crossing
and seabone.
Please let me know.
It sounds like there's a dispute probably saying,
hey, you know, we're not getting off traffic from you.
So we're breaking our peering agreement.
It could be something like that.
And this is exactly what could happen
with a multi-tiered internet.
So now a large part of Europe,
Italy is a pretty large part.
Cannot reach feed burner and other parts of the world
may be affected as well.
In fact, while I'm here right now,
why don't I just check to see if I can reach them.
Feed burner dot com.
And yeah, no problem.
No problem from the UK on easy net.
So that works.
At the end of the day, my friends,
where there comes to lawsuits, arguments,
broken peering agreements, theft,
endangerment,
when all of a sudden done
and when it all comes down to it,
there's only one type of person
that wins consistently.
There are rats.
There are bats.
There are sting,
community cats.
But the worst thing in the world
is a lawyer.
There are easels.
There are scones.
There are bandits.
There are pups.
But the worst thing in the world
is a lawyer.
With their clips and their committees.
Their fees and their contingencies.
There are lies.
There are my spare lots of things
but the worst thing in the world is a lawyer.
Music
But the worst thing in the world is a lawyer
With a raise, heeps so lucky to
And they respond the art superior
Yes, the worst thing in the world is a lawyer
There's thrombosis, halitosis
But the worst thing in the world is a lawyer
Diarrhea gonorrhea and saborea
With their proximate causes
And their escape causes
Yes, the worst thing in the world is a lawyer
With a firmative defenses
I would rather see a dentist
Yes, the worst thing in the world is a lawyer
So long now
I would rather see a dentist
Yes, the worst thing in the world is a lawyer
There are rats, there are bats, there are stingy magic cats
But the worst thing in the world is a lawyer
There are weasels, there are scunks, there are bandits, there are punks
With their coops and their coitities
Their fees and their contingency
Yes, the worst thing in the world
Is a lawyer
Steve Newman and friends
Lullaby for lawyers
Actually some of my best friends are lawyers
Everybody that said I tried to keep it around 40 minutes
Didn't quite make it, we'll do more tomorrow
And I'll let you know everything went with the lawsuit
Adamaccurry.com for your feedback
DailySourceco.com for the latest show
And the podcast speed
Thank you very much for subscribing
See you tomorrow
Another pod show podcast
Stick it in your ear