Already a hit state side. Now you can check out the following podcast and good old
blightybtpodshot.com. Single-handedly making a mens for giving you Madonna.
One show at a time.
And of course, your host, Adam Curry. Delta, Sierra Charlie episode four, Niners seven.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I like the car here.
Worrent, your car lover and Your cracking belly.
I want you to, I want you to, I want to learn from you
Your reason I make, your reason I'll stay
I never asked you.
Come on, we are here.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh
oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh yoga language
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh I Ele mesa
not a lot of sleep last night, I have to say Patricia getting a really early, like 430 this morning to jump on a commercial airplane to go to a Rotterdam.
More rehearsals for strictly come dancing as you would say in the UK or dancing with the stars.
So she'll be back tomorrow. So I'm Mr. Mom and of course we didn't get a lot of sleep at all considering Christina has come down with a very, very severe case of the flu.
She's really, really congested and just not feeling well.
So I'm kind of running around doing, you know, there you go.
Mom's got a lot of work to do, damn it.
Then of course I have two cats in the dog to look after as well.
But anyway, so I was previewing songs for the show and Christina kind of like tumbled in and she said,
Oh, what was that song?
You're just playing.
And I said, it's a bucklist. She said, oh, that's really good.
So that's why it opened the show, obviously.
So I didn't have a lot of preparations.
A lot going on in the London office this week, which today I'm not going to be able to attend everything.
I hope Christina is doing better tomorrow.
So I can slip off to London.
But as she is today, not really tonight.
Late somewhere between 11 and midnight, I'll be checking in with San Francisco.
We've got management meeting.
This is the second one that's been here. So I've been here a month.
Time to go back. And yes, indeed, Sunday.
Sunday going off to San Francisco for at least a week to, well, to be with everybody.
Man, I think, there are now at least 10 people who I've not,
not yet met who actually are working at Pod Show HQ in San Francisco.
And just a lot, just a lot happening.
A lot of correspondence.
I always know that it's really busy when my curry.com email basically shuts down because of the amount of spam mixed in with the huge
enclosures that people send me.
And so just reminder, it's Adam at PodShow.com.
We're PodShow.
Do it.
Others want to copy us.
These catches like old hamburgers.
They need to catch up.
The whack shows, whack flows with no spine.
This is the main part of the mix.
Yeah.
Greg Miller, from The Weekas Beat Bren News show on the PodShow podcast delivery network.
He definitely want to check that out.
Weekasbe.podshow.com.
Produce by Adam Raemer from Matown Audio production.
Madtown Audio Productions, these guys got some good shit going on, check them out at Madtown
Race, a MadtownAsers.com, Ash, you'd know I've messed it up, I gotta put it a link in
this show notes.
I'm gonna be relying heavily on the music today, and some interesting comments coming in.
Adam, how are you doing?
It's Paul Nichols here, South of Spirming, Central England, but the Sun that you can
hear is Swasaland, I actually recorded this fantastic, absolutely amazing, just want to
talk about a couple of things, really sits in journalism, you can hear the show podcast
Paul.com, and it's not just about the plight of orphans and the plight of the country
of Swasaland, but just how great things are, and the some fantastic science and stuff.
Anyway, more current is the fact that I'd like to thank pod show for taking a sponsorship
role at Podcast Conference, as you know, it's this Saturday, I look forward to seeing
you, and there are many other folks as well, CC Chapman, Mark from Tart and Podcast, loads
of guys coming along, and it's really, it's just, you know, it's really good to have
your support, and I'm very grateful for that, and just like to thank you, and pod show
publicly, it's a non-profit organisation for us, effectively put our money where our
mouths are, and it's going to be a great day, really it's going to be a good day.
But also Roger Blessing, I'd love to see Roger, and I think Roger's got the wrong
end of the stick, you know, we'd all absolutely love to see him, gosh we would certainly
wouldn't be taking the mic out of him, we'd like all that to buy in the bear, and let me
just say Roger if you're listening, there's a free ticket for you mate, and Adam, you might
seem to be able to give Roger a lift, mate, look forward to seeing you all Saturday, all
the best.
See ya, bye my name.
All right, Roger Smalls, the Elvis now of independent audio and video production, go to
a conference, Roger, there's always a ticket waiting for you, that's what a lot of bands
do, they always have Elvis Presley at the Will Call desk, just in case he shows up and wants
to see their show, so I guess that's what we're doing now with Roger Smalls, Roger Smalls
always will call the Elvis of podcasting.
Yeah, no, very happy to sponsor the event, and this is something that could fully stand
behind, because it really is, the money is really going directly towards the enjoyment
for all independent producers who are going to be there, and you know, it is done by volunteers
and it just really felt right, it really did.
I'm not sure what time I will be arriving, I'm not sure how long I can stay, I really
hope I'm there to see the shakes perform, it'll kind of depend on the situation here
at home, and of course Sunday morning, I'm leaving early to go to San Francisco, so a lot
of stuff, I'm definitely coming, I'm definitely coming Saturday, I just don't know what
time or how long, and and welcome by the way, all the new listeners who have checked us
out through BTpodgeo.com, this is the definitive place to find all things podcasting, if
you're looking for something from the BBC, well, guess what, we got it as well,
just go to the program guide, you'll find that under channels right up at the top of
BTpodgeo.com, and of course you can participate, interact, do something with these shows,
make it your own, call me baby.
Or if you're in the United States, hey Adam, it's Suzanne San Diego, I am so excited, I just
listened to this morning's DSC, got out of the shower and turned going, and I can't believe
you're inviting me up to San Francisco for Thanksgiving, I will do my best to try to get
out of doing the family thing and fly up there, I really want to see you, and I think
it would be so cool for us to be alone on Thanksgiving.
Anyways, thank you so much for the invitation, and I'm going to do my best to take you up
on it, got to go, have a good day, bye.
I'm and I'm going to be in so much trouble, Giselle, send me a picture, just so I know what
you look like, so you know what I look like, so I have kind of an unfair advantage.
Would you mind terribly dear?
What's up, everybody?
This is Brother Lowe, coming to you from New York City.
Got a show coming up, rock and roll, Monday night before featuring Brother Lowe, has
come in Monday, November 20th at Slate, which is 54 West, 21st Street, New York City,
and the show time is at 7.45, kick off of the big giant game as it ate 30.
There's an open bar from 7 to 8, free pool from nine o'clock till closing.
We're going to rock it out and proceeds for the evening, go to living, beyond the
leave, and check that out at living, beyond deliche.org.
Want to give a big up, thank you all so much to podcasters for rocking out, brother Lowe.
New brother Lowe is on its way, it's coming soon.
You know what I'm saying?
Thanks a lot, everybody.
Go to BrotherLowe Rocks.com and pick up album of the year for your Christmas present.
Come on.
There you go.
Also available on the pod save music network and I just realized that now we've been
hanging out together for over a year now, front of all one of the first pod save music
stars to enter the scene, classic from him, there she goes.
So good to you, what ever happens, don't leave it so soon, it's alright when it's okay.
You know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I
'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, I know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying and you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying you know what I'm saying, you know, what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying, you know what I'm saying you know
She'll be back again, yeah
This goes, this goes
She goes, yeah
She's gonna stay
She died until the story
Oh, she died until the story is still
She was basically cuted by, and everybody's lovely in hair
I'm sorry
Love
I wanna be numerous, but hopefully I wanna be a rebel
Tonight, today, I end
We'll go outside
And all of a sudden, you didn't, yeah
No, I'll be thirsty
But I can't run
Someone's today,é¸ badge
I want to read you the guys, because I'm ain't known to me
Be very+, if you praise it or like it, I'm Genike
But it just smells real nice
And now that I'm sitting back I can't bear
Let's go, let's go, let's go it's
Let's go z noticeable
yeah
I gotta wake up from
My mama's in charge of
I leave once you make up your mind
When you go in, I always go in
Come on and love me in
I'm not gonna get low
Not gonna get low
When you make up your mind
There's no reason
We're all our club
When you go in, Three, two, go
Brother Love, there she goes.
You can find him in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Of course he's a huge pot-tick music network star.
You know, let's do a little, a little kind of hit test here for a second.
If you can tell me who the author and composer is of this song, you'll weigh an absolutely
nothing.
We'll be able to find it on podshow.com slash music because he's just uploaded his first
track to the pod set music network.
Do you know it yet?
I'll give you a little bit of the vocals just like we're getting into the groove.
There you go.
Not one of my favorite songs by him, by the way, but a classic nonetheless.
Go find that for yourself.
I will not put that in the show notes.
Oh, this is kind of interesting.
Apple announced that a whole bunch of airlines are going to support purchasing music with
your iPod on the plane.
So in essence, what is being said is, if I understand the release correctly from Apple,
is that you'll be able to plug your iPod into your seat on the following airlines.
Anental delta, Dubai's Emirates, United Airlines, Air France, KLM, which is actually the
same.
What's funny about this is that Apple went ahead and released this.
KLM says, excuse me, it's way too early to confirm any such details as did Air France,
which of course is the same company now.
Very premature what Apple are saying is that a KLM spokesman noting that there have been
informal contacts between Apple and the airline, we have no idea if this is even technically
feasible if it's financially viable or if customers wanted, he said, at this moment,
we have absolutely no intention of introducing it on board, oops, little shark jumped
there by Apple.
Not a big one, but still, it kind of makes you wonder about all the other press releases
that they do seem to send out.
Comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip,
turns out C.S.B. is a huge fan of Steve Gilmore, good fucking foot, hi Adam, so when I commute
in another gun, I have my both hands busy with one, I have to hold on to the carriage
and the other hand, you know, I used to go up on ladies, so we see that I have no way
to switch podcasts parts, if podcasts is split it into parts, so obviously I hated it
that Gilmore gang was split it, but it is good ship, so here are three public advices
to him, Steven Gilmore, you monkey sausage, firstly resume your podcast because many people
liked it, including set a monkey who likes to draw doodles, more, secondly, whenever this
fet me jet, calacanis, gets on your nerves, Steven, just tell him to shut the fuck up,
but don't damn him, even if he has competitive podcasts now, thirdly and lastly,
stop splitting podcasts, please, so that I could freely grow court ladies, okay, and you
Adam tells Steven that you will bring him back on serious, if you will keep it all up, you
know, I think I understood what he was saying, but he's really a big fan, he likes it,
this is what I'm here for everybody, they love the show, despite it being all the obstacles
that are put in actually getting show in one go, oh man, all right, let's do something
completely different to wind down today's show, this is actually I have been subscribed to this podcast
Mario Agero.blogspot.com, and I will of course put a link to that in today's show,
it's a daily source code.com, and Mario teaches at the Steven F. Austin State University in Texas
and he plays the piano, here's kind of an emager, and I suggest you just sit back, relax,
and think of wonderful things, like Splenda, co-daddy, EarthLink.
Now, isn't that pretty? And no rights issues, no crap, no R-I-A-A, just music that's been
around for 300 years, performed by Mario Agero, it's Johan Pashal Bells, Canon and D major, and
you can find them on the podcast music network, it's got tracks up there, yeah, it's got some
slamming tracks from Ludwig Van, Beethoven, Robert Schumann, and Joseph Hayden, just to name a few.
Okay, well that put me in the right mood, I think, so I'll tell you what, tomorrow's going to be
pretty busy, but I'm confident I'll get a show out there, and the lady Patricia will be back
of course, I'm Friday and I hope to drag her in front of the microphone so she can tell us all about
her Remko experience, that's the dance guy that she's dancing with right now. By the way,
did you see in the New York Times that a renowned cardiologist said that dancing is just as good
for your heart, certainly if you have cardiac issues, as standing on a treadmill, I thought that
was very encouraging, and once again the lady Patricia is spot on, everybody take care, see tomorrow.
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT Pot Show Media Network,
powered by Pot Show and Limelight Network, control your part in the show at btpotshow.com.