Delta Sierra Charley
A year of Charlie heading forward the highway, looking for adventure and what it
becomes a bad save.
It's gonna be Friday, it's gonna be Friday, it's gonna be Friday.
What yes?
There's no sailbodies on methane hyper.
The drink too much coffee and fun to guess today.
When you're locomotive down the Stratford,
a filler owner with 16 gallons of flammable waste
wrapped in my ass and the destruction of the music industry in my ears
I like to think I'm a greasing up the future.
Delta Sierra Charley is still doingafood.
Little loose Cristo Wagyu
Listen,
It's first round's on me.
All right, Adam, have a good weekend.
Oh man, where's the stopwatch?
Oh, yes, everybody, one more day before I get to go home.
Once again from the Curry condo, Danny Sorsko.
For fuck's sake!
Are you ready?
Let's party!
Keep me hanging on now, baby.
Yeah, put your hands on the dashboard.
When the night on the subway, I'd be on a Monday.
Just a blackware head, the screen and shower.
We're still in the last class.
We're gonna make take a pop star.
We're gonna roll it right above.
Go on now!
I love you, baby, love.
I love you, now, baby.
I love you, you, you, you, you, you.
You know, I love you, baby.
I love you, now, now, now.
I love you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you
Me, you, you.
We're started off sweeping,
you know you're pregnant, you're asleep,
you know what's that all about?
We know I love you, completely.
You're all in this dream, man
Come on up, girl, let's work it out
Maybe in a waste of my time
If you're not gonna go, man, man
I know that's gonna come in
She gives it to you, girl, for free
What's watching, girl, in the fog
Damn it, it starts in my car
Come on, man
I love you, keep it up
I love you, keep it, keep it, keep it, keep it
I love you, now, man
Tell me.
I love you, keep it, keep it, keep it, keep it, keep it
We're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out
We're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, there's no reason we're ready not to are ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come up, we're ready to lucky us, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready to come out, we're ready ! We're ready to come out
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on
Friday and my last day of our to the two week, the two week stay here in the condo and
really winding things up exactly the way I'd hope they would time out.
Got a whole lot of stuff accomplished today.
Whew, I'm ready to go home, I must say.
I missed the girls terribly.
And you know, for all the shit I give Apple, thank you so much for I chat.
I mean, just we've got an eye Mac here and an eye Mac at the cottage.
And it's just so easy, you know, Patricia can use it.
And if she runs into trouble, I can always just SSH in and fire up VNC,
young in the command line and help her out.
You know, it's kind of like the air traffic control helping the stewarders land the jump
both seven, four, seven, young on me.
And so that's good that really has made all these trips a lot easier to bear.
Because I miss them.
But soon I'll be back in my girls arms.
Let me see where to start.
It's early Friday morning here in San Francisco.
Got to get a head start on stuff because we got quite a full day, you know,
keeping it going all the way to the very very end.
And then of course tonight I'm hanging out with my buddy Greg.
I'm going to have dinner with him and his son Zach.
And then I'll be heading home tomorrow.
I'm looking forward to it.
Okay, so here's what happened today.
Oh, man.
So I call Patricia on the eye chat and we were chatting.
Oh, um, did you read my email?
And of course, uh, and this would make most of you feel really good.
Who sent me email and didn't get a reply for some reason in the past.
As early as yesterday.
As a reason as yesterday.
Um, so she had sent that it, you know, sometimes I was clearly asleep because of the time difference.
And it had already scrolled way down the list.
So I had not seen it not.
It wasn't on the the main, you know, the the first screen when you log in to Gmail.
You know, it's more than 40 messages or whatever it is, 50 messages.
And, uh, I said, no, I said, hold on.
We pull it up.
Okay.
So here's what happened.
This is now this is quite a story.
Now, you know that we left the Netherlands a year and a half ago.
Um, really, uh, because, well, we did a number of things.
You know, we, uh, sold most of our stuff, our houses, everything.
Just said, screw it.
We're going to go chill out, rent a place for a while.
Figure out we want to live settled down a bit.
No attention.
Just don't want anyone hanging out.
Now, you'll recall if you are a longer term listener to the source code.
You'll recall that, uh, we were in the cottage for a little under a year.
It must have been what six, four months ago, five months ago.
And some paparazzi showed up from a magazine.
Okay.
So that really sucked and, you know, they had gotten from a database of magazine subscriptions from their publisher.
So partially our fault, I guess.
You know, the one subscription we carried over, they, they used to find their address.
So of course, that's not known in the paparazzi world.
And, uh, so there's this magazine called Weekend, which is, uh,
builds itself as a family-oriented magazine.
But it's a, it's a gossip rag.
Um, came out, I guess, Wednesday in the Netherlands with front page of Patricia.
And, uh, man, it's one of these pictures where she, uh,
she's walking out of Sainsbury from doing shopping, right?
And it was really, really cold that day.
And so she has, uh, kind of like a wool hat over her overhead.
You know, to keep a nice one, we're pulled down pretty low.
And, uh, you know how it works if you take 10 pictures of someone in quick succession.
There's always a shitty one in there.
So, of course, they take this shitty one.
And then, um, it says drama.
Literally drama.
Um, and this is a whole cover page.
On the inside, now check this.
They took pictures from my, um, weblog.
Actually, um, there are pictures that are posted on my flicker site.
But, uh, I guess, uh, there must have been some links to it from, uh, from my weblog.
And one of them is a, is a full page again, almost.
Of a shot that I took of Christina and Patricia in a limo in New York.
And another one is the three of us sitting on a, on a,
a bench in New York in Central Park and, you know,
me taking the picture with my arm extended.
And, uh, so the story basically is, um,
they, you know, they're pretending that everything is all fine.
But Adam has been away from home a lot lately.
And therefore it's drama.
Things are not going well.
So, you know, that's kind of, you know, we can laugh about that.
And although it's, um, it's kind of the price you pay, you know,
that, uh, that people are basically fucking stalking you and following you around
and taking pictures of you, um, you know,
and that they say stupid shit like that.
Yeah, okay.
So, well, we all know what I'm doing.
And I'm over here.
I'm back and forth.
You know, I'm, uh, trying to make it all work.
And we're all making it work.
And the sacrifices that everybody makes.
You know, yeah, I believe me, you know,
you could follow around Bill Gates's wife or Steve Jobs's wife or
the CEO of Shell or any other corporation.
And particularly a smaller startup companies.
You know, there's a lot of work involved.
So, that's not really fair statement, but for any woman, any woman
to have a picture taken of them when the just, you know,
when it just isn't the picture you want, you know,
and it's easy to make someone look like shit.
And of course, my wife could never look like shit,
but I know what she's thinking when she sees a picture like this.
Okay, so it should happens, right?
We don't live there.
So it's not all that bad and whatever.
And they can write whatever they want about me.
I don't care.
However, two things, the most important one,
and this is just amazing for a so-called family magazine.
They published the name and location of my daughter's school,
15-year-old daughter of my daughter's school.
And then just are very happy to mention that,
and a cab picks up and drops her off every single day.
That is endangerment.
All it takes, you know, of course, we've now changed that.
This is why I'm going to tell you this.
But all it takes is one idiot to say, hey, now that's kind of cool.
If I just pretend I'm a cab driver, I can get their daughter.
You know, it's unbelievable.
I just can't, that really, really pissed me off.
You know, that's just upsetting.
And especially, of course, we're lucky.
And fortunately, nothing has happened.
And you know, this has only been publicized for two days.
So I guess we're okay there.
But, you know, in pictures of my house, of course.
And there's all, you know, it's all under the freedom of the press.
So I'm just really upset about that.
Because you can say what you want about me,
and Patricia's the same way.
And you know, it's like you can say, you can make up anything you want about us and our relationship.
We've been married for almost 20 years.
You know, nothing is going to phase us.
But stay the fuck away from my kid.
And so, you know, usually, and they've written about us a lot.
And usually on the guy that says, ah, you know, whatever, you know, let them go.
You know, I'd be much rather be yapping about pod safe music or about pod show or doing some cool stuff.
I don't want to spend any negative energy working on backwards stuff, right?
Particularly not in other countries.
Just like who cares?
It's too bad for my family and for Patricia's family.
They have to deal with that shit.
People always asking him about it.
But okay, you know, so that's the way it goes.
But this time, first of all, I'm really upset about what they've done,
which just shows total lack of understanding of what it is to have a family.
Secondly, and this is where they tripped.
And this is going to be very interesting.
If you look at any of the pickers, pickers, any of the pickers on my flicker side, any of the pictures on my flicker side.
You'll see that they are published under a Creative Commons license.
Specifically, the attribution non-commercial share a like license, which means you can share this picture.
You can copy it.
You can do basically anything you want to do under the following conditions.
One, you provide attribution, which means you have to point a link back to where the original is.
And you have to say that's mine and copyright, whatever.
That's pretty normal.
Share a like means you can't mess with it.
You have to share it the same manner.
And non-commercial means you cannot use it for commercial use.
So that's how we're going to sue them.
And I called my lawyers and I said, you know what?
Now is the time.
Now we're going to go get these fuckers.
It's going to be very interesting to see what the value of my Creative Commons license is.
I'm pretty sure it's a shoe in, but it's going to be very interesting to see that.
And endangerment of a child.
So we're going to basically say you have to pull that magazine off the racks entirely.
Every single one has to be recalled from the stores.
And on top of that, of course, we want to rectify the situation.
So we'll get the same amount of page space and cover space.
And because there's no money in this shit.
You know, it's like, yeah, I'm sure we'll sue for damages.
But the Netherlands is such a socialist fucked up court system with no jury by the way.
It's a professional judge that makes the decision.
So there's, there's not any money in it, but I just can't believe.
And we also were, we're suing the, the editor himself.
It's anyway.
So, you know, it was kind of like a night in, in shining armor.
You know, my girls were bombed, you know.
And they've been waiting for me to get up to call them for them to lay all the shit on me.
And they were, you know, obviously bummed out.
And so I came into action for the first time.
I'm actually going to go after one of these magazines.
It's, uh, you just cross the line.
So one legally on the pictures.
That's theft and the arrogance of that.
The arrogance that you think that you can take something off of a website and publish it in a magazine.
What arrogance?
You know, if we turn around, if we take something of yours, how fast your lawyers are here.
Now watch my boys, okay?
Have you ever seen the discovery channel where, like the, the Orca whale, it gets beached.
Or it comes up on the beach and it grabs a little, uh, a little baby seal.
And then he keeps him in his mouth and they slings him in the air, like 30 feet and he lands the further up.
And he go get some, he catches him in his mouth and they're playing with him back and forth.
Like a beach ball.
That's what my lawyers are going to do to you.
Okay?
Ha, man.
It's Friday.
Okay.
So I was going to, um, open up the testing for the podsafe music, podsafe music network today.
To test the purchasing.
Um, oh, man, we had a great meeting today about, uh, you know, how we want to put all this in place,
about, uh, the pricing and really about the creation of the unlabel.
And I want to talk a little bit about that right now because when we open this up,
there's a number of elements to it.
And I just want to explain.
If we were to just go and recreate iTunes for independent music, that would be dumb.
You know, we really want to see if we can change something.
This is what they call that blue ocean strategy or whatever.
I think, um, the following scenario is something that we want to experiment with.
So first of all, we all know that these are free and clear MP3.
So we're, and this is, this is big thing.
Okay?
We're basically saying, uh, we're believing in humanity here and all the artists who, uh,
participate in this will, will pretty much be doing the same.
Consumers have not really had an opportunity on any reasonable marketed scale, um,
you know, to show that they will pay from music and, and, and, and respect rights of authors,
um, within, you know, some kind of boundaries that will make it work for everybody.
Uh, so that's the big risk right there.
But I, I have just a belief in humanity.
So, you know, I'm, I'm just feeling good about the fact that that'll work.
Now, look at where artists are today.
Um, you don't need a record label, a record company, because you can get all the pieces that a record label
offers independently and, and it's available out there.
Okay?
So let's say, in a traditional recording contract, you get, um, financing of the recording of your album.
Well, you know, everybody can use garage band.
And that stuff's been leveled out.
Okay?
Now distribution, distribution is obviously the piece that, um,
iTunes has done a great job at enabling people to purchase individual tracks.
Uh, of course, um, there's, uh, there's a few issues with iTunes.
One is you can't really go as an independent artist just to list a track.
You have to go through what they call an aggregator.
CD Baby would be an example of that.
And it takes a long time.
You know, you can't really just say, I want to sell something today right now.
It can take a couple weeks, which makes it very hard to implement your marketing plan.
Um, so record companies spend a lot of money on marketing and paying radio stations.
Uh, or paying radio stations to keep them friendly.
So they will, uh, then don't really pay for play.
But there's all kinds of money transactions going back and forth.
Um, so, but, you know, they work it.
They have independent promoters.
These guys go out and work it and get the record played and the record played.
Reports the billboard and then billboard, uh,
shows chart activity and then you might get an article.
And then if there's enough budget, they'll do a video clip.
And you get that on MTV and body, body, body, body, body.
That's how the whole thing goes.
So in our world, which is completely separate, but has an amazing amount of distribution.
We have podcasters who through the pod safe music network can play the songs.
Now, if we have a thousand podcasts with a thousand listeners,
playing one song that's a million impressions, a million spins.
That's the equivalent of having a huge radio air play in traditional radio.
So if you have a million people, I can only presume that what?
Maybe 1% will show up and buy.
Now, with 99 cents, you're talking about some serious rent money,
beer money, whatever you want.
So how does that piece kind of flow from a podcaster playing it?
Podcaster plays a song says, hey, like today I played was a valley lodge hanging on.
Go to my show notes if you like the song.
And there will be a link.
And you click on the link and you'll go into the artist's page.
It's very much like it happens right now.
You can go to my show notes and see it at any time.
It takes you straight to the artist's page.
But then there will be a by-link.
And the by-link right now, we are doing worldwide credit cards.
So anywhere you are, you'll be able to register.
And you only have to enter your card details once.
You know, it's like a real store.
And we have a partner for that who does it all secure.
You know, we don't want to be a credit card transaction company.
We want your details to be completely safe, obviously.
Then you are shuddled back after you've purchased.
You come back to, we don't really have a name for you.
But I guess you're your collection or whatever.
You'll have a little bit of space or not a little bit of space.
You'll have an area within your account on the pod save music network.
Oh yeah, listeners will have an account now, of course.
And everything you purchase will be in there.
And it'll just stay in there, okay?
So it's not like iTunes where if you lose the file, you can't get it back.
No, it's there.
And you can just go back and download it again.
Now, of course, you should be able to load it on any device.
And it played anywhere you want.
But we want to encourage people if they turn other people onto the music
to get their friends to buy a copy as well.
Now that piece going from the show notes into the purchase system,
we feel that that is an important part of the unlabel.
And that podcasters should be able to participate in sending someone over there to buy.
So we're going to make it so that they become a part of the marketing program of that song or that artist.
And that they get a piece of the transaction.
Now, of course, we'll make it so that you can put a link and you don't have to be a podcaster.
If you just want to promote someone, you could basically have your own little mini record label.
By promoting all the songs that you want and being able to point right into the store.
And just like any other affiliate program,
only I think you'll see that we have some benefit and we'll be working very closely with the independent promoters of music,
whether the podcasters or listeners.
And then the circle is complete.
You know, what else do you need?
Is there anything else that a traditional record company can bring to the table?
I don't think so.
Oh, shoot.
I'm glad I got most of that out because it was important that the folks on the satellite hear about that because we got some cool stuff happening here in podcasting.
And actually, I'm coming to New York on the, was it the week of the 12th going to be dropping by a serious HQ and going to be talking to the big way.
Actually, Scott Greenstein, major big way about what we can do with pod safe music on serious satellite.
Anyway, serious listeners have a great weekend. I will catch you guys on Monday.
So we here on the podcast can just to happily continue.
Okay, so do you understand why I'm really excited about this?
Because I can't see any other piece.
Well, yeah, I mean, the only thing you could argue is that record companies have a and our guys and a people who hook up musicians with producers and writers and videographers.
Hey, guess what?
That's called the social network.
You know, we're going to be building that so that we can also facilitate within the network.
People who are writers who want to hook up with musicians.
Look what we did with pod safe for peace for Christ's sake.
It was just an idea.
Within two weeks, we had 32 artists all together doing a song.
And, and selling it with the proceeds going to UNICEF.
Okay.
So anyway, because we won't actually do the final testing of every single piece of the track.
You know, we want to make sure that the transaction part is really, you know, that we have all the security down for that.
It's going to have to wait until Monday.
I know you may bummed out and you wanted to try it.
We'll, we'll basically have that, I think by Monday we'll have it up and running.
I just, you know, it's, it's, but it's all going to be baited stuff anyway and we're really, you know, testing it out with the amongst ourselves here.
So it'll only be, you know, like maybe one song you can test it out on just to get your account up and up and rolling.
And then, of course, it'll be up to the artist to select which tracks they want us to, they don't have to sell, by the way, to select which tracks they want to sell.
We'll test that part out amongst ourselves.
And while we're doing that, we'll get this, the unlabeled pieces in place so that people can start promoting music and we can all participate in this.
And I, for one, really looking forward to getting it all together.
So apologize, you know, a little bit of a delay, but give me a little, a little time to get home and have sex.
That's not right. That's really funky. How did that happen?
I was like, wait a minute, this is not the promo.
What was thinking it was? Wow. I'm using cast blaster, which you probably know, but that's really weird.
Someone, I was trying to play one of the cart things and for some reason, the hanging on kicked in again.
Let me see if it works now. There we go.
Hey, this is KFC from the pod chick show and we're in the big time. We're in the big time. Hey Adam, thank you so much for all of your help over the past few months getting into podcasting and being so pod father Lee.
I really appreciate it. And wow, look at how far we have all come.
What an amazing, amazing ride we're having. And I'm so looking forward to riding some more as a member of the pod show family.
Thank so much for having me. I'm so, so glad to be part of this new venture and this new industry. We're changing the world, man. We sure are.
For those of you who don't know, I am the pod chick and our whole theme is positive vibe podcasting.
Check out our show and learn to live your life a little bit more rich. We have a positive vibe message every show.
And we just try to have a little fun along the way. We're looking forward to having you join us.
Check out our videos too. We've got some skydiving and some hot chicks dancing. You know, regular stuff like that.
So with that, I look forward to working with everybody from the pod show and I'm just so happy that things are working out the way they are.
And wow, happy 2006. What a way to start it off. Hey, like we say on the pod chick show, make them smile.
Dan poets. All right, what up, Jay Mack?
I see you. What up, Detroit? George, what up, Phoenix?
Come on, this area. Stand the fuck out. Let's go.
Let's go. Listen.
It's good.
Hi.
Dot. Come.
It's all good.
Hi.
We drop off. They call me the pod.
What my aliens make a joy. I hail from that sun.
Same solar. Just hold now. We got that source called updated.
And we're going to give it to you on the daily. Passing our hurry.
I can't wait for them to blame me. You're all serious that light.
It's a strong hype. And I'm a serious man with lights.
Dan poets till I die. Keep your head lower. You're not rocking with the best.
But you already know it. Transform and courtesy in the major.
To be all about courtesy and getting this paper.
All start currently. I take a terrible fellow freaks in that nature.
Disaster. It's like a trainer. Hip hop scene. Yeah, I got that never last blow.
So call me now related. Fuck the haters.
The hate lanes and you can stop hating me.
Picture me on your favorite countdown. I'm out now.
Top one two three. I'll hit and take that spot now.
Where you can jot down the digits for a no-to-be specific.
And I'll add to nature if you want to come get it. You're the best.
How do you say that? I'm serious with my fuck.
The bag is an ex-girl. They kill me as a bar.
I have the industry for the style.
They take the chapels. They like dice. We strap pipes.
And take it in the ass. Well, me, boys, you're me.
Just keep keeping the cash well.
It ain't hard to tell.
Yeah. I love the hood high promos.
I sent that one over to the execs. It's serious too.
Got to hear this. It's like an awesome fantastic.
You might hear my T-Cettle in the background there.
Yeah. What was it going to say?
Oh, pod chick. Yeah. So pod chick welcoming her to the families.
So what we're doing with all these people who are joining the network.
They are going to actually be beta testers at the same time as they're joining the network.
They're going to help us work on the new systems.
The pod cast delivery network.
You know, this is not something that you just open up and say,
Here it is. Come on in. It's fantastic.
You know, I'm really, really careful about that because we're talking about
Lots of people who are, you know, very serious about pod casting.
We don't want feed, screwed up, and stuff like that.
I mean, and shit happens, right?
You know, software sucks sometimes and just shit breaks.
And it just happens. So we got to be careful when we do this.
So the first people that are coming in,
We, you know, who've been diligently working with on the,
They've actually helped us, you know, create our agreements.
You know, really been able to refine the offering that we have for pod casters.
And then not only going to be using the pod cast,
Liberty network interface interfaces, I might say,
But also the, the listener portion.
And this is the stuff, of course, that we're going to use to lure in our hundreds of millions of listeners.
And so, you know, based upon their feedback,
And that'll take, you know, a couple of feedback loops,
And we'll open it up to more, and then eventually we'll open it up to everybody.
Yeah, I was, you know, I was saying that it was like 15 million things went through my head.
And I can't remember what they were.
Oh, yes, okay.
Let me see what's this.
I have so many, you know, I have like seven more things I want to talk about.
So I hope you're in the mood for it because it is Friday.
We're off the side like the windows closed.
Let's just continue on and just do this whole thing.
But first, these words from one of our sponsors.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
Where are the link?
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers.
We believe your personal information should be just that personal.
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe.
Where are the link?
Make this smart choice.
Visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
Okay, okay.
That gave me just enough time to grab the tea, slap in a tea bag.
Oh, I can't wait for some sale when I get something.
Some sense, some sense, some sense sale when I get back home.
Let me tell you.
So I've been using cast blaster.
And I think I've gotten a much better, a much better sound together.
In fact, let me just see some feedback here.
It was actually pretty funny from podcast crew budget.
I thought you were supposed to be the best of the best, the pod father.
So what's the deal with your shitty sound production?
Every time I listen to your show, your pod safe music, skips and pops.
Are you going to blame that on your piece of crap?
Mac too?
Interesting thing, Adam, is that your show is not live.
Did you know that means you can give it a listen and fix somebody's things
before sending it out?
Yeah, that would make me like mainstream, dude.
So I guess Jack asks, oh, I'm sorry.
Podcast crew budget, who calls me a jackass,
hasn't heard the cast blaster shows yet.
We've gotten it down much better.
I really liked yesterday's show.
I thought the sound was pretty good.
Now that turned off the internal limit, or it's still working on it a bit.
I did actually, I got a note from Mark Yoshimoto Nemkov from Pacifico's Hellway.
He says, dude, I'm curious.
What EQ and compression are you using on your voice?
It sounds really fucking good, especially the last couple of days since you migrated to cast blaster.
Yeah, I don't know, Mark.
That's the secret of the Big Hared Fag, man.
You know, I can't go telling you all that.
Because, you know, then you'll be a big Hared Fag like me, too.
I got a, you know, I had asked, or I just been kind of talking about some of the stuff that I was experiencing with, with cast blaster.
And, well, you know, there is a community for this, this is a wonderful program.
Oh, shoot, I remember I was going to say before.
Let me just write it down so I don't forget.
Sorry.
I forgot again, no hold on.
I'm so fried.
Okay, let me just write that down.
There's quite a cast blaster community that you can find at castblaster.com.
And the community is taking note of my, of my recent switch.
And here's some feedback.
Hey, Adam, this is Barry J, cast blaster form moderator over castblaster.com.
Hey, the other day on DSC 317, you were complaining about the card buttons on cast blaster.
And the fact they don't have countdown clocks.
Well, that's true.
They don't have countdown clocks.
But they do have progress bars.
Is that little thin line under each button.
So when you press a button like this.
I'm asking for a new Hampshire.
This is Radio QRM.
The progress bar actually turns green as your promo or bumper plays.
Okay, now it's time for the shameless plug.
I now have a podcast.
It's called Radio QRM.
It's a weekly mix of pod safe music from where else the pod safe music network.
And it sounds something like this.
Yeah.
Right on Barry.
So, you know, it's funny because.
Oh, I'm sorry.
This is Radio QRM.
So I was listening to that comment earlier today at the office.
I'm like holy crap.
They're actually our progress.
They're great progress bars and countdown timers under the track players in the cast blaster.
But I hadn't seen.
It's funny.
The progress bars underneath the cart buttons.
And the reason why is because the angle, you know,
this thing is on the on the countertop and the open kitchen thing here in the condo.
And I'm significantly taller.
It's really just too low for what I'm doing.
So the angle that I'm looking at the laptop screen doesn't actually.
Translate all of what's going on the screen.
And when I got really close, see if I go down here, I can see it.
I'm straight looking straight into the screen.
But of course, I can't see the mic.
Indeed, there's a progress bar there.
Holy crap.
A lot of that stuff that I was, and by the way, I don't think I was complaining.
It's called feedback.
You know, complaining is, I'm, I'm a lady, man.
This is great.
You know, I'm no fan of windows.
But hey, look, I can use unique some machines.
I can use dust machines.
I can use max.
I can, you know, I could probably still do some peek and poke shit on the,
the Vic Commodore Vic 20 and the Sinclair ZXA to you name it.
You know, as I can work with windows, it may not be my favorite machine to,
you know, to manage my life with.
But, you know, hey, that's not what I got it for.
I got this thing just to sit here and do its job.
You know, the extra sound card and next Wednesday, I believe,
Kenster J and I are going to do another MTV chronicle.
So I get to try out my Skype theory with the dual sound cards.
So we can really, you know, see, we can get some good recording going on
and set it up the way I think it should work.
So, you know, it's, it's cool.
No complaints whatsoever.
Amigo.
Okay, here's, this is not a complaint, okay.
But, what I was used to on the Mac is I was able to,
take any document that quick time can play.
And I could basically play that in Megaseg and I just discovered,
I wanted to play an MP4, which is a video.
Excuse me, a video.
It's really the, it's kind of, it's an open standard,
but that's now kind of known as the iPod format for iPod video.
Because an old colleague of mine, Bill Elberg,
better known as Vladi, the Mad Russian scientist, a different one,
then I spoke, you know, that this is not George, this is Vladi,
and Vladimir.
Bill Elberg, who used to work with us in the early days of
thinking my idea, it's actually on ramp before that.
He was fucking great.
And he's in LA and he's working at, I don't know if he wants me to tell you
where he's working, but he has a great, a great gig,
and I'm really proud of the success of all these guys
that used to work in our, in our previous companies,
you know, him and Brad's certainly.
Actually, I mean, there's 700 people, so I could keep on name and names.
But I knew I've played Miss Prince with the Z at the end
on the daily source code quite a bit, and he told me this
before, after I had already played Miss Prince,
and I guess I kind of forgot, but I, you know,
that's his band, and he's in it.
And he gave me a video to one of their songs.
And so that won't play in the cast blast,
which I guess is kind of default behavior,
so it's not a bug or anything.
But I just can't play right now,
it would take me, you know, to have to pause the recording
to go and get it.
So you'll have to hold on to hearing the Miss Prince
and on Monday when I'm back, then we'll put a link
into the video, but in the meantime,
you can always check out the podcast,
Music Network, and it's good to hear from Bill.
Dude, I can't believe that's you, Bill.
Let's just put it down.
Yeah, I won't take it right on the list.
Woohoo!
Oh, yeah, there it is.
Brad with Adam, it's a really big deal.
Cook it slow, cook it fast, we'll have the United.
Just jump on board and take it on night.
We're going out on the test drive.
It comes rockin' right.
Let's move it on.
That's right.
We're going on a test drive.
Today, Ron and I have a meeting at Google and we're taking Trinity.
Yeah, baby.
We are taking our science experiment on the road.
So that's going to be a lot of fun.
It's actually going to be great.
We're meeting with a whole bunch of interesting people.
Remember I talked about the music search.
So that's one of the main reasons we're there is to talk about including pot-safe music.
Pot-safe music network in the music search.
We're also meeting with the guys from Google Reader, Google Talk.
Guys and gals, I should say actually.
It's going to be fun.
It's more fun that we're taking Trinity.
I hope she makes it.
It'll be great karma if she does.
Speaking of Google, I'm not really speaking of Google.
I always think of a big hotbed of software developers.
I don't know if it's open for business.
I think it should be.
I didn't actually synchronize with Andrew before the end of the day.
Now that I think of it.
But as a part of our, you know, getting into beta and soon launching my pot-show.
Pot-safe music, the podcast delivery network and pot-show plus.
Oh, there's a new one for you.
Pot-show plus.
We are launching our developers program.
And you can find that at developers.pot-show.com because
And I'm really proud of this.
I think this is so cool.
And this of course is one of the main reasons why we have Andrew.
Andrew comes with a lot of cool, cool little tricks in his tool bag.
But he very successfully ran the,
the iPod 11, the juice receiver, open source project,
collaborative amongst like three or four continents, you know.
So he'll be, he's been setting this up.
And, and so you go to developers.pot-show.com.
Everything will be open.
Everything will be all API is open.
All the inputs and outputs of this puppy are all going
to be available through APIs that you're probably already familiar with.
But, you know, there's modules and stuff to do and check that out.
Developers.pot.jout.com and I'll see you over there
because I like to lure out that shit.
I love hanging out with the geeks once in a while, you know.
Hey, since it's Friday, not only do I have a, by the way,
Jeffrey Smith dude for doing all these, all this music and all these songs and stuff.
You, you just rule so incredibly major.
He did a re-edit of the Roger Smalls intro.
And, of course, we have a message from Roger Smalls.
Hello, my name, Roger here.
Quick question for your mental sexual section.
I was wondering if you had any tips for shaving walls without any bleeding.
I'm sure that it's for his light Robert Teneerow or Victoria Backabilition in right now.
Thank you for sharing the advice too.
Thank you.
Yeah, what you've got to do is another message from Roger Smalls.
So I heard that from Roger.
And I didn't get it at first.
I didn't.
And I'm not only if he's trying to be funny or this is, or if he really meant this,
but I was like, Victoria Backim doesn't have warps on her face,
like Robert Orp.
I don't think Robert Teneerow is a ways of mole on his face.
And then I figured out what I think he was trying to say.
You're disgusting, Roger.
Man.
But you do get my weekend off to a good start with that stuff.
You're nuts.
Let me see.
Oh, wow, yes.
So the news about this week in tech,
that I noticed quit taking advertising through pod track.
So I said that I was really excited about this.
And it was so hard to believe because Leo Leport has been,
you know, so clear in the past about, you know,
staying non-commercial.
He made, why did it deal with AOL for the bandwidth,
which I understand?
And I thought that was, you know, that's actually a pretty pretty damn good deal,
because bandwidth, particularly the numbers these guys are doing.
You know, that's, I can get pretty costly.
But he, you know, his keynote at the portable media expo.
He, you know, was all about passion and not about taking money
because then, you know, it would be, I mean,
you go, look, look at his keynote.
I don't want to put any words in his mouth.
And so it showed up in CBS Marketwatch.
And as I told you, I even pinged Frank Barnock on said,
do, did you check this?
And so, of course, I know Leo.
I fired off an email to Leo, and it's true.
He's taken ads.
He's there.
They're in some kind of auction or something.
And we'll have to see how that works exactly.
But that is phenomenal.
And I'm very, very, very, very happy for everybody, really,
for us as such a validation, you know, of that.
Because I don't think this show is going to change.
So they'll have a sponsor.
Who cares?
You know, it's great, you know.
And, you know, if it'll keep TWIT going, you know,
I'm quite, there's a whole thread over it to TWIT.tv.
You can read about, I guess he was already kind of preparing the audience
by asking questions, you know, should we do like an MPR model,
listen or supported model, and looks like he went,
I don't know if it's a hybrid that he's going to do
a full ads, whatever.
But it is a validation of, you know,
great content, professional content that can match up with advertisers
who are willing to step into the medium and make it work.
You know, money has to flow somehow.
And I think that we all can work with this.
You know, look at what's happening in the world.
Media is changing right before a very freaking eyes.
And ears.
So, you know, if you remove the concept of time immedia,
you know, it doesn't matter how long or how short something is.
If you remove the concept of limited frequency and ether,
then it only makes sense that you can't do the same type of advertising.
Now that doesn't mean that we have the answer yet,
and that we know exactly what it's supposed to be.
But it's happening.
It really is taking place.
And any advertiser,
whether, you know, however they're working with us and with other ad networks
or whatever system or any podcast,
thank you for doing it because we're going to figure this stuff out.
And by the way, listeners,
thank you so much for bringing your feedback in.
Because if you think that feedback doesn't go straight back to advertising agencies
and the companies themselves who are utilizing podcasts to advertise,
I mean, of course that's what's going on.
So it can only get better.
So your feedback is incredibly important.
It is incredibly important.
That said, here's another great example.
Hold on a second.
Remember, I went to the Johnson and Johnson conference.
It was all the brand managers and media buyers in Seattle.
I actually did a show from there.
Well,
I'll give you, which is a Johnson Johnson brand,
which I know very well by the way.
I've been an IQ view user all my life.
I stopped using contact lenses.
Let me see.
Actually, when I started flying,
because it was the night flight, I think.
I was doing some night flying.
And I put my glasses on instead of my contacts.
And I really noticed a difference.
And I don't know if that was just a night stuff specifically or whatever.
And then I kind of got into,
well, I got into the pink glasses that I wore.
So I just wore prescription glasses.
I had these rose colored glasses, which was really nice for a while.
And then I have,
these actually had a blue tint when I first got them.
I don't kind of rubbed off.
And I just got into glasses for a while.
But I've always used active view.
Yeah, active view colored lenses, which is pretty trippy.
So I like the company regardless of whether they're,
whether they're sponsoring the podcast,
the podgeo podcast network or neat or neat.
This is my Dutch slipping, or not.
But they are.
Specifically what they're doing is there's this,
they're actually underwriting an entire podcast.
So it's, I think I've mentioned them before.
Heather and Janelle,
two high school girls, high school girls,
trying to get an audience basically.
And, and they're just talking,
you know, talking like high school girls.
And the reason why,
and I can certainly mention that on this podcast,
is high school girls are interested in contact lenses.
Because that's a big decision you make, you know,
when you're young.
We used to do,
one of our clients when we were,
when we had thing new ideas was,
excuse me, I got something about it.
I'm like, so I'm slipped in my throat there.
I won't even tell you that story.
I'll tell you that story another time.
Anyway, you can check out Heather and Janelle
at download.acview.com.
Acview is AC, women, let me do that probably.
I'll for Charlie Uniform, Victor Uniform Echo.com.
There you go.
Okay, let me just wind this up with one thing.
I actually, I really contemplated not playing this
because I, here's what I did internally.
This, this audio feedback is particularly in this show
because I was, I'm talking, because I've already talked about them.
But I afforded this to a number of people within Pod Show,
not as a, as a,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's definitely work and not like that.
But to reiterate how incredibly important it is
when you come out with any type of service
or offering for people who are serious about podcasting,
how carefully you have to be with this stuff.
Because one glitch can really ruin your day.
Now, this is from the financial aid podcast.
And it's about pod track.
And I just want you to listen.
And again, this is not, you know,
sticking the tongue out at anybody.
But it is important to understand what can happen
when you start integrating pieces of your profession
with other parties and how careful we all have to be.
And this is, this could go for feed burner.
This could go for any other company including pod show.
So this is really just something for podcasters.
I want you to understand what can happen when things go wrong
when you basically give up control of your feed.
Hey, I don't, this is Christian, the financial aid podcast
with some feedback for you on pod track.
As mentioned at DSC319, I noticed in mid December
that one of my fellow New England podcasters was using pod track
as a means of tracking their traffic
and their listenership more accurately.
I looked at the website and it seemed like they had
a pretty promising offering so I signed up for it.
Now, I'm not so terribly upset about the fact that
in the month I've been a pod track member.
I've never once gotten a report about my listenership statistics at all.
No, as I terribly bothered by the fact that
customer service kept replying with it.
Oh, we'll get a report to you any day now.
No, what bothered me was this morning.
I went to the website, the pod track website.
And I wanted to see if the reports that had been promised
for so long were available.
And instead, I got a server application error.
Hey, no big deal.
I figured I would just get out of my day and check back later.
So I recorded the financial aid podcast as usual every morning.
Got it up to the server and got it out there.
iTunes was showing the dreaded exclamation point next to the feed.
And I was like, oh, what's going on here?
So I went to my web server and I made sure the file was there
and they had not done a pre-coffie move and named
something I shouldn't have.
And everything was fine.
Well, it turns out the way pod track works
is basically they have your pre-pend there URL to all of the episodes of your podcast.
So whether it's the MP3 posted directly on a website like my space or
whether it's in your RSS feed, you always have a pod track URL
at the beginning of your MP3 references.
No matter where you are.
And here's the part that annoys me this morning from 6 to 9AM,
which is when the peak listenership of the financial aid podcast is
because that's when the show is released.
And that's when people tend to get to work.
Pod track was completely unavailable.
And when they're down, all of your MP3s are down too.
There's no way for your users to get to your show.
I don't know what podjo has waiting in the wings for podcasters around the world
in terms of measuring listenership and things like that.
But please, please, please, please, no matter what you do,
make it reliable.
Have backups, have redundancy, have fail over everything
because there's nothing more frustrating to me as podcaster
than not having my podcaster available to the world.
As for pod track and the form emails I've gotten
from CEO Mark McRearify his assistant,
I will never, ever, ever use pod track again.
And for any other podcasters out there who are considering using pod track,
make sure they've got their reliability problems under control
before you switch over.
Anyway, this is a bit of angry audio feedback from Chris
from the financial aid podcast.
Have a great day at him and I hope podshow does a much better job.
Okay.
So, the most important message here,
you heard what he said at the end,
make sure that you have redundancy, fail over double,
double told lots, et cetera.
This is why you have not seen podshow come out with
it's offering very quickly.
We really took some time to understand bandwidth.
Now, of course, we spend a lot of time looking at
solutions like bit torrent or things that big companies
like Microsoft are looking at.
Something that could really scale,
but, you know, without everybody buying in
everybody means all the aggregator developers.
And I don't think we can count necessarily on
the biggest one, the biggest podcast aggregator
iTunes, you know, to necessarily see the benefit
to themselves by participating in a bit torrent type of distribution.
Mainly because it makes a whole bunch of people in Hollywood
really nervous and no one wants to deal with that angst.
I understand that, by the way.
So we went looking for the best solution for bandwidth
and hosting.
And we have some experience.
I actually had a company called the data barn,
which was interestingly enough,
the right idea.
We were at a peering point.
We had peering agreements.
It was at the wrong time.
We had peering agreements with, I don't know, you know,
guys that were operated by Enron and companies like that.
So it was called the data barn.
It was, you know, I understand a lot more about this stuff
than, you know, we may have really talked about on this show.
So we spent months, literally months,
experimenting, testing, working, talking to people.
Now in the valley, you know, what's people used to call
Silicon Valley, what we call valley would.
There's almost like, and the solution you always take is,
oh, let's just go to Akamai.
Akamai will make it all work.
But when iTunes came out and when, you know,
the big bandwidth slurp took place,
the bandwidth burp of 2005.
We cut a real quick deal with Akamai.
And I believe that the pricing,
I'm just going to do this from memory,
but the pricing for a content delivery network.
It's pretty much between one and, you know,
a buck to a buck 50, I'd say.
The bigger you are, the more bandwidth you eat,
the cheaper the price is going to get.
What was it going to say?
Okay, so that's, that's per gigabyte,
per gigabyte of data transferred.
And this is what all the, you know,
all the big streaming hogs bandwidth hogs use,
you know, like ABC or CBS or NBC.com
and you look at their videos and stuff.
And the thing that's really good is that
the thing that is not used is that
it's not used to use, is it?
I think, maybe Apple doesn't Apple have a direct investment
in Akamai.
I think they do, or they invest like $100 million or something at some point.
And we were really looking for a company that would fit with us,
would understand kind of the renegade nature of podcasting
of the idea of user generated content.
You know, and really would work with us,
the thing that sucks the most about independent podcasting is,
when something catches on and people start to listen,
that's when you run into trouble.
And we've seen, you know, I mean, for the stuff that's
no publicly, there's a lot of podcasts
that have really had some major bandwidth issues.
And it just cost money.
Now, the company that we, so, you know,
so we decided we needed to go with a content delivery network.
We really have to because, you know,
just like we're using an outside company to do
the transaction for the pod, safe music network.
You know, let's use some professionals who are doing this stuff all day.
Now, this is podcasting is a little different from streaming media, okay?
You're talking about shipping huge files all around the world,
all around the network.
Instead of passing bits and bytes on on demand basis.
So you want files cached in different geographic locations.
You want this bandwidth done,
not through thousands of edge servers,
but through peer networks.
I mean, this whole, I mean, I've really made a study of this.
And, and Ron and I worked,
I particularly Ron, I have to say,
worked just tirelessly with Bill Reinhardt,
the CEO of Limelight Networks,
to come to a deal that would really work for both of us.
Now, I'm kind of jumping the gun here,
a little bit.
The pod-pimp is going to, it's going to hate me.
But I just wanted to let you know
that we have been teaming up with world-class partners.
And please feel free to go over and take a look at,
you know, what you think your bandwidth would cost
on a content delivery network.
And then know that any podcaster,
anybody who wants to come into the network
and who wants to work on building the network
and making the network better
and creating fun stuff and having a kick-ass time
with an actual possibility of beside social reward,
having financial reward,
you're going to get the bandwidth
and the hosting all for free.
And I'd like you to go take a look
and see what that would cost if you had to pay
for it out of your own pocket.
So that will be my damn announcement for the week.
Everybody have a fantastic weekend.
I'll talk to you on Monday
after I'm back and after I've had plenty of sex.
Bye-bye now.
Another pod-show pod guest,
sticking in your ear.