Think Advertising sucks.
Think you can do better?
Pod Show and EarthLink are willing to put our money where your mouth is.
Listen to this podcast or go to adchelens.podshow.com to see how you can win big
in the EarthLink make advertising better challenge.
Delta Sierra Charlie 412
I know for our job but listeners.
Back in the dust.
I'm calling to the show.
I need you for show.
I've got a mental picture.
We're on the show.
I'm on the show.
We need you for show.
We're gonna be with the police.
If we all work together.
I'm on the show.
We're on a small minority.
We're gonna make like misery for their neighbours.
And communities.
I'm on the show.
These types of learning that the rules are changing.
We're on the show.
I kid, I only do autograph after the show.
Welcome to the show.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
I'm in the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need non-sticky in prison.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm guessing it's a fellow curry.
I know this girl, she's a friend of mine.
I see her every day.
Time after time.
I wanna take her out.
To dinner.
After time, I wanna take her out
To dinner downtown
But she only looks good from the neck
On taxi to night of the plane
She's nine times a day
But the rest of her shows fine
You should see that girl
She has stuff from the back she's great
But from the front she's rough
And when she turns around
My god would have died
I only take her out in the middle
Of the night course she's nine times a day
She's nine times a day
But the rest of her shows fine
She's ten times a day
She's nine counts a day
She's nine times a day
She's ten times a day
she's fourteen times a day
I don't think she really looks good after nine of him
Trace because she's not a cousin of her
She's not a cousin of her
But the rest of her choice is fine
Only in America, the bot's at music network, the detonator's nine cans ugly
I was a cousin through PMN this morning, I just could not resist
Y'all's up
From New Jersey, of course, we're out
Love it, love it, love it
Although I must say, you know, I don't think there's one single woman in the world that I can't find some fantastic beauty in
There's no such thing as nine kinds of ugly, but that's song did crack me up, no doubt about it
Everybody, how are you doing?
Coming to you from the curry cottage in the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Gilford the United Kingdom
It's the Daily Source Code, I'm out of curry and here for the next foreseeable two weeks at least
Before stuff starts to happen again, but good to be home
Of course, got Christina with her with her knee
Yeah, they're hissing, I want to try something for a second, hold on
How's that?
You know, I think I'm gonna leave it like that, I think that sounds better
Yeah, so we have Christina with a knee she did go to school this morning, man
It's like she has a little mini knee growing out of her, out of her leg there, it's quite amazing
I'll tell you right up front, I'm a little bit, I'll just say, this combobulated today
I had a long chat with my mom last night
And those of you who have not been listening to the source code for a long time
My mom is suffering from lung cancer
This has been ongoing for two years and it's quite an outrageous unfair disadvantage
Fight that she's taken on here, or has been thrust upon her
And yeah, it's the conversation I had with her yesterday
It's just so hard to hear someone, you know, she's going through an anger phase right now
Which is totally understandable
But it just it really throws you out of sorts, you know, because you're not quite sure how to respond
And so anyway, so I just want you know that has influenced me a little bit today
I woke up this morning still thinking about it, of course, as I do probably every morning
But it's good to know not we're not alone in this and thank all of you for
For sending in your own personal stories and your thoughts and prayers, et cetera
Now let's get back to porn and stuff like that
Actually, today I believe is the vote in the house on the net neutrality bill
And I've talked about this
It's really it's one of these very interesting phenomenon
That is just coursing through the veins of the internet as it so happens
And the memes are fantastic, you know, save the internet
Which I think is probably the one you hear the most
That big companies are going to take away the power from the little man
That it's no longer will you be able to reach spots
There'll be, you know, it will only be mainstream media all of these things
And I've really done a lot of investigation, a lot of reading, a lot of understanding
Man, if you look at the actual telecom's bill
And the main thing in the telecom's bill is I understand it is that it now allows
Telephones companies to compete with the cable companies in the television access
Which of course is all kind of subjective, what is television, you know
Let's just they're calling a television which means something else I believe
And we just call it video or programed or serialized video
But that's the main part, the main crux of the of the bill
And so this is a amendment that is that several groups are trying to get onto
It's interesting one of the groups is
Oh, what is it?
So it's saved the internet.org
Yeah, you see a whole bunch of companies that have signed up
And that are for the petition over I think a million signatures
Actually, which is quite well signature signups, which is very good
That's actually valuable by Silicon Valley terms
To have a community of a million people as worth some real money
What's funny though is I maybe I misread it or didn't see it
But I don't see Google or Yahoo or any of those companies signing up for this
Nor do I see any of their own initiatives other than what they're doing at a high level political and high level political venues
So anyway
I disagree that
That we need net neutrality or some kind of legislation for something that actually has not happened yet
That to me is almost un-American in a way
To start putting laws into place on some positions of something that may happen in the future
That we're not really completely sure of no one can say it with any certainty or accuracy
So I have a fundamental issue with that
But also I just don't believe it
I think that the people who are most people don't understand how the internet works
And it's not I'm not saying that I understand it
I have been in the business of data centers and peering and internet exchanges and BGP
Boardergate we protocol and peering and how all these things fit together
And it's a very very complex matter
And the internet is always kind of hung together and grown by commercial parties connecting
And I've been around long enough to remember
When you can actually tell the difference when you had you know bad peerage or you were going through a horrible route
To your ISP wasn't connected to enough other or to sufficient backbone, etc
And I don't even think that experts can clearly explain it
It's such incredibly geeky stuff
But I truly believe that in open free markets and I think that it will
That we will not have any issues and actually I want to talk a little bit more about it
But I got some feedback. I got a ton of feedback actually
This one really hit the nail on the head on what I believe is happening with this
That is zero for the area 51 group one more call
The neutrality thing
I just got that listening to your full explanation of it
And you make it really hard to argue with you
I don't want to argue with you
We're not arguing about the same thing
Don't argue
The high speed bandwidth is going to pay for it if you really want to
This is not what the argument is about
That's all fine and good
And anybody who is running fiber and boosting your network etc
I'm talking about executives from major telecom companies saying
Google is making a mint
Because they are using our pipes and we want a piece of it
That's what everybody is talking about
Fantastic
You've nailed this piece of it right on the head
Without trying to get into that whole cloud thing again
Whenever you see a presentation about the internet
And how wonderful things will work
There's always this cloud drawing in the middle
Is the internet stupid
And it just kind of works
But there is a lot that happens there
And you have to understand that if Google all of a sudden
Let's take a pod show as an example
That'll be much easier
So maybe now we have in a month
I don't know anywhere between eight and nine million downloads
That will grow
And as that number grows
That traffic is being put on to different networks
And big networks like AT&T
Or SBC or whatever it is or Verizon or you name it
Actually have to start upgrading their gear
In order to handle the traffic that we're sending through
And which is kind of normal
We have to upgrade our gear because we've got a lot
And we're connecting directly to their networks
Remember that at a higher level
In fact we're seeing more and more of this
That's how the podcast delivery network differs from many other systems
Is we actually connect to directly to one of their machines
Don't traverse over any other parts of the internet
Of course that connection by itself
Is an interconnection and therefore a part of the internet
So we have to buy upgrade stuff
Or our partner does in this case line-light networks
And AT&T has to do the same thing
Now what I believe AT&T is saying is
Hey, you know what?
We're going to leapfrog here
We're going to try and get up to par with Europe and with Asia
Which is a very good idea
Excuse me, since sail this sense sail moment
Brought to you by the jersey touch show
So you know it's critical because we want to you know
We're all used to these small little video clips
Which is nice but you know is that the end of the road
Or do we want to have better quality more capability
Faster reaction times?
Of course we do
So I believe what SBC is saying
Or the chairman said quite clearly
Hey, if you're going to shove all this traffic on to us
You know, there's going to be a charge
And at no point that I hear him say if you don't pay
We're not going to pass anything through
But yeah, there will be priority
But you know there's priority in this priority
When you think priority you immediately think
A home man it's like waiting in the doctor's office
I could be shoved to the back of the line
Waiting for 45 minutes
You know this is very this is milliseconds stuff
Micro second stuff
So don't get too freaked out about it
But I think that's a good point
That you know we just got more traffic
There are several main sources that are indeed
Making money off of it
And if there's you know
SBC rating doesn't want to pass all of their
Costs onto their customers
We'll say indirectly we'll do over time
So they're looking at the other side of the equation
I really don't see anything wrong with that
If if you're Google size
Then you will probably have to deal with that
If you're not then I don't think you're going to have any problem
This is not about shutting everything else off
This is about huge volumes of traffic
Coming from single sources that have to be dealt with
The technical manner and that dealing with it takes money
They're going to double charge Google
They're going to find other ways
So it's not double charging
They're not charging Google
They're going to offer an extended service
I'm quite sure of this
I'm really not freaked out about the internet dying overnight
Do this and they're going to hurt the internet in the process
That's what this whole thing is about
I think it's gotten confused with this whole new plan to tear
And people hear the two things they're talking about the same thing
It's not that you're at all
They don't come guys or look at a drive Google out of business
No, they're not trying to drive them out of business
That would be ludicrous
That would be stupid
It's like you know we're the drug dealer
And we're going to remove the drug supply
No, no, no, no, that's not what they're trying to do
They're trying to recoup on their investment
For passing it through
And Google you're wondering why they're building up dark fiber
Well, that's because they're going to go directly to the consumer
The competition is right there in front of your noses
All right, it's looking to hurt the customer
They don't like the internet at all
I think that's what this whole thing is about
If there's nothing there, much to do about nothing
Great, great, we can go on as we were
But those of us who are kind of paranoid conspiracy theories
Think the companies don't like little guys standing at hands
And they'll hurt us when they can
I think that's what this whole thing's about
Thanks a lot
See you
Okay, so what you said there is really what it's about
But it's not really about big companies
Not caring about little guys
That's bullshit, that's a customers
If anything, the big guys would like to convert their customers
into audience, they'd love to be television networks
And I've dealt with the cable guys
They all think that their HBO
They're just trench diggers
That's what we call them in the broadcast industry
Sorry, if you're offended, but you know we say it
No, this is about something inherent in the end
By the way, this is only United States
The internet, when people say the internet is going to die
It could live without the United States
Okay, there would still be a thriving internet
And lots of people would be very happy
Yeah, we'd miss a lot
But it's not the internet by itself
Nor is SBC the only backbone provider, et cetera
There isn't inherent fear in the United States
Of big companies screwing the little guy and not caring
That's the fear, and I think that's crazy
Since one of we've been afraid of big companies
Shoot, American citizens have brought down big corporations
Many times, for many reasons
We haven't quite had a revolution in government yet
We've brought down a government, but I think we would be quite capable of that
And she guess what? We're also armed if we need to do it
So this is, it's much more an issue of
Ooh, it's the evil big company
You know, and look at Google, Google was great until they became big
And now they're evil
You know, even when they said they don't want to do evil
Or be evil, I can't remember exactly what the quote was
So it's something else that's going on
And we're really afraid of the big guy trying to kill us
It does not be who of anyone to look
We're all hooked on this stuff
YouTube, Pod Show, Google, Yahoo
You name it, we're hooked on this stuff
And the telecom providers know it
And what they're doing is they're saying we want to open up
A much bigger access pipe
And yeah, we're going to talk to the dealers about it
Because we're going to be able to add new capability
It doesn't mean that you on the other side of the cloud
Won't be able to be accessed
Unless you become a really big drug dealer
And then they're going to want to talk to you about new capabilities
I just don't see this hole
We're not going to be able to connect to each other
I just don't see it, I'm sorry
Now when we're really in trouble here on issues of this magnitude
Of course, as always, one person we can always
Always look forward to hearing from
It's time for your tin foil hat
And now it's time for another tin foil hat moment
From the financial aid podcast
Hey Adam, it's Christian the financial aid podcast here
For everyone trying for legislation for network neutrality
Stop it, stop it now
Listen up, the last thing in the world you ever want to do in order to get something done
In a fair and equitable way is get the government involved
Their ability to screw things up are legendary
Let's take the most recent and net neutrality bill
Which internet companies and private individuals have been pushing for
For starters, this turns over the regulatory power of internet service and content providers
To the FCC, the Federal Communications Commission
This is the same FCC that screamed bloody murder when Janet Jackson's breast
Was unveiled on national TV and furthermore
It's the same FCC that is easily readily and routinely hijacked by a political conservative moment
The parents television counsel
Do you really want these right wing jobs in charge of your internet access
On top of that you can bet this so-called freedom legislation will introduce lots of new domestic spying capabilities
After all, a government will need to have unrestricted access to major data centers to ensure fairness
Right, they wouldn't abuse that power for other means right
The free market is and always has been the best mechanism for getting things done
The real solution to net neutrality is to vote with your two feet in your dollars as much as possible
Do business with companies that follow your values as often as you can
But for God's sake, don't get the government involved
This is Chris from the Financial Aid Podcast
Financial Aid Podcast.com
Signing off another tinfoil hat moment
Exactly, Chris
I'm starting to feel like a republic
No, no, no, I totally believe in the free market in this case
There was something else I was going to say about that
Yeah, you know, so the arguments that I'm hearing are well, you know
I just lost my train of thought again
Oh, well, I was going to give you an analogy actually
And then I'll just get off the top because I was going to give you an analogy as to a parallel
There we go
We have the US Postal Service and a delivers and it delivers pretty good
Then we're all pretty happy with it. It's been that way for several hundred years
But if we had put in postal neutrality, you know, would FedEx exist
You know, are you allowed to have a service next to the postal service that delivers faster
And has online tracking?
Yeah, of course
Does it mean you can't send something the same size? Well, of course not
Does it mean that there's a difference when you receive it?
Yeah, there is a difference
But this is what it's about, it's about advancement of the network
People who want to utilize that and in true business models
I think it will all shake itself out. Let's just not get all crazy
That the internet is dying
A lot of people pointed me at the Rocket Boom, Rocket Boom did it episode
Trying to give an analogy of roads and Amanda driving in a car
Very cute, but you know, Amanda's an actress
She doesn't really, I don't believe she understands what is happening
In the underpinnings of the internet
And it's a very populist piece that I saw
Interesting, though, that she was using a via notebook
I wonder if that was, I never see commercials
Or advertisements on Rocket Boom
And I'm thinking that maybe that was an advertisement
I really don't know, I thought that I really believe she was a Mac person
But then I saw it with a Sony via
One just like mine, which I can't wait to talk about in a bit
I don't know, it's David Cohen, I'm a UK listener
I'm just picking up on the last week's source coast
Catching up on them, all the one going to the car
I just want to leave you some feedback about the net you chose you debate
I'm all confused by your start
You know, you've been complaining about things like the
Thanks for most credit card being denied
And you say all the American credit cards
I'm going to get out
The IAA and Ask Cat BMI
Not one thing card cards, let's see, promote their needs
It's free, but once it's a charge of extortion at fees
I remember a couple of months about you complaining about
And touch on, not be enough to send emails to people
And you have to pay what you call the email tax
To get the email through
Because that's what I've been paid for
Isn't the net you chose to think exactly the same
Isn't that just a price gouging by a comm to companies
They just want to take an extra price of the sharing
And they've got to return their investment
With their investment and models can't return their investments
On what they're currently charging
And then, you know, they shouldn't be in business
And, you know, one day these guys are going to come to Port Show
And they're going to say, hey, you're making extra money
Or for a band or a band with vision
We want our extra money to show from you as well
And asking the sector classes generally in Port Show particular
So I'm just interested to know what your thoughts are
And that would you think maybe you should take their site
This is something
Anyway, I love the show
I love the debate, I love the feedback lines
And the photography
Right on, yeah, right on dude
Glad to hear you in the UK are interested as well
Let them come
You know, they can't extort us
You know, that's the time to go to the government
If the telco start extorting us
And now I remembered what I was going to say
Early when I lost my train of thought
You know, the true thing that has to happen here
And maybe this is something that has to be a part of legislation
It's clearly when you need more choice of providers
If it's really going to be an issue
So in that case we should
Wow, it's my time already up for the satellite
Window, correct?
Yeah, I can't believe I've been yapping way too long
Those of you checking us out on serious stars 102
This is the daily source code
It's part of the pod show lineup
Which you can hear every single week
Day after noon from six to nine, six to ten
Eastern time
Calculate your own darn Pacific times
Speaking of Pacific Pacific Coast, Hellway is next
With Mark Hirsch Motor Nemcoff and I'll see you later
Tomorrow here on stars 102
Okay
Done with net neutrality
I don't think it'll pass anyway
I would be highly surprised
Quick bit about football
I spoke to you a taxi Eric yesterday
He's the guy that does all ground coordination
And transportation for us
And he's a cab driver
But he does a lot
Whenever we're in Holland
Tomorrow I think we'll give him a call
And ask him for an update
He's way into football as you can imagine
I mean like way into it
And he's a funny guy
So he'll give us his predictions
Et cetera on all the games
Maybe we'll make it a regular feature
And call him every day as long as there's an interesting game going on
Hey Adam, this is Casey from Irving Texas
And I call him one time listener
Early just a podcast show
That I was able to find on my machine
Was a 321 and a 2005
We're the way in on the C4 World Cup
And I just express my opinion on why
There may be more than usual
Viewership in the US
I don't think it has to do really necessarily with
Interest in soccer
I think it's a lack of sports
We had at this time of year
He had two very small markets playing
In the NBA final
My hometown of Dallas and Miami
He had even small markets playing
In the NHL
Stanley Cup
Carolina, I'm not sure that's a city or a state
But Carolina and it's even small and marketing
So I think the ESPN is kind of
You know push the soccer thing on us this year
To preseason American football starts
The real football right
It's Lisa's King down here in Texas
And pretty much in the US
You mentioned that
It's not a TV-friendly sport
I feel like it's not much of a viewer-friendly sport
Sometimes the camera angles are odd
And I don't know
At least my opinion is
A little bit I've watched this year
It appears to be 20 guys running around in circles
Two guys kicking the ball back and forth each other
It's actually a nice set of days
If you're trying to get the sleep
All right well thanks and I love the show
You know there's something much bigger going on with football
And look at all these
Look at the countries that are kicking ass
Look at Ghana
Look at the Ukraine
We saw a play yesterday
You know what's great about football
And in this case I'm talking about association football
Soccer
Is that anyone can do it?
You don't need any equipment
You can do it with anything that kind of resembles a ball
And anything that kind of resembles some goal posts
And you can do it with eleven guys
You can do it with three guys
With two guys
You know it's you don't need much
I guess the closest thing next
It would be basketball
But you still need some special equipment for that
And the countries where
It's a way out
You know you can beat you
This is what
Maradona and Paylay were all about
Is you know local boy makes it huge on the world stage
And the world stage of course
Includes a lot of other countries besides the United States
And this has been going on for a while
In the US you kind of you play high school ball
Then you go to the right college
There's a whole system that will bring you right through
Into into the major leagues of whatever sport it is
And with soccer you know
You just play your ass off
And anyone can really do it
And that's you see the street fighter mentality of a lot of these countries
And I think that is beautiful to see
About the television direction
Yeah
I'm not quite sure I should look into that
Who's responsible for all the for the telecast
If it's all being done by German crews
You know I think there could be a lot more
When I look at it on ABC is an example
Man they're really adding a lot of graphics
And they have the commentary
And it's also an important part is who's calling the game
But it is much more than just about the ball
You know it really is about you know
Hey look at look at this kid he came from nothing
He's kicking ass he's representing our country
It's a whole pride thing
Um
Not unlike the European the Eurovision is so fast of all
Yo Adam it's Martin from
Wevel squash center and there's been a strier actually
He'd love to listen to you so dude
It's a little bit bummed up to watching the strier
Go to Italy last night after a referee
The lambda should have gone extra tall
And then we would have won the penalty suit
Anyway, I might love your show to keep it up
And yeah
Yeah
What a night
See you later
Just messing around with my outline here
Hold on a second
Let me just get on this right
Yeah
Just messing around
If you got anything to say
Give me a call on the voicemail numbers
Number in New Jersey which is probably the best for your Skype out
Two zero one six two five six three five seven
In London zero two zero seven six eight one three seven five three
The Earthlink ad challenge still rages on
Um these things are not going through the judging process
I got to get an update and I want to play a couple more new pieces for you
Um
Actually since I moved to the new laptop I had a lot you know a lot of my passwords
I just in Firefox I just say remember
And then of course I forget about them
Well when that in the transition
I was definitely afraid of using any migration tool
So I figured I just start all a fresh all you know all new
And it's really not that much
But it is some stuff like your password file
And yeah, I'm sure I could move it over and whatever
But I'm just kind of going through the motions again
Um
So I can't actually get into the database
And listen to any of the submissions as they come in
But podcasts are now getting into it
Listen to Angie Beast chill cast
She did something with the Roger Smalls
You definitely have to check it at the end of her most recent episode
And even our friends and it'll you're getting into it
Think advertising sucks
Think it gives always the same message again and again
Listen to our revolutionary advertising for Earthlink
Earthlink
You will get late
Frank, remember
With our clink they're going to put their mouth where your money is
Let's Franco from Rockhouse, Detalia
Dude you're outrageous
This of course goes right along with what I said
This is about advertising works
Tell someone that they won't get laid or anything similar to that
And they'll buy your product
It's the way it works
We should try that for the next presidential elections
I'm telling you
Vote for this guy
Or you won't get laid
Go to adchallens.podshow.com
To register your entry
You can win pretty big prizes
And actually we'll use your commercial
Or your endorsement or your jingle
Or your song or whatever
People are getting really creative
So don't think it just has to be something you produce
It can be just you know you talking about it
How should I? How should I? How does this work for daily source code listeners?
You know, it's not and maybe it's only for the source code listeners
It may be the advertising shouldn't work across the board
We want you to tell us
And Earthlink is hooking up with us for the ad challenge
To do just that adchallens.podshow.com
This is Dan Johnson with the journey inside my mind podcast
at jimmpodcast.blogspod.com
And if you come up and take a journey inside my mind
I'll be your host and your tour guide for a trip
Through lots of pod safe music
We'll share a sound seeing tour of two
Lots about what goes on here in our home
And since now you'll hire with me and my wife
And our daughter who happens to be hard of hearing
Yes, that can be an adventure in and of itself
So you'll want to come over and check out
At jimmpodcast.blogspod.com
It's work safe and it's family safe
Good for the entire family
And it's new tris just too
Did I mention it's free?
JIMmpodcast.blogspod.com
Background music provided by Josh Woodward
Off the pod safe music network
With the song Adventures of a Death Dreamer
Right on, what happened from a man goes through his own portal
We'll be journey inside my mind
I do not hear anything
Spent a little bit of time yesterday
And second life of the pod show island
Learning a tremendous amount about people
While doing this
Learning about you know
And once again, it's so interesting to see what happens
Podcasters grouped together
They live together, they talk together, they promote their own shows
They totally, I'm really working on audience
Please
You know this whole whole notion
It's like
It's just
I'm learning a lot about communities
And
Wow you know
I'm so forgetting listeners involved in this
And audience members
And that's what I love about the voicemail feedback
And a lot of the knowledge that I'm garnering
Through just observing how people are in
Oh, let's use the pod us here
And actually how little we project outwards towards
Just people who are listening
It's quite amazing
It really is
And so a lot of that knowledge is being poured straight into pod show
Plus
Hey, we're getting really close
I can say I can safely say
What are we today the 27th
Oh, did you hear that?
Shoot
It's my, oh this is interesting
My mic cable, some
Okay, I had a buzz there and now it's gone
Good
I think within a week
I think I think we're that close
Oh, man
It's going to be so incredibly cool
So on the pod show island
It's a great place to just hang out
Here's something I'm going to try
I'm going to try a live daily source code
Now it'll go out
It'll be recorded as a pod cast
So it will be
You know
Available in the traditional manner
But I'm going to do it live for people who are
At the palace
So it'll be probably fairly music intensive
But I was thinking
You know, we can also hook up
People through Skype
I don't know, I just got this whole mind mel
That I'm working on
I think it could really be a fun experiment for the show
Which of course this is the show
To experiment with all kinds of shit
Whether it's programming in the
In the programming of entertainment
Sense or programming in the code sense
Plenty of spots left over for vendors to come in
Sell some crap on the on
So some podcast and crap if you want
Or advertise your podcast
I saw CC Chapman in there yesterday
He's rented a spot
And we also have
Oh man, learning so much
This is game called
Slingo
Which I guess is a form of
Second life bingo
Man, that's popular
It's really how
Rageously popular
You've got to check it out
Yeah, I'm just
I'm thinking of the way we can do that as well
Outside of second life
This is just
It's really interesting
At the end of the day
All the human elements come out
You know, all we really want to do is
Just hang out
Play games
Watch people play games
And good light
Do you know what you want?
Do you know why you want?
Do you know who made you want it?
Do you know what to do about it?
I do
Listen to partini
Partini is a show about the people who make you want
The stuff you want
And how they do it
Go to partini.com
Now go ahead
Do you know you want to that
Partini.com
You can check out my podcast at the serieshow.com
That's HWBY
Anyways, so
I was sentenced here about
Christina's
Little miss hat that
Steel day
I'm going to call a field day
That's cool
So
I just want to give her my best wishes
And give her a little story
That should
Share her up
I was running track
I'm 15
To
So
I was running track at school
And
It was basically running the mile
For PE
And it's 4th lap of
Drinking around
And
Basically what happened is
My femur broke
My
A little bit of the bone
The thigh bone
The entire thigh bone
Clean cut
It was in the hospital
It felt stone
But I was on morphing
Yes, not
Not nitrous or accept
Morphing
And then
What the surgery and everything
And I'm still going
This is it all
We had so
I hope that Christina
Feels better
And I trust me
I know we're slowing the slowing
Sock
Thanks
Yeah
No kidding
Thanks, dude
Thanks for calling
I'm sure she'll appreciate it
She wasn't quite up to doing a show last night
And of course
We're getting so close to the
Unleash of pod show
Plus the podcast delivery network
The upgraded pod safe music network
It's been really busy
So my my
My actual second life
Which starts around 4 p.m.
Which is 80m San Francisco time
I was pretty busy
It's going to be busy again tonight
All the way up until midnight
Just doing all the meetings
Trying to fit in with the schedule
San Francisco
Sometimes a little tough
On the
The home life here
But
Ah, these girls are so flexible
So anyway
So we'll do a pod save the queen tonight
That'll go up and
So you can be able to listen to that
By tomorrow
So an update on
Am I via
On
Imagine that
Adam Curry
Using windows
Using a non apple product
It was this a comment that I got
That maybe want to talk about this with you
Hey Adam this is David
I'm son in California
That's tunes entertainment.com
My show is behind the wedding bay
The wedding mic
And we talk about weddings and things going on
In the wedding industry
And about this track
These are music
And I love your show today
I'm referencing the show
4-0-9
The copyright issue
It's really cool
I really like that
You talked about things going on
A little technical
I'm a little bit of a technique
But I really like when you lean into it
Not so much
Well you take away all your other funds
That's like talking about the games
And the soccer
Where it came from
And the porn stuff
Now you could go with that
The text type
This time I pour a lip
Of these things
Did you imagine that you would bring chocolate
An apple again
Fly high
F Billy
Bribe
Your best friend
But one thing that I think is
Boy
Dr Kaitlin
Clark
I liked the
gypt
You know, but they haven't done anything about it, so I don't know what the future holds,
but I know Canada does have a license to where they can copy and use different formats
for their music and they pay one fee.
The U.S.A. has nothing like that.
That's not entirely true.
The establishment has to pay ASCAP BMI rights for a disjockey performing, but I appreciate
the fact that you like the geeky stuff, because I'm going to get just a little geeky
on your ass.
I can hear people around the net going, oh no, he's going geeky.
I'd love this via.
I got to tell you, you know what happens?
You use a piece of software or a gadget or something, maybe early on, and I guess what
you'd call an early adopter.
And you use this very early on and you see all the shortcomings and usually it eventually
winds up propping up a table somewhere or discarded or sent off or given away or whatever.
That experience sticks with you for a long, long time.
My whole experience with Windows, and particularly the hardware part, I know what Windows
is the operating system does, but there's no tight integration between the Windows operating
system.
Microsoft doesn't make PCs, so they don't really have a lock on, okay, this is how we're
going to do it.
It makes it much tighter, much easier, which is exactly what Apple does.
But they have fixed a lot of things.
I have to say, you know, I plugged in on my wireless keyboard stuff, it worked immediately.
I can plug in cards, SD memory cards, a lot of the drivers, this UNP and P, or universal
plug and play, it does kind of work.
This via laptop has a camera built in and guess what, it kind of works.
Stuff that I never could get to work on the Mac or with a lot of issues, unless I'm
using their dedicated software, and you know, I got to say, I'm just, it's not bothering
me that much.
At all, in fact, I'm really enjoying the speed of it, it is definitely the fastest computer
I've ever had.
Now, I think this has a dual core processor, so it's, it's hot shit that's going on inside.
Yeah, there's, you know, you have to kind of figure it out, each manufacturer puts different
things in, and it has different widgets and software, and you know, they're all pretty
much related.
It's the stuff that, you know, does not come in Windows that pertains particularly to the
hardware, so you have to kind of figure it out, and I think Sony does a pretty good job.
You know, I'm able to mix and match my monitors, a docking station, when I undock, you
know, it used to be, you'd undock, and you'd basically have to reboot Windows, don't have
to do that anymore.
So it really has come into its own, I have to say, yeah, it's, it's not bad, I can't
tell you any, any different, you know, and there's little applications for all the things
that I was doing on the Mac, and yeah, you have to learn different key commands, and it's
nice about it, you can customize it, you can do a lot of customization.
My Sony Vio looks very much like a Mac, it's got the Mac background, the icons, I have
a dock, I've got, I've got an Apple menu, which I never really use that much on the, on
the Mac either.
I have a control H command now for hide, and there's a few things that you have to kind
of learn, but it's just, it's not that bad, I'm sorry, I just can't hate it.
Hey Adam, it's Carl here, I swear tonight, if you, if you're considering actually
going back to the Macs, when the new things just come out, or if you'll be thinking
about going for Windowsista, thanks, bye.
Well, so there's two things you asked there, one is about hardware, and the other is
about new software, I don't really care about Windows Vista, I have no idea what it would
do, you know, what, you know, I'm sure it has all kinds of technological things, oh, by
the way, for those of you who were using something like QuickSilver or Spotlight, I installed
Google Desktop, and I really like it, because you just hit the control key twice, and it pops
up right in the middle of your screen, a little search bar, and you type in your search
request.
Now if you're looking for an application, you can set it so that it brings up the application
and documents first that are on your, on your machine, so if I want to start cast blast,
so I just hit the control key quite twice, and then CA, and it comes up cast blast, or
when I hit go, and cast blast, or launches, you know, that's the type of speed stuff that
I really had figured out on the Mac, and I'm figuring it out on Windows, and, and I know
this hardware is going to hang together, you know, the Sony has a great QA process, and
they do make great consumer products, they've been at a huge disadvantage, it's not
pretty, it's nice, I like the keyboard, especially, really big keys, it feels very nice.
I have to stretch a little bit more than I was used to on the Toshiba, but it's not
as beautiful, I mean, they should hire a couple of real designers, and it would be even
better, the screen is phenomenal on this thing, you know, it's got, it has a edge network,
networking, if I want it, and it's got all the ports, it's got everything you need, and
with the Mac, you know, I've been following along with the new MacBook Pros, and I'm
now I'm seeing it from a little bit of a distance, and I'm seeing people going through
the Wi-Fi not working, the overheating, Joey Eto has been writing on his web log about how
we can't use it on an airplane, because it draws so much power, it keeps popping, fuse,
breakers, circuit breakers in the plane, so you then have to turn it off, and then it has to
charge, and then it's just, you know, all kinds of nightmares, I think they're on their fourth
series of of power books by now, and I'm just seeing the people saying, oh, okay, you know,
I'll go for the next one, or wait for the next one, or I'll get it upgraded, and, you know,
it can't just be beautiful, and yeah, the operating system is I love Unix, I grew up on Unix,
but I just don't use the command line that more anymore, you know, I just don't need to create
little quick applications, and pipe stuff out from one process to another, and if I needed to,
well, you know, I could probably find an application that does what I want to do, because
you know, Windows does have a lot more people developing for it, so I don't know if I'll
go back, I mean, I like the mix, you know, I still have a Mac here in the office, a Mac downstairs,
but for my real productivity machine, the one that I live on, my window to the world,
I got to tell you, so far, so good for the Sony Vio. Hey Charlie fans, Brian here from
Procrasticast. I think I just found a great way to get high, turning on a musician to the
pod safe music network. So the other day, Jeremy Row, a musician who lives way up here in Michigan's
upper peninsula where I do, stops over at the house, well, the Procrasticast studios.
And we did a show together, which you can find over at audioaditude.com if you're so inclined.
Anyway, guess what? After that, he decided to upload one of his songs to the PMN.
Is that cool or what? The song, in line to die, it's about a good friend of Jeremy's facing
redeployment to a rack. Now on the pod safe music network, as if that's not cool enough,
Hey Jeremy, put this in your bowl and enjoy the buzz. A debut on the daily source code.
Kick an ass. Jeremy Row, within line to die.
There's a cold window, no way for combat. There's time, I am shaking.
We have a familiar feeling.
Jeremy Row, within line to die, it's about a good friend of Jeremy Row,
and we have a good friend of Jeremy Row, and we have a good friend of Jeremy Row and we have a good friend of Jeremy Row
and we have a good friend of Jeremy Row and we have a good friend of Jeremy Row and we have a good friend of Jeremy Row
and we have a good friend of Jeremy Row and we have a good friend of Jeremy Row
and we have a good friend of Jeremy Row, within line to die, it's about a good friend of Jeremy Row
and we have a good friend of Jeremy Row, in line to die, the pot say from music network,
I know that this show gets downloaded in portions of Iraq and Afghanistan by members of the coalition.
We're thinking of you guys and gals as well.
All right, that's it for the show for today.
I'll be back tomorrow, same, I'm just gonna say, same time.
That depends on you, doesn't it?
So yeah, I guess it will be the same time.
Same time.
A daily source code.com is where you can find the podcast feed the latest episodes.
Curried.com for your general feedback.
And of course, anything else is welcome through adamantcurried.com.
Looking forward to hearing from you guys again tomorrow.
If you're looking for a fantastic deal on a domain name, go daddy.com.
Use the checkout code DSC3.
And you'll get that for only $6.95.
See you tomorrow, everybody. Bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it.
On the high performance pod cast, a delivery network from Podjo
and line-wight networks.
I love it.
Thanks for watching.