For the first time ever, the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr. in one action-packed DVD collection,
own all 27 episodes, the cult hit, including all new interviews with Carlton Koo.
First thing that Brisco did that impressed us was, we're not only to come in and really read the dialogue well as an actor,
but he also did a standing flip in our office.
You flipped too for Brisco County!
If you like the kind of TV you can't get on TV, get your copy of the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr.
Available now on DVD!
Hi, this is Andy Rooney. Have you ever noticed that Adam Curry is up to 473 shows?
Why is that? Is it because he has nice hair?
I used to have nice hair, and then at all turn gray because I started getting real cranky,
and my doctor says it somehow related to my heredity.
But 473 shows is just amazing!
I do a weekly show, and if I wanted to do 473 shows, I'd have to do one every week for over nine years.
That's what that of vacation, and I kind of like my vacations.
So Koo knows that, I'm Curry here and all, that's just amazing 473 shows on the Daily Source Cup.
I think I'm flying into the future.
KK, this way, okay this is all too late KK, this way, okay this is all too late KK, this way, okay this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late K
KK, this is all too late KK, this is all, this is it KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all better KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, here has been decided KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, it's all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is all too late KK, this is
I can't wait, I can't wait
I can't wait, thinking of you
With all the thoughts you could be through
I'll tell you for days and days
I can't hold my knees and die
Oh, I can't take it anymore
Just to know that we've fallen no more
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey
I can't wait I can't wait
I can't wait, I can't wait
Fire Apes.
Hey Kate from the pod safe music network
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
It's Wednesday coming to you
from the Couricotteage in the affluent
supper of Surrey Known as Gilford
It is the daily source code
Episode 4703 already
I still wonder if I shouldn't just
shit.
I do appreciate you sending in those customized intros because it doesn't make it that
much more exciting.
And really, of course, it's been more episodes of 473.
I've got a comment today from someone who said he's been listening a little bit longer
than that.
Hi, Adam.
It's 4am for Nichols, of transport, of dot com.
I'm just weird.
I was like, I've been listening to your shirts for two years, nice to be able to use that.
Yeah.
And, um, Blimey, I remember when it was, uh, the DSC, uh, message me as a Charlie.
Uh, you didn't number the shows.
I think the first time I listened to your show, or a ran the first time, um, you're
waiting for the cash results from your mum, um, and, um, you're just as good as Matt Weinstein.
And, um, um, I'm just trying to see why me, it just seems so long ago.
It's been a bit of a lifetime, really, but two years got just been really quite quickly
long this time.
But same day, another way, so, anyway, there we are, um, all this.
So, yep.
I'll fold it at least.
Bye.
Yeah, thanks Paul.
Yeah, you know, uh, so much has happened.
We think about it.
We've been doing this for quite a while, haven't we?
And time flies when you're having fun.
Man, oh, man.
Oh, man.
You're right, Paul.
Wow.
It's, uh, that was still when I was living at the Curry Castle in Belgium.
Uh, so it's, uh, it's Wednesday morning and, uh, got home, uh, relatively late last night
because we had our, our, uh, London live, uh, I'd have to say extra have against almost
because it was, it wasn't just one event or one show that we were doing.
It was, uh, really a conicopia of programming all from the roundhouse, which is a, uh, actually
that's where Hendrix played, um, hasn't the who played there as well.
I mean, it's recently refurbished and, um, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
and the Digital Music Awards 2006 for being held there, which is sponsored by our partner
here in the UK British Telecom.
And it was, it was a lot of fun, um, uh, I'm sure that most of you, looking from the statistics
and, uh, even some of the problems for some people getting into seeing the streams, most of
you who listed the show may have, uh, taken a peeker to, it was a lot of fun, uh, we recorded
a couple different programs, but also streamed everything live as it was going out.
And I have to say, it had a very, uh, I think I said this before, it had one of those
real good live fields to it.
You know, I was sitting at home in the morning, uh, watching all this stuff just happening
live and, and what was so cool is that it was, no one was really briefed about what was
going on.
Um, yes, of course, the, the, the people that we had hired to host the shows and to produce
it, and they know what podcasting is, but didn't necessarily come out of the podcast
in community.
There is, of course, a beautiful podcast in community in the UK, but we purposely went, uh,
for something a little bit different, and we found, uh, some guys who helped us out
with, uh, with the video, um, you know, we really, it was, it was old old school, man.
It was like Scotch tape and, uh, and bailing wire was just stringing everything together,
but we have footage of everything from beginning to end.
Of course, the actual, uh, award ceremony itself took place.
It was recorded by, uh, um, channel four.
I think this Saturday, they're doing some kind of highlights.
Uh, I haven't even seen the newspapers today.
Of course, uh, I'm, um, I'm well aware of who the winners were and, uh, the most exciting
one, of course, with the podcast category was kind of interesting.
We came into the game pretty late, and I think that of all the nominations for podcast,
only one was a completely independent podcast.
The other ones were, um, I think BBC, I believe there was a couple radio stations who had
podcast that were nominated, but the London electricity podcast, uh, one by, like, like,
10 miles worth of votes.
Uh, and I was so pleased that it was the only independently produced podcast that was nominated
that actually won.
So that was extremely cool.
You know, uh, dinner wasn't your typical rubber chicken dinner.
Actually, it was, it was pretty decent.
And the performances were great, although, you know, this is so typical when you get a venue
like the roundhouse, which has just been refurbished, it's completely redone, it's beautiful.
And, um, I think the soundproofing has changed.
Everything has really been redone and rethought and it's, it's a great venue.
But the, uh, the sound in the house meant it, although, perfect, they turned it up just too
loud.
I mean, when, when glasses start to shatter because they're touching each other because
the basses is reverberating.
So, you know, all the way through to the end of the, uh, to the back, to the back of the,
of the venue.
And we were up front, of course, uh, then you know, something was just going on.
It was way too loud.
With some fun stuff happened, uh, let's see Peter Gabriel drop by and he hung out, uh,
we got him on the stream and, uh, and of course, that'll also be on, uh, a number of
different shows.
It, um, what I, what I'm, really, what, what, what, what I've learned is, and I, I mentioned
this yesterday on the show.
I really do miss, um, that live feel.
Uh, I love doing my podcast and, you know, and it, yeah, it takes time to do it every
single day, but I, I do it, I love it.
I love just getting up doing it.
I know you guys are going to hear it eventually.
And we, you know, I have a real feeling and a vibe as to how it flows and how people
listening.
But when you do something live, it is very, very different.
And there is a whole different type of excitement.
And I think that we're going to be doing a lot more live, particularly with video.
I think we'll be doing a lot more live stuff because, you know, it's live at the moment
it's live.
And then there's all the stuff that you can pull out of it that can obviously be time
shifted and and download it and enjoy your convenience in the podcast delivery format.
But at the end of the day, it's all independently produced stuff.
It's all stuff that, you know, talent people who have the tools and the distribution
are just making things.
And I'm, uh, I was excited already, uh, about what we're doing.
But just doing that last night really brought a lot of things back to me.
Uh, you know, I remember a lot of the live MTV shoots.
You just can't parallel that excitement, particularly when there's a party.
So I think we'll be doing a lot more.
There's, there's something else coming up, which I think is, is it end of October or November?
It's in the city in London, which is a huge independent music event throughout the entire
city.
And it really is the event in the UK.
I have a feeling we might do something with that because we've just learned so much.
And the audience clearly was into it.
As we could tell from all the traffic coming through on on the streams.
Yo, Adam.
Yo, truck time.
I heard you complaining that you didn't think there was enough audio coming out of the
portable media expo that was held this last weekend in Ontario, California.
And I wanted to make you and everyone else aware that I recorded a bunch of audio while
I was there.
I was able to attend and been rolling that out ever since the Saturday night that it began
and coming up over the next few days.
And next week, I was able to record an interview with Father Roderick that does the
Daily Breakfast Podcast and the Catholic Insider Podcast.
I've got an interview I recorded with Brad Gibson that does the Bradcast.
Yes, the Bradcast is back.
Also have an interview I recorded with Chris Mark court.
Of course, Chris does the tips from the top floor, digital photography podcast.
Last but not least, I've got an interview I recorded with Bruce Murray that does the
Zedcast.
You can check all of these out at trucker-tombpodcast.com or trucker-tomb.podge-show.com.
We'll see you later, my friend, and you have a good one.
Alright, T2, trucker-tomb.
Yeah, that is the other side of it.
I really am bummed that I didn't get to hang out and hook up with everybody at the podcast
that I spoke.
It looked like everyone had a great time.
Both involved and not involved with Podshow.
And it looked like it was a very successful event and everybody had a good time and I
have been listening to Podcast now as I started to flow out.
There is always that delayed effect.
You know, when you go to a blogger's type conference, it's always live happening at the
very second because it's much easier to write and post something that it is to record,
perhaps edit and upload.
I saw some amazing video on our UnExpo2 feed.
Marion Carley in the pool, I'm still live on that Michelle from whispered pearls apparently.
Also in the pool, Michael Butler, she sent me an email and said, you know, I sent
them, I gave a naked picture of me to Michael Butler to give to you.
Hey, Butler, dude, stop Jones and William, I mean, not Jones and what is it?
Stop, harshen.
Stop, pass it on, then.
Come on, Butler, where's the picture?
Hey, Adam, how you doing Darren here with extreme Pods.com.
Hey, I, on the Asparagus P and being compatible with my wife and I both have that gene.
So maybe you're on to something there, but my wife would be a, a wrap around the fingers
then a folder and I would be a scruncher.
So there goes your theory right out the window on that one.
Okay, well, we're still going to continue.
I do believe that the compatibility of Asparagus, skunk, smelling people, that if you both
have the same gene, maybe you do belong together, that's a theory working on now.
I have to agree that it does not seem that there's any correlation between being able
to smell or smell like Asparagus be and being a folder or a scruncher.
And also, thanks for everything you did down at the expo, we had fun with all the Pods
show family down there, room of girls on and group, Pods, sick, amateur travel.
All those guys were a blast, who'd like to say, thanks to you and thanks to Pods.
So have a good one and check out extreme Pods.com.
Bye, I'm in.
Hope everyone had a good time.
Ah, Sunday, I head off to San Francisco for a couple of weeks.
It'll be good to be back in, in San Fran at Pods Show HQ.
It's been, how was it been now two months already?
It's just been a long time.
Not that I don't mind being home, mind you.
It's going to be interesting because we're still working on the house with the covenant
before the garage.
It's not going to have to be doing that with eight hour times own difference, which always
makes things a little bit more interesting and challenging.
But I think we're going to get this done really, really hope so it'll be so nice to just
have a place to call our own finally instead of being stuck in the rentals.
So it's still got a busy week ahead.
In fact, when I finish up and get the show up today, I'm off to London because this week
was not just for fun and games and for making content, but also for a number of sales
calls.
So we're hitting a number of agencies and advertisers that we've been teeing up and lining
up for our official launch or unleash, I should say, of Pods Show in the UK.
You can tell we're already doing this a little bit differently than a year ago, basically.
And also, it's a whole different country.
So there's different things and different ideas we want to try out.
And of course, we have a partner here.
So there's a lot to be done.
And also more meetings with more creative people who want to do some podcasters and just
non-podcaster or podcaster virgins, I would say, who just have some creative juice
they want to let go.
So that'll be most of this week.
Probably we'll get a shot every single day.
I'm hoping.
And then, of course, the trip will be on Sunday.
So I'll be back on Monday, obviously.
I'm going to miss the girls because I always do.
It's been here so long that now I really know I'm going to miss the girls.
They tried to stop us.
They tried to move us.
But we're back.
It's the Pod Show music rewind, audition to pool party.
We're featuring the hottest podcasters on the planet.
Canna Slupis.
I'm doing fine.
I'm on about 3rd or 4th Corona.
So I'm good.
Drew Domkiss.
Square One is that they're around.
And they're Dawn's favorites.
She's had them for years.
My gold bookler.
By the way, Marcus's wife really wants to bang me.
And GB.
Yeah, I was a virgin to the podcas.
Expo before.
This is my first time.
C.C. Chapman.
The head home for I do.
What's up?
C.C.
I've been seeing you all a lot.
I've been running around like crazy.
I know.
I've been going to party after party, after sweet, after party.
And you know.
Please help me.
Brother Long.
Thank you for baking that special.
I appreciate that.
Julian Smith.
What's up, man?
I just got alcohol in my eyes.
I'm not going to explain to you how that happened.
But it did.
The test drive girl.
Hi.
Brent Bradley, booze and networking.
That's it.
In that order.
Yeah.
Bill Fortune.
50,000 wants something like a million.
MB.
I am hanging out with podcasting music royalty.
J.A. Donley.
Rock roll geeks at high to your life.
And how's everything going on?
Uh, good.
I'm very secure with that.
Okay.
Joe Clyde.
Are you ready to rock?
Jasper Borgman.
I've never seen or tasted anything like a Richard Bruer.
Hey.
To use an arrow.
I think we could put a good job this time.
Joe performance by Whitney Steel and Jimmy Golding.
I enjoyed it thoroughly.
Thank you very much for the experience.
With your congenial host, Marcus Couch.
Download episode 45 now at rewind.podshow.com.
To reach Adam in America, dial.
1, 2, 1, 6, 2, 5, 6, 3, 5, 7.
Okay.
For Adam in Great Britain, dial.
Plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3.
Plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3.
Thanks for going to Daily Source Code.
Goodbye.
Oh.
Folder's congenial.
Hey there.
I'm Christina Curry, one of the hosts of the BG Blast.
Be sure to tune in to this week's episode where I showcase new music by Melo Bright
Van.
Sean J. and more.
Listen to hear about the exciting hollow scream promotion where one lucky listener will
get a free trip to Bush Gardens.
We even learn about hippo camps.
And I share the star of my most recent drama in the dressing room of London's
pop shop clilling star.
Tune in this week and check it out.
I was pretty cool last night when we walked down the red carpet.
So it was me, Ron, his wife, Marta.
Patricia, as you know, couldn't come because of the dental surgery.
She felt really shitty and still feels bad today.
So I had my daughter on my arm.
Man, she's so beautiful.
And of course, as we're walking up the red carpet and the photographers are flashing.
Then Olivia, who was doing the London live red carpet coverage for us.
You know, she asks Marta, what are you wearing?
And I think it was all Gucci.
And then she says to Christina, what are you wearing?
Christina says top shop, of course.
Which is so cute.
Anyone who lives in the UK knows what I'm talking about.
That was very fun.
Let's see about five minutes left before the satellite window closes.
Daily from writing with the windows down sent me a comment about foldering or scrunching,
which I've not listened to.
So should we take the gamble together?
I think we can.
Hey, Adam Chris daily here from the PMC Top 10 at pod music countdown.com.
And I have some information for your folder structure database.
I have sent you a copy of the image from playboy February 1994.
The one with anonical Smith as a red hot Valentine on the cover.
But inside is the real story in a section of random facts.
It's said, according to a survey by the makers of northern bathroom tissue.
Percentage of Americans who wrapped their toilet paper around their hand in the prepping stage 30.
Percentage who fold it 30 percentage who crumple 40.
So we're talking way back in 1994.
Northern bathroom tissue did a survey 30 percent folders 40 percent scrunchers
and another 30 percent who wrap it around and then fold it.
I know I've kept this a secret through all my comments.
I'm one of those 30 percent who wraps it around and then folds it.
So I'm a modified folder.
Just a more info to add to the extensive folder scruncher database.
And you know, I always end my shows by saying keep it real.
It doesn't get any more real than folding and scrunching.
Next Chris.
Okay, 12 years ago, though.
I think that the makeup of that those percentages may have changed a little bit.
I really believe folders are on the rise.
Remember whenever you call into the phone lines.
Let us know if you're a folder or scruncher.
The consensus or the census does continue.
And eventually we're going to publish our scientificly found results that I promised you.
One more song from the pod save music now.
We're this one showed up on the top 10 that was played yesterday, top 10 pod plays.
And I really like that it's hip hop, but it has a strong message.
And I'm just a sucker for a great audio sample.
So even though we face the difficulties of today and tomorrow,
I still have a dream.
It is a dream deeply rooted in the American dream.
I have a dream.
It's one thing.
This nation will rise up.
Live out the true meaning of its dream.
We hold these truths to be self-evident.
And hold me in our creativity.
I have a dream.
To take a nation of willingness to hold this back.
Brown for sport.
I have a dream.
To take a nation of willingness to hold this back.
A game civil rights bill voting rights,
Axe, ass, modern day Jesus.
Turnin' under cheek, some blacks like dog,
that's weak.
I'm not lookin' to give me deep in the next week.
My everyday life is pretty brutality.
Maca picked up Axe and dropped his slave name.
Radical change to fence by any means.
When our hearts turn back,
select our protection.
Why sublacks shall we enlist together?
They're race crimes.
People that don't care, warfare or watch tier guests,
bullets flying.
GMK, gotta assassinate it.
And they're okay.
He got assassinated.
Malcolm X, got assassinated.
So it's up to us to keep that dream alive.
Freedom ring, freedom ring, freedom ring.
I have a dream ring.
That's a lot of things to do with you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All that freedom ring, freedom ring.
Freedom ring, freedom ring.
I have a dream ring.
The creating of criminal truth,
and one who thinks he calls the evil self,
a favor for freedom.
My blamed him from the cockpit, is his maker.
Flowcabulari, let's freedom ring
from the pod save music network. Of course, the link to that in the show notes today at daily
source code dot com. See, I told you it was a little different, but I kind of dug it.
Sidelight windows closing everybody on serious. Those of you still hanging out for the podcast,
you are in luck because, uh, well, it's a more cool shit to listen to.
Oh, baby, you've got us. You've got us completely. And from now on, Adam, every orgasm, we have
as a pod show orgasm. This is Michelle at whisper pearls. My sister and I are very happy to
join the pod show family. Thanks, Adam. whisper pearls now at whisper pearls dot pod show dot com.
Yay. I love that. As nothing like sitting on a 10 hour flight listening to girls talk with
low sexy voices about having sex. That is the true magic of whisper pearls. Is your computer
a hacker magnet? It won't be anymore because Earthlinke is here to save the day.
With Donald's faster than speeding bullet. And far while it is more powerful, going to look
on the motor. It has an anti-virus system that cleanses your PC with the click of a mouse.
It's a bird. It's a plane. It's Earthlinke. Perfect internet from outer space that
links to Earth with powers and abilities far greater than those of normal high speed. And prices
so low that it will blow you out of this world. So make the right decision and turn to Earthlinke
as your internet provider. All right, everybody, that's it. I really got to get dressed,
which would require a shower before that. So I got to go. I got to get off the London town again.
Thank you so much for tuning in. As always, Adam and pod show dot com to send you love. And
dig me at atom dot pod show dot com. And of course, daily source code dot com is where you can
find the show notes for links to everything mentioned and played in today's show, particularly
the pod save music. I'll be back tomorrow. Everybody take care of yourself. Thank you so much for listening.
Bye. I mean, really. Thank you for listening. Bye. Bye. Bye.