Delta Shara Charly 3-1
7-
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass
3 minutes?
Than the next generation radio content in my ears
We don't need no thinking 3 minutes?
I like to think I'm flying into this jar
Fantastic!
It's a battle curry
Good morning, good afternoon, good evening, wherever you may be
This is your daily source code coming to you once again from the
And this moment kind of dark and chilly
Oh man!
Northern California, it's a hit for Cisco, direct from the condo
Kicking off with the butterfly catchers
We come, wake up and climb
You've been asleep so long, I die
No, not just a time
Get up and climb
Don't you realize we could set the world apart
Because here I am
I'm coming to say that
Even if you don't want to be safe
Well here I am
I'm coming to get you
Think we know I like just for this day
You're so annoying
I know you've been trying
Just trying to make it through the day
You've been lying
You can't cry
But believe me, baby
Where I say
We've done
Wake up and sing
Stand up
Stand up and shout
You and I salute you, can't find your way out
I'm coming to say that
Even if you don't want to be safe
Yeah here I am
I'm coming to get you
Think we know I like just for this day
You're so annoying
I know you've been trying
Just trying to make it through the day
You've been lying
You can't cry
But believe me, baby
Where I say
We've done
Wake up to me
You're so annoying
I know you've been trying
Just trying to make it through the day
Think we know we like just for this day
Think we know I like just for this day
And then pretty song, butterfly catchers wake up from the potsafe music network.
So you can find the music.punch.com, direct link, we'll show up in the show notes.
And a wonderful start of the show with that fine audio skipping problem in my $2.5,000
power book.
I figured I'd just let it go, I wasn't going to restart the show or anything, because
at least we've had it right, it's behind us and hopefully it won't happen again.
So it's Tuesday, I thought that was kind of a nice tune, you know, to ease us into Tuesday
and kind of, you know, like the week is already started, we're not halfway, you know,
just kind of chill.
I think I've actually played that song before, but I was listening last night before I went
to bed.
I was listening to the ultimate mix podcast, ultimate mix dot blogspot.com and it was actually
was a very mellow show by itself, and there were a whole bunch of really good tunes,
including the butterfly catchers, so I figured I'd play that for you.
It's been a long, long day, yeah, shoot, I don't know, what is it, maybe 16 hour
day, it feels like it's, it is technically, it's actually Tuesday just about everywhere
in the world now, but I'm just kind of getting back from from a late late dinner, and
of course, a long day at Pod Show headquarters, man, it was holiday, Martin Luther King day,
and it was not compulsory to come to work, but just by everybody showed up anyway, which
is very cool.
I'm missing some of my acute come on here, let me see, one of my missing, I don't have
my, oh my gosh, we'll never be able to end the show because I don't have my lighter,
my T is just out of reach and this microphone doesn't have the same dynamics as it does
back at the cottage.
So there's going to be a lot of cool stuff coming up this week.
Now for those of you who haven't been listening to the source code since it started, which
was well over a year and a half ago, this really is the show we test out a lot of stuff.
In fact, it started out as a show that really was just for software developers, and
I would tell them about my experiences with their software, and they would use my show
to test their software, and it got a lot of things rolling in the Pod Catching community,
the software developers predominantly, and as we're getting ready to start to roll out
the Pod Show Pod Cast delivery network, it's just a part of the Pod Cast network itself.
We're going to be testing it on this show, so expect stuff to be all over the map, and
expect weird stuff to show up, and I'm hoping that you will help me out and give me your
feedback.
You guys have been great, all listeners have been fantastic, not just give me feedback on the
content of the show, but the audio quality about feeds that are breaking about download
issues, so it's very, very helpful, and I'm just kind of for warning you right up front,
that stuff is definitely going to be all over the map, so that should probably start happening.
I hope as soon as tomorrow, and from then we're going to start moving in some new podcasters
who are joining the network, and of course, we'll be migrating our existing Pod Squad into
the new architecture, so it's just so much happening, and here's another guy who's going to be
part of the big mess, hitting you right between the years with the message of hope, love, and
good news, this is LifeSpring. Hey Adam Steve Web here, wow, who would have thought back
well, Tunnel members ago, when you played the very first LifeSpring promo back when you were at the
Curry Castle, that a scant 14 months later, the LifeSpring podcast would be a part of the greatest
podcasnet work in the world, podshow, as you know, I was one of the original godcasters, and now,
partnering with podshow, we can really kick it up enough enough. I'm telling you, I love
religious podcasters. Excellent, thanks Adam for the invitation, and I'm really looking forward to
quitting my day job, and thanks everybody for listening. I'm out of here.
Thanks everybody. Oh man, perfect. It seems like it doesn't even seem that long ago, and then again,
when you hear that audio, you think, wow, that was a long time ago. Well, we welcome the LifeSpring
podcast Steve Web into the podshow podcasnet work, and it's great to see a godcaster jumping on board,
and just having all kinds of fantastic ideas about where we can take pod casting, very excited about
it, Steve, and great to have you on board. Let me see, we're going to be, we will do a brief
Metrosexual moment. I tried to plan a little bit earlier, so our friends on the satellite,
a serious satellite star is 103, who sometimes missed the Trinity and the Multi, the Multi-sexual.
Yeah, there you go. The Metrosexual moment. I got to tell you the story. I had dinner with Ron and his wife
Marta, and they were at a family function over the weekend, and I think the conversation came
down to women's handbags, and I think it was basically a fashion conversation, and Marta loves
handbags, and actually I've been shopping with Ron. I've been pretty impressed when he knew exactly
which handbag to pick out as a gift, and Marta bless her heart. So the conversation came up about
Ron having this, this knack, this capability, this skill set, and they were in a restaurant.
She said, well, you know, my husband is the true transsexual, and of course she meant Metrosexual.
Needless to say, down there in Atlanta, they were pretty surprised about Mr. Bloom and his many
many talents. Hey Adam, I'm a relatively new listener. My name is Alex. I am totally hooked
to podcasting. I can't wait to get my show off the road. I anxiously await the pod show delivery
network is a first thing to put my podcast together. A comment about advertising effectiveness.
Since listening to your show, I purchased or I've had bought for me basically because I asked
the following items. And I dog, the mock three turbo razor, egg knot, countless songs on iTunes,
music store, a bunch of songs are downloaded from the pod safe music network, which I will gladly
pay for. And a $300 connection for the iPod to play in my new car. But here's the best.
I've actually switched from a lifetime of MSDOS based PC machines. And last week, I purchased a totally
souped up power book G4. That's right. I have become a Mac user directly because of your
comments regarding Apple computer products. Thank you. Thank you. All right. All right. Calm down.
I apologize. It's just an operating system for crying out loud. Directly because your comments
I decided to actually go to a store and look at the Mac in detail and I fell in love with it.
I can't thank you enough for pushing me in this direction. As far as the coffee machine,
I think I'll stick with my Nespresso by Nestle. Nothing can come close to this product.
Not even your beloved Sinceo. I will be highlighting Nespresso on my podcast and hope to get Nestle
as a sponsor. Wait a minute. I don't have a podcast yet. Fuck.
Damn. Okay. It's a good podcast that I want to do. About last father's day, my wife and
kids bought me a brand new guitar. I've always wanted to play. And this Christmas, I received
guitar lessons. My podcast will be one man's journey to learn to play the guitar the hard way.
Sixth string torture is going to be the name of it. It's going to be an acoustic guitar program
featuring indie artists from the pod save music network from garage band from my space.
Any other independent artists source I can find. Each episode, I want to devote a segment
also to promos of other acoustic podcasts like acoustic cafes, outstanding. I'd like to do an
IMAX moment that highlights and lists the songs that are in a acoustic IMAX on iTunes.
I'm not going to play the music. I'm just going to discuss what's available, the free download,
the week, etc. And finally, the meat of the podcast will be a torture me section.
It's going to be a segment which I review and discuss in sample and internet related learn how to
play guitar site. There's a lot of them on the site. I'll also play clips from my real guitar lessons
so you can hear my instructor torture me while simultaneously being tortured by my playing.
I need help putting this together at him. It seems so friggin easy, but I just can't get over the
hump of designing the actual show. If there's anyone a pod show that can help me, I would be forever
grateful. I need equipment too, at least I think I do. I have a great mic, headphones, my new
power book, and with the new I web and garage band, I probably have what I need. I don't have a mixer
and I don't have a mobile recording device yet. Hey wait, I have an idea. Since Chris Rockwell's
being such a loser and literally not giving a shit to us anymore, maybe he can donate his equipment
to someone that will actually put it to good use. Thanks again for doing what you do and doing
what you do to make what we are doing doable. Hey don't steal that phrase, that phrase pal.
It's a line of one of my new songs. I told you my music was the torture. Take care and have a happy
and healthy process me. Thanks again. Nobody listen. Now the reason why I played this for you
for basically a promo for a podcast that doesn't yet exist is I just want you here that thinking
because this is literally how simple it is. Actually, I think he's gone quite far in this thinking
about he's actually describing a format of a show. It's something he's passionate about, something
that he'll be able to, it goes along with a pair of parallels and interest that he already has.
I'll be tracking the podcast. This is kind of interesting because now I've been able to hear
the idea from inception, looking forward to hearing how execution goes. Of course,
it seems like a lot of work to get a podcast together when you listen to that and that of course
is a part of what I'll be testing out this week is a lot of those tools that make it really
as simple as just recording, filling out your show notes and clicking a button. Everything else
is more or less done for you. There's something else I was going to say. Oh yes about pod
safe music this morning when I got a bless Chris, Chris Rockwell's hard man. So he's back
and I had a whole dealing with all kinds of family business but still he's on the machine and
he sent me a link and today I actually made my first purchase of a track off the pod safe music
network and it was just the, I mean it's funny because of course I've done a store before,
you know I bought something online but to see it actually work and then to have the track
right there the download it and have it play it was just it was a great experience so it completely works
and we're working on some some design stuff and well then of course we have to complete
the terms for artists who are interested in participating and then we're going to just open it
up you know we're going to blow it out with anyone who wants to sell their tracks so it's not compulsory
they don't have to which of course for listeners will be a great way for you to support the artist
that the music you love you can download the tracks MP3's in the clear you can copy them onto
as many machines and devices as you have and and it's a great way to support as I said a great
way to support your artist for pod castes of course who are members of the pod the pod
safe music network the deal remains the same you're allowed to download these songs for free
and to play them on your podcast as long as you report that play back into the network.
Hi Adam this is Andy from the polar bear pod cast. I listened to your DSC 316 and in your
training to segment you mentioned your trip to IKEA and as a sweet I of course felt very proud.
I've been talking a great deal about IKEA on my podcast since I seem to be the ambassador for
Sweden in the pod is fear. For us IKEA has become somewhat of a national trademark and it's
impressive that this now global multi-million dollar company won't start it off in a basement in
Elmhurl Sweden and you should know that it has grown to what it is today in only one generation
and it's all thanks to one single guy in your account pad there's an entrepreneur for you
Since I know that you're a traveling man I just thought I'd let you know that
IKEA is opening their first door into pad in April so you might want to pop over there and check that out
although I believe it will look just the same as a story you visited except from the science being
fairly hard to read but maybe you're fluent in Japanese as well as English Dutch and god knows what
love the show Adam I don't miss a single episode so keep up the good work and if by any chance
your Mac will start staggering in this clip it's okay now at least we know you just have too many
audio applications running this is Andy from the polar bear podcast signing off
do you believe anything is possible we do where are flink we believe in an internet that's
safe from viruses and scammers we're earthlink we believe your personal information should be just that
personal and we believe your internet should be a friend not a foe we're earthlink
make this smart choice visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you earthlink
we revolve around you had lunch with the kj today and he's got a meeting that he's working on
setting up with earthlink folks to talk about all the great feedback you've been sending in
about their uh about their commercials about user generated advertising about truth and advertising
uh then the messages are all getting back believe me see uh we're talking about since sail they're
earlier on i'm gonna message here from mark dimick when do you say uh about since sail we said
let you know i'm using you mr. curry in a case study as an example of a blue ocean business
i know someone has emailed me about this before about a blue ocean business because on to say
basically you're creating a business which is breaking the boundaries of the radio and recording
industry building a business in an uncontested area keep it up fantastic love listen to the show
tailwinds i just want to know does everyone who says tailwinds are they actually a pilot
i'm gonna have to consider that you are if you say tailwinds that's got to be and we've got to keep
some things exclusive to the to the airman and airwomen you know uh thank you very much
appreciate it oh you know i got a hurry up here because we have uh only a few more minutes
was sadly metronome yeah yeah yeah the Greg man uh was kind of happy that i coped
to having uh been more or less addicted to the figure skating championships and really enjoying
watching them he says uh Megan Hyde is my roommate's niece that's like a Kevin Bacon
six degrees of separation so our house has been figure skating crates the past few days
yes you actually want i think the junior championships it's all about the double axle and the
tollets and all that's you know my mom actually uh was a uh i think i said my professional figure
skater and uh i still remember i think the last time i saw her she was uh over 50 still on the ice
doing uh doing some well tricks that i thought at least were pretty damn impressive
uh let me see here mister Adam says uh who's this from video flat okay having this
almost three months worth of your informative yet interesting podcast i could not wait to send
my small collaboration there are too many subjects to have an opinion on so i'll start with
the subject of shaving shaving must be the most damaging action one can take against one's face
so careful consideration has to be taken i shave under a hot shower only hot when i shave
i use the big double blades for sensitive skin the ones you'll find uh in the supermarket anywhere
for four bucks it does and i use target shaving cream in 139 made with the same ingredients as
the gelette it looks even the same with the blue gel now you would ask how can you shave with such
cheap blades and cream well very carefully shaving is damaging to the skin so one has to take
the time to do it right time is of the essence that's how you get the best results
once you finish the task i recommend using neutrogena cleanser that's where you spend the money
you know i really appreciate this kind of feedback because uh we just don't get to talk about
this stuff enough you know as guys kind of amongst ourselves and once again we have uh a woman
checking into the metro sexual moment Elizabeth Bonne stale says not to get too personal but
the more stubble my husband is sporting the less i want to wear to bed gentlemen it's just one of
the things that you learn right here on the metro sexual moment yeah yeah okay friends on the
serious satellite stars 103 you've witnessed it the metro sexual moment that's what it's all about
where we gather around our virtual water cooler the talk about things guys would never talk
about face to face and never in front of the real water cooler um and you can find uh this type of
good stuff and even more like it on the podcast the daily source code dot com uh we're about to
close our satellite we know which means that coming up next you get the hell way uh mark your
shimmer and mcalf on the pacific coast hell way followed by uh uh uh match wine steen uh don and
drew uh tension tech is on the way we've got uh pod safe music uh later on taking up until 10 p.m.
eastern time if you want to know more about what's going on this podcast as i said daily source
code dot com it's have to check in and and download it come join our side of the fence it's
pretty cool as well we'll see you guys tomorrow and meanwhile on the podcast more feedback um just
to quick uh mention from Brad he was as i listened to DSC 316 was a static to hear the argol pimps
on your show we did an interview with those crazy cats got them connected to the p.m.n thanks dudes
really appreciate it um the interview is on sound pollution number eleven if you want to listen to
get some insight on who the argol pimps really are and Brad cool man thank you very much yeah
like that song a lot it was it was very trippy and uh following up on an idea had uh several source
codes go hey Adam says Derek's dean or stain been listening since around July oh five when iTunes
got the podcast feature loving every moment we wanted to email you from many different things
we never got around to it until now listening to DSC 313 where you were talking about the idea
of a car cast of thought of this idea too boy what i love the test time some Subaru TSTIs
and many other test world the cars and broad i mean make that pod cast it to the world i live
in Sydney australia you know i gotta get down to Sydney man there's it's just the australia
there's so much going on it's just such a you know if i could find a real good business reason
that would make it even but i i don't think i can get the girls unless it's like the
the big summer vacation i can't get them down that far um and we got the dogs and the cats
and all that crap and it's just you know you really got to spend at least two weeks in australia
when you have to make the trip really worthwhile but i really want to come and visit i really really
do let's find a business reason to go anyway i live in Sydney australia so i'd have the right
hand drive thing going i could easily look the part the only hitch is i'm nineteen into rent
cars you have to be twenty one here not sure about test driving i'd be interested to know
what becomes of the car cast you know we talked about this today at the office and i think we
really should put this together um and the model that i have here is not not really a commercial one
because i'm a big fan of top gear on the BBC and the reason why that show is so good the reason
why it wanted i think in any award at the most recent awards is because they're not sponsored by any
car manufacturer and they just you know they're so brutally honest and it's a funny show it's
well produced well put together um on the google video go ahead and just search for top gear and
you'll find many of their episode or not not full episodes but at least you'll find some of
their test drives that they've done it's really fantastic stuff so the concept here is uh we just
do test drives but you know i'm thinking ten minutes um where you either do a test drive in a in a
car a new car or rent a car you should be really easy in Los Angeles there was this budget rent
a car and you could say i want a rolls or i want you know uh BMW Z8 or uh Ferrari or a Corvette whatever
you wanted uh they'd bring for you i don't think you have a rental place like that in San Francisco but
i don't think it just ten minutes you know and we have a basic format of the description about how
the car feels how it rides this suspension and anything just you know imagine you know you've been
in in my in three of my cars now if you've been listening for a while and uh and people always
seem to enjoy just you know cranking up the sound and listening to the ambient noise and you can
really using your theater of the mind you can really get into actually being there um so working on
that if anyone knows of many places where we can rent uh all different kinds of vehicles in the bay area
let me know uh because there's no better place to start than right here right here in my second
home by the bay Jeff Smith who uh did the tune for Metro sexual moment and for Trinity
conjured up something else actually i should uh should go to the page here for a second
because this could actually be a whole new uh a whole new segment, a whole new second let me get the
most recent posting on this page so i can kind of do it professionally let me see is it working
yeah there we go okay check out another Jeff Smith extra have a cancer
come on yeah
unfortunately i don't have an audio feedback from him but
i will read the latest blog entry to Roger Smalls uh blogspot.com weblog titled lonely oh man hold on we
need some we need some like real lonely music to read this hold on a second let me find something
i'm sure iTunes has something that i can use hold on there oh this is it's almost just the
title alone oh i should have prep this hold on let me just find some music here hold on
library now i want uh what do i want pod save shoot you know i don't have anything lined up
that's good for this let me see maybe just in the regular library one purchased that's not
gonna work okay well that was a really good idea uh we're not gonna do it so let me just read this
to you entitled lonely wait let's do it like this lonely i've been keeping myself to myself this
last week i found the nice website that has lots of free passwords for porn sites so i've been busy
checking those out a lady emailed mister Adam Curry saying that she had a bad reaction when she
heard my voice that's not the first time a lady has had that reaction and reported me i've discussed
these matters last night with my therapist and we both came to the conclusion that the last thing i
want is to upset Adam's audience i don't want Adam to lose any audience because of my interactions
with him even mad just upset with me for no reason i know that Adam understands my feelings and
knows i would never do anything to harm him listening to him seems he seems so very busy these
days jet setting and whatnot i wish i could help him in some way even if it's just a tidy up
those plants by a dry way i don't mind doing it i know i have no experience in running a million
dollar company but i can always leave him to do that in his study area whilst i perform task deemed
too meanial for him if it's just cleaning his car taking his dirty clothes to the laundry or
mowing a lawn if Adam does not do these then he can record more shows it's just no good when
he's not in the country i don't know what to do with myself in the evenings i don't know what to do
with my time i think i will draw some pictures i should stay off my feet for a while
Roger Smoss
oh hello meet enough the the room there okay hopefully Roger will send something in again
that was really sweet Roger i appreciate it but you know it's okay i've actually do all the
you know all the bacheling i've been doing here at the condo i've probably gotten pretty good
to do in my own meanial task i'm kind of liking it winding it up Michael Cooper gave me some
feedback about the London airshow great to hear you're setting up a fantastic flight sim at home i'd
like to invite you to spend a day at the London airshow taking place it oh wait did i already have this
let's just stupid that's not what i wanted someone else this is the wrong one i'm sorry
someone else that reported this was a great show to go to and i can i have the wrong email here i'm
sorry shoot okay you know what why don't we just wrap up the show with the one final piece of
pod save music this is something cc Chapman turned me on to very i have to agree with and very much
a seal type vibe to this guy frances jockey my life on the daily source code
you're making me crazy damn you're so rude but it's not easy
in my life in my life i tell you which my life
just be gone
tell me story is
we love the films and story trust all is
what do they don't it me
my life
baby it's my life
Every day I woke up at this morning, we looked around, we were gazing at it
Easy, easy, my life Baby it's my life, yeah, just be my life
Can you reach my life Baby, be gone, whatever you say you say you say you say you say
It's my life Baby, be gone, whatever you say you say you say you say you say
You say, yes, you say
You know what also has a bit of a like a Robert Palmer vibe too
Francis Chockey, my life from the pot, the same music.net where music.pot showed our calm thanks to CCC
the Chapman accident hash and the U-turn cafe,
but pointing that one out to me.
And if you have any suggestions, any songs
that you was in a listener might have run across
either hearing it on a different podcast
or finding something on the podcast music network.
Please let me know.
Send me a link.
And there's so many songs now.
In fact, we've had, what is now 20,000 over 20,000 songs
reported played?
Today, I mean, those are phenomenal numbers.
Think about it.
You know, an average of all of those podcasts
and let's say an average of,
call it 500 listeners,
times 20,000, a simple big-ass numbers.
This is a real exposure.
Now, it's gonna be interesting to see what happens
when we activate the sales from a number,
from a number of different perspectives.
The first one being just a people will buy.
I'm pretty sure that people are going to buy music,
but also what's gonna be interesting about it
is that it's no DRM, it's MP3.
So it really comes down to humanity
and people wanting to support artists.
And I believe that the pod safe revolution
is much more about the connection between the artist
and their audience and people are sending
little messages back and forth
when they're buying CDs and artists
or sending personalized notes back.
And people feel very involved.
I believe it's going to work.
Over time, who knows what's gonna happen?
But what if it did work?
What if those 10 million virtual spins resulted
in a million people purchasing a track?
It'll really screw up some other people's business.
You know, I'm talking about it anyway.
Okay, so maybe tomorrow we'll start testing out pieces
of the podcast delivery network.
So if stuff goes a little screwy,
then my apologies in advance,
but please let me know what problems you're seeing
if they do occur in the same token.
Everything could be just pretty smooth
and just work.
In fact, that's what I'm counting on.
We've got all kinds of technology
that's being put in place that can insert audio.
It's gonna be a crazy couple of days
before I head back.
That's for sure.
All right, you guys have yourself a fantastic day.
I'll be back tomorrow with more stuff to talk about.
We probably some Trinity stuff.
Now see, we can get out to the biofueloasis
before I either run out of diesel
or I have to go back home.
Stay subscribed.
Pot show.
Tough on dirt, gentle on your ears.