This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Everybody welcome to DevCast Number 2.
It's Adam here at the Curry Cottage, just south of London.
And it's good to see that we've got a couple hundred developers, I presume most of
you are a developer, so we're subscribed to the DevCast.
This podcast will actually contain a golden ticket, so if you receive one and you'll
know and I'll let you know exactly where that will happen, because you of course may not
get one.
But if you two then you're in and we're going to get you up and running and working on
Pod Show Plus and the podcast that we network ASAP.
On the Skype now from Pod Show HQ and San Francisco, Kevin Ostrowski, known as K-O or K-1,
how you doing buddy?
Not too bad, how you been?
We missed you out here.
I miss you guys too, it's been the longest time we've been a part honey.
I know we've been growing, there's some people that have even met you.
I keep seeing the introduction emails, hey, welcome so on, so welcome and I, oh man.
So yeah, do we have enough seats and chairs and tables left?
We've got one extra desk, but they were all just put in last week, so we're running
out quicker than we can to get them.
Oh crap, well if you guys need to use my office, you know where it is, just follow the
smoke trail.
Oh, by the way, happy for 20.
Yeah, happy for 20 back at you, my friend.
That's right.
It's 420 somewhere in the world.
I did, you know, I'm a complete idiot, it is indeed for, well, by the time this air
is probably will be 421, but the all developers know that or is it only the developers
who smoke, who understand that?
I think it's a pretty common for the common, so Kevin, why don't you give us a little
bit of background about yourself, and because I don't think we've really talked about that
a lot, you know, where you were before Pod Show and why the heck you joined this band
of freaks?
Well, I used to work at a company called Signature Network, which is the leading music
merchandising company on the web, core business that I was selling t-shirts, around the
online side of that developed a fan club system that is used to this day still on youtube.com,
kiss online, we did a site from Adana, Britney Spears, all these pop stars that I don't
really care for.
Yeah, all your type of music, right?
It's right up your alley.
It's all rocking out.
Did you meet any of them?
No.
The only person I met was Sammy Hager, which was actually kind of cool.
He's pretty cool.
I've met him a couple.
He's a good guy.
Yeah, he seems all right.
In fact, he was the guy that convinced me I should go work for MTV, I met him over in Holland
and I said, yeah, MTV called me and said, oh dude, you should totally do that, that's right.
And this of course was early 80s, right?
So when MTV was still playing music, it's still cool, so right on.
So you were doing that, how did we find you?
Did you find us?
I can't really remember.
Oh, I was recommended by one of my old bosses at Signatures to come on over and work
here and you guys gave me an offer I couldn't refuse here.
Who was that person?
I got to go thank you.
John Bellistery?
I think you know.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Oh, all right.
No, I don't know.
I don't know.
I understand the connection.
It was funny, we had like a Friday celebration, our food bar Friday and it was really cool
because I was dialed in through the eye chat, so I could see what was going on.
And we brought up a picture of the very first, you know, early days when we were right
in South Park on when we really had the official podcast, Ali Office, where the homeless
people were pooping in the back in the alley there.
The good old days.
And you know, when we started out, and I think we, I talked about this on daily source
code not too long ago, we really were planning to do something of a much smaller scale
I think.
Was that your impression when we started?
Yeah, maybe originally we were going to just kind of make podcasts and easier for
podcasts, and it's really been snowballing ever since then.
And so from just, well, just, well, from making something for podcasters and making podcasting
really simple, we've actually turned a lot of our attention towards the audience.
Yeah, we're really gearing stuff up for the listeners themselves, letting people connect
with other people, letting them connect with the podcasters and eventually artists.
So come a long way, the few months.
Now how long have we actually been, because you're really, I would have to say, you
know, the core of all of this development of our social media network and all these, and
really bringing all these pieces together, what have we, how long have we been working
on this now?
Eight nine months.
Uh, back.
That's September.
So, dude.
Yeah.
So, uh, are we ready to release yet, Kevin?
Okay.
Can we get this?
I'm ready.
I'm ready to push the button any time I get the okay, so we're getting really closely.
Yeah.
A few months to look forward to.
How many builds are we doing a day now?
Ah, a few.
Once or twice a day, I'll push up some stuff.
So, so yesterday we talked with, uh, with Andrew Grummit, uh, a little bit about, uh, the developers
program that we'll have going on, and, but you really kind of blew us away, you know,
early on with the whole concept of the modules, uh, in podshow plus, which is, uh, something
that's going to be complete, audience controlled.
So, uh, what, why don't you, uh, tell us a bit about the modules and some of the stuff
that the developers will be, uh, be able to work on first, the stuff that you would work
on because, you know, it really is your brain child.
Oh, the way that the modules basically work are, they're just little widgets, so to speak,
that, uh, let you put in whatever code you'd like, and, uh, people can add them to their
profile page, they can move around, they can add more modules, they can remove their modules,
they can, you know, change the color of the page, kind of, give the actual users complete
control over how they want to develop their own, their own profile page, uh, and this applies
to both shows and to the listeners themselves, um, so, while there is a ton of, uh, podshow
exclusive modules that tap into, you know, the different features of the pdn and podshow
plus, um, there's also third party modules, uh, like, for instance, uh, bringing in your flicker
pictures, uh, bringing in your delicious links, uh, weather modules, all kinds of third party
stuff that are just, uh, let you customize and really make your site, what you want it to be.
Now, these, um, you said something interesting there because we, we do have a lot of APIs,
which will be publishing and all kinds of stuff that ties in, you know, um, you know, one ties into
the other, of course, we actually have a whole entity out there, the pod save music network
going to be tying that in as well. Um, will developers be able to, uh, work on some of that stuff
as well, or, you know, will it, will it be a place where they can, uh, ideate and, and work on ideas
of, of integration of existing podshow stuff? That's definitely planned. Uh, this first SDK release
is, uh, really limited to third party, uh, applications and bringing in content, uh, but I'm definitely
planning on opening up some of the, the core functionality of the PDN, letting people get in there
and do stuff with our show data, our user data, um, and really, you know, actually extend
podshow plus, uh, completely. Excellent. Hold on, hold on a second, Kevin. Oh, oh my gosh. Oh,
that, uh, up. I just saw a golden ticket swoosh by saw a couple of them go. So, if you didn't
hear about 30 seconds of me telling you how to get in, then you didn't win. I'm sorry.
Ah, some lucky developers are already registering as we speak. So, um,
what is your involvement going to be in, um, in, in this process, Kevin, uh, you know,
Andrew's really going to be managing, I think, a lot of the, um, the, uh, the source for
project, whatever we're going to use for it. Now, I see tons of comments on, uh, the dev cast, uh,
show site. What, what are you going to be doing? And will you be accessible to the, to developers
who have questions? Uh, I definitely will be, uh, you can reach me at Kevin at podshow.com. If you have
any specific technical questions, uh, I'm really the guy that is behind the SDK and the code in the,
in podshow plus. So, I'd be the best person to contact on that. Um, my time's pretty limited. So,
I can't guarantee I'll get back here right away, but I definitely welcome feedback questions,
comments. Uh, you can cost me out if you want to. That's all cool with me. Oh, excellent way.
That was Kevin at podshow. I said, right that down for the cursing. Uh, so who else, um,
of the dev team should we have next up in the dev cast? I mean, there's so, so many different
moving, you know, parts to this that, you know, and as you said, there's even employees that I haven't
met yet in the time that I've been back in, uh, in the UK, who, who should we have on next and
how will that pertain to the, uh, to the developers who are coming in? Wow, that's a, that's a
tough one. Yeah, everybody's doing such cool stuff. Um, you know, we have, uh, saw who's really
gearing up our search technologies, uh, letting, letting us expand beyond, uh, you know, normal,
PHP, my sequel, text indexing, uh, brought in a, uh, new guy Kurt, who's just really been kicking
some ass on, uh, on a lyrics system. Um, we brought a, a Gavin from a, from tag.com. He's,
Oh, Gavin? Gavin's Gavin's in? Oh, that's cool. Yes, Gavin is in. He's been here for a couple
weeks now. Oh, shit. No, I know, because I personally, uh, and, you know, I call them a couple times,
uh, trying to convince him to come and work for us, and I think he, he, like, lost his cell phone or
something. I was really bombed, and then, you know, just as I was leaving, we got, we got, we got in touch
again. So he's in. That's fantastic. Good. Okay. He's, he's working on our back and admin stuff,
which is going to be really cool. Give us a lot of flexibility and control. So I'm,
there's, there's all kinds of people here that you, you should be talking to, not just me.
How about, how about Erin? I, I'd love to talk to Erin because she's, she, she is so trippy, man. I love,
I love it. I love what she's doing. She's, she's great. She's, uh, definitely a trip to work with,
but, uh, man, she's a smarker. And she's, uh, our, our DBA, or she's our DBA, and she's also heads up
our, um, IT department, essentially, uh, but really focusing on the DBA work and working with a
rack space, our managed hosting solution to make sure our servers are off and running.
Excellent. And, uh, and doing a good job, except, uh, there's a little hiccup last night on the
PMN. Yeah. What, uh, I got, like, ton of emails this morning. Oh, man, something's gone wrong.
I can't, and I'll tell you, I was about to do my show and really bummed me out. I'm like,
I can't, I can't get any songs. It was really, it was horrible. It was like,
but some wiki got set up and it bogged everything down or something like that.
Um, it was a combination of that. And I think there's a patch applied to a patchy, that didn't
take so well, so we've rolled everything back and things should be good now. So I apologize to all
the people that needed to get to it. No, I think everyone understands. And, you know, but it's,
I hope there's also a couple of, you know, maybe non-developers who are listening because now you
really start to understand how much work goes into doing this. You know, when, when you hear how
many people are on it and all the different issues. And of course, we're, we're actually scaling
internally pretty quickly, you know, just on podshow plus and the pdm, we've got a lot of shows.
We've got a lot of users in there. Of course, you know, all of our, um, uh, a lot of the podcasters
that we, that we met at the portable media expo, it's, uh, it's, it's, it's really kind of growing
all in, uh, simultaneously. Yeah, definitely. I'm Richard's been doing a great job of bringing
in some good quality shows. Um, and I see the, I see the sign-up emails coming by my inbox
almost daily if us bringing in these shows and letting them actually use the tools and, you know,
put it out into their feed currently, uh, I'd like to turn it on. So, you know, people could start
using the podshow plus feeds, but I mean, it's great to see people actually using parts of it.
That's a lot of good feedback. That's a question I actually had is, um, will, will be able to
selectively turn on some of the show sites before everything is, is publicly available?
Um, not necessarily entire show site, but, um, we could start slowly exposed the, you know, the
XML, uh, start with that, and then maybe just open up the listener side without, you know,
it's up the registrations. I mean, there's a lot of stuff we can do to kind of slowly ramp up
and get people in there and isn't it? But, uh, you know, opening the floodgates is an out of the
question either. So, uh, as he throws down the gauntlet, I love it. I love it. All right, dude,
well, listen, I don't want to keep you too much longer. Um, I'm going to get in touch with, uh,
I just saw a mail coming from Andrew, so I guess we can get this when I'll set up for those
golden tickets that just flew by. And, um, um, maybe just to tell, uh, tell, if you don't mind
tell Aaron that I'd love to talk with her tomorrow, if she has time, just to get your insights into
what she's been doing, because that database stuff. That's like, that's art, man. That's not
science. That's fucking art. No, that is an art form. But, uh, guys, go over real quick what this
SDK is going to, yes, please. So, yeah, let people know what they expect. Um, and basically,
it's just a lightweight framework. Um, we'll be providing a first that, you know, we'll just
basically let people say preference data to start. So, you know, it's, it's really small lightweight.
You get a single class with some helper functions. Um, we do use the script calculus, uh,
JavaScript framework, so Ajax all over the place is cool with us. Um, and since this is
really just, uh, PHP, straight PHP coding, um, you know, all of our modules are going to have to be
reviewed and analyzed and make sure that nobody's trying to hack into us kind of thing. But, um,
I mean, I've been trying for months. What are you talking about? It's really, it's really flexible.
I mean, it's really just a blank slate for people to, to create on, um, you know, the actual SDK itself
will provide you with starting points, um, you know, you enter your module name. It'll create
based off of a base template to get you started. So, you don't have to reinvent the wheel there.
But then it's really up to the, the developer. And this time goes on, we'll be adding, you know,
supporting classes to let you tap into our shows and our, and our users. So,
look forward for some really cool stuff. And, uh, you know, you'll have lots of control over
what your module stays. So, so, you said, you only mentioned PHP. Does that mean that if I have
even, uh, a working knowledge of PHP that I can participate and I can try and create a module,
is it something that will eventually, you know, that anyone can do this if they, you're like,
on my space, right? They've, you know, my daughter is now hacking up HTML, um, yeah, and, and she's
figured out how to change something so she can hide her comments. Yeah, it's pretty basic stuff.
But, I mean, will we get to the point where it, where, you know, even someone like that,
can, can create a module? Absolutely. I mean, you can make a module that's just a simple
hello world module, or you can build a full application. It's really what your work knowledge
is. On the other side, that's time goes on. We'll be releasing a client-side SDK as well.
That'll let developers use, you know, just JavaScript, uh, XML, and, uh, it's a VHDML.
And, and that will be instant, you know, you'll be able to just basically send a module
to the developer friend and have them install it. But that's, that's some time out, um, as, you
know, we prep up for launch. I've got, uh, lots of other things to worry about. Yeah, I hear you.
Right here. Busy, busy, busy, busy, right? I'll code no sleep. That's my model. Yeah, I'm sending
some mountain do your way. Sweet. All right, Kevin. Dude, cool. All right, thank you very much.
And, uh, we'll check in sometime next week and, uh, just, see how's everything's going on.
Keep these, these dev cast relatively short. So I'm going to take too much of any one's time.
And, uh, say hi to everyone at, uh, at HQ for me. I will. I'll tell Aaron to expect a call for me.
All right. Yes. So, uh, around the same time tomorrow. Sounds good. All right, buddy. Thanks,
like, Kevin. Take it easy. Okay, but bye, bye, bye. There you go. Get this podcast and more great ones
like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from Pod Show and Lime Light Networks.