This is Soccer Girl. I just listened to the first episode of Shadow Falls and it's scared me
crapless.
This podcast is brought to you by Potcho and GoDaddy. Want killer content with a badass
domain name? This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charley, 4-3-8.
Sometimes an atom's all alone, and he needs his love right there on the microphone. So here she is
is the lady Patricia.
The say to heads on better than one, and with this angel from above, there's nothing
that they both can't do. A make you wild as dreams come true. So grab your earbind
and jam a man, and let the fabulous show begin.
It's atom and Patricia. Yes, atom and Patricia, atom and the lady Patricia.
Heavenly Liberty Jones, works in the shop that she owns.
Lessons to music like swing. When there's no customers in, just because she don't like
to drive, takes you see I stood fine. And these are thoughts out of sight to the river at night.
This is the awesome thing, why don't you come for me, take me away with my friends.
She's got a kid in her eye, because her name would imply.
Things are only designed.
Why don't you come for me, take me away with my friends.
This is the awesome thing, why don't you come for me, take me away with my friends.
This is the awesome thing, why don't you come for me, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends.
This is the awesome thing, why don't you come for me, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends.
This is the awesome thing, why don't you come for me, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with my friends, take me away with
You know people hate this, you always hate people talking about the sound of the show, I'm not going to say anything, but yes, I have a shitty sound
No, you don't have a shitty sound, we just have to get you another pet, we have to get another pair of those headphones, after I bought these wonderful Sony's
Yeah, that's where mine, I know there were yours, but this is so good
Let's see
Hey baby, how are you doing?
Yeah, good
Did you get some messages from people asking you to come on the show?
Oh, yeah, oh, geez, really?
I wonder why
Did they didn't come from you?
No, they didn't come from me, what did they say?
Well, that they like it when I'm here and
And where the hell are you, is what they said, right?
It adds something to the show, you know, and that, you know, it's sort of an
Adam is more
Fuller, more
Fuller?
Yeah, complete
I'm more complete when you're on the show
You're more complete when I'm on the show, I don't know what they mean, but
No, I understand that
Yeah, that makes sense
Your hair is very pretty by the way
Oh, thank you
Yeah, I told you when I came home
But you haven't been on why you've been on the show once, kind of, quick, one point
Oh, that's what you mean, with a little bit of gold blonde
Yeah, but it's also, it's a different style
I thought I'll, you know, add a little bit of sunshine in it
Yeah, I thought I'd just suck up to you at the beginning of the show
So you don't go too hard on me
Go, you don't need to, you know, man
So, what's going on?
We got you Vaughn coming
Your sister is coming
Yeah, and I like to contact Beaumacartney
For your sister?
We need a good woman
Uh-huh
It is a nice man
I have a nice woman
Hold on a second, let's just back up
So your sister who has been single for how many years?
A long time
Yeah, long time
And, you know, she had some friends here
Like, what's a long time?
Let's just define a long time
Twenty years?
Yeah
Twenty years
Oh, my goodness
She's had a couple of boyfriends
Most of them capital L losers
Well, her biggest love was Steve Harley
You know, she, she lived with him for nine years
For nine years
From Cockney Rebel
And, uh, he started to drink
Uh-huh
Hugs and everything
Then he didn't know what he was doing
And then what happened?
He sent her home to Holland
Oh, no
And she went, she loved
Biggest mistake
And he said that later to her
But then he was too late, of course
She moved on
Right
But there still were
There's still in contact with each other
And I think that that was her real love
And he's remarried now, isn't he?
He married later on
He married a stewardess and he has
Good for him
Yep
And well, no, no
They're gone a lot in their heart
Yeah, so easy
You know, I'll find a stewardess
Well, excuse me
Don't I was clevering
First of all, it's a
Uh, it's not a stewardess
No, I'm not anymore
A flight attendant
And don't put them down, dude
No, no, this is not what I'm saying
Not the flight attendant
Yeah, I'm from the aviation industry
I know
We defend our own hearing
Or did I say something wrong?
No, I mean like
Typical
I was traveling
I was very busy
And there was a nice woman in the sky
That's not an all typical
Like two people in show business
Hoking up at some television shows
Well, somebody's doing it mean to you
Yeah, I mean, that's not an all typical
You can't believe it
You know, okay, but I still think that
They were meant for each other
Okay, so anyway, so that's not going to happen
So
Now you're trying to find Paul McCartney for her?
Yes, yes
She's a wonderful old-fashioned
Very good-looking woman
And you don't find them like that at all
The Paul is looking for someone with a hook
You know, so we had Linda
With a hook on a hook
No, no, no, no, no, no
I'm not on a hook
I like captain hook
Madam captain hook
Paul, come here
No, Linda was a vegetarian
Yeah
Big Veggie
Veggie person
Yeah
And Heather, of course, had a wooden line
Oh, don't lie
I'm not laughing
Yeah, I'm laughing
But it's not, you know what I mean?
Yeah, it's just a joke
But anyway, so can you sister have some kind of deformity
Or something that will make it
I think he's into that
No, he's interested in things
Yeah, yeah, yeah
There is something about people
With definite, look at Pete
Who's in the big brother house right now
Well, actually Steve Hardy had something
Yeah, it wouldn't lag
So
They're probably the same then
He had a deformity
Respected him and never talked about it
Of course, because it doesn't make any difference
But you see with people like Pete and the big brother house
Who has to read
He's going to win this thing
He's going to win because people like that
Once they can look at this
It adds something
It does
That's a lot of movement to your life
Yeah, yeah
But you know, he should have because he's a nice guy
I believe that
He was like him as he was the nicest beetle
And yeah, he was the nicest
And so I think he needs an old fashioned woman
It can cook for him
He likes that
He's not somebody who wants to go out
Do anything
Just wants to do a nice thing
Exactly my sister
But I think don't you think he is
Who is this?
She
Don't you think Paul needs a little
A little rest now
Yeah, he needs some rest
He shouldn't want to read my sister
Yeah
There you go
I'll be sure
You know what?
Is he going to come on the show?
I will
Ask her
I'll be sure
We have some plans of course
Oh, really?
Yep
What are your
Please
Tell me your mind
She's been very busy
She has a she owns a shop in Holland
So she's been standing on her feet a lot
And she's tired
So I said when you arrive
I've got flowers later
I have an appointment for you
Oh, nice
So we start off with a nice pedicure
And then
With the Korean muffin
Or then a Korean
Yeah, yeah
Hello
Oh, maybe
Swivel
She's on my bars full swivel chair
And of course, her feet don't reach the ground
It's just literally swiveling
180 degrees away from me
One more
She's fine
As long as I can go
Should I get the booster seat for you, man?
Should we get a little booster seat for Patricia?
Sit in the studio
So
You have just everything is high here
For you
For your size
Yes, man
So what I was like
And then we want to go a day
So you move the microphone up
But now whenever you're talking
Looking down
I'm going to go to London with her
Yeah
Oh, really?
What day is that?
I don't know yet
Because I've got to be in London a couple times
Next week
Oh, we have to go and see a museum
Uh-huh
The British Museum
I want to see the dresses
To go into the tower
Yeah
The British Museum
Cool
Yeah
So, you know
That's it?
No, no
And shopping
And high street shopping
A little bit
She has a shop
So she doesn't need to shop
Yeah, that's true
That's true
Okay
You aren't aware
Because you don't listen to the show
But I gave away an iPod in a contest
Really?
Yeah, it's a guy had a
He registered a domain name
And had a website
Troy needs an iPod.com
He was asking people for donations
And I said, you know, that's kind of cool
Because then someone else came in with
I need an iPod more than Troy.com
And I said, come up with the craziest
With the craziest domain name
You can think of
And the winner
Is very interesting person
You must listen to what he has to say
Hi Adam, this is Marty Abernathy
I am a 38-year-old
Transsexual scruncher
From Indianapolis
I'm a designer of crappy websites
You know, the thing there is
I don't care about someone being transsexual
What do you do?
I am a Paul Dior Scruncher
This is horrible
Yeah
Okay
And shitty URLs
Yes, that's right
I want an iPod on the daily source code
And why did I win this iPod
For my great humanitarian deed?
No
I won it for talking about
PILL
My mother is going to be so proud
Don't worry, my mom would be very proud too
I'm sure this will go in our scrapbook
Oh and Adam
I didn't register my URL at
GoDaddy.com
That was the whole point
It was like I was tying it into GoDaddy
Sanco Register, your domain name at GoDaddy
Yeah, yeah
The daily source DSC3 code
And get it for $6.95
So it just shows that
You know, contests are
Yeah, they're working
Yeah, only she didn't register
GoDaddy.com
I registered it
Directknick.com
I have an affinity for them
Because they kept me regular
During a flood
And a hurricane
That's loyalty
I want to pimp them
And help them out as much as I can
And finally I wanted to pimp my podcast
Because I mean, that's what I'm here for, right?
Check out the second thought to podcast
Or we discuss the differences in social interaction
In second life and in real life
Think of it as second life sociology 101
Okay
And yes, you upfront
This will be on the test
My other podcast is the fat-trany circus
I named it that because I'm fat
The fat-trany circus
Oh
I'm a tranny
And I've been called a clown in many of the forums across the internet
So check out STpodcast.com
For second thoughts
And the FTC podcast.com
For the fat-trany circus
PS
Podfather, I need you to forgive me
Uh-oh
Podfather, I've sinned against you
Every time
The lady Patricia comes on
I think of one thing and one thing only
Bang and us both at the same time
No, it's not sex
Even though she is really hot
That's not what I think about
That's right, Podfather
I think of green acres and A4
A4
Do you remember green acres?
Yeah, cool
Can I look at the Albert?
No, and I look like Eddie Albert
Anyways, gotta go, Podfather
Let's go
Green acres is the green
You do have a little bit of A4
A4, but it's not bad
No, no, no, no
No, just listen to me
No, A4 was the good one
She was the good one
Not the judge, I think you got it
I'm not a judge, I think you got it
You're the only object that I'd rather pass
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, the way it's about anything
You know, you're kind of like the
The New York socialite type, I guess?
Yeah, in country, in country life
Yeah, was the phone ringing?
I think the phone was ringing
I hope
Do you think the next door neighbor?
Do you think she got it?
The teenager is picking it up
I'll show her
She is quite a teenager
Now, did you tell your listeners about
Uh-huh
You know, that we wanted to have
And you organize a nice party for
I told them that I was going to
Arlis, you can say Arlisner's baby
Arlisner, not just Mark
Yeah, I told them that we were going to that place
Yeah
And how hard it was I could
So many pubs and places
Well, they don't want teenagers
They don't want teenagers
Isn't it said?
That's said
Well, it's said because on MTV here
The same show that runs in America
Uh, my, what is it?
Super sweet 16
Yeah, that's what she's watching
Yeah
And she thinks, you know, I want to have a nice party
And so she's like, where can I find a pub
That has a door big enough for my dad to drive
With a big bowl on it
She's too young
She doesn't even want that
She didn't even mention it
She hasn't asked for it
And she never asked for anything
Which is kind of cool
But she thought it was cool to have a nice party
And she wanted an Alice in Wonderland party
Right
That's the theme
Okay, so it was very hard
Because all the people I talked to
She said, no, you don't want any teenagers
Yes, problems
Yeah, because when you're 16
You can drink right?
True
Because here in England
And Christina wasn't thinking about that
She's not a drink herself
Teenage is drink
Yeah
And then it starts
You know, they start to hit each other
And it's violent
And it's puking
And it's sex
And that's sad
You know, you know, my theory right
Where you can feel the frustration of a country
Or a community
By looking at what's happening in traffic
Yeah
That's the gas station
And it was really busy
And I actually had to pull up into the
The pump for left hand gas tank
So even though mine is on the right
Yeah
You pull it over the trunk
And stick it in kind of upside down
And it was like two guys
A grown-up guys
You know, like my age
Yeah
Real men
And someone, you know
So everyone was waiting
And she was inside buying something
And paying whatever
And then she got into her car
And she drove
For whatever reason
They started yelling at each other
But it was really unbelievable
The things that they were saying
And I was like
It could tell it was like real anger
But I moved it especially
Because I didn't want to hear these things
Yeah, so anyway
Oh, just that that's
I was actually shocked
I was like
I was just very disappointed
Yeah, I was really shocked
Like, man, I can't I can't believe it
You know, just
Oh, for nothing
Yeah, I was like
Go on a diet, you fat content
Oh man
Yeah
And yeah, I was thinking
Like should I say something to this guy
Like, you know
You're such a
They were like painters
You know, they had the painter
Smocks on and the latter on
And I thought, no, I'm a pussy
I want to get the crap
The thing is they're probably
Extremely unhappy
Because otherwise you're not
You don't do that
There's just no reason to
But I've seen it myself
You know, when I'm driving to the airport
The first eight times or whatever
That I drove
There's a lot of turns, you know
And you're following the navigator
And so I'd make a wrong turn
Then I'd go left and whatever
People who would be behind me
Would be frustrated with me
Obviously trying to find the way
I know
But they would be really like yelling
Yeah, but like really
I mean, come on
They do that in New York
In New York, in New York
In New York, it's our language
This is how we speak
That's how you communicate
I'm one of those assholes
When you're when you're crossing the street
And don't walk
I am on the horn
And I'm on the accelerator
Fuck you
I know you
Fuck you because not you
But fuck you
Because you are
Fucking up the system in New York
I remember sitting next to you
When you were driving
In New York
You were always like
You want to die
Mother fucker
Go ahead
Yeah, right
But that's how we do it in New York
That's just nice
That's nice
That's identify yourself as a New Yorker
I am a New Yorker
Fuck you very much
Get the fuck out of my way
The first thing I learned
When I came to live there
It was fuck off
No, it was
You have to put on a sort of don't fuck with me face
And I didn't know that in the beginning
So they fucked with me constantly
Then I think you got the don't fuck with me face
Don't you dare fuck with me face
Yeah
You need that
That's what gives you respect on the streets
Nobody ever did anything
Was said anything would touch me
Or that's what it is
Is it sort of attitude
But it's disappointing
But they can't see my face
I'm in the car
So that's why you have to be a little more vocal about it
But I'm glad I'm in an English car
I mean that's a different
Oh, that doesn't make a difference
Otherwise you're that fucking foreigner
No, because I know just when I had a different
Oh, they were very courteous
Yes, true
They thought, oh, poor woman
She does, oh, she's Dutch
Yeah, but that's because you got to it
And nice ones
Oh, my dad
Yeah, no, I'm the
I'm the
I don't get that treatment from the guys
No, they don't see my friends
That's a big-haired faggot
It's on
Believe me
You in that jag
Exactly
Glossy lips
They're just like, god damn
Damn
It's follow that bitch
No
Comics were bloggers sent in a comment for you
Oh, yeah
Hey, Patricia
It's a toy boy
Adam Kerry playing Prince Charming
Properly still
Well, screw him
My question is to you
Patricia
Bye
I have impression
That you are too vague about your ethnicity
About your origins
Saying that you are half Dutch, half Greek
But that inner reality
You don't fear any association
To neither of them
That you're a cosmopolitan
And others such bullshit
If you're pardon me, my friends
So
Mrs. Rishuoshi
Could you tell me
Would you believe in European Union idea
Particularly because your current right to about in UK
Is based on European Union citizenship
Do you think the Patricia that European Union has long-term future
For example, 100 or 500 years
Or will it fall apart
Soon or sooner
Patricia
Don't be flipping what she was she
Love it
Or hate it
Speak up babes
Yeah
Two questions there
Two questions
Locker
Conextive vlogger
Lotka
Oh
I am too different
I love that
Lotka
You got to be old
You have to remember taxi
I am too different
Okay
Play it on and baby
You know
I've been traveling so much
That I'm still looking
For a place that I feel at home
And
So
I was born in Holland
But I always wanted to go somewhere else
And whenever my parents said
Come on, hop in the car
We're going over the border
I was happy
Really
Yeah, I always liked it
So I'm sort of sigoina
Gypsy
Yes
So
You are 100% Dutch, right?
I'm 100% Dutch, yeah
Hold on, hold on, hold that thought baby
Because the satellite window is closing
Yes, wave goodbye
Shake those movies for the serious satellite listeners
You felt a draft
Yeah
Peed up, close the window
She feels a draft
Yeah
PCH is next for y'all
Talk to you tomorrow, bye
Okay
So
Now
Well
Of course, but in the Dutch
I mean Holland is a very small country
So everybody
Do you feel like Holland is your home
That's
Who knows?
Don't be wishy-washy
No, no
Have you ever felt like Holland was your home
Okay
You lived in a...
I always wanted to live somewhere else
Miss Pie, during your glamour years
You lived in the United States of America
In the garden state
Yes, I did
Known as Jersey
I love that
Okay
Did you feel...
That was home for you?
I lived in Germany a long time
When I was...
I think six years old
And...
Oh, before that
And after that
Did you feel like that was home?
No
Well, I loved the bridge
How about New Jersey?
No, Jersey felt very much like Holland
Did you...
Maybe you felt more like a Jersey girl than...
Absolutely
Yeah
Yeah, yeah
You're a golden hair flowing
The convertible
Mm-hmm
That's very Jersey-Gurly
Yeah
The coupé rings
You're kind of a chef
Well, and also being in show business
You always heard
Especially in the time that I was working
That...
Oh, you're from Holland
Oh
You know?
I love that city
I really love your work
You're from Holland
Yeah
It's a pity you're not coming from America
You would be such a big, big star
Or, you know?
Oh, it's a bit of, you know, come from England
Or anything
But Holland
Yeah
Can be right
You know, it can be good
That is kind of...
It changed a little bit with chalking blue
And all the things
You know, but still, but still
Golden Earing
But that's it
That's it
So how about England?
Well, I always wanted to be British
Don't know why?
Do you want to become a British citizen?
Yeah
What?
Do you want to become British?
I would love to
Really?
Yeah, I'm thinking about it
Wow
That's it
But I'm still...
You're still getting the vibe
Still getting the vibe
So what if you don't...
What if it turns out that this is not the right place
I mean, you're trying to shoot route now
Yeah
You're trying to grab onto a place
Where you can...
Oh, it doesn't work
Because you don't need to live somewhere
You know, in the place that you are
Or, how do you say that?
I don't know
What are you trying to say?
Do you have a day geworden?
Represent?
Yes
You don't have to live there
But I love to be British
I've been British all the time
Maybe everything was different
Yeah, it would have opened more
Doors, I guess
Excellent
Yeah
I got a piece here that I'd like to play for you
Normally I wouldn't put it in a show with us together
Because it's a little bit long
But I was going to let you hear it
Anyway, you just have to listen to this
Remember I told you about Chubby Checker
He was on the strip podcast
Yeah
Talking about how he felt that he's been so dist
Because he never gets any airplay
But he invented...
You know, stuff that he invented back then
Like hip hop
And he said that was the pony
And he said, you know, he had like 30
30 top...
More hits or whatever
Yeah
But he's really frustrated
But he doesn't get the airplay
Did you just thought I was very frustrated
Did he came up with the...
No, no, no, no
No, I haven't lined up
And now because the link
No, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no
But now that you mentioned
Are you frustrated?
Sometimes
Okay
No, no
Of course everybody is
No, has nothing to do with it
It's just because it's such a good piece
And I wanted to play it for you
But I figured I'm going to play it for you
Might as well do it on the show
So then I can play it for everyone
Yeah, yeah
No link with frustration
Okay
So
Chubby Checker is saying that he's frustrated
That he doesn't get any airplay
He says, you know, it should be
The Beatles, Elvis Presley, and Chubby Checker
He felt that he belonged
You know, in that triage
And I didn't know much about the history of Chubby Checker
Do you know anything about Chubby Checker?
Well, I remember
I remember
It's so clearly seeing it on the news
On the news
There was a big thing
When Chubby Checker came to Holland
And he had this hit
Twist
Right
And they even showed it on the NTS
The Dutch television service
Yeah
Did they have NTEU
NTEU
Steak thing
Yeah
Okay
And so he was a very big star
Do you think that he belongs next to Elvis and the Beatles
As influencer of music?
No
Okay
Do you believe that he gets enough credit
for what he has done for the music business?
Yeah, I think so
Because he never hear about it
But it was a big, I'm telling you
But the thing is on the news
Right, so do you think that he's today
Still gets enough credit
For what he's done
Does he deserve credit?
Yeah
He does deserve it
Yeah, for what?
Well, for being the first one
With this lovely dance
It's lovely new moves
And
It was a totally new era
You're not going to believe what you're about to hear
You're not going to believe it
And I'm just going by the supposition that
The satellite repairman Uncle Jesse
Peter Lee Fenton
Does nobody's talking about
Okay, are you ready for this?
Hold on
We're going to do a single first
Because you know he can fix your misconceptions at any time
The satellite repairman
Coming after you
What's he going to do?
He'll fix your misconceptions
And answer questions too
Learn nothing in the universe
And he can't do for you
The satellite repairman
What?
Here it is
Hey, this is PW Fenton
Of digital flats
My word
I've just finished listening to the
Chubby Checker in a view on this
Script
Thestrip.potshow.com
All I can say is that it
Makes me live it
He compares himself to Elvis
And the Beatles
My record
And the industry is
It's probably the best batting average
In the music industry
It's not that it still holds
Maybe the top five or the top ten
In the music industry
Of all the 60s
There was always the Beatles
And there was a British invasion
There was Jimmy Hendrix
And there was Woodstock
A score of a lot of things that happened in the 60s
Uh-huh
The number one record in the 60s is a twist
And not only that
Here's the number one
Only on the number one twice
The twist
All of the great things
It happened in the 60s
The twist
Elvis came back out of the army
In the 60s
And the Beatles came off the plane
Woodstock
And Motel
And Ray Charles
And out of all the 60s
The twist was the number one song
Of the decade
Only song to be number one twice
First platinum
Let's twist again
And at the same time
It was the Grammy winner of the year
And the way we danced
In the 60s and 70s
At the 80s
And the 90s
And now 2000
It's all about show
We took a very quietly
Hidden in the archives
Of the music cabinets
When
If he should be comparing himself to anyone
It should be the monkeys
And Millie Vanillie
Chubby checker
Was manufactured
By Dick Clark
Dick Clark
Spotted a great tune
Written in perform
By a great artist
Who was just a little too black
And scary
For mainstream
A.K.A. White America
Clark
The most powerful man in the record industry at the time
Made a record company
And an artist
And offer they couldn't refuse
And the myth of Chubby checker
Was born
When Ernest Evans
And that was his name
Vegas style cover artist
Doing imitations of popular artists
Was offered the chance to record a song
For the powerful Dick Clark
He was willing to do anything
Including imitating Hank Ballard's voice
And taking on the name
Chubby checker
But don't take my word for it
Listen to the man who actually created the twist
Mr. Hank Ballard
A few years ago
I created a two hour radio documentary
About the blues history of the Tampa Bay area
One of the items I covered
Was the birth of the twist
At a local high school dance in Tampa, Florida
I had the great honor and good fortune
To talk with Hank Ballard
Before he died
Here's a portion of that documentary
Having to do with the twist
Next comes an interesting bit of Tampa folklore
From the late 1950s
Hank Ballard in the Midnighters
Was a touring R&B band that made frequent stops in Tampa
In 1958
They were playing a high school dance in Tampa
When Hank noticed the kids were doing some kind of new dance
They were swinging their arms back and forth
And twisting their bodies
Right then and there
Hank found the inspiration for a hit song
The Midnighters was doing a dance
I can't think of the name
We didn't know he was going to hear the downtown camp
We were playing a gig somewhere
It's been so leaner it's been a long time
And he was twisting about it
And the lyrics just came to me
We left the upper and then we went to Miami
And I got a test with a guy named Hindustone
Hindustone had a record coming to Miami
We went to the high school
He took it totally equipment
Recording equipment
We went to the high school and recorded it
That was the first version
I recorded it three times
The story really caught on
Of course the story doesn't end there
King Records pressed Hank Ballard's twist
And a copy fell into the hands of Dick Clark
Clark loved the record and seeing dollar signs
Started searching for an artist to record it
His original choice was Freddie Cannon
When that didn't happen, he settled on a local Philadelphia performer named Ernest Evans
Who we now know is Chubby Checker
He went into the studio and recorded as close to an exact copy of Hank Ballard's recording
As you will ever hear
Yeah Freddie Cannon, he had a first shot in Dick Clark talking about it
And Nick, he knew Dick Clark has nicked David Checker
And interviewed you in clone and did a clone version of my written a twist
Yeah, he did a hell of a clone
He glared with the audition about fifteen different people
You know trying to get somebody that's not supposed to meet
And it seems to have a tickle of the person in the past
You know he had a, you know he had a, he has a gig with him
Presbyton's name, the artist you know
Then the most powerful man in pop music went to King Records
Sid Nathan to make a deal
Hold back Ballard's version of the twist
And I'll make it worth your while
Here's what happened man. Here's what happened. I'll let it find out. Read it well.
I'll declare when I read the version when he had made a deal with King Rickard.
Two King Rickard, the president of King Rickard, the lead student of Nathan.
If you hold back Hank's a ruler version of the twist, I will make think of part of the time he had found.
That's what happened there. King Rickard had to publishing him on the fingerprint time and the twist.
So you too, and I wonder if I could kind of do what American men stand playing to it at Rickard.
And that's the story of how the twist was born in Tampa, and why we never got to hear about it.
If you've never heard the two recordings side by side, you'll be amazed.
First, I'll play a verse and chorus of Chubby Checkers version, followed by Hank Ballard's original recording from 1958.
Come on, baby man.
Let's do that.
Take me back my little hand.
And go like this.
Come on, baby man.
Now here's Hank's original version.
Okay, so did Chubby Checker do a great job with his covers and his career?
Sure he did.
Was he as important as the Beatles and Elvis?
No way.
They were originals.
He was a cover artist and always will be.
Yeah, that's amazing.
So the dance, this is the part where Chuckers, Chubby, Chubby Checker's story breaks down,
is the dance was their first Hank Ballard saw the dance, then made this song.
Isn't that incredible?
Yeah, but, but Chubby had a hit with it.
Right, but, but.
But if Chubby never, you know, recorded well because back in the day,
I'll tell you why.
Back in the day, American bandstand, right, was the place for music.
So Dick Clark, you know, basically, because the publishing writers still with the record company
that had Hank Ballard.
So they were going to make the money whether Hank Ballard had a hit or Chubby Checker had the hit.
Hank Ballard wasn't going to make shit anyway.
I'm sure he got shafted.
So Dick, what was wrong with him?
What do you mean?
With Hank.
Two black.
Oh yeah, he was two dark.
Yeah, that's what I heard.
I mean, this is what was going on.
Chubby Checker is kind of coffee color.
Yeah, he's a bit like, you know.
Yeah, so he married a Dutch woman.
So Dick Clark.
He basically said, look, why don't you, you know, I'm going to play this one to death
on American bandstand because he had kind of a monopoly on what people could hear.
Yeah.
And you think Dick Clark got also from the records.
And wasn't it something that was in Holland absolutely not done.
You were not interfere with the record business as a presenter and everything.
Oh, I think that I think it's that way everywhere.
Yeah.
It's absolutely.
I mean, that's the machine.
That's the machine.
But the American there was normal probably.
Yeah, but, you know, this is, this is what we're breaking through.
Baby.
Stopping all that shit.
Yeah.
Anyway, yeah, I think he's cool.
And he was the first one that we saw doing the twist.
He did that very well.
And we loved it.
He just has the tone down.
I mean, yeah, if you hear that whole interview, the whole interview was about
Chubby Checker.
While I was listening to him.
Yes, man.
I remember that he, he, we know him as a man with a lot of attitude.
And I think that he still got it.
He's still got it too.
And I think that ruined his career a lot.
He probably convinced himself that he really did, you know, come up with the twist.
Nothing wrong with thinking.
It's always good to think more of yourself than, you know, it's, it helps a little bit.
Yeah, but I think it's at the same time was also a frustration that he didn't actually.
Yeah.
And that's, that's what you hear.
Well, sometimes you have people with a character like that.
Yeah.
You know, whatever they do, they just think the frustrated.
And I know he did, but he married Miss Holland.
Yeah, you got a good look or didn't he?
Yeah.
I mean, I bet you they're still married.
I think they're still married.
I think that a very good marriage, a beautiful daughter's beautiful children.
And you always turn this, turn this something positive baby.
That's so good of you.
Oh, I know.
So good of you.
All right, we should stop.
I do have, um, like, that's it.
That was a very interesting story, Mr. Curry.
Yeah, I thought you'd like that.
Yeah, I enjoyed that.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Oh, shoot.
That reminds me.
I've, uh, another draft.
On the draft?
No, not another draft.
Um, so I had another contest.
Uh, you know, at the end of each podcast, uh, on pod show you here, um, get more great pot.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast,
the little reading network from pod show and limelight networks.
And then you hear this, oh, I love it.
Yeah.
You know, that the female voice.
So people started, you know, kind of guessing who that voice was.
And I said they'd never guess it.
They'd never guess it.
And you know, most people think it's you.
Some people think it's Callie.
This is a great brief TV.
Oh, I love it.
That's kind of what it is.
Yeah.
But it's not you.
You didn't do it.
No.
Uh, and I told people to go to daily source code.com and, uh,
uh, enter what they thought was the right answer.
And Rob us didn't.
Rob us didn't.
Just Rob.
His comment is there.
Posted eight eight two thousand six at twelve twenty nine central time.
Says.
P. W. Fenton's wife.
Roz.
What?
Yeah. He got it right.
I have no idea how we figured that one out.
But he got it right.
So he wins it.
What should he win?
He wins a prize.
I hadn't figured out what the prize was yet.
What should I give him?
Do you have some panties?
We can give away.
Yeah.
One of Patricia's panties.
Can I have, can I go with you autograph him?
Yes.
Just one.
All right.
Yeah.
Oh, we can do lots of contests with that.
Cool.
Yeah.
Okay.
So Rob, congratulations.
Yeah.
Really.
Yeah. That's cool.
That's a good present.
You, you would thought it.
Yeah.
When I just met you.
That's how you got me, baby.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Speaking of which, you know, our 18th wedding anniversary passed.
Yeah.
And.
I already told everybody you felt that this was a really important one.
All of a sudden, for some reason, because 18 is like, what's a good number?
It's always important.
There's been years where we both forgot it.
Yeah, but then probably we were very busy or, you know, now we're here.
Yeah.
And you came.
I was really busy.
I just came back from America.
And then it's like, oh, shit.
Tomorrow's our wedding anniversary.
So I didn't have time to buy you anything.
And I want to go buy something.
But then the airspeed indicator broke.
So we were too late to go buy anything in Holland when I was.
Oh, you thought it was a nice day.
I, I'll go flying.
That was, you flew off.
I fucked that up, didn't I?
Yeah.
And then he came home.
That's it, tell it.
And he hurts.
Do you think we look so bad?
So bunches of, or it's free.
Three, three.
Three bunches of, who was all that flowers.
It was the last ones at the gas station.
Brownleeves.
And, and then those green curly stamps in it that I really hate.
That they put in every, every bunch of shitty flowers.
You know, that's new, that's new way flowers.
I don't know what it is.
So sort of stamps with nothing with one leave.
It's in there.
And he said, yeah, I thought you'd like those.
I said, you know, yeah, I don't like them.
I hate them.
I'm an old fashion woman like beautiful flowers.
Beautiful pink and white and gorgeous.
And, you know, not green stamps.
I said, I was sorry.
And they were so old.
They were they stink.
Unbelievable.
Okay.
At the column real short.
And.
But.
I put them in vones room.
Which you, she will think, oh, that's nice.
Got a bunch of flowers here.
They're old, but.
Stinky, but.
I'm sorry.
I was confused.
I really was.
I hadn't thought about it when I made the appointment to go flying.
I just wanted to go flying.
It been, it been three weeks.
I had a rough time before that.
I just wanted to go flying.
And I didn't think about it.
Yeah.
But I love you.
I love you.
Just because of you.
Well, 18 actually happens to be a very important number.
Yeah.
Did you know that?
Listen.
I told you.
Hey, Adam, this is Tom Rockle from Buck.
I drive time podcasts.
Listen in the number 436.
And heard you say that you guys had kind of decided for some reason that number 18 in your
anniversary would be special.
Well, number 18 in a Jewish context is very special.
That's why 18's wedding anniversary.
And that kind of stuff is is really important because 18 is the number for life.
So when you say, look, I am, which is too life.
You're actually also saying, two 18 because high or a wife is the number 18.
And so I'm sitting there thinking that to myself,
it was like, I bet you didn't even know that.
And then immediately after you say that, you follow it up with or you day.
A subliminal context or just a just happens dance.
I don't know.
Talk to you later.
See?
Oh, by the way.
Full order.
See?
You were Shalamil.
Shalamil.
That day you were Shalamil.
The chicks is calling me a Shalamil.
Yep.
Stop already.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm done.
I feel, I feel bad now because I'm a bad husband.
Good.
I'm a bad, bad husband.
Yeah.
But I have to say sometimes when you come home, you just have gifts.
Just like that.
Just because.
Very nice.
This is true.
Nice.
I don't know what the message is.
But a nice eye cream.
The must be a mess.
No, there's no fucking message there.
No, no.
No.
It's.
You're looking.
Look, where do I get a chance to shop?
This is exactly two places.
You're sitting in a play airport at the airport or in the plane.
Yeah.
Although sometimes if I do go out shopping for myself, I'm always looking for stuff for you.
If I go in, but this like one time in three weeks in San Francisco that actually went out to market street or something to go get something.
Yeah.
I didn't buy anything.
I bought nothing.
Yeah.
So.
But I think you'd like that because I see how this is revitalizing eye live.
No.
New, new, new flashing new at me.
Yeah.
And then remember that boob cream?
For you daughter.
Yeah.
Is that a message to her?
No.
I saw this thing.
It's like make your boobs look bigger and firmer in the airplane.
I'm virgin.
Oh, that's interesting.
And then.
And she comes to this.
The flight attendant comes up to me and says.
Who did not have huge boobs.
And she says.
What do you want to order?
Oh, this is.
Wow, this is new.
She says, yes, I've heard that's quite good.
I said, have you tried it?
No.
She went.
Oh, I've got no.
No.
As you can see.
It's like, it looks like a socks baby.
This is shit.
She had a shining work.
Yeah.
I'm perfume.
You're perfume.
Yeah.
Whenever there's a new like J-Lo.
Well, fuck the flowers.
Perfume is good.
But the new J-Lo is confusing because she comes out with new stuff.
So off and listen.
Listen.
This is a marketing lesson.
So often, I saw it.
I'm like, is that still new or is that new again or is-
The model didn't look different.
Yeah, same model.
Exactly.
So I was confused.
They probably already know that because it's all J-Lo glow glow glow ago.
ahead.
Yeah.
So the new J-Lo live or live, that's the new one.
He has all picked that one up next time.
Yeah.
I've never glow.
Good liked that.
I also sometimes I've given you cars or kinds of stuff with big bows on it.
Have I not?
was that. That was the Chrysler. You wanted that Chrysler as a convertible.
There was before. If you like me to buy it, I just bought you Jaguar.
It's yours too. No, it's not mine. We've already established that. It's your car. Are you happy?
You're unhappy? No, I'm not. Do you see me cry? Yes. I'm a little streaming down your face.
Carefully. Carefully, give me a push, please. I'm almost.
Man. Okay. I see that's the most beautiful gift. You make me laugh. Oh, man.
Make me laugh. Are you turning around and make everything right again? Yeah. Okay.
Well, I don't think we didn't top that. We won't play another song. Should we just turn it off?
Well, I have to go and see you. Sorry.
With my sister, he's a, has arrived. Okay. I'll just end the show then. Okay. I love you, baby.
Love you, too. See you this week. Okay.
But man, it's a lie. I don't want mine. No, I'll be mine.
So can't see you. Sorry, I don't want mine.
Can't feel this rock down in my home.
And I can't see you. Sorry, I don't want mine.
I'm about my side. I feel fine.
You're my revelation. You're the answer to my question.
How long have we seen my time yet?
See if I feel it's real. You crawl out of that perfect skin.
I'm climbing down with your shine.
Will you be my life? So can't see you. Sorry, I don't want mine.
Can't feel this rock down in my home.
I can't see you. Sorry, I don't want mine.
But my side. I feel fine.
I feel fine.
I'm a show with two young two real.
Hey salad ya'll tell me I'm slow.
He-et-me-he-my- llevar will save me.
He-et-me-ho man
You're weak, him because I can't see the sun.
And I burn.
Can't feel this rocks down in my home.
I can't see a sun, I'm on
But I don't mind
I don't mind
Can't see the sun
I can't see the crown
I don't mind
Can't see the sun
Black live live
Let's see the sun
We can find a link to that
Object Music Network
Show notes at dailysourcecode.com
Parts of the show brought to you by our new sponsor Akira.
They've got a really awesome target cast to go listen, listen to it accurate.podshow.com.
The first episode is Grammy winner, Elliott Shiner, who talks about designing the Akira
RDX surround sound system.
Go ahead, have a listen.
Tell me if you think it sounds like a commercial if you actually got some content and information
that you'd like.
Habitchi, it's the latter.
I'll talk to you guys tomorrow.
Take care.
Bye-bye.
Have another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the Hyperformance podcast to
live re-network from Podshow and line-white networks.
I love it.