This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want to hear content with AdAS domain name?
This show will give you a special code, get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie, three, six, one.
$60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
$60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
$80 million worth of plane strapped to my ass.
$60 million worth of flying strapped to my ass.
$60 million worth of airline strapped to my ass.
$60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Are you my rally show? Are you the answer to my question? I have always been my time now
Because if I feel this feeling, but you call out of your perspective, I'm scared of calling the mind
Will you shine? Will you be my life? Because I can't see someone
I can't feel crying more, I can't see someone
But I don't mind, you're by my side, I feel fine
I feel fine
I can't shout to you to be alone
Hey, shout in your heart, silly little stone
Hey, baby, I can't see you
Baby, I can't hear you calling me calling
I can't see someone
Can't feel drugs anymore
I can't see someone anymore
But I don't mind, I go blind
I can't see someone
I can't feel crying more
But I don't mind, you're by my side, I feel fine
I feel fine
I can't see someone
It's from Montana, the call to the sun
Go, check, go
Oh man, it's good to be back, I'm at the hell of processor
It calls themselves black lab
Let's see the sun, of course it's podsafe
From the podsafe music network and music.pot show.com
Let me just hit a button here, let me see something
I take that mixer with me everywhere I go
I really got to get a second set up in San Francisco
This is ridiculous, I keep setting everything up again
It sounds a little funky, it could just be my ears as usual
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
Welcome to the daily source code
What is on from the cottage in the affluent suburb?
How many people hate me saying that?
The affluent suburb of Gilford and Surrey in the United Kingdom
It's unbelievable, I have castblaster completely lined up today
Everything is, every single slot is filled up
Because actually yesterday I had prep the show
I got up, I was really out of whack from the travel
I got up relatively early, of course
And I slept a little bit on Sunday and in and out of consciousness
Is what you could call it more likely
And I prepped everything and I got to go to London
Because I had to go to the guardian
Changing media summit I think is what it was called
Which was something that was agreed to a long time ago
The dates actually changed
I thought it would be interesting because I was invited to sit on a panel
With the head of BBC interactive radio
And I'm forgetting if he was the president of the president of interactive
I believe a virgin radio
And the whole thing was mediated by a senior editor from the guardian
And let me tell you
Very interesting, although I thought the conference by itself
Was probably mediocre at best
I'm not quite sure who was for it, kept asking who was in the audience
And to say well it felt like just a lot of broadcasters in general
We're in the audience people who wanted to learn about social networking
About podcasting about the future radio and all these
I mean really if you just keep up reading a little bit online
Then you probably could have gotten a lot of the questions
Answered that were I guess we're brought up yesterday
And the session was really short, it was like 40 minutes
Maybe I could barely get into it
It was so interesting I said well you know
We have our 550 rule within five years
50% of all content consumed by people will be made by the same people
Consuming it and it was like
Man, you could have heard of it
In fact I said you could hear a pin drop, couldn't you
And it was like completely dead silent
But
What was really nice about yesterday is I met a couple other people
A Joe twist was there
She showed up because I know her for a long time her and castle
Robert Dolby from top of the pods was there
That was great it was very interesting to meet him
Very enthusiastic guy
I met another guy later on
And you know just listening to one of the BBC is about to start as from what I understand
It's about to start with a huge podcasting trial
And I'm not quite sure how long it's going to last or what they're going to do
But they're actually going to call it podcasting which is new for the BBC
And I'm thinking man it's like
The opportunities upon us my friends
There's a lot of alternative content waiting to get out
And I think if we had the right partners and we had the right tactics
I think we could really open up the UK market to podcasting
Now I feel it's primed and it's just about ready
So I'm excited about a lot of the prospects
A lot of the things that I heard and felt yesterday
Tells me that it really is time to break into the market
And I wouldn't mind having a London office to go to once in a while
So that's what we're working on
Before I forget about black lab
That was a suggestion sent to me by Artith Makala
who sent me a Gmail and it was perfect
Adam longtime listener of the DSC
Really enjoy Monday mornings when I open iTunes and see your new podcasts there
But you really need to play more rock with a hard stretch
Get back to your head bangers ball days
And hence the suggestion black lab with the see this on
Thank you very much
You'd be amazed how easy it is for me when people send me suggestions
Send me a link to the podcast and music network as well
For whatever suggestion you send in and it works man
It does thank you appreciate it
Adam it's Callie
Hey Callie
I'm sick
Oh
We both must have got something on the plane
You mean you mean you and Neil not you and I both dear
Been in bed since one day which should be fun
But it's not
I've been wanting to try and try and get my day at Part Show up
But when neither of us can concentrate long enough to do it
So thank you and I want to go any longer
Without saying thank you for having me out to San Francisco
We had a great time and I appreciate everything you guys did
I feel better Callie
I feel really horrible that you're sick
He must have been something you picked up on the plane
Because everyone at Part Show has already been sick
We've had all everyone's been sick
So can't be us we're past the incubation period
I hope you feel better
I'd say a geek brief pop up but I guess that wasn't the San Francisco one
So yeah I know what that can be like man
That sucks
You know it's so weird but I'm just trying to figure out
Somehow it just doesn't sound the way it used to
I got tons and tons of promos
As I said you know I had everything prepared yesterday
And you just you know it's
It drives me nuts
You guys are feeding me so much information
There's so many great audio feedbacks, promos
Things that I definitely want to put on the show
That this show you know if I skip one day
It's like what am I going to get?
I can't throw all this stuff away
It's too good I want to keep it up low that song
Yeah upload that song
I'm about to put it on the check this out
These guys are great
All right Adam
Yo what's up?
What's up?
This is OT cries
Like an afa mega podcast
And I am a lady of the afa mega podcast
What's up?
Mr. Curry
Now I've been listening to your show now for the last few months
Right on
And I believe back in three, three, four
You mentioned that you wanted a hip hop podcast
Here we are
Right on
And also we're ex military, US Army
You're your show
I love this man
Listen to these two guys
Ex military Army
I heard the call
And now they're doing a podcast
I love it
It's called
The Delta Sierra Charlie
Am I boy a lady?
Yeah
Explain what I come from
Yeah, I know you know Mr. Curry
Adam
Where it comes from
But as far as the folks who don't know
The other Sierra Charlie is the
Fanetic alphabet for the military
Mm-hmm
So that you when you speak and teach other over the
Over the airways on your radios
That you don't confuse
S with a
I don't know
C or T or whatever
So there's no confusion
Yeah
So you got Delta for D
Sierra
Is an S of course like you use
And Charlie
Or whatever you want to
Charlie might continue mission
Is that it?
Charlie Mike
Right just like if I was to say
You know D you say
Did you say P
Right
No, I said okay Delta
Okay
There you go
So Adam
Yo
Hit us up man
You know just go to
To our podcast
Right
Alpha
Dash Omega
Cash.com
Or if it's in the
In the
iTunes
It's Alpha Omega
Alpha Omega
Check us out though Adam
We want to set this thing off
And give some people some things to listen to
We enjoy your podcast
I think that you throw down myself
Personally, this is a learning company
And you actually
I think from listening to yours
It made us want to do things
A little bit better
Cause we know you're a professional
And you've been doing it for a long time
Professional DJ and all that
We do appreciate what you've done
For a podcast
And so
Check us out
Give us a shout
You know
Alpha Omega podcast
Out
Latte right here
Alright and this is
O.T.
Out
From the Delta Sierra Charlie
To the Alpha Omega
Charlie Mike
Continued mission
Looking good
Did you guys this go over to Iraq
Were you there?
I'd like to know what your service record was
Anyway congratulations
Guys welcome to
Welcome to podcasting
Definitely subscribe
If you got any
If you got any cool hip hop tunes
You want that are pod safe
Let me know
I'm looking for some good ones
And from time to time people
Send me some but sometimes like
Whoa
Little two shoot my bitch up
But if you got something
Think what fit on the Charlie
Just let me know please
Adam PD love from Love House
Radio and interview with a stranger
I just wanted to thank you for playing
My cop skid on DSC 356
Last Monday
And I wanted to know
I keep hearing about the
Charlie the Charlie
And now the Golden Ticket
You have a Wonka Complex
Is there something going on there
Little Chocolate Factory
Hidden somewhere in your basement
Yeah
Started to wonder with the Golden Ticket
So I got a chocolate factory
My basement
Uh-huh
Tell us more please
Tell us more
Talks you later Adam
Thanks a lot
All right
Yeah I'm almost forgot
What
Yeah a lot of people picked up on that
So the test is going to commence
Tomorrow
Had a back and forth with Andrew Grummit
The legendary Andrew Grummit
So tomorrow we're going to test out
Our D-Gap system a little bit further
Again it's just a test
So she could go wrong
And it could break and it could
Anything could happen
But this is just a test
We will attach a real prize to it
It was a
A special super powered remote
For your iPod
An RF remote
So not this silly little infrared
But just something you can actually connect to your
iPod and you can change it via remote
From huge distances I'm told
Ah
Excuse me
A little heartburn there
Uh-huh
The way the way it's going to work
Or the way we're going to test it
Should say is
One of the downloads of the Charlie
One of the complete downloads
Will include a special piece of audio
In which I'll basically congratulate the person
Because that person will have won the Golden Ticket
And they'll be a phone number for them to call
And they'll have to give us a secret code
Doesn't really matter because only one person
Can claim it and that's the first person who listen to it
Um, and uh, and that'll be automatically inserted
And everyone else won't hear that special piece of audio
So, uh, it's just a test to see if we can make a work
And what I'm really more interested in is
Uh, of all the downloads
Will the person who downloaded it
Listen to it and actually call in with the code
Um, so we'll make sure that within the first
Day of release that it definitely will get downloaded
Um, and then we'll just have to wait and see if someone finds it
So, um, and it'll just only be for tomorrow's episode
Of course in the future we're going to build this out
It could be across multiple shows
Could be across archives
It can be anywhere within the podcast
Uh, it's kind of be pretty cool
I'm very excited about it
Hey there Adam Howard Greenstein here in New York
And I was listening to the Charlie 358 and 360
And I heard you talking about the Golden Ticket
That you're going to be giving away to one lucky
Listener of the Daily Source Code
And, um, I was talking about this with my kids
And, you know, Willy Wonka is one of their favorite movies
And, when I told them this they said
Daddy, I want the Golden Ticket
I said, you mean Adam Curry's Golden Ticket
And they said Daddy, I want the Golden Ticket now
I said, why do you want to Golden Ticket?
I want to go to the Pod Show Factory
And see Mr. Curry and watch him make all his pod shows
With all the little people running around
And then the train squirrels in the chocolate
And I said, it's not really like that
They don't really have a factory
Adam actually has a cottage
Daddy, I want the Golden Ticket
Well, how's Daddy supposed to get you a Golden Ticket?
I mean there's thousands and thousands of people listening to this podcast
Daddy, get lots and lots of computers
And download the Pod Show over and over again
To get the one with the Golden Ticket
But, but that would take hours
By the way, it's not just the downloading
That would take hours and hours
You actually have to listen to each individual
So this is how we're going to combat fraud
Is it can be inserted anywhere within the program
So you'd have to know where it would be inserted
So you'd have to listen to every single entire show
So, yeah
The Thousand Computers Daddy, I don't think that's going to work
Daddy, I want the Golden Ticket now
See what you started Adam?
I don't know what I'm going to do
I really hope you get me that Golden Ticket, man
And hey, when did my kids turn British?
Anyway, peace
That's a very good question
Yeah, I guess I do have it
Well, I think I've said before
I really want it in the chart effect
My favorite movie of all time
Of course the Gene Wilder version
Although after many doubts I did check out the Johnny Deb version
And actually like that one very much as well
But still the original
Nothing goes beyond that childhood fantasy
Well, you've kids picking up on it, I dig that
So hopefully tomorrow
It'll all work out
And somehow someone will get
The Golden Ticket inserted
And we'll win that wonderful
Remote
Which I'll plug tomorrow
When I get back to Sam Levin's email
To figure out what the name of the brand was
So you've probably noticed across all these pod shows
That we are plugging Go Daddy
Really heavily, they've made a nice investment
In the podcasters who are on the podshow podcasent network
And the cool thing about this one brand
Many voices is that everyone's free and clear
And open to communicate it
However they want to
And man, there's been some
A Callie I saw
Oh, talk about
Rrrr
Callie did a sponsored wardrobe change
And slipped into the
String strap tank top
The Go Daddy String strap tank top
I bought some domain names immediately
Hi Adam, this is Safi
From Dorf Dishore
That's Dishore with the DJ
Oh, you are
And on Friday's Charlie
You were talking about the Go Daddy girl
Being on your list
Well, I want you to know that you've been on my list
Since the 80s
Beware and all
Hmm
That's my wife
Listen to Dorf Dishore at
DorfDishorepodcas.com
Oh man
Patricia heard the show
She heard the show about
The Go Daddy girl being on my list
And she said she was no match for Angelina Jolie
And absolutely
Could not be interchanged on the list
So
That's a bummer
But she made up for it last night
After the conference
And yeah, I'll talk to the Go Daddy girl
But my list is my dance card is now full
If you know what I mean
And of course my buddy Jeff Smith checks in
Helping us out with the Go Daddy promoter
In the only way Jeff Smith knows how to help out
Hey, I'm going to make a website
How am I going to do it?
GoDaddy.com
Make a dot com name with us
GoDaddy
Get your dot com
Dot net dot or dot
Is time in forever
GoDaddy
Get your dot net dot
See you soon
Dotty
Anything you want at
GoDaddy
GoDaddy.com
Has new domain names, transfers and renewals
As low as $1.99
By a ball can say
In fact, order your domain name
Get your credit block
Staying at your website
Feelin'
Clean email at
GoDaddy
Get a start-in webpage
Forwarding and masking
Total DNS control
GoDaddy
Hosting plans started
$3.95
And you get $24.77
As protection hand private domain registrations
GoDaddy
And get your business
If all on more than 200 surchanges
GoDaddy
Come on
Daily source co-blissner
IntercoDSC1
When you check out
Save an additional 10% on any order
GoDaddy
Good
You're outrageous
The Jeff Smith dot com
And the Jeff Smith kiddies, I guess
His girls
Yeah, I've been talking to Jeff
We're gonna do more stuff
You know, I think that
Independent artists like this
Also deserve a chance to quit their day job
Man, you're just too good
There's too much good shit going on
Love it
Fantastic
Thank you very much.
Okay, here's something very interesting
That I came across yesterday
Now we kind of have our own little social network
Excuse me, social media network going on with in Pod Show
Chris McIntyre is usually the first one to spot stuff
And send it out
And he's saying that something
A link to an interesting press release
On an outfit called
Pod2Mob
As in Pod2Mobile
Automated software solution
Transform podcasting from new medium to thriving marketplace
And so as I kind of skin through the release
I was like, I, okay, so this looks like another typical
You know, add insertion thing
I'm like, okay, that's really good
Where are all the add insertions, by the way
The de-gap systems working
The go-daddy tags are in
I don't hear a lot of others being automatically inserted
So I'm always interested in just skimming through it
And in the release a couple things called my eye
The first one was according to business week
Sequoia capital, which is one of our investors
Police podcasting is positioned to capture
One to two billion dollars away from the 30 billion
Dollar traditional radio advertising market
Over the next three to five years
And so first like, wow, did Sequoia make an investment
And these guys and so no, they didn't make it
They just quoted the business week, okay, I thought
And then I read a little bit further
And Brad Zootout
Who is, I guess one of the founders of this company
Pod2Mob
It's quoted saying with our solution
Anyone from a Fortune 500 company
To a blog with big ambitions
To a budding band can quickly and easily launch an ad campaign
That is highly targeted and affordable
And then they go into all this functionality
Whether you can insert
So basically what they do is they have a little application
Which you download for your phone
I couldn't test it myself because it's only for US carriers at the moment
You download that to your phone
They have a little directory in there
And you select something from the directory
And it starts playing on your mobile phone
No, in general, pretty good
I like the idea
And then reading in the functionality
They have podcasts category targeting for audio ads
Advertise a control panel for easy campaign
Creation, stat tracking, easy and cost effective means to launch
Advertising campaign
Ads can be submitted in broadcasts and 24 hours
All this stuff
I'm just okay, okay, I'll go over and check it out
Pod2Mob.com
And the first thing I noticed is they have a very nice endorsement
For the pod save music network
They have our pod save music network
Headphone, head logo, plugged into their page there
So I thought, oh, that's nice
And I'm looking around like I don't see really anything for podcasters
It looks like this is pretty much all for advertisers
And I'm hunting around hunting around
And I'm thinking to myself, wait a minute
These guys are selling advertisements and podcasters
That they are streaming to mobile phones
And it appears that they're putting ads in front of that
And like hold on a second
So I sent out the email blast to everybody
Yeah, so if you look at their website pod2Mob.com
It is pod2Mob.com
Listen to any podcast on your cell phone for free
And so immediately Andrew Grummit signed up
Downloaded the application to his podcast
And he recorded and it's funny
The daily source code is the first entry into their
They're so called directory
But if you search on Adam Currier Daily source code
It pops up as well on the phone
Mind you, that's pretty cool
And you have an account which is created online
But then when you fire up the daily source code
And Andrew actually recorded with a microphone next to the telephone
So it's a crappy quality
But this is what you hear
So we just heard this podcasters brought to you by
Modtones.com
And then my podcasters which has by itself
An ad in search of a podcasters
And it's a really good idea
So we just heard this podcasters brought to you by
Modtones.com
And then my podcasters which has by itself
An ad in search of a podcasters
Which has by itself an ad in search
And we're really a tag in search for go daddy
And that's p-dog there
With a go-dog with a go daddy
Now you'll hear
We'll give you a special code to get
Great discounts at go daddy
So now you'll hear the Delta Sierra Charlie
360 tag
Delta Sierra Charlie
Right so that was a Friday show
So these guys are stealing our content
They're stealing our shows and putting ads in front of them
And charging advertisers
Look guys
Stop immediately
I mean I truly believe just looking at the site
And looking at the press release and all the pieces
That you guys probably smart technologists
Put together something really nice
It's not really spectacular what they've done
They basically it's a streaming playlist
So you're streaming in MP3
Down to your phone in a very low bit rate
And because it's a stream you can insert one thing into another
So it's not really a full file
But it's just an actual stream you're accessing
But they're putting ads and it even says this podcast is brought to you by
Modtones.com
I'm sorry you don't have that right
And I'm gonna be really easy about it
Because I really do believe you guys just miscalculated your opportunity
But you can't do that
You cannot take someone else's content and put ads in or around it
That's you know Jesus Christ
I got slapped by Jason Calc
Oh my god I can't believe I said that
I'm so sorry I apologize
I did not mean to use that name
It's only because I have a segment coming up about it later
That it triggered in my head
I've been trying I'm sorry
Apologize let me continue
Guys you cannot do this
This is my content
I own it
You have no right to advertise on it
And by the way any podcast that you access through this pod to mob system
We'll have ads inserted into it
So I suggest you guys stop it immediately
Close it off right now
Rethink it because all you have to do is just ask
It's just ask podcasters to sign up with you to enable that to be sent through the wires
And otherwise you're gonna look at a humongous glass action suit
Which I don't think you want to get into
Because every single podcasters
Here's about this will be pissed off
It's wrong
It's just completely wrong
So send me an email at amercurry.com
Let me know what you guys are doing about this
But you cannot continue and it has to stop by tomorrow
Otherwise all kinds of people are gonna jump in action
Believe me
But I think we can solve this amongst ourselves
And we don't have to get lawyers involved
You just have to shut that down for now and figure out
How you get podcasters permission
To actually start inserting ads into their podcasters
Or before or after or whatever
Speaking of ads
Hey hey be quiet
I've got an incoming transmission
Let's see if the computer can translate it
I think I got it
No amount of time you read one
Look at the third one from the star
I detect signs of life with higher forms of communication
Many life forms spread all over the planet
How do you think they communicate over such vast areas?
I'm detecting a worldwide grid
An incredibly secure high speed digital communication
And information super highway
Let's see if we can open a channel
I think I've got something
Welcome to earthlings
We provide the crucial link to planet earth
Earthlink
Appealing to those on and off our planet
Make use of it
Earthlink
You're a little early for a one-brand many voices
Quit your day job campaign for earthling
But I liked it so much
And these are starting to come through now
Who was I think was add on the curry comments
Curried calm comments he set up some kind of system with delicious bookmarks
Anyway, so I think the end result is there's an RSS feed
Which is comprised of MP3s that are posted anywhere on the internet
But are tagged with delicious tags
Curry comments
And then they automatically show up in my
In my iTunes actually is where I have where I've subscribed to this
And it does work you know because a couple of things I picked up today
Came from that feed so you know it is much more effective than email
It's just you know the publishing part I think is still a little bit too hard
But if you have something that if you have some kind of upload system and all you and you can actually attach delicious tags to it
And if it's for me put curry comments and it'll automatically flow into my media inbox
Which is what I'm calling that so system does work. I appreciate you setting it up
Speaking of the curry comments now it's all in older posts
But gosh man the the comments spammers have gotten to me
And I'm really not sure what to do about it, but it's horrible
And if you look at the entry for daily source code 208
I mean they hit that one really really hard
And it's all the same thing. It's like wow great site you have here. What a wonderful resource
Oh man I hate it. I really hate it. I wish you know I wish we could figure something out with that
I like the the concept of open comments and not having to register for
For leaving comments but man is it a pain in the ass and a lot of talk about my space everywhere
And I just had a minor epiphany about my space parents are very worried. You know another finding out that
Oh, it's all this inappropriate stuff that's going on and
And everyone is calling for legislation and FCC rulings and you know hey look parents
Let me just say something about this if you want to know what your kids are doing
And get on my space and look at it and hunt around you know
You can't governments are even more backwards than then parents are when it comes to technology
They're way way behind most governments. I would have to say
So if you want to know what your kids are doing if you want to form an opinion
Don't get it from people magazine or USA today get on my space my space.com hunt around and you know and start a profile and
And see what happens and if you really really really don't like it
If you really disagree please don't go running to your senator and your congressman and and you know and and yelling around about how this is
Ridiculous and it's hurting our kids hey parents of the world get on my space and make it the most boring place in the world and kids
A little go away all by themselves. You can shut my space down in ten days
If all of the parents got on and started creating really parenty profiles
I'm just sick and tired of hearing about parents calling to the government to help them with what their kids are into
You'd lazy asses lazy lazy lazy lazy figured out for yourself will you get on my space good
I got a nice long email from Ray Lane who's one of our board of directors. He's from
Clienter Perkins he used to run Oracle have a lot of respect for this guy and
He listens to the Charlie. I think that he got the message about about the secret board of director member of the day and he's now back up to date
He's he's he's he's synchronized. I think he's heard every Charlie and he's up to speed up until Friday
Even the videos and he had some really good feedback and and I appreciate that and even had feedback on a comic strip blogger
And he says, you know, I really like this comic strip blogger, you know, although I think the
Paraphrasing here it sounds like he's sucking your dick too much now, which of course is true. I told CSB to dial it down from 11 to about five
And you know, and he's cranked it up just a little bit have to say the stuff that he's talking about on the on the comments
Although it's still very heated and a lot of words and allegations are thrown out there that well it's CSB so you know what you get with him
He doesn't know a lot about Europe and the EU and the EU laws and what's changing and how it's supposed to work and which countries are
Are in and out and half in and I find that extremely interesting and
Well, you know, this is leaving up to don't you comic strip
Ladies and gentlemen, the following comment from comic strip blogger is definitely not family safe
So you may want to shield young ears and protect them from the comments from comic strip blogger
Hey Adam Kerry, so I have noticed that you were present as speaker at that media
Sammy organized by those commis
So he's talking about the guardian media summit that was at yesterday, which is he's saying are those commis the guardian?
Well, let me remind you that in UK there is such a thing as of come
Something similar to FCC but in UK and read your present is in UK during phone in a scared like hell
That if they let us something uncensored then off come we'll dump them
So I had to listen to that two times before I understood it
But there's an organization here called off com which he says like the FCC
I thought there were more like the ANC trade and FCC kind of combined into one
But so apparently
What he's saying is it organizations like the guardian are afraid of off com because they have so much incredible power and can change you know policy here in the UK
And that's why I guess the conference was lame is that what he's saying?
Yeah mate, there is no fucking freedom of speech in UK off com kills it
So to foster freedom of speech in UK and as well here is little joke from me
Do you know what do you call it if you have nuts on the wall
Well nuts
Okay, and how do you call it if you have nuts in the urine?
In the urinal
This cannot be leaning anywhere good. Here comes the non safe fart
P nuts. Oh, okay, and how do you call it if you have nuts on the chest?
Then you call it cock in your mouth
No, yeah, mate fuck FCC USA and fuck off com in UK fuck them
And if we can't fuck them through regular radio because fucking off com blocks freedom
Then let's fuck them through podcasting fuck yeah
Okay, so USB
So if I'm looking through all the the efforts there the F bombs
You're saying that off com limits freedom of speech in the UK very interesting
I'd love to hear from some of the UK podcasters what their stance is on off com
Where are you guys I got a lot of promos and stuff but
Let me know which where you stand on these kinds of issues UK podcasters looking for you. We're looking for you
And the podshow podcast network making some waves with one of our new members the strip
Which is the podcast from and about Las Vegas just the day and they had a celebrity on their show
An honest to God celebrity an MSM mainstream media celebrity Dennis Miller
Hey, it's Miles from the strip on this week's show. We had Dennis Miller take a listen
Now I was at the famous Andre Agatha the grand fan for children fundraiser in 2003 when you did the routine
Yes, we're getting a lot of laughs
You know, that's the odd thing to me about it
I don't remember doing poorly there. I think I killed you had some choice words for the N. I wore it
It would write when the war was starting and Hillary Clinton and the French and all this and later in the show
Alton John told the audience that when people say why do they hate us so much? Dennis Miller
All right, were you surprised by that? Were you sitting backstage listening to it?
No, I said not the crowd listening to that
So what were you surprised so you take them take a nap?
Yeah, you know, I don't John and I don't know each other for man and from what I gather he's a bit of a TV fellow to begin with
Yeah, you know, I don't like my name being used in vain like that, you know, don't know him from Adam please
Seems to get angry periodically
That's fine with me. All I wish he would have acknowledged is it wasn't like when I left that stage
It wasn't going well
I think I killed so it wasn't that incendiary in the language
Well, you would say that you don't know him and Madonna does know him and he called her you know a fat horse
Something recently, so he's clearly none
Yeah, I think his MO is to be a bit of a crank on it so long
And you don't want right I'll just be honest with you as much as I love your song and burned down the mission and some will you connection
I could not care less what else
Thanks to me
It just doesn't matter to me
Next week how we manned out and don't forget to visit us at thestrippodcast.com
So what I like about the strip is that these celebrities they're in Vegas
And when you're in Vegas, you know things start to get loose and you start to like you know have fun
And shit happens and people open up and they're happy to talk and these guys are right there and everybody's face
And you know, and I'm sure that people are going out if it could's a phone or it's a podcast, whatever
But wow, you know, that wasn't pretty choice words
And I missed that whole bruhaha between Elton and Dennis Mill
I'm quite happy
I'm honestly
I'm starting to care less and less about that kind of stuff
You know, I was watching and I was at entertainment tonight or action entertainment or there's a million entertainment shows
When I was at the condo
And I'm just listening all these stories, I just don't care
I really don't
You know, it's the same about mainstream music, top 40 and just I really, I like the songs
I just don't care, I can get into it
But I really don't care like the way I care about what we're doing
It's because of comments like this
Hey Adam, this is Jim, I'm a longtime listener and I love your show
I wanted to bring to your attention and upcoming milestone that you're going to be hitting
On Friday you will be releasing if I'm not mistaken
The Charlie number 365
This means you have
Developed a year's worth of material
I bring this up for an interesting point
It's about 530 in the morning here in Hong Kong on Tuesday
I just woke up about an hour ago, couldn't sleep
I got here yesterday from San Francisco
And I was really looking forward to playing this morning's Charlie
While I was getting ready and doing some email
Unfortunately, I see it hasn't been posted yet
Now I think with a year's worth of catalog to draw from
You could have Uncle Jesse together some
Best of Charlie's or maybe in box
Anyway, I hope you enjoy your vacation next week
And maybe you can have a P.W. Take a look at doing this for you
Take care, again, love the show
Oh no, oh no, it's him
You called Uncle Jesse and the jingle comes out
The sad light repair man coming after you
Sad light repair man, what's he going with him
He'll fit your misconceptions and answer questions too
There's nothing in the universe that he can't do for you
Sad light repair man
What?
He might
Sad light repair man
Yeah
Everybody
Another P.W. is here right now
Because he's waiting another nine minutes
Until my satellite window for today closes
And P.W.
You know, it's all in jazz man, we love you
You're not just a sad light repair man, of course
You're not
You're not just
Uncle Jesse
You're much more than that
Hi, this is P.W. Fenton
And I'd like to invite you to go to digitalflotsom.org
And acquaint yourself with my podcast Digital Flotsom
It's an eclectic mix of music and talk
That will sometimes make you laugh
And sometimes make you cry
But it will always make you listen
Hello my Royal subjects, now it's not Christmas
But I do invite you to join me this and every weekend
Watching the maximum newest video sandbox
We are highly amused
I feel really bad, I messed it up man
I messed it up earlier in the show
I said something that I had really been trying not to say
And I was doing so good
Let's talk about it now
Hey Adam Steve Web here with the Life Spring Plancast
Hey it seems as if I've started a mini thread
On the topic of using the Lord's name and vein
Who would have thought it on the Charlie
One thing I want to point out is this
In my original message to you Adam
I never mentioned using the Lord's name and vein
I didn't say that
That was you said that
And now a few others have used the phrase as well
When I brought the topic up to you Adam
About using Jesus name and conversation
I was coming from the perspective of maintaining respect for him
You know I believe that one of the reasons you brought the lawsuit
Against that gossip brag recently was because
Two of the people you love Patricia and Christina
Were brought into it
I know that in the end it became a dispute over creative comments
And that's a good thing you pursued that
But I remember you saying that you took that tack
Because the court would probably not give much weight to the family issue
But if you remember what really got you riled
Was protecting Christina
Now I'm not saying that Jesus needs my protection
Or anyone else's
All I'm trying to do here is draw parallel for you about
Carrying for your loved ones
Now if it's okay I'd like to address the issue
Of taking the Lord's name and vein
Far more serious than just saying Jesus Christ
When something goes wrong is this
As a Christian I've taken on Jesus name
I supposedly am one who said that I am a follower of Christ
I'm identified with him
Now if I have taken his name
And then live a life that is not in line with the way he teaches
Or if I live a hypocritical life
I have taken the Lord's name and vein
Even if I never swear
For me to take the Lord's name and vein in this manner
Is way more serious than using his name inappropriately
If I were to do that habitually
One might come to the conclusion that I don't really value who he is
Or my association with him
I think that's probably where the whole thing got started
About swearing by his name
It's not so much the name
It's the relationship I supposedly profess
So to sum up
Because I love Jesus
Hearing his name used inappropriately
Is uncomfortable for me
Like if someone were to say something bad about Patricia or Christina
Well that would bother you
The commandment about taking the Lord's name and vein
Is really something that is aimed primarily
At professed believers in God
Hope this helps
Remember Jesus said
Whoever drinks the water I give him will never thirst
Indeed
The water I give him will become in him a spring of water
Welling up to eternal life
You see it doesn't matter where you're at
It doesn't matter what you've done
It doesn't matter your age, your sex, your station and life
Jesus said
Who do you say that I am?
Lifespring is about answering that question
And the question of how and why the answer can
And does affect your life today
If you want to hear more about that
Check it out at lifespringpodcast.com
Now here's a real fast PS
Adam I was watching the video you sent over the weekend
With Trinity
Think I've got some bad news for him
It looks like that star in your windshield
As most likely not repairable
It looks way too big
Why don't you take a picture of it and send it to me
Maybe with a ruler in there
So I can get it kind of an idea of the scale
Anyway, thanks Adam
Appreciate it
And source code listeners
Check it out
Lifespringpodcast.com
Steve, thank you
That's the first time anyone actually
Splane to to me
So I appreciate that
And know that I'm really trying
And there's a lot of stuff that people
Ask me to say or not to say
And they feed that back to me
I don't usually bring it out publicly
Because they usually send me an email
They don't send me an audio comment
But I understand
And so I slipped today
I'm getting better
I'm really going to try it
I understand
There's no reason
I'm just going to replace it with something else
Like
If I hit my thumb, I'll be like
Ah, profit my homet
Hello Adam
This is David from the Catholic Family podcast
At CatholicFamilyPodcast.com
I was listening to the Charlie
Cha Cha
Jimmy Chang'an
And with 360 when I heard this
Jesus
The weed is like everyone's like
Oh, that's really weird
I just wanted to tell you that I am very proud of you
Although you didn't quite catch yourself
I consider this a step in the right direction
Now I'm not going to let my kids
Listen to you of course
But maybe someday
You see
I have a dream
That one day
I will download the Jimmy Chang'an
And a clean tag will appear next to the episode
And iTunes
Yes
And on that day
Catholic Family
We'll listen to the Cha Cha together
For the first time
One in spirit
With a big man
Just wanted you to know that
All right, buddy
I'm sure many shows have been completely clean
And could have had the explicit tag removed
I just don't really remember
To be quite honest
But yeah, I'm trying
I'm really working guys
Hey back to what Steve website about
About Trinity
So the video, man
I'm amazed how many different comments
Of coming about the Trinity video
And I think I have video figured out by the way
I think I know now
How I want to use it
As a part of the Charlie Empire
The Chumpire
If you will
But here's the stuff that amazed me
An actual threat of conversation
People saying
Oh, you drive too fast
And you're holding the camera
And you're blackberry at the same time
That's dangerous
Like wow
Look at the video again
Please
Oh, there's another one
I can't believe you took the card
For that little short distance
First of all
I walk all the time
But this was a special occasion
Because it was a video shoot
For crying out loud
I caught myself again
And
It was edited
Okay
You'll see there's all kinds of edits
And G
Do you think that there were some sound mixed in there
From a Ferrari
And do you think that maybe the video was sped up
At certain points
And maybe I was at the stoplight
When I was filming the blackberry
Please look for the edits
This is how you get fooled
Time and time again
With television
And it still carries over in the podcast
One thing several people did point out
Is I do seem to be leaking some fluid
Or at least there's plenty of fluid on the floor
There where a Trinity is birthed
As in a birth
Not coming to the world birth but a boat birth
And here's the thing
I'm not sure if it's from Trinity
It's certainly because I noticed the spots myself
It's like I drove Trinity into the garage for the first time
Parked on the spot
I've never been to that spot before
And when I pulled her out
That's when I saw the junk on the floor
So it could have been there from the previous owner's automobile
Or from just years of the garage being there
I mean I don't know
But it doesn't seem to have gotten worse
And it seems to be dry
But it is really black
And I hope she ain't leaking
But we're going to green my machine
Very soon
The Pimping of Trinity
You've heard the jingle green my machine
And that will be sponsored
All under the slogan
Save the world wind valuable prizes
I have one last song I want to play for you
Folks on the side light
You're only going to catch just a little bit of it
Because the window is now really closing
And the PCH is coming up next
I asked PW to keep it open for an extra half hour today
So with the satellite folks could catch up as well
Otherwise they only get half an hour
We had such a catch up show to do
To do whoops there's my Dutch Sorry
This is pretty interesting this song
Because it just showed up on the pod save music network
And it's from a Dutch artist
At least from what I can tell
Wait a minute, first let me just wave goodbye to everybody
Pete, go ahead man
You can go ahead
You can close it up
Yeah, don't worry about it
I'll be back with you folks tomorrow on this series stars 102
So there's a record company
I'm not going to tell you who
Because I'm not quite sure what I can say or not
There's a record company who is working with this artist
I guess they paid for the recording of this artist
And the mixing and they are planning on releasing it
But now what they're doing is they won the releasing on the pod save music network first
And they were already very excited about getting a couple of spins
Then of course that's how it works
So with your independent artist or record company
It's still exciting to see you get in pod play
And my feeling is that they're using it as a testing ground
To see if it'll catch on or not
And so I said, hey, I'll play it
It's not one of my favorite songs
But it's shoot just for the experimental loan
It's worth playing
And I shot back an email which I haven't heard back from you
And I said, hey, when we open up commerce on the PMN
Here's the big question
Will you be selling it as well?
Will you sell the track for 99 cents in DRM-3
MP3
Here's Adam and Minky
A blind girl
From the pod save music network
I look beside me
And I see you notice me
I look at you
And I see you smiling back at me
You pull me closer
We don't wait out to speak
Yeah
And for the first time
I feel what you really need to me
I'm a partner
Walking
I look at pictures
And see the life you've been living
Hey, I'm jealous
You know I should've been a part of it
Still I'm happy
With the ways we can go in
You show me feelings
I'm never new you had before
I want to find you
I want to pay you
Well
I know you were engaged
Me too
Well
I want to see you
And I don't care
So I can look at you
Yeah
You
You wanna be, if I wanna be
You want to marry to me
You
He said in my bag
I would SME
And I'm on the way you are
And just let me turn your back on me
I'll feel the anger building up inside the day I'm right
And for the first time I see what I really mean to you
Oh my dear, you won't give me a chance
Not knowing where it is made to go
I want to sleep tonight, I don't dare
It's why I'm here to ask you
You're the best I want to be
You are letting me
I'll feel the anger building up inside the day I'm right
You're the best I want to be
You are livres I can't see if I'm ready
I want to hear a long time
Make sure all members get some help
So get a guide with you, come on with me now
One of you, I need to be
Please let me let it be
I'm not the one
You're the good one
You're the very same imagination
Keep feeling my baby days
And I love them day
I want to be on a real way
I need to be on me to be when you go
You know what?
I take it back
I do like that
Adam and Minky
Blime Girls, the title you could find on the Podsit Music Network or the links in the show notes
You could find it directly
Yeah, from the Netherlands, had a little bit of a new vibe to it if you know what I mean
Hey, okay, I feel caught up, I hope you guys are too
And we didn't run exceptionally long, just about 55 minutes
Tomorrow will be back, Golden Ticket Day everybody, make sure you download and listen
Another Pod Show Podcast
Stick it in your ear
Get this Podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance Podcast of
Liberty Network from Podjo and limelight networks
I love it