This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
The show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy.
Delta Sierra Charlie, 432.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic.
It's now curry.
Those mornings.
Start off nice gym ass.
Baby.
It's not a right.
You should say it now.
All the things that you know.
I want to do.
Oh.
I want to be there.
I don't feel new.
You feel me.
And tonight,
You gonna be my baby.
Oh.
I'm telling you that I feel new.
And you telling me that you love me too.
But I need more than you can prove.
I need to know the money.
All the time.
You should know that I'm flying into the future.
And tonight,
You gonna be my baby.
And you'll lose my money.
You'll secure me.
But I need more than you can prove.
And tonight,
You'll lose my money.
You're a race baby.
When the close hurt don't come,
Don't go all the only you'll be blind.
I know you'll rewind me.
But you thought so.
Baby.
Without you.
Free me.
If I'm telling you that I feel new.
And you turn into the piano to
But I think more than you're in trouble
But I hope to know you love me
All the time
You should know that I like your heart, baby
And I love the light, tell me
And you wish for me like you as a child, baby
And you want a bottle, baby
Love me
And you wish for me like you as a child, baby
not work. It's been one of those mornings, my friends. Six o'clock came too early today.
Haven't really had this kind of an awakening since, uh, since I got here for this trip.
Oh, man. So tired. Sometimes I feel like I'm in, uh, in my own little private big brother reality show.
Yeah.
Walked away from his family.
You. Okay. I thought there was kind of a cool tune. I had that, uh, in my playlist on the podcast music network for, um, I don't know.
Like a week now or something every single day. And I thought, oh, maybe we should play it today. Now, but today is the right day.
We're up a kind of late last night, deep bugging.
Uh, this is one of those things. Um, you when you get sporadic reports from around the world saying that a certain page,
in this case, I'm podger plus the my page for some people was loading really, really slowly. And none of us could see it.
Uh, I couldn't, I hadn't seen it in, uh, at the cottage. I hadn't seen it here at the condo.
Obviously not at the office. And then last night, finally Andrew Grummit had it at home.
So then we got in touch with Jersey Joe out on the east coast. And, uh, we basically were working with people around the globe.
And, uh, I think we, we got to the bottom of the problem. I had to cut out at a certain point. I just couldn't stand in my feet.
Um, and I don't think the, uh, the problem has been resolved as of this morning. We said in senior email saying as much, but, uh, this is, uh, that's one of these things.
You know, it's, uh, servers are, uh, interesting animals. As are the people who maintain them, by the way.
Jersey Joe, how you doing? Yeah. So a little bit tired. Yes, they were at a great day at Pod Show HQ, uh, took, uh, the, uh, engineering staff out to lunch.
Got to know each other a little bit better. So many people have come in so quickly. And we, you know, eventually,
we're sitting at the table like 15 people, um, and all very diverse backgrounds. Some of them have
known each other from previous, uh, work experience, uh, but it was just really good to get inside everybody's head.
And, uh, really, it was an opportunity to lay it all out on the table and just say, okay, how do you think we're doing?
Um, and it was a cleansing man. It felt good. Really did learn to shit load yesterday. Really did.
Here's an example. I was talking to sod, uh, who, uh, to something. I don't know if, I don't know if
you'd listen to the daily source code. Um, he's our search specialist. And, uh, who also has a very
interesting background, which, of course, is not searched. But it's what really interesting is what
it's been doing for the, I guess the past two, two or three years. And so we're talking about,
uh, the show, and he said, you know, you know how I know when to, oh, it's actually does listen. He says,
you know how I know when to go and listen to a show. Um, because this, this is what it was about.
It was about the show notes. And you noticed yesterday, as I said, I changed, uh, the way I'm doing
show notes. So I'm not giving you a complete rundown with time codes. And my personal feeling is if you
want to listen to this show, you listen to the show. You know, if you just want to listen to the
little bits, then someone else is going to have to extract that and pass it along to you. That's fine.
That, to me, that's, uh, that's perfectly. In fact, it's fantastic. But I don't want to,
you know, this isn't, this is my painting. This is my part. You know, if you don't like it,
don't listen to it. Uh, if you don't like what you're hearing fast forward, but I just don't feel
right about giving you, uh, hooks deep into the program. I just, my personal feeling, you know,
anyone can do whatever they want. And so I'm, I'm rethinking what show notes should be. And,
and quite honestly, after I talked to Sada, then he said, you know, um, what I'll do is, uh,
I'll read through the comments. I thought that was interesting. He says if there's a lot of
comments and, um, and if people are talking about an interesting topic that was discussed in the show,
then I'll listen to the show, um, and I was like, wow, what a one-of-mind blower that is. Of course,
that makes so much sense. So immediately we said about, um, discussing how to, how to weigh indexing
of comments that are associated with the show, which, of course, in Podio plus is great because
it actually is attached to the episode. Uh, so, so we can do that kind of stuff. And then, uh,
and then, then my head just started spinning about all the different things we can do with the context
of, uh, of comments. Um, so leave a comment to daily source code.com. You know what, and, and,
in this, in almost three weeks now that I've been out here, I have not fulfilled on my, uh,
upon my obligation. I feel so shitty. I have not gone to see little man, the movie. And I was talking
to Ron's son, um, two days ago. Was it Sunday? And we had brunch, Augie. And he, he was telling me,
he would, he wanted to go again. He wanted to go with me to see the movie and can. That's how much
he liked it. And the last thing that I would be perfect to get Augie on to do a review. But, uh,
I don't think, uh, I know, I know he's not up this early. So maybe Friday show, when I'm back in the
cottage, um, then we'll have a little better time to different, so I'll be able to give him a call.
I shoot that may not work either. I don't know. He says it's really, really good. So I do
intend on going. Um, and again, this is, uh, you know, the reason why I have to go to the movie
theaters because, uh, they really want to advertise the movie on the daily source code. And I said,
send me a DVD and they said, well, we can't do that because, you know, if piracy, as it
thanks for the trust. But we predicted it, Patricia and I predicted it would be a summer blockbuster.
So that definitely came true. It's a way in brothers. You know, you can almost expect a good
silly laugh from them. And of course, I'd like to be properly medicated when I go. But I'm going
to go see it. I think I'll take Christina for sure. Turning on the TV in the past two days, all I see
on television. Of course, this is summer, right? And the summertime, um, it's all reruns and
not all reruns with most of it is. And, um, it's all about Mel. That's right. Mel Gibson,
his career is over. The superstar has fallen. It's like, geez, I can't believe the crap that
they're talking. So, you know, look, first of all, of course, you shouldn't drive them to the influence
of alcohol. And, you know, maybe he yelled at the officer and you know, maybe it was,
maybe it was inappropriate what he said. But, you know, for to say, his career is, and this is
very consistent. You know, his career is on the brain, gets teetering and maybe he does have a real
problem with alcohol. You know, just, uh, it's just people are just jumping on this with joy almost.
It reminds me a lot of the internet, by the way. If anyone fucks up for for any reason or even
looks like they've fucked up, people jump on it. This has led me to the conclusion that whenever
you have, how should I put it? Whenever there's no risk of the person you're talking about,
punching you in the face, particularly when, um, you're separated by a series of tubes,
known as the internet, and there's almost complete anonymity. And even if they know who you are,
still, you know, you could be separated by thousands of miles of distance. People will say
the darnedest things about you. They really will. And she don't have to be Mel Gibson who messes up
and then all these jackasses on television are just taking the Mickey out of you all the time. It can be
anybody. Uh, it'll be interesting to see as we move forward in the proverbial 15 minutes of fame
for everybody. How many people really like being the center of attention anywhere? It's just, it's,
it's so easy for people to take shots. This is what happens. You know, I see this, we were talking
about this yesterday as well, that I've, I've yet to see a mailing list or, um, anywhere where people
can be a forum, you know, anywhere where people can basically collaborate, ever end in anything good,
or have an indefinite life cycle at the end of the day. People start disagreeing and, and then the
flame war start and then the, the, the, the signal to noise ratio of that particular channel of
information just becomes crap. You know, and it is. It's human nature. I think it's, it's, that's
is why we're at war all over the fucking place. It's the same thing. I guess humans just don't have
their shit together yet. And all these hundreds of millions of years and we still haven't really
figured it out. In our Troy needs an iPod contest for those of you who have been participating,
what I've been looking for is, um, an even better domain name telling me why you deserve an
iPod. Troy, Rutter, of course, started this off with Troy needs an iPod.com. And he actually on
that site, he had started collecting money for the iPod that he needs, um, and yesterday I said,
because he kicked off the whole thing and I felt kind of bad. I said that would send him an iPod.
And, uh, he sent back a note and said, for those wondering about the $57 I collected, uh,
through Troy needs an iPod.com. I'm going to go ahead and donate it to the blank children's hospital
in Des Moines, Iowa. I know, keep the donation page up until yesterday, of course. So now it's down.
Good. Troy, that's very cool, dude. And by, I think Friday will choose the winner. Of course,
part of the requirement is that the domain name. I don't care if you register it with GoDaddy. You're
not using checkout code DSC3, which gives you the domain name for $6.95 for an entire year.
Shoot. I should get myself a Boeing for that one.
I don't care if you register with GoDaddy, but you do have to register it. I mean,
come on. It's got to actually end part of the whole joke is if it resolves to something.
So make sure you do if you want to be eligible, uh, for, uh, for the drawing, for the announcement
of the winner on Friday. A couple of voicemails that came in that I should share with you.
The number, of course, is a new jersey, which will work best for you Skypeers plus 201 6565657
or in London, O2076813753. Um, it was a little party in, uh, second life the other day. I think
got some calls regarding that. Let's see here. Now Adam and Britney,
Mason, if you're listening, it's going then just so, so. Okay. So Britney, of course,
kind of runs the pod show island in second life, but has, has built her own, uh, pod show plus page.
It Britney Mason, our pod show dot com. This is what Go name is talking about.
The second life again. It is Mike Turner, real life name. I've just checked out your page. Britney,
looks all right to me. We have pod show page. Britney Mason dot pot show dot com.
But I'm not so long to rise growing there. Um, so there's a, just looking to see the shows you
big. And there's one who's been digging you for something like 40 shows, 75 digs, and quite a few
in your, uh, underrised air. Um, so it's anyway, I'm off the bed now. I'll pick on second life
all night. Yeah. Um, uh, just me. Oh, by the way, I forgot saying last week's comment.
I'm a scruncher, not a soldier. Bye. All right. I'm sorry. If you're scruncher, you can't be on the show
anymore. It's officially banned. Yeah. It's kind of what I like about, uh, about those personal pages
is that you, you don't have to be a podcaster and you can still promote your favorite shows. And
there's a lot of stuff in there that works. And the people like Britney definitely latch on to that.
Hi, then it's mini Paul from the UK, uh, although I'm not calling for the UK. I'm currently on
holiday in North America, driving around my little Honda, and uh, this is into DSC 427. And I was
hearing your comments by getting all spam, uh, at your email, Adam at curry.com. I wanted, uh,
when I first started mini Paul.co.uk, and I had a mail to link set up there, and I was getting a
head of a lot of spam. And, uh, I read an article that we said that if you have a website, it's best
to have your contact email address as a picture. So you just have a picture file on the home page,
there, rather than a mail to link. And then the web pool is can't find your email address, because
I'll see they can't read pictures. And it worked really well, and it reduced my spam by hell of a lot.
And, uh, almost none now, actually. And so I hope that one helps you out, maybe you could try
that out as a one suggestion and get you with a spam. And I can't have a good work with baby source code.
And I'll talk to you again soon. Bye, bye. You know, actually, I think I discovered something
really cool about, you know, I had all these problems. Thank you, by the way, for, I'm quite aware
of you. The more your email addresses out there. And of course, mine is all over the place. And I've
had curry dot com for, uh, krikey. How many years have I had curry dot com 15 years? No, that's too long.
That's too long. Maybe 12 years, something like that. 93, 13 years. Yeah, probably, probably about 13 years.
Um, your email addresses out there. Your domain name is out there. It gets on all the lists.
Particularly if it's anywhere that a web crawler can get to, you're absolutely right. That's a great way.
There are a lot of people who will say, you know, Adam at 80 curry dot com. That's what I put down
because a lot of crawlers are looking for the, uh, the ad sign to use that. Ah, another email address. I can spam.
Who knows, maybe his wife will want to buy pills from me. Um, oh, man. I'm so fried.
I wasn't going to say. Oh, yeah. So I think I've actually discovered something cool. If, if you,
actually shut off, you bounce email from the domain name long enough. I guess what, uh, even these
spammers are are kind of sophisticated. Eventually, they just say, fuck it. This is no good. We're
going to remove that one from the list because we're not getting any, uh, we're getting bounces from it.
And yeah, so it screws up your email communications for a little while, but I don't know if I actually missed anything.
What I, what I don't know, it doesn't hurt me. And the spam has reduced almost to zero. It really has.
So I have to say, you know, a surefire way to absolutely get rid of the spammers is just a
bounce message is back out. And for, well, you know, of course, everyone gets the bounces. But if you can do that
for a week, if you can do it for two weeks, it's even better because man, it really does work.
Hey, Adam, jump from the Netherlands calling this morning. I drove to the office,
listening to the Charlie of Friday edition. And you mentioned the podcast of Mark Yosimoto,
Nenkov called, where the hell is my fucking latte or where's my fucking latte? And been
listening to the, say, the cause of hell way for two weeks now, and it awesome. So the first thing I did,
what I got into the office, start up the pod show and looking for the new
Mark Yosimoto podcast. And there was no link in your show notes. So
try it again through the search module of pod show and there it was. So no problem at all.
Got it and download it and go and listen to it and hope it's as good as the particular
hotel way because that show rocks. Take care. I'm a folder. Yes, of course. Of course you are.
Yeah, the search is working. That part works pretty well. I think you'll enjoy it.
And I was amazed to find that there are already 10 episodes of that show out there. And yeah,
I'll put a, I'll put a link in the show notes today. So you can find it easily. But yeah,
this search does does work. I think actually we're going to start putting that show on on
serious as well. In fact, it may even be today because as I'm looking at the lineup for those of
you listening to to this podcast on this serious stars 102, of course I do recommend you go to
daily source code.com so you can listen to the full shows because you only get about half an hour of
me. Of course, that may be more than enough for you. We have a special 30 minute segment from
Pod Show LA coming up right after the daily source code. And I believe today, where's my
fucking latte? It might be one of the shows. After that dawn and Drew, then we're going to bring
you the rumor girls. Very popular video podcast, which translates beautifully to audio. And then
check this out, man. Peter, you've got to send me more information. So between eight and nine tonight,
we have the fantastic podcast known as the rotating guest slot. After that, it's a use radio and
Scott Siggler will wrap it up. He's on all this week between 930 and 10. If you've never heard
Scott Siggler and his pateo books, you've got to listen tonight between 930 and 10. That's Eastern
time right here on serious stars 102. You got about, was it a couple more minutes with you guys?
Ah, you know what? Just time enough.
Name in the band after he's cop. Nice to know. Roger. So good to hear from you. What are you
doing, man? You don't call it off and enough. Yeah. Today is MTV's 25th birthday. And you've
probably read more stories about the fact that MTV is not doing anything to celebrate it,
then you've actually heard stories. So I figured that I could take 10 or 15 minutes and give you
a couple of stories. White Snake is a good start, Roger. Actually, I did hang out a little bit
with white snake. Less because of David Coverdale and more because of Tony Katana,
I have to be honest. I'm also a Adrian Vanderberg, a friend of mine from Holland, who Patricia
also had known for many, many years. When they were at the height of their heyday, he was in the band.
And he's a fine, fine Dutch guitarist. He still does all kinds of music stuff.
Well, I could share what kind of music stuff, but I'll find that out. And so whenever they went
town, we'd hook up or Patricia now would go see the concert. And when he hooked up with Tony
Katana, that was kind of cool, you know, because, you know, I could look at Tony Katana all night.
And at one point, I don't know if this is a cool story, it's kind of sad. You know, they've been
separated. I think they're married really only in the last couple of years. And then she went on
to date apparently, O.J. Simpson. Now she's married to a baseball player. I think she also
didn't she also go out with one of the guys and rat? So, you know, Tony's been around for sure.
But at their wedding, which we were invited to, when we went to, it was at the four seasons in Los
Angeles. It was very expensive, very, you know, just a perfect wedding. But after everything, the
reception, at the ceremony, we just went to the reception, we didn't go to the actual ceremony.
Tony got pretty hammered. And I really got to tell you, and Patricia will back me up on this.
She was sending off all kinds of weird signals towards the two of us. I mean, you know, like in
the sexual sense. And that was really weird. We attributed it to alcohol, of course,
but it just felt very uncomfortable. It always felt she was a bit skanky, honestly.
I don't know, have any other white snake stories? Actually, I don't have any other. If Patricia
were here, we talked about the time that we went out with Rudy Sarzo and his wife, the drummer.
And we went to a movie. This again was in Los Angeles. And it was just like a hang. He's like,
hey, you want to go to the movie? Yeah, we'll go hang out in the movies. And Patricia,
remembers going into the movie theater, doesn't remember anything because she fell asleep.
It fell fast asleep. Ah, I've only she were here, then I could, uh, I could really hammer
into her about how she falls asleep at all. The all movies we ever go to, at least all the
ones that I like going to. I think it was probably total recall or something. Anyway, as I said,
Pacific Coast Hellways up next for those of you checking us out on serious stars 102.
And don't forget that rotating guest lot show. You, you do not want to miss that. It's coming
up just a bit later. And we'll be on all this week, um, except actually I will be on every single
day this week, um, bringing you the best of, uh, of the pod show on serious. Have a good one, everybody.
Now for those of you still sticking around. Let me just look, I wrote down a couple, uh, a couple
of different things I was going to talk about some MTV stories. Uh, what should we do? Uh,
another, uh, another celebrity hitting on me this time. You like this? Uh, it was Marty Grah.
In I think it was 90 or 91, uh, MTV used to do live at Marty Grah. I think this was the second year
they'd done it. And I have to say that was a fantastic time to have basically a police escort
24 hours a day because, you know, there was no other way you could get through the crowds if you
needed to get to the, to the, to the French quarter to do, uh, do your segments back from the hotel.
It's just no way. And, and New Orleans police really knew how to, how to take care of, uh, of logistics,
particularly in big crowds, just amazing how much patience they have and, and, and how well it
will always work. So we were doing, I think it was three days of Marty Grah. And you can imagine that
basically everybody is partying. You're not just the people around us, but the artists who came
down, uh, the other celebrities who were brought on to the show, uh, we were all partying the
camera. People were partying. Everyone was partying. It was just one big party. And this is actually
the predecessor to all those spring break shows. I think it, I think someone just caught on
saying, you know what? Let's just figure out what we can go party and then we'll put a budget together.
So we can, uh, party. Oh, yeah. And we'll also do some television. Um, but it was during that
particular, on by the way, you know, Patricia was really into the whole show as your tits thing.
And so she was doing that from the balcony and, uh, and quite honestly, there was this, uh,
she has some nice ones to show, you know, the guys. Uh, but then, um, Matt Dylan started hating on me.
And so Patricia had gone to bed back to the hotel when I had a couple more segments to do. And then
Matt Dylan and, and I can't remember, there was some other, I don't know, I think she was an
actress. She had, gosh, my brain is so fraught. I wish I could remember. He was like, yeah, you know,
the three of us should hook up with this other actress. I'm like, dude, I don't think so.
Want another one? How about the Michael Jackson weekend? I think I've told this story before.
But, um, and by the way, I have no, uh, crazy, uh, stories about, uh, massive drinking and drug abuse.
I've, I've never really seen that at MTV. Really, never in, in the almost eight years that I
worked there, never really saw any massive party and going on at any of the offices or studios.
Yes, some of the executives, but they weren't all different building. And they always did a kind of
quietly. So Michael Jackson was, uh, slated to appear on the video music awards. And, you know,
the music business, of course, the traditional mainstream music business. Everything's, uh,
part of a deal or a setup. Nothing wrong with it, by the way. But when you get Michael Jackson on the
video music awards, you know you're going to have to do something in return. And that's something,
uh, consisted of two parts. One was the Michael Jackson weekend. And yeah, I can't remember which
video was a world premiering or planetary premiering, remember those. But, you know, we, of course,
MTV committed to doing a Michael Jackson weekend, which basically means four times an hour,
maybe five times an hour you would see a Michael Jackson video. And this, of course, is in hours
when every single, uh, when everything set the commercials was a music video. And he also wanted
it his own award. And, uh, and it had to be given to him, uh, the first time round. And so what was
concocted was the Michael Jackson video Vanguard of the Year award. And it's not just the
video Vanguard award. It was, I don't know if they, uh, they probably don't say that anymore. They
may not even give the award out anymore. But that was the point a new award category was to be created
called the video Vanguard, the, sorry, the Michael Jackson video Vanguard award. Kind of like the,
the Heisman trophy. Yeah. Um, and, and part of that, and that was interesting is that I had to
give it to him. And this was, um, this was 1990 Patricia was very, very pregnant. And I mean,
she was about ready to pop. And I'm like, dude, I'm not going to fly to Los Angeles. I don't give
a fuck if it's Michael Jackson. I'm not going, you know, I can't leave my wife here alone. And even
though we knew she had two weeks, you know, anything could happen. So, um, MTV just kept begging.
This is when they'd still beg me to do shit before they started to just like me,
because of my attitude. And finally, I said, look, you fly my mother-in-law over first class.
I'll go to Los Angeles. I'll do one day. I'll come back on the red eye. I'd, you know, and they
did understand in all honesty. Um, so they finally complied and, um, flew to LA with Tom
Freston, uh, who now, of course, is, uh, head of Viacom. Yeah, he was head of MTV networks at the time.
He's a partier, by the way. And, um, we show up at the MJJ Studios, uh, Michael Jackson's
own studio. And it was a very, very weird vibe, you know, come in and I swear to God, there must have been
there must have been eight or nine kids running around. And they had their pretty young, um, and it
got even more interesting because, uh, how he Mandel was, was there kind of like in the lounge area.
And he was just kind of like hanging out, you know, and he, and he was doing the Bobby, Bobby's
world voices, and these kids were, it was, it was a very bizarre scene just in general.
And so, uh, you know, all right, let's, uh, let's do the, uh, let's do the award and, uh, you know,
my, I was all Michael kind of roaming around and it was very, very soft spoken and you said,
hi, he's not a small guy, by the way. He's got to be about six feet tall, close to it. Maybe
even a little over, it's quite tall, slender. Um, so I have the award and, you know, we get ready for the,
for a little video segment that we're going to do. And of course, a photographer is there.
And, uh, you know, so we're kind of lining up the three of us, Michael in the middle,
meet the left, Tom Freston to the right. And this is one guy who's only job at was was to Windex,
Michael's shiny pants. I think they were latex or they were obviously more leather, but some kind of
synthetic material. And so it, every, every five minutes. Rubbing it down. Okay, we're ready,
everything shiny, we're all good to go. And, uh, we're standing next to each other and I start and
then all of a sudden, I can see Michael, like kind of motion over to his guy and his guy comes over and
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Guy leaves, you know, and we're all waiting like what the
fuck was what, what is this all about? Guy comes back with an apple crate and he puts it down
to the Michael can stand on the apple crate. So he is literally seven feet tall. I have a picture
somewhere. It's been on, it's, I've published it on the internet a couple of times. I'll see if, uh,
actually it might even be on my flicker account. And you'll see Michael Jackson literally stands,
you know, four, five inches taller than I am, because he existed on standing on the apple crate.
All right, I have no more. Yeah, I do have more. Should I do the, um, you know what, I'll keep the,
the Sebastian Bach from Skid Row, uh, Red Square, Moscow Music Peace Festival. I think I'll keep that
one for, uh, for another day. What I will bestow upon you, however, is one of the finalists for
our EarthLink, uh, ad challenge. This is where, uh, you get to win valuable cash prizes for coming up
with the best advertising for EarthLink. Visit adchallenge.podshow.com to hear all of the entries.
Here's one of the finalists. So I believe it's already one $250, but uh, or $200, but it's vying for
the grand prize.
You know what? If that were actually one of the finalists, I would be amazed.
That's another song I wanted to play for. Hey, everyone. This is Eugene tomorrow. My question
for you is this. How long have you been with your internet service provider? How many times have
you switched? My internet service provider is EarthLink, and I have been with them as a subscriber
since April 17, 1998. Now, that's a long time before anyone had ever heard of iPods or podcasting
or even cable or DSL broadband. For over eight years now, I have relied on EarthLink for internet
connectivity and spam for email, and they have never let me down. If you are tired of bad
service, inconsistent connectivity, constantly rising prices and email accounts full of spam,
come on over where I am, EarthLink.net. Go to www.EarthLink.net, and you can get a great deal on
internet service. Yeah, you know, as songs kind of go, it was pilot error, and I do apologize,
but this is a song that I found on the pod save music now, where I can shoot since you've already
heard it. Why don't we just play it? It's an instrumental at something different for the Charlie.
It's a jazz track on the Charlie. Monica Herbsick. Just something fun.
Enjoy.
So, jazz on the Charlie. True American art form. And let me make a prediction.
Jazz Swing. It's coming back. I guarantee you. You know how I know it's coming back,
because you can feel it. You can feel it all over the pod save music.network at music.podshow.com.
I kind of feel like I've done it. You guys have a disservice. I've been so
mellow and tired this morning. I hope you don't mind. I hope you're able to sit through this,
particularly because the show notes didn't tell you about that. I'll think up some other
headline. I'll be back tomorrow. I promise I guess some sleeping will make my page work. Take
everybody. Oh, sometimes I forget that. Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network
from podshow and limelight networks. I love it.