This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie, 3901.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I never met someone who hit a guy in the aisle like the way she came to me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And my best defense could've told that she was looking back at me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I never think everything will be.
I never think all I'm so sweet.
I think it better to new kids than just me and her.
And a two-car watch.
That she all knew we'll let you laugh at you.
Easy payment so much out.
Is that another look and did you mean what you meant when I thought that you meant indefinitely?
Yeah, yeah.
And I can't figure out why it is that I know I'm sitting next to her.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I never think everything will be.
I never think all I'm so sweet.
I think it better to new kids than just me and her.
And a two-car watch.
Magic, I knew, yeah, magic, magic.
It's you made it time to die.
Whoa.
Can't you find her?
Stand one down if you tell me she's me.
Whoa.
If you tell me she's me.
Thanks for the drink, but my boyfriend is right over there.
I think it better to new kids than just me and her.
And a two-car watch.
Magic, I knew, magic, magic, magic.
It's you made it time to die.
Yeah, yeah.
I think it better to new kids than just me and her.
And a two-car watch.
Magic, I knew, magic, magic, magic.
It's you made it time to die.
Whoa.
Magic, I knew, magic, magic, magic.
How American is that?
Cool water's ban, two-car garage.
Man, that's loud.
Go.
Okay, there you go.
From the pod to the music network, of course.
At music.com, every single song we play on the Carlos.
It's now become the Carlos, by the way.
Yeah.
From daily source code to DSC, you dealt with Shira to Charlie to Carlos.
Why Carlos?
Because we have the Delta Shira Charlie.
Yes.
See.
I mean.
Every song that's played on daily source code becomes available for sale on the pod-sake music network.
As we start to ramp that up and roll it out, of course, after we get permission from the artist.
So sometimes it takes a day or two longer than we like, but it's just an email thing.
And of course, you'll be able to, they've got a whole bunch of songs on the pod-sake music network.
What do you think?
You like that?
Yeah.
I like the bit.
I like the bit where the grill goes.
Thanks for the drink, but my voice sounds.
I love the cowbell on it.
Oh, that's huge.
Oh, my gosh.
Ladies and gentlemen, the lovely lady Patricia joins us for the Friday.
This is my share, because I just did some vacuuming.
I like it.
It's very sexy when you stick it up like that.
Oh, really?
Well, it's kind of bird nesty, but the whole idea of it.
I think that's I started to sweat.
First fire deer, you don't sweat.
You don't sweat.
No, I don't sweat.
I don't like it.
Say it with me now.
I'm a lady.
I don't sweat.
I don't sweat a lot.
Are you kidding?
You know, as big squads go, you sweat much less.
That's true.
Yeah.
What is that?
That's my dad again.
What's he doing?
He's putting away the vacuum cleaner blood.
Your parents are so sweet.
Yeah, of course.
They really are.
Kidding they help.
You mean your dad comes in here.
And after the first day, he's like, I'm bored.
I need something to do.
Give me something to fix.
He can't stay down.
His body is meaningless.
He just can't, you know, mean something.
He completely rearranged Christina's room yesterday.
He did the bed, you know, took stuff off.
What stuff in different places, completely redid her room.
Today they're both vacuum.
He's vacuuming.
Yeah, put the bed in another direction.
Yes.
She didn't have much space.
Let me just let you know.
Excuse my, my lisping.
What's wrong?
Because I don't have tea sounds.
So hot baby to stop with the no tea talk.
I love it very much.
No.
But you just had, well, we talked about that.
You had a major dental work done.
You know, we have to make sure we repeat everything.
Well, I do have a piece of plastic, but that's even harder.
Yeah, with others, just general fake things.
It's only on the back molar.
So you don't really see it.
You just called it your Halloween teeth.
Really?
It's more you Halloween teeth.
You're fucking fucking very much.
I actually fall down when I speak.
So that's nice.
Very charming.
So we're going on our trip tomorrow.
Yeah.
We'll be meeting lots of important people and luminance.
Oh, that's nice with a piece of fur.
Yes.
You're going to be my trophy.
You're supposed to be my trophy wife.
And I can just see you know.
How come?
Who's that?
He's black.
Right.
Anyway, what I was going to say is that I'm going to ask the Jeff Smith to do some kind of
Jingle or announcement thing for you.
Could you just give that door a whack on?
I think it's it's it's the it's the it is storming here yeah.
No, I can't.
The show of course is coming to you for oh there she goes she's yes closed on.
The studio is secure.
Yeah, no it's coming.
And everything is, as we like to say.
Windy.
Stormy with the.
Where my love and I, we're together.
Yeah.
Everyone is at home going like, yeah, keep saying it, keep saying it.
So I'm going to do it.
So I'm happy to have you on the show as usual.
And everyone else is, you're getting fan mail and comments.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, check this one out.
Listen to this.
Adam, hi.
I thought to send you a quick audio comment for the Charlie.
Of course, this is your boyfriend podcast part, right?
OK.
Big brother.
It's just started over in the UK.
And it's a huge hit over here.
If you're anything like me, I absolutely cannot abide watching it.
It's really hate it.
Oh, I love it.
Well, actually, we always hated it.
Because in Holland, we didn't watch.
Well, no, that's not true.
The first season, because I was actually involved with that.
We were doing some of the bandwidth for the data market.
Yeah, but I didn't like it.
It's stupid.
It was originally called Golden Cage.
And interestingly enough, no, you were there from the beginning.
Yeah.
OK.
Let's listen to the podcast.
And I sort of love to hate it.
My wife's so absolutely loves it.
And good mates.
My poor pinfield from the calm cast doesn't know whether it loves it or hate it.
Well, anyway, we hate some of my idea.
And we thought we would do the completely unofficial big brother podcast.
And it's had some great comments.
We recorded it last night.
Got it straight up.
And there's some comments on the blog there.
You can find it at podcast.pl.com.
And just one other thing.
Just bought some equipment recently.
And I am so chuffed with it.
Hang on.
I'll give you a clue.
This podcast is produced with the last episode.
Yeah.
It's a great piece of equipment.
Really, really plays with it.
And that's just belted out through my entire office.
Oh, dear.
OK.
Well, anyway, podcast pool that come for the completely unofficial big brother podcast,
all the best.
Bye-bye, man.
So I listen to this.
It's funny.
It's for adults who actually are quite successful professionals.
Yeah.
Sitting, you know, like lawyers.
Sitting around and talking about all these different people.
Exactly the way you and I would do that.
I OK.
Do you want me to set you up so you can hear it or you're not interested?
Well, how can it be like big brother?
No, it's not.
No, it's about big brother.
No, no, no, no, no.
So after the show airs, then they sit down and they talk about it.
Oh, they were talking.
Yeah, yeah.
About the people.
Well, let's first mention a little bit who were in there.
So we know what it's all about.
So yesterday, and I'm a little bit pissed because I know y'all love me, but no.
Well, no one called me.
I'm up here.
You want my business?
No, I was not.
Absolutely not.
About 10 minutes of our 10 minutes at the end of the program.
I'm in second life.
You come up and say, oh, you won't believe what you missed.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, I thought you knew.
No.
Yeah.
OK. Well, I didn't know you were interested actually because you're
Well, I definitely won't.
I didn't think you had a patient for it.
So we were, they introduced themselves.
So they went into the house yesterday.
It's going to be a long hot summer of broth.
Just give me a broth of broth.
Just give me, don't go through all 10 of them.
I'm not that interested.
No, no, but give me the ones you like.
You're pigs.
Patricia's pigs.
I love, of course, the homosexuals.
I mean, you need a good homosexual in there.
Good gay guy.
So do they have a good gay guy?
So I have a couple of nice gay guys.
They have one there.
That's necessary.
Yeah, but no.
No, you know that at end of all, they're actually sitting there and they have
to be eating and it's like, OK, what are we going to do?
What we need some good gay guys in there?
I think even, you know, these people were thinking about it.
Because what's life without gay people?
Nothing.
So Shabbas.
It's a dirty service.
That's the pocket poof.
Never worked in his life.
But has never found love.
So that's going to be very interesting.
If you're locked up.
Found love on.
Then there's two ways.
Also, very interesting is done.
And don hates people.
Oh, that's good.
You're in the right place.
She hates people.
Show me a picture of Don.
Show me what she looks like.
Yeah.
But she has a wig on.
She does not really.
No wonder.
But she doesn't.
She has a wig on.
She's a complainer.
And she hates people.
She doesn't want to communicate it or nothing.
Then.
Very funny.
Oh, then there is.
Super, super, super gay guy.
Oh, there's not just one.
You have a super funny gay guy and super gay guy.
Super, super gay guy.
I think I saw him in the paper.
I thought he's going to be trouble.
He's gone to be trouble.
That's Richard.
Uh-huh.
He even had it Canadian.
And he's a muscle man.
Uh-huh.
And he talks about sex all the time.
He loves it.
And he says, I'm going to show them.
Every man in the house.
I'm going to show them.
What's what, you know, what sex means.
So, and then there is a gorgeous guy, Mickey, who is a...
Are you think he's gorgeous?
Well, I don't think so, but...
Why'd you say that?
Well, that's what the girls say.
And that's what the presenter is.
You know, but I want to picture a pie approval.
He's not bad, Luke.
He's on the list.
But, you know, you write, you see right away that he likes himself.
Oh, Luke.
So, that makes him help.
Now, I don't do guys that they're like that.
Twenty years old, dislike of ugly people.
Oh, very nice.
He and that, that wig chick should get along fine together.
Give me one more.
Give me one more that you think is really good.
Then there is Leah, a divorced mom, glamour model,
with the biggest tits from Great Britain.
Mm-hmm.
She has a joke.
30 M.
She's a student.
I'm not interested.
She's not interested.
How about the Tourette's guy?
Yeah, the Tourette guy.
How is he?
They already say that he's going to win.
Really?
Yeah.
So, what was he like?
What kind of Tourette does he have?
Does he say no?
No.
I thought you saw it last night.
Well, that was a bit...
I switched it on a little bit too late.
Because we were watching some festival, you know?
Oh, man.
The Eurovision song contest.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
And my mom and dad were watching.
So, I became in from the kitchen.
And I was actually watching with them.
And then I thought, oh my god, big brother.
We gotta make sure people understand.
Let's move on from Big Brother.
We'll listen to the unofficial Big Brother podcast.
And we'll watch it too.
Yeah.
I'm interested in the Tourette's guy.
As you know, being part of the Tourette Posse.
Yeah, of course.
Can you imagine a hip-hop group, the Tourette Posse?
Fuck, motherfucker.
Fuck.
Oh, that would be great.
I don't see the picture.
Oh, you were easy.
You were easy.
So, Eurovision song contest.
If you don't know what this is, this is something
that has been going on for...
I would say, what are they?
Oh, it's beat.
Beat is the Tourette guy.
Yeah, from South London.
Well, Pete has actually has a better chance of being successful
after Big Brother, whether he wins or not,
than anyone coming out of the Eurovision song contest.
This thing has been going on for 35 years, 40 years,
maybe, huh?
Maybe even longer than that.
Yeah.
Maybe they're in their 50th year.
And the concept is...
It started as...
It was really...
I think it was a broadcast project to show...
Oh, look, we're hooking up all these countries via satellite.
Yes.
When it was a big...
I'm sorry, go ahead.
Yeah.
And David Bowie and I also...
Oh, a name just dropped.
Yeah.
We did song contest.
That was normal.
If you wanted to start...
Then you did it...
You did your song contest.
Yeah.
You wanted to be famous worldwide or something,
or European in Europe.
You had to do this.
You know, that was good for...
We're talking about 1970, something.
Well, I was 19 when I did that one.
I was 17 when I did my first...
When I was 17...
It was a very good year.
Yeah.
In Belgium.
But wait a minute.
Aren't you supposed to only perform for your own country?
Yeah.
I did for...
Always for Holland, of course.
What we doing Belgium was the whole contest.
The contest was in...
It was very famous.
Which means they won.
In high school.
It's a very famous place.
Fly over it all the time.
It's gorgeous.
Yeah.
So...
That was my first time.
I was 17 years old.
But back in those days...
What did you get selected to be?
Because this is the part that I'm trying to figure out.
They found you.
Who's there?
Famous people from the...
No.
Who is in charge of the selection for the Eurovision Song Contest?
Well, most of the time you got somebody from the TV.
A...
Well, so it's the broadcast companies that are in charge, basically.
Yeah.
So somebody from TV.
Very good.
One of the biggest...
Management from Holland.
Also, it was like an idol.
It was their judges.
Yeah, judges.
All rounded judges.
Yeah.
And records company.
Somebody, you know, director of a record company.
You know, maybe producers.
And so they would select...
Guys, a couple of six guys.
Famous...
Very important guys from Holland.
We'd say now, which is the best singer for the weekend.
I disagree.
It's not about the best singer.
It's about the best song.
I know.
Okay.
So they always thought...
No, no, no, no, no.
I believe.
Let me just correct you.
Let's just make sure we're right on this.
They select the song.
And then usually the songwriter gets involved.
Yeah.
And he helps choose who's going to sing that song.
The songwriter.
And then I was...
So what?
What do you think?
Oh, crap.
See, exactly my point.
This is...
They would say this is a very interesting and...
A very talented, talented person that could be very big.
And she said...
I think you're wrong, huh?
I'm sorry.
I think it's about the song.
Not about the performance.
You've only said in these days, I'm telling you that is one.
They would say that to you.
Why wouldn't you bring the best...
Of course, you would give the best performance.
Okay.
So when did it change?
When did they go from choosing Patricia Pi to choosing the crap that every country seems to choose?
Because nobody wants to go anymore.
Because why?
Isn't it a great exposure?
Because you loseers now.
Right.
There you go.
You're not all down from there.
After David Bowie.
Right.
Came to David Bowie, participated in the Eurovision Song Contest.
You ever hear him talking about...
I know.
I don't know.
So...
Well, that was in the Eurovision Song Contest.
No, I don't...
I was just telling you, Mom, yesterday.
That was...
That was exactly before his first release...
The Space Auditing.
For people who haven't heard that story,
Do you want to tell it again?
Because it was almost two years ago.
Well, that was actually...
When we did that music contest.
That's when you did David Bowie.
That was in Mozart.
Molta.
And...
No, I did not.
What are you saying?
No, no, no, no.
So we met there.
All these people from Germany.
I don't know where.
And then you start to talk to each other.
Because you're bored out of your skull sitting around doing nothing for a movie.
And you see already people choosing,
Oh, that's a nice person to talk to.
Or, you know, I can relate to that person.
And so you said the guy with two color eyes...
I was always...
And the white skin, he's nice to talk to.
I was always very artistic and a very rocky kind of girl.
You know, I was always a little bit different than the rest.
Ah, Han.
So you don't have to inform me of this.
I'm quite aware.
And so was he.
So that attracts right away.
Yeah.
You know?
So he was a bit of crazy.
Crazy.
So you hooked up with David?
We were a little bit friends.
Who then was not David Bowie?
No.
David Jones.
And so we had walks.
And sometimes we just had dinner together or set next to each other.
But we know when we...
He was always carrying around his guitar.
Always.
And he...
His guitar.
His music.
Yeah.
He always wants to sing.
And in these days he was just almost overflowing of, you know, all sorts of ideas.
And songs that he had in his head.
Yeah.
So yeah.
I think so.
Yeah.
So we were walking on the beach.
And he was playing again.
We sat down.
And he said, I want to play you a couple of songs.
Had you kissed at this point?
No, no, no, no, no.
I just wanted to get to the good part.
And he was...
I thought this was the good part.
I'm not kidding.
He was playing that song over and over again.
Whenever we were every time the same song.
And he was singing and strumming his guitar.
And he was singing, Graham couldn't play.
Or to me, your tone.
You have to know Patricia.
Yeah.
She was crying.
If I hit this song.
Yeah.
So this was...
He hadn't written the whole song yet.
He was writing it on the beach, basically.
Well, he just wrote it.
He just wrote that.
And then he said, don't you think I sound like John Lennon?
So I can just see, because I'm going like,
Shut the fuck up with that ground control crowd.
Said no.
I don't think so.
You know, it's one of his biggest hits ever.
Yeah.
I love that story.
He was doing it over and over and over.
And we can control the whole tune.
Every time the same thing.
I said, yeah, that's my latest.
And you thought it was shit, right?
What do you think of?
I don't know.
So that was...
So it got the Patricia endorsement.
That song contest.
We all went home again.
And then his record was released.
And it was a big hit.
Big hit.
Yeah.
Where was I?
Oh, man.
That is so funny.
Yeah.
And then there's some other stuff.
But I guess you're not interested in telling us that.
What?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Well, actually then we snogged a little bit.
And you know, like teenagers did.
Wait a minute.
Won't you guys...
In his hotel room and that Angie was at the door?
I mean, it was...
I'm listening.
Something was happening there in Malta.
And we were very nice.
This string.
Just picked on me.
And I like it.
And suddenly suddenly he said,
Oh.
My girlfriend is probably coming.
She's an American.
That's Angie.
And I didn't know that.
She said, but she wants to surprise me and come over and I thought,
Oh, okay.
Uh-huh.
That's a pity.
You know.
Because, you know, we were very...
You need a friend if you were all lonely Malta.
Yes.
So she came over.
And...
But hey, she said, yeah.
Yeah. She said, she's very cool.
So we can...
We can have a...
A three-cent.
Easy.
What's she had?
No, not at all.
And she...
And he added...
Um...
Oh, yeah.
And by the way, when she comes over,
you will see she looks like Barbara Streisand.
Uh-huh.
Compliment of all compliment.
Oh, okay.
Alrighty.
Once she came over, I thought, well, you know.
Well, alright.
Yeah.
Because when we saw David Bowie in Montro,
well, that was a long time ago.
But after that, when he came over for real,
Can't go to do this, we...
You know, we got it on again, and we did it.
And you did it?
Yeah, he's a fabulous lover.
He's a fabulous lover.
Is he better than me?
Just be honest?
Yeah, he's a fabulous lover.
Is he better than me?
Just be honest?
Yeah, he's a fabulous lover.
Is he better than me?
I remember.
No.
But I remember, Angie came in again.
Oh, damn.
Curse.
She was very jealous, and she was troubled.
She was just...
Hmm.
But indeed, the only question.
But then again, if you're married, you shouldn't do that.
You know, that your wife is coming over.
Yeah, really.
You know, in the hotel.
Uh-huh.
But then later, I heard in one of the programs that he...
Later, when he was in his marriage with Angie,
he did that a lot.
Just, you know, slept around.
Yeah, slept around.
Yeah, it was the 70s.
And he...
You could do all that shit.
He caught a record with Lulu and I heard...
He did more than just caught a record with Lulu.
And he's saying one of the programs that just aired in Ray Britain.
And she...
And he came home and he said, you fucks her.
Fuxelsing the serious stars 102.
Have a great weekend.
We'll be back on Monday.
For to hear the rest of Patricia's David Bowie story.
No.
It's a daily source code.com.
Take everybody this out.
I went to his closing PCH's next.
And we had a little bit two nights ago.
And this is actually after the show that you said to me that I don't satisfy you enough.
You forgot.
Oh, it's true.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Thank you for gotten.
Yeah, okay.
Just...
No.
Okay.
Have you forgotten that evening?
Day before yesterday.
Yes.
So speaking of the Eurovision Song Contest.
We're in bed.
And we're...
Because there's all this preamble on the BBC just doesn't...
You know, all these flashbacks and lookbacks.
And every single public broadcast in Europe is doing this now.
And they had Brotherhood of Man.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Kisses.
Join me.
Save all your kisses for me.
And of course, I'm a disjockey right.
So I go, it's a Brotherhood of Man.
Everybody in my bed.
I said, there's not the Brotherhood of Man.
No.
And I said, oh, you want to put your money where your mouth is.
Yes.
And I had to put my mouth.
Where is it?
There.
Can you tell that I won the bet?
Yes.
You did.
I was...
I thought...
I was right.
So just as a...
As a measure, just for the audience.
Are you satisfied enough today?
Is it okay?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
Oh, I'm fine.
Okay.
So just back to the Eurovision Song Contest really quickly.
Yeah.
I think that what all this proves is that democracy is mediocrity.
It's just everything that comes out of it is mediocre.
You know, it's...
It's because gone through so many committees.
And it's just...
It's lame.
It's so inspiring.
You know, girls allowed kind of group and they have sort of a...
You know, a boy group that...
Yeah.
So bad.
So...
The best part, of course, is Terry Woven, who does commentary.
Oh, fantastic.
I think he drinks like 10 pints of...
I don't know.
So...
So fun.
And we've got to comment from Holland, huh?
Oh.
Yeah, it's cool.
Dear Adam and Patricia.
This is Ray from Holland.
Adam, you know, I'm a big fan of yours.
Although I'm not in the situation to listen every day.
I really love to hear you on the Charlie, and especially the shows with Patricia.
You two really make it here to complete.
Anyway.
Last Wednesday, you were talking about all the burping and the sincere...
Actually, you blamed it on the sincere, but...
Come on, Adam.
You know better than that.
Really dear Charlie, friends.
Way back in the 80s even before the work-offing machines.
Adam hosted the radio show in Holland on Friday night with...
Do you remember this?
I remember this.
I remember the moment.
Okay.
I'll let you tell the moment after he plays the segment.
Well, I think three million listeners.
He was already doing these things on air.
It's not new.
He's just a boy with a big mouth.
Burping on air.
When it was a dream, you had an Amsterdam.
You're doing it.
I was even better with the series.
I lived in California for the years.
The war didn't end.
It was really cool.
That was the video video.
M.C.
It was the M.C.
It's the middle.
Yeah.
I don't know.
That was bad in these days.
This was 1984, I think, or 85.
There was only one popular radio station that was legal.
We both come this...
Do they do that on the BBC right now?
Burping?
Yeah.
Can Terry Burp?
I don't think that doesn't fit with Terry.
But Chris Moiles, I'm sure.
I'm sure we'd do that.
But in 84, I mean, there's just no way.
No way.
And so this was my co-host who was reading a story.
And then he couldn't find the words.
And I just...
I remember it.
I had this big gulp of coke.
And I went...
And then I immediately blamed him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because it sounded like he did it.
Yeah, and I remember I was in the car.
Because we were having a secret affair at the time, right?
I know.
I was driving to you to your house already.
You're like 180 in your poor.
When my poors, I had to park the car.
I was in shock.
I wasn't sure.
I had to park the car.
And I was thinking, did I hear that well?
God, he was burping.
I couldn't believe it because that was...
That was no...
Not done.
Not done at all.
No.
I've never...
And it was my...
The first time I heard it from...
I'm such a visionary, aren't I?
You are the first with everything.
And my boss at the time, Lex Harding, was on a boat.
Right.
But he was on a boat when he heard it.
And he almost fell overboard.
But it was called you, right?
Yeah, right in your heart.
I didn't even show you.
Yeah.
He said, dude.
The red telephone was...
Dude, not only can you not do that, but you almost got me really wet.
But that was it.
It was no problem.
Yeah.
He was a guy who understood that he had to...
I had to park the car.
Yeah.
That was awesome.
That's awesome.
But I tell you, he's back.
Roger?
Yeah?
He's back?
Yeah.
Yes.
He's back.
He found me again.
I know he's back.
He's like a couple of...
Yeah.
get me very excited. I'd like to join in too when I'm listening to you banging away,
but this is a good list. The camp has very expensive and hard to buy. You can always try your
local dairy farms, see if they've got any old ones lying around, or maybe a music shop.
I don't know. If you live in a city, maybe you don't have any farms nearby, or maybe I've
been issued with a call or they'll keep me away from livestock. Then there isn't
you away. All you need is a can of baked beans, a can of cano cano in a plate.
I can of baked beans, open them up with a can opener, and then she's been from the plate.
Then let's with a can that you can tap with a ballpoint pen, and it sounds just like a cowbell.
You can use any type of can really, not just beans. I could make the mistake though of the
human evaporated milk in a can would be or would be evaporated. Fortunately it wasn't.
So she's got an empty can, and there's not too resty, and she's got any shops there.
Then you should be fine. Now let's go. So happy banging.
I want this.
No, no, that was baby. You can bang my box from Channel J Robin Bird Show.
I'm very rude. I think I forgot to finish the Dutch guy's comment.
I'm sorry.
Hi, how are you doing?
Have you ever done any of your apropos?
Come on. You're watching a little bit of a link in this video.
No one understands this.
Of course I am.
I know it was because of the brochish freaking del.
Anyway, thanks and have a wonderful weekend. Bye.
And that's your song in the background.
Yeah, and yours.
Yeah, that's it.
That's another story.
We have to explain, because that's actually very, that's a beautiful story.
So we tell them, now we should know.
We'll save that for when we're on the road together.
Now, do you want to do the show with me every day?
I guess I have to, I'm there.
But you don't have to, but sometimes we have to do it.
We're there with so English.
Have to.
You don't have to.
Don't have to.
Yes.
You started to become a little bit English.
Or have sexes.
Kids call the bill.
The problem is, and when we go out west, west coast,
we either have to do it late at night before we go to bed.
Or at the end of the day, basically, for the next day,
which is kind of fun.
Maybe next time we should do it in the bed.
Maybe people want to come with us.
And we record.
You might want to, you might want to rephrase that.
People want to come with us.
Yeah.
Come into the bed with us.
Dutch birth.
Who?
I do want to talk with you about Paul McCartney.
But before we do that, I play the song.
Yeah.
We'll talk about that in a second.
I played a song Monday, I think.
And I heard it on the Martina Butler Show, Emot Girl Talk.
Yeah.
You have no idea.
I mentioned the Christina.
I said, I'm getting all these comments about this one song.
And she said, oh, yeah.
I know this guy.
I don't know them for a long time.
But listen to the comments that people are sending.
If you know, mind, it's really cool.
Hey, Adam.
This is Christian Philadelphia.
And egoatepext.com.
I'm a listener.
And I was delayed here.
I'm going to work at death cancer study on the podcast.
Literally on the podcast, literally on the pod show.
And you can get work on it.
Whatever.
Not done.
This makes me realize how big this is.
This is the first artist that I've heard on the podcast.
He's in that work that I've heard of before.
He's following a podcast.
And it's going to take off from here on out.
Every time you get one band on.
They talked all their band friends.
And you get 20 bands on.
Soon enough, you had the whole indie music scene on the
podcast music network.
So awesome.
And keep to the work.
So for some reason.
The people now say the podcast music network is validated.
Excuse me.
Since so.
Because this is the podcast.
What?
I have to park the car.
Because you're burping.
And I am sorry.
I'm sorry.
Because we just, you know, we were talking about it.
And I had to park the car because you were burping.
Oh, sorry.
I'm sorry.
No, it's the short term memory loss.
It's the.
Yeah, you got that.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Dude, Adam, I'm sitting here listening to straightening on.
I had no idea that death cat for cutie had pod safe music.
It just freaked me out.
You hear that.
Such a good song.
I actually had it on my computer.
It was making a thing about listening to music.
But I just had to flip on the source code instead.
By the way, this phone line is great for these impulse comments.
Thanks, Adam.
So I want you to hear the song and tell me what you think about it.
Because I like it.
But I was just blown away by, and this is maybe, you know, just 2% of all the stuff that
people are sending about this particular song.
Deathcab for cutie.
Title and registration, please.
The glove compartment is an accurate laying down.
And everybody knows it.
So I'm proposing.
A swift orderly chant.
Because behind it's door.
There's nothing to keep my fingers down.
And all I find are soothing here's from better times before the clear.
Of your tail lights fading.
To find yourself a better life.
I was searching for some legal document.
It's the laying deep down on the hood.
When I stumble upon pictures I tried to forget.
And that's how this idea was drilled into my head.
Because it's too important to stay the way.
There's no plan for how our love did slowly fade.
And now that it's common.
It's like it wasn't there at all.
And here I was.
The disappointment ever went.
It's like it wasn't there at all.
There's no plan for how our love did slowly fade.
Now that it's common.
It's like it wasn't there at all.
And here I was.
The disappointment ever went.
The lie lying away.
What do you think?
Yeah it's not your style I know.
Well.
I liked it but I was missing, you know, the core or something.
Really?
I don't want two, three.
Right.
It's kind of like round control to me.
Yeah.
Before I got a whole bunch of things.
You know what we always in Dutch say?
No.
We always say.
And find you.
Well, you just did it.
That is their hunt.
That's probably.
That kind of sticks.
And then I.
Tom the pod save music now.
Hey, a couple of things before I forget.
Voice mail numbers for your feedback.
Jersey 201-625-6357 in London, 0207-681-3753-3.
Congratulations to Marcus Couch.
Today is one year anniversary in podcasting.
Check them out at the scenes scene.
He sent me this whole thing with a song.
But I don't.
We'd already agreed to do our show.
So I can't play that.
And I so much I wanted to talk to you about hunt.
It's unbelievable.
Oh, I see.
How much people sent me that link to the.
You know, the guy.
I told the story the other day on the show.
The guy who was interviewed by the BBC, but he wasn't the expert.
Oh, that was so funny.
I have the video of it.
Oh, really?
You wanted to see just a little bit.
It's it's hilarious.
Yeah.
It's hilarious.
You can see the minute he's introduced.
The guy's like, you have to come over here.
That's okay.
Just turn around.
I should put the.
Put the sound system on.
Amazing.
Yeah.
This is the guy.
He was there for job interview.
And they pulled him in for an interview about the Apple records versus Apple iTunes lawsuit.
But I'm going round between Apple computer.
The company behind the iPod and Apple.
I just want you to see his face and the shit he talks.
At the beginning of this interview.
So this is on BBC News 24.
And they pulled this.
They pulled the wrong guy from the from the waiting room.
Instead of the in the expert who were there were going to interview.
What about this lawsuit?
As long as they pulled in this guy.
And the minute they introduced his name.
He figures out that they've got the wrong guy.
And look at his face.
He's still.
Okay.
He's when the round started.
Well, the judge in the case as we've heard has just ruled in favor of Apple.
Call.
Time to record label.
So what does this all mean for the industry and the gross.
If music online.
Well, by Kumi is the editor of technology website.
News.
Look at his face.
Hello.
Good morning.
Well, you surprised by this verdict today.
I'm very surprised to see this verdict too.
To come on me.
I was expecting that.
When I came.
I was a totally something else.
And I'm coming.
He's basically saying.
I didn't know I was going to talk about the big surprise anyway.
A big surprise.
Yeah.
It was a God to the costs and.
So now he's just.
Now he's just.
And he just keeps on going.
But you know how that happened.
And now we met.
Yeah.
Now I already told the story.
I already told about the stupid stupid.
Yeah.
Stupid producers.
They don't have brain dead.
Even though what you're doing.
All right.
Okay.
Let's talk about.
And I'll put the link in the show notes.
Of course.
All right.
So Paul McCartney.
And I'm a guy who will.
Who will dispute this all the way through up until the.
Yeah, you do.
I said it.
You know, is because you read all this crap in the papers for about a week and a half.
It's been going on.
Yeah.
And we read too many things about ourselves until I hear it from the guys mouth himself.
I'm just not going to believe it.
And now they've actually released the statement.
I guess.
Yeah.
That he and what's your name Heather Miller Mills.
Split up.
You know, that.
That right there is a clue that there was destined to end up in failure.
Because she never went by Heather McCartney.
She went by Heather Mills.
No.
Because she's somebody to.
Yeah.
Like Patricia Puy versus.
No.
Not a dog.
Because I've always been Mrs. Curry in America.
I've never.
For the past two months.
I think you've been saying to me, this is wrong.
This is not going right.
This is not going to work between these two.
You were way before the papers were saying this.
And it was just one moment.
I saw one moment.
They had a show about animal rights.
And she does a lot for, you know, against for.
And she had a whole show about it.
And.
Yeah.
And you're totally.
Very interesting.
I mean, I do agree in a lot of things.
And they make for from dogs and cats.
And that's ridiculous.
I mean, that is absolutely ridiculous.
So.
Why did it.
It's less ridiculous than from a mink.
It's it's ridiculous.
Anyway, we don't need it because the the fake is beautiful.
Right.
Beautiful.
That can make it as beautiful.
Even more beautiful.
So.
And they match nicely.
Different.
Right.
What?
And then the fake firm matches nicely with your teeth.
It does.
Yes.
So, but I was watching that and also Paul McCartney was in it.
And I saw them.
They were talking together about something.
And she was explaining something.
And she was.
And she said, you know, we're going to do this.
I'm going to do that.
And my husband Paul.
He has a lot of famous people that he knows.
And they're going to help to.
And a lot of relations.
Yeah.
And and she looked at him.
Uh huh.
And that was the moment.
And I saw.
Yes.
Uh.
Looking at her like, what the fuck is she saying?
I missed it.
Yeah.
And really, I really.
So he's like, I don't want to do this.
You know, I'm all.
That was the boy.
Would you do it?
But no.
He doesn't like that.
He doesn't like to, you know,
get his, you know,
use his friend.
Use his famous friend.
You never see him in publicity.
Really.
Except when he's with his women.
His women always want to drag him into public.
He is a very quiet person.
And now I know that the marriage that he had with Linda was the most wonderful marriage.
That's exactly the woman that he needed.
And they were very, very extremely happy.
And.
And he was, you know, smoking is clear.
And she was baking her.
Um, a vegetarian meals and everything and cooking for him.
And they, they loved it.
They were never an hour without each other.
I think the whole.
The whole, the, the life that they had together was only nine days that it were apart.
So it's a little bit like that.
You would kill me if I was around.
No, I want you gone.
Yeah, exactly.
Get him out.
So.
Get that stinky sweaty man out.
He depends on what kind of life you have, of course.
But so, and then, and then,
I saw him.
Meals, you know, when he started to date her.
And I thought, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can see that, you know, he's a sweet guy.
He's a sweet man.
And he already seen it.
Had it dated, done it.
You know, actually it could have moved in here with me.
Yeah, really.
You know, it would be the same as having me, huh?
I'm just an old guy smoking a split.
Hangin out.
Yeah.
Watching your cook.
Yeah, Paul.
I know what you mean.
We did it all.
Yeah.
But, and she just wants to do her own thing.
And it is.
And then she probably wants to use him for that.
And, and she does, and I think she means well.
She's in for a rough ride.
Now, man.
But she's in for a rough ride.
His kids didn't like her.
They really tried.
Yeah, Stella.
And I've heard a lot of famous friends from Paul.
A couple of time mentioning.
Hey, Paul.
Get the slagger out your life.
And like, sir, Alton.
You know, he has a big mouth.
Yeah, no kidding.
And he was meant to say something nasty.
Heather, a couple of time.
He said, it's a very cold cold woman.
I don't like her.
She's such a queen.
Yeah.
Why does he do that?
He's always into a thing with everybody.
Everybody.
Right.
So knows.
He has nothing to lose, I guess.
No.
He doesn't care.
All right.
So, so now everybody officially hates Heather.
No, now they have a child.
Oh, but now they're.
Yeah.
Especially.
She's going to be.
They have a kid together.
Yeah.
She's beautiful.
That sucks.
And they're married now for four years.
And I think that everyone's going to hate her.
I'm going to look at her.
Like, oh, you're going to take his money now.
We hate you for more.
Yeah.
But it's not real.
I think it's the tabloids.
They're really good.
They feel good.
Yeah.
And she just had another operation four weeks ago on her.
That was already going on.
Well, it's something messed up there.
She works around so much.
Yeah.
She overdid the walking on her.
You know, with her artificial leg.
Yeah.
And it started to hurt.
No, no.
I thought that the plate inside her.
Yeah.
Also, and her knees started to hurt.
That connects to the leg.
That it shifted or something.
I saw her complaining in that documentary.
Well, no, shit.
I would, I would be complaining.
Yeah.
I can like that.
Nothing to do with it.
No, no, no.
But still.
He knew what her leg.
So I guess the question is, did he, was this a rebound love that he jumped
into this too quickly after Linda's death?
No, I think he believed that he had, you know, he found another pal, another
friend.
But that's not what she is.
He wants a pal.
He wants a friend.
He wants, you know, like we are.
We're buddies.
Yes, we are.
We need to buddy.
And she's going the wrong way every time.
Every guy needs a buddy who will come into your office at 11 o'clock a night and say,
it's okay, huh?
You can play as on second life as long as you like.
That's what every guy needs.
As long as you play with me now and then.
I satisfy you long time.
All right.
So I'm prepping this morning.
Going through my email, listening to voice mail comments.
And the doorbell goes.
Yeah.
And I know I don't have to go and get it because there's no.
There's a lot of people in the house now.
You never pick up the phone.
It's not for me.
You never open to door.
Yeah.
What, what do you, you lost for you?
Well, in this case.
Yeah.
Right.
So Patricia brings up this package.
She says, are you a virgin flying club member?
Yes.
I have a package for you.
So it was a special delivery.
And in an, um, a beautiful, what is it?
Silver plated silver plated travel alarm clock?
No, not silver plated.
Yes, it is silver plated because the instructions said how to care for silver plating.
Oh.
Silver baby.
Well, it doesn't look good.
No, no.
I took off the plastic shielding.
Oh, no.
It looks better.
Yeah.
Please put your fingers on it.
Make it on all messy.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's the diamond.
It's quite handsome.
And accompanied by a letter from the CEO, the chief executive Steve Ridgeway, actually signed
by him in a hurry.
I'm sure you had to send it.
A shit lover.
But writing personally that, thank you personally for your huge contribution to
Virgin Atlantic.
Let you know that during the last 12 months, you have managed to earn over 100
tier points by flying with us.
So I'm reading this to you.
And essentially, what's kind of nice about this?
Forget the alarm clock is I now get what they call a personal account executive,
which means I have a special number and an email address.
And through that, I can reach either Pauline Box or Morgan Morag Morton.
And so these are my professionals.
And they'll take everything I never have to, you know, I guess.
Oh, your fly bitch.
It's like my fly.
Yes, my fly bitch is.
I don't know if Morgan's going to go my fly bitch.
One moment, please.
Yeah.
I got my fly bitch.
Let me go text my fly bitch.
Give me some points and two points.
So I'm reading this to you into your mom and my phone rings.
Yeah.
And I pick up the phone.
And it's hi.
This is Pauline Box.
Did you just receive a letter?
I'm like, god damn you guys are good at virgin.
There is my fly bitch.
And my fly.
I got to tell her that next time.
Yeah, cool.
I guess the other day when I was booking our tickets to New York, you know,
it was kind of complicated because I was trying to do miles plus money, you know, to save money,
essentially because it's very expensive.
And you know, everything was all confused as it turned out.
And then when I was all done, then she says, you know, because you had this gold card line or whatever,
the representative before I had the fly bitches says, is anything else you'd like me to look at?
And I said, yeah, what do you think of my hair today?
And it was like a silence.
You go, I think of pardon because you repeat that.
I got to record that shit when I call those people.
I know you do that a lot.
I love that.
You confuse people with it.
But you know, it changes their day.
Doesn't it?
Well, it didn't get her, did she?
Because she wasn't ready for it.
But next time she, I'm bombing, I'm bombing big time.
And you do that a lot.
What bomb?
No, we are serious talking to somebody, you know, having a serious conversation, which
it may be very important for that moment.
Give me an example.
And people look at us like, no, that's not all about.
No, I don't know.
What important are you looking at a house and then, you know, lady,
you know, from the real estate agents, just a dry person with papers on there.
Oh, she was kind of dry.
Yeah, I know.
And then you could stupid.
Well, what?
Like what?
You're looking at a house and you say, oh, that's nice.
I can hang you on the ceiling.
I didn't say that.
That's not stupid.
That's a pretty good one, actually.
I have to remember that.
I have to use that line.
And those ladies.
Because he breaks the tension of the stupid dry person with the papers
on the ceiling.
Sometimes I have to say, oh, he's only kidding.
You know, but it's, it's, it's the way I talk.
Yeah, I know.
You okay?
I don't know.
I like them.
It's not exactly why you said, this is the man I want to spend the rest of my life with.
That's why I like you.
I like those.
Just like.
It's like no.
We went from love to like.
No.
I've been downgraded.
No, I mean, the remarks.
I'm not saying I love the remarks, but I'm like him.
I can, you know, laugh about them.
You guys, I think else for us baby until we wrap up.
Well, I'm already 52 minutes.
Well, I don't like it when they're tired.
I do this every single day.
Oh, it's looking, you know, following me through the house.
They are telling me what I, that's exactly what you don't this.
They're like, they're like furbies that follow you around.
And then when you point them towards each other, they go,
let's do this.
Let's do that.
Have you did the bed yet?
Oh, God.
They steer clear of me, boy.
When I'm in my office, they're like, they tiptoe past.
They're like, he's working.
Don't disturb me.
I'm in second life.
You know, hanging out with people on the castle.
And then he's working.
Don't disturb me.
That's what I saw.
This week, would they be able to handle Christina for the next 10 days?
Sure.
Crikey, man.
I don't know about that.
That's going to be interesting.
Say the least.
Yeah.
Interesting.
Well, I told her to be very, very nice.
Well, your mom will give me a report, right?
She'll give me an honest report.
I told Christina, fundamental things in her life would change if I don't hear my mom.
That's true.
She will definitely kick her ass.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
I just don't want to get that call on an eight hour time dear friends of three in the morning.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm going to call my mom.
I'm going to pack.
You pack.
Oh, call my mom.
I'm picking up Christina at school.
Oh, I have to call.
I got to go buy a new mobile with her.
Yeah.
Because she's, how many mobiles has she now broken five?
Oh, so many.
It's unbelievable.
Yeah.
It's just unbelievable.
I didn't do anything.
Yeah.
There's kids.
You know what they do.
No, I don't.
I'd like to know.
It's unbelievable.
I don't know.
Even the cheapest ass.
No.
It's unbelievable.
Oh, man.
Okay.
I had another song.
I'm not going to play it.
Excuse me.
Oh.
Who should I play song?
Yeah.
One more.
One more song.
I heard this song.
Someone sent me an email that CC Chapman played it on the accident hash.
Lee Colter.
The Booty Voodoo.
Oh, man.
You throw some cowbell in there, man. It's just rocks in.
I bet it drives people crazy.
Yeah, some people really do not like me doing that.
Yeah.
But a lot of people...
You can see your face. You really can see that.
I am enjoying myself.
You can see the face with him.
Bye, man.
From Papotum, boom, boom.
It was Robbie Williams, wasn't it?
A little bit.
Time to rock your body.
That's good.
Yeah, there's no shit as perfect.
If you have a good song, you always think,
Do I know this?
Do I know this song?
Then it's a good song.
All right, baby.
So, Monday you'll join me for the show?
Yeah.
And then Tuesday, when we're new year...
Our Monday, I don't know.
It depends on you.
You do it in the evening, right?
Um...
Because I meet...
I think I meet my sister.
Oh, she's gonna be in New York too.
Oh, excellent.
Well, Sunday night by the way.
Marta has changed the tickets.
We have tickets for Sunday night to...
Julia Roberts on Broadway.
Okay.
That would be fun.
Yeah. Good.
You don't like that?
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I've heard some reviews.
Uh-huh.
Some say that it sucks.
Yeah.
And she sucks.
Right.
And some say it's brilliant.
Perfect.
So we'll do...
Sunday evening after we get...
Let's find out.
After that, then we'll record Sunday evening.
And then we'll have a show from Monday.
And we'll do the review.
If she sucks or not.
And we are honest.
Uh-huh.
Some of us in the room are extremely honest.
Yeah.
Beyond the honesty.
I love to do this.
Yeah.
And I love you.
Well, thank you, Mr. Curry.
I mean, I love you, baby.
Okay.
All right.
Hey, Petrisha.
How do we get weekend?
Yeah. Thank you.
Yeah.
Shall I pack yours, too?
Your suit case?
Would you please?
Would you mind just leave some space open for the gear?
Because otherwise, you're going to do it.
Last minute.
My end.
I'm the last minute.
Yes.
Me and me.
Just leave room for the gear for the microphone, the mixer, and the compressor.
Story of my life.
I know.
I have a great weekend to everybody.
Love you, honey.
Love you, too.
Oh, shit.
That was, that was poor.
I have a great weekend to everybody.
Love you, honey.
I love you, honey.
I love you, too.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this pod cast and more great ones like it.
On the high performance pod cast delivery network from pod show and limelight networks.
I love it.