This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 405.
Mr. Curry, the pod father, forgive this intrusion on such a joyous occasion.
We've come to ask for your blessing.
My name is Ed, and I'm Carlos.
And this is Ed.
We are from a podcast we call the Starcast.
We want to know that we have lived up to your example.
You boys come to ask my blessing and my daughter's wedding day.
Well, these boys have honored me and my family with your good music.
You're an interesting bubble and no questions attitude towards what is asked of you.
This honor is the pod father.
In one day, I may come to ask a favor of you.
No kiss the real.
Thank you father.
You were a little lower.
May your daughter's first child be a masculine child.
Hi, this is Sophia Ramos.
If you want to hear great music, keep it here on the daily source code with Adam Curry.
Check me out at myspace.com slash Sophia Ramos.
Rock-on.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped my ass.
Three minutes?
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking friends, man.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Ob whoa chestic his madam Curry.
One big green brother, Friday.
Play the time.
Play the time, please.
총.
Play the time.
Rajé.
Rajé, hey anger, teasing me.
Hey, I'll make it my mercy to the grave
Take your dreams to you, catch the disease
The age in the most powerful space
Love is so I need them, they look at me there
Cloth is ever changing, hope is shining in my eyes
Yeah, yeah, yeah
And I will always still answer them
And I'll make it my last time to move them
And I will always clean and take you
But I wanna be to no date
Love is so I need them, they look at me there
Life is ever changing, hope is shining
Love is only needed, they forget me there
Life is ever changing, hope is shining in my eyes
I hope is shining in my eyes
There's all I need, and then go get me there
I'll be able to change, and hope is shining
Love is all I need, and then go get me there
Love is ever changing, hope is shining in my arms
Love is all I need, hope is shining in my arms
Oh yeah, that'll wake you, to fear of us
Esperanza, coming to you from San Francisco, very sunny northern California
Hey everybody, how you doing is the daily source code today is Friday
Man, I'm ready for the show, I'm ready to rumble
Lots of positive music for you today, lots of feedback, all kinds of stuff that I've been saving up for the end of the week
And you know, I woke up this morning, actually I did normally I wake up before the alarm clock
So it went off at 6 o'clock and I'm like, hey, I'm really tired
Why am I so tired? I went to bed at 10.30
I know why
I've been traveling a lot
You know, what did I, I arrived Monday, went straight to the office
And I've just been nonstop since then, I think I'm ready for the weekend
How about you?
Some of you may be listening to this on your way home
If you're in the UK, you probably got it around five in the afternoon
Some of you, and on the west coast, you're probably getting this early morning
I may be you're 11 o'clock meeting if you're on the east coast in the US
And if you're in Australia?
Well, how is Saturday?
Hi, it's Friday
I know, I know
It is the Marco from the show
Hello, hello
Happy Friday, Charlie France
This is Ray from Holland with a little sucker update
Because not only Holland is orange, the whole world is getting a little orange
And that's a lot better than the Greengrassi Marijuana colour
We're refining up to everywhere I come and I tell that I'm from the Netherlands
People always start to talk about the coffee shops
Anyway, today at 1,800 hours European time in Stuttgart, Germany
The World Cup match Holland against Ivory Coast will kick off
Actually, I'm not such a big sucker fan, but I really like to watch all the World Cup matches
As much as I can
Tonight, our Dutch coach Marco from Buster
We'll start with the same 11 as last Sunday
That means that Rafa El van der Fart won't play
But, Wesley Snyder will be in the center of the field again
I hope Ruth van Nisleroy, show off a little more
And Aryan Robo will play with his 10 friends on the field
Ivory Coast coach Henry Mitchell has a knife on his throat
They have to win this game
I think the World will beat more orange at the tonight
And I don't underestimate the gang, but they're going to be spent
By the Italian Big Swinging Dig
I'm sorry, tell, but the 11 girls from the States are not going to win the World Cup
Anyway, hope you have a wonderful weekend
See you soon
Bye bye
Hey Ray, I'm fighting words, man
What are you talking about?
The 11 girls from the States give me a break
I have a really good feeling about him
And tomorrow a couple of the enthusiasts from Pacho HQ
We're all getting together, we're going to watch that game
They have a shot, I know they do
And they just had to kind of get into the whole vibe
So funny that all this World Cup stuff is going on
For me, in my limited little world of podcasting
But there's a whole other championship going on as well
Which is the NBA finals
Basketball here in the States
And it's funny because I really didn't know about it
Until last night, Ron said, hey man, come on, come on, come on, my place will have dinner there
Of course, we had to take cabs since the Trinity option was out
Trinity is at the doctor, by the way
She'll be okay, today we get full diagnosis and cost structure
But I'm getting her fixed no matter what, I love my Trinity
If you're new to this show, Trinity is my french fry oil, burning Mercedes station wagon
300 turbo diesel from 1984 that dropped her transmission
So we actually watched the heat gain, heat against the Mavericks
Miami versus Dallas, it was a good game
Finally, Miami actually played a really good game
It was alright, you know, it's funny because
Once you, I don't know, this is kind of hard
Something about soccer, you know, even though you get relatively low points
There's just, this seems to be so much less structure to the game
How things can happen and for some reason with basketball
It seems like it really is based a lot on the tech, you see
In soccer, you're not supposed to foul the guy
And of course, you know, they're always trying to do something
To knock someone down without getting a yellow or red card
When basketball, this filing thing is really important
Because then you get your free throws
I don't know, for some reason, it just didn't quite hit me as I thought it would
I don't know, what is happening to me?
I'm turning into a European, gosh, dang it
Like in that soccer stuff
Hey, voicemail numbers all weekend long
You may be listening to the show over the weekend
Love to hear from you, we have two numbers in New Jersey
201-65-635-7
And I have a number in London, so whichever is cheaper for you to call
Feel free 020-768-1375-3
Some cool news yesterday, some pod show news
Podcast Ali is now featured on the new Nokia phones
They have some kind of podcatcher aggregator built in
And you can now search through
portions of the podcast Ali directory
And it will download stuff automatically
I posted it on curry.com
So it's definitely cool and pretty proud of that
It's all part of the evil master plan
As we unveil podshow plus and the podcast Ali
Renette word my friends
Adam, hi this is Charles
From London
Just had to ring you know, everything
Two last Friday, so to 402
Yep
On May, I have to say, London in the summer time
Yeah
Well, you know, I'm saying, oh my god
You should sit in so close square
On a weekday
Around about lunchtime
When all the secretary is coming out
All you can do is get it up
Mumbling the top down
Oh my god, it's fantastic
Hang on second
You shouldn't really put this on a
No talking about alcohol
Anyway, I'm sorry
Well I say, hello Adam
Renette here
I can't get it
No wait, I am a vacuum
Charles, I am a vacuum
I can't get it
Okay, thank you
There you go, it's all one guy apparently
Oh man
Yeah
I mean, please don't
Don't think that we're opening up a London office
To do any business
We're just there for the boobies in the summertime
Failure to comply radio
Show where we make you laugh
Cry and touch you in that special way
Or maybe just laugh
From conspiracy theories
To throwing Katie Holmes into a ghetto
This show has it all
We're random
We're retarded
And guess what?
We're politically incorrect
It's failure to comply radio
Visit us at www.ftcradio.net
Hi
This is Caitlin Smith
And you're listening to the daily source code
With your benevolent host
The podfather himself
A guy with really great hair
Adam Kirk
He's like it's so dizzy
But before
All the smoke I've been heard
Life's for you
Like many times before
It's difficult to see
The melodies
Coffers
Like you know
My struggle here for my friends
And you
Let's give me
Can you
Will you
Like wind you've carried me to a better place
That I'm here, I understand it
My mind has hearts and love, I love that feeling
When you rest, let's be awake now, you're sleeping
When you're sleeping, I love that feeling
When you sleep, you're well, you're well
When you're well, you're well, I love that feeling
When you're well, I love that feeling
When you're well, you're well, you're well, you're well, I love that feeling
Caitlyn Smith, from the pod save music network
Here me, let me just check out her bio for a second here
Something magical happens, I read from the bio
When she grabs a guitar and steps up to the microphone
Coffee shops become silence, loud band, loving teens, turn quiet
It's all turned an ear to the obvious gift and embrace all that this artist has to give
It may be your confidence or the heartfelt expression of her music
It's Caitlyn Smith, from Minnesota
Cool, like it
Oh, this is kind of cool, her influences, jewel
Nicole Nordman and then this is cool, Beth Thorne Lee and the Bitties
Excellent, very, very cool
So pod save music, artists influencing her, I like that very much
And people ask me all the time, how may I, how can we get our song played on the daily source code?
Well, really easy one, I have to like the song, it's just that's sorry, it's my show, I don't care
I have to like the song, and I like a wide range of stuff
Two, it always does help when the artist cuts a promo and this was even pre-mix
It came to me in all one pre-mix form, and of course, at the end of the day
Make it pictures also help
I had him, this is at Hagen from the editing.com photo cast
Just listening to episode 404 and you play the comment about the guy from the Eurostar
Excuse me, and then licensing pod save music for their commercial podcast that they are producing
And I was wondering if you could talk a little bit about where does the line get drawn for a commercial podcast
And we have a lot of podcasters out there that are looking at or have already quit their day jobs
And they are collecting income from their podcas
And some of them do play pod save music
So what is the definition of commercial podcast, I'm sure it's in the license
But in the terms of agreeing to it, but you know, it's a computer guy
I'm trying to just click except on the terms of whatever software I'm looking at
Can you talk a little bit about that and thanks a lot
And if you're a photographer out there, check out Editing.com
Right on Ed, it's real simple actually, I'm glad you asked the question
It's about the distribution
So this is really for podcasters
If you make a podcast, which they call it a derivative work
Or whatever the legal term is that you click the way the minute you signed up
That's okay, and it can be commercial, I mean, witness the daily source code
Totally a commercial show
GoDaddy.com, DSC3 upon checkout for your domain name for $6.95
But if you were to burn this to a CD and distribute it to clients for a fee
Which is the case of the euro star
Well, then you have to go and get permission
Because now you're doing something else with it as that the license intends
And I think that's pretty much, you know, also commercial clients often
They want to compensate and I think that's kind of what was going on here
There was an agency working for the client for euro star
There's podcasts that were being developed they may or may not be if their internal podcast only
Then the same thing would kick in because then it's
It's not a public work and you have to give all the attribution
So really it's about the distribution
But if you're just if you're quitting your day job if you're quit your day job
If you want to quit your day job you just want to make a show
And you're making money by doing your show
It's not a problem as long as you signed up to the podcast music and then that work
And of course you have to report back in
You just want to think about all the music, you know
I really do like playing all different types of tunes along Fridays
I do like to kick it a little bit
Um
Was it?
Have you ever heard that in over your head
Julian Smith
So he's noticed that I've been picking up on some R&B and hip-hop stuff
And I think I saw on his one of his show notes
That he was happy that I was coming out of the closet
As a closet as a closet dancer a closet hip hopper R&B you're not alone, Julian
Hey Adam this is Jeff Hines
Right in that dance party podcast
And I'm glad you're finally coming out of the closet
Forget all that head bangers ball full shit
And who cares about a mallet
I mean does anyone look good to mallet?
I know I don't you look good to mallet Adam
So it's all about dance and it's all about shaking your ass
Adam, what kind of ass do you have?
Is it round? Is it square? Is it fat? Is it thin?
Is it loose? Is it tight?
You know you like to get it like that
So I'm glad to see that you're finally playing some dance music on the
ESC that people can shake it and make it to
And that's what it's all about
So this is Jeff Hines with a Friday dance party
And all I have to say is keep on dancing
What to come over here and see what kind of ass I have man
If you're that interested
So it's Friday normally I'd be doing pod save the queen with Christina
It's time for episode number three of course I'm not home
And she is or I mean our other home as it were
She really wants to do the show and of course I want her to do the show as well
And I am I guess I'm the producer
So we have figured something out
Hopefully but it won't be today because
It's just all the time zone stuff because what time is it now
It's already deep into the afternoon
And I have to get off to the office after I'm done with the with the
So it'll be over the weekend but we're going to try and do it via Skype
She's going to email me the songs and I think with the new Skype
The PC version at least
As you know, I'm still on windows
And she has windows as well
I think the sound quality just might be good enough to actually pull it all together
And pull off a pod save the queen
I can't wait to hear what she has lined up for
Obviously
Madam A, Moose Lawrenceville, California
Sorry to hear about Trinity's transmission
But hearing Christina's podcast
Which I really enjoyed
The thing that comes to mind is for the last
No longest time that I can remember
You've been kind of complaining about not having a producer
And well long behold
You're a producer for your daughter
And you're doing a great job and so she so
Cheers
Peace
Hi Adam, this is Chris and take us down there
I like to hear you play straight
But I think you guys are going to get some close going on
Thanks
Bye
Wow
Your wish to my command
You'll be music heavy
Straight on the Charlie
I have described
Nothing but black
And I'm afraid
Still I am dying to tell you
Crane
Into the room
Make a mistake
Let's see just how much it hurts you
I'd like to crack
I can't be alone
Always a pack
And they're just itching to bite
Crack
I can't be alone
Always a pack
And they're just itching to bite
Down
Show me the way to the perfect
I work as a bomb
I find seen my reach
I want to love my myself home
Show me the way to the perfect
I work as a bomb
I want to love my head
To get me asleep
So I like to tell me how long you're
From the snake
To get me asleep
So I like to tell me how long you're
From the snake
To get me alone
Always a pack
And they're just itching to bite
Crane
Nothing but black
And I'm afraid
Still I am dying to tell you
Crane will work as a bomb
And will work as a bomb
The soup born throne
Straight
Those of you listening to us on serious stars
One, two, the satellite window
Is a close and PCH's next
And I will see you guys back here on Monday
So what's code listeners we continue now on the show
Tagged am it
Almost had a perfect lead back time
I don't know what went wrong
I'm using the new version of Cast Blaster by the way
Which is kind of cool
Cast Blaster Mike heard me talking yesterday about
ID3 tags and not being able to see those in Cast Blaster
So he turned around last night or whatever
And made me a new version
It's like great
So when I mouse over
And so if I mouse over
Scrape let me see
Almost second
Of course not all songs have ID3 tags
And yeah
Okay there we go
Some of them are working
Although I would notice one thing
For some reason my F1
Which is my AC to the future
If I hit that it doesn't do anything
All the other F commands
Start stuff like the thing out of the slide
And then I've got
Running walls
And I've got the Metro moment
But when I hit F1 it doesn't happen
So I don't know if that's a changing Cast Blaster Mike
Or if that's something that's changed on my machine
Subborn throne of course by request
New Hampshire's fastest rising band
Formed in the sea coast area by
Brothers Kobe and Kerry Dodd
Who added bases Adam Hor and percussionist Travis Barton
The band has performed throughout the northeast
An open for such acts as Vince Wellnick
Of the grateful dead and Todd Rungren
And Gary Hoey
He, Gary Hoey is playing tonight everybody
All right
I still have one more
So I got so many cool things I want to share with you
Oh yes today
K2 Kevin ready asked about Snake Bite
Which is the mixture of cider and ale
I guess in the UK which he thought was outlawed
And he really had a legitimate question
So he asked that by calling to the voice mail numbers
And of course we have an answer already
Hello Adam
Mike Turner here from Bristol England County working in Chelm
Also known as Gimm in Decito on Second Life
There are comments on Snake Bite I Charlie 404
Snake Bite is actually perfectly legal in England
Although some pubs won't actually serve it
Because apparently it doesn't make people a lot more pissed
A lot quicker
I don't think it does actually be a thing
It's just another legend
Anyway what you say is beer
We brits actually call ale or bitter
Now
To make a snake bite
Cider is normally mixed with larga
What called larga which would be both liser
Fosters or Croninburg
Some it like that which is the under beer
You would never mix cider with ale
Or bitter
Also that other bloke I'm going to choose the show
The one who will criticise and you'll show
Your sound and how to run it
I think he's an asshole
And I agree with you
I mean who would tell Gimm the end
It's a guitar sounded distorted
And he should turn it
Distortion off
Anyway
Yes
Bye
Alright man
Thank you
Okay so we've settled that
I think it's time for a sound seeing tour
Snake Bite in the UK
You know I still have not
Actually you have to have your own pub
I think it's kind of like the an unwritten law in the UK
And that's the pub where you're going
Hang out
I have not chosen one
And I really do need to do that
So perhaps a sound seeing tour
Of a
And believe me lots of people have sent me pub rules
And you know when you're supposed to buy a drink
Or accept a drink
And how you're supposed to strike up a conversation
There is a several rule books on all this
How to do it properly
But it seems to me like it's time for a sound seeing tour
of Snake Bite
Maybe a Snake Bite or two
Interesting discussion going on over curry.com
As of turned on the comments again
Seems like the
Comic strip blogger and
Jacic watcher stuff is all calm down
And if it starts up again
I'm just deleting comments
I'm so sick and tired of that
Can we all just get along
But the comments now are about the earthlink ad challenge
That we've been running
And this is pretty cool because this is where you get to
Make the advertising
And of course just listening to all these
Different submissions is by definition advertising
But I look at it as content for the show
And so there's people saying
Oh, you know this one sucks and that was no good
It's just like mainstream radio
But the whole point of this is
Then why don't you just send in your own submissions
So you should tell us how it's supposed to go
How it's supposed to work?
What will work?
AdChallence.podshow.com
I got another submission for you today
They are getting very good
I think we're seeing like 20 new ones a day come in
And this is for valuable cash prizes
$2,000 in prize money
We're doing the earthly clues
That's right baby
Earthlink
Bombastic broadband
Delicious dad
That's Earthlink
Ethnic comes home to you
And brings it home to mama
That's our assistant
That's what I'm talking about
In Earthlink
We'll help you out with all your internet needs
So just go to Earthlink.com
Let them know that pop a section
Yeah, that's your favorite
That's what I'm talking about
All right
So this week and I guess I'm going to go look for a table
And some other solution for the studio
Because it's really gotten bad now
I should take a picture of this
You know what?
Hold on a second
So I've got everything I'm running everything off of
The Tashiba laptop show notes
Run down my playlist for music
Cast Blaster
But as you know
I've told you about this
It's all in the kitchen
That's where it's all set up
And it's just way too low for me
So I have a roller bag
Which you know when you roll on
Take the airplane you can put in the overhead bin
And so the laptops on top of that
Now the microphone
I only have a really small stand
A portable stand with heavy foot
And I just snapped the high LPR 40 in there
But since it's so low
I've taken a candlestick
And let me take a picture of this
You won't believe it unless I tell you
Hold on
Let's see if I can get the whole thing in the shot here
There we go
Oh, wait
I want to get the microphone
This is not easy
Getting the whole whole thing in the shot
There we go
Do we take the picture?
Let's try one more
Just move this picture
There we go
I think we'll get a kick out of that
I'll post that in the show notes somewhere
Link to a flicker page
Okay
I had one more song lined up
I know I know I want to play it
Because I really like it
What is this
Antonio Bastian from Spain
Let me see lead singer in
Frogmouth, Labuelet, Muff
And Bastolich duo
Antonine, Antonine
Antonine, Bastian's
Bastian's voice
Harmonica
Are his signature
Currently working on his label
And first solo album
New site coming soon
Excellent
Link to all that goodness in the show notes
Let's check out Don't Break it
I think you will enjoy it
Oh, I remember
Georgie Todd sent me this one
Yes, funny
You don't need to be on the radio
My friend
Stick with us podcasters
What must I do?
To get on the radio
I'll message it up
But I know to the low
What's on my place
But I can dance
Please, Mr. Radio
Give me a chance
What must I do?
To get on the radio
I'll message it up
But I know to the low
What's on my place
But I can dance
Please, Mr. Radio
Give me a chance
I don't care about the fame
And glory
Just pay my song on the radio
I don't need much never
I don't worry
I don't have a Rolex or a Casillo
Give me a chance
Let the public decide
Give my video on prime time
I don't have a thing behind
Just want my chance
Is it the crime
What must I do?
To get on the radio
I'll message it up
But I know to the low
What's on my place
But I can dance
Please, Mr. Radio
Give me a chance
What must I do?
To get on the radio
I'll message it up
I know you're the Lord, want you on my page, but I can dance
Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance
Three or four plays in the day
I'm not asking for the moon
In review me, I got things to say
A brand new LP, come and soon
If you're septic and you're critic
Don't take my music in the first degree
If my music gives you static
If it's my soul, don't you agree
What must I do to get on the radio?
I'll message it up, but I know you're the Lord, want you on my page, but I can dance
Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance
What must I do to get on the radio?
I'll message it up, but I know you're the Lord, want you on my page, but I can dance
Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance
Like a pit bull I will never let go
One of the critics come to my show
All publicity is good publicity
There a opinion will never harm me
I will always do my thing
Leave my heart and sing
If you don't like it, don't buy it
If you don't buy it, don't break it
What must I do to get on the radio?
I'll message it up, but I know you're the Lord, want you on my page, but I can dance
Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance
What must I do to get on the radio?
I'll message it up, but I know you're the Lord, want you on my page, but I can dance
If you don't buy it, don't break it
What must I do to get on the radio?
I'll message it up, but I know you're the Lord, want you on my page, but I can dance
Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance
What must I do to get on the radio?
I'll message it up, but I know you're the Lord, want you on my page, but I can dance
Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance
if you don't lie it don't break your tweets
if you don't be dirty okay
if you don't really okay
if you don't lie it don't break your tweets
if you don't lie it then don't break it
I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake,
I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I'll do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's sake, I do it for God's
Okay, I'm looking forward to resting up this weekend chilling out as I said we'll be trying to do a pod save the queen with Christina
But of course, we'll be back here Monday. We got a whole another week of stuff that we're doing here to pod chill. Keep you up to speed on that
My stuff slowly starts to become available. I'm I'm I'm I'm so ready and so tired
And you know what there's a whole this about 50 people at the office who are also pretty damn tired and work and really hard
Okay, Adam and Craig dot com daily source code dot com is where you can find the feed and the latest episodes
Last year
Have a great weekend everybody for 20 C a Monday another pod show pod cast stick it in your ear
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from pod show and lime light networks