Already a hit state side, now you can check out the following podcast and good old
blightybtpodshot.com, single-handedly making a man's for giving you Madonna.
One show at a time.
The end of course, your host, Adam Curry, Delta Sierra Charlie, 4-9-8.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation
radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
You like sleep alone and I say, I miss the way you breathe, you say, I get away
with you.
You know I've paid for it, and someone can't leave me.
Do you feel something when you're back and they see something you want to see
you get, I could be the one.
I could make it up to you, say goodbye.
I'm the only boy, I love you.
You say, I broken heart because we I say, I tell it sheeps to you, say.
You say, I'm the only boy, I love you.
Never ceases to amaze me when I hear a song.
That's, yeah.
Think, hey, that sounds like you, too.
And then you go to the artist page.
And there it is.
Influences, you, too, echoing the bunny men's
psychedelic for his radiohead and prodigy.
And I believe if it's not, then it should be part
of the recommendation engine that you find at poncho.com slash
music because what a great amount of data that is.
Instead of having to kind of figure out what other people
have listened to, add to that the data that the artist feels
that they sound like, you, too, or influenced by echoing the
bunny men cross reference.
Look at other artists who have done the same thing.
And voila, you have a recommendation.
It's Thursday, everybody.
How you doing?
Coming to you from the Curry Cottage in actually a rainy
affluent suburb of Surrey, known as Guilford.
Been busy.
Been, well, as you know, Mr. Mom Patricia's coming home
from Rotterdam later tonight from her rehearsals for
strictly come dancing, as we call it here in the UK, or
dancing with the stars in the rest of the world.
Last night was a late one for me and other folks in the UK
office because we had our monthly management meeting, which, of
course, means we all dial in video through iChat or Skype
video, multitude of protocols and formats and systems.
And it was very good, of course, but around 130, I definitely
started to fade and Christine was coughing all night.
That's that's that flu, man.
That's exactly what I had a month ago, and I'm just not
getting over it.
And you know, on top of all that, her knee, I remember she
dislocated her knee about four months ago during a field day,
or sport day, as they call it here.
And actually it was doing quite well as she and Patricia
been to the gym a couple of times.
She was thinking about doing some more horseback riding.
And I think a week ago during PE and school, she
heard her knee again.
And now it's swollen, and it's quite swollen.
So I took her to the doctor this morning.
And a doctor said, well, there could be a piece of
cartilage that is roaming around there.
And of course, it, you know, gets jarred loose and floats into
other places and it can hurt and can irritate and you need to have an
MRI scan.
That's no big deal.
Now, in the UK, they have a national health care system,
the NHS.
I think it stands for National Health Care Service
or system.
I don't know.
But it's nationalized health care.
Which, of course, comes with good and comes with bad.
The good, seemingly, is that you get free health care, just about
anyone under 16 gets free medication.
If you have to buy medication and you're over 16, I think there's a
cap on what you can pay, like five pounds, essentially
10 bucks no matter what the prescription is.
That's kind of your copay, which is obviously quite low.
So, you know, that is without doubt the good news.
Of course, anyone in the UK listening to this show will say,
oh, but it's a crap system, it's bankrupt.
But of course, because it's nationalized and everyone's sharing
the resources often people die unnecessarily.
That's just the way it goes.
But at least, I think the majority of people are enjoying the
benefits.
Now, you certainly can understand that with Patricia's
cardiac condition, I have private insurance as well.
And that private insurance, of course, is for the entire family,
and it's quite comprehensive, it's very expensive insurance.
By the way, every single pod show employee has medical insurance,
has health benefits, including dental benefits.
And every company that I've built, and certainly the ones that
run and I've done together, that's always been something where
we're very, very keen on is making sure that everyone is properly
insured and can be healthy.
So, when the doctor said, well, Christina needs an MRI, I said,
well, how long can we get one?
She said, well, you know, it could be two weeks or whatever.
And the kids in pain, you know, just so you know, I'm more than
happy to pay for it privately, because I know that I can
declare that from my insurance.
If you think that will speed things long, she said, oh, yeah,
well, I'll pass that along.
So, we barely even got home in the hospital calls.
Yes, calling for Christina's MRI.
And, you know, do you have health insurance?
Yeah, but it's based in the Netherlands.
So, I'll have to declare that and get the money back.
So, you know, I got to pay him up front.
It's 500 pounds, 1000 bucks for an MRI.
And I said, well, you know, how quick can you get us?
Then she said, well, you know, any time today, if you like, I said, well,
I thought it was really busy.
Because that is certainly the impression I got from,
from the doctor who, of course, wanted to send us through the,
the, the national health care system.
Just, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, we've got plenty of spots open today.
You know, almost any time this week, you know, and whenever you want to.
And so, it struck me that, you know, there is a huge disconnect there with the
health care system, because clearly the resources are there.
And this, you know, people always complain about having to wait.
And I basically do the same thing.
She, I don't want to wait two weeks.
Kids in pain if she needs an operation to remove cartilage, then we've got to get this
movement.
But I think what happens is the national health care system probably buys a block of time,
because they use the same MRI machine.
I, I omitted that piece of my explanation, because it's very expensive equipment.
So there's, it's kind of a time share.
But I guess the only bite in blocks were very small blocks.
And, you know, and this is where it breaks down for me, because everyone who's in line for an MRI
is going to get the MRI, whether it takes a day, a week, or a month, or a year.
Eventually, they will get the MRI.
So to me, it seems like you're going to be paying the money anyway as the national health care provider.
You know, why not buy a bigger block of time?
If you, and I'm sure that comes down to the actual accounting of how it all works.
And maybe politicians sit in, in parliament and say, look, we're going to get to everybody
eventually.
So why don't we just spread the cost out over more years?
Could be, but it was just, to me, it was, you know, almost flabbergasting that here's this resource
sitting there.
And if we go through the national health care system, which has to pay for it anyway, you have to
wait, even though it's just sitting there idle, not doing anything.
You basically eating a wattage from from being in low power state or whatever the
held these things do.
So, uh, interesting.
Good old ducto called in through the voicemail line.
That would, of course, be the UK voicemail line number, which I want to kind of program that
went into your memory as well.
So feel free to assume.
Remember, add the plus for extra savings.
You're just, make it functional on your mobile no matter where you are in the world.
So here's the, you see the sparkers when they show, so that's noise.
And so I really know these buses and love that song you, uh, open the show is.
I don't know if it's echoed, but fast, or buses, if you call them.
And in Scotland, and I think in some sort of thing, then sucks fast.
And that's the type of cheapest, if you're blind, I don't even know what it is.
The minted fruit for some sort.
But it's cheapest, cheap, cheap, you get, and you see, uh,
poppers of it, get to the round the trains late at night, aren't you, ladies, and seen that.
And it's also a favourite with, uh, you know, um, the same kind of people who's,
jinx tenants, or such and fruit.
Um, anyway, I sure have a great funny, a band called Buckfast.
Okay, bye.
Well, there you go.
Learn something again.
Buckfast.
Yeah.
Bravo uniform Charlie Kilo, Fox start Alpha Sierra Tango, Buckfast, Buckfast.
Buckfast.
Yeah.
I got to get me a bottle of that.
Is that a brand name or is that the actual type of liquor?
And, and Joe, a doctor, call me from somewhere quiet.
Next time, will you?
I hated, you're always calling me from the bus or on the street.
What castle won't let you call from the house?
Are you embarrassed that you're calling me?
Come on, baby.
I don't want to hear you.
That's such a sweet voice.
You know, I've been, uh, on the, uh, window side of the personal computing equation
for quite some time now, uh, being a lifelong Mac guy just totally got fed up with all the hardware
failures couldn't deal with it couldn't live with the in unreliability.
And so I've been using windows and actually, uh, friend of mine last night said, uh, hey,
you know, do you miss the Mac?
Because I was, uh, actually, uh, using the Mac for, uh, for the I chat for the, for the conference,
uh, for the management meeting.
I said, you know, when I sit behind the Mac and of course,
I don't have, uh, a Mac book pro.
I have a G4, which, uh, oh, only, uh, a year ago with state of the art, 17 incher, uh, which, of course,
has been repaired and come back and other batteries crap, you know, the batteries fully charged,
you unplug it, you use it for 10 minutes batteries completely dead.
So that's how I received my power book back from Apple.
I sent it off with a good battery as far as I can recall.
Maybe this is their safety measure.
It's probably one of those batteries that blow up so they just make sure it doesn't work anymore.
Um, and then I was thinking, you know, do I miss anything, uh, of the Mac on Windows?
And besides some of the display things, the Mac is really, it's just slower.
I know the MacBook Pro is probably on par with my via dual core, etc.
So I'm not going to say that's a real comparison, but I really don't miss anything.
Some things do just work simpler and better.
Um, not know, not even better, but just simpler to configure things, you know,
less steps, more intuitive, but once you kind of understand, uh, Windows and you've got it down,
it's no problem whatsoever at all.
And of course I got rid of that stupid, um, uh,
tele-tubbies background that XP comes with by default.
I don't know if something is that.
I put a nice OSX background in.
Um, for some reason, and I don't know if there was a Windows update,
that's another thing I don't really like, um, you know, sometimes that you turn it off and say,
you know, don't reboot and do shit without me saying it's okay.
And sometimes it just does it anyway when it's a critical system update.
Um, but now when I open up dialogs within an application.
So let me just use cast blasters the example, because that's where it's most irritating.
Um, so it'll open up a, you know, so you say, okay, I'm going to add a file to cast blaster.
It opens up a dialog box.
So not a folder.
The folders are okay.
But in a dialog box now, it opens up and it is in the pretty much the default,
which is sorted by name.
And I want it in detail mode.
So I can see, you know, um, file size, et cetera, any other information.
And I want it listed by date, uh, last modified.
And I want the most recent modified files, which is the ones I just put into that folder,
because that's how I prep my show.
I want them to be on top.
So I don't have to go hunting around for stuff that I've just added.
And, you know, so I'll, I'll set it and it takes two clicks for set it to details.
Then it takes three clicks.
Then click on date modified.
Click on date modified again so that it sorts from, uh, most recent at the top.
Select the file, uh, click okay.
And I'm good.
And then I do it again.
And it opens up in the same default mode.
And I've tried everything.
I've tried opening up the dialog box and set the properties.
You know, I say, sort this way.
It just, it won't stick.
I don't get it.
And that is really frustrating.
Please, if you can help me on that, it will be greatly appreciated.
I think I'm doing everything right.
Um, in fact, let me just do it right now while we're here together.
So I'm going to open up.
Okay.
So it's opened up my DSC-bin folder.
And it's listed now.
It's in, uh, what mode is it in?
It's in list mode.
And it's sorted by name.
Uh, I can see because it has the folders at the top and then it starts with the one
o one o one o one and then pretty soon it gets to a.
Now I'm going to go to details mode.
And I can see date modified.
Of course, I have to expand the dialog box because date modified is the third one to the right.
Click on date modified.
Click on it again.
And so now I can actually add something.
So let me just add something here.
Okay. Now I'm going to do it again.
I open up boom.
It's in default mode again.
It's very, very frustrating.
And then, you know, so when you open up and then you right click, there's like properties
and properties gives me sharing, customized.
That's all.
Then do anything for me advanced.
God, this is the stuff that I really hate about Windows.
Okay, okay, that's not it.
Please help me out.
Can't you help a brother, huh?
I really want to understand how this works because it wasn't doing this before.
Something changed.
And then, I don't know.
So Windows is successfully added over three clicks per part of my daily routine.
I'm liking that.
Hello, they spirit is coming my friends.
Steve Webb here, host of the Life Spring Family of podcast.
Beginning on December 1st, the Life Spring Advent calendar will make its debut.
Together with James Cooper of the WhyChristmas.com website,
a brand new Life Spring member will begin that will enhance your Christmas season.
Each day from December 1st until Christmas,
James and I will be talking about Christmas traditions from around the world and helping you to
focus on the real reason for the season.
We'll discover how many of our traditions began like the exchanging of Christmas cards,
bringing trees into our homes, and the singing of Christmas carols.
And of course, we'll talk about the very first Christmas gift, the birth of Jesus.
If you love Christmas like I do, I think you're going to love the new Life Spring Advent calendar.
You can get the show at advent.podshow.com.
James and I are excited to bring you these very special new shows.
Come join us for the Life Spring Advent calendar from the Life Spring Family of podcasts
and WhyChristmas.com.
Nice.
Advent.podshow.com.
I would mind knowing why we exchanged gifts and why we bring trees into our house.
I'm going to it right now, Advent.
Of course, it is automatically switched now to advent.btpodshow.com.
Which is kind of cool. We can finally got that working.
That was also a source of some of the feeds messing up.
Is this the kind of the digital version of...
Remember you had, I don't know if you still have the calendars and on December 1st,
you get to open a window and there's a little thing behind it and then all the way through to the
25th. Let's see each day from December 1st, they'll Christmas. James and Steve will be talking
about Christmas for today. I'm going to get this show.
So let me get this show. Get it and I'm going to add it to, which led to, I got a channel here.
I've got my on the go. Here we go. On the go. It has no episodes yet, but...
I'll be ready for when they do come up. Cool. Most excellence, Steve.
Christian Leonard says, Adam, in case someone is making notes about where splendid is distributed,
yesterday I spotted it on the shelves, then to shop here in Norway. I don't drink coffee.
I don't drink tea and I otherwise have no use for an artificial sweetener. However,
being confident about the fact that I could probably use it in some way or other, I bought a box.
I now have a large box of splendor on my shelf and no idea on how to use it.
But every time I hear splendid mention, well, I look over it and say myself long lines,
well, now why the hell did I buy this? I can say one thing for sure. If I ever find a way to use it
and get a regular use for sweetener, I'll be using splendor and thinking of the DSC every time I do.
I had some in here from SRAM Idol. You mentioned on a couple of shows ago that the
all tracks were now able to be purchased from the podcast music network. I just checked them out.
I went on to podshow.com as I do quite a lot of these days. It redirected me,
so they're going to podshow.com and redirects me to btpotshow.com. I wonder whether that's something
that you've got to have a new K. But if I'm going to be saying, you can still get to podshow.com.
But I can't, I always get forward to btpotshow.com. Which is fair enough. It's more or less the same
content and the same basis available. I was trying to find this button to buy music and I couldn't
find it. I don't know whether I just can't find it or whether it's just not a feature on btpotshow.com
and the podshow music tracks are only able to be purchased in the US. So if you question there,
I don't, I've been interested to hear what you have to say about those. Thanks a lot, mate. Cheers.
Yeah, I'm in command. You're going to tell me something. I don't know.
Okay, a couple of things here. First of all, we have integrated the pod save music network
into podshow.com but really the audience side of the equation. Which the pod save music network didn't
do a very good job of. That was really intended for a place for artists to put their music up
and for producers of podcasts and other independent programming to put them on a playlist,
mark them download them and report back that they've played them. Now, we have show note links.
I'm this is music.podshow.com which I'm here in the UK now. Let me just double check. I'm pretty sure
that music.podshow.com just want double check. Yeah, that just results to music.podshow.com. That doesn't
go to anything else. We have their links in there on each artist page. The takes you to an artist page
which we call the show notes friendly link. And I just opened up a ticket for this in our
system because I want this changed. So if you copy that link, which I've been doing for the,
you know, even though the new podshow pluses out, I've just been kind of, you know, a creature of
habit, right? You just right click that link copy it, paste it into the show notes. That will actually
take the listeners to the pod save music network. The old pages where you see, you know, it's a
sparse page. Let's put it that, that, you know, no recommendations. Now, the new artist pages
at podshow plus include a lot more information. They include, you know, recommendations. There's
a playlist that pop up all kinds of groovy stuff. And actually, I think, you know, much, you can actually
get all the songs from an artist, put them in your collection and you can play them through the
dashboard later if you want. There's all kinds of great stuff. But we need to change that link
obviously because we want, I want my audience to go see the cool page, not the sparsely, you know,
kind of hop-alongacity page that we've had for how, what is it now two years, almost. We've had the
pod save music network up, something like that, two years. Yeah, getting close to two years.
So that has to change. And I believe the second part of your question, Simon, is, you know,
if when you do go to podshow.com slash music, any artist that has songs available for purchase,
it'll show up in that little play or next to each track, it'll say buy, it'll be highlighted,
if you can actually buy the track. So now there may have been some weirdness when you call this in
because although it sounds pretty simple, really creating a localized version of something big,
like podshow plus, it is quite complicated actually. You know, you're sniffing out where IPs are
coming from and, you know, there's stuff that you that you do want to portray in the English version
stuff. You don't, and of course, with it brings a whole nother set of what we put on the home page.
I mean, it's a whole bunch of things going on and on that actual cutover, you know, DNS has to
propagate. It's all kind of technical jargon. What I'm saying is it all sucks, but it'll fix itself.
I think, so far it's working for me and the UK feeds are now also updating quite nicely.
Hi Adam, I'm the manager of a band called Three Blind Mice, an aims Victoria, or sometimes I'm
called the Farmers Wife. We've had some tracks available on the pod save music network for pod
gasters to play for about a year now and we're really grateful for all the pod play and all the
positive feedback we've received. However, we do need that pod play to translate into sales and we've
heard you for the past years saying it's coming soon. It's coming soon. Soon, all artists will be
able to sell tracks on the pod save music network. That's exactly how I sound. That is exactly the hype.
So imagine how excited we were earlier this week to hear you say, finally, we could make
our tracks available for sale directly through pod show plus. Yeah. Well, I paid off the promise
didn't I? So I rushed to our artist page on the PMN to check it out and I found out the payments
to artists will be made by check in US dollars. Well, with international banking charges the way
they are, that means there's no point in us making tracks available for sale yet. Okay. I'm going
to stop you right there. Not with that attitude, madam. Not with that attitude. What do you think
you're all you're going to do is nickel and dimes off this stuff? If that's all you think you're
going to do, and that's all you deserve to get. So, you know, yes, I'll let you finish your comment,
but I just can't stand that attitude. We'd end up paying the bank more than we receive.
What I wanted to ask you is do you know if there are any plans to make payments to UK artists
via PayPal? Thanks, Adam. I don't mean to seem ungrateful, but we have waited a year.
Oh, and since you asked, I'm a folder. Yeah, it's crunchier. Oh, the mood takes me.
Nice voice, by the way. Mm-hmm. But before I get wrapped up in that, that's strange because,
you know, we don't actually touch the money. As you know, pod show takes nothing of the sale.
We have priced it competitively. If you'll, you know, each track of the pod set music now work,
it should be no better or worse than anything anywhere else on Napster or iTunes. So 99 cents,
industry standard, I like that. Nine cents of that goes to a company called Click and Buy.
And we chose Click and Buy specifically because they deal with international payments.
And I believe they're even UK based. So it makes no sense to me that they only hand out checks in
US dollars. And I, of course, I totally understand what a pain in the ass that is.
I still have checks here from Amazon laying around from when I had cents sale on the home page.
And it lets like $1,000. I just like, I can't be bothered. You know, it can be bothered.
But it makes no sense that they're not cutting checks or sending out payment in in local currency.
I can understand some, well, no, I think it should be, you know, dollar should work. It should do
the euro and it should do the pound. Does it do euros, by the way? Because anyway, I was quite sure
that one of the main reasons we chose Click and Buy is for their international aspect. So,
I shall inquire on your behalf, madam. And while we're at it, let me see if I can make up for it with
a free blind mice, too.
I don't know how to be any pain, so I'm gonna sing it out like I think of the same as me.
One more between us until we believe in a star and a big offering free.
Look to the north when the watch's always gather up your soul from the light.
Here's a way while the wind turns around to a time yet on time.
And the star sends you back to the sun.
Look to the north when the watch's always gather up your soul from the light.
Here's a way while the wind turns around to a time yet on time and the star sends you back to the sun.
Here's a way while the watch's always gather up your soul from the light.
So I don't know how to be any pain, so I don't know how to be any pain.
One more between us until we believe in a star and a big offering free.
Look to the north when the watch's always gather up your soul from the light.
Here's a way while the watch's always gather up your soul from the light.
The watch's always gather up your soul from the light.
I will say that tracks and music have been completely commoditized through the series of tubes we call the internet.
I can't tell you if I compare the time Christina has talked to me about a song or track versus the band that is playing somewhere.
This is a piece of feedback about the show where we're talking about Heather Mills and if I recall correctly,
I did step up a bit for Heather Mills who of course is the former Miss Lady McCartney or not even former yet because they're still married but they're in a very public messy divorce process.
Which of course is made messy and ugly by the press?
I think there's so many people calling in from the UK now.
Just a follow-in from the last call.
Just a bit about Heather McCartney or Heather Mills or whatever you want to call.
She actually comes from not too far away from her.
I'm going to ask her to hear the press go on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on.
Just a funny grubber who's even behind boyfriend's back Marianne and well just a divorce together with Penny.
After all, it's certainly done.
It's not really up to when you're as to George but the last set up very important charity doing landmings.
I'm letting you know I understand that's what you've been up to.
And you know if you don't need to time and money to bury prominent causes.
And I just think it's about saying that the press just back off because I honestly don't think this is coming from men's of the public.
And this is the public really honestly don't give a damn.
I'm not really interested.
It's just probably crap in all stuff to stick on the front of your glossy magazines.
Let's have a go and a little headache.
Because we've got nothing better to do with our things.
I'm not more like for for.
I think she's a she's a canny last she's a bunny last.
You know good luck.
I just talk this thing doesn't get any worse for them.
It's a bit of a shame the Satan people split any two people.
You forgot fold or scruncher but I'll let you slide.
I really appreciated that comment because you know and when Patricia was doing this as well and boy I.
I'm sure she sometimes just may want to pop me over the head because I'm always the guy that says don't believe what you fucking read there.
You know how many times have we been on the front page and it's something completely stupid fabricated or so far from the truth that it's just not the truth.
And everyone believes it's the truth and we've definitely in our own little microcosm of the lowlands known as the Netherlands.
We've had that out of control thing happened to us.
It's it's not nice now.
Luckily it wasn't about divorce or anything like that but it's it's horrible.
And this is really nothing you can do about it and let me just say there's no difference between glossy magazines and web logs.
It's human nature people like to do this and and I just keep going back to that one that one comment I should look that comment up again.
The Robin and Suzanne from the inside works at me.
You know it's people projecting their baggage on to you don't accept other people's baggage.
Of course when it's when it's in the papers or when it's on a web log and most many people read it you know they happily accept the baggage.
I'll take that because I've got some of that and in fact it goes nicely with this piece of luggage I have over here.
So it just happens and you know we shouldn't be quick to judge.
Absolutely.
I had a whole I had a whole point to that and I was really going to go somewhere with it.
Oh yes I know.
This is why I love watching I'm a celebrity get me out of here.
I don't know if you've seen this program I don't know if it's as successful in the United States as it is in the United Kingdom but it's big.
So ITV program 8 million viewers at least that's what they had historically I don't know they just started so I don't know where they're at.
But I love this because you know you you find yourself being surprised at how judgmental you are about people thinking oh this guys like this this this this woman is probably like that.
And and of course there's a lot of manipulation because it is edited but in general it's a reality programming you do get to see a lot of the true people but again there's a lot of manipulation that takes place on the.
The the production side literally making it more fun to watch by trumping things up which is very easy to do very very easy in video particularly.
But as an example David guest is on I'm a celebrity get me out of here on the UK version he of course is known as Lysamonelli's ex and you think it would be this real slimy.
Dork and he's actually got something got a vibe about him I'm really starting to to like this guy.
And you know what the person who is the most shallow the most self obsessed and has the largest ego.
Is a journalist who is in the jungle.
She reblairs sister I forget her first name.
She reblairs of course wife of the prime minister of the UK.
She's horrible she really really is and and by the way David guest called her out before that even went in the jungle just when they met each other he said oh you're the.
You're the person who was in the newspaper saying that I had a horrible face lift and I shouldn't stay in the sun too long because my face will melt and you know she was busted and she said oh yeah you know these were flippant remarks I shouldn't have made them and she didn't really even say I'm sorry.
But you know she had also just you know just one often just said stuff because she was being interviewed for going into the jungle and there you go celebrities.
You should say the journalist was more offensive.
Then then.
I'm getting stuck on what I'm trying to say.
It just blew me away that this came from a journalist or she calls herself a journalist I have no idea if she really is a journalist.
But anyway you got to watch this show it's fantastic because if you watch it kind of with an open mind and say wow I really thought this person was different than that good or bad.
It's just because you really don't know someone until you actually know someone which is why I defend Madonna which is why to a certain extent I defend defend Michael Jackson.
You know people who I've met and you know it's not like I hung out with them for days on end but you do get a vibe from someone when you look them in the eye your neurotransmitters are in close proximity actually making some kind of connection.
You do get a different a different view about someone.
What should we do well have you 41 minutes forget about it one more song.
Nigel who brought Thomas Dolby on to the podcast music network keeps emailing me and says dude you haven't played this song yet and you have to.
All right now I don't know problem clear but lie on your daily source code.
I don't know I don't know I don't know I don't know I don't know I don't know I don't know.
I don't know I don't know I don't know.
I don't know I don't know I don't know I don't know I don't know.
I don't know I don't know I don't know I don't know.
I don't know I don't know I don't know.
I don't know I don't know.
I don't know I don't know I don't know I don't know I don't know I don't know I don't know.
I don't know I don't listen to the slick mainstream radio anymore because you get sick of it.
I don't mind it's nice to hear something that's really slickly produced.
I have a lot of stuff happening at the Pod Show crash pad in London which of course I'm not able to attend now but I'm checking in regularly.
I hope you join me because of course we'll have all the usual suspects I hope to have an
and more great ones like it on the BT Pod Show media network.