Delta Sierra Charlie 3-2-7
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass
In the next generation radio content in my ears
We don't need no sticky and grizzly
I like to think I'm flying into the street
Oh, fantastic!
It is time for the Tuesday
I woke up on the wrong side of the bed
My communications don't work out really
It's not the fish of the daily source code
I'll calm down though after the sun
It's Tuesday everybody, how are you doing?
They?
Youúps?
You?
They didn't hear that song
I don't know
Who wouldn't tell them about
Do I really your feelings
Wait, can you listen
We've only been there
Sing initely
Not you
I don't know
You could tell them about
Don't listen
It's true to you, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it
Is true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's
I like it, but you're our show finally hit at the end
You're boleh-the-son, I'm gonna do it,
Don't mountain, don't listen to me
You'll never agree,千er still,
Don't behave so clichable
Don't misunderstand me
This is one of those mornings, this is take two of the show by the way that's far for the course for all my technology.
ValleyLodge, that song from the Podsafe Music Network, music.podshow.com, everybody's the daily source code.
Have you ever had one of those days where you woke up and the first thoughts that start to flood your head or about what you were thinking about before you went to bed?
Well, that's what happened with you this morning and it's just kind of gone downhill from the air.
I started off with me thinking about my mom, she talked to her last night, she's home.
But the doctor said that she had just about every single side effect and negative reaction you can have to chemotherapy.
Every single one, except the effects were three times the intensity to boot.
And they'd never seen this before. And when I hear that, I get really angry because I'm immediately thinking they did something wrong.
And I just want to find out what happened. She's home though.
The good news is her appetite is back. She's eating like a truck driver, no offense to trucker Tom, of course.
And she really feels much better. She's regaining her strength and she has her appetite. That's the most important thing.
The doctors now say they want to do, they want to try some radiation instead of chemotherapy.
So I'm going to go there on Thursday and get the full scoop.
You know, that stuff just came into my head this morning and like, and then as I did a quick check of the email,
I noticed that something was very wrong because there's no way I wake up in the morning. There's only two or three emails.
Well, that was the case because my email server. I have a server that is dedicated just a handling email sending it off to wherever I wanted to go.
Of course, can store messages as well, even though I might read them only on my Gmail account or elsewhere.
And I don't know if the box is crashed, you know, I can't just can't figure it out.
It's all those trouble tickets are on the way, but luckily.
And this is, this really is a testament to the importance of having a domain name.
And really being able to manage the DNS yourself through like GoDaddy for curry.com.
I actually use network solutions, I think.
It's not just a vanity plate for your email address, your website address.
It really does help you control your entire digital identity without being dependent upon hardware,
which, of course, is exactly what's happened in this case.
So it's fairly simple for me to go find an email provider.
I was thinking of doing this anyway, and of course, usually you don't do it until it's too late.
I was thinking of outsourcing all my email to a company that just does email only.
Actually, I've gone with the run box after about an hour and a half worth of research.
I really like what they're offering and they let me trial their stuff out.
And they, you know, I have an understanding of MX records.
So, but even there were some helpful screens there and, you know, to help me make the transfer of the MX records from the DNS.
And the founders of the internet, man, those guys deserve a medal.
They thought of some really smart stuff with this email stuff.
So if something goes wrong with the receiving email server, the sending email server will actually hold that for up to three days.
You've probably seen one of those messages that came back saying we couldn't reach this address after three days.
I'm giving up.
So the minute everything was reconfigured, my Gmail just started flooding up again with mail.
Of course, that in turn bounced, you know, all these attachments coming in at the same time.
I filled up my blackberry email box and, and that started bouncing stuff.
So it was a pretty interesting morning and I had to reconfigure email addresses for Patricia, for Christina,
for my mom, for my sisters, you know, all this stuff.
And then to boot my blackberries busted.
I have the new one, the new flashy one from Singular.
Thing is the, what is it?
8700.
It's the thumb wheel.
And I'm going to call this a hardware fault and I've already said help.
I need a new, a new thing, although it's not going to be easy because, you know, what?
I'm going to express me one from the US, hopefully.
I think it's hardware because
scrolling down in any function I do pretty much works, but scrolling up the minute you do that.
It starts to interpret that scrolling up as commands that are not the commands of scroll up.
So if I go to the message list, for instance, I'm scrolling down.
It works fine.
But if I scroll up, then all of a sudden it goes to select folder.
And if I keep scrolling up, it starts throwing really weird characters.
Like a Y with an oxalnte goo over it.
And if you scroll down, then the Ys are capitalized and then it's completely hose.
And even from the main screen, you can see scrolling right to select something works normally,
but scrolling left it'll get stuck and you have to roll it three or four times.
So it is the Achilles heel of the blackberry.
And I hope this is not something that goes across this whole range of new model.
Because that sucks.
Just sucks.
And without it, the device is virtually rendered useless.
Yeah, I hate that.
So I'm going to say there's something else I was going to say about the blackberry.
I can't remember.
Was it about the e-mail stuff?
Anyway.
So it just went from bad to worse.
And then I started recording the show today's show.
And I don't know what it was.
But my just stuff, I was hitting button one and sound two was going off.
So I had basically just rebooted everything.
So I'm rebooting everything in my life.
I'm going to start this day over all fresh again.
And I got to keep my eye on the countdown clock because I was talking to PW Fenton yesterday.
Now as you know, PW produces the, the Syria stars 103 pod show four hours of podcasting entertainment
from six to ten Eastern three to seven Pacific.
Syria stars 103.
And this of course is a simulcast of the podcast on serious.
And you know, yesterday, so I was, I found out that there was a discrepancy between countdown clock.
It's timing.
And cast blasters timing.
And then I said the PW yesterday.
Because of course he has to deliver 24 minutes and 30 seconds exactly for the satellite window.
And he comes within a thousandth of a second.
He said, dude, you were 14 seconds off.
I'm like, what?
He says, yep, ever since you, you know, that new sound came in.
You started using the new sound when the satellite window closes.
You've been off by 10 to 14 seconds.
I'm like, I don't get it.
First of all, I have different timers, different time, different value showing up in two different
timers running on the same computer.
And then it started to dawn on me that maybe this, this to Shiba just can't keep time.
You know, I've never had that problem on the Mac.
So actually today, I'm running the Chimoo timer on the Mac, which I used to use previously.
I have there 14 minutes and two, one, zero seconds left.
Already the countdown clock is one second slow.
And I started them exactly the same time.
So I'm going to keep my eye on the Chimoo timer.
And then we'll see what the discrepancy is by the time we have to close the satellite window.
But what the hell is this?
Computers, it's not like the essence of what a computer has to do.
Is it, you know, at least it should be able to keep time.
Something weird going on.
And then the question is, you know, how do you call a timer function in windows?
I mean, you don't actually have to write the whole command.
You know, you have to write your own timer that counts back or what are the dependencies.
It can only to me seem like it's the computer chip.
And it's just an outrage that these things won't keep time.
And I'm telling you, I bet you it's the PC, I bet you the PC.
I don't think this is.
And of course, there may be a different clock that it's using for the internal sound card.
God knows what's happening.
Here's something interesting though.
This will kind of show you how I'll just say mainstream media thinks about podcasting.
But it's not entirely true because I had to listen to this clip of Howard Stern, which AJ auto sent me.
I had to listen to it a couple of times before I could analyze.
And I'll walk through it with you.
I think it starts off with a caller who calls in and I think the question was,
you know, how come I can't get the Howard Stern show as a podcast.
If you've been following the news, then you know that there's a,
I think there's a 15 minute daily podcast of highlights that's being made available,
but not the entire show.
And by the way, I think that I don't think I would listen to it myself.
I love listening to Howard Stern, but it has to be a live thing for me.
And actually, I'll talk about that a little bit more.
When we listen to the comments from Howard in the crew about podcasting.
Check this out.
I don't know how you do it, but it seems like it's possible.
I mean, but I'm not doing a podcast.
Well, I was just wondering, you know, I'm talking about the whole show.
I said, oh, just some of it.
No.
Already there's some hostility there.
That was coming from the back.
So the question was clear, but the answer is a bit surprising.
You know, Pike, if I go to a podcast, I'll start soon.
I'll start, like go knocking door to door and do it.
You go into a person's home and just do it.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right. Well, thank you.
But I don't understand those podcasts.
You know, Adam Curry, I think his name was.
The guy who used to be on MTV.
I listen to his show, the podcast show.
Yeah.
Okay.
First of all, Howard's no dummy.
He definitely checks out everything that has to do with all forms of media.
So of course, he listens to the daily source code.
Of course, he's probably listening to it on stars 103 because it's only one channel
click away from his two channels.
And I'm sure that he's, he's very clued into what's going on.
Don't take that act.
You know, don't buy into that for a second because he totally knows what's happening.
Now, of course, he, he, he thought I was just some.
Well, check this out.
No, what that is.
It's weird.
I don't know what he's talking about.
I think he's a big dumb guy.
MTV.
But he.
Let me tell you a story about Howard Stern.
I think it was 88.
He was just becoming a meteoric star in New York.
And he was, and to me, he was, of course, I didn't know what podcasting was in 88.
But he was breaking all the rules.
He was a truly the original podcast.
And when it comes to a non-traditional format, he was still was constrained by frequency
and by time, which is, you know, how radio is divvied up and how it's monetized.
But he was doing something, you know, he wasn't doing the WNLNBC and all that stuff.
And he came to MTV to do a shift, which in the time of things like a four hour block of
programming, you tossed the videos and stuff like that.
And it was all recorded just in segments and the segments are shipped off to the Network
Operations Center and then they'd insert the videos.
Well, rather, they'd insert the VJ segments into the stream of videos, which, of course,
is a thing of the past.
And I was actually out for most of the day for whatever reason I came back.
And he was with doing segments with downtown Julie Brown.
And I was kind of remember her, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And she was supposed to be doing the show with him or whatever.
And Julie Brown and I definitely did not get along.
He might call it some form of love, hate relationship.
But the balance was much more towards the age than the L.
And so I was like, you know, I'm not going to go up and, you know, everyone's kind of hovering
and, you know, everyone was a fan of Stern.
I just didn't want to be one of those gawkers, you know.
So I, and especially not with Julie Brown because I knew that she'd say something completely
fucked up that I didn't want to hear about, probably put me down and just, you know,
and I just want to talk to the Howard for two minutes.
So I figured I'll catch him later.
And they wrap pretty quickly and he left.
And then the next day on the show, he was talking about me.
I was an incredible jerk and I was arrogant.
I wouldn't even say hi.
And I was like, oh, I was crushed.
I was crushed.
And I don't think he's ever forgiven me for what he thinks was a snub.
But it wasn't.
And I remained a big fan of the show.
Anyway, maybe I'm just a big hairdo, fact from MTV.
It's come up with some kind of technology and all these podcasts.
Now, I hear people yelling and screaming about all kinds of crazy things on there and I never
know what they're talking about.
Doesn't any do a podcast podcast is no fun.
You know, why?
Because you need something where a group of people can get together and people can call
in.
That's the life of the show.
You do a part.
Now, this is a very profound.
See, I learn my lessons.
It's a very profound statement.
And this is, and this is what, how I know Stern knows exactly what's going on.
Because the format of his show, indeed, really only work works best in a live environment.
You have to have the, at least the feeling you can call up and talk to them live while they're
on the air.
That is a big part of what Howard Stern is about.
Robinson Tyre role is the news.
And if that's not, you know, the way they format it their show.
If it's not news that is happening that day, it doesn't work for the show.
So there's no reason to listen to that in delay.
I mean, I've had many opportunities to even subscribe to bit torrent downloads through
podcast feeds, to be able to receive the Stern show in a regular basis.
So you get four hours of a show.
It's something entirely different.
And this is what mainstream media needs to figure out in Lachon to.
They have the unique selling proposition of having regional and in many cases, national
live coverage.
And they have to start adjusting their formats to make that work.
For them to be able to monetize and continue with their business models, because when it
comes to asynchronous communication, and in this case, let's just call podcast information
or entertainment, it's a very different format.
And it's a completely different type of audio information and entertainment than is done
with live radio.
Of course, you can do the same with live radio, and it's done all the time.
But that's not the most effective use of it.
So when he says he doesn't get it, I think he understands extremely well what's going on.
But it will not work for the Howard Stern show.
I have to agree with him there.
And also, let's be honest, even if he were to change the format to an asynchronous version.
And the podcast where pay for play has an example.
I don't think at this stage of podcasting, we would have been able to come up with almost
three quarters of a billion worth of dollars in guaranteed money.
You know, the 500 million plus the 220 million in stock, et cetera.
No way.
And Howard's not a young guy anymore.
He's, is he 50 now?
Is he a 47, 48?
He's up there.
How many more deals is he going to make?
You know, this is the retirement deal I think.
So, and he's still breaking new ground by making this step.
So make no mistake.
Let's see what else they're doing from your living room.
Yeah.
Well, doing it from your living room, obviously in an asynchronous format can be very entertaining.
There's a lot of stuff that come out of living room that a lot of people are listening to.
You know?
Yeah, I thought, you know, was the podcast is big shit.
Podcast.
You don't deserve to smell my shit.
Well, clearly Howard has never, nor Robin has ever listened to the daily download because
they are you do deserve to smell his shit.
I, that those last couple of comments kind of include me into let me know that they're
not worried about it because they're all paid and they've, and it's great and they haven't
fun, but it's on the radar.
So if you're listening to stars 103, every single weekday afternoon between six and
ten Eastern three and seven Pacific, it's the pod show line up, taking it all up through
10 o'clock on the East Coast, whining up with some pod sake music, all kinds of shows.
East radio.
You know, that, if Howard is listening to the source code, I'm sure he's listening to
As your confirmation, match, not go out and get him girlfriend.
Okay.
Uh, I'm so confused, I had to start over again because everything was all met.
I messed up.
Did I already talk about the countdown clock?
Like, I don't know if I did, I had to, gosh, this is horrible.
There's a discrepancy for some reason, something is going wrong with, I really, I don't
know if I just talked about this and not, I did the first time I would start to record
the show.
Uh, there's something wrong with the countdown, uh, timing on my, um, I might just sheba laptop.
I was talking to PW Fenton yesterday and after, you know, we discussed all this about
running two timers and that the countdown clock was off compared to Casplaster's timer.
He told me that the whole show was still off by 14 seconds, which means, for some reason,
this laptop is, can't keep time.
You can't, you know, I'm not going to believe that it's hard for any application made
by an independent or by Microsoft to actually just display time and count back.
Isn't that like a primary function of, of computers?
So I'm running the timer on the Mac as well, because when I was using that, it worked fine.
And so there I have three minutes, 47 seconds left.
Looks like everything's still pretty much on time.
So maybe when it comes down to the last few seconds or something, it starts to, you know,
really shift out of phase, I don't keep my eye on it for you.
In the meantime, let's, uh, let me see, what do we have here, when we roll out this, this
audio comment, it's pretty long one.
I was talking about Patricia's ability, apparently, to feel the, um, the raise or the,
the radio frequency coming from a cellular phone mass located very near to the cottage.
And I got some interesting, um, comments back about this, the most interesting one, probably,
is from Trucker Tom.
Yo, Adam, Trucker Tom here.
I was listening to DSC 326 where you were talking about, uh, Patricia's arthritis, uh, doing better.
It's really likely that, uh, wherever she is at, uh, she's getting minerals in the water.
The mineral content of the water can make a big difference in something like arthritis and other health problems.
I was skeptical at first, but after taking the mineral supplements for only a short time,
I noticed the difference, uh, I had started experiencing some aches and pains, including aches and
pains in my hands, and after I started taking the mineral supplements, uh, those aches and pains
went away.
I'll send the bottle to the pod show HQ, so Patricia can try it for herself.
The only thing I ask is that, uh, you let me know how it works out.
As always, you can find everything I'm involved in at truckerphoto.com.
See, yeah.
Trucker Tom, where the signature trucker Tom to.
Of course, you know, that is, we hadn't even, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
Hadn't even taken that in a consideration.
It was a very unscientific test.
I have to admit, just saying, well, you know, there's no cell tower there so that must be it.
But Trisha actually, I think I'm going to talk to her about this and I think she definitely
knows where to get some extra mineral pills or whatever, and I'll ask her to check that out.
So far, actually, it's not like she slept here for two nights and has had incredible
pain, so it could be something else.
I did tell her, though, I said, if you keep telling me about this, if I keep hearing
cell tower, cell tower, we're moving regardless, whether it affects you or not.
I don't want to hear this for the rest of our days here until we've built a new house to
go live. And I'm moving out of here if I have to listen to that crap.
Some transmitters send the strongest signals out in a certain angle of vertical degrees,
as John Vermont, so the signal hits the ground fairly far away from the source.
You know, this thing is on top of the hill. We're underneath it, so I'm pretty confident that it's
rolling straight down towards us. And we've probably got the strongest amount of signal possible.
He says, if I would get to choose where to live in relation to a 3G mass, for example,
I would choose to live under it. And that works signal. I would get would be very
weak compared to what the guy a kilometer away gets. It would still be more than enough for me, though.
Well, I of course can get a radiation meter and I can check it out and see how bad the radiation
is, but I think we're pretty much in the full, full blown view of this stuff.
It's interesting because the neighbor across the street has horrible migraines. I'm starting to think
there's really something to this, you know? All right, those of you listening to us on stars
103 on the serious satellite, our window is about to close Pacific Coast. Hellway is next
followed by Madge Weinstein, then Donandru. And it looks like the countdown clock is two seconds off
compared to the old method. Now, I've timed it on three timers, three. So one of them has to
come at least relatively close. I would hope. We'll no doubt hear this from Professor Pdeb when he puts
everything together for the pod show. More comments on the GSM cell phone masks.
Hey Adam Jack Elias from the GetJacked podcast. Getjacked.Honomas.com with an audio comment on today's
DSE326 two audio comments. I guess first on Patricia's ability to sense the electrical fields
and radio fields. I totally believe that that she can sense that many people can.
And interesting, I used to work for a large one of the largest manufacturers of cellular
telephones. And as a rep and we were a given a a wrote scripted response to reply whenever
anybody asks us about the specific absorption rates, which is what the federal communications
commission calls the the microwave energy rating as, you know, to safety rating for coming
off of a cell phone. And basically, we were to say, quote, all name of giant multinational
corporation here, cell phones are designed manufactured and tested to comply with FCCSAR guidelines.
And then someone would say, hey, Jack, see the black helicopters are coming from. Yeah,
someone say, hey, Jack, but, but, you know, as it's safe, and I would have to say, all
name of giant manufacturer cell phones are designed manufactured and tested to comply with FCCSAR
guidelines, which leads me to another point. Not a people use headsets, whether wireless or wired
to avoid holding the cell phone next to their head for fear of these absorption rates of
microwave energy. My question when I was a rep, especially, but even now is always this, if you
don't want to hold the cell phone next to your skull, how is it safer to clip it to your belt
using a wired or wireless headset, where it is now radiating its energy next to the the soft
tissue of, you know, your kidney area versus the thick skull area. You know, very, very good point
there. I always keep my cell phone in my pocket and I was wondering about what that means to my equipment.
Still works last time I checked. Stu Coates says, Adam, listen to Delta Sierra Charlie
326 loads of information about the effects of cell phone mask can be found at mastaction.co.uk.
It's the National Campaign for the sensible sighting of masks. You'd be shocked where phone
masks are actually placed. Some schools have them in the playground. Well, for all the information
that we don't have on these things, that definitely doesn't seem like a very good idea.
If you get more about that and also I hadn't received any information about death right if you know
what's hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Yes. I have a message for you. Would you mind talking
into the microphone, into that microphone? Okay. I have a message for you from your pilot.
From the wing commander. Yeah. The wing commander wants to it's urgent. He wants to talk to you.
He was trying to call you, but he couldn't reach you. Okay. Well, I can't talk to him right now.
I'm doing this. I know. I said that to his wife. Okay. So this is the message. So we can't fly Thursday.
Is that what the message is? I don't know. It was very urgent. Of course. He was somewhere
calling from from the air. He was in the plane. He was in the plane. I think. Well, that's not going to be
easy to reach him. No wonder he couldn't reach me. I don't know. That's what he's wife said.
Okay. Who called? Who called? He and him or Mercurife. So who do I have to call him or her?
No, uh, uh, nay. Who? Really? Okay. Thank you. Message service.
I've been watching Commander in Chief. I bought all the all the back episodes on the iTunes
music store. Oh, man. I don't watch them. I'm the video iPod. I just watch them on the on the
power book. And interesting. You know, I just sit there. My name on business. No other audio
applications open except for iTunes. And I'll be damned if just about every single episode, the
audio looping problem didn't show up. Very, very, very annoying. It lasts for about eight seconds. If you don't
do anything, then it goes away. What a great show. Oh, man. Uh, let me see. As I said, lots of audio feedback
today. Oh, um, the numbers are in for Mark Cuban's projects. Mark Cuban, you know, he sold
broadcast.com for, I don't know, he put, I think he put a billion dollars in his pocket is what they say.
I don't know. You can't look in anyone's pocket. But he set up this network of digital
cinemas and uh, Steven Sondberg created a movie called Bubble. And uh, this movie is being released
simultaneously in their own uh, chain of theaters. I think they have 32 theaters on DVD and on cable
TV. I think it's on their high definition uh, channels. And uh, so uh, this is actually an article that
I found at variety.com. And that kind of slamming him because, and of course, they're right, you know,
the gross of 32 theaters, these new digital theaters was $72,000. So, you know, that real
boils down to about 30 people per theater. Now, of course, you know, you can't compare
this movie, Bubble, which I've not seen. I'm sure you can't compare it to a King Kong, right?
I think like that, they'll get a huge draw from people. But I do think it's, it's pretty brave
what, what he's doing. Um, and, and of course, you know, let me see what is how does this article
and it's kind of mean. Let me see. Uh, uh, but for the most part, uh, the audience was basically
what one expect at a low budget art house film, people in the industry and connected to the film.
There you go. Another non-pro, a young woman who said she was just visiting from New York,
said she was seeing the movie because she was friends with the casting director and then melted
into a crowd of six other people. So mean. Um, but anyway, so it did work, but it seems like, you know,
I don't know how the DVD sales doing. I think that they're 100 million, 100,000 DVDs that
ship, not sold, but were shipped. And of course, they added on their TV stations. I hope you
pull that off. It's a big game. Very, very big boys, game that he's playing. Uh, shoot too bad. The
serious sidelight window closed. This was for the serious said management. Yeah, I'm this is Louis from the
cause of totally connection. Hey, I want to tell you a real live story that might help you
sell a few more serious videos. So anyway, we sent you our promo right and it was, uh, we before
last. And, uh, a download daily source code and we didn't you know, look at the show notes.
Hey, the quality connection promo is going to be on the show. So I'm happy to see it, right?
Now, like, hey, if we're going to show before the little beeper thing went off, that means we're
going to be on serious radio too. So what do I do? I take the freaking day off work. I go to
end of my local electronic retailer and I buy a serious radio. Now, I'm not kidding. I used to be an
XM subscriber, but I went and bought a stupid serious radio so that I could sit at home and
sit to clock that night and listen to our promo, go across the serious airways.
Guess what happened? It was Martin Luther King day. Somebody dropped the ball. I'm not sure who
it was, but, uh, we didn't actually get our promo plate on serious that day because, uh,
yeah, well, whatever. Anyway, uh, hope I could give you the opportunity to play our promo again.
But, uh, sure that I thought I'd let you know that, hey, you guys sold a serious radio and
I guess the only thing you have to do to sell more of them is just keep playing people's promos
for the first time. It used to work for me. Anyway, thought I'd let you know that, uh,
when we say tailwinds, it means something totally different. So, uh, I'll see that one. Anyway,
yeah, check us out with quads to wikinection.com. I'll do it. I messed it up. See, I spent so much time
bitching and moaning about my, my own problems that I just didn't make it into the satellite window.
Okay, send me another promo. I promise you I'll put it in early in the show. Quasitility,
boys. I'm so sorry. Hey, I found out that the indeed is absolutely no problem to submit as many
podcasts as necessary, um, from one account into the iTunes music store. So, um, I haven't said this
up yet, but I'm going to see if, if I think what we would want to do, it'll be very cool. It seems
like it would be a web application that we could make. If you make it, I'll use my account.
Basically, the submission process is fairly simple, but you have to have an account.
Um, so I'd like to set something up so that anyone who has a podcast in a New Zealand,
was it, uh, was Australia as well or just New Zealand? Well, if you can't open an account
because there is no iTunes music store for your region, then we just make it like a simple web
form so you could use, like, my account or anybody else's account to submit your podcast. I think
we could, we could set that up. So, um, I'll get to work on that. And this is actually Richard
von Iperin, uh, said that he has been able to, uh, to open up to submit many podcasts through one
dot mac account, which makes sense. Makes sense. Uh, okay. A couple of promos, maybe I should call
the wing commander while you're listening to these. Hi, Adam Scussie, John for the brand new
little show podcast for 22 years. I've been in radio for the last year. I've watched an MV.
Guys, like you had to create a freedom to do what you wanted to do while I sat my little
air-conditioned studio getting yelled at because the bits were longer than two minutes.
Well, as of two weeks ago, I am no longer a morning man and commercial radio. I know
longer work for clear channel. I can do what I want. And I have my own podcast, scotted.com
scot.h.com. Check it out. And one thing I'd love to do is I'm playing music from the pot
safe music network. How about we set up an interview show with the artist? Would they be into it?
Would you be into it? Let me know. I'd be into it. 22 years in radio. I've interviewed a lot of
people and I think it'd be fun. Let me know. But check out the podcast scot.com. Thanks.
Hi, Adam. This is Copper from the garagepunk.com podcast. And I just wanted to thank you on behalf
of all of our podcast show producers for fighting the good fight for podcasting and for all of the
work you put into the pod safe music network. And I'd like to invite all your listeners to check us
out sometime. The garagepunk.com podcast is basically a podcast radio station similar to a college
republic radio station where you'd hear various different programs with separate show hosts.
This gives each program its own distinct personality and helps broaden the scope and appeal of
our station. And so far it's been very successful. We currently have seven shows in rotation,
basically one new show per day, and we'll be adding more soon. All of them features some form of
primitive rock and roll. We're talking the really trashy obscure stuff here. All the new garage rock,
garage punk, greasy R&B, broken blues, sleazy surf, frantic rock ability, obscure 50s and 60s
rock and roll in garage 45s, 70s pro do punk, power pop and wild and wooly modern garage punk noise.
Let's face it. This ain't the kind of music that will ever have much of a chance on commercial
radio or most mainstream media channels, but is perfect for podcasting. Not only because of its
obscurity and independent degenerate nature, but because it's pod safe. All of it. So check us out at
podcast.garagepunk.com and subscribe. You'll be glad you did, but your neighbors may hate you for it.
Thanks again, and stay sick.
Do you believe anything is possible? We do. We're our flink. We believe in an internet that
saved from virus, hidden scammers. We're Earthlink. We believe your personal information should
be just that, personal. And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a fellow.
We're Earthlink. Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet
experts can do for you, Earthlink. We revolve around you.
Hi Adam, this is Laura Nostomon speaking. I'm studying physics at the University of Innsbruck in Austria,
which is one of the leading universities when it comes to quantum optics and quantum information
or quantum computing. Friends of mine and I recently came up with the idea of a physics podcast.
Would it like to answer questions sent to us why are you male? Or discuss with our listeners,
why us type about interesting physical phenomena and dichanist stuff? We're going to do this
podcast in English, although our mother tongue is German as Austrians clearly. Because first of all
we want to reach quite a big audience and on the other hand we're going to practice our scientific
English as a matter of fact. And yeah, I'd just like to hear your thoughts about this. Is it worth
doing it or anything special to consider when starting a new podcast directed to quite a few people?
Yeah, thanks for your time Adam and I'm really looking forward to hearing your thoughts about this.
I'll send you promo when we're ready to kick off. Thank you for now and bye bye.
I would kind of dunk. Of course you should do a podcast. You're crazy? Of course.
The only tip I can give you is just do something you're passionate about or you're interested in or something
you want to talk about. That's it. It doesn't have to have any more or any less. That'll make it
compelling to listen to. I guarantee it. I'm sorry, this is a two-spliff day.
Definitely give me some insight into string theory.
If you've never heard, what is that? The astrology podcast?
Man, what is the name of that thing? Hold on. I might as well look it up for you. I want to do this.
I love that show. I've just looked in my subscriptions here.
Draw low G. What was the name of it? I've used this an example so many times.
Astrology. That's not astrology podcast. I can't find it. Okay, but there's lots of them out there.
It's really I think depending on the audience you want to reach. If you want to reach an audience of
your peers, then you'll probably want to keep that pretty technical and it may not be interesting to me.
You can also, of course, always try and translate it to people who are just interested but have no idea
what you're talking about. So that may be a bigger challenge. But certainly could be a fun one.
Particularly if you're trying to hone your English language skills at the same time. So it could be
pretty cool. I'm going to skip over a whole bunch of stuff. What are we at now? We're like at 40
minutes. Okay, listen, let me do the final feedback I was going to do for today. What else did I
have to talk about? Oh, yeah, I want to talk about Google.cn. Here's something I discovered.
This is the Chinese Google. If you miss Spell, a forbidden word, like Tiananmen Square,
it will still give you all relevant links, which it thinks are close to what you tried to spell.
So definitely type in Tiananmen Square. If you don't know how to spell Tiananmen,
all the better, but even try to purposely miss Spell it and then click on the images link, which is
the squiggly second to the left or right next to the far left link at the top of the page.
It's a Chinese character, which stands for images, I'm sure. If you mouse over it, you'll see the
URL actually says images. And then you'll get all kinds of very graphic pictures from Tiananmen Square
on google.cn. So there's clearly all kinds of ways around this. And I'm starting to think more and
that part of the deal is Google just can't talk too much about it. Maybe they're actually doing
some really good things here. I do give them a little bit more credit than all the bashing of
I've seen going on. All right, final piece of feedback. It's about digital sales and the
pot-safe music network, but it leads into our last pot-safe song of the day. So I do want to play that one.
Hey, I'm at Stank Cody, the drummer of the reverse engineers. I wanted to give you some feedback
regarding how much the artist should receive out of digital sales. And I do think it's best to
take a look at what we actually are most artists are receiving from the various big digital
download services out there. And even an idea, music net actually gives us only like 2,000
cents of a cent. It's like 0.002 on each sale through music net. So that's like one of the
streaming services that is not the actual song, which is part of the radio stream. Now, obviously,
we make a lot more money on iTunes. In the iTunes and in the U.S., we make 65 cents per download.
Canada, iTunes, Canada is pretty close to that around 64 cents up to 67 cents per download.
And our per digital sale in MSN music, we make about 70 cents per download. It's a little bit
more than iTunes surprisingly. With iTunes Europe, we actually make a lot more than we do in the U.S.,
we make up to 81 cents. In iTunes, UK, we make up to 83 cents. So it's interesting to see that over
in Europe, for some reason, we make more on our iTunes sales than we do here in the U.S. So
have this comparison to the pot safe music network. I think if even if we had 70 cents per
download, I'd be happy with what we'd be making. I love the fact that pot show is actually going to
not be taking their share at this point. I mean, you guys are setting up the system. You obviously
want to beta tested. But even if you guys took 30 cents, we'd be still happy with that because that's
seems like the average right now of what the digital sales services are actually taking as their cut.
But we're really excited. We can't wait to see what happens with these sales.
It's great. We're looking back on how the pot casting has helped us so far. We're actually
getting a lot of our visitors are coming from the podcast. We've been played on. It seems like
about two thirds of our hits these days are coming from podcasts that people are finding
either through the blog for the podcast where they have a link back to our website or just the podcast
we're mentioning. It seems to be driving a lot of traffic our way. So we're really happy about that.
But I just want to give you some feedback and the people play one of our songs that we really
cool. We've got a new single called Sunshine of the Shave that we've released on the podcast.
I just want to give you a few back out of it. Thanks again. Thank you again.
All right, your wish is my command.
Another love knife to the sunrise.
Here's the sunshine in the morning.
Another mistake in making what's this trip worth taking.
It's the sunshine in the morning.
There's the silver in the sky.
There's always sunshine in the city.
There's always sunshine in the morning.
I'll get a blast for the long day.
She was the long road until next time.
And nothing to stay in making.
Now I'm just going to take you.
Can you still remember in the morning?
There's always sunshine in the morning.
It's all been in cover.
It's all been there.
It's all been discovered.
There's no need to walk more than anyone else.
I thought what was to change in the night.
And there's always someone upstairs.
A smile, who is so spa staff.
There's saying it's been great
and the sunshine room changing.
Um, there's always sunshine.
There's always sunshine
and there's always sunshine
Alright, I like that message. There's always sunshine in the shade. The reverse
engineers from the Podscape Music Network find the link to their page at music.podshow.com.
Alright, thanks for listening to me, bitch, and today I'll be back tomorrow. Hump day
edition. I'm sure things will be looking up a little bit more because there is always sunshine
in the shade, everybody!
Another Pod Show Podcast. Stick it in your ear.