This is Delta Sierra Charlie for 8-7, off-deutch Fiat Zibon, Bavoski, Chitiria Vosimthium.
Warning, if you have impression that Adam Kerry is in your head, then it is not an illusion
he actually is in your head.
In this situation, only one thing can cure you.
The great taste of Splendaz Wittner.
It was $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio contenting my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this journey.
Fantastic, it's Adam Kerry.
It's my day.
It was a car of setting sun.
There was a car couch.
There's a gig on my shower.
It was all this this.
All these things that I wanted me wasn't somewhere
You were around the wheel and I let it turn
We'll give everything
We will y'all like no one's been here for
You were queen and I was king
Yeah, no one's ever left me wrong
So if that gets to that dream
I can see what it is I'm waiting for
You'll be coming through my door
That's why I'm waiting for
If you come into my door
There was a weather rush
It was as fast as I could run
It was a switchback
I couldn't keep myself from coming under
It was all these things
All these things that I wanted me to learn
You were around the deck and I let it turn
We'll give everything
We will y'all like no one's been here for
You were queen and I was king
Yeah, no one's ever left me wrong
So if that gets to that dream
I can see what it is I'm waiting for
You'll be coming through my door
That's why I'm waiting for
If you come into my door
We will give everything
We will y'all like no one's been here for
You were queen and I was king
Yeah, no one's ever left me wrong
So if that gets to that dream
I can see what it is I'm waiting for
You'll be coming through my door
That's why I'm waiting for
If you come into my door
You'll be coming through
That's why I'm waiting for
If you come into my door
Mould doing rules
to the band, whiplash, on the pot safe music network.
Damn, nice way to kick off the week.
Everybody, how you doing?
Welcome to the Daily Source Code episode 487
as expertly introduced by Comics Dream Blogger.
Coming to you from Curry Cottage,
in the affluent suburb of Surrey,
known as Gilford, it's very busy.
Told you all these weeks are going to be busy.
How you doing?
How you doing? I had a great weekend.
Of course, you know what I did Friday, right?
The solo channel crossing Saturday, a big shoot day
in the Potcho UK shortage office.
Yes, the trendy shortage office, which is,
I think shortage is the new so-how, is it not?
It's very urban, very crumbly,
but it's the place to be.
And that's where we've got our office slash studio,
doing a lot of promo shoots and stuff,
getting ready, ramping up for the big launch,
week of November for Potcho, BT Potcho.com,
Potcho UK essentially, which very excited about.
We had OJ there, not that OJ.
OJ UK, I guess we'll call him from now on.
I hope you might have seen it London Live,
which we did from the roundhouse during the digital
musical awards Olivia,
and Dr. Cockney.
So it was, yeah, it was quite the mess.
I'll have to say, but it was great.
I'm really looking forward to this launch.
It's going to be fantastic.
And then, I'm still pushing.
I'm still pushing to be at PodcastCon UK on the 18th.
I'm hoping that I can stay the 18th
and then fly off the San Francisco on the 19th.
And then, let's see, yes,
so they did some more flying training,
actually, only a couple hours with Captain Dan.
Now that I've, you know,
now that I've got my bridge is a little bit bigger.
My bridge is arbed.
Now that I fit into my bridge is,
I guess, after the channel, the channel solo crossing,
he took me out for some unusual landing circumstances,
which means crosswind, tailwind,
believe me, you really don't want tailwind
when you're landing for us me on the one.
But also a flatless landing.
So if in case you would have an electrical failure,
then you still have to be able to land the plane,
which is not that hard to do.
You just come in a little bit faster.
And then, of course, an engine off emergency landing.
So good workout.
I think we did.
We flew down to Goodwood.
And everybody loves Goodwood, don't you?
That's a Chichester airport,
which is really nice.
They've got three runways, all grass,
all bumpy, all messed up, and plenty of traffic.
So that was good.
Hey, Saturday night,
so we're just chilling out.
After I got back from from the shortage offices.
And all of a sudden, boom, big explosion fireworks.
And of course, we are the foreigners here.
So I couldn't quite figure it out.
But I have been told that this was a bonfire night.
And this is for Guy Fox Day.
Now, I'm going to paraphrase the way it was explained to me.
In 1700, something, a rather.
There was a guy, I think named Guy Fox,
who tried to blow up Parliament,
the English House of Parliament.
And he came just inches away from doing it,
but was thwarted.
And they celebrate that here in the UK.
With bonfire night on Guy Fox Day,
by blowing shit up and having huge bonfires.
Which, of course, I'm all for.
I just wish I'd received an invitation, you know?
I had him.
This is Andrew Kerr.
I've listened to from a few miles north of Oxford in the UK.
As we're getting near and near at Sioux, bonfire night.
So I've always wanted to do a fireworks night.
It would be up in the air and sea.
Or fireworks in the bonfire night, not from the air.
I just wonder if that's something you'd ever done or considered doing.
Or even if, you know, you're allowed to fly like aircraft at night.
In the UK, I don't know if you're a clumpy and drunk smuggler.
Or something like that.
But anyway, I'm back.
I've always had to do a sea of fireworks from the air.
It's been a folder.
I'm not going to show you again.
Bye.
Yeah.
I think if you're Colombian drug smuggler flying around
at night, you're very lost.
You've got the wrong route.
Yeah, of course you're allowed to fly at night.
The question is, where can you land at night?
Ferrokes closes at dark.
Most airfields close at dark.
But I am also licensed to fly at night.
As long as it's under visual flying rules condition,
I can actually see the ground and see what the heck I'm doing.
The problem would be where to land.
So it could be done.
It could go to farm bro or one of the other places.
But a lot involved.
And if I had known about it, I actually might have set that up.
Because yeah, of course, of course you can, you can fly.
I don't think these fireworks go up to 1500 feet.
I sure hope they don't.
Who knows anything about fireworks?
So on fortsite didn't get to your voice mail on time.
Otherwise, I might have actually considered trying to set that up.
So let me give out the voice mail number early then.
Plus one 201 625 635 7 or as you can sing along with the jingle.
And I'm got to tell you man, a life saver.
Living here in Italy for last 12 years.
This channel on the network thing that you put on the other day.
That's always charged as they are.
Man, now I can watch American television and get away from this incredibly bad Italian.
Going to rock and the stock.
Air sea television that really sucks.
Soon the sister knows about this also.
So great thanks for the tip.
And fuller.
Yeah, the TV unit works thing is pretty cool.
And I forgot to put a link in the show notes last time.
But it did show up in comments.
I forgot to post that.
But I do appreciate it.
TV unit works dot com.
This is a appeared appear based streaming video application.
And what they've done is they've hooked it up to I guess a cable box somewhere.
In San Francisco because you can get ABC, NBC, CBS.
You can get Fox.
You can get Comedy Central.
In fact, here's a little tip for you all.
A tip from the pod father.
If you install this TV unit works, which of course will only work on windows.
When you quit the application, make sure that you quit the little system tray application to for two reasons.
One, you'll continue to be appear on the network and you may not want to do that.
Although I'm happy to leave it open when I'm not using my bandwidth.
I don't care anyone else can use it.
But it was was this.
This was sometime early last week around 4 a.m. all of a sudden.
This racket, you know, in the middle of the night.
And Patricia really freaked out.
She's like, what's going on?
And she jumps out of bed.
And I'm like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And what it happened was even though I'd close the application.
I left the system tray thing running.
And for some reason, it decided to start playing Comedy Central.
It was the Johnston show.
Very loudly coming from the studio B.
Which of course is located right next to the master bedroom.
Our bedroom.
So that's just a little tip.
You might want to quit that.
If you don't want or turn the volume down in case something funky goes wrong with that application.
But I have to agree.
It's fucking cool.
I wish they had an east coast feed as well because, you know,
the eight hours time difference.
Actually, what is it now?
Seven hours time difference has the US fallen back an hour yet.
We got an extra hour of Saturday through Sunday here in the UK.
So I think I only have what now.
Like four hours difference with the east coast and seven hours difference with the west coast.
Very nice.
You probably noticed, if you listen to East radio,
that Madge has been gone for several weeks.
And quite frankly, I wonder if Madge is coming back at all.
Richard Bluestein has been hosting the show.
I was Richard Bluestein, which kind of up in the I like Richard.
I like the way he does the show.
But I have to tell you honestly, I really do miss Madge.
And there are more people who miss Madge.
This is now the political season.
We are just about a little over a week away from politics and people getting very involved.
Well, the attack ads are already coming out.
Because you could, of course, choose from Madge Weinstein.
You could vote for her if she were not in the hospital and were back on the podcast.
Or you could consider Cheryl.
But it's getting nasty.
The attack ads are out.
The soldiers dying every day, fighting for freedom.
What kind of person when champion the rights and freedoms of the downtrodden?
Yes, the kind with a badge of woman named Madge.
Madge Weinstein of East radio.com would have voted against the angelic clump of cells
that will one day become a beautiful cognitive capitalist system.
She would have voted against the effective and cost-conscious program that prevents the murder of unborn children
and could spend a little education and health care for the already-burned children.
Madge would have voted for pedaling, smut and graphic descriptions of lesbian, fisting and homosexual punchfucking.
Calling you to arts that it reaches the undeveloped ears of fetuses.
Madge says she cares about East more than cancer.
Even though she herself has lost a breast to the cancer.
Don't you want a candidate that can stand up for the right to be wrong and can tell you.
They are an elemental hospital instead of making up lies about being the undisclosed hospital in Mexico.
Don't you want someone that has lost something more important to cancer than a breast?
Maybe one in a fourth of a long?
Sheryl and Macau scheme is a smoky woman of honesty.
A woman not afraid to be four of the children in every sense of the word.
Madge would have believed that Sheryl is only about making creepy sounds and low production quality.
But using her popping others when she exerts the effort to please her own listeners.
Maybe if Madge were not so lazy, actually puts an effort into her own program, maybe then.
She could stop attacking such a beautiful and lovely people like Sheryl and Macau scheme.
Madge will refuse to take part in something simple and principal, even if the principal is retarded or self-serving.
Sheryl is a complete horror, and will do whatever she wants, especially if so, doing will benefit her.
Would you rather vote for an elderly, lying lesbian fetus murderer or a beautiful 25-year-old woman,
smoke her and honor three-fourths of a long and lover of all children aboard her not?
Voting for Madge lets the terrorists win.
Voting for Madge is anti-freedom anti-children and just downright wrong and immoral.
A vote for Sheryl is a vote for the children.
Freedom honesty, everything right in the world and beautiful.
If Madge wants in her better priorities, you want to be having to hear those.
This election season, exercise your rights by supporting the children and visiting her whole daughter.
I'm Sheryl Macau scheme, I have approved this message. I'm nay.
Payed for my whole daughter work.
I should have warned you about that one beforehand, I guess.
Truly disturbing. I have no idea what it's about.
But I do mismatch, that's for sure.
I've got a hurry up today going into the city staying in the city this evening.
We have early morning meetings in presentation. I told you it's really ramping up, getting real busy.
But I have been quite busy with home base with Brian Longest, who is our director of operations as well as he is also a lawyer.
Don't hold it against him.
And we've reached out to the appropriate organizations and we have started down the path of arranging certain performance licenses under certain restricted conditions for something very important, very dear to my heart and I think to yours as well.
I'm proud of you casting with Adam Curry.
Adam, are you ready to be stumps?
Bring it on.
He's back, everybody.
Adam, this is hit test number 70 on the daily source code.
According to all the emails and other responses to the last weeks, he tests the one time return of the hit test in the daily source code.
It's still very popular, so hopefully this can occur more often.
And of course, that all depends on the possible licensing agreement, so hopefully you can tell me more about that.
In me time, there's a hit test, three intros and three answers and this is intro number one.
What the fuck is that?
Oh, what happened?
Oh man, what is this?
Oh shit.
It's over?
No, no, no, this can't be right.
Hold on a second, something.
Oh shit.
Don't tell me it only got like partially downloaded.
Oh no, and I deleted the original.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh crap.
I can't.
Hold on a second, let me see.
I'm so sorry about this.
Hold on a second.
Let me.
Oh, I suck.
Does Jan have the new one up yet?
Crap.
I can't believe that.
Well, just goes to show.
I don't cheat.
I don't listen to it beforehand.
I'm so sorry.
I was so fucking ready for that.
Crap.
All right.
I'm sorry.
I'm a loser.
I'll have to have Jan resend it.
I don't know.
Maybe he got mulched on his end or mulched on my end.
And I didn't even get the first one.
Sorry about that.
Crap.
That really harsh is my mellow.
All right, then.
Adam says, Edgar.
I'm a folder in a long time.
I want to be Mac user.
I love Macs.
Ever since 1996 when I first worked on a Mac.
I wanted that little machine in 1997.
I was working as Webmaster and ISP.
Had a performer in Windows and T.
Now I'm wondering, what does that make me buy?
I cannot afford a Mac and my old to Shiba is almost six years old.
But I'm back at the university.
They're only IMAX.
There's more people wondering about this correlation between folders,
Macs, scrunchers, windows, and there's more.
Hello, Adam.
Yes.
This whole thing about Mac users and Windows users,
whether they're folder, scrunchers.
I have to have an idea.
Or it's, well, not an idea about.
Some thought.
What do Linux users do?
Are they all folders or scrunchers?
They can?
You know, I use these books for a while.
I'm going to get into our PC.
Well, that's when I use this book.
I've got the moment.
So, won't go to do it with this PC.
It's a good insight.
And I both fold and scrunch.
Is it the same with all my users?
Oh, my God.
We're on stuff.
Yeah.
I'm talking something quite random.
It's an imaginary cigarette.
Oh, what the fuck?
Anyway, Adam.
I'll call you back later one day.
Bye.
Yeah, please do.
When you figured it out, what Linux users do?
I don't know, man.
Those of you, uh, hoping to hear the lady Patricia,
we had it all planned out.
But then, of course, uh, I came up with the announcement
that I had to record really early earlier than normal.
And she said, well, that's exactly the same time.
I just put my hair on point then.
We don't have to be a node.
It's under time.
It's not like you.
Hi.
This is Lauren from Seven Stories Podcast.
Come to sevencast.potshow.com to hear some of our great interviews
with Jeff Smith.
Do you lean one way or the other?
Mmm, let's say boxers.
No briefs.
Uh, or, uh, one of my doing tonight.
Boxer briefs.
Matthew evil.
You have been described as the love child of Billy Joel and
Elton John.
I think that's my favorite quote so far.
How's that for a, uh, uh, an image that you won't be able to get
out of your head?
How that's created.
Uh, me up the other night.
Isn't that a fact?
Well, all it takes is some soft music and two superstars
and a bottle of red and a bottle of white, you know.
There you go.
I have a port.
These are the nerds.
Not us.
We're, we're doing stuff that's important.
It's making a difference.
It's changing the world.
We're inventing stuff that is making a huge difference.
They're just playing games.
So I don't, I no longer, you know,
I don't feel like we were the nerds in high school.
They were the nerds.
Uh,
And Cali and Neil from Geek brief TV.
She thought I joined a camp because I kept talking about what
Adam said.
Adam said that.
Yeah.
He started listening before I did.
And he was always talking about Adam this and I'm,
Who is Adam?
I was, I'm too younger.
Well, maybe not too young.
But I didn't grow up knowing who Adam Curry was.
Mm-hmm.
And just this craziness I'm thinking,
Who is he?
And what is he doing now in your life?
And don't forget to subscribe
because they're more on the way.
Join us on the web at Seven Stories.
That's me.
Seven Stories.
Let's go our story.
That's cute.
Listen, I got to listen to that.
Now that I hear that Cali is talking about me.
I didn't know Neil was in love with me first before Cali.
Crap.
Ah, Neil.
Uh,
Sounds a little bit like a show.
We've got going on here, which we'll launch with pod show UK as well
at bdpodshow.com as who's on it,
which highlights podcasters,
podsive music stars, et cetera,
not just from the UK also from the US obviously,
but it's a new format that's we're trying out.
Pretty excited about it.
On the clever little pod Halloween special,
we dine out with zombies.
Uh, this is Herman.
Uh,
Vernon and Dave.
Man.
Now, let me get this right.
Herman, you want it flat.
Uh, Vernon, you said flesh thing you've made.
Dave?
You sure you want the cod?
Mmm.
It's full of bones.
Yeah, I think so.
Three types of flesh, please.
And for you, sir.
And just a green salad, thank you.
It's all on iTunes,
Brickcaster, and it clever little pod.com.
Like, come on, Scoop.
It's Delta Sierra Charlie 47.
Ah.
Random worry.
Are you a blogger?
A hotcaster, video blogger, web 2.0 programmer.
Are you a marketing or PR type?
Citizen journalist.
The center of your online social network.
And you'd be in San Francisco, November 9th and 10th.
Rainjams, social media club,
the social media cast,
and a group of intelligent and good-looking sponsors,
want you to join us for web 2.2.
With the same people who brought you the web 2.1 event last year.
Web 2.2 is an uncomference.
Down the block from that other web 2 conference.
They're charging $3,295 in vitally.
Or is only $32,95 and everyone's welcome.
You can help us create our own agenda.
Two days of intelligent discussion about the growth of the net,
social media, identity, disclosure,
word of mouth marketing, and more.
Now work with some great people,
and did I mention we're going to have an awesome party.
Check web 2.2.org.
That's web.
The number two,
heoint2.org.
The point is people.
November 9th and 10th in San Francisco.
I got to thank Peter because I know that he was just able to squeeze
that into the satellite window in Syria stars 102.
We were preempted.
Wednesday Thursday and Friday for a whole bunch of chick shows.
And that we're back on the air now.
All right.
It's going to be tough.
I think to get a show out early tomorrow.
I'll probably have to do it when I come home late.
And we've got a lot of stuff to do tomorrow night.
We have a pod save the queen.
Christina wants to do.
She's ready again.
Of course she uses it.
This is a tough year for her.
This is a very important, very important school year.
And from here, after this, she goes to what they call the UK college.
That's before you go to university.
So she's really been doing a lot of her course work.
She's really hitting the books pretty hard.
Last minute, of course, you know.
It's a tradition in the family.
But she's really working it.
So for her to squeeze that in, it's pretty cool.
And we're also going to do a B.G.
Blast.
What's it?
Episode 7.
I think in which she announces the winners of the hollow screen contest.
Who gets an all expenses paid trip to Bush Gardens.
Now, since the hit test messed up.
And of course, the next opportunity I have, I'll bring you that one.
I feel so stupid about this.
I mean, maybe just didn't download completely from Gmail or something.
And then, you know, to save space after I've received it, you know, a big attachment.
I deleted it.
So it's now gone.
And I emptied the trash as well on my Gmail.
So it is definitely gone.
It's something else I want to do here.
Let me see.
This is a member Joseph Jaffee.
Bend over bitch.
He was in New York as I told you when I was on my panel with a chat.
And from YouTube and Chris from my space.
And he talked about it in his most recent podcast across the sound.
Let me see if I can find it.
I just wanted to play this bit for you because I thought I was pretty funny.
I see what's being completely honest and open.
It's only Joseph can be.
Here we go.
Being wanting to meet.
And it was just an amazing, amazing experience.
Just to kind of admit more people.
I admit.
Help me.
I've got a link.
What about who you are?
Get to my part.
I remember your name.
And that's going to come to me.
It always does.
Come on.
Jeff Bukett.
Thank you.
What a right.
Another.
It's the sound.
And by the way, it's no a person that I wanted to tell you about it.
You can tell this is completely honest.
Right.
So it was a terrific day.
And then I got to be honest.
I was invited by my friend Sean Finnegan.
Here we go.
That's all of digital for OMD.
The real, I mean, the tipping point for me, the reason I went was to meet Adam Curley, who
was there for the first time.
And I was a little disappointed because I arrived late.
I was leaving on mono's event.
I arrived only to hear the final 10 or 50 minutes of a panel that Adam was on with Chad
Hurley from YouTube.
Someone from my space.
Some muckily mucked my space.
I didn't know who he was.
You know, just clearly didn't remember his name either.
I think much autumn memory is definitely going quickly.
But I heard Adam at the back end of the panel.
And disappointed it only in the sense that I didn't hear the whole panel.
And also I just very briefly went up and met him and Ron Bloom.
Just shook his hand.
He is a tall, tall mother fucker.
Let me tell you.
This guy could have taken up basketball.
A long time ago and been pretty good at it.
He's a very good looking guy.
He's sent the props back to me originally about my looks.
And I want to return the favour. He's a very good guy.
And when he sort was me, he smiled and just said to
Very precious words.
Bend over.
That was good meeting you two, Joseph.
You couldn't check out Joseph at across the sound.com.
A dot net, sorry.
One last song for the start of this week.
Brand new Matthew Ebel every color.
I was kind of blind and standing.
I thought that all that I was handed
Was all that I was to see
All I had was just this pencil
You saw me sticking a grey
And I've been living in this pencil
But I'm breaking out today
There's another very colour
And I've every colour
I think that's for the right
Is that I've every colour
Not just regular white
Blank white paint when it feels so bright
I'll light it outside the light
You give me a bite of sunlight
With every shade cast
Hold around and I'm unstable
But I don't really care
World's not spinning now when I'm stable
Kind of everywhere
Is that I've every colour
And I've every colour
The rainbow what a false
Stayed fast from the light
Is that I've every colour
Not just regular white
I've every colour
Is that I've every colour
And I've every colour
The rainbow what a false
Oh, it's entertaining, Matthew Ebel.
I love every color from the pod save music network.
You can find it at link in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Okay, got to get out of here, get the show up on the pdn,
and then off, as I said, to London tomorrow morning.
You know, just as cable networks now are offering telephony service,
so you can get your television, your internet, and your telephone from,
and I guess also your mobile is, don't they connect that all into one account?
You know, that's what now the cable companies are doing.
So you see, of course, the, with the deregulation or pending deregulation,
which is pretty much happening around the world telephone companies or telcos
or now getting into delivery of video because they can.
And they, and of course, if you look at British telecom,
they have the proper network in place to actually make something called IPTV work.
So the question is, you know, what are they going to show on their set-top box?
Well, that's what we're talking about tomorrow.
It's, you can imagine that we got some pretty big ideas for those guys.
So I'll keep you in the loop on that, and talk to either tomorrow afternoon
or early Wednesday, but I'll get four shows done this week.
I promise, that's for sure.
Take care, everybody.
Adam and pod show.com.
Have yourself a great week.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Thank you.