Delta Sierra Charlie 339
Delta Sierra Charlie
Almost live from Northern California
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass
Than the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into the future
Dear Adam, I'm an old lady in Pennsylvania
That listens to your show every day
I'm not a podcaster but I love the technology
I'm a kidney cancer survivor and I wanted to say that I love this song good day
You played on Wednesday's show, it touched me
I play it over and over
Take care of the good work
57 years young in Pennsylvania
I'm a friend of the fact that we are here
Must that make today a good day
A good day
Wake up as time derives in shine
Just another day in this life of mine
And take a deep breath
My lungs still took a pass
He's got to be a good day
Because that has to be stretched out my arms
I fail out my memory
To be true-binated
No end of the possibilities
He's a mine
It fills my blood
Never so becomes old
As I swing from the bottom line
Some with time
I finally feel fine
Days as it should be
Of my own design
There's no alarm clock
Need to when I'll rest
Need to dream mine
Decating with them's arm
All that I need tonight
And choose a bad day
And I'm on choose to be
Because you can't have a good day
Unless you believe
Every day couldn't battle
Both be around
So let's focus all this
Into the pocket
It's down to a bread
I don't want to talk about the bad day
But my friend
All the fact that we are here
Then be next to Jay
I don't care
Now come I should, I don't care
Go there
Don't let them talk about the bad day
And my friend
All the fact that we are here
Then be next to Jay
I don't care
Hey!
Hey, hey!
You'd make the sun find the horizon
The home shadows stretch out
A risk-air flies in
Figuring in the room
Cooling the conversation
Cones sets in
The moment of meditation
The whole base playing
Back in my mind
The whole of people in the faces
In this moment of time
The summer
Wearing smiles on this bottle
In the misery
Some find tomorrow
While others become history
Now we're the wild end
And my people off the wall
The artists love
One of the stars
One of the solar lights are darkness
Could be the dumbest
And a good convenience part
Has learned about respect
Between the close and the pharmacy
I've been the farmer in the season
Not the harvesters
Learned as old as seeds
And I leave where the harvest
Now everything
Goody, valuable
Be around
So that's what we saw
Listen to the five
And it's not all the other day
Yeah
No more
Talk about the past
Hey, hey, hey, hey
For my friend
I want all the fact
That we are here
We're here
That makes the day
Oh
Oh, today
No more
Oh, now
Talk about the past
Oh, my friend
Oh, now
Oh, now back then
We are here
That makes the day
The goodness
But it
Yeah
Oh, now
Yes
Don't you diverge
All the fact that we are here
That makes a day of good day
No more life, the door to the bad, the bad day
No more life, all the fact that we are here
That means to take our door, our good day
I wish you could be here to see this
The sun just coming up in Northern California over the bay
Looking out over the entire city from the 24th floor of the Curry condo
This is truly magical
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
Yes indeed, it's bright and early on Tuesday morning
Decided that I want to make this week
An early morning week, so we can kind of be kind of in sync with each other
I'm sorry for the European friends who are listening
You'll just have to get the show a little bit later
When you're at work or maybe on your drive home
You know, all this talk that we do about monetization
And sponsoring and advertising and selling songs on pod save music network
You know, it's emails like the one that I got from Mary Gautier, the one that I read
Just in the intro of this song, that is the reason that I get up this early in the morning
You cannot, there is no bigger reward than with this stuff we're doing
For actually to hit home and make someone feel good
Don't want to talk about the bad days
It's a good day just because we are here
That's the latest of the new dawn
The second song that I've played by them that I really really enjoy
Hey everybody, sorry about yesterday
Even though there's a lot of room noise here
Especially because yesterday was president's day
I was thinking, oh, it's going to be great
I got in Sunday into the condo
After again an un-eventful yet lovely flight
I'm virgin upper class
And I was like, yeah, how Monday will be good
And it'll be president's day so I can take my time and I'll get a show out
Well, it turns out that one of the, there was like that
We've had problems with this server before
The one that runs indiepotter.org and curry.com
I think it finally bit the big one
And of course this is one of the final legacy systems
It's always at the back of the list
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we'll migrate all that stuff one of these days
Well, I guess we're forced to migrate now
So I spent most of the Sunday setting up WordPress
Migrating everything over the archives of course
Still on it there and it was bound to happen
Oh, we just got to get in indiepotter.org back up and running
I know that Marcus was working
I went to bed last night he was still working on it
So that will be pretty soon and then we'll be back in rolling
That's just so much going on
So I'm here for the week and yesterday was, oh, it was just beautiful
Although the power blew out a transformer exploded near the office
So that kind of bummed everybody out a lot of developers
It'd come into just work on some stuff
Kind of a quiet day, no phones ringing
Kind of hanging out together
And so I did hook up with a couple of people
And we'll talk about that later on today
Lots of audio feedback, lots of friends
Checking back in with the show
Some news about stuff that's coming up
Oh my gosh, let me see a metro section moment
Which turns out is loved by quite a bit of people
Mail and female alike
Despite all of the jokes that are being made about it in the potter sphere
And all the, I'd say the complimentary rip-offs
Of the metro moment
Maybe we should just make it the metro moment
Maybe that's better than metro section moment
Because now there's the real man moment
And the macho moment and the heterosexual moment
But still the only original is to be found right here
And we'll continue some of the conversations that we had over the past week
One of them was about parenting
This is Koenberg from Holland, the land of the Sincere
I wanted to comment about what you said about
Let's just call it by name weed
When I was a teenager I lived in the States
Columbia South Carolina to be exact
And I saw at high school more wheat than I did
When I went back to Holland
Generally in Holland everybody had tried it
And it didn't find it very interesting
So I saw less people do it here than in the States
And I just wanted to let you know that
Okay, I've been listening for about a year and I love your show
So keep on going
Yo brother, thank you, oops
A little bit of dust there in the mixer
Yeah, well, so that's kind of what we, oh man
There is a lot of dust in there
This is the, I think everyone pretty much agreed
At least the people who responded
That they're not making it a big deal
Oh shoot, hold on let me just run this open
Okay, here we go
Time for a new mixer I guess
Gotta use that corporate card
Anyone who sent in any feedback about
About how Patricia and I are raising Christina
And for that I refer back to the show last week
Oh shoot, what was it, when's it, when's it show I think we're talking about it
When you make these things just not a big deal
Turns out it's not a big deal
And you're right, when I went to college
And my college career lasted for all of three months
I went to West Virginia
And the reason why I went to West Virginia is because they would let
Freshman on the radio station
So I was running the entire music department within two weeks
And running
Not by title, but running a lot of the production
And really the on air
The on air production of the station
It was within the first few weeks
It was great, you know, because of course I'd come from
Pirate radio stations and you know that
I had I knew how to queue up a record at least
These of course were the old days of the records
And I knew how to you know to fire up the transmitter in the morning
All ten watts of it, WITB, Salem, West Virginia
But yeah, it was there that
Well, after those first couple of weeks and like man
Everyone here is just trying to smoke a lot
Drink a lot and drive as fast as they can
And I did not appeal to me why?
Because I'd grown up with all those things
Not being a big deal
Let's see, I think I actually will skip this
I was going to play a little bit
Why not?
I subscribed to the wired news podcasts
And I was blown away last night when one of them came through
Because it does say wired news podcasts
And you know why it usually has some pretty good stuff
But when I listened to it I was like wow
You know, this is either
Either their
Well, you listen, listen to a little bit of this piece of
Quote news and tell me what you think about it
Howard by
Sonobide
Whatever sonobide is
So they have a little commercial beginning
I'm not not listening to this
Yeah whoever, body we got some
So I'm arrogant
Now check it out
Listening post
By Elliot Van Busskirk
Ever since computers picked up the handy ability
To play decent sounding music
Fans have overwhelmingly defaulted to the MP3 format for audio files
Because it sounds pretty good
You have to live
I can't even play the rest of it
Because it sounds pretty good
No other reason
You got to listen to this
I don't think this is written by one of the editors
That actually writes for the magazine
Maybe it is
But man full of all kinds of factual mistakes
And just this guy reading with this
With that same voice going on and on
That's much more on and on
Perhaps most importantly
Works with more devices than any other digital audio format
So there's a
I should and you know what I'm going to do
I'm going to pull some pieces from that
And use that isn't open or works with more devices than any other audio format
Yes indeed
Kind of weird what the guy is over at wire to doing
I couldn't get through the whole thing
I actually fell asleep with the power book on my chest
In bed last night
At nine o'clock
Let me tell you
And I really again
The sun is just coming up over the bay
It's shining through the condo
There's this kind of orange
Just a reddish glow
And people are coming off the bay bridge
And the day has started
And it will be another sunny day in northern California
With some good news for those of you
Of the back persuasion
I had a name, my name is Basil and I'm from Belgium
And I sent you this audio comment to regarding your power book
Sound problem
I call reports that this problem should be fixed
From version 10 to 4 to 5
But you can download from software upgrade
So I hope you try it out
Because I want to know if it's really fixed or not
I think a lot of listeners would like it this as well
And I'm also a fan of the power book recording
Because the volume of the power book recordings
It's much better than the crossblaster version
I listen to the Charlie everyday in the subway
And half of the time
I can't hear your voice
Because of the ambient noise of the Metro
And the people around me
So I hope you either raise the volume
Of your recording in crossblaster
Or go back to the power book version
Where the sound was much much louder
So that's all for now
I hope you're playing this comment
See you
Bye
Yep
Okay, nice fade
Yeah
Well, I've loaded it
It came
You don't have to do anything
If you have a power book
It comes with
What is it?
The upgrade 10.4.5
And so far
And I've loaded it on the power book
So far, no problems at all
I've not had the audio looping
But I must say in the interim
I've grown so attached to the setup with Cast Blaster
And I do agree with you on the volume
And I'm still trying to figure out
Just what is the sweet spot
Where how high I can turn this thing
Because basically
The meters are hitting
0 dB all the time
Which is the end of the scale on Cast Blaster
I think I'm there
I've been working with PW Fenton
He says that I'm really at the max there
Of what I can reach with volume
So I'm not quite sure why it's still
Is softer than the power book version
Excuse me
No, I'm not going to say it
Use your own imagination
And I really do
I don't know, I'm just digging it
And there's all kinds of little things
And issues that are being worked on
And I actually have some feedback about that in this show
Well, let's get to it right now
Because there's some good and some bad
Check this out
Hello
Ah, yes
Hi Adam, this is Tom from the Fog View podcast
I'd like to publicly thank Cast Blaster Mike for his great Cast Blaster program
I just recorded my first podcast
And used the podfather edition of Cast Blaster to do it
My first podcast is a little rougher on the edges
But once Mike improves Cast Blaster
And sure it'll sound much better
Just kidding Mike
What's great about Cast Blaster is all the support
And the Cast Blaster forms
And how fast Mike responds to problems
And supplies updates
Just along with the podsaic music network
Provides a great set of resources for
Often coming podcasters like myself
Many thanks to you and the podcasting community
So the great work and support in this exciting new media
If you'd like to hear what a first time podcaster sounds like
You can check out my podcast at www.fogview.com
Sternwinds Adam
What was that?
What did you say?
Did you say Stern?
I didn't hear that
Let me just check that whole
Let me just get to the end there
Oh my god
My podcast at www.fogview.com
Sternwinds Adam
Sternwinds
Hmm, it's a little different from tailwinds
You know, I only mentioned that once or twice
That I feel that you can only with someone tailwinds
If they're pilot and not just about every single email
I get as either saying, okay
I can't say tailwinds
Or you know my dad's a pilot
So I get to say half a tailwinds
I don't know if you saw a curry dot
Call my post to the picture of the Delta Sherry Delta Sherry
Delta Sherry
My airplane, which is now being rebuilt
It's getting the black edition engine
All new interior. I'm very excited about it
I might even be able to test fly it
Next Monday or Tuesday
As I get back Sunday
Then I'm going to the Netherlands
On Monday because I have this
Remember the court case against the paparazzi magazine
The
The gossip rag
So that serves Tuesday
I'm not sure is it I think late morning
Or early afternoon in Amsterdam
And then with a little bit of luck
Because the wind commander will meet me somewhere
And we'll go flying because it has to do like
15 hours of him flying it
Before he's completely convinced that everything is good
And before we take it across
Stuff like oh I don't know like water
Maybe just a thought there
Direct from a small water cooler
Located inside the voice booth
Cross-gear to New Zealand
Beams directly around the globe
To all of the seven continents
And all way through the galaxy
Informing an entertaining millions along the way
This is the amazing water cooler podcast
Join David Toby for juicy gossip
Amazing interviews
Monster music mashups
Everything else important happening in the world
And beyond
The water cooler podcast
One small step for men
One giant leap for podcasting
A podcast for the voice booth
Don't come
New Zealand's leading podcasting network
Dude since say it will also come in D-caf
Just say you know
I've got a special call coming up
From one of our favorites today on the source code
Don't go skip in ahead to it because there's a lot more in the mean time
Including a metro moment
But before we get to that
Yes, it's spreading far and wide
This piece comes from
Ant Barnes
Ant and Ant Barnes
Who found a nice spoof ad on the
What is it the cymochrome podcast?
Cymochrome cymolycrum
So how's the more cymolycrum?
My brother
The cymolycrum podcast
Is your shave still not close enough?
But despite the constant pampering and vanity products
You still feel all man
Well McWilkow saw turbo have the razor for you
On you 94 blade razor
Shaved so close you can see bone
And are unique contours
Make it perfect for the back crack and sack
Listen to my authority and enthusiasm
Is this a man that can't be bothered to lacerate his face daily?
I think not
This is the ultimate shave for where 93 blades just aren't enough
The new McWilkow saw turbo 94
Our best ever razor
What could we ever do to better it?
Metrosexual
It's Adam Curry's
Metrosexual moment
Yeah I've been up here
And Curry's Metrosexual moment
Yeah
Adam says Phil Walker
Time for a new subject for the Metrosexual moment
How about the underwear debate?
Oh man
I knew it was going to pop up eventually
Breeze versus wife runs versus boxers versus free balling
I know my life would be much better for an in-depth analysis
Of the pros and cons of this vexing question
Again, the categories are briefs versus wife runs
Versus boxers versus free balling
Well, then I might as well come clean myself
I'm definitely
I guess a white a white front is
Yeah, I guess I have a white front
Is a white front kind of like a boxer that hugs you more tightly
Is that what that is?
Because I'm not into the briefs
And that's just because uncomfortable
You know, it's like the male version of a thong
Only you don't show it
And that's probably really a good thing
So let's find out what our source code
Audiences into
Again, briefs versus wife runs versus boxers versus free balling
And since we have plenty of female listeners
As you'll find out in a few moments
You might as well
If you're a woman, you might as well tell us what you think is
Hot sexy or what the Metroman should be wearing
Mark Kelso, pops in, Adam wanted to give you thumbs up
On the Frank feedback regarding raising your daughter
Yep, no one can doubt the love you share
My wife and I are blessed with a daughter
Who although has not seen a smoke has seen a strength
The difference simply is drinking as worse yet
No kidding
Now I'd like to hear from listeners on how to keep a good go-to go-to
But I hear you talk about the right razor
What makes a good moustache and go-to
How long should it be?
How thick should one wear it?
Best wishes looking forward to your uncles interview
Yeah, you know, the Uncle Don thing is really caught fire
Everyone's talking about it
I'm very excited about getting that interview
And Denise Howell, who I believe is from baggin' baggage
Who is an attorney, says, hey Adam
Further to your theme of paying close attention
To wives and girlfriends product stash
And of course this is what I've suggested to all of you
If you want to look for the right stuff
You want to go into your wife or your girlfriends
Bathroom cabinet there
And you want to take her moisturizers
Because that is the real shit
I've been a long time fan of
Outturners straightening balm
It's a superb tamer of the frizzies
Better still?
It just taught me this morning
The whole bloody line is made with hemp
Wow, okay, so we can straighten the hair
And feel good at the same time
And of course Denise ends it up there with
What big hair'd fag could do without
I agree Denise
Okay, so you got lots of homework for this week
Regarding the metro section moment
Those of you checking this out on serious stars
We have the Hellway next specific coast
Hellway and on the Gilmore daily today
For the first time in public
I hear Steve Gilmore drops the F-bomb on Doxero
Stay tuned for that
It's all coming up here on 103
And we'll continue
Right now
On the podcast
Because I got at least another 15-20 minutes to go
Let's see
There was Alistair Jenks sent me a link
About mainstream media and music cannibalism
Now we touched on this before
And I've heard a lot of
I've actually got a lot of
Music industry
Like folks who've talked about this with me
This is from Macworld
And the title written by Johnny Evans
Is iTunes steals music
Music's soul
And what's happening now
Is that record companies are becoming
Increasingly dissatisfied
With the sale of single tracks
Because they feel as cannibalizing the product
Which they've always sold up until now
Which of course is albums
And although I don't have any numbers to back it up
Apparently they're holding songs back
They're not putting songs on the iTunes
And this is really, I mean this is changing
Very quickly right before our very eyes
There's all kinds of movement going on in the music industry
And meanwhile we're just kind of
Puttering around, you know, going around
That if you've been to the podcast
MusicNetwork of Music.podshow.com
You'll see that
There are little bylinks
Now each to next to each individual track
They're not activated yet
Because we're definitely in beta
We're barely out of alpha on this stuff
And all man Chris Rocco was so pissed at me
Oh boy
He said, well, you know, next time you tell your listeners
To go check and see if this stuff works
Tell me ahead of time
Dude
So sorry
Because he's actually done a fantastic job
Very intricate
And making the user experience work
Particularly the sign up
Because, you know, basically what's happening
If you're not a registered listener
Of the podcast music network
You have to basically sign up for the podcast music network
So we can help you track all of your downloads
And nice little handy store
These are all MP3s free and clear
So you can download them as often as you want
And put them on any of your devices
You're only going to pay for it once
Lost my train of thought
This sun just hit me in the eyes again
Yeah
So the only one that's active now
I think is pod safe for peace
If every day we're quite Christmas
Which of course is
You know, it's not really a Christmas
It's not really that time of year
But it is a great song to test stuff out with
And we've all been doing it because all the money goes to unice
And we're just going to keep it going
Keep the feedback reports coming in
I've got one here from Australia
Which was kind of interesting
Hi Adam, Steve Springl here
Just a little bit of feedback regarding
Purchases of the PMN
Just thought I'd give it a try
And buy pod safer for peace
And
Shut me off to click and buy
To put my career card details in
Because I'm not already a customer
It asked me for my details
I put those in
And then it basically said
Your account's not activated yet
And you need to call us between
8am and 6pm during weekdays
Well, that's not much good
I don't really like that idea
It means now I can't make a purchase
And as an Australian
It means I've got to ring an international number
To activate the account
It's a Sunday here
So I can't do it today
I'm going to have to wait till next week
It just makes the experience
It's not such a good experience
So anyway, some feedback for you
From an Australian
Trying to put
Find music
Off the pod safe music network
See you later
Enjoy your show
Catch you next time
All right, it's mate
Okay, so we looked into this
And here's the best we can come up with
Because this is supposed to work worldwide
And we have had other people
able to purchase from Australia
From New Zealand
From other spots in the Pacific Rim
Excuse me
So the closest I can come up with
Is that there may be just an issue with your credit card
Maybe
Who knows
I mean, this shit happens all the time
I've seen the richest men in the world
Have their credit card
You know, run into problems and restaurants
And you know, particularly when it's
Cross country purchases
So I would really appreciate
If you did call into them
Did find out what the reason was
Why they wanted you to call
Because this is not the default behavior
Of clicking by
Who is the partner that we're working with on this
And just to reiterate one more time
We're not building a store
We're not replicating iTunes
All we're doing is adding a little bit of functionality
And we want to just make it as safe as possible
For everybody that's why we chose a partner
That has a great reputation
The drawback
But of course, your own security
Is that you have to create a separate password
Separate from your
Login at the pod set music network
Which of course, you can store on your computer
So you won't have to enter it again
We have to do that for security reasons
Because we don't want your credit card information
That's all going through clicking by
If there are any other issues
Then please let us know
We're working on some silly stuff
When you sign up you get like 3, 3,000 emails
From clicking by
That's very confusing
So we are trying to make the experience better
And once you're logged in
I really hope that it works out for you
Because we have gotten
All kinds of varying response
And the good news is
Just about everybody is actually able to buy
And to download
And to go back and go into your cubby hole
There on on PMN
And retrieve it
And download it again to different devices
So all that's working
But just credit cards
There's always some crap going on somewhere
But thanks for the feedback
And keep it coming
Adam
This is Matt Campbell
And I'm a relatively new listener
With the Charlie as you like to say
And I've been noticing lately a problem
With your audio setup
Where when playing music
The playback will speed up
For a fraction of a second
And then return to its normal rate
Now I'm going to show you a couple of clips
Where I've observed this
First in DSC333
During I wonder
By Natalie Brown at the end of the show
And I heard this
In the fourth time she sings the chorus
After the second verse
And you can hear it in the strings
Just before she sings
I wonder
I'll play this twice
Time and space
I wonder
I don't know, man
That's why you can hear the pitch
Goes up just a little
And then returns to normal
Now I also heard this
On DSC338
During not on the radio
By Jeff Smith
This time it's in the bridge
And you can hear it in the piano
Just before
I'm just better
I'll play this twice
Maybe
I'm just middle
What you say
Maybe
I'm just middle
What you say
I heard it there
Again the pitch went up a little
And then returns to normal
So as you can hear this isn't an isolated incident
But a recurring problem
I think I also heard this on
334 and 336
But I figured two clips would do it
So that's all I have for now
Keep up the great work
Alright man, thank you
You know what?
You would do me a great service
By posting
Any time you hear something as a listener
Going over to castblaster.com
And posting something in the forums
Because that's
And I've got to get in the forum as well
Just to get some feedback going
And some really good conversation happening there
Also stuff about accessibility
For blind podcasters
So they can use it
And I think Mike has actually put out
Yet another beta
Addition
Which now has some form of accessibility
At least I heard Darrell talking about it
So I guess it's getting better
But any type of feedback
And this is a weird one
I have no idea what that is
It could be so many different things
It could be your player
Although I think I heard this before myself
And wanted to other people who have mentioned it
And of course, often I'm just sitting
Dude, you know
Maybe it's just the stuff I'm smoking
That makes it all warm
Hey, happy
What you doing?
Oh my computer is so slow
I'm bogged down in spyware
I spend hours deleting spam
This is no information super highway
This is a dead end street
Well happy
You need to try a airplane
Yes, Earthlink
Earthlink's protection control center
It gives you automatic updates
To help keep your computer protected from the latest threats
Earthlink stands for both viruses and spyware
And Earthlink's next generation software
The lot's viruses and spyware
Be sure they install on your PC
Can I get on the super information highway with Earthlink?
Sure
Get in
I love Earthlink
Earthlink
We revolve around you
That's the gofers from bedtime stories
I tell my kids
Okay, so folks thinking about it
Thinking about the New Earthlink campaign
Today Tuesday we have our meeting
We're going to be talking about all the
All the different thoughts that we've been discussing here on the show
Because now finally
After, well really, only after two months
Time of all the feedback
And all the
Sometimes even the flaming about the Earthlink campaign
That's been running on the pod show pod castle network
We now get to turn it around
And we get to decide how we're going to do this
What is the perfect user generated
The listener advertiser
What the hell do you want to hear
And you know what?
It's not just me and you, my friends
There's more people thinking very, very seriously about this stuff
Yeah, you're ready
Yeah
Yeah, there's another message
Wrong
Rajas
It's my body
Fuck
Hey, I've been running here
As you're asking for people's record
Some Earthlink commercials
I thought I'd have to go
Haven't got any musical sound effects
I'm afraid
Hopefully this will sound okay
And I should have done a much bad advertising
But I've heard the sex cell products
Not talking about viruses and scammers
Because when you think about it
If you get some idiot paying $10 million to the print in Nigeria
Just to buy some bagra
And if they're on steepest bullets to get ripped off
You should remember that there's only one time that people
wished to have a fast room or private internet connection
And that's when they're hunched over a keyboard
Where you can put two meg file called
That's scared
So MPs download and Windows media player
You really ought to try and appeal to that side of the market
And try sexy things
Don't try rewriting it
Hold on
He wants to download porn quickly
Then you can wank
We do
We're a slink
He wants a horn
They give it a net unicorn on our panradverse
We do
We're a slink
Haven't noticed how it's the men in the house
So the film needs to upgrade the broadband
We do
We're a slink
Go on and visit airslink.net
And put some letting it pencil
Just slink
Because we revolve around men
And say she will appetite to download
Naked pictures
Quicker than you can say
The enemy's prison sentence
I think he just needs a bit more money
Than tell it like it is
Anyway, give it a happy back in the country
And make the wind be with you
He ain't gross
Ha ha ha ha
Our Roger man
I love you
I'm so happy you're thinking about this stuff
And I'm sorry we haven't
We haven't hooked up for lunch yet
The travel's just been a little bit crazy
But I love it
You've got the little sound effect there
The bell
For sound linking
Soundvertising
You've used all the principles
And of course the honesty and advertising
I will definitely
Use this today in our conversation Roger
No doubt about it
And I think the real key here
To this stuff is having variation
Having variations on a theme
I mean I'd love to have a hundred different earth linked spots
You know all different, all appealing
To different people for different reasons
And I think yours definitely belongs there
Roger
You are a true friend for working on this with me
Yeah
Roger
Daddy John
Is another message from
Rages
Names
Hey Adam, this is Chris from Chicago
Just listening to your Friday, February 17th
D.S.C.
And just wondering if Uncle Don may have gotten to Rumsfeld
You know you were talking about the war
And the way that you know our government
Is not adapting to this media age
And you know Rumsfeld basically came out today
And said you know
Our enemies are skillfully adapted to fighting wars
And today's media age
But our country is not adapted
For the most part the US government still
Functions is a fine with a dime store
In an eBay world so you know
Go Uncle Don
And you know at the same time
I don't necessarily think that
Putting pictures of our dead soldiers
On the front of
You know the New York Times for instances
I'm really going to do anything to help
I think of anything
We are media here
Definitely shield us from that
But at the same time they are not telling us
The good things that are going on over there
I know people in the military
And they see far more successes than failures
Going on over there
Although all we ever hear about
Is the failures
So anyway keep up the good work
And tail
Oh I'm not a pilot
Yep, watch yourself now
You know I agree with you
Of course with the bad should also come the good
But let's do both of them
And I believe that
Well first I know first hand that there's
A lot of great work has been done in Iraq
Because I visited there myself in April of 2004
At Camp Smitty in Asimaba
In Iraq so that's the
About the western part of Iraq
Still a good 150 miles from Baghdad though
And yeah I mean there is
The reporting really does seem to be only about the failures
I was just saying
And now that we know based upon
The interviews that I've seen
First hand interviews with the editor
Of the Danish newspaper who started the whole cartoon
Controversy
It literally was done as a
You know
How did he put it?
I wish I could quote him directly
But he said look
He didn't want any religious group ever
Making his editors and his journalists
Participate in self-censorship
So he said we're not going to do self-censorship
We're going to put out there what we feel we should put out there
Which of course basically you can insult any group of people
Very very easily with any type of cartoon
And you'd probably get
What I don't think you get the same reaction
Not as violent
But you know there's a lot of other stuff here at play
So my whole point was look
If you want to do some shocking stuff
Then do some shocking stuff
And why don't you put dead soldiers dead coalition soldiers
Put pictures up there
Of what it looks like when someone's killed
Don't just put it into a couple of words
And say you know an IED
Took out
You know a tank
You know a troop carrier
And ten people died
You know that just doesn't cut it
That's not shocking enough
You know
Just turn on the TV
And you can see the kind of stuff that we're used to
So that was my point
But then also indeed there also should be
Which I'm sure people immediately would call
Fluff stories
But there has been a great amount of
Good work done in Iraq
Of course at the end of it all
And this is the stuff that we'll be talking about
With Uncle Don
He made it very very clear to me
He said look every single administration
The administration always goes to the intelligence units
To the intelligence community
And ask them to back up the policy that they're putting in place
With intelligence
And boy did that happen with Iraq
So I guess I guess we'll just have to wait a couple more weeks
But Uncle Don was very excited about doing it
And so am I because I think this might even have to be a multiple parts to hear
He's just because there's so much to talk about
Along those lines I've really been thinking about
Doing some different stuff with the Charlie
Obviously I want to keep the
Pods have music going and the feedback
And the metro moments and all the stuff that we're talking about
But from time to time
Where you know I haven't actually done a sound seeing tour
And a while I should do one of those
But I want to get some other topics going here
And I want to have other people on the show
Because I like talking to people
I keep noticing that time and time again
When I'm talking with Patricia
Just how much fun it is
Just to have a conversation with no limits and boundaries
On language and time
And are one of our investors
Clientaire Perkins
Who invested in Pods Show
While we're in New York they announced something very interesting
And investment fund
And I guess I'll have to ask right off the bat
And when I do this interview
I'll have to ask how that works
And how did the investment funds work
Because you know it may just not be very clear
But at any rate there's two hundred million dollars
For this fund which means it will be invested
And it's called the pandemic preparedness
Biodefense fund
And essentially what I can gather from the press release
Is that they believe
The Asian the Avian bird flu
Will eventually start spreading from human to human
And I'm sure you see I was it was it
Maybe it was 60 minutes the other day
That did this whole thing about you know
How easily you know a minimum of two
But maybe 10 million people in the United States
Could be killed if it started to spread from human to human
I guess that kind of betting on this actually happening
And they don't see the government being able to respond quick enough
And so they started an investment fund
A commercial fund mind you
To protect the citizens of the world
And it sounds so controversial
You know I'm like two hundred million dollars
Not a lot of money when it comes to you know
And the scheme of big things look at what we're spending in Iraq
You know what is the government not capable of doing this
What happens if it never
If there is never a pandemic
Do investors in the funds still make money
I mean what what are the long-term goals of this
It was just it crunched my brain
And so I'm going to interview
Brookbires one of the
The partners whose name is on the door
Kleiner Perkins
Callfield buyers
Brookbires and I think we get some other people on
And this is actually going to be a first time recording
With Skype and cast blaster and routing through the mixer
So hopefully it'll all work out
I'm going to record that for tomorrow's show
And let's see if we can get a conversation started with that
Because I just find it phenomenally fascinating
It was actually in the New York Times
It was like Tuesday or Wednesday
It was on the front page was this
Like a half page picture of birds being called
And you know there's now been reports in France
Of course it started kind of in Turkey
Even the UK now birds are being brought indoors
So this thing is definitely spreading
It's still going bird to bird
But if it goes bird to human
Which it does actually
I've actually know a guy who got bird flu
He lived but he was pretty damn sick
And of course the big fear is person to person
So we can get the word from some experts
People who in fact are
Believe they're so educated in the matter
That they're going public with this fund
And taking money from people to invest in it
So I kind of freaked me out
I was also on the other hand
I was very happy I'm thinking
Well you know if this shit does hit the fan
God that's that's cool that I know these guys
Because I probably can get first
Why?
Hey thanks everybody for sending in the information
About David Letterman's microphone
I asked if that was a high LPR 40
The same microphone I'm using right now
PW summed it up the best
PW Fenton said here's the story
As well as I can piece it together
For many years going back to his NBC show
David has used an antique RCA DX77 ribbon microphone
On his desk that was given to him as a gift
By the crew when he left NBC
It was the mic originally used by Jack PAR
The model is highly treasured and is still used
Yeah I think that's the black one I think
That was kind of tilted back on his desk
Not too long ago apparently
It was reportedly stolen from his set
And it's now been replaced with a high LPR 40
In both cases it's only there as a prop
What you hear on the show is either a mic that he wears
Or a boom mic just out of sight
The desk mic is never live
Some reports say it's wired as a backup
But he beat up doubts it
I doubt it as well
Because this is not the type of microphone
That really works from
It's meant for close mic operation
Really I think these type of mics
We're originally built for recording kick drums on drum kit
Continuing PWM says I believe the desk mic is there
And silent tribute to Johnny Carson who always had a desk mic
Which wasn't used for on air sound either
Carson's mic was a shoe or model SM33 ribbon
Made especially for him
It had an inscription on it
Johnny's mic
Not Ed's
Not Fred's
Sure wanted to be sure it got to Johnny
That mic saved from the trash by the boom operator
That worked on the Carson show was auctioned
And sold for 50,787
Dollars doing anonymous bitter
Which of course some folks believe was David Letterman
And just about everybody sent in a similar story
But PW really
Really summed it up perfectly
Thanks buddy appreciate it
Hi Adam, it's Derek Kay Miller from the Penn Machine podcast
Once again
And I got a couple things for you
And then I got a promo that if you want
We'll segue fabulously into the Metro section moment
So if you want to do all those, let's see what happens
Anyway the first thing is Letterman and the PR40 mic
I heard somewhere
I think it was on this week in tech a few weeks ago
That yes Letterman does use a PR40 on his desk
And it is pointed toward the guests chair
Not at him
And the reason for that is apparently the guests
Where a little tyclip level ear mic
But sometimes when they get a little crazy
You know you got Jim Carrey on there or something
They'll jump around and that mic will become disconnected
Then they can flip on the PR40
And it will pick up their voice
Most of the time it's off
So you can, you know, do the old Johnny Carson tap as pencil on there
The second thing is a nomdex
Where you did DSC number 200 last year
Wondering if you're going again
I'm going to be there
And Chris Burrell asked me to write a theme song for it
So I'm working on that
And he's got a thing on his website
asking people to phone in and leave comments
That we're going to mash up into the song
So if you want to do one, you're welcome to do that
That'd be fabulous
And the next thing is the promo which is my wife
And her friend are starting their first podcast
It's called Lip Gloss and Laptops
For the thinking woman they say
So if you want to play it, it's coming right up
Then you can segue right into a mental sexual moment
If you want it, it'll all work
Just give it a shot
Here we go
Hi, I'm Eric Dree
And I know the difference between a lip smacker
And a local area network
And I know my way around a juicy tip and a JPEG file
On March 1st, Lip Gloss and Laptops
A beauty and cosmetics podcast for the thinking woman premieres
Each week we will bring you thoughtful discussion
Of modern beauty culture
And controversies
Lip College in anyone
We will also bring you reviews of the hottest new beauty products
Let us try before you buy five thousand times larger
Do you really want your lashes that thick
So go on to lipgloss and Laptops.com
And tell us what your favorite lip gloss is
And subscribe to our new podcast
Speaking of which, do you remember the avon fun burger
Popular in the 1970s?
I remember the avon chocolate chip cookie
But we're going to be talking about lip gloss in our first podcast
Excellent
Alright
Women with lipstick who know about laptops
Coming soon
Dude, don't tell me how to put the show together
That's not perfect for the metro sexual moment
It's something completely different
But I do love that idea
Oh man, I've been waiting
This is kind of like
What is that website?
Daily candy
That was that Bob Pittman's site that he put together
It just sold it for like $100 million
Or something
Oh, what an incredible audience there is out there
For something like this
I would love to talk about having this show
As a part of our network
I think I have a sponsor for it already
So if you're interested, let me know
Speaking of such
As it comes into business models of podcasting
Big news rocking the pod atmosphere
Ricky Jervais
The Ricky Jervais show
Which of course is now in the
Guinness Book of World Records
As the most downloaded podcast ever
Which I'm sure they'll have to change that
Sometime around
Oh next year when they do the next
Guinness Book of World Records
Had been making
What city they did 12 episodes
For free
Available through the Guardian
Which I thought was a great combination
A great team up between the Guardian
The UK newspaper the Guardian
Who I guess were
We're dealing with all the business side of it
So they announced today
Or actually on their 12th show
But I guess the news now is official
That the next series
Season 2 as they're calling it
Will be available exclusively
Through audible
And that will be done through iTunes
Of course audible is the exclusive
Provider of iTunes
So actually I guess it'll be available
Through the iTunes music store
As well as through audible if you remember
They're very interesting
I think the first four episodes
We'll cost you about six
Dollars and they're just basically
Changing from the free model
I don't think they didn't have any ads in there
I don't think other than for the Guardian
I haven't heard every single show
So I may be wrong
But it doesn't matter
Because
Essentially they're going to a subscription-based model
A four-pay model
Which of course I presume would be without commercials
And I cannot wait to see how this goes
I'm very very curious
Because here's something that
Arguably but I think pretty much without doubt
Is definitely one of the most downloaded podcasts
Amy you got to believe the Guinness World Book of Records
Right?
If that indeed works
And they have what are they claiming
Like
250 download
No I think it was
And with someone you're two million downloads a month
That would of course
If you're spending 50 cents or a buck
Or I guess it's more than a buck
It's what it's 125
And you're aggregating that on the other end
That's a pretty nice chunk of change
The only thing that I'm not too sure about
Though is if there will actually be
Still be available as a subscription
The way we know it in podcasting
Because when you sign
I guess their audible does have this
But it wasn't very clear
You sign up what I want to do
Of course I want to subscribe
And have these things show up automatically
In this case it would have to be iTunes
Because that's basically what
What you can play back on
Because it won't be the free and clear MP3s
But we'll still come through automatically
If anyone has signed up let me know
My audible subscription has been
My audible subscription has expired
And I couldn't find it on iTunes yet
But it's a just you know
Is it like the video stuff where you click it
And then it downloads and then you've got it
Or can you set it up?
So every single time this new show
It comes in
Good luck to them though
And I hope that they continue to report back on how that's going
Because that's very very exciting
People who have content
They think that other people will pay for
Actually go out and do it
For email from Chris
Snethon
Adam until this week and I hadn't listened to the Charlie since before
Christmas it wasn't until today for example
That I know it's now the Charlie
Instead of the Chuck which is the next logical step
Now I don't think we're going to go to the Chuck
Anyway, I checked out DSC338337335 in that order
And I have to say I'm sorry I left for so long
It's stimulating for me and gets me thinking about possibilities
Rather than just existing in my cubicle drone haze
One thing really struck me listening to the show
Not was the number of folks
Bitching about this aspect of this aspect
Of DSC or that aspect
People were variously griping about the Metro sexual stuff
Which I love he says
The Earthling ads
Minor compared to what they could be
And the sound advertising which is interesting to me
Heck, I even had a bitch back in December
Which drove me away for those eight weeks or so
Which was too many people kissing your ass
Not that I didn't try myself
But a couple of the bits go way out of hand
But I figured that
I figured out my iPod can fast forward through this stuff
I don't care to hear and I still get what I want
Oh really that's what those arrows are for
I guess the point is I'm back
I'd forgotten until today how much I got out of the show
Keep up the great work and just remember that people are only griping
Because they care if that makes any sense
Of course they do
Next time you're in Portland, Aurora, blah, blah, blah
Yeah, you better believe it man
I will be coming to Portland, Aurora when I do my instrument rating
Which one of these days I'll get around to doing
Okay, just briefly before we wind it up with a pretty funny song
That's someone that sent me
Stuff going on at the office
Yes, they had a great hang with the K2
He's Kevin ready
New guy to the office
It's amazing how many people speak Dutch
You know, he's lived in the Netherlands for
Often on probably about a year or so
And he just picks up languages really easily
I'm sure it has something to do with
With his developer developer noggin there
But we had a really good hang in South Park
Yesterday if you know what I mean
And just caught up on stuff and I'm really excited
And just another guy that I'm so excited about working with
We have so many people doing so many cool things in the office
Hooked up with Andrew Grummet who was
Completing D-Gap
Oh man, this thing is just mind boggling
You imagine, check this out
So imagine you could record your podcast
And then after you're done
You could record any number of slots of different stuff
So you say and you can program that
So maybe after the fact you want to record the opening
Because now you know what you did in your show
And then that opening
You could schedule it to be married automatically
To the opening of your show
So where I say you know what is it
Delta share of Charlie 339
I could actually do that later and say
Delta share Charlie 339
Chris is back stay tuned for it
Whatever boom and it could start immediately
Or I could schedule a promo
It's just mind boggling the stuff that we're going to be able to do
And I think that I saw on the board
Some stuff is going to start
Well some stuff is already starting to happen
If you look at the podcast music network
But we've got a player that is coming along with that
I'd say somewhere around
Sixth of March is when we'll really have a lot of stuff out there
I think we're going to open up
For a couple hundred people to come in
And start using
Not just the podcast delivery network
But also the listener interface
Where you can register as a listener of a podcast
And it's just
Hey, I love it
There's so many good things happening
All right, let's see what we got
Oh man, 56 is going to be a full hour show today
Russell sent me an email
Adam looking for songs from my astronomy podcast
Which is astronomy.podcastformat.com
If I'm one that is not quite appropriate for my show
But I figured it would go very nicely on the Charlie
It's by Deirdre Flint and it's called the boob ferry
When I was in my teenage years
I did just what I should
I listened to my mother and I was kind and sweet and good
And my friends and I did rituals
And I prayed with all my might
That this would be the evening
That she'd stop along her flight
Well that was several years ago
And that chick's long overdue
And it's time I came to terms with something plainly clear to you
The boob ferry never came for me
No the boob ferry never came for me
Okay, I'm spunky and I'm cute
And I've got a great personality
The boob ferry never came for me
Well we were the third house on a country drive
I thought maybe she just got lost
So I hung my bra on the mailbox
To the neighbors took it out
And all my friends got visits
And expanded through the years
And left me whaling to the gods by training
Bross and Sears
Still I harbor hopes she'll come for me
I know she will
I get them done myself
If she'd agreed to foot the bill
The boob ferry never came for me
No the boob ferry never came for me
Look I wasn't wanting melons
Just a cute, curfaceous bee
But the boob ferry never came for me
This isn't a song about boob's
Not really
The boob's are just a set of metaphors
To symbolize everyone's fear of human anatomy
Hey, we've all found the pain of being dissed
By one ferry or another
So during the next refrain I want you to join in with me
With your own ferry that never paid a call
Maybe it's the height ferry or the buttons
And maybe it's the pectoral or hair ferry
Or maybe some other ferry you just want to mumble about
Look nobody's going to ask you to announce the A
And sisters, I don't want you feeling alienated right now
Because you happen to be full figured
Just change the line to the boob ferry
Just wouldn't let me be or the boob ferry became obsessed with me
Okay, here comes the refrain
Everybody, join in
The boob ferry never came for me
No, the boob ferry never came for me
Though the hip ferry came two times
And the five ferry came three
The boob ferry never came for me
That boob ferry never came for me
So what ferry do you pray to?
Very cool, the boob ferry
You can find that a music dot pod show dot com
That wraps it up for today
We've got the rest of the week to go
Lots of exciting stuff here in San Francisco
Making it just about a full hour for the Charlie for today
Addabraccurry dot com free feedback and daily source code dot com
For everything else related to the show
Take everybody and I'll see you tomorrow
Another pod show pod guest
Stick it in your ear
Thanks for watching