For the first time ever, the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr. in one action-packed DVD collection,
own all 27 episodes, the cult hit, including all new interviews with Carlton Koo.
First thing that Brisco did that impressed us was, we're not only to come in and really read the dialogue well as an actor,
but he also did a standing flip in our office.
You've flipped too for Brisco County!
If you like the kind of TV you can't get on TV, get your copy of the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr.
Available now on DVD.
Adam, well, stranded in Cleveland.com, and I'm getting really sick of thinking about you every time I wipe my arms.
This is Daily Source Code Number.
481, $16 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this genre.
I can't believe what you said.
I think it's driving me mad.
Because all the time that we spend, doing the things that we train, the stories come to an end.
You say you gotta meet, if I wanna tell you please, don't treat another good job.
If you treat me, I don't want you to stay.
I want you to come out and weigh and weigh and weigh and weigh.
I just have to say what's wrong with you and make me blue.
Since I do, the love is gone on earth.
I just pity, day and day again until the end.
I can't stop because they know I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm
oxygen obstinate and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and my baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm played well and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby and I'm baby is U 6 SECOND
I Just City day and again until the end
That's like the double class
There's no what they need
I play it a play
I make it a play
All the time
Then it goes on day
Leading
Let's go with you
It seems like it
Who's always gone earlier
Come on, you make me so I can start to cut my work, but I don't need you, you're my daughter, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need
What's wrong with you, it's really Rongtes a shot,孢érif... yeah, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need to, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't like you, it's really don't mean it, that someone will get sc κι away, I don't need a star and then once thatwriter won't pay thatressing for this, I don't need you, I don't need you, I still don't need you, I don't want you to care about,
It's like a Japanese know of me
And a free and a free
It's been a pain, a pain, a pain
I've done it, it's got something
And it was so weeping
And weeping me and weeping
Oh yeah, you can't get more popular than that man
That's perfect
Girl's stuff
From Switzerland
And of course, available on the Pot-Safe Music Network
Blue with the title of that
Send me by Jersey Todd
for a little midweek cowbell boost.
Thanks Todd, I really appreciate it.
Yeah, there you go.
Cowbell on a Thursday.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
Coming to you from a very sunny Northern California
from the Curry Condo in San Francisco.
It is the daily source code episode 481.
You could tell from the kind of generic opening,
I need some more openings.
Send them on, please.
Adam and poncho.com.
Me or in the end of the trip.
And I'm feeling much better today.
I got up a little bit later than normal 630.
And these days, it's kind of hard not to wake up early
because this memory told you that if I look up my window
and I look out at the bay, which, of course,
is, I've got such a view.
I've got such a great bachelor pad.
I've got everything I need, it's a bachelor in here.
Every single thing except girlfriends, the clean and cook for me.
So I used to have the Bank of America tower right outside
which reached up about, I'm on the 24th floor.
So it was probably 20th floor or something like that.
So I could just look over it.
Hey, San Seo with some nice vanilla splendor, everybody, I do.
And they've started building this thing called one rinkin' hill.
One rinkin' hill.com.
It's going to be two towers.
And I really, and I can see now that they're just about as high
as the Bank of America tower was.
And I was riding up the elevator yesterday.
And, yeah, yesterday after work.
And, you know, it's a guy in the elevator
and we get the chatting a little bit.
Yeah, I got to go up to 24.
So he says, have you heard about one rinkin' hill?
I said, what do you mean?
He says, well, it's apparently, 90% sold out.
He says, oh, that's interesting.
I said, you know, how high is this thing going?
It says 59 stories.
It's supposed to be the tallest building west of the Mississippi.
I'm like, well, it's going to be two towers.
Yeah, two towers, 59 stories each.
I'll have absolutely no view whatsoever.
I'll have no form of pay for you.
It's going to be gone.
Oh, man.
So what amazes me?
And I've never seen this, and I've lived in a lot of countries.
But the work starts here at 5 a.m.
That's when they start building.
And, you know, so, of course, you can hear some of it.
It's just across the way, you know, they got,
they're pouring concrete and lifting steel.
And they do not stop until 10 p.m.
Unbelievable.
The rigor that goes into this.
Yeah, in most countries, I don't think you could do that.
I think it's illegal to work that long on that.
Imagine getting that done in France, huh?
Well, you're 35 hour, 35 hour work week, lazy French bastards.
Hmm.
Okay, stuff to talk about today.
I wrote a couple of things down, stuff that I wanted to mention.
These are just some general things that I caught on the six hour jet
blue flight from New York to Oakland.
And I just want to say a lot of people sent me email about jet blue.
Yeah, jet blue really does rock.
And I forgot to make one more comparison about jet blue.
It is so much like the Concord, except for the speed, obviously.
It's not funny.
The Concord had a very, very similar type of layout, kind of, you know,
for the, you know, these jet blue seats are wide enough
that they actually equal what you'd get on the Concord.
And the Concord, you had really nice, you know, nice legroom.
You couldn't stand up straight in the Concord.
There was no television, no movies on the Concord, basically because the flight was so short,
you know, by the time you got started that have to, you know,
at the hand your head sets back in, and we'll get warm in the cockpit and everything.
Yeah, of course it was a thrill to fly the Concord.
Did it a couple times, but jet blue, except for the speed, rivals it completely.
So anyway, so they give you 36 channels of, of direct TV.
So there's got a little dish on top of the plane.
And so I watched a lot of television, I really did.
And I was able to basically sit through all six hours without freaking out.
I could find something at least somewhere on one of the channels.
And I saw some entertainment shows come by and two things that caught my eye.
One is Wesley Snipes. What is going on with that?
Wesley Snipes now being sought.
There's a warrant out for is a rest of for back taxes that he owes.
How can you mess that up, dude?
If you, and he owes like $15 million in taxes, you got to make a lot of money to
$15 million in taxes.
So I don't know if they've found him yet, but this is, you know, kind of atypical for Hollywood celebrity.
So watching that story very closely.
And all, you know, New York State taxes trying to nail me.
This has happened, uh, this has happened four or four years ago.
All of a sudden New York State sent me a letter and said, oh, you owe us, uh,
I don't know, something like $1.7 million.
There's some crazy amount like that.
And I said, you haven't lived in New York since 1987.
I lived there for one year, you know, what do you after?
Apparently I had a, I had a mailing address.
After we moved from, uh, from the states to back to Europe, I had a mailing address in New York,
which was basically, um, and a former employee, her, um, her apartment.
And so I had to prove that that, you know, that I did not live in New York.
And I had actually lived in New Jersey and we had sold the house and we had bought a house in Amsterdam
at the time. And it cost me about $10,000 in lawyers fees to prove it.
And now they come back. They've actually checked this. They've put out a warrant on me,
New York State for like $48,000. Not a warrant for my arrest, but you know,
I guess should I have tried to sell anything property wise or, I don't know,
maybe they will arrest me if I tried to re-enter the country.
Uh, and so now, you know, I've had to send off another $2.5,000 check to the lawyers to go and
figure it out, just to prove that I, you know, there's no way you can't tax me if I,
if I haven't lived in New York State. So, uh, so who knows what mean, what made you going on with
Wesley Snipes? We've got to figure it out. And the other one that I, this is, I just love this story.
Steve Winn, who's a major major mogul in Las Vegas, uh, he owns the, yeah, what the
Bellagio and I guess the, does he have a Steve Winn hotel now? Whatever it is, uh, apparently he'd
been working, you know, in the Blagio, if you've ever been there, has filled with beautiful paintings.
And, uh, I guess he was spent a long time trying to get hold of this one particular Picasso for
like 130 or 140 million dollars. And, uh, so he finally got the, the painting. And I believe it was the
same day, maybe the day after it, he's showing this painting off to people. And he makes some kind of
weird move, and he pokes a hole in the fucking painting with his elbow. 140 million dollar per
castle. Fantastic. Of course it's all shareholder money, but still, just a great story.
So if you want to do some charity work and want to have some more information, check out
www.dalypart.de or sms.partspart.de or podcasting for children.de.
All you do is some charity work via transferring money to our PayPal account. You can find
all information on podcasting for children.de, the four written as a number. So take care of them,
photo. Bye. Choose. Who's got Duncan? Not a good initiative there from our German colleagues.
Very cool. A couple of people said, and I've received this before, maybe it's now heating up.
We are not being in the UK. I can't really track it all that well, but, um, there's now a
word, and I guess this is coming from partially from the UK, but also from the European Union.
There is a draft proposal regarding, quote, television on the internet. On the internet,
it's on the series of tubes, and what they, uh, and I don't have, I've not seen the draft
proposal, but apparently there's some folks who want to regulate video on the internet,
the same as television is regulated. Now, in the UK, by the way, there are already some laws
that carry over to the, uh, to the internet regarding safety of children, and, uh, there's one other.
I guess you can't threaten to kill someone. Something like that. So it's a little more restrictive
than, uh, than the free speech that we enjoy in the United States, but not much. But now there's this,
and I mean, you know where this is coming from? You know, this is coming from scared media companies
who have some kind of cloud inside the EU, or was it, you know, some of these ministers are
parliament or whatever. It's like, I think the quote was really good. If it looks like television,
if it feels like television, and it smells like television, it probably is television, and even
if it's on the internet, it should be regulated like television. And like, whoa, that's pretty big.
Now, I'm sure that this is never going to pass. This will never become law, but it is kind of
interesting. People are sending me, I'll put a link to, uh, to one of these stories about it. I guess
the, uh, the times in the UK did, uh, the story about it. I've seen this story around,
seems like something that's very, very hard to police to me. And it just doesn't make sense.
I would definitely revolt against that. And that's crazy. Absolutely crazy.
Uh, you know what, can you just bear with me one second? I got to have a crap. I've got, uh,
the, uh, the shades here. The sun is now coming in. I can no longer see my computer screen,
because I'm at the Baker's Rock. I, you've probably seen the picture of the set up before.
So all that. I just got a plug in the, I don't have enough outlets. I don't have enough outlets for
all the gear that I'm packing here. So I have to unplug one one a second. So I can plug in the, uh,
the window blinds. They are automatic. There you go. Oh, much better. It's starting to,
I was starting to perspire just a little bit. Okay, and let me plug the computer back in.
Oh, man. I'm so ready to go home. I miss my girls.
Interesting voice mail is coming in. I don't know how this happened, but for some reason now these,
uh, these two numbers, the plus one two one sixty five six three five seven and then the, the,
the UK number, which I can't remember off the top of my head, but it's on daily source code.com.
People are now basically using that as a voice mail to get a hold of me. You know,
which, of course, is really dangerous because we'll play your shit on the air if you use that to call me.
And even though we've been gone for two years from the Netherlands, have not appeared on
anything media-wise in, in the Netherlands at all. No interest. No reason.
I still get calls. It's been a show. Can I come from the data chain for Adam Curry? Oh, check this.
Those of you who are Dutch listeners, you'll probably get a kick out of this.
And we'll meet in a black-nix program that you did to make a mark before someone's making an investment show.
A television show about investors.
At your zeven, um, a pair of lighting interview, uh, not shut the fuck out.
How stupid are they? Why what I want to be on your show about investing?
I'm not interested in that.
It's not wasting my valuable bit time.
Here's something closer to home. Adam Curry was happening. It's a month. It is 7.30 and I am an
onsu in the NISO Hotel. I hope you can come down and join me.
Now, is that, does that mean that monk is in San Francisco?
Let me say.
Ah, to be called to come up. Okay, so I at least is his cell phone number.
Monk, what are you doing, man? I want to, if you think that I'm in New York or if he's in San
San Francisco, dude, you gotta drop by the office today. We're gonna, we'll have some fun for sure.
And, uh, and this was one that I've been waiting for. I've been waiting for someone to comment on this.
I have been love the fact that we've got 24 minute segments.
I am much, much preferable for any four-minute long segments,
feelable again. Much, much, much easier this week to finish my listening day.
But I thought for the first to play trials, which were a bit shorter.
You know, I don't know, a lot of empty trees, one of the zones to play 90-minute long track
and that would get through it. There was a variety of tracks that I've become in this long.
So, I, with my say, I absolutely prefer the split-out deal-more games.
Um, yeah, that's a blessing on this way. It's worth not had anyone saying how great it is.
Really, really, I do much, it's very much the spirit. Thanks for adding.
So, this is indeed something that's been an ongoing discussion about, uh, if you've never heard
the Gilmore gang, go to Gilmore gang.podshow.com, G-I-L-L-M-O-R gang, Gilmore gang.podshow.com.
Steve Gilmore does a weekly, I'd say I just like a chat, a conference call with, um, uh, industry-pundits,
media analysts, not media analysts, the technology analysts, I was the only media analysts.
And, um, you know, there's some interesting people on there. Uh, like Arlington,
uh, from TechCrunch, Jason Calicanas, Weblong Zinc, and AOL, and Netscape. Um, uh, there's always a,
you know, uh, Dan Farber, Dana Gardner, uh, there's always interesting, really, I enjoy listening
to the show. And what Steve has been doing for the past, God, I don't know, months and months and
months is splitting this up into, uh, segments of, you know, 24, 25 minutes, and then releasing them.
And they, of course, they come out on the feed and reverse order. So, you get the end of the show.
First, if you listen to it in, in, in that chronological order, and I've found it rather confusing,
uh, and there's been a lot of debate about it, you know, should you cut, you know, I think we've
been through this with Joseph Jaffee. I don't like it when you cut shit up like that. But at the, of course,
there is no necessarily no right or no wrong, and it's up to Steve to treat his audience over.
He wants to treat him. So this is a happy audience member. And I know I've talked about this
particular show, uh, earlier this week, maybe, yeah, earlier this week, where, um, we talked a lot
about Pod Show, we talked a shitload about Splendid. That was pretty amazing. It was just so,
so fun to hear that the, the Splendid vibe has been, uh, has been cruising throughout, uh,
throughout the network, and everyone's very aware of it. Um, but Jason Calcana's, who I know from
uh, our previous company, when Ron and I had a think new ideas, uh, which, that was a huge company.
It was like 700 people, and we were, we were publicly listed in a, it was a fantastic time. We were
based in New York, uh, the days of Silicon Valley. And Jason Calcana's actually, um, uh, founded,
I guess the Silicon Valley reporter. So, you know, we, we've known Jason for a long time. And, uh,
uh, you know, wherever, in the same time, we will hook up and try to have coffee or drink or something
like that. We exchange ideas from time to time. I mean, I think he's, um, there's a lot of the same
DNA there. Uh, he's an obsessive folder I found out. So that's kind of cool. Uh, but he did something
on the most recent guilt go more going, that I just wanted you to hear. Uh, he did an, an Adam
Curry in, in impersonation or impression. Um, and, uh, well, listen for yourself, make your own decision.
But, uh, I couldn't stop laughing. Miami shells. You know, why are you doing that YouTube? And then
boom, it's like, why comes up, it's like, stop it, you know, stop. You send me that Jason. I want to see
that. That's great. So class. All right. Well, don't be so nice to each other because of the
destroyers. Oh, man. Adam. Yeah. Adam and I are, uh, uh, a good, good pass. I know. I've heard
that's why I can bust the balls a little bit. Well, certainly you knew that coming in didn't just
see. Uh, well, you know, you told me that two days ago. I'm, uh, you know, I can't do it already.
The most is my Adam Curry invitation. I, uh, dude. Um, you got to do it. All right. Let's do it. Well,
it wasn't an impression or impersonation. It's an invitation. There you go. Right out on it.
With $400 million of airplanes trapped to my ass. It was a big side of reaper in my mouth.
And slender being snorted up my nose. I feel like I'm flying into a billion dollar market cap.
Why? When the credit card is, hey, my daughter is going out with this guy. He's, we don't do
show. Ping-pow. Hey. Football is screwed up. Big time, lost a domain. But hey, what are you
going to do? And let me tell you something, Joseph Jacky, you're my bitch boy. Ben Dover,
we're out fold and crunchy for you. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Well, I'm pod. Say if music network
come to live. I'm a Gary Gasville Curry condo. Curry condominium. Curry mode. Great
day, man. Curry coppid. Yeah. I'm crying. Oh, you know, back in the 80s, I was hanging out
with, you know, a mega desk. And we were on the plane and like, everybody was really fucked up.
You know, Phil Collins came in and I mean, Phil, we're talking to you. Phil and I used to hang out all the time.
It's got crazy coke addict. It was insane. Phil and I, we were doing coke from literally.
The bathroom in the back of the G4 all the way up to the pilots. And the pilot, he was doing coke
right across the dashboard. I'm telling the G5. We had to get, we had to get rid of fuel because there
was so much cocaine that we snored. We had to drop fuel. And, yeah, that was the 80s. You know,
and that was the Zinvot MTV is, you know, MTV. I don't even get invited to the 30 years.
But let me tell you something. There was so much cocaine in MTV. It looked like it was Christmas
in Miami all the time. And I was, yeah, when the real world happened and we called it the real
coke. It was the real coke world. I mean, that's basically what it was. And that was great. It was great.
And that's a little bit of that MTV. I'm telling you right now. Hey, it's my wife. How you doing, honey?
I'm all going to be a fan later. Seriously. I know what? My floppy ass. I can't take it anymore.
So flabby. And I'm getting no sex from my wife. And we put it in a bid for another castle.
And I know you guys are broke. But I'm buying my 16th home. And I'm just going to open an ass
because I can only fit four cars in the garage. And I'm trying to convert my neighbor's house into a 16
car garage. And it's a real pain in the ass. My life's terrible. It's terrible. I'm spending my venture
capital on $16,000 around trip virgin elite air ticket. And, you know, virgin elite air.
Let me tell you something. It's fantastic. UPNs will never experience it. No, it's private aviation
like I do. But let me tell you something. I know you want to live by characters for me. They serve
you. Good dive a chocolate. And it's sprinkled with cocaine. I'm not a virgin Atlantic double elite.
I was up there with Richard Branson. It was great. So it was great to Branson. I would hung out a
lot in the 80s. I was great. I'm not saying that my life went downhill after the 80s. But
you say that nobody's life would be what the 80s work. Because he was crazy. It was crazy.
Mega death. I'm telling you poison. Those guys. Holy cow. Mega death. I'm poisoning us.
We used to have crazy crazy crazy times. Crazy times. It was like the first life that
lives it. I was there, you know. It was the first life it. We were there. We're backstage.
Be a white Aussie, Sharon. We're having a great time. Do you mention I know Aussie and Sharon?
Absolutely. Fantastic. I was on Aussie's plane back in 89. He hasn't returned my goal since.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. There were some other fantastic moments in that Gilmore gang. You
should definitely check it out. If you're on a serious star's 102, we have another three and a half hours
of awesome stuff coming your way on the pod show on series today. If you're listening to the
podcast, when you're in luck because we got more stuff. Yeah, we got lots more stuff. No, I don't know
a second. Oh, man. I love that. Let me see what I was going to tell you. I think we're
continuing with another season of Shadow Falls. That's cool news. But I know we're going to have
a call with the Mark Yoshimura and him cough today. There's all kinds of ideas. It's guys full of
fucking ideas. I'm going to do some of that. What else are we doing? Working on some video streaming
stuff that I'm going to tell you about probably next week, end of next week. I'm actually
been testing some stuff. If you go to curie.com, you can find a link somewhere that has a, that's a
test link. It's just a test. Okay. So just just to see kind of some of my, some of the ideas were
working on. And in the big UK launch, first or second week of November, that's on the horizon.
And, and also a refresh, well, refresh, I can overhaul a pod show plus. There's a lot of cool stuff
that we're doing. And, you know, nothing I can show you this week. Excuse me, send it. Say it with some
splinter. But I definitely will be able to talk a little bit more about it next week as some things
have firmed up. It's just cool stuff. Very, very excited. All right, what was this? Oh, check this out.
This is a young polette master. I'll tell you about it after the song. It's like bad 80's pop remix
something listenable.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
And maybe at a silent floor
I'm having four districts
Why choose red lights all the time before
Who just wants to switch to the junction
I've got to get you
You're on maybe at a silent floor
Why choose red lights all the time before
Giving an amulet on a blind
So where did I let your skin shine
Why hold back why try to find it
Take this tension
My kids are like kids
So you're right to have some fun
And the touch of the sunshine
My queen of the night
The world you're real alive
The night you blow my mind
No tied generation seduction
You can find that on the pod save music
Now work that as a project
A mastering project done by young poet
Long time listeners of the Charlie will know that young poet used to do the hit test
Which of course I had to stop doing
When we went completely pod safe
I love doing those hit tests
Young maybe we should do just one more
Just to reprise you know
I'm sure we could get away with one
Just to remind people how cool it was
And how cool it could be if we could actually play
Some of the older songs from our yesterday year
You know the soundtrack to our lives
So young is now apparently the business of mastering stuff
It's pretty cool this is from the UK
No tied generation
As I said it's been like really bad 80s pop
But it sounds cool and new and fresh
Thank you very much for sending me that to sending that to me young
Give me a call 201 65657
That's a plus one
If you got yourself on put the plus in first
So if you travel outside the country's borders
You can still call into the Charlie 201 65657 in the UK
In London, O2O 766113753
Alright tomorrow will be food bar Friday
Hopefully an assur-size from Amy Mack
I have not seen anything show up today
And I didn't hear any knock at the door
So hopefully I'll have that
And of course I'm sure our musicologist
Jersey Todd will check in with a couple of cool tunes
To roll out for you
And then I'll be going home
I'm very very ready
It's been a shitty shitty two weeks
A lot of fun, a lot of productive stuff
A lot of good things, business wise
Fun with everyone, good to see everybody at the office
But I felt like absolutely fucking crap
So I can't wait to get home and be pampered
He's been promised to me
Talk to you, everybody, for Food Bar Friday
Take care
Another pod show podcast
Stick it in your ear
Oh wait man
Almost forgot that, that's pretty damn important
Get this pod cast and more great ones like it
On the high performance pod cast delivery network
From pod show and lime light networks
I love it