Already a hit state side, now you can check out the following podcast and good old
blightybtpodshot.com, single-handedly making a man's for giving you Madonna, one show at a time.
80 Patricia, and of course, your host Adam Curry, Delta Sierra Charley Ford 9 or 6.
I'd like to thank you all for coming here today.
You all know me, I am done, Lindon, of ask, play none, and three blind mice.
I'd like to make you an offer you can refuse.
Please come see me, subscribe me too.
Charlie, all day, he's so cute!
The podcast of my good friend.
Adam Curry!
And making a substantial financial contribution
toward the smooth morning of the show.
In the acquisition of a suitable family villa in Sicily.
In return, I will try and answer any questions you may have.
And also, I pledge to protect your family's from this intimidation.
To eat this wreck a kid on, ask me for slain on the radio.
It's turns our should all act clear.
With the dispossence of melody that might just catch their ears.
Whoa, this...
Oh, my baby, we should go on and roll out some slain, we should go on.
And roll out some...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, we're headed straight for the...
Oh, we're headed straight for...
Oh, we're headed right for the...
Oh, we're headed straight for the...
Oh, we're headed straight for....
We had it straight for the hit parade, it's on the pod save music network and music.potshot.com.
or you could go to potshot.com and click on music and you get a whole new kind of potsate music experience.
And after I checked yesterday, indeed the buy buttons will be showing up in the players.
And actually those will be the embeddable players will have the buy button linked right into it.
So you can help out your band, your favorite band, just if you're a fan or if you have a band,
buy embedding the player with the band songs. Of course, we pony up for the band with and all that stuff.
Of the 99 cents, 90 cents goes to the artist, 9 cents in transaction fees. We just want people to enjoy.
There's some major work going on in the background today here at the Curry Cottage in the affluent suburb of Surrey, known as Gilford.
You hear it there? Actually, it's not that bad right now. It was really bad early on like I was going to.
It's just, it was just par for the mood that I'm in. I had words with Christina this morning on the way to school because
it went those big teenager, you know, just a big mouth, you know what I mean? Then and she
sometimes she just forgets that, you know, if you say it in a normal tonal voice, it's okay, you know,
she gets so defensive. It really it really throws me off whack when when I'm with my daughter
after saying it just like bugs me for the rest of the day. It hurts me than more than her turn, right?
I guess that's it. Well, once in a while, I just got to say, please don't talk to your mom that way.
Don't talk to me that way. Don't talk to anyone that way. You're not going to get anywhere in life.
And you know what? In the past couple of weeks, I've talked to a lot of grownups who talk like that.
And it's annoying. It really is like no one ever said, hey, shut up.
So as always, when I'm feeling a little bit blue and I just don't know what to do, I reach down
deep into the pod safe music bag of tricks. And I come up with this song, which always makes me feel good.
You may sing a lot. You may sing a lot.
Here we go.
I think a look at my enormous feelings. And the happy times are coming to stay.
I got to sing and I dance when I glancing my pants. I am the feeling like a sunshine he did.
Take a look at how he normates.
Venus and everything is going my way.
Yeah. The Vinci's notebook and my enormous penis from the pod safe music network.
Speaking of which, check this out.
Hey Adam, it's Gizelle from San Diego.
You know, I was thinking about it and I wasn't going to say anything, but I'm on my way to work.
And I just have to tell you, I got really pissed off at you for saying that you thought I was
speaking my last song all to you. I was totally not taking it.
So anyway, I got pissed off and I stopped listening to your show. I have to admit it. I'm sorry.
I stopped listening. And then I saw my ex-boyfriend over the weekend.
Got all horny. Went out with him. I saw a guy that went like you.
I kid you not. He had blonde hair. He wasn't as cute as you, but he did kind of look like you.
Totally reminded me of you. And I got all horny again. Went home and, you know,
anyway, I made me think about you and I missed you. And I really really want to meet you.
And I really really want to do you. Anyway, if that makes me crazy, then I'm crazy.
I just wanted you to know how I felt. And hopefully we can get together someday and get crazy together. Bye.
I wish I had time to use my enormous penis. I certainly have opportunity.
Well, Giselle, I'm sorry. I really, you know, a couple of the people said to me,
they really thought it sounded like you were reading off a piece of paper last time.
So I didn't mean to offend you in that regard. How far is San Diego from San Francisco?
I'm going Sunday. I'm going to be on San Francisco next week.
We don't celebrate Thanksgiving here. So maybe there might be some lost souls to celebrate with
in San Francisco at the office. Giselle, if you want to come
celebrate Thanksgiving, then what am I doing?
Hi Adam. I see you still haven't found out to change the message at the beginning of the recording.
Okay. I can't live with that. I have a complaint to make. So this pod show plus
unbeater thing that I am currently getting when I try to go to any of the pod show sites.
We interrupt your pod show and be key pod show social media experience for a taste of the
plus. Fine. I've had a taste. Now I want to go and look at the shows that I want to go look at.
There's no sign on here saying whether this is because of a technical issue or whether this is going to
be, you know, try again in an hour. Try again in a couple of days. I'm not liking this dude.
I'm missing my shows. I want them back. Thank you very much.
Hi. Yeah. I apologize for that. What happened was we had an outage yesterday. I'm not
quite sure how long it lasted. I think at least 30 minutes, maybe even an hour and it was like
an infrastructure thing. And I've come to learn that, you know, someone says, hey, it's this
and this and this and the infrastructure and that's it. I just wait and then wait from to fix it
and they, they always do. But what happened in that case is automatically
our unleash page rolled over and went live, which of course we had changed for the unleash,
which was scheduled downtime. And without a doubt, that page should have changed for this
downtime. But I think that people were just trying to get stuff up in a hurry and didn't want
to bother with with any of the details. But I apologize. That was not the right message.
Absolutely. You mentioned something very interesting there at the beginning of
at the beginning of your comment that the phone, the phone lines, the daily source code
voicemail that you call to leave a message. Wait a minute. Those numbers of course.
And that's for if you're in the United States. If you're in the United Kingdom,
we have a number especially for you.
So I heard something really interesting on the BBC radio one. I think it was a
was the Chris Moile show and I was trying to remember the name of what they called it. I
think they called it the date diversion line. It was actually very funny. The concept is you use one
of those phone numbers. Like if you're in the US, you say, hey, you know, call me my US cell phone number
is 20665657. And in the UK, you can use the UK number. But since it doesn't have a greeting,
it's kind of undefined like it could be anyone's voice mail. And so if you meet someone
who wants to go out with you or is desperately trying to get a date and ask you for your phone
number, you give them the daily source code number instead. And then when they call in,
we'll play the comments back. We'll play the recordings back or what those people said.
So feel free to do that or anything else you want to do, they are after all your phone line numbers.
Hi, I'm Matt and Newton here. Hope I find you well. I just like to comment on the situation
or the conversation rather between yourselves and the man and woman who was speaking about
Port City PD. I found the conversation fascinating for several reasons, but I just wanted to say that
for me the strap line for you also the podcasting is Adam Curry. It's never been true.
That conversation, I have no idea why it really hit the spot for me. I think it almost bruised
the gap between reality and virtual technology etc. And podcasting and I really think that
that's the sort of thing podcasting should be and it really hit the spot for me. The lady that was
was speaking, I just want to say to her, you feel a fantastic job and I'm sure you make some
fantastic family therapists and just thank you on the last days that you helped. I hope
thank you well and I love to say and keep doing what you did. Take care. Thank you.
Folder? Scruncher? Bet you was a folder. Well, I appreciate the comment and you're right.
We do try to keep it civil here on the source. So this is a reference to Susanna Robin from
Inside Works, calling in about the Port City PD promo. And along the way in the conversation
in this back and forth, we've discussed the placement of where's my fucking latte,
which is a fantastic show, which Mark Yoshimoto Namcoff does, you know, from Pacific Coast
Hellway. And it's essentially diaries of executive assistance or personal assistance of Hollywood.
So not just of stars, but also of directors, producers, etc. And they're really, really entertaining
to listen to. And Robin noticed correctly that the logo for the show had gone from where's my
fucking latte to where's my F apostrophe C.K. ING latte. And question the censorship, which we're
past that. But luckily Mark Yoshimoto Namcoff was listening in and here he is with his
slant on what went on with the art for the program, where's my fucking latte? Is it fucking
without you? Well, I guess that's the question and no Adam. Keep your pants on because I'm not
talking about you personally. I'm talking about the letter you and how it applies to so-called
self-censorship and my show wears my fucking latte. Well, Robin from Inside Works mentioned yesterday
on daily source code that my show wears my fucking latte, which is a collection of Hollywood
assistant stories that I gathered here in town, had gone from where's my fucking latte to the
word fucking with an apostrophe where the you used to be. So it's fucking without you, which might
be appropriate for the internet. And the story, which is hardly worth telling once let alone twice,
is that Joe Carpenter called me up one day and he said, look, where's my fucking latte
tiles up on the front of the pod show site every now and then? And sometimes in the cosmic randomness
of the laws of random, it ends up right next to like bedtime stories for my kids. Now let me
make this clear. Joe did not tell me to change it. At no point did he say, you got to remove the word
fucking from the title because, you know, the word fucking next to bedtime stories is usually only
reserved for well pacific ghost hallway, which reminds me you got to come on the show and tell
that story about the time you passed out on out in John's yacht or even better the one with
Kurt Loder and the latex fist. But I digress. What it came down to is I understood Joe's concern
and he actually had a really good point. Is that the word fucking even with an asterisk in it?
Was just a salacious even more so? Some may even say titillating. I just like saying titillating.
Then the word fucking with the you in it because this way you can get away with just putting
fucking right out there without it really being fucking. And I thought, well that's pretty
fucking subversive and truth be told when the print version of where's my fucking latte comes out
with a whole bunch of other stories that weren't in the podcast. The plan had always been
to put the asterisk in in the word fucking anyway because I'd seen a bunch of covered designs
and the one that actually had the asterisk in it was to me a lot more eye catching
than the version that just had the word fucking on it and also we knew there would be a marketing
problem with a version that just had the word fucking in it without the asterisk. So yes in the end
it was a business decision and not censorship that changed fucking from fucking to fucking with an asterisk.
And not only did I create this comment for you just so I could say the word fucking about
46 times on your show. Which I still fucking love I got to tell you I got to tell you man.
But also it gives me an excuse to tell you that in the latest chapter of where's my fucking latte
I dig into my own personal vault of stories and talk about how my upcoming podcast novel number
one with a bullet which started out life as a feature film script that I had optioned several times
all over this town and went through a lot of years of development hell. Before I realized
that screenplays are routinely taken away from their creators who are oftentimes left
with hardly credit on the final product and then how I was able to reclaim it and turn it into an
intellectual property. So Adam thanks for your time and in the end iTunes never allowed me to put
latte in their podcast directory. They're the ones that chose to censor it because of the title.
I have no idea what their fucking problem is.
Alright well that clears it up. Obviously the word latte is a problem mark. Can't you figure that out?
Look at my Google notebook. I really love this Google notebook. If you haven't seen it
where did you get it from? Google.com slash notebook and you can install it into any browser
and stores your notes on the server. These guys are so smart. It's kind of like an outline
because you can add subsections and so I'm looking at that now. A couple of things just
wanted to wing by you for a second. Good news looks like the clear channel breakup is starting.
We talked about this. The final phase in any company's existence or any industry's existence
actually is when the company starts to roll up and then it goes private and after that
after it has all the assets, a long-come guys like KKR. Let me see who's actually bidding for this.
Apollo Management, Carlisle, Sabirius Capital, Oak Hill partners. There's KKR. So essentially they're
going to break up this company and they're going to sell all the individual assets and that will be
the end of mainstream radio as we know it my friends because it'll just be bits and pieces and
not coordinated. No we're near the power that we have in podcasting. So that's a nice light note for
today. Great to link from Sinclair who sent me a link to openatc.com. If you're in
aviation, you got to check this out. You can download a KML file which is a Google Earth file
and it will show you with a five minute delay but it's exciting nonetheless. It will show you all
of the current IFR flight paths in any region around the globe and you can actually see the flight
numbers and see where the aircraft is. As of five minutes ago but still extremely cool in
it auto updates openatc.com. You definitely got to look at that. And then finally and this is a
little concerning. I've been getting a lot of people emailing me and a lot of pointers to this post
that Steve Gilmore put on his gesture lab which is gesturelab.com. And it's about the most
recent Gilmore gang. Now I want to say upfront that I feel the past weeks, maybe even the past
months of Gilmore gang have been really exemplary. The addition of Jason Calacanis has been fantastic
and I hear the same message basically. You know people listen to the show sometimes just because
they love to hate it so much which is great. Now that is the stuff that great shows are made of.
And Steve wrote this post, really emotional. The let it be gang is the title of it and he says
that he's really unhappy with the way he is on the show even though he knows the show is really
liked now. Maybe he doesn't want the show to be liked. I don't know maybe he's not trying to make
entertainment maybe he's trying to do something else but that's not clear from the post.
But apparently a lot of this came out during the most recent recording of the Gilmore gang,
the let it be gang. And so he only released three pieces. You know how he breaks up the show.
He only released three pieces and says he doesn't want to release the other piece of the show
because he hated the way he sounded on it and he felt that the whole show fell to shit. And obviously
I think that's a huge shame because I'd love to know what it's about. Interestingly enough,
Dan Farber, who was on the show, he has this he waxes very poetic about the only way that
audio and video and podcasting is going to work. He is a clairvoyant and quite a visionary.
And he says that independent is the way to go and this is the reason why Steve hates doing his
show on pod show. And he points to this page and I look at it and I don't see anything about that.
So maybe that was what was in the second half of the Gilmore gang that has not been aired. And I think
as an audience member, I think we deserve to know what's going on. I really think we deserve to hear about it.
So it's quite a shame. I really love to know more. And just if you read that post,
and of course I'll put a link in the show notes. It's emotional stuff. I'm like, wow, you know.
There's anything I can do to help. But I don't really know what the problem is because
everyone else seems to know, but I can't help. Otherwise, yeah, what I have done is
a company man and all I registered to Gilmorelessgang.com just in case.
Yeah. I just like to say what's the success. I think your screen phone to campaign is.
Every time I'm doing any activity involving tissues, I always think it's you with crying,
cleaning the staffing of fire. I always wish you a bad night's side. So maybe you should get
sponsored in this possible. It makes nice, soft toilet height for a mighty white mags.
If I can now. Roger. Roger. Roger. What a brilliant idea. I think that's fantastic. And
was it the wanker mags? Do you fold or scrunch after a, after a wank? Well, that's the next big question
on our minds. Roger and I've had some back and forth emails and private conversation. And I really
don't think he's going to come to podcast con UK. Between you and I, I think that he feels that his
appearance, you know, people ridicule him or something like that. So I really want to build up his
confidence, but I don't think we're going to build it up before podcast con UK. But Roger, I just
do want you to know, even though you probably won't show up, you really are a pillar of podcasting
in the UK. And I just love you to death, man. Absolutely. Yeah, by the way, that domain name,
I registered Gilmore less gang.com. I used DS, the three checkout code got myself a great deal,
695, go daddy.com. All right, everybody on serious. I'll talk to you guys tomorrow. And for those of you
still here, let's listen to some more complaining. Hey, Adam, this is Steve Dinn from Halifax on the East
Coast of Canada. I was just listening to show 495 and I had a comment about what you said about the
Zoom. Now, I probably won't be getting a Zoom anytime soon, but that's beside the point.
My point is, who cares that the Zoom doesn't support podcasting? What does that even mean?
Why does a portable device need to support podcasting? Do iPod support podcasting? No, they actually
don't. iTunes supports podcasting. So you're going to accomplish the same thing with the combination
of any old podcast downloader like Juice and a fantastic feature of Windows Media Player that I
sorely wish was in iTunes. Media Player can scan a directory. So it monitors a directory on your
hard drive and can automatically add new files to your Media Player library. So I then used a dynamic
playlist to automatically sync un-listened to files from my Media Player library to my portable
player. And it's just goes to show the end-general. I think it's better to have multiple tools that do
one thing very well than to have a single behemoth that tries to do everything. That's the end of my
comment. So this is the start of my plug. SpineRadio.com. And folder. Yeah, folder. Okay.
I think well you make a good point. Although I don't look at these as devices. I look at them
as receivers. And I think that the general public looks at them as receivers. I spent an hour with
Christina yesterday. Here's what she wanted to do. She wanted to move all of her songs
from iTunes. She doesn't have an iPod. She lost it or broke it or whatever. Into her creative
Zen player. And what she was about to do, she was about to just delete everything. When she opened
up Windows Media Player, the software that controls the device. Because, you know, she doesn't know
any other way to do. It just doesn't know about, you know, about mounting it and opening it and
dragging stuff in directly. She just, you know, what popped open is Windows Media Player. That's the
way it's configured. And as she was about to just delete all of that, not knowing that it would
the same files because both iTunes and Windows Media Player scan your entire drive upon request.
Which, of course, everyone says yes. That's where, you know, I've seen people look at dialogue
boxes. Okay. Okay. Click. Okay. Click. Okay. Click. Okay. Then I don't even read anymore. So by default,
what happens? And it's just shitty software. You know, and all people who make software make shitty software.
The files were essentially the same because there were files that, you know, and all illegal
MP3s, I'm sure, as she had downloaded and put onto iTunes initially. And then Media Player had
scanned those same files. So she was about to delete a boot to delete everything, as you would say.
And so I was able to stop her, but it's really complicated. So I guess what we're all looking for
is a standard way, just so we can make it easy. It's what is what was attempted with the standard way to
subscribe, which is the RSS, why don't orange XML button? Well, that didn't work. And look at it now.
Now, you got like 20 fucking buttons to subscribe to stuff easily. That's not what you want. And would you
want a television or a radio that couldn't receive signals that you could receive on another
television or radio? I think that's the analog way that people still kind of look at these things.
Instead of podcasting support, perhaps I should say, couldn't we just have one comment? Maybe
just all players, when you plug them in, they just open up and then, you know, you can drag stuff
onto them. It wouldn't that be the easiest. It doesn't work that way with the iPod as example.
And the iPod has the market. But I think you know the point, just want to make it easier for
everybody. I know you know how to do this stuff. You know, you've been listening, you've been following
along. You had to learn. You didn't know from day one. It's much harder to learn when all the cool
people are doing it and no one's really sharing the information. It's just hard. Just trying to make it
easy. That's all. Well, I'm fat. And it just forces trying to hold my forces out. I want to get
serious yet. Because I sure wasn't looking. Man, I'm meant to. Ever since a day, we met.
Now I'm falling in deep prey. And for sleep, three hours a night ain't enough.
Yeah, just call their baby. Lord, help, baby. And just a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a
something tells me there's no such thing. A little bit of a little
and the next thing, you know, you're out behind the ring. And there's got to be strong and I'm trying to
hold on. But be in that tough thrill. But I'm all about her. One thing's for sure. I'm just a little
little bit of a little.
Ever since Rose, neighbors getting notes. She's been over three times this week.
The last little sweeten. Every time I see her, I'm thinking that I must be.
Something tells me there's no such thing. A little and the next thing, you know, you're out
behind the ring. A man's got to be strong and I'm trying to hold on. But be in that tough
thrill too. Because I'm all about her. One thing's for sure. I'm just a little
little. Well, I guess it sounds crazy. It's too late to save me. I know there I know, Rose.
So I must look funny. Down here on the one here, five just a little and a little
love. Something tells me there's no such thing. A little and the next thing, you know, you're
out behind the ring. A man's got to be strong and I'm trying to hold on. But be in that tough
thrill too. Because I'm all about her. One thing's for sure. I'm just a little
in love. I'm just a little in love. I'm just a little in love. I'm just a little in love.
Sean Patrick McGraw. The spot to save music never worth. I'm just a little in love.
Why ended up in Charlie for today? I'm happy now if you don't mind. All right, everybody.
I will be back here tomorrow. Take care of yourself. Bye bye.
Another pod show podcast. Stick it in your ear.