This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 4-1-1.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic, it's Adam Curry!
I know everything's all just a little bit crazy.
Days gone by month and year I'm fine.
Your friends let's say you should blame me.
I think that I'm wrong, I know they're right.
I said it home, we didn't fall in for you for me.
I know you'll think I'll be heaven fun.
Let me tell you that my life is boring.
And I miss the times we had when we were young.
I'm sorry for the way I left you standing there.
I know I made you look just like a...
I know it's hard to make up.
I know it's hard to wake up.
All I want is you that you're my yours.
I know all you need is a little time.
Someone just bring me next year.
I hope you know that I'll read in minutes.
I will fly around the world to make you see.
I'm sorry for the way I left you standing there.
I know I made you look just like a...
I know it's hard to make up.
I know it's hard to wake up.
All I want is you that you're my yours.
I'm sorry for the way I left you standing there.
I know I made you look just like a...
I know it's hard to make up.
I know it's hard to wake up.
All I want is you that you're my yours.
I'm sorry for the way I left you standing there.
I know I made you look just like a...
I know it's hard to make up.
I know it's hard to wake up.
All I want is you that you're my yours.
That's too bad you didn't listen to the whole song because I was playing it for you.
Back in my arms.
Yes.
Hey just sitting there like looking into space.
No, I was listening.
How?
I didn't know it was three.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
I welcome to the loud enough...
If you don't have it, I know.
Come to the daily source code.
It's Monday coming to you once again from the cottage.
We're back.
A rive yesterday morning from San Francisco.
And I'm back with my lovely girls.
And you feel like shit.
I feel like total crap.
I really do.
But I didn't sleep yesterday.
Didn't have my regular nap except for after the...
After the Holland versus Portugal game.
I think I was drooling for an hour or so.
Wasn't I drooling on the couch?
Totally dead.
But can you imagine how your body is feeling?
The body doesn't know where it is?
Oh, my body is saying...
Day or night?
My body is saying...
You're almost 42.
Are you out of your mind?
What are you doing?
But don't you think you could use to that?
Yeah.
If that's a body you could use to doing these things.
Yeah, oh yeah.
I think so.
Oh yeah.
You were even more used to it last time.
Which of course is my problem because...
I do very well.
You are fantastic.
But I have to say you're losing weight.
Yeah, no shit.
No shit.
What do you expect?
Do you think I lost?
Are you feeding you there?
No.
I've got no girlfriends in the corner.
You have to be careful.
People are going to bring food to you.
There's one rule I had at MTV.
It's like, once if someone leaves food from me, it'd throw it out.
Yeah.
Not going to eat food that someone prepared that I don't know.
That's very dangerous.
People send brownies and cookies.
I'm sure it was all the best attention.
Yeah, you never know.
Hey, just wanted to say something about that song.
The one I played for you that you weren't listening to.
Yeah.
It's not true.
I was listening.
The band is called Tate in My Arms.
This is from South Africa.
Really?
This band.
Yeah, this is Glenn from the Zed A show.
To Americans that would be the Zed A show.
We say Zed A.
He sent in this email.
It was like, he got, it was it.
A huge independent label in Cape Town called Fresh Music.
He got him to upload over 30 tracks.
The podcast music network.
This is just one of them.
It's cool, isn't it?
Very cool.
No idea what the pop scene was like.
No.
It's South Africa.
And apparently a live and well and vibrant.
And you know what?
I always meet people from South Africa, especially in England.
Especially in England.
And we can always speak with them because they speak South Africa.
Which is very similar to South Africa.
Do you speak South Africa?
And they say, yeah.
So yesterday we went to look at this house that Patricia found while I was gone.
Which is without a doubt a spectacular home.
Yes.
Spectacular.
And the guys also from South Africa.
Beautiful views.
Amazing views.
Yeah.
I got to go count the pennies, baby.
See if we can afford it.
It's beautiful.
Yeah.
It's expensive here.
But this is really, it's the Beverly Hills of the,
Yeah.
Or maybe it's at the Hollywood Hills.
The Hollywood Hills of Gilford.
I found it.
It's beautiful.
Finally found it.
You look all the way down.
And you can see how Gilford lay in there.
Yeah.
And it's beautiful.
There's no place to land a helicopter I noticed.
No.
I wouldn't.
It's a pity.
It's just a minor pity.
But man, was that a great house?
Yes.
It's a holy crap.
No.
And you know what you liked?
Yeah.
Because it looks a bit like a man's thing in there.
Totally.
This guy got it together, man.
He designed this thing, right?
Yeah.
Because he likes it.
Everything goes switch off switch on.
You can all do it by a remote.
Wireless sound throughout the entire house.
Plasma screens building.
That's why you had to see it because yeah, this is what you want.
And normally you have to, you know, you have to put that in, which never happens.
No.
Because I don't even have music in my living room downstairs.
Nothing.
Or did you request it?
Oh, don't you think that is, you know, the most normal thing you were you to have?
No.
Well, I miss it.
When we're in the living room, we only want to television or entertain guests.
No.
You know, all the, also the reception room and family room.
For your clients?
I didn't.
And do my, you know, my reading and, and it's nice because now.
Okay.
I got the message.
Yeah.
When I got the message.
Just, I just played the four seasons downstairs because, you know, it was raining a little bit.
Your, you know, you could be a disco jockey because I'm in the bathroom and I hear Patricia go.
Oh, I think I should play some four seasons.
It's evolved.
Yeah.
I haven't played them for a long time because, you know, it's not really classic.
They call it actually popular.
I think it's classic and not for me.
So, and I saw the, you know, it was dark and a little bit, a little bit hazy.
And I thought, yeah.
Yeah.
And I thought, oh, it's a pity.
Can't play it in living room.
Okay.
Well, I'll make sure you can.
Can't play house.
Yeah.
That's the problem is that we're renting the cottage.
We cannot open the walls.
We've been here for a year and a half and I have to say we're pretty sick of the place.
I mean, it's a great house and it's got, it's the location you almost can't be.
It doesn't function.
Well, you can't do anything because and everything we do to the house would be for the, for the, for
Cox, for Kevin Cox, for the owner.
Well, I like him a lot, but I'm not going to.
Sweet.
Yeah.
I'm not going to fix his house.
No, because things you need and you want to do, you know, you can do that.
No.
So, I missed you.
I missed you too.
I don't know.
But this time, I really, really miss.
You know, why is because I've been, we've been together for two months.
That maybe that was it.
We were in Portugal.
I was here.
What were getting the pleasure.
You came off us going.
Then we went to California together.
We came back.
Yeah.
And then I kind of like, and also because I left a day earlier than planned.
I kind of like did a, we came back.
You and I and we did a 360 and I went right back.
Yeah.
Almost a week later.
Right.
That's why I'm tired.
Yeah.
I'm wrecked.
That was pretty tough.
Yeah.
You know, being with Christina all the time.
So for teenage level.
So this is interesting Friday.
Friday morning.
I was at the Department of Motor Vehicles, which is a fantastically fun place to be in San Francisco.
I had to get Trinity registered.
And I have to get a California driver's license on that crap.
And there's only one department of motor vehicles and all of San Francisco.
Only one.
And it's, it's always fun.
Very fun.
And so just as I'm at the counter.
You know, getting ready to go through all this paperwork.
I look at my blackberry and there's a message from you.
And you tell me that Christina had an accident in a school.
And I want my, my, my gut just went, oh my God.
Yeah.
You want to tell the story?
Well, I got the same call from school.
Here's the call.
You never want to receive.
No, never.
Never.
So it was sports day.
And a couple of schools in Guildford had sort of a sports day.
Field day as we call it.
No, yeah, it's a sports day.
But in Yemen and states, I say, field day.
And Christina said, in the morning, I'm not feeling well.
My neck is a little bit stiff.
I don't think I go.
And I thought, well, it's pity because you know, the teenager.
And she's good at it.
And she's good at running to move a little bit.
Because they're already a little bit lazy.
A little bit.
And yeah.
And she got MSN, but my space asks.
And they do snack a lot.
You know, so that should, you know, of course.
You snack.
You have to also move physical education.
Very important.
That's right.
So I said, you know, she was going.
And she didn't want to.
Then we got a call at nine thirty from her girlfriends from school.
And we heard all giggling in the old outside and everything.
And it was nice weather.
So there's the orchestra in the police.
Come, please.
If we need you, because you're such a great runner.
Was it against another school or just different classes?
I don't know.
I think so.
It was something going up.
And she said, Mama, should I go at you?
Okay, you're such a great runner.
You should go.
You know, it's good.
It's nice weather.
And if you don't want to just be there.
And so she went.
So I felt so guilty afterwards.
You forced it to go and look what happened.
Okay.
So you got a phone call.
So I got a phone call.
And they said, Christine had an accident.
And she's already.
The ambulance is coming.
And I hear ambulance.
And my God.
It's like your heart.
You want to like you want to puke immediately.
Yeah.
So I said, where is she?
And they told me the guilt for the royal guilt for the hospital.
No clue where it is, of course.
Where is it actually?
Is it the one near school?
I don't even know where I went there.
Well, how did you get there?
I called the taxi.
I called the cab.
And I drove behind him.
Oh, okay.
You had a.
Because I don't know how long it takes.
So sorry.
And you still don't know where it is.
You just followed him.
I followed him.
Okay.
But I found my way back.
Good girl.
When I came down, I was actually earlier than ambulance.
And I had to give.
And it's so funny.
Because you have to give your name.
You have to give.
You know, Christina was born.
I didn't know anything anymore.
I said, I'm so, I'm Dutch.
Oh.
No, not just.
My brain is moist.
No, I'm Dutch.
I'm so, I'm Dutch.
And I'm so nervous.
Yeah.
So I'm very nervous.
I didn't know anymore.
I didn't know my address.
But then.
Did you have your teeth in?
Yes.
Well, you know, no, there was nothing to smile about.
No, no, no, no.
Um.
But I could just imagine.
I gave it.
I don't know who I am.
There's one with no teeth.
Remember when I was pregnant?
That's the same thing.
I didn't know, you know, lots of things that I didn't know anymore.
No.
Which is normal for pregnant women.
I think I, I think I didn't remember either.
I think I was.
When you were pregnant, I was in mush too.
All right.
So come on.
People want to hear the story now.
Yeah.
So she came in.
And I hear her outside.
And I hear
I hear
And the door's open.
And Christina screaming.
Um, she dislocated her kneecap.
Well, it was located on the outside.
Oh, that's so horrible.
And that freaking hurts.
Yeah, no kidding.
That hurt so much.
Yeah.
And.
I said, I mean, is this?
Mom, you see your mom is here.
Yes, she didn't, she did.
a nitrous oxide. They gave her nitrous oxide so she told you. She's sucking on something.
Yeah, he is. She said she was really stoned. I'm stoned.
She was saying that. She was saying I'm stoned. That's my daughter.
Yeah. So anyway, so she's been home now for her.
How do you know about stone darling? You said that night, so they popped it back.
Yeah, so no, she had to, when she came in, you have to wait so long.
I think you die if you, if you know, if you're, I mean, obviously a kneecap.
This okay, kneecap is a press, press, or it's you in.
Yeah, of course, but there must be some other people with, I mean, it's not life-threatening. So
no, it's just like any emergency room. The ambulance is they, they are all queuing
with their, with their patients for the patient. Sure. Sure. So took a while, finally a
Chinese doctor came and he said, well, I have to put it back. No, she screamed no. So they gave her
a letter, more, read on something else. More, more, more night or so.
We're relaxed, her, her muscle. And while the muscles were relaxed, he puk her pop. Pop the
back. Pop the back. Pop the back, so that was it. But now it's like sort of a baby head. It's so.
It is, man. It's huge. Yeah. But as it's, and I'm going to do her show with her today. So she'll
tell, exactly what happened. She'll tell that part of the story because she's ready to do another
pod save the queen. Yeah. Yeah. So, all as well, the end's well, I guess.
Me. Yeah. That's, that was pretty frightening. It was actually, I felt so horrible. Of course.
And I said, oh, go, it's beautiful. Well, and I feel felt so guilty about it. See, Mom, I shouldn't have
got, oh, yeah, she's going to lay that out on the road for quite a while. You know, fried, I know
you don't listen to the show. But Friday, I played another song for you, actually. I know,
but you know, sometimes I talk about you. And I'm, but we'll play another song for you.
Yeah, but didn't I tell you that if I sit and do things on the internet, that thinks in the house,
and it's all about it. It's in the refrigerator. So I said to you, you know, I know now that it's
not good when Mommy sit, you know, and this, and it's automatic. You don't have to sit and listen.
You can just walk around, like you listen to Terry Morgan, except you actually have sex with me.
And not with Terry Morgan. No, but I, you know, I need to hear the news and know that I got news.
And then you call, and then I hear you. No, but see, the thing is, is if you want to know really what's
going on, see, whenever we call, when I'm in San Francisco, the eight hours time difference. So either you're
going to sleep, or I'm going to sleep, or I mean, we're almost exact opposite to the clock. And I'm not,
and I'm high, right? And you're asleep. Right. So we rarely really have anything to say other than, hey,
how you doing, yet it's going great. It's 11 o'clock in the morning. And then you said to me, something
wrong, no, I said, tired. End of the day. Right. But if you, if you would listen to the show,
then you could hear what's going on. Okay. What's going on, dear? Well, no, I just wanted you to,
so someone else, a couple of other people were listening to the show. Yeah. And one guy
called in about this song that I played for you. Yeah, it's nice. It's kind of for an hour.
This is me. This is me. This is better. I've gotta go home. See, I'm screaming. I gotta go home.
This is my Pico. I'm the voice of Scotty eyes on children of the gods.
I mean, that's W. W. W. That's one of the gods done. Next. I'm also, uh, the guy who does the
creepy podcasting news with Garland P on the Sunday Go to meet in podcast, which is never on Sunday.
Anyway, I wanted to say that this song, when you play at the end of the SC410 on 6206,
happened to coincide with the last five minutes of my day and I'll pay it gave me the drive to get
one more thing done. I want to thank you for that. Thank you very much. I hope you've had a
soap, fake trip home and enjoy your girls. You hear this song? I'm going home. Yeah.
Yeah, it's very song. I'll play that some other time. Isn't it nice if you, you know,
you're happy to go home? Yeah. Go be the other way around. I got no place to go in. I don't want to go home.
Oh, it's so. Yeah. If you want to call in, uh, we certainly would like to hear from you this week.
I'm going to be home for a couple of weeks now. They've got nice. Yes. We have a numbers feed
to call in New Jersey. 201, 201, 605, 657, or in London, O2O7, 681, 3753. Because people have
called in for you as well, but now the comments are so old. It's warm. Is it just me or is it warm? No,
you know, I know, you know, you just put on the heater. Well, but you turned it down, didn't you?
I turned it off. Yeah. I don't know. My body is on the place. But I was called this morning because
it's a wet outside. That's making a little bit, you know. So what the hell did you do for two weeks?
You were, you know, I know what you were doing. You were watching football. I was watching football.
I had my, my, my, my, my, um, operation. It's nice to those pieces of, uh, of iron in my
image. Yeah. They put the metal rods in your head. Yeah. So I was very, very great. And I felt so alone.
Yeah. See, not, go ahead. Stick the knife in. Yeah. I feel, that's what, yeah. It's just not,
not good. No, it's not good. I mean, you know, you come home and then you teenage, you said,
oh, yeah, you went to the, uh, okay. How are you? Yeah, okay. He makes somebody eat for me. Yeah.
And now I want. And now I would like to, uh, yeah. I was amazed at how into the football you were.
I was in meetings and you were sending me the score. Yeah. You were texting me the score.
I said, this can't be my wife. She must be there with like three guys. It's impossible. Yeah.
I've never known you to watch football. Even, they're so buy yourself. They're so good.
Oh, yeah. This is it. I think since David Beckham is, uh, you're smiling and your eyes are,
are just twinkling all of a sudden. Great bodies. And I'm waiting at the end of the, uh,
thing, when they take off their shirts. Oh, are you really serious? No, of course. No, I think you are.
I'm too intelligent for that. What head of a port? Is that have to do with it? That's nothing to do with it.
I like it when women take off their shirts. I'm pretty intelligent. It's nothing. So,
literally nothing wrong with that. But Beckham, yes, they may be puking all over the place. That was,
yeah, well, that's interesting. No. No, I didn't think it was interesting. I felt bad for it.
Yeah, yeah. But what a goal, man. Yeah, but it was a real. That gave, they gave you a
beautiful, that was Beckham. That was Beckham, man. That was unbelievable. Yes,
today was a double header. Um, it was the Netherlands against Portugal. Yeah. And the winner of that
game would determine who would play against England. And I was so ready for a Holland England match.
And what a game. What a game. I mean, three guys kicked off the field. The most yellow cards handed
out ever. He was he for history. Oh, the, uh, the referee. He didn't have the game under control.
No, no, it was just handing out all those yellow cards. Yeah. But I think Portugal was a little
bit stronger. I mean. Oh, but they've, but didn't we didn't Holland lose against them in the
European championship? Yeah, I think they did. But you could just see the Dutch people on the
stands, just with disbelief going like, oh my god, how is this possible? Yeah, I'm not up. Oh,
we didn't expect this. Yeah. Well, it makes it easy. It had a hard time. They had a really hard time.
Yeah, well, it makes it easy because now all we have to look for is a little bit the way they played
was a bit like street fighters. You know what I mean? Nasty. Well, and I thought there might be
some not something else here because, you know, the Netherlands and Portugal always, you know,
had a lot to do together historically throughout hundreds of years. And if anything, the Dutch
are always vacationing in Portugal. Yeah. Maybe the Portuguese are just a second time of the Dutch
coming to their country and build golf courses that they just like, we're going to kick your ass. Yeah,
now we're going to kick your ass. Yeah. Well, but this team, this Dutch team, next championship,
I think they'll be, they'll be really good. Yeah, it was pretty much all new guys. Yeah.
You know, Snyder and fun. Look at me knowing all this shit. But listen, what's happening to me?
They weren't actually not, not, they were actually from other countries. You know, they buy those.
It's not fair, you know? Well, one or two, one or two, one or two, one or two, we're, one or two,
we're Dutch. No, they're all Dutch. They're all Dutch. Yeah. You have to be Dutch.
Yeah, of course. Because I, you know, some of them were even in Portuguese. In case you had noticed,
there's like a lot of immigration that went on in the middle of the past 15 years. They just bought
those. You know, let's buy a couple of new food bulk players. No, that, that works. Isn't it possible?
Well, no, not really. In fact, they tried to get, there was another guy who's been playing for
Dutch team. I don't know all their names. And he's not a Dutch citizen. And they tried to,
to get him on a fast track to get him citizenship so that he could play in the, in the world cup,
for Holland. But they refused to fast track him. No, of course not. No, why? Why would just because
if a football player are you going to give him preference over everybody else? No, of course not.
So what you also didn't hear is I've been trying to figure out the history of the word football.
And why in America, it's called soccer. Okay. And I, I, would you, I always want to get how it was
one of them. Thank you. I was wondering. Well, what's got soccer to do with your cha cha friends?
I've been saying soccer soccer soccer soccer. Okay. So your, your Charlie friends have been,
oh, shoot. It's not like windows closing. If you listen to serious stars, we got a whole
three and a half hours of pod show podcast lined up for you. But if it goes to hell,
way is next and I'll talk to you tomorrow. Okay. So in America, I can't go through the whole thing
because we've learned most already in the past two weeks. We were talking about this when you
went listening. But it comes from association football, association. Oh. So that's how they got the
sock association sock, SOC. But then what I didn't figure out is how to the curb get land
and get added on to it. You got sock curve. So the sock I understand from SO, you know, association
is ASOC. So they just took the SOC. And member Malcolm from Abu Dhabi. Malcolm, you know,
you will when you hear the voice. I think he's going to demystify how it became, it went from
association to sock to soccer. I much appreciate your encouragement with regard to starting my own
blog. There's a DSR on the way. And I think I'll start in a regular audio cast from the sandlands
after the summer break. I appreciate somewhat less being outed as major Tom from way back in the
day of space oddity. Remember the guy now? This is the guy who directed the major Tom video. He
outed himself by the way. Oh. Yeah. I'll start now. I've heard him. And it took a long time before I could
find someone who could send me the photo you found on Flicka. Why so long? Because Flicka is not
accessible from the United Arab Emirates. The sensors want to protect people from having to see an
awful photo of a strange looking get who was snapped at some kind of event in Can of which for
some reason I have no recall whatsoever. He's not interesting that in the United Arab Emirates
that like Dubai, that you can't reach Flicka, you know, Flicka where we have our pictures too.
Oh. Yeah. It's censorship. Oh. Yeah. Because they, you know, because it's naked pictures.
Stuff like that. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. But the reason I am once again subjecting you to a
surface of turbulence is your perplexity would regard to the curve in soccer.
May I humbly offer the missing link? Yes. We have to thank the students of the 1880s for the
word soccer. The well-bred students of Oxford had the affectation of abbreviating words and then
adding err to the end. Breakfast became Brecker. Football played according to the rules developed
at rugby school became Rugga. Oh. Those who had this preference were disparaged by players
of association football rules as Rugga Buggers, which typically killed two birds with one stone.
The obvious retaliation was to abbreviate the term association Oxford style to soccer.
Google answers confirms this by the way. And that's it for today from Malcolm in Abu Dhabi.
Thank you very much, Malcolm. Well. But what's so what's doubly interesting that actually the
name was developed in the United Kingdom by Oxford University. But how come when you guys play
a football on the table? It's football. Well, no, that's football. Well, that's a good sound like
football. Well, it's because the game was, I think the game was developed in Germany, the
table top of the ball. So that would be football. Yeah. And that just became a brand name. It
just became a brand. So I think we should get one of them. Maybe we don't we have a football table
somewhere we had one. No. Yeah, New Jersey we had one. Sure we did upstairs. Remember? Yeah,
that's right. Yeah, that's right. Whatever. You know that we had, we were because we moved so many
times. I sometimes don't remember what kind of shit we feel about like where has this in the
where is didn't we have this? And then we have no clue. It's either in Holland in storage or thrown
out or sold or given away somewhere. There's so much shit I don't know about anymore. And I really
don't miss it quite honestly. No, but we have to go and take a look. But wouldn't the football table
look beautiful in that house? Yeah. So radio is 100 years old. This week did you know that?
No. Yeah. Oh, second. I have it here. Which I think is so antique.
Yeah, there you go. It's officially antique. Yeah, that's an antique. 100 years old. Which you can
hear now then. So now we can actually say an antiquated medium. Yes, it is. The web page isn't
coming in. I'll put it in the show notes so you can take a look at it. But yeah, pretty interesting.
100 years old. So, oh, it all out's loading. Let me see. Load, crap, bitch. Here we go.
Christmas Eve. Okay. It's almost. Christmas Eve 1906. I guess it's almost 100 years old.
Oh. Apparently Canadian inventor Reginald Fessendon made the world's first radio broadcasts
where wireless operators and several ships need land to pick up an unusual program transmitted
over their radio sets. This wasn't the first actual radio transmission. But he was broadcasting
a recording of Handel's Largo. Okay. And they did his own performance on his own violin.
Ah, nice, nice. So I thought it would be particularly nice in conjunction with this email
message that I got from Marcus Couch from the scenes scene. He does this and the pod
hit music rewind. So he's a pod show network podcast. And so he sent a private email to me.
I'm just going to read a little piece because it really touched me. I really like it. Thanks again
for the video cast plug. I received great positive feedback. I'm quitting my day job of six years
and moving to Orange County, California on July 31. The compensation I've received from
Pod Show has enabled the opportunity for my wife and I to make the move. Her son and nephew are
there and the move will bring us all together again. We really appreciate everything you would
poncho provided us and I can't thank you enough. Ah, in that beautiful. That's beautiful.
And this isn't and it's not like we, I mean, this is just based upon his own creativity and
performance. And anyone who signs up because, you know, we're about to unleash if anyone knows,
you know. So that anyone can do this. And here's a guy who actually made it happen.
I mean, I just love it. That's what you want to know. Exactly. And I'm just like, I read and
there's more, there's a whole bunch more to it. But remember, you told that that story on TV
in Holland and everybody laughed. Oh, that I said, everyone will have their own brother,
the transmitter. Yes. Oh, yeah, they all laughed. They all laughed when. And we're reset it.
Who's got the last laugh now? Yeah. All right, baby. So what are we going to do this week? What
else do we have going on? I don't know. Just enjoy each other. I guess. And I have to go to Holland.
Wow, that's right. Yeah, I have to do that. Yeah, me too. I got to, I got to get my,
and there's something ahead. Oh, my, I got to finish some paperwork, which I have to do with the
the consulate. Yeah. But we have to wait until Christina feels a bit better. Yeah. But she'll be,
I mean, she'll be walking around in two days. That goes much faster than you think. Today,
you saw the difference with her knee today versus yesterday. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I think she'll be able to
go for. She should be able to go to school tomorrow too. Yeah, she's going to try. But she can
do, she come to the steps. She has to go upstairs with the class. Does she have a friend who she's
in every class with? I don't think so. No, she's going to, they're going to keep her downstairs
and I'm going to bring everything to. Really? That's what the, the teachers at this morning to me.
Okay. So, and we may be, we'll find some other houses to see if you want to see it. Okay.
Interesting. Well, I'm glad we're going to be here. Glad I'm going to be here for a little while.
Oh, and Ron's coming over next week. Not this week with next week. Yeah.
With Marta or probably. Yeah, probably. Yeah. We're going to, you know, we're working on the
big advertising campaign. It's going to be so fucking cool. Oh, man. Yeah. I got to show you some of the
video we've done. Yes. Yes. It's going to look really good. And what else? Mmm. I don't know,
nothing actually happened. You're going to do really in two weeks? Yeah, I guess nothing happened.
I'm not here. Yeah. Nothing happened. Of course. A lot of things happen in the world. Thank God.
But it's nice and quiet here. And the afterwards supper looks serious. You know, full on the hill.
Uh-huh. Proceeding here on the hill. Okay. What's good to see you again, huh? Good to see you too, baby.
Yeah. And by the end of the day, I'll probably tell him how you came in with the beard.
We were disgusting. I was trying to stay away from that conversation. He said, I had a
you man. What? Everybody knows I had the beard. Oh, you, you, you said that. Yeah, I had a little,
I have a little bit of beard. A little bit. He comes in. I mean, I literally, the door opens.
And I'm like, hi, and you go, and Christina, what? It hurts. It hurts on your face. Even though you
are women who like it. We don't. No kidding. You actually, you're like gagging. What's this?
That she is. Hello. Hello. Heather. Heather. What did you say?
Heather wants to go. Heather wants to go. Heather wants to go downstairs.
Heather, you know. Yeah. Really? Why is mom, you go?
Don't know. What else do you, what is your got to do with someone? She was married to John Lennon.
There you go. Yeah. And John, then, and listen to her. Okay. No, no. I know. And you listen to me.
And Heather Mills was married to Paul McCartney. And Heather, you don't have one leg. Don't even
make jokes about that. Be lucky you have to. That's what I said. You know, can you imagine? Every time I
said it, can you imagine? Can you imagine if you, if you look at her leg, it's like twice the size of the
other one. It is. You're so lucky. So we're going to do a pod save the queen today. You got the
tracks ready? No. Well, once you, once you fall down the stairs. Okay. Full down the stairs.
All right. Good. Then we'll end the show. And then we'll help you. Yeah. Can you see mom's doing something?
Yeah. I need to hobble. Just a moment. Okay. Can you, can you sit down for a second?
Yeah. Wait in line. All right, Yoko. I guess I can go. Yoko. Oh, man. All right. I'm going to play one
more song. And then we'll take a bite. Okay. Oh, this is from New Jersey. I think you're like this
guy. It's great song.
I put a new guitar on the only credit card that I had maxed and now I'm walking down the
track. There's the rhythm parts. No job, no home, no hard. Got the knowledge to kill.
Cherry, big trash, hell. With a rubbish and watch the cars roll up a ramp.
Had the sun take slow and throw in the shadow of the ship of factory cross. The
BQP race leads through doors of the bars. My wish it be on. I got a record deal and all the
records I can see him from the midnight show. How did the pirate trade deal behind the
side? Emily and E-Line. Broke has the line between pipes and pants. I know how to turn
their search lights on kids. I told me jump in the building side. Everybody's scary.
It's going to trap the trends. And take their hands. Tomorrow the cranes will put the club out
for bed. I got a show to do. Guess you got one too. Strike a record as they nail boards over
the sheet rock. A new glass, a tree's blue for him. Say, here's the club on. Here's the
cup cake, and then coffee.
I am aware of all the memories
Always don't need
Man, you flatter your teachings
Lay down
With a sound effect
I've heard of you getting tall
With only shred of clouds
That's what city group
I can see that age keep
Crawls near down
Dream, I've been to the show's dream
Man's a new way to read
To the song
The next song
The Polish specialties
Heart and rookies
And the transit path
Everybody wants to check out
Everybody, come out
For subway stop
The clock records in a bag
The magnet in the cream
Is to contrast your will be a dream
The new continent of earth and fire
Trips We call
From New Jersey
It's kind of a back five
Jersey Todd the official musical
It's got the daily source code
I gave you that tip
He says cowbell, forget about it
It's all about the halbs of cord
Babs of cool
Yeah, he's cool, very cool
Well, of course the pontine methicine
Now we're putting links to that. The where Wolf of Bretton Woods Trismacall on the daily source code
I'm gonna ask Jeff Smith to make a show opener for us. Okay, all right, will you pay the half half of the money?
Do I not have to pay me? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Kristina, did you get in so you're in touch with Richard Brewer? Hey, no, because they have big plans with her
The whole two weeks I was there they couldn't get a hold of her and I'm like look, I'm not gonna get in you know
I'll do the contract, but she has to actually respond and of course, you know when people are pursuing you and you just you're lazy bugger
Well, no, but because you need to do another podcast, that's why that's what always happens if I don't do a podcast
Then the message yeah, then the message board gets taken over by people about all kinds of stuff
So but yeah, they want to put it on the home page and stuff. I heard that that's fantastic. It's gonna be cool very cool
All right, so lots of stuff to do
Yeah, yeah, I'd save the queen. I've got to do some audio stuff and
I need some food. Yeah
I gained some weight. Well, you where are those shakes you used to make for me? You know
I came in. Yeah, I still have some protein
Yes, for every single time because I go through you know for 20 years you've seen me go up and down with my weight
And then whenever you pull the protein shakes out then I gain it back pretty quickly
And you know, but you're but you never do the protein shake
You'll do like one and then you forget me if you get about me again. Well
Yeah, it's true
Yeah, there's so many people want to lose weights and you're the only one who
Needs to drink those so I have to those protein shake yeah because I'm burning up your way
Do I'm burning up all the energy people hate you?
Yeah, I know that but not about my way but see that doesn't mean that you just can't eat anything you want like
Wrong things because you're too old for that thank you because over 40 you need to check, you know
You're cholesterol you need to check yourself. Yes, so you have to be careful with that. So it's not like you can eat
Well, I'm back now dear. I'm back now and you can
feed me
Well, I'm 60
You still feed me will you still smell me? Oh, yeah
Okay, all right, you then thank you dear will you come back uh yeah, of course you're come back later in the week, right?
Yeah, okay, yeah, I need you
Okay, the public is it's clamoring for you
Imagine but yeah, yeah, they like it they like you
Yeah, don't give me yeah
Okay, okay, okay, I can't help. I live in the house anyway, so yeah, I'm talking with you. Yes
You come with those. Okay. All right, baby. Thank you so much. All right. You're welcome. I love you. I love you too
Justine
Adam or curry calm daily source code dot com. We'll talk to you tomorrow everybody. Bye. Bye another pot show podcast
Stick it in your ear
Yet this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from podshow and line-white networks