Delta Shere Charly 314
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass
And the next generation radio content in my ears
We don't need no sticky drinks, dude
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk
Fantastic, it's a battle curry
Coming to you from the condo
The curry condo and northern California is a business power
I got a couple emails and I said, you know what?
You're right, I should bring back the rock money and off once in a while
Just to get into the vibe, the feel, the power of your intellect
Everybody, how you do it?
We're halfway through the week, it's Wednesday
And I'm really early here in the morning to bring you your daily source code
Coming up today, your Metro sexual moment
Of course, since I'm in San Francisco
The whole entity of talk about the macro world
And the new products that Apple has been announcing
What's up with our microphone sounds kind of low here today
And just to let you know, you are host with the show
Although fully capable of driving the equipment
Is only dressed in a white house code
And black up boots
I mean, who needs more?
Damn, it is foggy outside this morning
All right, so we're going to get all kinds of stuff today
Stuff going on around the office, stuff going on around San Francisco
Stuff going on last night, stuff that's happening today
It's truly going to be one of those shows that the jam pack
And just about everything
If you're listening to us on a serious start 103
How to y'all?
It's the patchy old
Kick it off a crazy infatuation from the road or not a band
No context, no more games
I think this boat is on a little insane
He's got me so many stuff
But I don't know what to do
Next emotions runs so hot
One minute I am the next I'm not
He's got me so many stuff
But I don't know what to do
It's a crazy infatuation
I'm a cell
One minute you wait to go
I'm stuck in this crazy infatuation
Don't more I get to know you
The more scares me so
Meal smooth, a little too fast
One kiss I forget the past
I'm so mixed up
I don't know what to do
Turn the tables, make them run
You have no mercy for anyone
I'm so mixed up
I don't know what to do
It's a crazy infatuation
By myself
One minute you wait to go
I'm stuck in this crazy infatuation
The more I get to know you
The more scares me so
I've got to turn this around
If you were to get my feet off the ground
Tell us why if it's lost the ground
Don't begin my feet back on the ground
Wild dreams and type things
If this is love, it's not what it seems
It's got your soul mixed up
I don't know what to do
It reminds me sweet goodbye
I want you to go about my heart just dies
It's got your soul mixed up
Don't know what to do
It's a crazy infatuation
By myself
One minute you wait to go
I'm stuck in this crazy infatuation
The more I get to know you
The more scares me so
The more you get to know you
I'm stuck in this crazy infatuation
I want you to go about
Patricia's already, what the hell is she doing? It's already she's almost ready for Christina to come home from school
I hate this I hate being on this side of the clock
Because I'm a night guy. I'd like to stay up late, but it doesn't work that way
Not when you're out here not when you got to get shows out not when you got to do stuff
Big day today
You know I've talked about
Hold on a second my Mac is doing all kinds of stuff here today. It's syncing and updating and
God knows what oh, of course. I did the the Mac OS X OS 10 update. That's where it is. Anyway
today the ZDF
due to the deutsch's fans in will be visiting the condo
This is in Germany. They have I think I was at like two or maybe three really main big television channels
That it's not just for Germany. I mean these these German television stations. They're all over the you know German speaking
portions of the world. So it's Germany. It's Austria
portions of Italy, Switzerland. I mean it's just huge. I mean anyone
Who knows anything about
German media is just that the numbers are astronomical and
despite
the huge influence that
That the German public broadcasters have and I guess there
There must be some there must be some commercial broad. I don't know enough about the German media seemed to be quite honest
But there's a lot of podcasting going on in Germany. There's a lot of pod safe music showing up from Germany
Particularly reggae interestingly enough
Sometimes even in German language German language reggae. Go ahead look for it on the pod save music network. You'll see what I mean
So they're coming here to interview me and
And the one thing every single television now if it will always say is okay, you know we've got these
Wait let me do the German okay if you have this great idea for them
Fatima the pod thought of we're going to
They're mocking him
Making a podcast
Every single time it's like no
I'm not gonna do that
That's my magic, you know
That's that's it's my magic. I don't want I don't want you to see when I'm doing this
I'll be making a video podcast don't you think
But I did say that okay they wanted a real San Francisco vibe
I said once you come up to the to the condo because I've got the you know the 180 degree
View of the day and of the financial district and the Bramuda Triangle here in Soma that I call home
Because there's nothing here nothing going on except concrete and as I look out the window today
I have visibility of oh, let's say 50 feet. It is the foggyest day yet
And I hope it's gonna burn off because they'll be here a little bit later on, but so far looking pretty damn bleak
So I don't know maybe I'll have to at least show them my equipment
My podcast equipment that is to make them feel like they've got some kind of groovy shot going on
And what do I have here? Well, I have
My power book
outdated just bought it. I have my iMac G5 just bought it outdated
I don't feel too good about that. I mean doesn't seem like apples releasing stuff a little bit too fast. You know, I just just
You know, I haven't even made my first real
You know
Scratch on any of my machines, you know, there's there's so new as I have no real incentive to go out and buy a new one
Yeah, yeah much faster. Well, we'll talk about that a little bit later on today, obviously
Let me see we got some more pod save music coming up as I said in the rock mining off intro
Which I brought back for you know, just to feel good today
We'll be doing a metro sexual moment and I'd also like to talk a little bit about the demo that I received of
of
All the stuff that has been going on at the pod show HQ
Which will be something you'll be able to see pretty soon, too, I guess
First let's get to some audio feedback. This one was pretty funny, actually
Hi Adam. This is Rachel from the audio collective pod cast
We do our podcast with myself my husband David and our friend Cory
We of course influence to new podcasting because of you and the daily source code and at first it was okay
But then things started happening
David's been influenced to not only start his own podcast, but to buy things like in iPod then in I river in I dog
Then a Mac mini which he claims was for me an m3 power razor, which he is very proud of right now
a frothy since sao coffee maker to add to the list and
And lately he's been saying the numbers and letter combinations 1 8 2 RG
I'm not sure if I'm gonna let him get that yet, but Adam we've got a talk
You've either got to provide us with a better way to support our
Daily source code buying habits or help us out give David a job or something we just need the extra cash
Because you're doing such a great job advertising
Unfortunately, we have a hard time pain or mortgage bill. So please help
Thanks and keep on the great show. This is Rachel from the audio collective pod cast at audiocollective.net
So Rachel he's got he's got all these groovy goodies even once a
Charlie 182 Romeo golf that would be the sessna
Won't just come over here, baby. Come over to the condo and get the real thing
See all the real equipment
Actually with what I saw yesterday at pod show
You will be able to make some extra money and I believe that some people will be able to quit their day jobs and we've got
I think we've got it figured out man. I was so blown away
yesterday because the the thing that the yeah, of course, there's a huge piece that we're focusing on for pod casters
But what I was really really happy about what I saw yesterday at pod show which will be releasing
I guess in drips and drives
This is not the kind of thing you say oh and here it is come on in you know, it's just it's too much we've got a
Releasing in bits and pieces but for listeners my god
Man think about one click subscription
You know just just don't even think about subscription just get a show. Okay, become a registered listener to a show
Find out who else is listening to the show provide comments easy way to do audio comments easy way to keep track of your favorite shows
Easy way to sync up the pod cast the elixine to across multiple machines whether
Regardless of what operating system you're using so if you have shows that you listen to at
At home you can have the same shows waiting for you at work
Spin it off and any device you want
Participate in show notes. I mean, it's just it's gonna be unbelievable and some of it's actually some of the wacky age acts 2.0 stuff which we love so much
So I think we're gonna spend the rest of this week
Doing some iterative loops going around around around a processing stuff then we have let me have like
Well a number of new pod casters were bringing into the pod show network and they're actually going to be our first
Real beta testers because they'll be beta testing the podcasting side of the equation
But also the listening side and everyone now at the office has become a listener and
Man, it's it's fun. You know, you what happens is you you go into what you can't go in there yet
But you'll be going into podshow.com and it's just like you don't want to stop you're just finding all this new stuff and and
hooking up with with people and other listeners
I think that's really and you know the what I'm really happy about is that what I'm seeing is we're going to
strengthen the bond
between listeners and podcasts and podcasters
because right now
The the whole concept of the technology underneath podcasting you know RSS and subscriptions
That's seen as the as the relationship, but it's really not working that well as a as a relationship for a whole bunch of reasons
Mainly because you don't know who's at the other end of the subscription and it
Then it really does help if if you can make that connection
So really becoming a member of
Listening audience to to a podcast or multiple podcasts and then having that that connection that two-way street working
You know even better than just the asynchronous part that we're doing here with me talking and you sending something back once in a while
So be on the lookout for that more updates of course as we move along
I may we'll talk a little bit later later on the show about it after rev closed the satellite window last night
I was going to do the actual is going to do the show last night because I knew that had a big day today
Went over to Ron's house
Had a quick bite to eat because he's been having problem. You know
He's maximum and I'm telling you so I have the the old now
The outdated power book
G4, but you know the with the 1.67
Gigerhertz processor or whatever
And I still have that audio problem
In fact while I was prepping the show for today even though I downloaded the new quick time update and the new OS 10 update
Damn if it didn't come back
And Ron
You know he's been in musicians since longer than I've been on this planet earth and
He finally went back to to setting up his studio and he got himself the 17 inch
High-end power book which now of course is also outdated and he's using logic pro
And it's the wackiest thing and of course
You know this is something that
That is not new
We looked it up on on the web and saw that this error basically if you have more
Like five tracks or something
His CPU load, you know goes right off the scale and then it stops playing and you get a core audio error
Which basically means yeah your CPU is is maxed out
But that shouldn't be happening with just a couple of tracks especially not on a on a machine that powerful
I mean I've I've run pro tools on
And you know like whatever
Dec and and stuff like that with with maybe 20 tracks without a problem on really old hardware so
Little down on the apple stuff right now. I have to say
Let me see I had
I have a little a couple of things of course
When I did get back last night in lieu of
of going
Deep into the night and recording a show I looked at the Steve Jobs keynote which no longer is live
I find I thought they used to do that live they would
Webcast the keynote at the same time but they don't do that so
It came out late last night and some of the highlights of course
The one that that I like the most is that apple over the Christmas quarter so that's the past three months
Sold 14 million iPods that's 14 million people
Who are out there walking around with a
Hard drive that can be filled up with all kinds of stuff besides what you get from the iTunes music store
It can be filled up with pod safe music tons of it
Oh, and by the way
The purchasing for pod safe music I think that that will be
We'll be beta testing that this weekend
We have a board of directors meeting coming up next week and I more or less promised that it will be done by then
So it will be it will be done by then and maybe ready for prime time by the end of next week
So that was cool of course the new max came out the new Intel processor based max
I think I'll wait for a couple of generations of machines before I switch to that
I'm a little bit tired of paying to be a beta tester for apple still love the stuff, but I just cannot believe
Can't believe these are audio problems which is why you have them back in many cases
Of course the big news
I thought yesterday was that I life oh six which means that now you can
picture cast although that seems to pretty much only work from
From that from Mac to Mac although it will be an RSS feed there was no demonstration of how the RSS feed works and what happens when you remove pictures from your
From your photo cast published folder, so you know that was a little unclear, but the podcast studio and garage band certainly one way of doing it
With multiple tracks you could even see when when Steve was doing the demo that you know
It did turn out really well actually, but of course it was completely you know pre-produced to even had to read his
His little his little podcast thing, you know verbatim to you know put it into the right amount of time so he could drag in this his music track
Auto ducking so when you start talking the music
Automatically goes down low well that's something we've had in cast blasters since almost day one so
for those of you who aren't fortunate enough to be an owner of
Macintosh stuff
and you got windows and you want to you know have a cool podcast studio check out cast blaster dot com
It does all that and then some and you don't need a
Dot Mac account to publish I don't know if you actually need that for garage band if you it probably no of course
Now you can probably just you can just spin it out but the big offer here and I did look up on the looking to that the big offer on
On the podcast studio if you buy your what I think it's $99 is it $99? Yeah, I think it's
It's something like 10 bucks a month for for your dot Mac account and you get three what is it
Man, I should have looked at something like an idiot
You get some storage which I believe is one gigabyte of storage and if you look at all the details
You get 25 gigabytes of data transfer per month and that really does kind of work out to what I figured it would be because if you do the math and of course
Apple doesn't doesn't own bandwidth
They purchase it and of course they I think they own a stake in
What is it to an akamai who delivers all that stuff it runs on the akamai network?
But they have to basically
Buy that on the quote unquote free market and I think that they are pretty much somewhere between
27 and 35 cents per gigabyte of data transfer now podcasts as we'll know what that means
Because you know if you get a whole bunch of people listening to your show
Well, you run out of bandwidth and Apple will certainly be great for the smaller individual stuff. I think anything
under
probably under
a couple hundred listeners and if you do that
You know no more than once or twice a week, then you should be okay. It depends on how long your show is
You know what what quality you recorded at
But it certainly is not free
Hey, this I hate having to bend over. I need another podcast complex here. I'm like leaning on my arms during the entire show
I did get a funny email a couple of people notice this stick actually
Send the two of me said that did you see the the mac world keynote
When Steve was the demoing the I web
So this is you know and that was by the way very very very cool
You know to create a website with blogs all click and you know point click shoot and it just kind of all works and that was very very
Zippy
So what Steve wanted to say was
When you're done creating a website push one button except what he said was
When you're done creating a website push one button. I did hear that
He kind of like weather website like okay. I'm glad you made me a website man
Very cool
Let me see I got
Another song coming up from Barry Coral attached to a promo so hold off on that because we've got only a couple more
Minutes here with our folks on the satellite for those of you
New to to serious stars one oh three you might have purchased your serious box over the Christmas to listen to Howard
Maybe receive that as a gift
Here on channel one oh three every afternoon from six to ten eastern from three to seven Pacific we roll out the pod show
Today is one of those special days. We got
The roving bit in the middle after myself Pacific coast hellway
Madgelinestein I think is it the Frank true the thing it might be Brian know who's on today
Sometimes beat-up slips in there with with digital flots and
So make sure you just to hang out here we got it all going on, baby metro sexual moment coming up
I've received an email if someone said something that the metro sexual moment was not here it is word on
Vogue I Adam says jail
I knew they hate getting emails as opposed to voice feedback by my works. I don't have easy access to Mike right now
What kind of excuses that
This is in regards to the constant use of the word metro sexual the word was coined back in
2004 so any guy who referred to himself as a metro sexual back in 2004 wouldn't still call himself a metro
Sexual because the word has just become passe. I think the word developed into uber sexual in 2005
But now that it's 2006. I'm not sure what the term will be
By the way, I love the show. Thank you, Joe. Okay. I don't know. I'm you know we got the imaging
We got the jingles from metro sexual moment so why don't we keep it at that until someone comes up with something better
I'm sure that uber sexual was kind of cool
Well, maybe we are just still kind of metro sexual. You know maybe we are a little bit behind the times
We haven't talked about you know men's health and beauty and shaving and smelling nice and you know we haven't done that
So maybe you are in 2004 maybe men are just behind the time it could be
I see
Something else was going to talk to you about here
I don't know
I really don't remember
I'm sorry. It's too early. What time is it? It's now
7 30 a.m. I only slept for like six hours
And it's going to be another really long day and I know you don't care
You shouldn't care you shouldn't feel bad because you've got your own miserable life. Oh wait the fog is clearing
I can I now have 150 feet yeah at least 150 foot view so maybe the Germans will be happy after all
Funny thing the Germans yeah come from the Netherlands where I grew up
Whenever Germans show up we yeah we have this like love hate relationship has something to do with
1940 to 1945 and there was some other thing in
1920 before that
But the thing we always say is hey good to have you here. I want my bike back
Now if you're Dutch you're laughing if you're German you're probably not laughing but hope
Okay, now we said goodbye to the satellite folks. Let's continue here
Check out some really cool podcast. I did some selection on the promo today that came in through promo's dot
You can upload your promo right there to podcast feed and you can subscribe to promo's you might want to put in your own podcast
These are some of the better ones. I think and of course very apropos for the apple launch is the following beginning January 1st
2006 Apple Matters dot com presents a series of site stories daily email and daily podcasts
Featuring this day in our day in apples diverse and fascinating history
From corporate milestones to landmark software and hardware releases
And articles covering all the colorful character to apple hardware event that took place on that day in apples diverse and fascinating
history
From corporate milestones to landmark software and hardware releases and articles covering all the colorful characters in apple story history
This day in apple history will be a fun and an apple history
Beginning January 1st from applematters dot com subscribe now
So you won't miss a single day on the next episode of beyond science chip cruiser right now
We have six billion people on the earth
We're projecting by 2050
It's going to be something like 10 billion people
I asleep saving the earth by
Most of the scientists in the Apollo era scientists
Got into a Apollo believing that by now we would have a colony on the moon
www.biasedlead.com
Certainly don't mean packing up our bags and leaving earth to live under domes on the moon
If we all understood we have to do this we all get behind it we could do it
Beyond science podcast dot com hey gang. This is Jason from Insomnia Radio
All right that's my first grade
Jason evangelo host of Insomnia Radio leader of the podcast revolution
6,000 listeners featured on blah blah blah and i'm part of his gang
Give me a break we are devoted fans to the music to the hosting to the help he gives freely to anyone
Trying to get into his business and the band to sustain it and not a single promo produced to this date
I'm not going to take it anymore. We are cutting edge and so isn't some new radio get connected
some some new radio dot net
You haven't been listening to the confessions of an indie girl podcast with Barry Coral and Howard Greenstein
Here's just some of the things that you've been missing
Morning. I offered in a little voice depressed. Now bigger age
Horny Horny. I reluctantly practice. Come on do better. Horny. Horny. Horny. That's it. Very convincing
Yeah, New Year's I play poker and I drank 20 year old bourbon and I also noticed that the more bourbon
I drink the force I get at poker
That is the key the Las Vegas people do know that about you
We've done this before, but let's play sparring angel because that's my niece's favorite song
It's great the day at the moment
One of the things I'll say is it's been played on over six podcasts on the pod safe music network
We edited it to the pod safe music network and
Had six people played in addition to coverville and Adam Curry's it's the confessions of an indie girl podcast
Available through your favorite aggregator or at wwww dot Barry Coral dot com b-a-r-i-k-o-r-a-l dot com
And hey Adam Curry. It'd be great if you'd play aspiring angel again on their podcast and
Help us increase our pod play. Now they run the pod safe music network. So hint hint. Thanks a lot take care
Hey
Why didn't think that he would offer lots of comedy
I didn't know that every night will make it the last to me
Well, I just gotta get through this world. I just gotta get through this world. I'm just gotta get through this world. I'm gonna sparring
Maybe
When new lessons feels like getting push and some all that to me
Keep hanging on to the old that it might all come back for me
I just gotta get through this world. I just gotta get through this world. I just gotta get through this world
I just gotta get through this world. I just gotta get through this world. I love someone like a
Hit
But you believe the love is hidden everywhere in the darkest nights
They're lightning bugs that shine for you when you can't see the light
Well I just gotta get to this run
And just gotta get through this run
I just gotta get through this run
But don't explain me line and am
I just gotta got through this run
I just gotta get through this run
I'm just gonna get through this world
I gotta smile it and I'm down
I'm just the way you are
Not just the wrong way you go
Not just the wrong way
Mary, Cloroll
And a bit of a podcast confessions of an indie girl
It's cool about berries that I met her
That's B-A-R-I, by the way
K-O-R-A-L
Verychoral.com
Or you can find her at music.podshow.com
When I was doing a radio show
In the Netherlands a couple years back
She was on tour
She came through, I think, was Holland, Germany
She made it been to France, I think
And she, I can't remember exactly how it happened
But she stopped by and she played a couple songs live
And at the time I was like, wow, this is really cool
And she always has no major record label
She was selling out gigs all over the place
Doing clubs and stuff
And it's so cool to have her back
In my life
Through podsake music
Of course her brother Howard Greenstein does
Does a whole bunch of stuff for promoting her
And helping her out
And he has his own career too
But thanks guys, really appreciate it
Great song, love it, very very much
Hey everybody, it is time
Metro section
It's an increase
Metro section moment
It's never bought enough
And increased Metro section moment
Okay, by the way, I see that
The recording has been skipping at least six times
That's probably when my Mac decided to do shit on its own
That I didn't ask it to and it just sinks stuff up
So I apologize and shouldn't
Be any problem for the rest of the show
So let's start off today
Oh Horrors
I remembered yesterday
When I was preparing for the German television interview
I didn't bring my Mac up back
Oh yeah
Little secret
Well it's not really a secret
But I've worn
Make up a lot
Throughout my life
Particularly when I was working MTV every single day
But back then
And she do my makeup and I learned a lot
And check this out
How Metro section is this?
I said to Ron's wife, Marta is at Marta
You know, Kai Barrel, she's Latino
Latina, she said
And she said, well, you know, you can't borrow my makeup
Because the color she uses is way too dark
And she was so sweet she went out and bought me a whole set of Mac makeup
But now I blew it already
Because I was supposed to take the brush
She bought me a beautiful brush from Mac
I think it is
How coincidental
And I was supposed to shampoo it and wash it
And leave it dry overnight
So it'll be nice and fluffy
Oops, fuck that up
So hopefully it'll work
I'll take pictures
So you can see me doing my makeup
We've got some audio feedback
For today's Metro section moment
So let me just
I want to second how we do that
We did it like this
Right?
We bring that down
Oh my god
Sorry
Because that fabulous auto ducking feature
I was talking about
Come on
You know it's here so long
It gets in your coffee
Have you used your hair to floss
And you have so much hair on your back
You can cause a scene when you take off your shirt
Well, you need the Metro moment
The Metro moment is the Metro sexual
Been yet till the unwashed masses
And yes, that means you
And if you're a teenager then it most definitely means you
Metro moment is a 2 to 5 minute podcast
The tips to keep working sexy and well groomed
But it's not just for guys
It's for everyone
Like you there young lady
Leg roamers are not in style
There is no topic that a sacrosanct
Well covered all nail care hair care
Party etiquette skin care health tips
Diet recommendations
And even motivational tips
We've got it all covered
You just need to stop by
And hey, if we haven't covered it then ask
It just brings more fun to the party
So if you're out there
If you're out there we can help you
If you're a geek that thinks a pocket protector
Is a fashion statement
Don't worry
If you're a girl that thinks green fungus is a nail color
Fear not
Here's help
It's the Metro moment
Find us at Metro moment.blogspot.com
Metro moment
Metro style
And maximum impact for you to look your sexy best
Oh yeah baby
I am so subscribed to that podcast
Okay
Well good to see you there
More podcasts come along
When it comes to Metro sexual moment
Hi
Let's see a couple of pieces of feet back here
Timothy Pilgrim Adam
Love the podcast
Especially the Metro sexual moment
And Trinity moments
Yeah, I got one of those coming up later on this week as well
What are you guys?
Total losses?
I shave in the shower
By feel no mirror
No cream, no after shave
No problem
Oh, comes out smooth
There's a baby's butt
And the wife loves it
Dude
You've got a moisturizer
You got to
Otherwise
You're going to wake up one day
Your face is going to be all cracked up
As for Trinity
Timothy says
Oh yeah, this whole biodiesel thing
I'm sorry
Didn't mean to confuse that
Onto the M3 power in the shower
From Matt's not grass
Starting here you've had some different culpants
With the Gillette M3 power
I should have mentioned that the M3 power
Was designed to be used in the shower
I find that the shower is the perfect place
With the closest shave in a steamy hot environment
Your beard is much softer for shaving
Give it a try
The only downside is that the fogless mirror
Was always fog up after about a month
Was that true?
You know, there is quite a culture of guys
Who shave in the shower
That's not my culture
Because I have the reason why I guess
I don't like to get my hair wet
God how Metro sexual in my today
So, you know, I think that
It's probably just better to in front of the shower
Okay, we have another Metro sexual moment
Contribution here
Hold on a second
I'm loving it guys
Thank you very much
I really appreciate the fact that you're sending audio feedback
Hi Adam
This is Bernie Zabord
From the Martian Chronicles
The most improbable podcast on the planet
With only one episode released in 2005
I'd like to share with you my own personal debons shaving
Which was given to me by an esthetician girlfriend of mine
Basically, she told me to use a official scrub
On a weekly basis
Before shaving
Because she told me as she told me wrong
That it removes the dead skin and grease
And everything that gets encrusted
Into your skin
And then it eases up the work of the blade
So, that does work
And you do end up in the oven
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Hey, how cool
I hadn't heard that for a while
You probably won't be the only one in house to enjoy it
By the way
Well, that was my contribution
The Metro sexual moment
And hopefully we'd have a word of encouragement
From the Pathfather himself
The Martian Chronicles
Bombay that impubole anymore in 2006
Well, keep up the good work
And thanks for listening
Bye
Yeah, we do thank you very much
I apologize about the
The apple problem that I just had there
Second time in this show
Cutting
Scream off
What's crazy about this is
I don't think I had it for the first month
That I had this machine
Okay
Back to then
Center myself
We're still in our Metro sexual moment here
Let's calm down
David Toasty
He says
Noxima Creme
I find it does a really good job
Better than the shaving creams
To soften up the hairs
But I stopped a few years ago
To be using electric razor now
Since using a blade
Does a number on my skin
Plus
It's a moisturizer as well
You know, I've used that in a pinch
I've used some noxima
But I kind of swear by the
Gillette gel
And I guess the jury is so kind about
Is it really the products you use to give you the better shave
Or is it the technique
Or is it the razor
Let's see
Robert Walsh
Oh, of course
That's Rob from podcast 4
And he pointed out a podcast called
What is it?
Cancer
It's a cancer.com
It's about women who shave
Everywhere
The Rob you're a sick puppy, man
It's a keto alpha tango Sierra uniform
Robio tango hotel.com
I'm not going to play that piece
Because it kind of ruins my home
Metro sexual divide
You know what?
Let's keep it that
This was our Metro sexual moment
For Wednesday
I said Wednesday
Metro sexual moment
Yeah
The Metro sexual moment
Do you believe anything is possible?
Fuck
I was going to say
Metro sexual moment
Is brought to you by Earthling
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do
Where are flink?
We believe in an internet
That's safe from viruses and scammers
We're Earthling
We believe your personal information
Should be just that
Personal
And we believe your internet
Should be a friend
Not a fo
We're Earthling
Make this smart choice
Visit earthlink.net
And discover what our internet experts
Can do for you
Earthling
We revolve around you
I wish we had like an earthling for
Shaving
That would really help
If we had a company that
It really helped us with
Shaving the way Earthling helps us with
Being connected, staying connected
And protecting your data
And protecting your privacy
You know that would be something
I wouldn't really look forward to
Okay
I was going to bitch about iTunes
Maybe I shouldn't do that
Other than the fact that
People are having all kind
You know I read somewhere
And I don't see how this can be true
But I read that a lot of
People are having problems with
iTunes downloading podcasts
Because ISPs around
Certainly around the US
But perhaps around the world
Have been installing all kinds of filters
And all kinds of trickery
To
Basically I think it's to stop
Bit torn which makes no sense
Because that's using completely
Different ports on your computer
But we are seeing people
Often on the same
Segment
So a particular ISP
Who are getting broken downloads
And if you're seeing this problem
Let me know
And also let me know
Send me an email
And I'll probably send you back a few technical questions
And some stuff that you can look up
Easily on your computer
We can find out of
Where these problems are coming from
But it definitely seems to be a problem
Okay
So I don't want to bitch about that too much
I did see the
Was it
I saw a piece of video
Let me just see if I can tell you what that video was from
It was a video of podcast or content
It was really good
I think it was the Mac podcast
Let me see
Where is it?
Let me just look at my
Looking at all my shows
That I'm subscribed to
Where is it?
It's Shelley the Republican
Oh the new pod finders up
Podfighter episode 15
That's cool
The first one of the new year
Maybe I should do a little search here
For podcaster
Cone, podcaster
Or is it pod?
Was it podcaster
Cone?
Yeah here it is
The Mac Pro podcast
That's what it was
Hey, it was a great
It was like a 12 or 13 minute video podcast
Was really good
And it was about the
Is really an impression of the podcaster
Con
They went on in that
Was it South Carolina?
I think
Which unfortunately I couldn't go to
Because I was in the UK
I really would have wanted to go
Because a lot of people there
There were teams that recognized
Which shows I listened to
And what was kind of amazing to me
Is that I haven't
Hard a lot of podcast
Coming from podcaster
Con
I heard the legal discussion
Which was really poor audio
Recording
Yeah, kind of like live Mike sounds
It was a little hard to hear
But that was a very interesting
Very interesting session
I was wondering if there were more sessions
Or if there was an archive
I looked at the podcaster
Con wickie and couldn't really find it
Because I know that
There was a lot of good stuff that was discussed there.
Madge Weinstein filled me in on she was there, probably a sleuth undercover, but she gave
me some feedback on that and I'd just like to know more about some of the conversations
and did we come to any conclusions to what did we learn so please do let me know.
And then to wrap it up today, for those of you who don't know the show notes for this
podcast, there's two basic show notes that's kind of like a rundown that I post along
with the show, which shows up probably in your pod catcher, if you're using the juice
receiver, if you're using iTunes or something else, also what shows up on the individual
posting on the show site.
But then there's a link to what we call the time code based show notes, which is really
a misnomer, even though it is kind of done by time codes, what it is, it's a wiki
show notes.
And this was set up by show notes, Michael at show notes.info, and this thing is growing and I'm
really, really happy for him because it was just kind of an idea, but I threw out there,
he set it up, you know, all on his own dime, his own time.
And he's got a lot of shows that are now using the whole concept of user-generated show
notes.
And he has a message for us all.
Hey Adam, it's Michael over from show notes.info, I just wanted to drop you a line to let
you and your listeners know that I've created a Google group for the show notes website.
The purpose of that is because now that a lot of people are updating the show notes,
not just me, sometimes editorial things come up, people maybe need to change other people's
comments.
And there's no real good way right now to let people know why you're making changes,
maybe that you think are going to affect somebody else.
So I just wanted to let you and your listeners know, I mean, I don't think this is something
that every listener is necessarily going to want to sign up for, but certainly to people
that are active in updating the show notes websites and the other podcasts are out there
that are using the site for their show notes as well.
And they want to check it out.
The other thing that it's going to allow me to do is if I have to do any site maintenance
or upgrades or anything like that, I can let people who are interested know quickly through
an email.
So again, it's a Google group for show notes.info and there's a link to it over, I updated
the site news page on the wiki itself or if you just go to show notes.info, the main page,
there's a link to it there as well.
So again, just ahead's up for anybody who might be interested in checking that out.
All right, Michael, thank you, buddy.
Great job on show notes.info.
It's very cool.
We're working well and I really support that initiative and if there's anything, well,
he might go, you know, if there's anything I can do, you'll let me know.
Okay, you know, it's been 45 minutes.
We've, the crappy thing has been skipping and we've had, we've had a pretty out of control
show today and some portions really sucked.
I'm sorry about that tomorrow will do even better because that's the great thing about
podcasting.
There's always the next show whenever I feel ready for it.
Everybody, have yourselves a great Wednesday, I'll be back tomorrow with more to talk
about and hopefully, even my lighter doesn't work today.
Hot show, tough on dirt, gentle on your ears.