This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charley, 363.
Hello, I'm Adam Curry.
Come listen to my show.
Call that Damie Thorst code!
And if you want to find out what's going on in Pod Castan,
right now, then come on over.
Cause I am the master.
Pod Caster.
That same sturdy.
Is that dirty, Peed Up?
That same too, dirty.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Transmidders?
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need nuss.
I like to think I'm flying.
If you want to...
Pod Castan, it's Adam Curry.
She comes to me and nice.
The moon shines through my window.
But you whispered in my ear.
Those amazing words I never thought I hear.
But she said, yeah.
Just close your eyes.
Lay our hands down.
And let your fairness be staying.
Hold on now, cause I take you over this down tonight.
On my magic cup, it's all on time.
I'll take you away from the rising light.
The places you never ever been before.
As we passed in your bonestar.
But she said, you never do so.
All struck by my fears.
And I saw that all the dreams.
I didn't see it like red.
Who we played I'd see.
And she said, yeah.
Just close your eyes.
Lay our hands down.
And let your fairness be staying.
Hold on now, cause I take you over this down tonight.
On my magic cup, it's all on time.
I'll take you away from the rising light.
The places you never ever been before.
All that I didn't see.
Just close your eyes.
Lay our hands down.
Let your fairness be staying overnight.
And I'll take you over this down tonight.
On my magic cup, it's all on time.
I'll take you over the rising light.
I'll take you over now, I'll take you over this down tonight.
On my magic cup, it's all on time.
I'll take you away from the rising light.
The places you never ever been before.
You face down, yeah, I'll be there to you.
It's another one of those songs, man.
Just can't get it out of my head.
It has a combination of so many different things.
I really like it.
Pretty, pretty song.
It's from New Leaf.
Song is titled Magic Carpet.
Now, guess where they come from.
Nope.
They come from Sweden.
That's right.
And I didn't actually realize that until I just pulled up the page on the podcast of music.
Now, where I tagged it a long time ago, my playlist to play.
There you go.
Loving it from music.podshow.com.
Well, good afternoon or good morning, everybody.
Probably good afternoon where you're listening to this show right now because it's a little bit later than normal.
This morning after dropping Christina off at school, I jetted back to the cottage.
Immediately begged Patricia to do my hair because I had a meeting in London.
Which is actually quite convenient.
I was so surprised.
I was able, you know, I was back.
To see, I left the house at, was at 930 and I was on the east side of London and 11 o'clock from my meeting with British telecom.
And the reason for that, of course, is that, you know, there's not, not often that you get an opportunity to sit with the top brass twice in quick succession.
So I felt it was more than warranted to despite all the packing and the last minute stuff we're doing.
And of course, I do have double days here.
So this all fits into the pre San Francisco awakening hours.
And I was back.
I was back sitting in the big green ugly chair, which, for those of you who have been listening to the show since the curry castle days,
the big old green ugly thing just went right along with me.
I still, you can sit still my recliner.
And I was sitting here about like 230.
It was fantastic.
Actually, I was back at the station at 130.
The car was waiting for me 145.
I was home.
Fantastic.
It did not a nice day.
So I'm looking forward to leaving.
As you know, we're going to Portugal to the Algarve.
And we leave tomorrow.
I will put up a thank God.
It's Friday show just to get us a whole new mood, of course.
And after that, we're at a here.
So I can't say too much about the B.T. meeting, but you pay podcasters.
Doing stuff for you guys here.
Thanks for all getting touched with me.
I was at the Guardian Media Conference, the Changing Media Summit.
There's like, you know, one podcaster.
Okay.
It's okay.
That's fine.
Just don't complain that we're not doing anything when we get it all rolling.
Lots of stuff going on.
Plenty of stuff in the form of feedback.
It sounds like this.
Hey Adam.
It's listener Jeff.
And looking on dig today.
And there's this huge set of comments about this.
A ledge, podshow contract on the Keith and the girl podcast.
And I think we need to hear a podshow side of the story, also.
I really don't believe the things that people are saying.
And since there's nothing that I can actually read.
I don't know who's blown smoke out of who's asked or what.
So what's the deal?
Is this legit?
Is it complete total BS made for fun?
And you're just having, they're just pulling shots at you.
Or what's going on?
Let us know.
Okay.
Well, obviously our response was all taking everything kind of ingest.
But it's interesting when I look at dig and all that.
It's amazing how creative people can be when insulting me.
It never ceases.
It never ceases to amaze me.
Let me set a couple things very straight.
First of all, podshow is not an ad network.
Okay.
That's the big disconnect here.
We are not an ad insertion company where we do a revenue split and publish everything up front
with the contracts and the agreements.
Now, that's stuff that podtrack and keep trying.
And man, I'm trying to think of a couple more.
Podtrack, keep trying.
There's more.
Okay.
Send me which actually have a list of which ones there are.
These guys, they state their information publicly because they're like ad cents.
This is very typical of where I think the podcast and community is turning left
and we should be turning right.
You know, the Google Adsense model, go look at your check.
Tell me how big it is.
Okay.
Because that's probably going to be about the size of your check if you use these types
of ad insertion networks.
And the whole point there is that advertisers show up themselves.
And oh, not a lot of all of them I have to say.
But it's, you know, they publish a rate card.
So, you know, if you look at the rate card for Keith and the girl,
and it says they have approximately 257,000 downloads in a month, which is good.
I have to say, but hey, no, don't and Drew.
And they charge $67 per 1000.
So, you can almost do the math if they were completely sold out.
They would actually be doing pretty good.
But the question is, how do you get completely sold out?
And how do you, how do you justify a cost per 1000?
The so-called CPM?
I think that's the wrong way to go.
What Pod show does is we market the relationship
between the podcast or the pod, the proofs of the podcast and their audience,
which we find far more valuable than $67 per 1000 downloads.
So, we don't have any contracts like that.
So, we're not going to publish anything.
We don't discuss our private contracts with the podcasters that have joined the network.
And quite honestly, when a podcaster joins the network,
it's not just signing of a contract.
There's a whole discussion.
There's a contacts.
There's an often trips to the office, so we can discuss things.
How do we build the future for a podcaster?
What can the network provide for you?
What type of advertisers are we looking at?
What kind of promotions?
How do we drive listeners?
And that's really the key point that I want to make.
The insults that are flying around is that...
And it's not even Pod show.
It's me personally.
That's the funniest thing that I love reading it.
That I'm raping podcasters for my own benefit.
Yeah, you clearly misunderstand.
Pod show, as we've said from day one, is about listeners.
We're about getting the audience in, okay?
And audience comes for several different reasons.
But that connection is what we're making.
We're not going out there trying to snap up as many podcasters.
We can't even... it's not scalable the way we're doing it.
We're creating a network of shows that we feel will draw an audience
and the audience will not be disappointed when they come to podshow.com
and try out that podcasting thing.
So now, of course, I'm not going to discuss any contracts.
And if you do receive a contract from Pod show,
then I suggest you talk to a lawyer
and don't take your advice from Keith and the girl.
That being said, with the, you know, standing on one leg
and praising Murphy and all that stuff,
we're hoping to go public beta with podshow plus and the pdn,
the podshow delivery network around...
Well, it's supposed to be... the schedule says April 13th,
but I'll just say, let's take the worst day in our lives,
which would be April 15th, tax day.
And let's make that a little bit brighter.
By then, we should have it up and rolling,
and there will be multiple levels.
And for people who just want to come in and use the network
and don't want to join the podshow family,
that we plenty of opportunity for you.
All kinds of you can even pay for it
and just take the services with no advertising whatsoever.
Those, of course, will be published.
But the level that we're talking at here is something completely different.
So that's about all I really have to say about it.
And it's just, again, amazing.
Amazing how creative the insults have gotten.
Hey Adam, this is Chris from the Financial Aid podcast
with some audio feedback about taking people's names into vain.
From the Buddhist perspective, which is the perspective I associate
with the most, there are three general reasons why you shouldn't do this.
None of which actually have to do with respect.
The first is taking people, the names that people are taking into vain
are names that are connected with the, I guess we'll call it the sacred.
You know what, let me just set this up.
If you haven't heard the previous episodes,
this started with Steve Web of the Life Spring podcast
who respectfully asked me to not use Jesus Christ in a derogatory way.
Which I totally understand, I'm trying to respect.
Not just for Steve Web, but for other listeners of my show.
I don't care about anyone else.
My listeners, you know, within my own community.
And that has sparked a pretty interesting conversation about what does it mean to take
the Lord's name in vain or anyone's name in vain for that matter.
And I've gotten lots of feedback, but this one from the Financial Aid podcast
is pretty good.
Listen to some more.
The ability to switch between your ordinary everyday mind and the mind
that is focused on spiritual practice is very, very difficult to combine.
One of the ways that you get there is the use of sacred names, words, and rituals.
It's kind of like warm-ups before concert.
You make the transition from everyday mind to empowered mind.
By using the words and sounds connected with the sacred in the context of the
profane, you dilute the power.
You make it that much harder to get the groove when it comes to spiritual practice.
In Buddhism, we reserve power words and names for times when they'll do us the most good.
Using the amount of context, it's like a police officer firing warning shots.
They're loud and all, but if he needs those both to save his life, he should
out of luck.
Second, you actually have proven this more than anything with this and say
or burping.
In addition to power dilution, if you consistently use any deities name and
link it to negative experiences, the guess what?
Yep, you will naturally be by force of repetition.
The same as burping and say or begin attaching negative associations to it.
Until you're.
That is so incredibly true.
So now we're getting down to something.
Some socios, psychological aspects of this that I hadn't really thought about before,
but believe me, I know where all this came from.
I know where that negative association came from.
It is from my parents.
Practice is not a labor powerless from pointless repetition.
But I just want to blame all the nasty shit people say about me.
All my parents don't mind.
Actually disempowering as using the name of your spiritual practice,
starts to conjure up all the bad stuff in your work day or whatever with your
stubborn toe.
Everything that hurts everything that's gone wrong with your life is associated to this
name.
It's so disempowering.
Finally, words and names have power in and of themselves.
Above and beyond any context associated with them.
In Buddhism, in the Sanskrit language, there's a concept of a seed syllable,
a sound that is so powerful that it has meaning, whether or not you understand it,
whether or not you believe in it.
Invoking these sounds with intention, focus and power can have awesome effects.
Invoking them have hazardly, but with lots of intention, like swearing, can also have
awesome effects, but they usually negative ones.
Consider the sound, ah, it's the first son you make as a baby.
It's the sound you make as you fight for your life.
It's the sound you make at the peak of orgasm.
Hold on.
Is that the sound you make at peak of orgasm?
Uh, dude.
Not rolling out the snake for you.
The last sound that passes your lips is the force of life fades from your body.
It's universal to all of us, and it's a noomestake that in alphabet.
A or A, if you French, is the first letter.
It's also no coincidence that most of our deities and powers use that sound in them.
God, Allah, Yahweh, Brahma, Kanon, Avalo, Katasura, Shiva.
In Arimek, Jesus Christ is Yeshua, which stems from the biblical Hebrew, Yahosua.
Christ, of course, comes from Greek.
In his time, the role of the Messiah, the name of the Messiah, would have been pronounced to
Mosjak.
Taking power words and names and veins, again, sticking your finger in a wall socket.
You're tapping into tremendous power that you have no idea how to channel properly.
And as a result, you'll probably fry yourself.
Not to mention caught off any chances you have for enlightenment or salvation.
Whatever it is that is important to you.
Respect is important, but at least from my point of view.
A prohibition against taking power words and flinging them around,
mostly has far more drastic consequences for you and for the people around you.
So, some audio feedback from the financial aid podcast has nothing to do with financial aid.
Check us out at financialadpodcast.com and thanks a lot Adam.
No man, thank you, I appreciate it.
That's interesting.
All those A words.
Very cool.
And something to think about.
And there's some lessons in what you just said that I want to process,
but perhaps we can start making some other associations or using that power for good.
A names like Aerowana.
The god I pray to you.
Adam, I just was listening.
DSC number 362.
And her manges answer to your golden ticket.
I don't know if you noticed or if you did it on purpose,
but immediately after she makes the comment about what she's going to do for you,
then you have the earthling fairies come on and ask,
do you believe in anything's possible?
That's it.
Can I clear up?
Wanted to drop you a quick comment.
Yeah, you don't think that was intentional to you.
Man, that stuff gets lined up in Cas Blaster and it's green to go.
So yesterday we launched the first golden ticket.
I'm going to tell you just briefly again what that is.
We have this technology we've built called D-Gap.
The dynamic generated asset placement,
which means we can put stuff into our podcast on the network,
which of course could be tags at the front of a podcast,
which is most of the ones that the network now have,
talking about GoDaddy.
Or we can randomly insert them based upon odds,
where I think at a one to 25,000 ratio now on the golden ticket test.
So that somewhere in the podcast,
in fact, I'm going to note the time down right now,
because if you're listening and the next words are congratulations,
then you won.
Okay, I just want to write down that time code.
There we go.
So if you didn't, if you just heard me writing something down,
then you lost, because we're going to do it again today.
So here's how it works.
I am taking that exact moment in the podcast.
I'm going to add that into our D-Gap system.
And one listener will receive a different daily source code,
which will have those actual words,
which will have a separate set of words inserted,
which I pre-recorded and is on the D-Gap server as well.
Now, we've set the odds to 125,000.
So that's your actual chance of pulling out the golden ticket.
Yesterday, we served the golden ticket.
We know kind of where the person was who received the ticket,
and we know that they were using a juice receiver to receive the ticket,
but they haven't checked in yet.
So the thought mistake I made here is,
well, sometimes people are a day behind,
or maybe three days behind, or maybe they didn't listen at all.
So obviously, when we roll out golden ticket promotions on a full scale,
we'll have to lower the odds a little bit,
or we'll have to figure something out.
But it is kind of cool.
It forces you to listen if you want to win.
And boy, where there are lots of people trying to hack in
and scam the system.
That was pretty amazing.
I mean, feel free to do whatever you want to.
It doesn't really matter.
This is just a test.
It's not an official contest,
but I want to do it again today.
I have two people who have a golden ticket.
Remember, it's for that AV.
Was it the Keystone?
I hope it's the Keystone.
Thing is the Keystone AV.
iPod.
Doc and remote.
Our F remote is what it is.
It's a nice little Chatsky.
That's not the point.
So there will be another one going out today.
And so hopefully we'll hear from the new winner,
or from the previous winner, or perhaps from both.
Of course, we'll be happy to shell out both prizes.
But in the future.
And by the way, it's very possible that it didn't work.
That's another thing that Andrew and I, Andrew Grumman,
and I are taking into account that maybe it didn't get inserted
properly, although from everything we can see it did.
In the future, I think the way it will work is we'll have golden ticket
promotional weeks or weekends or whatever.
And then any podcast you listen to on the pod show podcast.
Now, we're could have the golden ticket inserted.
And it could be multiple.
So we're really working on this.
And this again, this is why I like the daily source code.
We can mess around and test stuff and try and break it.
And so if you want to try and hack it again, that's okay.
It doesn't matter.
If you hack it and you win, you win, right?
But obviously we have a lot of strategies and ideas to make that
much more difficult.
The whole concept of registered listeners will make that much easier,
obviously.
So if you receive that golden ticket, you got the message.
Make sure you do as instructed to claim your prize.
And I'm looking forward to talking to one, or perhaps two winners.
Are you ready or rock?
This is the story.
I'm a rock and low, but let's rock.
This is it.
My goal, but let's rock and roll geek show.
The hands down.
Cool.
Rock podcast online.
Hosted by the world's number one.
Rock and roll geek.
American Heartbreaker.
Michael Butler.
So crank it up.
And get that.
With some of the craze, rock and roll.
For the San Francisco.
We're all the geeks rock.
And rock lives off.
This is your rock and roll geek show.
With Michael Butler.
Michael Butler.
When you can listen to the future.
Hi Adam.
This is Chris Future.
With the Think Future Radio Show.
Happy to be the newest member of the Pot Show family.
Thanks for taking me on.
You know when I first started podcasting a year ago, I knew something was missing.
Kick ass, take no prisoners political rant radio.
Sure, there's probably a bit out there, but hardly any in the podcast world.
This is one of the reasons I started a Think Future Radio Show.
What's it all about?
Well, I'm a political commentator.
I'm libertarians of both sides hate me equally.
And I'm also into giving a voice and power and freedom to the people.
What else do I talk about?
Well, pretty much every goddamn thing under the sun.
Current events, politics, Hillary.
It's going to be the next president of the United States.
Crazy ass drivers.
I want to know what you're going to fucking do.
Use your goddamn signal lights.
That's what they're there for.
Stupid people.
Fucking spits in home depot.
Or even how to cook a perfect turkey.
Blining.
You never know what you're going to get.
Every weekday, I'm a Think Future Radio Show.
Now, part of the Pot Show network.
Thanks again, Adam.
No, Chris.
Thank you.
Welcome to La Familia, my friend.
And nice meeting you the other day at the Pot Show HQ.
If you're checking us out on Serious Stars 102,
don't forget to listen to Digital Flotsom tonight at 9 o'clock.
Mr. and PCH is next.
We'll be back here tomorrow with a thank God.
It's Friday edition.
Oh, the show.
Shit couldn't fit that one in.
Sorry about it.
I didn't have time to play my satellite repair managing.
Oh, I love hearing it so much.
By the way, if you.
Peter.
What is going on outside?
Oh, that's inside.
I'm sorry.
It's this cleaning of the cottage day.
Peter abused his own go daddy code to the set-up satellite repairman.com.
That's real easy to remember isn't I don't know how you spell satellite.
S-A-T-E-L-L-I-T-E.
Satellite repairman.com will take you to digitalflotsom.org.
Something just.
Man, that is a lot of noise isn't it?
I hate that.
Something else I was going to say.
Okay, I don't remember.
It is really time for vacation, my friends.
Hi, Adam Curry.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
We can't just start them off like that.
I'm so sorry, CSB.
Comic strip.
Hi, Adam Curry.
Enter the middle of April.
It means until the 50s April.
I will not be sending to you any more audio comments.
And by then, I will not be posting any comments on your blog.
You are going to holiday to beautiful Portugal, so you deserve some tranquility.
Speaking of Portugal, I would be grateful if you could plaque this message to Netherlands
because the time of decision is right now, exactly now.
Dear Netherlands, please take example from Portugal and some other EU countries
and open yourself for new EU citizens from Eastern Europe.
This will be good also for economy of Netherlands.
Please, with sugar and marshmallows on top.
So, Adam Curry have a nice holiday and don't do any podcasts or video casts while on holiday.
Enjoy your gals, some other gals, enjoy the sea and just take time off without podcasting.
Bye.
Oh, comic strip blogger.
That's so nice of you.
Man, what's happening?
You know, the CSB has really got, you know, he really knows what's going on in the European Union.
I do like it when he sends me something that's useful in that regard because there is a lot of weird stuff going on.
You know, if you compare the EU, the European Union to the United States,
which of course was the entire idea to create one monetary unit to create a single union.
There's all these problems at the local level.
I mean, just imagine that, you know, you could not go from one state to the next state
or from New York to Connecticut.
Yeah, you could go there to visit, but you couldn't actually work there.
You know, there's all kinds of things that are happening.
And comic strip blogger really is on top of it.
So, appreciate it.
I am taking along some equipment, not a full mobile set.
I'll take along cast blaster and the wireless love mic just in case,
well, this case is something that we want to do.
And of course, I'm taking along my video camera for, you know, our own vacation stuff and pictures, etc.
So, I'm sure that, you know, in the 10 days there's no way I can stay offline.
And, you know, I have to get online at least once a day to empty out my freaking Gmail.
God damn, you know, they're coming out with that, with that corporate Gmail,
where you can use your own domain name, etc.
I'm hoping, what it comes with now comes standard with two gigs per account.
I'm hoping that since it is a corporate service, that's,
God, what is that noise?
It's pissing me off.
Soundproof the studio now?
I'm hoping that I'll be able to buy more space when that becomes fully available.
I've signed up for the day-to-now and,
God, that is so annoying isn't it?
It's really distracting me.
Okay, so going on vacation won't be doing podcasts.
Yesterday, a great idea was thrown up,
it was thrown into the discussion about the box,
B.O.C.S. Bravo Oscar Charlie.
In other words, the best of Charlie.
Hey Adam, it's listener Jim again.
Hey, I just got back in Hong Kong from a couple days in China.
It's now 1230 in the morning on Thursday,
and caught up on the Charlie 361 and part of 362.
I'm glad to hear that you played my comment about the box,
and I'm really excited about Ellie's proposal to have the listeners generate that,
I think it's a great idea.
I'm not a position to start creating any podcasts yet.
I haven't even got my own off the ground.
But I do have some ideas that some of the other podcasters
that listeners out there might want to take and run with.
One would be a show dedicated to FAQ.
Another would be a show dedicated to the birth of Trinity,
and I think a couple of the funniest ones could be shows dedicated to feedback
from Madge or even better yet feedback from comic strip blogger.
Anyway, there's a few ideas.
Again, have a great vacation.
Look forward to hearing what your listeners come up with.
I think it will do make great shows.
Well, Julie soon.
Let me tell you, man, that already I've received three
of Bravo Oscar Charlie's.
Three of them this morning.
Just since that one thing, that one comment,
the one discussion we had yesterday,
I really, I can't tell you how blown away I am by that.
And how much I appreciated.
So I need four more, and anyone who sends that in,
I'll make sure you get a nice bag of podshow,
swag, t-shirts, and crap, and what have you.
Sam Levin will put some crap together.
It'll be nice and that you'll enjoy.
And I really, really appreciate the whole thought.
Great idea.
And it's unfortunate that we don't have the full PDN up in rolling,
because you can put shows up for delivery at a certain day,
or a certain time.
So I'm going to preload all those,
but it really would be before the launch.
So we have to figure out some way to be posting those shows,
while I'm, excuse me, I'm not even drinking a sense say,
oh, I don't know with, oh, heartburn, gastronomic issues.
But yeah, we got, we got some great, great shows,
and it's just blown me away.
Hey Adam, Jim again.
One more show idea that you've got to include
is a show dedicated to Roger Small.
Maybe even Roger could host that show.
Boy, that would be great to hear him talking about his own comments.
And what was going on in his mind when he actually made the calls to you.
Yeah, really.
Anyway, this whole idea of listener generated shows gave me
one more thing to think about.
You've already admitted that 70% of your show
or more comes from listener generated input.
Well, if you now have listeners that are editing and preparing your shows,
you may just be able to quit your quit your day job job.
Imagine that sitting around getting paid
for preparing shows that you don't prepare
with content that you don't make.
Boy, now that's my idea of hitting a lot of.
Take care.
Talk to you soon.
I love that.
That would be, now, when we get to that point,
that's when I can just slowly fade to black.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Great idea, man.
Love it.
Take the dudes and do debts, but dudes.
Have you seen the most recent soccer girl video?
You know, the soccer girl, of course,
part of the podcast network.
And she's also a part of the one message,
one brand many voices campaign for Go Daddy.
Just around you, the end of her most recent video.
She has a very interesting way of,
remember now, what we're doing here is we're leaving all of the creative
advertising up to the podcasts as themselves,
because only they know how to communicate with their audience.
And soccer girl definitely is onto what her audience wants.
I suggest you take a look at it.
It's certainly not family or kids safe, but very, very funny.
And by the way, soccer girl, I think I'd like to rent that space
myself in the near future.
I think it's very, very valuable.
And I just want, I wrote this down.
I wanted to talk to about this for a couple of days now,
because I guess it's kind of subsided in the world press,
but there's still a lot of crap going on in France.
And there's a lot of riots and burnings of cars,
and people getting beaten into the hospital.
And I just wanted to tell you what this was about,
because I find it fascinating.
There was a law that was proposed.
Now, I'm not sure, I'm sure comics are blogger.
We'll put in the comments the exact details.
From what I understand, the government, either wanted to
or pass the law that made the hiring,
but particularly the firing of employees much easier.
And much easier for young people to get fired.
Now, that, of course, is the way it's being portrayed,
but really what it is.
The relaxation on the employment rules.
Now, in the United States certainly,
and I believe in the United Kingdom,
the fire at any moment for pretty much any reason.
I think this is a good thing.
And this is a totally an American viewpoint,
but this is coming from an entrepreneur
who is also set up companies in other countries.
The Netherlands is one.
And in the Netherlands, when you're hired,
a couple of things happen.
First of all, guaranteed benefits, which is great.
You don't get that in many other countries.
You don't get that necessarily in the United States.
By the way, at Pod Show, you do.
And I must say, many of our podcasters also receive similar benefits.
That you get right off the bat.
Then you get something called the 13th month,
which is automatic, which means as an employer,
you have to pay all of your employees an extra month salary.
Not for working just because that's the law.
And then you have vacation money.
And you can't fire anyone.
Even with just cause, you have to buy them out.
And usually, there's a whole formula for it,
but you have to take them to court, and it's very, very difficult.
But what this breeds is laziness.
And I have seen this in every single one of my companies.
Because once people are in, they're like, OK.
I got a job.
Now, I'm set.
You know, they come in at five after nine.
They have the code on at five minutes to five.
You know, they, oh, I don't feel good today.
I'll just stay home.
Very, very, very difficult to operate a business.
And if someone just isn't working out.
I'm sorry.
You have to leave.
Now, of course, what happens is you can hire people on a short-term contract basis.
And this is the really bad thing.
His company's hire young people for a two or three month contract.
And then they, they say, OK, let's get into your contract.
I think you can do it twice.
So in total, maybe for six months.
But it's a horrible, horrible system.
Now, the contrarian view, of course, as Europeans will often say, or say,
they've said to me, well, yeah, but you know, you use this fear.
And everyone's afraid of getting fired.
And I was, you know, never in my life have I ever threatened or had to threaten anyone
with being fired.
In fact, I think you'll find in the US that it's,
it's so cultural that it's not fear.
It's just people want to do a good job.
You know, and they put in the work because they're excited about it.
Now, there's also lots of incentives at Pod Show.
There's, you know, there's stock incentives and ownership of the company and, you know,
all kinds of things that we do.
But now, here are these kids that are rioting in France because they are not
being given the security that they expect from a welfare state.
The very careful United States have ever tried to integrate this.
I mean, I'm all from medical benefits, and I wish we could figure that out.
And, you know, on a company by company basis, it's either good or bad, essentially.
But wow, I can't believe that this is what they're fighting about, you know,
instead of going out and getting a fucking job, you know, or work, you know, trying to get a job.
You know, no, we're just going to go riot because it's not what we deserve.
And this is this whole welfare state, man.
It's like, I hear people in Europe all the time talk about what they feel they deserve.
And, you know, this happened and I deserve compensation.
So France gets your act together.
People of France, I just say, please get your act together.
Just, you know, find, do something more productive than this.
Okay.
I don't know if that came out right, but I think you kind of understand what I'm talking about.
Hey, a couple more things before we wrap it up for today.
Hi, Adam, this is Peter from Internet Communicators.
And I like to comment on something you were talking about in 3601,
the Charlie 3601 about part two mob and the way that they tried to get to put
advertising stuff in front of your podcast.
We at Internet Communicators developed a portal,
site called part promo station.
You can find that part promo station dot com where you can find
podcasts where you can listen to podcasts where you can see some sort of a visual
that belongs to that podcast where you can download the podcast where you can subscribe
or you can see websites anything.
And we are seriously thinking about putting ads on that website.
Visual ads, not audio ads, visual ads like banner stuff like that.
And, well, you know, I don't see that much of a difference between ads on a website
and yes, that are in front of a mobile service like the part two mob guys did.
So I like to have your opinion on that because I don't want to get sued by the
part father himself.
Never.
I don't think that's a very good idea.
I don't have that much money.
I can tell you that.
Okay, thank you for your time and I'm looking forward to your comment on our
comment and I hope to speak to you later.
Goodbye.
Well, okay, that's very, and there's quite a healthy
conversation going on about this.
I think the easiest way to test your theory is why don't you take
a podcast from a mainstream media company.
So take one from clear channel has lots of the audio podcast and you could probably
get one from NPR and why don't you start putting ads in front of that.
And then see what and then let them know that you're doing it and give them your
theory and then see what happens.
Because it ain't going to work that way.
Wait, I have another comment about this.
Hello Adam, this is Kevin from Coloring Outside the Lines.
Then I have a serious issue with Pod to mom.
The issue is not monetary.
It's with associations.
I am very careful as a professional body painter of what gets associated with my artwork.
I just want to say that all that crackling noise that's his recording, not my, not my set up.
So kind of listen through it because it's worth it.
And I am also consider it to those people who would like to have ads in my
show.
The reason why is because of the nature of my work.
Associations can be very detrimental.
I really don't like the idea that a company could take an ad.
Let's say adult websites porn.
And put it in front of my show.
I really don't like that.
Now I'm not saying that Pod to mom is going to start selling porn.
But I don't like the idea that they could.
Now let's look at it at the bigger picture.
And this is what happens if let's say a casino starts running ads.
So these godcasters now have their shows sandwiched in between casinos.
Or let's say we find out that there's a company that screws you over in the past and now you're advertising for them.
I don't think I would like that at all.
Now I've seen some comments saying that well what's the difference between that and like the podcast pickle and podcast alley.
They have ads.
The difference is that there is a distinct difference in mediums.
The problem I have with Pod to mom is that they're using the same medium to do their advertisements.
So it makes it almost indistinguishable.
Now for those people who are starting to wonder exactly why am I concerned about this and
after all associations are no big deal.
I only have one thing to say.
I haven't even heard that way.
Okay.
Thank you.
It worked.
Okay.
Let's talk about Pod to mom for a second.
So there's a couple of different things.
First of all, anything that you create anybody anywhere, whether you just write something
down on a piece of paper or whether you record something automatically that is your copyrighted work.
You don't have to register that.
You don't have to do anything more.
It's your work and it's copyrighted and that is pretty much the law everywhere as far as I know.
The use of your work falls under whatever copyright you choose to give use choose to put on it.
So basically no one can use that work without express permission.
Things like creative comments have made it very easy so that instead of, you know, people having to contact the originator of a work continuously to find out what can I do with this, what you will allow me to do with this.
The creative comments licenses really say, okay, here's what you're allowed to do.
For instance, I would deem this this podcast.
Licenseable under the creative comments copyright attribution non-commercial share like, which means you have to share it the same way.
You have to credit where it comes from and you can't use it in any commercial venture.
That is very different from a directory link.
By the way, I have to say that using a shows picture as a directory link.
Actually, I guess you should ask for permission to use that, which brings up an interesting point a lot of people have mentioned about the podshow.com directory listings.
We're definitely changing that. We went through this whole thing with Jason Calcanas before and we've, we've now put in the website links.
But within two weeks, it's all going to change and there will be no huge ads next to the listing.
So, you know, that's, we're not trying to make anything look like ours.
Really, we're just focusing on a whole bunch of other stuff and, you know, the only thing we could do is pull it all down.
But it's now, you know, in the middle of an integration with podcast alley.
So apologies for people who don't like that.
The whole thing has been discussed and in open form, just look for the blog post from Jason Calcanas and myself about that.
So we are changing that because I don't think that's exactly right either. That placement is not proper.
But we could actually have the discussion where if you are, if you've not expressly submitted your podcast to the podcast alley directory to podshow that we shouldn't be able to use your logo, that would make sense.
It would be a shame, obviously, because it's all it is for promotional purposes.
It's like the phone book, you know, we're trying to get people to make it easy to find stuff.
So directories is pretty much inherent to the internet. Now, when it comes to taking, I'll just use my podcast in this example.
Taking that and presenting that to anyone in any way shape or form where it could be deemed confusing.
And the law does have an alloyer, but the law does have some very specific jurisprudence about consumer or customer or user confusion.
If it seems like the ads are a part of a podcast, then there's definitely a case.
Now, specifically with pod to mob, let me just backtrack a little bit.
So they have been around for a while, and they've, you know, either sucked out other directories, which is perfectly cool.
You know, we make our directories available, certainly, any part of that org to take that, that opium l file, the listing and use that anywhere you want.
Because that's good. It's distribution for everybody. I totally agree with it. I think it's great that you are able to receive podcasts on your cell phone.
Now, when I checked out the service, you know, the first thing I heard was this podcast is brought to you by and then there was a ringtone company.
And then my show started with our own ad insertion or tag insertion of go daddy. That's a violation of the copyright because it's confusing consumers.
Now, after, and by the way, I never submitted anything to their directorie, you know, the guys from pod to mob are very, very vague.
And since we've started this whole brewha, they have changed what they're doing, for instance.
So my show has been removed from the directory entirely upon my request, by the way.
But Don and Drew is an example of still in there. Now, what has changed is pod to mob is no longer serving ads. Here's what they're doing.
Let me see if I can make this work. It's coming from from a different computer that I've passed into the board.
And it's streaming, of course.
The podcast you requested is being brought to you by pod to mob.com. Please tell your friends. They don't need an iPod to listen to podcasts.
Thank you very much, and now here's your podcast.
See how that I like. I really don't have a problem with that.
I'm okay. I think they still should ask me for the permission to do that. Now, in fact, I demand they asked for permission to do that.
But I would say, yeah, that's okay. You can do that, but you can't go inserting ads.
Now, let me say something about pod to mob. So I've discussed this on the show.
We've had there's been many postings about it.
And I've sent several emails I've had Brian Longer, start director of operations, call them. They're not getting back to me at all.
And I think that these guys are a bunch of quite honestly shady characters from LA who are in the ringtone business.
And they're in the ringtone business, or being in the ringtone business makes them very knowledgeable about how to get stuff, you know,
little applications on to cell phones. So, you know, they have all the right knowledge, but I think they have the wrong business acumen.
And they're not being very apologetic at all. They're trying to defend their business model.
And what I'm getting, and this is the most interesting thing. I'm getting emails and comments from everywhere saying,
Oh, go sue them. Go sue them. Take them out. No, you know what? We're not going to do that.
Go take care of yourselves. I'm going to take care of our shows and make sure that we're protected because I don't want any more fights with people.
I don't want fights legal fights with these guys.
And there could be more on the horizon because ringtone guys are doing really nasty shit.
As an example, Jeff Smith, who makes all those wonderful jingles like...
This is popping up on ringtone websites all over the internet.
Without any permission to do so, no relationship to the creative of the work Jeff Smith and even worse.
They're putting a different owner, author name, onto this ringtone.
And I'll tell you why. The ringtone business is a part of the big record industry, the RIA.
And when you sell a ringtone, a portion of that sale goes to the author composer, the owner of the rights, basically, of that ringtone.
So what they're doing is they're stealing this ringtone and several others of Jeff's, by the way, putting it up for sale.
And then, first they take the sale amount, the transaction, and then on the back end, they get it, they get money paid from AskCat,
BMI for the distribution. And this is something that we really need to go after.
I mean, these guys are chisters. So I can only think that if you've got pod to mob, who are kind of in that ringtone business,
that they do not have podcasters best intentions at heart.
Unless they prove otherwise, which would be really nice if they responded in a proper manner, either privately through email,
by picking up the phone and calling the numbers we left for them, or by really getting into the conversation.
So far, I've seen nothing but hogwash, and I do not trust these guys.
And now, one last song for y'all, from the pod save music network.
If you've got a grandma, you may appreciate this song.
Or if you are a grandma, listen to this Charlie.
I'm almost turning I need to.
And that's a lot of years ahead of you.
So listen close to what I say.
This grandma's feeling old today.
She said I can't believe I'm sitting here, old as I am.
I've never been stoned.
I waited too long to bring it all.
Grandma's going to fly.
So rolled it up and passed it around.
Grandma smoked the whole thing down.
Said she was making love for wasted ground.
She's too many times, she turned it down.
She said you live your life until it's gone.
The things you never tried, just slip away.
So they're gone too.
I waited too long to bring it all.
Grandma's going to fly.
And as you talk about the old days,
Said some things I blew my mind.
Because you ain't seen a thing.
Do you see Grandma getting high?
Now grandma's she didn't have much time left.
She made use of every breath.
And swear she smiled before she left.
I felt the world fall off her chest.
And there's a gate to tell and open wide.
She slipped over to the other side.
She was saying, I waited too long to bring it all.
Grandma's going to fly.
I waited too long to bring it all.
From the pod safe music network.
John Nicholson, Tennessee, and Grandma's getting high.
Forzens of today's podcast brought to you by AccuView.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Thanks for listening to my banter.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast of
Liberty Network from Podjo and Lime White Networks.
I love it.