This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 405.
Mr. Curry, the pod father, forgive this intrusion on such a joyous occasion.
We've come to ask for your blessing.
My name is Ed, and I'm Carlos.
And this is Ed.
We are from a podcast we call the Starcast.
We want to know that we have lived up to your example.
You boys come to ask my blessing and my daughter's wedding day.
Well, these boys have honored me and my family with your good music.
You're an interesting bubble and no questions attitude towards what is asked of you.
This honor is the pod father.
In one day, I may come to ask a favor of you.
No kiss the real.
Thank you father.
You were a little lower.
May your daughter's first child be a masculine child.
Hi, this is Sophia Ramos.
If you want to hear great music, keep it here on the daily source code with Adam Curry.
Check me out at myspace.com slash Sophia Ramos.
Rock-on.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped my ass.
Three minutes?
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking friends, man.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Not just in kids to Petroo.
One kid.
Play that PCB.
Papa!
athleticmaking,
mac other star.
Oh ok,
I got it,
Friday.
me
Hey anger teasing your head.
No way, I'll make it my mercy to the grave
Take your dreams to you, catch the things
These are aging on both sides of faith
Love is only a medium, they look at me there
Cloth is ever changing, hope is shining in my eyes
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
And then we'll hold me still and stand by my mind
In the middle of the last time to burn
And then we'll hold me clean and take you home
But I want to be to love you
Love is only a medium, they look at me there
Cloth is ever changing, hope is shining
Cloth is ever changing, hope is shining in my eyes
I hope is shining in my eyes
Love is only a medium, they look at me there
Cloth is ever changing, hope is shining in my eyes
So, I hope is shining in my eyes
No way, I'll make it my mercy to the grave
Love is only a medium, they look at me there
Cloth is ever changing, hope is shining in my eyes
Yeah, hope is shining in my eyes
Love is only a medium, they look at me there
Cloth is ever changing, hope is shining in my eyes
Oh yeah, that'll wake you up to fear of us
Esperanza coming to you from San Francisco
Very sunny northern California, hey everybody how you're doing is the Daily Source Code today
It's Friday
Man, I'm ready for the show, I'm ready to rumble
Lots of positive music for you today, lots of feedback, all kinds of stuff that I've been saving up for the end of the week
And you know, I woke up this morning, actually I did normally I wake up before the alarm clock
So it went off at 6 o'clock and I'm like, hey, I'm really tired
Why am I so tired, I went to bed at 10.30
I know why, I've been traveling a lot
You know what I would say, I arrive a Monday, I went straight to the office
And I've just been nonstop since then, I think I'm ready for the weekend
How about you?
Some of you may be listening to this on your way home
If you're in the UK, you probably got it around 5 in the afternoon
Some of you in the west coast, you're probably getting this early morning
I may be you're 11 o'clock meeting if you're on the east coast in the US
And if you're in Australia?
Well, how is Saturday?
I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired
I know, I know, I know
It is the month of a month of the show
Hello, hello
Happy Friday, Charlie France
This is Ray from Holland with a little sucker update
Because not only Holland is orange, the whole world is getting a little orange
And that's a lot better than the Greengrassi Marijuana color refining up to
Everywhere I come and I tell that I'm from the Netherlands
People always start to talk about the coffee shops
Anyway, today at 1,800 hours European time in Stuttgart, Germany
The World Cup match Holland against Ivory Coast will kick off
Actually, I'm not such a big sucker fan, but I really like to watch all the World Cup matches
As much as I can
Tonight, our Dutch coach Marco von Buster will start with the same 11 as last Sunday
That means that Raphael von der Fart won't play
But, Wesley Snyder will be in the center of the field again
I hope Rut van Nieselroy, show off a little more
And Aryan Robwe will play with his 10 friends on the field
Every coach coach Henry Mitchell has a knife on his throat
They have to win this game
I think the World will beat more orange at the tonight
And I don't underestimate the gang, but they're going to be spanked
By the Italian Big Swinging Dig
I'm sorry, pal, but the 11 girls from the States are not going to win the World Cup
Anyway, hope you have a wonderful weekend
See you soon
Bye-bye
Hey Ray
I'm fighting words, man
What are you talking about?
The 11 girls from the States give me a break
I have a really good feeling about him
And tomorrow a couple of the enthusiasts from Pod Show HQ
We're all getting together
We're going to watch that game
They have a shot
I know they do, and they just had to kind of get into the whole vibe
So funny that all this World Cup stuff is going on
For me, in my limited little world of Pod casting
But there's a whole other championship going on as well
Which is the NBA finals
Vasca Ball here in the States
And it's funny because I really didn't know about it
Until last night Ron said, hey man, come on, come on
Come on, my place will have dinner there
Of course, we had to take cabs
Since the Trinity option was out
Trinity is at the doctor by the way
She'll be okay
Today we get full diagnosis and cost structure
But I'm getting her fixed no matter what
I love my Trinity
If you're new to this show, Trinity is my
French-Fri-Oil Burnin
Mercedes station wagon 300 turbo diesel from 1984
That dropped her transmission
So we actually watched the heat gain
He'd against the Mavericks, Miami versus Dallas
It was a good game
Finally, Miami actually played a really good game
It was alright, you know?
It's funny because once you, I don't know
This is kind of hard
Something about soccer, even though you get relatively low points
It seems to be so much less structure to the game
How things can happen
And for some reason with basketball, it seems like
It really is based a lot on the tech
You see in soccer, you're not supposed to follow the guy
And of course, you know, they're always trying to do something
To knock someone down without getting a yellow or red card
When basketball, this filing thing is really important
Because then you get your free throws
I don't know, for some reason
It just didn't quite hit me as I thought it would
I don't know, what is happening to me?
I'm turning into a European, gosh, dang it
Like in that soccer stuff
Hey, voicemail numbers all weekend long
You may be listening to the show over the weekend
I'd love to hear from you, we have two numbers
In New Jersey, 201, 65, 65, 7
And I have a number in London
So whichever is cheaper for you to call, feel free
020, 768, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3
Some cool news yesterday, some pod show news
Pod cast Ali is now featured on the new Nokia phones
They have some kind of pod catcher aggregator built in
And you can, you can now search through
portions of the pod cast Ali directory
And it will download stuff automatically
I posted it on curry.com
So it's definitely cool
And pretty proud of that
It's all part of the evil master plan
As we unveil pod show plus
And the pod cast Ali Renett, where my friends
I've met him, I've just had to ring
You know, I'm looking to last Friday
So to 402
I'll have to say, London in the summer time
Yeah
You know, I'll say, oh my god
You should sit in so close square
On a weekday
Around about lunchtime
When all the secretary is coming out
Hosing the skirts up
Mumbling the tops down
Oh yes
Hang on second
You shouldn't really put this on a
They're talking about
Lockup pose
Anyway
I'm sorry, well I say
Hello Adam
Renett here
I can tell you
No wait
I am a fuck you
I didn't get it
I am a fuck
I'm a fuck
Okay
Thank you
There you go
It's all one guy apparently
Oh man
Yeah
I mean please don't don't think that we're opening up a London office to do any business
We're just there for the boobies in the summertime
Failure to comply radio
A show where we make you laugh
Cry and touch you in that special way
Or maybe just laugh
From conspiracy theories
To throwing Katie Holmes into a ghetto
This show has it all
We're random
We're retarded and guess what
We're politically incorrect
It's failure to comply radio
Visit us at www.ftcradio.net
Hi
This is Caitlin Smith
And you're listening to the daily source code with your benevolent host
The podfather himself
A guy with really great hair
Adam Kern
Straight out of my mind
It's spinning around
What?
Simple things
That don't matter at all
And I get a share of them
It's my destruction
And sometimes I get so dizzy
And then for
All the smoke
I've been heard
Raves for you
Like many times before
It's difficult to see
The melodies
Cook the eyes
Like enough nice to welcome
Here in my eyes and you
Let's kill me
Can you hear me?
Will you please follow me
Will you hear me?
Like when do you've carried me
To a better place
Can you hear me?
That I'm here
I understand it
My mind has constant love
I love that feeling
When you've slept with me
Can you hear me?
Will you hear me?
Does this affect you?
Hey
hmm
it all
cause
here
coming
is
from
Katelyn Smith from the Podsafe Music Network and here me let me just check out her
bio for a second here. Oh, she's cute. Something magical happens. I read from
the bio when she grabs a guitar and steps up to the microphone. Coffee
shots become silence. Loud band loving teens turn quiet. Adults turn an
ear to the obvious gift and embrace all that this artist has to give. It
may be your confidence or the heartfelt expression of her music. It's
Katelyn Smith from Minnesota. Cool. Like it. Who are you? Oh, this is
kind of cool. Her influences. Jewel. Nicole Nordman and then this is cool.
Beth Thorne Lee and the Bitties. Excellent. Very, very cool. So Podsafe Music
artists influencing her. I like that very much. And people ask me all the
time. How may I? How can we get our song played on the daily source code? Well,
really is he one. I have to like the song. It's just that's sorry. It's my
show. I don't care. I have to like the song. And I like a wide range of
stuff. Two, it's always does help when when the artist cuts a promo. And
this was even pre mix. It came to me in all one pre mix form. And of
course, at the end of the day, naked pictures also help. I had him. This is
the Higgins from the editing dot com photo cast. Just listening to
that. But for a four and you play the comment about the guy from the Euro
star. Excuse me. And then licensing Podsafe Music for their commercial
podcast that they're producing. And I was wondering if you could talk a little
bit about where does the line get drawn for a commercial podcast? And we have
a lot of podcasts. There's out there that are looking at or have already
quit their day jobs. And they're collecting income from their podcast. And
some of them do play Podsafe Music. So what's, you know, what, where does the
definition fall of commercial podcast? I'm sure it's in the license. But in the
terms of agreeing to it. But, you know, well, it's a computer guy. I'm trying to
just click except on the terms of whatever software I'm looking at. So yeah.
And please, you can talk a little bit about that. And thanks a lot. And if you're
for talking for out there, check out Editing dot com. Thanks. Bye bye.
Right on it. It's real simple. Actually, I'm glad you asked the question. It's about
the distribution. So this is really for podcasters. If you make a podcast, which
they call it a derivative work or whatever the legal term is that you click the
way the minute you signed up, you know, that's okay. And it can be commercial. I mean,
witness the daily source code, totally a commercial, a commercial show. Go daddy.com,
DSC three upon checkout for your domain name for $6.95. But if you were to burn this to
a CD and distribute it to clients for a fee, which is the case of the euro star, well,
then you have to go and get permission because now you're doing something else
with it as that the license intends. And I think that's pretty much not also commercial
clients often. They want to compensate. And I think that's kind of what was going on
here. There was an agency working for the client for euro star. There's podcasts that
were being developed. They may or may not be if they're internal podcasts only, then the
same thing would kick in because then it's, it's not a public work and you have to give
all the attribution. So really, it's about the distribution. But if you're just, if you're
quitting your day job, if you're quit your day job, if you want to quit your day job,
you just want to make a show. And you're making money by doing your show. It's not a
problem as long as you're signed up to the podcast music and the network. And of course,
you have to report back in. You just want to think about all the music. You know, I really
do like playing all different types of tunes along Fridays. I do like to kick it a little
bit. Was it? Have you ever heard that in over your head, Julian Smith? So he's noticed
that I've been picking up on some R&B and hip-hop stuff. And I think I saw on his one of
his show notes that he was happy that I was coming out of the closet. As a closet, as
a closet dancer, a closet hip hopper, R&B, you're not alone, Julian. Hey Adam, this is Jeff
Hines. We're riding that dance party podcast. I'm glad you're finally coming out of the
closet. Forget all that head, bangers, ball, bowls, shit. And who cares about a mallet? I mean,
does anyone look good to mallet? I know I don't. You look good to mallet, Adam. So it's
all about dancing. It's all about shaking your ass. Adam, what kind of ass do you have?
Is it round? Is it square? Is it fat? Is it thin? Is it loose? Is it tight? You know,
you like to get it like that? I'm fine. So I'm glad to see that you're finally playing some
dance music on the PSC that people can shake it and make it to. And that's what it's all
about. So this is Jeff Hines with a Friday dance party. And all I have to say is keep on
dancing.
What to come over here and see what kind of ass I have, man? If you're that interested. So it's
Friday. Normally, I'd be doing pod save the queen with Christina. It's time for episode
number three. Of course, I'm not home. And she is, or I mean, our other home as it were. She
really wants to do the show. And of course, I want her to do the show as well. And I am, I guess,
I'm the producer. So we have figured something out, hopefully, but it won't be today, because
it's just all the time zone stuff. Because what time is it now? It's already deep into the
afternoon. And I have to get off to the office after I'm done with the with Charlie. So it'll be
over the weekend, but we're going to try and do advice Skype. She's going to email me the songs.
And I think with the new Skype, the PC version, at least, as you know, I'm still on windows.
And she has windows as well. I think the the sound quality just might be good enough to actually
pull it all together and pull off a pod save the queen. I can't wait to hear what she has lined up for
obviously. Adam, hey, Moose Lawrenceville, California. Sorry to hear about Trinity's transmission,
but hearing Christina's podcast, which I really enjoyed, the thing that comes to mind is for the
last, though, longest time that I can remember, you've been kind of complaining about not having
a producer. And well, long behold, you're a producer for your daughter. And you're doing a great job
and so she so cheers. Hi, Adam. This is Chris and take us down there. I like to hear you play
straight by super thrown through. I think you guys will need to get some close going on. Thanks.
Bye. Wow. Your wish to my command. Only with the music heavy. Straight on the Charlie.
I have described nothing but black and I'm afraid, still I am dying to tell you.
Great. You're into the room. Make a mistake. Let's see, just how much it hurts you.
I'd like to crack. I can't be alone. Always a pack and they're just at danger by now.
I can't be alone. Always a pack and they're just at danger by now.
Show me the way to the perfect one where you're so far. I might seem angry to mingle about myself
while. Show me the way to the perfect one where you're so far.
There's a pack and they're just at danger by now. Great. Nothing black and I'm afraid, still I am dying to tell you.
The super thrown straight. Those of you listening to us on serious stars 102. The satellite window
is a closing PCH next and I will see you guys back here on Monday. Source code listeners, we continue
now on the show. Tagtabbit. Almost had it perfectly back time. I don't know what went wrong.
I'm using the new version of Cas Blaster by the way. It's kind of cool. Cas Blaster Mike heard me talking
yesterday about ID3 tags and not being able to see those in Cas Blaster. He turned around last night
or whatever and made me a new version. When I mouse over, I mouse over scraped. Of course not all songs
have ID3 tags. There we go. Some of them are working. Although I noticed one thing for some reason
my F1, which is my AC to the future. If I hit that, it doesn't do anything. All the other F commands
start stuff like the thing out of the Friday. I've got the metro moment, but when I hit F1,
it doesn't happen. So I don't know if that's a change in Cas Blaster, Mike or if that's something
that's changed on my machine. Super thrown. Of course by requesting a hamster, it's fastest rising
band formed in the C-coasteria by Brothers Kobe and Kerry Dodd, who added basis Adam Hor and percussionist
Travis Barton. The band has performed throughout the Northeast and opened for such acts as Vince
Wellnick, of the grateful dead and Todd Rungren and Gary Hoey. He, Gary Hoey is playing
tonight, everybody. Alright, I still have one more song. I got so many cool things I want to share
with you. Yesterday K2 Kevin Rady asked about Snake Bite, which is the mixture of cider and
ale, I guess, in the UK, which he thought was outlawed and he really had a legitimate question.
So he asked that by calling to the voicemail numbers, and of course we have an answer already.
Hello Adam, Mike Turner, from Bristol, England, currently working in Chelmum,
also known as GEM Indicator, one second life. He'll comment, Snake Bite's eye, Charlie 404.
Snake Bite is actually perfectly legal in England, although some pubs won't actually serve it,
because apparently it doesn't make people a lot more pissed, a lot quicker. I don't think it does,
actually. The thing is just another legend. Anyway, what you say is beer. We brew it's actually
called ale or bitter. Now, to make a snake bite, cider is normally mixed with larga, what called
larga, which would be both lids or fosters, or current bugs, something like that, which is the
under beer. You would never mix cider with ale or bitter. Also, that other bloke, I'm not too
sure. The one who criticizes me will show your sound and how to run it, but I think he's an asshole.
And I agree with you. I mean, who would tell GEM Indicator's guitar sounded distorted and he should
turn the distortion off. Anyway, just for now. All right.
All right, man. Thank you. Okay, so we've settled that. I think it's time for a sound seeing tour
of snake bite in the UK. You know, I still have not actually, you know, you have to have your own
pub. I think it's kind of like the an unwritten law in the UK. And that's the pub where you're going
hang out. I have not chosen one. And I really do need to do that. So perhaps a sound seeing tour
and believe me, lots of people have sent me pub rules and, you know, when you're supposed to buy a
drink or accept a drink and how you're supposed to strike up a conversation, there is a several
rule books on all this. How to do it properly. But it seems to me like it's time for a sound
seeing tour of snake bite. Maybe a snake bite or two. Interesting discussion going on over
curry.com as of turned on the comments again. It seems like the comic strip blogger and
jacic watcher stuff is all calm down. And if it starts up again, I'm just deleting comments. I'm
so sick and tired of that. Can we all just get along? But the comments now are about the Earth
Link ad challenge that we've been running. And this is pretty cool because this is where you get to
make the advertising. And of course, just listening to all these different submissions is by definition
advertising, but I look at it as content for the show. And so there's people who're saying,
oh, you know, this one sucks and that was no good. It's just like mainstream radio. But the
whole point of this is, then why don't you just send in your own submissions? So you should tell us
how it's supposed to go. How it's supposed to work? What will work? Ad challenge.podshow.com
I got another submission for you today. They are getting very good. I think we're seeing like 20
new ones a day come in. And this is for valuable cash prizes, $2,000 in prize money.
We're doing the earthly clues. That's right, baby. Earth Link, bombastic broadband.
Delicious, darling. That's Earth Link. Ethnic comes home to you and brings it home to mama.
That's our sister. That's what I'm talking about. In Earth Link, we'll help you out with all your
internet needs. It's just go to EarthLink.com. Let them know that papa sits here. Yeah, that's
it. That's what I'm talking about. Yeah. All right. So this week and I get something to go
look for a table and some other solution for the studio because it's really gotten bad now.
I should take a picture of this. You know what? Hold on a second. We'll do just that.
So I've got everything off of the Tashiba laptop show notes, rundown my playlist from music,
cast blaster. But as you know, I've told you about this. It's all in the kitchen. That's where
it's all set up. And it's just way too low for me. So I have a roller bag, which when you roll on
take the airplane, you can put in the overhead bin. And so the laptops on top of that. Now the
microphone, I only have a really small stand, a portable stand with a heavy foot. And I just
snapped the high LPR 40 in there. But since it's so low, I've taken a candlestick.
And let me take a picture of this. You won't believe it unless I tell you how long. Let's see if I
get the whole thing in the shot here. There we go. Oh, wait. I want to get the microphone. This is not
easy. Getting the whole whole thing in the shot. There we go. Let's take a picture. Let's try one
just for the picture. There we go. I think we'll get a kick out of that. I'll post that in the
show notes somewhere. Link to a flicker page. Okay. I had one more song lined up. I know I know I
want to play it because I really like it. What is this Antonio Bastion from Spain? Let me see
lead singer in Frogmouth, Labuelet, Muff. And Bastolich duo Antonio Antonio Antonio Antonio Antonio,
Antonio Bastion's best. Antonio Bastion's voice, harmonica are his signature. Currently working on
his label and first solo album, new site coming soon. Excellent. Link to all that goodness in the
show notes. Let's check out Don't Break it. I think you will enjoy it. Oh, I remember.
Georgie Todd sent me this one. Yes, funny. You don't need to be on the radio, my friend. Stick with us
podcasters.
I don't care about the fame and glory. Just pay my song on the radio. I don't need much
never. I don't have a Rolex or a caseload. Give me a chance. Let the public decide.
Play my video long time. I don't have a thing behind. Just want my chance. Is it a crime?
What must I do? To get on the radio? I'll message it above but I know to the low.
What's on my paints? But I can dance. Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance.
Three or four plays in the day. I'm not asking for the moon.
In review me, I got things to say. A brand new LP come in soon. If you're septic and you're
critic, don't take my music in the first degree. If my music gives you steady,
it's my soul. Don't you agree? On my side you get on the radio. I'll message it above but I know
to the low. What's on my paints? But I can dance. Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance.
What must I do? To get on the radio? I'll message it above but I know to the low.
What's on my paints? But I can dance. Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance.
Like a pit bull, I will never let go. Went to the critics come to my show.
All publicity is good publicity. They're opinion will never harm me.
I will always do my thing. Leave my heart dancing. If you don't like it, don't buy it.
If you don't buy it, don't break it. What must I do? To get on the radio?
I'll message it above but I know to the low. What's on my paints? But I can dance.
Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance. What must I do? To get on the radio? I'll message it above but I know to the low.
What's on my paints? But I can dance. If you don't buy it, don't break it. What must I do?
To get on the radio? I'll message it above but I know to the low. What's on my paints?
But I can dance. Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance. What must I do?
To get on the radio? I'll message it above but I know to the low.
What's on my paints? But I can dance. Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance.
If you don't buy it, don't break it. What must I do? To get on the radio, give me a chance.
If you don't buy it, don't break it. What must I do? To get on the radio?
If you don't buy it, don't break it.
What must I do? To get on the radio? I'll message it above but I know to the low.
What's on my paints? But I can dance. Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance.
To get on the radio? I'll message it above but I know to the low. What's on my paints?
But I can dance. Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance.
Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance. I do it forget about it.
I think I need to give you no chance. Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance.
Alright. Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance.
Please, Mr. Radio, give me a chance. Thanks for sharing your stuff, man.
Potset music, network links and the show notes.
You know, this has been one of the first shows ever, I think, where we haven't had a Senseo moment.
I don't know what's going on. Maybe it was, I had a great dinner last. I marked a cooked.
It was really nice. So, this is like no Senseo stuff going on. No gastronomic intentions.
Okay, I'm looking forward to resting up this weekend. Chillin' out, as I said,
we'll be trying to do a pod save the queen with Christina.
But of course, we'll be back here Monday. We got a whole, another week of stuff that we're
doing here at Pod Show. I'll keep you up to speed on that. My stuff slowly starts to become available.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm so ready and so tired. And you know what, there's a whole, there's about 50
people at the office who are also pretty damn tired and they're working really hard.
Okay, adamacroid.com, dailysourcecode.com is where you can find the feed and the latest episodes.
Have a great weekend, everybody, for 20 C a Monday.
Get this pod cast and more great ones like you on the high performance pod cast, delivery
network from Pod Show and Limelight Networks. I love it.