This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 382
My name is Sam, I live in South Florida and your headphones are backwards.
The elbows on the left side and maybe the elbows on the left side.
I'm not a pilot, so all I can wish you is post-modern blow drives in a giant split.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm coming back
No, he ain't as bad as I am
Just one
There's a door
You name it my head
So he hasn't been like a woman
No, he ain't as bad as I am
Just one
There's a door
You name it my head
So he hasn't been like a woman
No, he ain't as bad as I am
Just one
There's a door
You name it my head
So he hasn't been like a woman
Just one
There's a door
You name it my head
So he hasn't been like a woman
No, he ain't as bad as I am
Just one
There's a door
You name it my head
So he hasn't been like a woman
No, he ain't as bad as I am
Just one
There's a door
You name it my head
So he hasn't been like a woman
There's a door
Start now if you're Monday just right
Some different on the Charlie
Jessica Smith Wright, tip from Steve Webb
We actually told me to check out the English version over Commer
But then I saw that Oliver songs are English and Spanish
So I decided what the hell? Let's do a Spanish song
Man, she's cute too, thanks Steve
Hey everybody, it's Monday, time for a new week of the daily source code
The weather outside today outside the cottage in Guilford
Is exactly what we expected Saturday evening
On our way back from Rotterdam from visiting my mom
We thought we were going to have a thunder storm
It didn't warm up quite enough for that to take place
The morning around
I think Patricia said around five a.m. and so it's really wet today
Lots of traffic and you know because of water
Just because of water, but we needed it
We needed some water here because there's been someone
A water shortage and actually water coming out of the
Out of the tap is quite expensive these days in the UK
Sorry about the cowbell
I just couldn't resist
And Rob doesn't like it at all
Adam has a long time listener just wanted to ask you a favor
Please stop hitting the cowbell while songs are playing
From the song
I like some good old cowbell as much as the next guy
But if the artist wanted cowbell in their song
They would have put it in themselves
Just a comment from a long time listener
Thanks as Rob, yeah, I hear you Rob
But you know, it's
I'm not trying to take away from the song
You can always go listen to the song
And the positive music network is just it feels like
I need some
I got a fever, the only thing that will cure it is more cowbell
I heard and it's pulled from the flesh into a podcast
Just heard your shout out in try these DSC
I've got a drumstick here if you want it
I think to recall it being one of those end of geek thru out drumsticks
You know when the drummers finish playing for the evening
And he chucks all the drumsticks into the crowd
I can't for the life of me remember who from
But given that I was a bit of a headbang of back in the day
There's a good chance it was someone like Black Sabbath
Or Mozart or someone like that
But to be honest I was a bit of a stone and back then
I remember it came from
You know, it's true it really does square up your short term memory
You know?
You know, thanks Adam, thanks for attending DSC, it's good to hear
You've got your cowbell from Mr Nicholson
Hopefully another brick and give you your drumstick
That's about it. Oh, one more thing
Yeah, it really does square up your short term memory
You've got to be careful about that, you know
Cheers mate, take care
Bye bye. Yeah, dude, thank you
I was gonna say something but I forgot
Yeah, actually
I told, so what was that Friday or so I said that
You know the reason why I'm a little bit out of time is because I'm hitting the cowbell
The podcast Paul gave to me gave me a hitting it with a pencil
And I told Patricia that and she said, oh, no, no, hold on
We have something and she went into Christine's room
I love the I don't think the daughter knows yet
And she got her wiser drumstick
This is remember we went to the wiser show
We were invited there by Dan from parking a bit of a square
Bit of a square circle
I've got it all wrong now
Oh, it's the short term memory again
So it actually has the backstage pass wrapped around it
But it's a great drumstick
You can really really really whack it now
So hopefully I'll do a little bit better
Of course the person that really spurn me and spawn me, spurn me
Then encouraged me to continue with the cowbell
Was Beth Thorne Lee who's music I just loved a bit
Of course Mr. Lovely is what we wound up last week with
And that's sent in a comment and her comment really encapsulates part of what I love about pod safe music and about pod casting
Back in the day when I was doing pirate radio in the early 80s late 70s early 80s
You know you played a song because you knew that it would work
It would probably work for your listeners
Of course now it's even better because if it doesn't work for a listener you can just shuttle right through it fast forward
But there was also a relationship
You know we were building up relationships with artists and we were really supporting them because we liked the music
There was no other financial gain in the middle anywhere
Now of course these days on the radio
It's very hard for a
A presenter or a disjockey to
Really get behind a record because they have rotations and playlists
And they're limited by time and that's how commercial radio works
And back in the day we used to have some
Well the relationship we build up with artists could be very special in 80
I'm going to say 81 Madonna came through town through Amsterdam
This was when she was still she had she had joined up with jelly bean beneath us
And so he had of course done I think it produced her record
So that was the record with borderline holiday
Lucky star
You know it was the record and it wasn't till the second time it was released that it actually became a hit
But she came to our decimal radio studios and did hash under glass with us and it was a good time
That was about the extent of the relationship there with Madonna but Beth only understands
That these relationships
Between people who play the songs and
Cherish the songs and share them with their audience and the creator of this art
Well it can go a bit further
Hey Adam this is Beth only
And I think I'm going to have to come over there and kiss you full on the lips
Thank you for playing my tunes
And I'm digging the cowbell
Thank you Beth
Little cowbell for Beth
Yeah
I got to play you some of her slower tunes too
But the rock and stuff I just totally totally dig
Let's keep it with pod save music for a couple seconds here
Because there's always something going on with the UK music scene
One of the folks I met at our draft and darts meet up
Was it two three Sundays ago two Sundays ago now but three Sundays ago
Was our buddy from Burbs
What you're doing for our country is so cool
Hey Adam Barry Burbs here from British underground rock bands
I'm just stopping by to let you know about something quite new and exciting that I've started at Burbs with podcasting
Essentially it's called gig casts and if you go to the gig cast in page at Burbs, Kuk, slash gig cast
You'll find a list of subscriptions to gig lists in different areas of the UK
So the idea is you subscribe to the gig cast of the area that you're in
And every Saturday you'll receive an audio gig list which features snippets of the bands that are playing close to you
So I thought that was quite a neat idea and I just wanted to tell the world about it
And I thought well better way than through my good friend Adam Curry
Keep up the good work mate cheers
Yo mate back at you keep it up
Fantat is for you know the first two times I'll listen to that comment because I have to run through stuff
Because it's not always very descriptive the way it shows up in in my outline or in cast blaster
I thought he said gig cast but as gig cast and I think it is a great idea
Particularly by region and there is such an incredible culture of gigging here in this country
Of people playing anything they can they can literally play and I have talked to Christina once again
And I said look you know I know you're into into sharing music
Why don't we just do a show and she has everything else that up pod saved pod saved the queen
I think that you know she said I don't know what to talk about so just talk about what you know about
She said well I know about couple bands and why don't you just bring up one or two MP3s
It doesn't have to be a long show and if you feel comfortable then we'll do a couple more
So I think we're gonna do that because she is completely completely
Completely keyed into what's going on in underground
It depends in a positive music here in the UK by the way
If you want to call in our voicemail numbers are open in New Jersey 2016256357 in the UK in London
O2076813753 really appreciate what's coming through it's cool
It's cool
It's not the weekend probably about 40 different voicemail comments
Of course I can't use them all I told you with past that point
Unless I just made the show a couple hours long that would be the only way to get to everything
So over the weekend let's see Saturday gone up early went to Farrowks met up with Captain Dan
Got the Delta Sierra started
There was no known on it by the way a note about the diesel airplane that my buddy from Farrowks had put on it
But you know sticking stuff on to we don't really have windshield wipers
You can stick stuff under so I guess someone removed that as they were moving the plane out of the hanger
So first we went to Antwerp because I wanted to have a
Well, you know, it's been what hasn't been 30 hours
I didn't have to come back into my 50 hour until I'd flown 50 hours
So the wind commander could you know do the 50 hours service on it
But of course we'd had that issue with the spark plug
I'd had some issues with starting wasn't a real good cold starter
Which actually turns out to be my fault
I was priming it incorrectly
Oh, and also the last time we were flying around the castle
I don't know if Patricia mentioned this on the show
And I had noticed it inside the cockpit as well
I thought it was making a little bit more noise than normal
Patricia had said you know you're flying around the cat flying around the cottage
It sounded like you had a moped with a hole in your in your exhaust pipe
Traveling out baby is just a soup dub engine
And lo and behold Patricia was right
And William and myself and a whole bunch of people said now that's not possible
It's brand new
Well here's what happened when we were starting
And we were trying to clear out the spark plug member that on our trip around just around Farrow
Just in the neighborhood
And we had a couple of backfires
Well those were apparently powerful enough to blow out some of the
Some of the actual damping stuff inside both exhaust
So I can fly with it fine
It's no problem but it just does make more noise
And it's kind of interesting that Patricia was the one who caught it
Everything else is great not a drop of oil leaking out of this thing
It's it's flying perfect
So then we went off to Rotterdam
To the jet center landed of course Dan stays there
I went to visit with my mom
I could you know even though she was really doing her best
I could tell that Saturday was not a good day
She still has a lot of pain
That's the problem
It's really the pain from whatever is on the inside of her
Pressing against her ribs which of course they
They nuked a couple weeks ago with radiation
When is day we hear from the doctors about her
Most recent lung scan now she's already
She already has one lung that's been removed
And they think they might have seen something on the remaining one
Which of course would be quite a downer
And what the doctor said is look
We probably have something that we can treat it with which is a chemo pill
Which stays pretty pretty much focused on one area
But you have to be stronger just physically stronger
Mentally she's she's there
So she's got to eat you know got to eat more
And she's eaten her appetite is there
Nothing even the pain is not really getting rid of her appetite
But it was just oh man fucking hate it
You can see it you know once it was it was really different from from the week before
And it just was not one of her good days
So we're still fighting this fucker
That's for sure and mentally she's definitely there
And that's what you need
And thank you very much everybody for sending in your thoughts and prayers
It's very much appreciated and I tell my mom about it all the time
And she loves it too
Now here's I don't know if there's really anything
Such as coincidence
You've probably heard of this politician Tim Fortan who was assassinated
Man what was it four years ago?
He was assassinated in the Netherlands just days before the general elections
Where he probably would have swept the elections with his party
And in fact there was a lot of you know he was considered to be the Dutch Le Pen
And which was categorically untrue
And if it just go on Google and look for out you know do search on me and the big lie
I wrote extensively about it at the time
So I was a big fan of this guy
Patricia and I knew him both personally
Because we just met several different times
And I liked a lot of what he was saying
It was definitely something different than anybody else
And it sounded like a guy was going to go kick some ass
And that was exciting
And the whole country was very excited about
The change that was underway
You know finally everyone was sticking the heads up and saying
Yeah, let this guy have a go at it
You know let's screw the man let this new guy come in and be the man
See if we like him
And he was assassinated and
And I think that that really
That the Netherlands lost a tremendous chance for a long, long time
But there's still a lot of people who
Try to carry on his thoughts in politics
And it was a couple weeks ago
When I was at you know I landed at the jet center
And you basically you call ahead and ask them to arrange for taxi
And so I got this cab driver named Core
Which is such a typical Rotterdam name Core
And this is like 65 bald head
You know big fine or supporter
Of course me being from Amsterdam
And Ajax being my team
You know we kind of had a joke about that
But Patricia's from Rotterdam you see
And she is without a doubt the
The queen of that city
And will be for a long, long time
So everyone in Rotterdam loves my wife
Just loves her
So we're chatting away
Like you know this is kind of a guy who's got those taxi air qualities
That's my guy and Amsterdam
You know as a guy who I can you know
I can trust him to do stuff and get stuff
And if he has to get my in laws or whatever
I know that he'll be he'll do it and he'll do a great job
And so I said dude from now on give me your phone number
You're the guy
And he's in local Rotterdam politics as well
As part of what used to be I think
Late by Rotterdam which was
Part of the whole idea of Pimfortan
And then of course the guy with the bald head
Which is the same as Pim had
There's a lot of similarities there
Now I'm not anyone who can can keep a lighter or a pen
Or any you know one of those little things
I lose everything all the time
You know I have one
You for my credit cards my passport my money
I've got you know one girly like bag that I just keep with me
It's kind of like a it's a wallet
But it's a bigger wallet
All it's just missing the strap and it will be a girly hand bag
But everything's in there because I lose shit all the time
But in 2000 or 2001 before he was assassinated Pimfortan
Probably 2001 gave me a pen just nothing special
It's a plastic ballpoint pen
But it was of his political party lifestyle Pimfortan
And I had not been able to lose this thing
We've been through three moves
Amsterdam Belgium to the to the cottage
And at all times of the day
I'd like open up my jacket
Oh there's the damn Pimpan again
And I and I would tell Patricia this and we laugh about it
You know just once every couple of weeks or sometimes months
Oh there's the Pimpan again
And so I was coming I was late a little
I was a little late leaving my mom
He of course he was there to pick me up and he waited 15-20 minutes
And then we're in the car
And and I said stop at the ATM because I got to get some euros
Because I always you know like payment euros obviously
It's not that easy to get euros in Britain
And I said I hope you know mine that I'm a little bit late today
You know it being Saturday and all
I guess sometimes he takes at least one day a week off
He said now it's okay I only have something tonight at 730
So what is it? Well it's the it's the remembrance ceremony for Pim
Because 6th May 2001 he was assassinated
Was it 2002? I'm sorry
He was assassinated
And so that was four years ago
Today and we were talking about that and of course I remember the day well
It was a huge media coverage and it actually happened
The assassination took place right outside of radio studio
Where he just finished up a show with a body of mine
Who I was doing a show without the time I wasn't there
But I was I was close enough to it to get a lot of the inside stuff
And I've been on that parking lot a million times in my life
And so we're chatting about that and I and I get out to go to the ATM
And I opened up my girly bag and I get my card which by the way was refused
Because I thought it was suspicious all of sudden money was being taken out of an ATM in Holland
So I had to get another card but in the girly bag is the Pim for time pen
Don't ask me how it got there and I said this cannot be coincidence
You know this is it I said core due it's not much
It's but I just I and so I told him this whole story about the pan about how I and I gave it to him
So I don't know why but I have a feeling this is supposed to go to you and and it just
Something about that moment that just told me that there maybe there is no coincidence
Maybe there is stuff coming from up above who knows
And then we flew back and it was as usual quite enjoyable
Oh, I have to say though for this this is for the second time running
UK immigration has been awaiting me and we came in even after hours like a quarter of seven or seven p.m.
Which we can do because we're on base just fill out a form
We do without control tower and everything and there was the same young woman waiting for me
And she had said you know the previous time said look you've got all these stamps in your passport
You come in the country all the time but if you're married to a European then it's no problem
You can you can get a visa and you can come here and you can stay here and you can live here and you can work here and do whatever you want
And I said okay I'll do that
And so there she was again
I said look we can't go on meeting like this and she didn't laugh
So I knew that she was a little more serious this time
And I said look the situation hasn't changed and here's why and I want you guys out there
Maybe you can help me with this
So the first thing I'm actually going to be able to take care of the problem is we can't prove that
Well we can prove that we're married to each other
But we have to have an up or steal an up or steal is kind of like a wax seal that proves that the document in this
Case or wedding certificate is real and that it's official
The problem is you have to go get that in person and it has to be the two of you and even worse than that
We actually have to get a new a copy of our certificate because we have the outdated form we've been married so long
And the guy who married us dead
So we're going to do that
I think the with the 22nd or 23rd when we're in New York
Patricia's going with me and then of course we're going to San Francisco so it's going to be fun
We're going to be on a little tour together
But what I what I'm really looking for is I'm sure that it's not as simple as just getting my European
Family visa or whatever because it looks like you know with all things going the way the R
We will open up an office a pod show office in London
What I really need is an immigration lawyer and it's not you know
I don't really need the advice. I just need someone to do this stuff for me because I'm busy and lazy
And stuff like that. I hate doing it. So if anyone out there hasn't you know just it's got to be a company that'll do that for me and
And give me any advice I need I mean everything's all on the up and up. I'm a decent citizen
I pay my taxes you know no issues there, but just whatever it is forms are calling or stamps. Please
I'd love it if someone could could help me out with that
So you can just say anyone you know my way a daily source code.com
You know actually I was
Ah
I was going to give a shout out to the guy who turned me on to Captain Dan and I had saved the piece of paper
Now of course Patricia moved it once again. Maybe I moved it into my bag
I'll get that for tomorrow show. You're checking us out on serious stars 102
Well, you're in luck because at 9 o'clock tonight eastern time we've got DVD weekly
It's a fantastic podcast followed by CC Chapman who will take you up until 10 p.m.
On the way after the show Pacific Coast. Hellway used radio Don Andrew and Gilmore daily
I'll be back tomorrow as we continue our entire week here on the daily source code with your feedback
In my crap. Oh, that's a slogan for you. All right, everybody see tomorrow on the satellite that is and for those of you here
Well, you get to hear about partsmith.
I had a message Steve. Just a listening to your review on Joan Cohen
Just a little bit of geography and British history.
Hortmouth is a city. It has a cathedral. There's only one city in England
Which doesn't have a cathedral. That's your Christmas weekend. Which one is it?
He got the good work right show by for now.
Yeah, I appreciate it. And I was thinking all this weekend. I think it's got to be something obvious
Like a gilford or maybe even more obvious like London, but I think London has a cathedral
So you kill me dude. I got to know what is it. Please. Let me know what it is.
I had to encourage this issue a story.
Okay, Stuart Wolf on second life.
Just for make a little suggestion about the new Charlie Rewond
The only I enjoyed it, but the only problem was it lasted only 29 minutes.
And I don't think that was enough time to share the whole of all the big things of a week.
So my suggestion is to have it about 45 minutes so it can hopefully cover more of the subjects of week.
Here's the cool thing about that, Stuart. I didn't put that.
Excuse me, my microphone is a little bit crappy.
There we go. I didn't put that together. I think it was it's got Taylor who did that.
Now I made a mistake on my thinking on this because I said if you want to put together a best of all
I'll be happy to put it on the feed over the weekend.
And so I got the one from Scott and I put it up.
And then promptly I saw this morning that I'd received another one as well.
So I didn't of course figure that there might be multiple people putting these together.
So I'm happy to put multiple ones and actually I'm going to move it to a separate feed.
That makes a lot more sense.
Give me your feedback on that if you think I'm wrong.
And I'm happy to put up as many best of us as people make.
So let's just experiment with that a little bit.
It's kind of out of my hands, but I did listen to the one that Scott made.
And as I said, I'm completely sick of listening to myself talking about second life.
Hi, Adam. This is David.
I'm here in sunny Southern California.
To entertain mid dot com behind the leddy mic.
He is my podcast that comes out over two weeks.
I'm a mobile district here in the L.A.
And I'm probably the only district in the fantasy area with a podcast.
So there's a one sticker for me.
So I'll just listen to BCS 380.
Oh my gosh.
You are absolutely right when it comes to doing your stuff.
And actually not worrying about it.
It's a show with actually perfect.
It comes up so much better.
I got it.
ABC Adam, the guy told you that you couldn't play a cowboy to say your ass.
That's what he told you.
But that is so true.
Keep in coming out.
It sounds great.
And the bomb line is he doesn't have to be the perfect show.
Our cast class doesn't have to run perfect.
As long as the show is continuing,
you keep worrying, joining it.
And the continued is the laugh.
And like you say, this call like me say,
that's what the show is all about.
Good luck, Adam.
And I'll catch you later.
Tunes at attainment.com.
Thanks, dude.
And I really appreciated what you said there.
And a lot of people sent me email similar to that saying,
you know, it looked.
Don't let any topic overtake anything.
And overtake the show because that's just no good for anybody.
But pretty much everyone who sent in an email or a comment said,
you know, I listened to this source code because you have different things.
And there are different places.
And you do different things.
Different setups, different types of recordings.
But also different topics.
And some people fast forward through the Metro moment or Trinity.
And I've got those cute up for this week,
by the way, as well.
I've got some good ones for you.
And last week I was, I put a shout out and said,
hey, how about hypnotism?
Can we hypnotize someone through a podcast?
And I got some good feedback on that.
Mark Dond gave me a quote from the
part of a world English dictionary, which is copyright 1989 by the Microsoft Corporation.
Here it is.
The word is automaton.
A machine that contains its own power source and can perform a complicated series of actions,
including responses to external stimuli without human intervention or two.
Somebody who resembles a machine by obeying instructions automatically,
performing repetitive actions or showing no emotion.
I don't think that's what I'm talking about.
In fact, I'd probably want to program you to have an emotion.
Like laughter.
That would be the good one, wouldn't it?
Michael Dean says, hey, I'm no expert in psychology,
but I heard about and have tried brain wave therapy.
Apparently a person could be influenced by a series of tones
at a certain frequency to change moods.
Our bodies function because of electrons.
Also states of mind like alertness, depression,
sexation are supposedly controlled by what frequency those electronic signals are passed through the brain.
So in theory, we can deliberately program or steer our state of mind in whatever direction we're willing to let it go.
Much like being hypnotized, the key is, as it is with anything,
you have to truly be willing to allow yourself to do that.
So there's this software I came across that has samples of these tones that you listen to with ear buds that will do this.
Some of them are sort of like sessions of therapy and some are to heal headaches.
It was all very interesting to me.
Okay, so he has a link here. Let me just pop this link for a second.
Let me see if I can, oh, no, he didn't, that's not a link.
That's a link to his email.
Oh, that's why I put, of course.
Well, Michael, you didn't give me the link, dude.
Please send me the link.
Now I want to check out these tones and see if we can alter states of mind through the daily source code.
Send me the link, please.
Ed Ross says, dude, I'm not sure that attempting hypnotism on a podcast is such a good idea.
Consider those who drive or fly while listening.
Okay, they could try to turn the podcast off till they're in a safe place.
But what if they really want to listen to it?
Yeah, there's something to it.
Hi, Ed, this is David. I'm here.
Sorry about that.
Operator error.
Hey, Ed, this is at the zero from the area 51 group.
I'm just listening to the Charlie number 381 today.
And you've been talking a lot lately about mind programming, science.
Scientology, psychology.
And it made me think about a book I just read called The Game by Neil Strauss.
And this book is a real life documentary about how a bunch of nerds use the internet and something called
Neural Inglistic Programming.
In order to become really successful with beautiful women.
These are the internet is sort of a debugging tool.
They would try things and then report on their values on success.
The Neural Inglistic Programming is a real legitimate science invented in the 1970s by
Psychologist and a computer programmer.
It's totally worth checking out the game as far as I'm concerned.
It's the best introduction to Neural Inglistic Programming.
And it's really entertaining.
I couldn't put the book down.
I know you like it.
So give it a shot that book is the game by Neil Strauss.
Talk to you later.
Yeah, Matt.
And I appreciate you talking about a book on the podcast because we don't do that enough.
And we really do need to read.
That is important.
And I try to read a book on the plane these days just to just to keep up and just to keep the
mind going on different types of verbal or visual input really.
Yeah, I've read the game.
I've also listened to all of Anthony Robbins tapes.
So I'm quite familiar with NLP or Neural Inglistic Programming.
In fact, Senseo, the Senseo and the Burp is a textbook example of Neural Inglistic Programming.
It's worked on.
Well, let me just say conservatively tens of thousands of daily source code listeners.
It's carried over to my house.
My daughter does it.
And even though Patricia will never, ever, ever cop to the fact that she burps out loud,
she does it.
And there's always it.
Senseo coming from the other room.
So it does work.
I'm just interested in at these tones.
That seems like the stuff that Dean sent me.
That will be very cool to see if we can do more.
Because it's all kind of simplistic stuff.
But yeah, the NLP definitely works.
And if you've got any more thoughts about books or stuff, send it in for sure.
Our voice mail lines again in New Jersey, 201, 625, 6357 or in London,
O207, 68137, 5353.
As said, Patricia and I go to New York.
Ron and I are speaking on a panel as well.
One session I think at the Bear Stearns Financial Who Block Conference, which will be fun.
Then we're going to go to see the 24th of 25th is a retreat.
It's called the CEO retreat.
I think it's all of the CEOs.
And I guess even though Ron's a CEO, and I'm just a lowly president, I'm allowed to go.
Our one of our lead investors, Kleiner Perkins, puts that on once a year.
And it's held at Pebble Beach.
So we're going to go.
And I think they got some good speakers there.
Charlie Rose is going to speak.
There's some fantastic woman who is going to be giving a speech.
I think holding a seminar which actually Patricia wants to check out.
And of course it's golfing, which we won't do because we don't want to embarrass ourselves.
We might hit the driving range.
I'm sure Ron will be more than happy to help us out a little bit if we have some time.
And we should have time.
Then it's either two San Francisco or back to San Francisco.
We'll stay through the weekend.
I think we'll probably stay through Monday.
And then we'll come home.
And then I'll probably do a week and a half turn around and come right back out.
Because I've got to be back in the San Francisco office really for a couple of weeks at a time.
Because we're so close now.
In fact, over the weekend, I fired up the dashboard and it's working.
It's working.
I've now, I no longer use iTunes.
Unless I want to put something onto my iPod, all I have to do is fire up iTunes.
It knows what shows I want, how I want to categorize.
The playlists are all the same as they are in the dashboard.
And it just sticks it right under my iPod in exact duplication of what I'm getting online.
But I'm loving it.
I am totally loving it.
Now, of course, this is bringing stuff down in real time.
So it's a little different.
But the experience with broadband is exactly what it should be.
And there's more stuff we could do while we're out in San Francisco.
Hello, Adam.
It's Ranger Craig.
I'm the lock.
I'll catch my eyes island.
Hey, you're going to be in town sometimes since he's come out and see me.
Finally, went to go daddy and register, Ranger Craig.com, although I don't have a page to do with it yet.
So just temporarily, we're directing it to my scrapper page before I decide what I'm doing.
We're still helping to start some podcasts here from the rock.
And that's a lot of things I've just opened to talk to you when you're about when you're in town.
So I'm looking up when you're here in the city, Baghdad by the Bay San Francisco.
We'll see you soon.
Bye-bye.
Baghdad by the Bay?
All right, Ranger Craig.
We want to come, definitely.
So if you're there on the weekend, count us in.
The last time I checked, we don't have a whole lot of songs to feature the cowbell.
Hey, daily source code listeners.
This is Kevin Crossman from the Frappac Tributes podcast.
You know, there aren't a lot of podcasts at feature the cowbell either.
Except for, of course, the Charlie.
On our podcast, we cover all those guys in this comedy movies like Ben Stiller, Vince Fawn,
The Wilson Brothers, and yes, Will Ferrell.
So we're a big fan of cowbells too.
Adam must be a big fan of the Frappac because he's been playing clips from dodgeball when
he crashes and recent shows.
And if you want to catch up with all the news on the summer movies coming out from the Frappac,
you definitely want to check out the Frappac Tributes podcast.
Just go to frappacpodcast.com.
Come on, do it. Lay on right here, do it.
Do it.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
Where are flink?
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers.
We believe your personal information should be just that personal.
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe.
Where are flink?
Make this smart choice.
Visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
Hi, Adam.
This is Valerie in Toronto.
DescriptionTO.blogspot.com.
That's where my podcast is.
And I have an audio comment about this virtual reality thing.
You've gotten into that the wives don't seem to understand.
I'm thinking, maybe you could have a segment on second life like you do for Trinity or
the heterosexual moment, Metro sexual moment.
That's not a weird.
You know, the other regular segments you have.
So it's not like you're talking about it every day.
Driving some people nuts.
But you could compartmentalize it and have it every once in a while
to kind of update people on how your business thing is going there.
Any events that might be coming up you're involved in.
Or just the issues that come up in second life.
Because I just joined up because you mentioned it.
And I'm some sort of slave.
I don't know.
But it sounded interesting.
And I'm not really a game RPG even chat person.
But I've been in it for about two, three days.
Well, on and off.
And it's really interesting and it brings up a lot of interesting issues.
And I've had a really great time and met some really great people.
And I think it's worth talking about.
But yeah, the potential is there to get a little too.
Obsessed with talking about it because it's so immersive.
And yeah, that can drive people nuts who don't get it.
But if you can put into some sort of packages, sort of update people like me,
who are sort of starting on it and sort of get it.
And you've got stuff with really great potential that you could have going there.
And I know you're working on that to just kind of put it in a little place there.
And then see where it goes from there.
So that's my suggestion.
I hope you think about it. You've got to be thinking about it for as much as this is.
You've been thinking about second life in general lately.
So making consideration and try that out maybe.
And thank you so much.
As usual for the ideas you put into my head for me to try out.
It's your great amazing source of information.
I think that's part of what the source code's about.
So thanks again and take care and I'll be listening.
Please.
No, thank you.
Peace back at you.
Nice voice, by the way.
Like that.
Well, you did a good job, I would say.
Did a good job right there.
Yeah, it's just the, I think I got a little over-obsessed with talking about it.
That's all.
It's definitely not all of my day.
You know, in fact, there's a very small portion.
But a fun portion.
And sometimes exhausting portion.
While you were talking, Patricia came in.
She's so fantastic.
I'm holding here the most beautifully made BLT.
And I think BLT is the same in the UK as it is in the States.
Bacon lettuce tomato, tomato.
Oh, it's so good.
But she didn't have time to talk.
So I'll try and get her on tomorrow.
There are more people doing interesting things in second life though.
Comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip.
Here he is.
Hiya, I'm Carrie.
Guess whom I have met in person in second life yesterday?
It was Jeff Smith, who is making theme songs for Pat Castas for reasonable money.
We were chatting about making theme songs for me.
And he mentioned that.
His little daughter is running around the house and singing comic strip,
blogger, comic strip, blogger, theme song.
Wow, that's scary, don't you think?
So speaking of second life, Adam,
make it please meet Roger Smalls up.
You both live in fucking gulfot.
And he is now sad and bitter because he has no credit card to join second life.
So please meet him in R.L.
known as real life and cheer him up.
You?
Yeah, I've sent an email to Roger.
I've not heard back from him.
I hope he's okay.
It's very unlike him to be silent all this while.
So let's just hope that he's okay.
I don't think he was going on holiday.
I mean, I just don't know.
I really don't know.
But it's been weeks now since we've heard from him.
So I'm a bit concerned.
Maybe it's some problem with the draft and darts thing,
because he said he couldn't make that.
And that also didn't seem very Roger like.
Maybe he was there after all.
Maybe he'd actually met me and thought what a dick.
I don't want to send anything to him.
But your influence reaches far and wide comic strip blogger
because this is what I received this morning from the Jeff Smith.
Dude, look at this stuff.
Second life, man.
What is all this stuff?
Is that a pig?
It's that stupid, all that crazy stuff.
On my phone.
Second life.
It's that stupid, all that crazy stuff.
On my phone.
Second life.
What is all this stuff?
Ow!
Watch out.
Can you hear me?
Can you learn how to fly?
See you all night.
Come on, man.
No guns and running.
I like the castle is closed.
I'm out of here.
It's crazy.
No, you are crazy.
I think that's a Jeff's artistic way of saying,
man, I kind of got interested and sucked into that second life thing.
Yeah, like big fro.
That was pretty cool.
So just a quick update on what's going on.
I've gotten most of the land I wanted around the castle.
So now I can actually move the castle onto two parcels,
which will enable me to put down more cool stuff for us to play with.
And also having an area we can throw down anything you want.
And I can clean it up later.
Most of the stuff now auto returns after 15 minutes.
And check out the beach if you haven't, by the way.
We've got some cool places to lay down.
Yeah, that's fun.
Now, what's really cool is we're going to be organizing some events.
And in, well, I think it should start in the next couple of weeks.
And already met someone who potentially could organize some events for us.
Of course, I'm thinking pod save music.
Meet the meet a podcaster.
I'm even thinking fashion shows actually.
And that's going to take place at the palace.
And that's coming along quite well.
But something that's more interesting.
So how happy someone picked up on this is really that we have been working towards
this type of metaphor for a long, long time, even in our vocabulary.
Maybe not really with us noticing it.
Hey Adam, this is Jeff from National Tennessee.
I was just calling to make a comment.
One year.
What year's talking about how we go to websites and how we go to places.
Well, that kind of thing.
It's fun.
Interesting.
How people don't associate themselves with the way they live anymore.
But more, you know, I'm Jeff from yummybones.com or, you know, associate ourselves with
our websites now instead of the places we live.
I thought that was kind of interesting.
And I figured you're going to take on it.
All right.
Nice again.
Dude.
I'm so there with you.
I even thought about that.
You used to say, it all depends.
You know, it's really what label you hang on yourself.
You used to be.
I'm Adam from Jersey.
Now it might be.
I'm Adam from Pod Show.
Or I'm Adam from the Daily Source Code or Adam at curry.com.
You're so right.
And we're from there.
We're going to places when we go to website.
That's how we talk.
I'm going to CNN.
I'm going to the BBC website.
Like I'm walking over there.
You know, you're clicking.
And I'm from fill in the blank.
So I think in our minds, we've all, you know, really pick up a copy of Snow Crash.
You really should.
You know, and maybe I think somewhere I have the audio book.
I told you have the unabridged version, which is like seven hours long.
Maybe I'll get a snippet from that.
It's a fantastic book.
You really got to read that.
And now we're from our sponsor.
It's the Yanks versus the Brits.
We'll drive each other crazy.
But everybody knows that it's apparent to see.
They're just like you and me.
It's the Yanks and the Brits.
The Yanks versus the Brits.
Mind the gap.
Yes, please.
So even though I still have a whole bunch of them stacked up, including a great one from PWB,
which is going to be moved again.
PWB to tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
I'm just running out of time.
We're already at 46 minutes.
I still have one song.
I want to play for you today.
This was about the flyer I got in the mail about the water butt.
And I'm not necessarily interested in a water butt.
And a water butt pump.
Well, of course, I knew there had to be a logical explanation for it.
I had them water butt.
Yes, very interesting.
Well, it's interesting because over here we don't use the word butt, really.
We use the word bum, which you mean,
which you Americans know means something entirely different.
So it's all very confusing.
But water butt over here is just something you collect,
rainwater in.
What's it called in America?
So yeah, we collect rainwater as it comes off the roof and down the down pipe in a water butt.
And I guess a water butt pump would be able to pump it out of there onto the garden.
So for me, it doesn't sound like anything is very funny,
but I can understand why it's funny to Americans.
But there you go. That's what it is.
Thanks a lot. Bye bye.
No, thank you.
Thank you. You're so right. It's a butt versus a bum.
Right arm.
And it just goes to show that how confusing it all can really be.
Definitely.
Although looking at the size of some of the butts in the United States,
I think they've been filling up with rainwater too.
Okay.
Well, I had something written down.
Shoot, there was one more thing I was going to say.
I can't remember.
Other than that, Patricia and I are off to look at a house this afternoon.
We were scheduled around 2.30, so I've got about two hours, two hours to run.
And it's right near the center of town, yet it's kind of secluded on a hill.
I mean, it could be the next curry dwelling.
We're very excited about it.
Another reason by the way, why I need some help with my immigration papers to get it all set up
and square it away. I don't want to get any trouble trying to purchase this place.
If it turns out to be what we really want.
And just one more thing on the Yangtze versus the Brits,
I have noticed, I will say,
when you use British slang,
that that does make people happy.
And so it's not saying tomato.
In fact, if you say tomato versus tomato,
or podcast versus podcast,
they're probably good annoyed.
But if you say, oh, man, the bill was waiting for me,
the bill meeting the cops,
or something similar, that's when they all take notes of, hey,
this guy's paying attention.
Just an observation, a slight one.
But when he might be interested in it,
a Iraqi regime could launch a biological or chemical attack
in his little is 45 minutes.
I love this song.
Reminds me of Paul Hardcastle's 19.
Want some soul?
Without any question,
45 minutes.
Lies, spin and true.
Five minutes.
Now, 45 minutes.
Still trying to,
45 minutes.
Stiff, stiff,
Trying to, trying to, trying 45 minutes.
Still trying to,
45 minutes.
Technical Rood 45 minutes.
By logical,
45 minutes.
You.
Cl Took the40.
45 minutes.
For the 45 minutes.
Before the 45 minutes.
According to the British guy,
write.
Ahh.
Well hello everyone, I have to accept
Right, I have to accept
40, 40, 40, 40, 45 minutes
I have to accept
That we haven't found them
45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes
45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45 minutes, 45
25 minutes, 30 minutes, Americans stay in the
45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. 45
minutes. 45 minutes. 45 minutes. It's finished. responds. It's finished. 15 minutes. Is it finished? 11 minutes. Let's make no sound. Congratulations to the producers, an amulet with sound. When you press play button, I see you in !! dzamp a !! funz !! espacio ,  how much I play. 12 reps. 60 seconds. 10 seconds . 72. 600 seconds. 13 seconds. 20 seconds. 200 seconds. 21 seconds
I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road, I'm
going to go to the other side of the road, I'm going to go to the other side of the road.
You know I would change the title from lie spin and truth the 45 minutes.
It's called 45 minutes, this could be a huge hit in the clubs and let me just underlying
why I think that it's possible, I'm playing this, I'm playing this in my computer this
morning as I'm doing my show, Patricia walks in and says what's that, and you know when
she walks in and says what's that?
It's got something going for it.
She can predict these things.
Fantastic.
Quantum Soul from the UK.
Form in 2002 after years of jamming and producing
with a friend of mine started making beats in my computer
at University and Leeds hooked up with some pretty
talented musicians up there and got producing all sorts
of different sounds when pushing the vibes
since then and now looking to get out there.
Welcome to the Pods Haven Music Network.
Quantum Soul, Fantastic.
Schlink, of course, to everything.
Music wise that we play in the chat.
Yeah, you can find that music.podge.com.
Of course, you can look at the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
or at curry.com for the ongoing conversation.
And this is just the start.
So lots more good stuff coming this week.
On the daily source code.
Thank you very much for staying subscribed.
Portions, of course, brought to you
by Akibu Contact lenses, who underwrite download
with the Heather and Janelle download.acview.com, ACU, VUE.
And if you want to look for a great deal on a domain name,
only $6.95, if on checkout, you use the promotional code
DSC3, Delta Sierra Charlie 3.
All right, I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Come on, I'll be by Cass Lester.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Bye bye, everybody.
Another pod show pod guest, stick it in your ear.
Get this pod guest and more great ones like it
on the high performance pod cast of Liberty Network
from Podjo and Lime White Networks.
I love it.