For the first time ever, the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr. in one action-packed DVD collection,
own all 27 episodes, the cult hit, including all new interviews with Carlton Koo.
First thing that Brisco did that impressed us was, we're not only to come in and really read the dialogue well as an actor,
but he also did a standing flip in our office.
You've flipped too for Brisco County!
If you like the kind of TV you can't get on TV, get your copy of the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr.
Available now on DVD!
And the darkness key calm night.
And God saw everything that he had made and behold, it was good.
And God created man, and man created machine, and machine, machine created music.
And machine saw everything you had made and said, behold.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
The day is starting to look out into a brand new morning, and everybody smiles.
They do.
The one we do, they take your hand, they tell you that they understand it's true.
When you listen, when I tell you, do we know right?
Do we know, okay?
When the world comes out to greet you, do we know right?
How we show you place, where you can walk in the sun, I will show you a place, where you can be what you want,
I will show you a place where you love, count it free, I will show you a place, so come on, go there with me,
cause you do we know right?
Do we know, okay?
When the world comes out to greet you, do we know right?
When the world comes out to greet you, do we know, okay?
Oh man, wish I had my cowbell here.
I'm so ready.
Oops.
As you can tell, definitely in the portable set-up load.
Is this better?
Yeah, there we go.
Originally from New Zealand, and now build as from France.
She's from France, everybody.
Okay, that's when he grows, doing all right from the pod save music network.
Boy, this sounds like crap today.
As you can hear, definitely still having some health issues in New York City.
That's where the daily source code is coming to you from.
I realize it kind of sounds like I'm talking out of my ass.
I'm not quite sure what I can do to fix that.
Let's see if we can change a little bit here.
I've got the pod set up, so I need just a little more output home.
Let me try that.
Okay, that's a little bit better there.
Yeah, sitting here in the Grammarcy Park Hotel had a great early morning.
A great early started, five o'clock, of course.
I woke up, wide awake, saying, what the hell,
Hold on, that's the blackberry.
I think I, I think I definitely have an infection.
Even when I laugh, you can just hear all this flim is just sitting there ready to crush out all over you.
So two days in New York, it's a big advertising agency going not just agencies,
but also advertisers directly speaking on a panel tomorrow here at the OMD conference.
And it's really been fantastic.
We started this morning, early with a meeting with Jennifer and Chef Mark,
Chef Mark East Coast, regarding the culinary podcast network.
Very excited about stuff we can do with them.
And boy, there's some entrepreneurs there, let me tell you.
And I just been trying to keep myself kind of low-key, trying to keep my guts together
because even when I laugh, you can hear what happens, right?
It just all starts to come up.
I really miss Patricia.
She would make me better in half a day.
I know she would.
I just, I, anyway.
It's the beginning of a new week.
And this is Daily Source Code episode 479.
A lot of interesting stuff to work through today,
because you guys have been really doing my work for me, helping me out with the two main conversations.
Nothing on North Korea today.
Do you have some grammatical stuff to talk about?
Grammar, specifically.
And more on Corey Lydle, because I was waiting,
but finally we got one of our aviation buffs to check in,
who was actually flown the East Corridor,
so we'll be hearing from Robin from Inside Works in a couple minutes.
And of course, the typical other stuff that drops into the email box
to the voice mail box.
I had a time in tune here.
I wanted to let you know.
I found out whether I'm a folder or a scruncher.
I went along to the folder or scruncher.com website that you recommended.
And it didn't tell me anything at all about how to figure out which I am.
But I did do.
I went on to wikipedia.org and there's an entry there called Toilet to Paper.
And it tells you whether you're a folder or a scruncher.
And I can't believe these scrunchers, what they do.
I mean, how on earth do they think that, well, oh my goodness.
Anyway, yeah, so anybody wants to find out which they are,
then go along to wikipedia.org and have a look at Toilet Paper.
And Adam, I hope you weren't too offended by that video impression thing.
I did a view.
I really looking forward to the launch of the BT Pot Show,
Pot Show in the UK.
So how is that going, by the way?
Okay, thanks Adam.
And folder.
Yeah.
Another one.
Another one joins the ranks of folders.
Yeah, BT Pot Show going very well.
Looks like we're going to be opening up the doors first or second week of November.
As we get closer to this specific data, let you know.
It's going, it's, I've already seen what it looks like, of course, on the inside.
And it looks fantastic.
Here, I think you're really going to dig it.
I mean, it's, is it that different from Pot Show.com?
No, of course not.
It's all part of the same system, but it is specifically marketed for the UK.
The choices on the homepage for the UK.
And along with this launch, we're also going to be releasing or unleashing new features for
Pot Show.com in general for Pot Show plus new, new design stuff.
There's all kinds of things coming.
If I can just get my health back, then it will be fantastic.
You're always really interesting.
I've done 11 exercises now with Amy Mack.
And I didn't realize this.
But a lot of people actually think that Amy Mack is there with me in the studio or in the cottage
when we do those exercises.
Of course, the full intention be to get my ass back in shape.
And then the one time we actually do something that is set up.
So it sounds like Amy actually entered the curry condo the other day.
Now everyone's saying that that was fake.
Yeah, duh.
Please, you really thought that she was there at 6.30 in the morning?
Yeah.
Some ex-gives from Newcastle UK.
Oh, okay, everyone.
Amy Mack was so, obviously, not bad, but that was terrible.
He's an active person.
Put anywhere there, you go anywhere there.
Anyway, let me get some cool going quickly for my show at theboardjordy.proxual.com.
I've got 13 listeners in a minute.
And it's really good music.
Great stuff.
There's a mix of everything.
Get yourself an input.
Go on.
Quickly.
Actions.
Go on.
Yeah, I wonder, you know, how much of that you did not understand if you're listening
to this and your U.S. citizen and living in America?
I really noticed that, and some people actually picked up on that.
They say, hey, you know, when you're in America, you're your accent changes.
And you obviously, you know, when I'm totally assimilated into the UK culture, when
I'm in the cottage.
But I really have no problem understanding that.
And I know sometimes I'll be laughing about stuff.
And I can see a look around the room.
And I look at U.S.
Potshow colleagues.
And I can just see the puzzlement on their, the wilderness on their faces.
Because you really have to focus into it and really have to tune into to listen.
You know, as they say, it's, uh,
two, what is it?
Two countries divided by common language.
I think that's where it is.
Well, you know that, of course, is the whole premise for now.
We're from our spine.
Yeah, exactly.
It's the X versus the Brits.
Well, the Bible.
We'll drive each other crazy.
But everybody knows that it's apparent to see.
Let's just like you and me.
It's the X and the Brits.
Yeah.
The X versus the Brits.
Mind the gap.
So not that this is really a yanks versus the Brits.
But, you know, I did promise myself.
I was going to work a lot more on using my vocabulary and expressing myself with my American accent.
Much more in the fashion that the residents of the UK do.
And in order to do that, I have to have my language skills.
My grammar has to be kind of correct because this is the proper queens English.
Or is it the kings English?
And a question arose about the use of me or I in a sentence.
Boy, we got a lot of people out there who are pretty angled about language.
Hey, Adam.
This is Paul Barry from the window to the magic.com podcast.
And I was just listening to BFC number 477, where you were talking about the Karla and me.
Karla and I.
And you said you were always taught that it was always in certain name and I.
The way that I was taught that was that if you remove the other person, it should make sense.
So if you say Karla and me went to the store, that would not be correct.
Because if you took away Karla and you would not say me went to the store.
But if you said, I went to the store and you know, and Johnny ran into Karla and me,
that would be correct because Johnny ran into me.
You wouldn't say Johnny ran into I.
So, you know, maybe that that will be an easy way for you to remember.
Just take away the extra person and say it again in your head.
And if it makes sense, then that that would be the way you want to go with it.
I'm not 100% sure that that's right, but that's how I was taught.
So hope it helps and keep up the good work.
Thank you.
Yeah, remember when when we first moved to the States and Patricia, of course,
speaks fantastic English.
She really wanted to do much much better for her own, you know,
she felt that she wasn't up to where she wanted to be in communicating in the English language.
And so I would speak English with her exclusively.
And we'd go through these things to say, well, why is it like this?
Why do you say it that way?
And you know what all I could say is, I don't know, it just feels right.
That's the way I was taught and it kind of just feels right.
There's so many exceptions to every rule.
So I'm sure this will be a debate or a conversation that continues for quite a while.
By the way, do you know what actually people are in New York or talking about?
And are talking about sponsoring?
It's really cool.
I'm a sponsor.
We actually have multiple brands competing over the sponsorship of folder scruncher.
And we're coming out.
I can't even tell you what's how cool this is going to be.
We're coming out with something interesting because this is a worldwide phenomenon.
It was even on the Gilmore gang.
If you haven't heard it, the five episodes that are titled Friday the 13th gang.
I was that was recorded on Friday the 13th last Friday and released on Sunday.
I've got to listen to this show.
I think it was one of the most entertaining Gilmore gangs ever ever recorded.
The very little content about industry industry issues, as it pertains to web 2.0 and
Office is dead and all the other interesting stuff that they discuss on the Gilmore gang.
But man, when you put Jason Calcana and myself together, would it be Jason and I?
Yes, Jason Calcana and I together.
There's a very significant Laurel and Hardy effect that takes place.
And actually, I should find that for you.
I should let you hear when Jason Calcana does an impression.
His Adam Curry impression is so impeccable.
It is so right on.
You got to listen to it.
Gilmore gang.podshow.com.
So finally, I got the feedback I was looking for.
Out of all the news reports, all the in-depth analysis,
all the NTSB stuff.
Finally, we have a pilot who has been up the East River New York corridor in a light aircraft.
I had the pictures to prove it because Robin from inside works.
Actually, I just found these on my desk just the other day before we left for New York.
Beautiful, beautiful pictures of him flying.
When the twin towers were still there, flying a tail dragger around the statue of liberty.
So he has clearly done this route.
And what you're about to hear is really the best explanation that I've heard yet of what happened.
And it appears to be just a very, very, very unfortunate accident due to more than likely lack of experience
in flying in this particular bit of airspace, which is very tricky.
And as with everything, you know, it doesn't take much to trip up and to have a whole bunch of things go wrong
all at one time.
The one piece that I'm still not clear on is they were so many reports of a distress call regarding fuel,
which I believe now is just not true because I've not heard this confirmed by NTSB.
I did go on the NTSB website and there is a preliminary report.
There was no report whatsoever of distress call going out.
So you can just see how poorly the media works.
And by the way, I've made several analyses of this accident myself,
and which I believe turned out to be pretty much, well, in essence correct,
but I just did not have enough facts.
As I've said, over and over again, I really don't have all the facts.
And I've never flown in that particular bit of airspace,
but I think Robin can really lay it down for us.
And we'll have a listen.
Hey, I'm Mrs. Robin from InsightWorks and TheDivaCast.com.
Two things come to mind about the Cory crash in New York City.
First off, I really want to give our condolences to the family of Cory and the flight instructor.
But the two things I want to say, I flew into New York, which is just west of New York City.
That day, just a couple hours after the crash,
I have to say it was a really blustery day about time we got there.
So I expect earlier, in the time of the crash,
as it's been described, you know, overcast skies,
winds out of the east is probably a very blustery day,
because by the time I got there, it was a heavy rain, nasty, nasty weather.
Second point is, I have flown in those VFR quarters that you've talked about.
I've flown in my airlines antique 1931 Curtis Wright travel air,
and we took off out of JFK. We flew up the Hudson across the central park
and then down the east river.
Just through that exact same area where Cory was.
We've been talking to a LaGuardia tower,
and I have to say they're not always the friendlyest folks,
as you might expect in New York where it's always so busy in the airspace.
So I can imagine flying up the east river talking to LaGuardia.
You have clouds above you, winds from the east, city to the left,
LaGuardia airspace to the north and to the east.
You're getting close to the point where you look where you're going to let
us continue further north up the east river,
and then LaGuardia says, no, serious.
We're not going to let you come in here.
Stay clear of our airspace.
Well, what are you going to do?
And I'm going to turn east towards the airport.
You're going to turn west towards the city.
And if you're in that VFR quarter,
you're probably favoring the right side,
as we do here in the stage five and in a car.
It's not like you in England.
But you're going to favor the right side of the river,
and so you're naturally going to turn left towards the center of the river,
and make a left hand turn to head back south down the river.
Well, if you have a tailwind, like you were talking about,
what's it going to do?
It's going to push you right towards the city.
There are inclinations going to be a pull harder,
and I think that may be what actually happened.
They had a larger turning radius than they expected,
pulled a little bit harder,
and maybe got into a stall spend situation.
So that's my gut feel as to what may have happened.
I hate to play, you know,
the Monday quarterback in the whole situation,
and again, my best wishes and thoughts
to the families of all those involved.
There's Robin again,
he used to call you from the cockpit on my way in the 757 or 757.
Home today, but out tomorrow.
So long, older.
All right, Robin.
Thank you so much, dude.
So hearing that really puts a whole new perspective
on what took place there.
And quite honestly, I think, you know,
from what I've read,
there's now been a decision to close the east corridor
for fixed wing VFR traffic,
so small.
Well, that's the only type of traffic
that they can really get in there,
VFR to be quite honest.
So they're going to close that up.
And in this case,
maybe the right decision would have been to veer left
if at all possible,
who knows what is going on.
And then maybe still turn east into the wind,
because I believe there was quite a crosswind component there.
I think there was, you know, 15 knots
in order to be able to make the turn,
probably would have been a little bit easier to make the tight turn
if they hung it to the east instead of to the west.
It is very, very unfortunate.
And I think it is good to discuss these things, actually,
because this is how we keep other people alive.
And I'm a big believer in going over accidents
and understanding what went wrong,
and obviously trying not to get into the same situation myself.
All right, you know what?
I'm just going to wind this show up with the request,
actually, that came in through the email.
Hello, Adam.
It's Martin, H.K.A.D. from G.D.
by its size bonus.
Not wanting to steal your official news ecologists from there.
But I thought, so I'd come on for a Friday
and recommend a song for you.
Well, at least a band.
And the band is called Superkicks.
They've just uploaded a couple of tracks
for the pot-said music network.
I think they're going really well on Fuba.
I've been promoting them on my podcast last day
to nine months.
Absolutely terrific band, full of energy.
And what's even better,
from your Nicola Woods in Suri,
so go on, give them a play.
Superkicks on the Charlie on Fuba Friday.
Alright, one more thing.
I hope you feel better soon.
One thing is, it's not Friday, but who cares?
We can do a football any day we like.
Now you're gone, I'll need you now.
If I could only show you now,
if I don't get thrown away.
Come on and make me.
If they give up big shot,
but you're not.
You say you can take me.
Knock it take y'all,
and shit you got.
What is it better?
Why is it better?
To me now,
y'all, y'all,
I need you now.
If I could only show you now,
if I don't get thrown away.
Come and run and run and away.
Run and run and run and away.
Never come back,
because it won't be the same again.
Come on and make you and me.
Try to refuse me,
you want to say again.
Come and get me with me.
I'm not gonna fall for that again.
Why is it better?
Why does it matter?
Why does it matter to me now?
Here we go.
What is it better to me now?
Now y'all, y'all,
I need you now.
If I could only show you now,
if I don't get thrown away.
When y'all, y'all,
I see the light,
the million pounds of naked bright,
but y'all,
we have another day.
Run and run and run and away.
Run and run and away.
Super kicks,
get blown away.
Winding up this episode of the Daily Source Code,
coming to you from New York City,
apologies again for the sound quality,
but it's the mobile setup.
Was either there so using the wireless mic,
so I'm gonna wrap it up.
Also, if you check out that Gilmore gang episode,
I was talking about,
it was so interesting.
We got into a conversation about pod shows advertising platform,
and how we basically, how we make money.
And I said,
you know, our advertising becomes content.
And I didn't even have to reference the Splendor campaign.
Oh, excuse me.
God, I feel like shit.
I didn't even have to reference the Splendor campaign.
I think by the end of the show,
which is about an hour and a half,
I would not be exaggerating if I counted
the use of the word Splendor 50 times.
Unbelievable.
How good this stuff is working.
And you guys just keep this campaign going.
There's so much you have to say about this product.
It's really phenomenal.
So we'll do more of that tomorrow.
And, well, of course,
daily sourcecode.com is the website where you can go get all the show notes.
And Adam at podshow.com is where you can send me all your love and poetry.
So take care, everybody.
I will talk to you tomorrow.
Bye from New York.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast
delivery network from podshow and line-white networks.
I love it.