For the first time ever, the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr. in one action-packed DVD collection,
own all 27 episodes, the cult hit, including all new interviews with Carlton Koo.
First thing that Brisco did that impressed us was, we're not only to come in and really read the dialogue well as an actor,
but he also did a standing flip in our office.
You've flipped too for Brisco County!
If you like the kind of TV you can't get on TV, get your copy of the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr.
Available now on DVD.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass, and the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Walk over to the window sill, because that's where I first kiss you babe.
But don't think of me not being around.
Just listen for the sweet sweet sound of the taxi pool and off the driveway.
I'm coming home soon.
I love it when you're fall asleep, but arms numb and I can't feel them.
But to wake you up would be a shame.
That's how I remember you, stuck here on the Red House special.
I can't wait to see you again.
Don't think of me not being around.
Just listen for the sweet sweet sound of the taxi pool and off the driveway.
I'm coming home soon.
No, I don't want to make you cry.
No, there's no need for you to feel blue.
Because you don't see my reflection in your eyes.
I don't know that every time I know, it's never goodbye.
I'm trying to seek stays.
I'm coming home, till then I'm just a phone call.
Going out for you.
I'm just a phone call.
Go out for me.
I'm coming home, so
I do the day, day, day, day, day, day
If you're off on business, you're away from home, then I'll pitch you that song
Hit the perfect spot, didn't it?
Adam, what all bands?
Coming home soon, taking off episode
477 of the Charlie, Delhi source code
Coming to you from San Francisco, California, it's going to be another beautiful day
And no cow, and I feel like shit
Oh man, I haven't been this sick in a long, long time
And so when I play a song like that, of course you can find it in the pod
Same music now, works like, ah, you know what I need right now?
I need some Patricia chicken soup
Ah, long time listeners will know that Patricia's chicken soup with ginger
is the only thing that really helps against this
It's just been shit, shit, shit
I hate it, I hate it when my body lets me down
Everybody how you doing, it's damn early here in San Francisco
But another full day ahead, please
Anyone who's hearing this at the office
Remind me, I've got to go to black market magic
I've got to go pay for the equipment that I so far been borrowing
It's like, like every single day this week
It's been like, oh, what time is it?
Oh shit, it's a quarter to eight
I don't think it's open anymore, I gotta go during lunch
Ah, lots of things to talk about today
Some rather big news stories
And some small news stories
But there is an important story that we're following right now
Which of course is the continuing theory of folders versus scrunchers
I've discovered that I as a lifelong, lifelong folder
Actually scrunch toilet paper
When I blow my nose and it seems that we're on to something here
Yeah, I'm Jeff Smith, I think you're on to something
I am a scruncher, but when I blow my nose, I fold it up
And a nice little square
Hmm, oh, interesting
I'm telling you there's something there, there's a correlation
Wait, that's Jeff Smith, the Jeff Smith from...
So, all I had to do of course was ask you guys
If we had any proof that North Korea had really lit up a nuke
If there was any seismic activity
And immediately messages started coming in
I got to actually post it yesterday on korea.com
I posted a link to a map that shows a 4.2
On the Richter scale of seismic activity in North Korea
Interestingly enough, the report is at surface level
So it wasn't apparently a deep explosion
But more people have been after this data
Hey, and this is young, I'm just posting to your daily source code
From, well, today and I can't just leave the game
I'm on a plot right now, just end all of it
Well, anyway, the nuke in North Korea was 3.5, 4.5
On the Richter scale, I've heard both
They said it wasn't very big, or as big as the North Koreans wanted
It's the big, or that's what they say
But the missiles is true, they're over-exaggerating that
But I've been reading that North Korea has quite a few submarines
They have, say, you could bring them into the cargo
Or they could fly them in their planes
They're just, thanks to worry about why South Korea could fly in with their planes
So just, they're having it as a bad thing
Well, anybody having a nuke is kind of a bad thing
But just because they don't have a missile or a proper missile that can make California
They could just take it right into the bay
All right, pleasant thoughts, bye
And voter as I said yesterday
Bye, thanks
All right, this still doesn't, you know, it's not that I don't want to believe it
Couldn't a large variety of explosive devices
Created 4.2 on the Richter scale
You know, how do we know that it wasn't actually a nuke that was lit up
And is this the only sides of nuke they can make?
You know, there's all kinds of things to consider there
Now, I'll say right up front
That my uncle Don who, you know, I'm missing him again on this trip
But he has told me quite clearly, he says they're nuts in North Korea
Kim, Kim Yang Il
Is absolutely nuts
So if they had a nuke, yeah, he would probably use it
But it could, you know, look at this guy
He's totally, he's all image, you know, look at his hair
Look at his posture, look at his clothes
You know, his clothes really say
Hey, I'm the most important dude in the room
The glasses, the logger-filled glasses
He could be a very brilliant strategist in that regard
And I'm just wondering, I don't know anything about nuke
I don't know anything about nuclear fission
Or fusion
Simon Test does who's in the UK Simon
You're the expert on nuclear stuff
Once you dial in
And give me the opinion on this stuff
Okay
Because so far, yeah, there was a seismic activity
4.2 in the Richter scale
That doesn't seem like a huge deal
I mean, it depends on where it takes place
But just from my recent recollection of actual earthquakes
4.2 doesn't seem like it's like it's some huge deal
If you've got any information on that, you know what to call
1.2.1.6.2.5.6.3.5.7.
1.1.2.1.6.5.6.7.
1.2.1.6.6.7.
This week on the Big Break Music Podcast
You can hear the music and our interview
With Podsafe Music Artist Lisa Dames
As we explore her album, no one like me
Because it could have been me
The phone that's green or my face
On the cover of the magazine
Here, Lisa Dames as she reveals
The intimate and emotional story behind her songs
And then we went up into the studio
And he played it for me on the piano
And I just started crying
It's so hard to sing the song because I have to hold back so much
Because if I don't hold back, I will start crying
As I'm singing that song
And we get a behind-the-scenes look
Into the making of her chart climbing single
Just another day
And we get to hear about the fun times as well
In time we get it, we just get a little bit right here
And a little bit right here
Here
So check it out by going to
The Big Break Podcast.com
Or search for the Big Break in iTunes
Big Break Podcast and Lisa Dames
Oh, check this one out everybody
I mean we might as well stay in the country vibes
Since we're doing
We're going to a sad life repair man
Coming after you
Sad life repair man
What's he gonna do?
He'll fit your misconceptions
And answer questions too
Turn nothing in the universe
And he can't do for you
Sad life repair man
Yeah
Everybody
That's not like I have anything from PW to play for you
But yeah, you go from one country promo
Just about this North Korean thing again
The only reason I'm bringing it up
Is because it was not that long ago
That we were led to believe that Iraq had weapons of mass destruction
Capability
Capabilities
And I quite distinctly remember
Areal photographs showing
Possible launch sites, build sites, vials
Of anthrax
Remember that
G
So, you know, I'm just saying
It's like okay, we've got all these
You know, all these pictures of
Of ill walking around
Looking from mighty important
Of course, it's all file footage
Of rockets launching an air
And we've got a statement from them
Which is new
We've got nukes
North Korean
But I presume it's exactly what he said
And we have some seismic activity
That to me does not prove it's a nuk
But, you know, okay
I don't know what it takes to make nukes
Let's see what they're saying over in
In blighty about the deal
Hello Adam Lee from UK yet
While you're off in America then
I thought I'd just tell you something
I was really guardians of day
The 10th to the 10th to the 6th
And it's the the moment North Korea became a nuclear player
And on the front page
There was a huge fire in the grass
Extract
It's certainly nice
A seismograph in the geoscience Australia
Identifies North Korean nuclear threats
About the US medical survey
It's a magnitude 4.2 seismic event
So, if you really get on the Guardian website
I'm sure we'll be off a look at the picture
And I'm quite a bit sure
It's quite a
Physmal spike at the time
When North Korea said it's designated
And it's matched it as well
But there you go
If not I am
If we'd be locked on to the US
A logical server website that has it on there
Maybe the geoscience Australia
South America, I think British geographical
And even also pick it up as well
But it won't be as strong
Because anyway
That's about all these moments
I don't I'm now at university here in Cardiff
So no longer in Birmingham
I'm now in Wales
Oh
Cardiff
Where my girlfriend Charlotte Church lives
Have you ever seen the Charlotte Church show?
If you live in the UK?
It's interesting because she's competing partially
With Jonathan Ross, the big Friday night talk show
Which has been gone going for years
Which is also a fantastic show
I love the Jonathan Ross show
But this Charlotte Church show
It starts half hour before
Before Jonathan Ross and since that's on channel 4 I believe
She's nuts
Charlotte Church was the child prodigy
Who sang classic opera
When she was I think 12 or 13
Really took the world by storm
And she's turned into quite a media celebrity in the UK
And she's funny
She's funny and deering the shows
Kind of a mess
But there's something about it
That I really like
When the show came out people really slagged her off
And she does it from Cardiff
She says it's from Cardiff
Which is where she's from
I think it's a studio in London
But that's okay
A little bit of media hype is all right
I mean yeah
If North Korea has the capability to do a media hype
I wouldn't start a church
I
Yes
And I love it when you guys correct me on my grammar
Adam I got to correct you
You were talking
Playing a call from
Either Mary and Carla
Karen and whatever our name was
And you corrected her grammatical
You think she should have said
Carla and I
But did you a wrong?
She had a right
It was Carla and me
The sense of something like
I'm at the bunch of people at the podcast
Text bell including me and Carla
Why she has this correct you a wrong dude
It's not the first time you made that mistake
She only correct you
Well dude are you so sure dude
All right
I know that someone out there who's going to go back and listen to yesterday's episode
And see if I was right or wrong
I've always been taught it's
And I
Not and me and I think that's I think she said Carla and me not me and Carla
And I believe it's it would be Carla and I
Of course
It being Carla and I or Karen and I
It's all just a pipe dream
But a girl can dream right you know what I'm saying
Yeah
Long time
She heard about the crash
And then hadn't yesterday
Pitch for New York and I think it's quite a lot
I don't remember some trouble
I guess and wound up
Session to a apartment complex on the upper west side
So we'll be interested to hear your thoughts on that
I'm definitely pretty far behind
So we're also looking forward to hearing
You really thoughts on
Before we get to that
Let's let's pause here for a second with Corey Lidal
Because the same thing really
You know
Ever since I heard this yesterday afternoon
We were at the office
And it was a little unclear it was going on of course
You know for a brief moment there is shock waves
I go you know spread throughout the country and throughout the world
The first thing everyone thought is oh my gosh, you know another plane into a building
And every single news reporter would say
Five years on one month to the date
Because of course it was on the 11 so they had some kind of hook there
Some kind of tie in
But it was a very unfortunate accident
And when I heard this when I heard a small craft crashing into a
Into a building you know I immediately think wow
You know this is there's something very wrong
In fact I was like I'd be leave suicide before
I believe that a freak accent like that happened
And I started to amass the information
Very very hard to get any valuable information
On this particular story from mainstream news
And again, it just goes to show that when you actually know something about a topic
How piss poor just piss poor
The news media is at reporting
Now they get some things right like fire
We could see that you know
The level of floor of the apartment that the fire is on you know that stuff
I saw Bloomberg report that the CR20 aircraft was a 15 seat passenger plane
You know it's like no it's not it's a four-seater
Okay, so
And there was actually there was one I think it was on
I don't know if it was on Larry King. It was I think it was definitely CNN at one point
A former executive for the National Aviation Transportation Board
The NATB
Came on and this was clearly a guy who had
Researched a couple of facts and I must have been an airman because he did have some great information
So let me start by saying
Here's the information that I've collected that I believe to be
You know some of the facts. First of all Corey Lidal
Was a pilot who had 400 hours of experience
Any experience pilot will tell you that there is definitely a spike in accidents
Pilate error based accidents when pilots have between three and 400 hours
That is just about the time where you're feeling very comfortable
In fact they had a couple of
Guys really horrible and they've flown along with him in his previous aircraft
I guess a system 172 probably for some TV special or something that he did or some profile of him
And you hear him saying you know how comfortable he feels in the air
And that's exactly
The issue with these three to 400 hour pilots and and this has been told to me many many times when I reached
About 253 hundred hours the wind commander my instructor said dude
This is where you really got a fucking watch your shit because now you think you got it all down
You know what you're doing and something really fucking crazy can happen
So let's just put that right up front and
And I think that is actually provable by statistics that once you get to the three four hundred hours
Is a private pilot that's where really normally shit can happen
And it's purely a confidence issue so it's all about pilot error
Okay, what else did we learn?
We learned from from this guy from the NATB or formerly of the NATB that there was a cloud ceiling of 1500 feet
But in the the Eastern corridor of New York in order to fly there under the configuration that light
I was flying the type of aircraft
The type of license he has flying under visual flying rules visual flight rules
He was apparently at 1100 feet now 1100 feet is okay. It's not really high. You know it really isn't it's about 300 meters
So if you have an engine failure you're going to be on the ground relatively quickly
It's it's just a fact of you know a physics
So he was coming from north to south going down the east side of Manhattan
Manhattan
There was again according to the NATB former executive there was a rather strong wind from the east
So if you're flying along the Eastern corridor of Manhattan and the wind is coming from the east and it's relatively strong
If you have if you're under full powered flight and your engine is working
You actually will not be your your aircraft will not be pointed straight on a north to south track
You'll actually be pointing into the wind is very much like sailing
Where's you don't notice this when you're flying in a commercial airliner
You really don't notice it in any aircraft unless you're up front but you're actually flying sideways
And that's because the wind is pushing you
You know in the opposite direction of which the wind is coming
So if you have an engine failure
You know you're going to have to think about
You know what am I going to do because the wind is obviously going to become a more powerful force as you have less power
And you still have inertia and momentum
So you know if you turn into the wind you're going to slow down significantly
If you turn away from the wind
With the wind to the back you know you obviously powered or not powered you're going to be you know flying faster
And you're going to be going towards Manhattan
So from some of the some of the eye witness accounts
Some people said they thought it was a helicopter which is kind of weird now
You know a serious SR20 can look like a helicopter so I can understand where they're coming from
But others were saying that it looked like was kind of out of control like it was dipping left and right
And then there's a unconfirmed report of a made a about a either fuel starvation or
Something wrong with the fuel system
So when I put this all together
Oh and by the way visibility was eight or nine miles that was what was reported is eight or nine miles
So mind you only a 400 feet under the cloud cover it could easily have been a little bit hazy
You know these reports I've had lots of eight to nine mile clear visibility reports and you get up there
And you're like yeah it's more kind of like four you know that just happens
So that's all we know from the ground reporting or the terminal area forecast
So here's oh and then the final piece of information which is really really critical
Crap I don't know if I'm going to get this whole story and for you serious stars one or two listeners I really hope I do
Shit it's a good story
Apparently Corey also had his instructor on board
Now you'd think that would make it a very very safe situation
Well that really depends on the instructor and I have to say you know having been flying with the a safety pilot or instructor for a
Well for most of my flying actually I love having someone on the right hand seat even though I'm doing all the work
You know when situations occur and instructor will typically let you deal with the situation and maybe jump in and do something
If necessary now when it comes to an emergency
Particular something where the engine may fail a lot of the instrumentation
For solving that issue is on the left-hand side of the aircraft. It's it's in the pilot seat. That's where the ignition key is
That's where the fuel pipe. Oh in the series SR20 the fuel pump may actually be located in the middle on the middle console
Ask shit. Hey serious guys gals daily source code.com
If you want to hear the rest of my theory about Corey light. Oh, sorry about that windows closed and p-dub shut me out can't help anything
All right, we're still here, right
So a lot of that of the controls and instrumentation for engine management are on the pilot seats
So I'm just going to go into just assume that the pilot
Corey light on this case was sitting left seat and had most of the controls so
Here's what I believe may have happened and and the whole theory
gets more believable with the visibility
With knowing more about visibility and the actual strength of the wind coming from the east, but here's what I think could have happened
They're flying along
And they're going north to south and there's this eastern Lee strong, eastern Lee wind and the engine quits and I guess they determine that it is because
Either their tank or tanks are empty
But what they essentially try I believe is by rocking the wings back and forth banking
You know some significant banking which could give an out of control look
They may have actually been trying to have fuel spill over from either of the tanks to get into the ignition into the car
Rator into the ignition
I'm not completely 100% down on how the serious fuel flow system works
I'm sure that the fuel pump is necessary
I don't think it's a gravity-based system since it's a low wing
So they were probably trying to
Get the engine restarted and get some fuel flow and you know back in by rocking the wings
Now while this is taking place while you're doing this rocking the wings remember that the wind if strong enough is really pushing
The aircraft towards Manhattan now I've only seen some
Some flight paths that you know look like it might have been this particular aircraft flight path
They may actually done a 360 and no matter which way they turn that 360
If they're trying to rock the wings and trying to restart this stuff and you're to eleven hundred feet
And you're you're descending
You're going to be on the ground in just a couple minutes as no two ways about it
And I believe what happened here is the instructor made a bad decision
The instructor probably said you know, and if he were flying a left seat and he was in total control
It may have had a different outcome and this is again, it's just a theory, you know, and no one has to blame this is just how shit goes
I believe the instructor probably said dude, let's try and restart this thing
Rock the wings
Let's see if we can get some fuel flowing
They're probably doing this while
Turning
Out of the wind because you know when when you have an emergency like that you don't want to turn into the wind immediately
You want to get the best glide so you can stay in the air the longest so you have the long you know the most
Opportunity to find a place to land and guess what there is only one answer in this case there's only one place in fact
I believe when this happened
They should have immediately said, okay, we're going into the river there's no two ways about it
We're going into the river and you know you can try your restarts on your way down into the river
But what probably happened is they're trying to get their best glide they're drifting towards Manhattan
They're rocking the wings they may have both had heads down looking at the fuel pump looking at gauges trying to start some stuff
You go into another turn you've lost track of how far the wind push you you look up and you crash into the fucking building
I think that is exactly what happened and it's it's horrible and it's and there's no reason that it had to happen
It's just one of these things where all these elements come together at the wrong time and it's it's horrific
And it's bad for aviation it's it's bad for for people who were involved in this and lost lives and and property etc
But it really just sucks
Particularly because this type of aircraft and this is I think then I don't know how many of these seerses have crashed
But this is the only general aviation aircraft that I know of that has a ballistic parachute
And I'm not a big fan of that because you know essentially there's a there's a red handle in the roof
And if you run into trouble you pull that handle an actual you know rocket
Explode and blast off with a parachute which can help the aircraft float down to the ground
Don't for one single minute think that that is in dangerous or that you're you know you have a 100% chance of survivability because you do not
You know you're probably going to wreck the airframe you could harm yourself particularly your back, you know
The seats are designed to to withstand a certain amount of G forces upon impact
But you could you know still be seriously messed up, but the chances of survival are pretty good
I personally I don't think an aircraft manufacturer that supplies aircraft with a parachute says a lot about you know what they think of their product
And it's a and it's a very popular aircraft the SR20 and the SR22
And these guys never deployed it and again, I think that's because there was an instructor onboard and you know when you deploy the shoot you're kissing the plane goodbye
You know, yeah, it may be salvageable, but
The shoot was not deployed these shoots have been deployed I think nine times so far with varying results
Some people walk away some people have been pretty seriously injured despite deploying the parachute
And I think it's just a whole bunch of unfortunate events that occurred all at the same time and I truly believe that that's what happened
And I know there's a lot of pilots and aviators who listen to the daily source code, so wouldn't mind hearing from you guys what you think about it
You know, I'm going to stop the show now. I'm so bummed out about that I really am and I'm feeling like shit and I got to work to do
Hey, tomorrow will be football Friday. I promise you that I'll take lots of night quill tonight and I'll have all kinds of
Tylenol and and caffeine for tomorrow morning so we can really kick off the the weekend with a rock and fucked up beyond our repair daily source code
So send in your pod safe music tunes
Well, this stuff you want to recommend. I'm sure that the official music colleges of the Charlie Josie Todd will be checking in as well
One song that I left for you today. This is you know, I love the shakes with Liberty Jones and what pops up on the pod safe music network is a new version of it
And of course, you know, I love this stuff about, you know, pod safe music because you can release whatever you want whatever you want and it's a whole new version of the song
In this case, it's say duet with the or a yeah, to the shakes and featuring lady A
That's all I know about her and of course the song is titled Liberty Jones
Have a little little tea Jones
Was in the shop that she
Lissons to music like Spain
Well, there's no customers
Just because she don't ride to drive
Takes a sea a star of high
Depth is a thought outside
To the river and night
Liberty, you're so free
Why don't you come for me?
Tell me your way from the last days
Liberty, you're so fine
I wish that you or my
We can go back back to my place
Liberty, you're so free
Why don't you come for me?
Tell me your way from the last days
Liberty, you're so free
She's got a claim in her life
And as the name wouldn't fly
We don't sell all the design
Liberty, you're so free
Why don't you come for me?
Tell me your way from the last days
Liberty, you're so fine
I wish that you or my we can go back to my place
Liberty, you're so free
Why don't you come for me?
Tell me your way from the last days
Liberty, you're so free
I wish that you or my we can go back to my place
trimming ceremony
Liberty, you're so free
course links to both songs played on today's show in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Show was brought to you part by Splenda. I'm actually considering giving these guys some of their
money back because you guys listening are so excited about Splenda. I had no idea this seems to
be an entire culture of mixing these flavors together to come up with new exotic taste for
your coffee. So Splenda is a sugar substitute. It comes in the yellow packets and it comes in
was it French vanilla, hazelnut and one other one. It's only three flavors I think it is.
So a lot of you have been sending me emails about what you mix it with to get that perfect
taste of coffee to come up with new blends. Send me that stuff in audio. This is great. This is the
advertising does it just makes itself once again I love it. I'm more information about Splenda
at dailysourcecode.com in the show notes you can go check it out. Tomorrow was a sad food bar Friday
we're going to have some fun hopefully I'll be a little bit more together and I just did want to say
obviously thoughts and prayers go out to all of those involved in the Corey Lightle incident
and crap man look what's happened in the world that's just a little thing you know we're all
look at how consumed I am with that and what's happening in Iraq and around the world
and soon Korea North Korea Iran what is going on what was me
Dr. Namara another pod show podcast stick it in your ear
get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network
from pod show and limelight networks. I love it