Think Advertising sucks.
Think you can do better?
Pod Show and EarthLink are willing to put our money where your mouth is.
Listen to this podcast or go to adchelens.podshow.com to see how you can win big
in the EarthLink make advertising better challenge.
Delta Sierra Charlie 402
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, anyway, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, yeah, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, safety, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, eh, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, this never happens to feel so guilty.
Feel so guilty
You're just the pilot
Of the world and the rush
This crazy life we live in is all a part of the way
Oh
She's under self attack
Can't do this, can't do that
Or she might lose her precious hands
Watch her figure, watch her blade
Clean out that empty blade
Girl you know that ain't the way to live
Time for social intervention
Listen girl, pay close attention
Hey, hey, seriously, you can't let your head down
You ain't done nothing bad and nothing feels so guilty
You're just the pilot
Of the world and rush
This crazy life we live in is all a part of the way
Oh
You ain't never gonna praise them
No, but you don't have to worry about that thing
You don't need them
Hey, hey, seriously, you can let your head down
You ain't done nothing bad and nothing feels so guilty
You're just the pilot
Of the world and the rush
This crazy life we live in is all a part of the way
Crazy life we live in is all a part of the way
Oh
I don't care what you said
That's a Friday song
Absolutely
Laura Clap, hey, hey sister from the podcast music network
Kicking off the Friday show of the daily source code
Or should we just call it by its proper name
Mr. Curry
No, the lady and the tramp
No, I'm saying ha, Mr. Curry
How are you?
Thank you, Mrs. Curry
I was saying that's the name of our show now
The lady and the tramp
Is that right?
Lady and a friend
I'm a friend
I'm not a friend
No, what do you mean?
So I was in London this morning
And I was going between text messages with a p-dub in Florida
And figuring everything out in us in the Patricia
I think they call you or send you a text message
Can you make the show?
No, he didn't send
I see now I got one without any
Recognization
Oh, yeah
And then what you would typically ask me
How come people with unknown numbers?
Yeah, it was you then
It's the network then
And then you called me
Man, you are loud
Oh, I'm not in my ear
But you know what? I'm looking at you
I'm looking at you
I'm wearing your headphones
Would you like your headphones
I chose in in San Francisco
Yes, but they're so good
That I just naturally
Yeah, would you like the headphones?
No, it's okay
So it's Friday afternoon
It is a beautiful day in the UK
Yeah
It is the sun is shining
What is that?
It's close to eight degrees
You know what? I just said to Christina
When we went to the town center
Center for a while
I said, you know what?
This country is so beautiful
Even with lousy weather
It's still very stunning
And juicy and beautiful when you look at it
And very green
But when the sunshine
Then it's even better
It's so beautiful
Because that's exactly the first thing I was going to talk about
Is how fantastic
And how happy everybody is
Yeah, and the English people love it
And what they do
They take off a lot of clothes
Yes, they do
And let me tell you, in London it's
Boob heaven baby
It's like just wall the wall
Tids
Oh, I don't like toast
Well, the toast are coming out
And they have shorts on
You know?
Wow, I mean some awesome breasts
They are very thankful when this weather is so
It's funny because Christina said the same thing in her show
You know, we are now like the van
The van trap family
The van trap family of podcasting
She said the same thing
You can tell it's when it's summer
Everyone starts whipping off the clothes
Laying the grass and flashing their
Pasty white flesh towards satellites in outer space
Oh, they enjoy it so much
That's why they're having so much fun
When they're going on vacation
To Spain and to Tenerife
Oh boy, oh boy
Do they ever
Lends a lot of it
So it's been pretty much a week of
Pod Show UK stuff
I've been in London twice
And it's been on the phone and back and forth
And it's been a great week
I'm so incredibly happy
With
Just the people that we've met
The connections you're making
The advertising community very excited
This morning we were at a
You mentioned that they work so differently from American people
You noticed when they come into the meeting
Showing their boobs first of all, which is kind of
You're like a flashing
Honestly, it's not so far
Not flashing but
So we had this meeting
In the city as we say
Canary Warf
And there's really only one huge advertising agency there
And you had like senior partners and stuff
And it was just a three of us
Chris Daniel Winner who's a
You know managing director here in UK
You haven't even met him yet
I heard you like him
And typical agency people
Kind of wacky and creative
And the senior partner came in had like an iPod hanging around
His neck and stuff
It was very
He moved around a lot
Bouncing around
And it was a bit hyper
You know there's a cute blonde girl who came in
And she had only a t-shirt on
And it was a little cold in the room
And it was like immediately it was like
Nipples
And of course, you're like, look straight in the eye
I'm going to look straight in her eye
I'm not going to look straight in her eye
I was like, oh my goodness
So that's how it feels
And it pulls in now
You're used to it
But it's a weird thing
It's nipples always
Always interesting
Always appealing
Nobody had a great meaning
It was very cool
And thank you everybody so incredibly much for
Telling me how to get there
Yesterday on the show I said, what's the fastest way to get from
Waterloo Station to
Well the Jubilee line of course
Eastbound?
You did?
It didn't even take a taxi
Are you nuts that would have taken an hour and a half
Now Canary Warf is like all the way on the east side
On the ground
Okay
Yeah and it was great
It was 15 now it was actually a little bit about 20 minutes
It was fantastic
And I was quite proud of myself
As a London traveler
To be honest, yeah
And do you remember I told you this meeting came together
Because of a Greek listener
Yeah, he told us
So he was there
He came in
Yeah, he apparently
Of course
And the first question they always ask is what's her name?
Well it's a very Greek name pie
No, of course not
I mean that's what they always ask
What do you have to say?
Patricia
Patricia Anglaya
That's a Greek part
Because also
Like a
Patrioti
Yeah
No, what's a Patrioti
Patrioti is somebody who lives in the same country
Or comes from the same country
So
That's Captain Dan
Okay, for tomorrow
Well I hope everything's still on for tomorrow
Yeah
That's why check my mom is coming home from the hospital tomorrow morning
Oh
Yeah
So we're right on time
Just about right on time
Because we'll be there probably probably an hour after she does
So that's good
Very happy
She's out of the hospital
Patricia's going flying with us tomorrow
Yes
How excited are you?
I
I'm sorry
I like the flying
But if it's that long
It makes me very tired
The homing
It's an hour of 15 minutes
Uh-huh
Well you know
It's an hour of 15 minutes of homing
You don't like the homing?
What do you mean the homing?
Homing in my...
Yeah
Excuse me
Is the same feeling of you
Remember we have to
If you sit on a washing machine
Yeah
Exactly
Yes, that's it
But also remember we had a little boat
We went to the canal
Through the canal
And after a while you got so sleepy
From you know from the sound and the water
And everything
And it's a bit the same
Well we'll try not to fall asleep
While we're...
I always do you know
I know you're in the back
Like drooling
Yeah
See you guys captain Dan calling
On the other line
Oh
Yeah, well I'll have to call him back
And maybe your daughter is picking up
For this thing
Don't count on it
Oh, no she picked up
She picked up
She will come in
Yeah, let me just play this comment for a second
Hi Adam
This is Ed Stofel of FlyingReports.com
Speaking of pilots
Here's another pilot car
It's a blog and you convince me
I need audio content
So I'm working on the branding
To get up and running with a podcast there
But I do have a question for you
Does podcasting
Will podcasting
Okay
For my flying habit
Will support my flying habit
That's what I want to know
Whenever you go flying
It's the equivalent of burning money in the air
So
No nothing
Nothing will support your flying habit
I also wanted to respond to
One of the other callers
Who said
He didn't favor Patricia being on the show
And here's my own analysis of that
I think Patricia has a mellowing influence
On you
Maybe on the listeners too
So you're a bit more edgy when she isn't there
But mellowing is a good thing
So
You do whatever you want to do
Guy
And thanks a lot for the show
I'm going to continue to listen
And tell one's body
Tell one's body
What a man
Tell one's
Don't you love pilots
Don't pilot your sound great in general
Oh they do
Yeah
They do
And you know it's so important when you're in a plane
And you hear the captain's voice
And the voice sounds so good
You know so
Trustful
Uh-huh
And you think oh I'm good hands
I can't hear that
God what a man
I do remember once when I was very young
And we were in a
What's up
You don't have the immigration form for the flight
Tomorrow and you meant to have it
Twenty-four hours before
I sent it in yesterday
They said they don't have it
He talks so slow
So what did you do I need to call him back?
I don't know he says you have the form
And you know what to do
Oh okay well I sent it
I said facts that yesterday
The fact
I was like roll it up
Roll it up
Okay
I did do the immigration
But I guess sometimes
It's facts
I got it
I'll do it
It's facts technology man
Aviation is still based on facts
So how come they didn't receive it
I don't know
It's like maybe they have one phone line
At the tower where you send this off
And I guess sometimes a downloading porn at night
On the computer
The facts is don't come through
I don't know
It is
So yeah
I'm mellow you out a little bit
I guess so
It's true
I'm leaving Tuesday
Honeybun
I know
Are you going to miss your boyfriend
I'm saying that because all the men
Don't worry
Roger Smalls will be here
You can count on it
He's going to show up with his brand new phone
And podcast from behind the trash bins
So what you got?
Anything?
Well I went out with Christina
She wants to come with me
And
Because
Wow did you call the newspaper?
Well
Always when she needs something
Of course
And I said what do you need
Need bigger bras
Yeah yeah yeah
Finally
Yeah
So they love that
They love to
To buy bigger bras
So that was a
That was a great day
And
And we went to the doctors this morning with her
Because she gained a little bit of weight
From the pill
Because the kids
Especially that age
Do you realize that this will shock several many people?
No I think these
You know I
I'm a very
Sexy baby
No mother mom
And you're a milk
Sexy too
I hope so
And my daughter is very sexy
And she looks very beautiful
And men think she's older
Oh yeah
And though she had also some problems with her skin
And so
Talks about it with my sister
And she said well
You know Roxy
Her daughter
And was actually
Not sexual active
But she needed
Also somehow with some
With the hormones
And everything
With the hudders
Is that really
I mean is that
No no no no no no
For the hudders
But for skin
Skin
Especially
There is a big problem for them
The estrogen
Estrogen
More amount
Thing racing through their bodies
And it's not
It doesn't have a good effect on their skin
So we were talking about it
My sister
And me
And I
And
Me myself and I
Me myself and my sister
And
She said you know
It's maybe a very good idea
To put around a pill
Because
It's nice for protection
You never know what happens
Or you know
You never know
And also
It is
It's better for skin
For a whole body and everything
And she feels much better
I have to say
But then we have to figure out
What kind of pill is
Correct for her
This is an amazing process
That you have to go
Yes
As a woman
Well no I have not tried the pill
Not every pill suits you
They are pill for men
No there is no
No there isn't
One
A temporary
They try
They try all the time
But men don't want it
I take it
I'll take any
You got some pills
Maybe
You got some great pills
Yeah
The ones that start with the next
So we're trying out a couple of pills
And now she's got another one
Because this one
She gained weight
Listen to this
I mean four kilos
So
That's eight pounds
Eight pounds
Yeah
Wow
Actually nine pounds
Because our pounds are heavier
We're counting Dutch pounds
I think women's pounds are heavier in general
Anyway
But so the English and the American pounds are a little bit lighter
So say about nine pounds
In three weeks
That's a lot
And you know they don't want that
No of course not
That's all I hear
Yeah
So you know so we found it
It was so fun
I tried this one
I see what happens
So this was a woman talk
Yes
Well it was so funny the other day
The other evening
I think what Christina basically said is
Am I fat
And now all guys
No you know
Whenever you're
No matter what woman
No matter what your relationship
With a woman
If she says am I fat
No of course not
If my butt big no
I mean this is standard answer
Yes it is
But she will
She said yes it is
And I said no it isn't
Right
But then exactly
And that one
And it was amazing
Because there was yelling in the house
And I wasn't a part of it
It was kind of fun
Yeah
But you said it
And I said no I didn't
But it's my is my butt bigger
Yeah
A little bit
You said I'm fat
And then see you said I'm fat
No I didn't say you're fat
It was and it ended
Literally with two door slamming
One on the left
My gosh
It's a sitcom
You know what
You were shivering
In the room here
I was
The dog
Was shivering that downstairs
The dog was like dude comes
It was me
Like me
In front of the door
Let me out
Yeah
Okay but all is well
Back at the cottage
Everything is for me
I said mommy will figure it out
Everything
Hi Adam
Jamie here
Sorry about the background
I was just waiting for us to take me to town for two days
Just listening to the Charlie for I won
And I just had
As you mentioned the work
Jack
Which
I'm sure you meant to take charge
Pretty sure I can't be the only
You know the only one you came to figure stuff
But yeah
If you're really pleased with something
They need to say
You know you're really really tough
I have no idea what chapter is
But it's a town paper
Okay mate
Thank you
Right
Okay
So that was a little English lesson
I messed it up
I was trying
It's stuff slips in
And I was going to say
I was really happy about something
I meant to say I'm chuffed
Yeah
But I said I'm chuffed
And which basically means
My legs have been rubbing together
And my crutches are red
Oh thank god that's nice
Oh and then we also went
To the house
Remember we had
Oh update on Patricia's palace
Oh yeah
Yeah
We were in the family of the house
We saw in Guilford
And so
So this house is listed on a monument list
It's grade two listed
Which means
Any structural
Changes you want to make
Has to be
Have to be approved by the local council
Yeah
And of course we have no experience with this
Partially fun
Fun
Imagine that
Fun to find out how that works
We talk to Mark Mark is
What is it
Contractor Mark
And we brought Mark along
And he said well
Normally it's not such a problem
Some people really understand it
Because if certain things
You have to live in
If you have to live in a house
Right now
And it's from
And it dates from
1900s or something
Yeah
1700 this house
17 and 18
17 and 1900
You need a little bit of adjustments
You know to make it more livable
And so he said
Will not be a problem
So after some email back and forth
And I already from the emails that came back from the council
I was like we'll see
And so we went there with Mark
And
And the first question was
Can we raise the doors
Well you know we have to say that
The lady came
That she was
Yeah the council
The council
And actually I was already like
Oh
It's a pity
It's a lady
Yeah because you know if it was a guy
Man we're a little bit better
Yeah
I mean but she was so
Determined
She was not taking any of my advances
No
She was not impressed
I tried all my American jokes
Everything
And actually I started with a compliment
Because Mark said
I talked to her on the phone
And you know when we parked
And we saw her and she was in pink
Lovely lady
And she was around about
I think 45 I guess
Oh no man
She was much younger
Oh you think she was younger
Oh yeah I think she was younger
And Mark said what she sounded
Very nice
I'm very young
Yeah
And the moment I met her
I said hello
Hi I'm Patricia
She had it
Oh wow
Mark said
Did you sound like a little girl
You look like a young girl
Right
You looked like a young girl
I thought
Yeah
She proceeded to rip you a new asshole
About the house
It was like
And then right away
Let's go in
She didn't say anything
Just let's go in
So
It really was a nonstarter from from go
Yeah
It was like
So we started with the
Can we raise the door
Six inches so my husband
Can actually walk in the house
I said otherwise
I have to change my husband
For sure
Right
Which still seems to be a viable option
And
You certainly have the experience
And changing husbands
Taking them back to the store
When you don't like them
It's such an asshole
The forums and all you know
So
And it was very interesting
Because she said
No, we can't do that
Because
And I know a little bit about this
The ratio of the doors
Will change
In
Relationship to the ratio of the panels
Now I know that you don't care
I know that you think it's horses
But from a
Architectural standpoint
This is the golden ratio
For broochio's numbers
I mean this is something
And actually
An architecture is important
But from that minute
I knew like I mean
I guess the knocking out of the walls
Upstairs
It's probably
You know they were very small
No they
What the doors
Yeah
They don't care
They do not care
So that was one
I thought okay
That was one
That's one
Can always change the husband
No problem
So we started with
Well
There's some traffic here
So we thought about
Double glazing
No
No you cannot change
Because these are original winners
Yes but you know maybe
I actually can use them
I said can I wash the windows
Is that okay?
Yeah
At that point
At that point I knew we were going nowhere
And then you said
Well
And I gave her the look
You know what ladies and gentlemen
Or gentlemen
If you have a girlfriend or a wife
You know what the look is
And in this case
With Patricia's look
I actually had to look away
I actually stood in front of Mark
So he wouldn't get any of the look
Because that shit's deadly
That was very
And I thought okay
It's all over
Yeah
I thought you were going to go down
For a mud wrestle with her
We women know what the look is
On the one second
For those of you
Listening on the serious stars
It is Friday
Which means we've got
The scenes scene
Which at all
Rutherford coming up later on
Here on 102
Gilmore Daily Dawn and Drew East radio
And of course
Next
It is Mark Yoshimoto
Nemkov
Not just heading up pod show
But also with Pacific Coast
Hellway
You'll hear him in just minutes from now
And we didn't even
Came to knocking out
Some walls
No
That was it
And you said
Patricia
Is there anything else you want to ask
I'm done
And I gave it a look
And I was gone
So you know
That was it
What's my dream
Sorry
The problem is
We really like Gilford
And by the way
Thank you for forcing me to come here
Yeah
I do appreciate it
Very special
It is
The architecture of Gilford in general
Is brown and ugly
So that is kind of an issue
This is why Patricia liked the horny castle so much
Because it had the facade
In front of a brown
She had house like the rest
But we can use the power of the source code
If anyone knows of a house
In Gilford
And you know enough about
A little bit of glamour
And you can have a poopy brown roof
It's open up the possibilities
It doesn't matter
You know we're in the market
It does a Victorian look
We need to jump on the property ladder
Yes we want to
We would love to
You know and I have a good taste
I have a good taste
I make it beautiful
I adjust to the outside
I will
You know who you coming out to
No
The council doesn't care
Or do you put flowers outside or not
They don't care
Because we love a beautiful old
Historian building
We do love that
The style I do not like
I'm a little tired
Of course
I'm tired of the bathrooms
And the doors
Oh man
No
But we'll find something
Because you know there are some beautiful
I think some beautiful houses here
I've seen them
Absolutely
So that was it
Okay
And tomorrow we get it really early
Yep
Yeah
Okay
But I don't really have anything else
I figured
Now that's my phone
I thought I heard a fly
Now this is my fly
Here
Wait
See now I'm getting a phone show
We need to go away
I can't do anything
That Steve Gilmore
He wants me to do the show with him
I should do it
So we had a lovely dinner yesterday
All right
Hey Steve
Hey
I'm doing the show right now
I'll call you back about 15
And we'll do it today
Okay
All right
Bye
Sorry
So we had a lovely dinner
Yesterday in Cafe de Paris
That was wonderful
Sitting outside
Isn't it lovely when you can sit outside
Until very late
Yes
You know
And I even drank some wine
It was so cool
Because
I said
You know and this is a real
Real French people in a real French restaurant
I would kind of wine
Would you like
And I'm looking at it
Do you have anything with a screw top
Because that's kind of my wife likes the most
And I swear to God
The guy brought a bottle
By the way
A 16 pound bottle of wine
Where the screw top
Yeah
Some light
You know
Very light
Not very interesting
Wine
Yeah
So like that
Patricia's manager
From 18,000 years ago
John Forcalfaic came over
And we talked about something
For a long time
You were one and only manager
You know
It was unfortunately
That he came before
You know
Just as I'd already finished the show
Because I really want to ask him
About the UFO story
That you guys claim that you saw you
Absolutely
Now that would have been fun
Yeah
And we'll do another time
Just some house cleaning stuff
A lot of people confused about the
Feed for the show
The podcast feed
It's the official one
Is it DailySourceco.com
If you subscribe through curry.com
You could be disappointed
Or surprised
Because you may or may not get the show
And you may get other shows
And so the official feed
Is DailySourceco.com
Seems to be a lot of confusion about that
And something else I was supposed to say
I don't know
I can't remember
It's warm
You started very early
It started very early
But it was so nice
It's so nice to just hop on that train
Hop on the two
Have a meeting
Look at the boobies
Come on home
Honey von
I'm flabbergasted
You flabbergasted
Alright
I'm not going to tell you who this is
So you listen to it
Tell me what you think
After words
Roller
Do the guessing
Re-touch me
You're my town
And I'm home
You're like hell
Can't find a phone
You're myself
Any last words
Thinking I need help
But no one I want yet
We touch me
And I'm perfect
Follow me
With you
We touch me
Can't find a phone
We are over
Forever
We're over
Oh my die
You're my town
And I'm flabbergasted
We're here
We're in a safe house
We've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed
here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we passed here, we've passed here, we passed here, we passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed there, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've shortest, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here, we've passed here
I can't find what I really want Never find I could be your valentine
Reach out to me
Why is it that Debbie Harry meets Samantha Fox or something?
Yeah, okay
Well first of all the sound that you heard you know part of that is is my sound you know, so
Musicians hate my sound because it makes your record sound different. Yeah, a lot of compression
You know, no, it does not crap. It's a compression
Is it Leslie Gord?
No, no, no, no. I agree with you was kind of a blondie vibe. Yeah
It's Kathy Valentine who was in the go-goes
Really?
Yeah, she's on the podcast music network
Oh, yeah, you told me that
I'm telling you what I'm seeing now. We're just going to see more and more and more
I have to say she's coming
Her voice sounds better than
Bullinda Carlisle
Oh, baby
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Well, everybody sounds better than
Bullinda Carlisle
Okay, dokey
Alright, baby
I'm trying to facts the airport and that's not working
So let's just cut the show
Alright
And maybe maybe you'll show it in the Monday because Tuesday I'm gone
So that'll be the last show together for a while
Alright
Yeah
Sure, I'm almost there for you, huh
I know you are, baby
Yeah, to mail you out
Just to mail on me out
Hi, baby
Hey, have a great weekend everybody
We'll see you on Monday
Alrighty
The lady in the tramp will be back
I love you
But I love you too
Another pod show pod guest
Stick it in your ear
Get this pod cast and more great ones like it
On the high performance pod cast delivery network
From pod show and limelight networks
I love it