This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
It sounds something like Delta Sierra Charlie.
Hang on.
What's it?
All right.
It's Adam Curry, everybody.
Adam's here.
This just in on news from the border.
The Pope officially apologized today to Adam Curry and his daily source code for making remarks
which Adam Curry found offensive.
The Pope was officially quoted as saying,
Adam, who?
We now return your to Adam Curry's daily source code which here at the border.
He's known as Doritos Salsa Chalupa.
Number four, six, single.
Hey, you figured out.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Adam Curry.
Well, my baby don't wear no panties.
Ask me how I know.
How do you know?
I said my baby don't wear no panties.
Ask me how I know.
How do you know?
Since it likes that natural feeling.
She knows it turns me on.
But I do good for right.
In my drop top can't lag.
She would want food in the front seat.
She would want food in the back.
By banning food we're shouting.
In she even getting us queer,
keep your eyes on the road,
and your hands are real.
That's my baby don't wear no panties.
Ask me how I know.
How do you know?
Tell me the truth.
I came home late from work
Tired and flung you down
Baby, won't answer a party
She was dancing all about
Just stood up on the bed
It's got to be when the bump and grind
She raised up a dress you know
It was every time
Cause my baby don't wear no panties
It has been how I know
I need no
This is like a natural feeling
She knows it tells me how
I need no
Come
So dancing on the tables, I keep putting on the show
The crowd was going crazy, now everybody knows
My baby don't, we're no fanning
Yes, man, how I know
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
There's a like that natural feeling
And she knows the terms, me, oh
Took her right in the morning
She wore a leather-minister skirt
Dug a nails in to my shoulders
When we laid down to the curves
I went through all the gears
Max out to our feet
She was screaming fast to faster
With both legs and a wind
I'm not feeling well, we're no fanning
As we have our own eyes
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
There's a like that natural feeling
And she knows the terms, me, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
There's a like that natural feeling
And she knows the terms, me, oh
And she knows the terms, me, Oh
There's a like that natural feeling
And she knows the terms, me, oh
Let's wait, hey, go.
Yeah, me and Jean, count them to die hard.
So mama, though, that is coming home.
Our baby don't wear.
No panties.
From the Podsate Music Network, suggested by Daddy Dows.
Thank you very much.
I could have waited for it for the Fubar festivities tomorrow,
but I like it.
Hey, going through today's show prep,
which usually takes me about an hour and a half.
And I'm late today because we spent time looking at yet another house.
Yes, we've got to keep all of our options open.
Things are looking very good here in the affluent suburb of Surrey,
known as Gilford in the United Kingdom,
in the current Curry Cottage.
I was like, yeah, this is going to be a great show.
And people were sending in really relevant stuff.
There's great feedback.
I've got some cool tunes for you, some emotions, some,
well, just everything you'd want on a Thursday.
And the big news, this is actually with Patricia
woke me up with this morning.
She brought me my cup of tea, which is just before I have to get out of bed
and go take Christina to school.
And she had the news for me.
It was quite, it was one of those things that you go,
oh, shit, man, that sucks, that's shocking.
And then the other hand, you think yourself, wow,
how crappy it was, you play dangerous things can happen.
It was almost like a Steve Irwin moment, if you were.
Hello, Adam.
Well, you always talking about how much you,
I was like, talk to it, which is I'm as being an accident.
Just know the news report now, at a family service,
for some time, I'll be on Wednesday.
We're going to have 350 mile collision, not collision,
350 mile accidents with a jet power car,
somewhere in New York and then you've been flown to,
I think, lead neurological centre or something
in the air anyway, apparently in a critical,
but stable can.
I don't know, I wonder what, if it will change,
could I be, I wonder if they'll show it?
I don't know, oh, yeah, hopefully you're still getting
and I hope that you watch those films along very nice.
I can't wait to get it.
Anyway, Adam, again, recently, Kate, thanks, bye.
Yeah, well, no, no, thank you very much.
So that is exactly the news, Richard Hammond.
Now, this is not the god that I spoke about the other time we talked
about this car show that the BBC does,
which is received an Emmy from the American Academy of Television
Peeps.
This is Richard Hammond, who's the sidekick,
one of the two sidekicks.
He's a really adorable guy.
He's, let's say, vertically challenged in the opposite direction
that I am.
And they always do fun stuff on the show.
I told you, they raised amazingly fast cars,
they were kinds of wacky stuff.
And I'm reading from the BBC report here.
Mr. Hammond had been in a dragster style car capable
of reaching speeds of about 300 miles an hour
at Ovington Airfield, New York.
That's that I believe that we're the new top gear studios
used to be near to the cottage and dunce fold.
I'm going to read here from, let me see, one of the eyewitnesses.
Here we go.
Former firefighter Dave Ogdon, who runs private firm
event fire services, one of the first people at the scene.
He said, we were down there with top gear
who were filming him trying to break the British land speed record.
Well, you'd need 300 miles an hour for that.
On the previous run, the car had just gone over 300 miles an hour
but I'm not sure if it had broken the record.
They just won more run and they were planning to finish
when it veered off to the right.
So it's a little unclear if that was while decelerating
from 300 miles an hour or if it was on an actual run.
But one of the parachutes deployed but it went on over to the grass
and spun over before coming to arrest about 100 yards from us.
I guess he's talking about the car, not the parachute.
And apparently, so the car flipped upside down
and Richard's head was digging into the grass.
The final quote here, Mr. Ogdon said he felt for pulse
and heard Mr. Hammond breathing before the emergency cruise
worked together to turn the car right way up and then cut him free.
He added, he was regaining consciousness at that point
and he said he had some lower back pain, you know, shit.
But it was drifting it out of consciousness a little bit.
So it's very unclear as to how severe his injuries are.
And but it doesn't look good.
I have to be honest, it does not sound good.
He could be particularly lower back pain.
You know, we don't know if he could feel his legs or any of that.
I mean, this is just horrible.
But then again, it's one of those Steve Irwin moments.
You know, it's like, well, shit dude, you know, you go 300 miles an hour
and then you know, shit can go wrong.
Sometimes, you know, you get caught up and doing stuff for television.
And if I think back to the number of times that I've done celebrity races
in all kinds of vehicles, everything's subsci-diving.
That's where I always drew the line.
I've done, I've really done a lot of it.
And some pretty dangerous stuff when you think about it.
Not just physically demanding, but to being in dangerous places and dangerous situations.
And you do that because it's like, hey, I'm from TV.
I'm fucking invincible, right?
No, there you go.
Turns out it ain't that way.
And remember, the lesson here, it's not speed that kills.
It's the lack of speed.
It's Thursday, it's done for my ass to get back in shape.
Adam, it's Amy Mack, how are you?
Hey, baby, I'm good, how are you doing?
All right, if you don't feel today's but exercise,
I don't know what I'll do.
We hire or change careers or something.
No, no, no, no, no, we'll work on it today.
Get the ass work.
Today and this move is the least complex of everything we've done this far.
Okay, let me get the other mic.
Are you ready?
Yeah, I'm ready.
Let's hear a little more enthusiasm.
Yeah, I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready.
All right, stand facing forward.
Face and forward.
Be shoulder with the part.
Yep.
Toes facing forward.
Now take your right leg and lift it to the back wall.
Your foot should only be a few inches off the ground.
Oh, okay, yeah, go on it.
Hands on hips.
Just move that mic like this.
We need the butt.
Oh, yes.
Squeeze it tighter.
And balance.
Yeah, I'm balance, ooh.
Make sure that the left knee is not locked out.
I'm squeezing the butt.
Are you squeezing?
Squeeze in the butt.
Squeeze tighter.
What could we feel it?
Yes.
Yes, make it do more seconds.
Oh, it feels like you have it now.
Yes.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Bring that leg down and take the left up.
All right, here we go, left arm.
Make sure not to turn your leg.
Your toes should be facing the ground.
Yep, toes facing the ground.
The left knee should still be in line with the hip and toes.
Yes, yes it is.
And I'm squeezing the knees.
Not locked, squeezing.
Balance, squeezing.
Squeeze.
Highters.
We say that again, baby.
Good and bring it down.
Okay, I think that does it for today.
Maybe I should start giving you homework to do in between our segments.
Okay, what do you think?
Sure.
As always, you can find me at fitness.patcho.com.
Yeah, that'll be the homework, right?
Take care, Adam.
Until next time.
Thanks for staying.
Amy Mack, I love you.
I love you.
Particularly when you tell me to squeeze a tighter.
Something, all of a sudden,
I had like an erotic moment there with Amy.
Oh yes, and you know what?
I asked us feel much better.
Thank you, Amy.
Thank you, Amy Mack.
Adam, this is a bug producer of the industry justice show.
Hey, you should go back to the old single, man.
This is, this is true, straight up.
I'm walking the work and you play those new jingles,
which I love for your phone numbers.
The dude, if I got your show right now,
I just remembered.
This one, two, one, six, two, five, six, three,
these five, seven.
It's stuck in my brain, man.
Go back to the old single.
Okay, later.
Hi, man.
Thank you.
You were probably talking about this one, Amy.
To reach Adam in America, dial.
Plus 1, 20, a 1, 6, 2, 5, 6, 3, 5, seven,
Plus 1, 20, a 1, 6, 2, 5, 6, 3, 5, 7,
Okay.
For Adam in Great Britain, dial plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7,
6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3,
Plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 3,
Thanks for going on the daily soles code,
Goodbye. Oh. Hold it. It's concha.
Eeeeh.
Let me see. Where's that other one you were talking about?
And we see. Was this the one we check?
No, that's not it. Yeah, I know exactly what you're talking about. The, um,
what is it voice? I'm now just literally searching through my, uh,
it wasn't the voice momentally. It was, it was like something extreme.
Uh, X. I wish. I just wish I knew.
That crap. All right. Hey, that could be a real estate agent. I'll, I'll look for the other one.
I totally understand what you mean by that being, uh, being better. But anyway, it is
plus one two oh one six two five six three five seven or plus four four two zero seven six eight one three seven five three.
Uh, this was a nice piece of feedback. I got from, uh, Chris daily, the C dog.
Hey, Adam. This is Chris daily with the PMC top 10. And I have to thank you. I have to
publicly thank you for, you know, laying it out there and talking about your father. That really
to me was why I started listening to podcasts in the first place because it was real because it was
raw and hey, Kudos to you, man. It's one of the things I struggle with on the other show writing
with the window down. I tried to put it out there, but sometimes as you know, it's a little difficult.
Also, one of the reasons one of my favorite shows is Mikey pod on the buy you, uh,
Michael Herend doesn't amazing job and all his shows are like that. It's like rip it open and lay it out
there. Good stuff. I highly recommend it. And thanks again, Adam, you're doing a great job.
Those who say you have jumped the shark. Well, the shark has left the building when you start talking
about reality. Thanks a lot, man. Keep it real. All right. Chris, I want you to go over to podcastpickle.com.
And I want you to post that. And I want you to tell all the little pickleights, the pickleettes.
What you think, you know, there's so much negativity over there. Now be a big man, go over there
and post them exactly what you just said. Okay. More from the voice mail box. Hey, Adam, it's John.
You're fellow Surrey X-Pad, uh, stuck in the morning school on traffic hearing the, uh,
luxurious suburb of Gilford. Uh, one thing to be in this morning, congratulations on the BT deal.
That is fantastic. Looking forward to all the advantages that's going to bring me as a BT
internet user of the service. Uh, but was wondering this morning, uh, listening to Virgin,
if you're the big star, I was thinking maybe that was going to be your big announcement over the last.
So, well, that is a, is Virgin doing some kind of promotion about having a big star coming in.
That hadn't heard about that. We do listen to Virgin often in the morning.
Uh, it's the Christian no-connal breakfast show. I believe is what it's called.
Guys, okay, you know, he's functional. Let's put it that way. The music's good so that works,
but I was not aware they were bringing in a big star.
Last week that you were going to be coming back to the airways on Virgin UK.
Why would I want to do that? First of all, that's a real job. That means you got to show up every day.
I don't never work. Not with my travel schedule. Uh, uh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
And why would I want to go back to the airways and be restricted? Look at all, I can do, I can start
when I want. I can make it as long as short as I want. I can say what I want. I can do whatever I want.
I'm my own woman here. And that you were the big star that driving me nuts with this announcement.
I thought maybe you might actually come in and clean up their playlist.
Okay, God knows a sickie here in Brian Adams summer of 69 on that station.
They do play that a lot, don't they?
Anyway, as always, as most of you, you're listeners, a lot of the show.
Hope you're well. Looking forward to the next time the church is on and, uh, scruncher.
Yeah, my hi. No, a nice scruncher. Thank you.
Yeah, I'll get Patricia on tomorrow for sure. Hey, Adam, Chris from the Financial Aid podcast, you
with answers to listen to his questions about how to get the Adam Curry sound.
Oh, yeah, this is all about the Adam Curry sound.
Does it take a lot of money to get the Adam Curry sound? Or can it be done efficiently and
Adam sound comes partly from compression, partly from using a stereo condenser microphone.
And partly from his God-given talent and voice.
It has a some experts have said, a very wide sound.
If you're not using a stereo condenser microphone, a high LPR-40 or a compressor,
you can still get a similar sound here as hell.
Step one, using a audacity on the PC or Mac record some audio.
Be sure your mouth is close enough to the mic that you don't sound hollow with far away.
Depending on the microphone, this can be anywhere from an inch to half of foot.
Try to do it in a room that has a little or no echo.
Step two, compression is part of the mix, but normalization is even more important.
Select all of your audio. Under the effect of my new select compressor.
Crank up the compression to a 6-1 ratio by moving the slider, the shortest attack time possible,
and check the little box that says normalized to zero decibels.
Step three, split the track into two tracks,
and one track hard left and one track hard right.
This creates a wide stereo sound effect that sounds good and headphones and good speaker setups.
There are plenty of other options and things you can play with,
but these two settings can make a big difference in a little sound for free.
Tuning into the Financial Aid podcast at financialadpodcast.com
and here personal finance information daily with a big sound,
and a learn more about podcasting on sound. Visit podcamp.org to find a podcast near you.
Runa, thanks Chris. You know, I agree with that partially.
Remember, I do this show in real time, in live, live format.
So it's in line and linearly, and we start at the beginning, and we end when we're done.
There's a lot to be said for recording that sound.
I mean, basically, I have an analog setup, you know, it's a tube processor.
Very hard to replicate, although a lot of the plug-ins for stuff like Pro Tools,
No Dacity, and Audition have gotten very, very good. You can get pretty damn close,
but I still do something, you know, there's nothing quite like doing it through an analog device.
That actually, I think kind of qualified as a
Tint-a-t-a-t-in foil. Tint-a-t-mo-mas. Tint-a-t-a-t-mo-il. Tint-a-t-mo-il.
Tint-a-t-a-l. Tint-a-l. Tint-a-l. Tint-a-l. Toil-it-t-mo-il.
And now it's time for the Tint-a-t foil hat moment.
At a zero, the area 51 group. Now we got a talking.
You keep using the 10-foil hat moment about degree subjects and, you know, that's okay.
You can expand the meaning of it, but on the little sense of about this because, well, being part of an organization called the Area 51 group,
the real meaning of the term is quite just doubling that in my psyche every time you play it when you're talking about 10 or something.
10-foil hat is worn by a conspiracy theorist.
They work 10-foil hats that don't go, because they think it's about keeping the government from scanning our brains or something.
Now, like I said, you can do it any more with the term.
We need a better term than nerdy moment or some crap like that, that's fine, but I just want to hear you about it.
I think you know that's a really mean conspiracy theory, guys.
You know, like somebody who believes in the moonlight, it's a fake jerk.
Never mind.
And, folder, scruncher?
Okay.
Yeah, no, I acknowledge that.
Of course, the 10-foil hat is, but it's all, you know, 10-foil hat is not just useful for area 51, like conspiracies,
and the government being able to scan your brain.
It's also very useful for ELF emissions from my monitor.
So I do wear my 10-foil hat frequently, of course.
And whenever in the air, I mean, you're blasting the 100 watts of power when I'm flying.
I'm talking on the radio.
You know, I always have little 10-foil hat folded over on the top of my nagging underneath my headset.
It's critical, of course.
But it does kind of stand for nerdyness and geekiness and electric bits and bobs.
And I think that it's for that reason that we can kind of let it slide a little bit into the geeky realm, if you will.
And this is just no, no.
Yeah, it feels right.
It does.
And I hope you don't mind me kind of adopting the 10-foil hat for some of the nerdy moments on the Charlie.
I hope you're okay with that.
And by the way, I'd love to do many more official certified 10-foil hat moments.
I just need more conspiracies to be sent in.
You know, a lot of the show is determined by you and what you send me.
I had a little sense, say, a moment there earlier.
Pardon me for that.
I did want to share with you.
I found a new sensei-o sensation.
I'm really working on it.
I'm working on the taste.
I've got some ideas for that coming up soon.
I'm going to try this flavored sugar substitute called Splenda.
But I've now, Patricia bought this frothing thing.
And you pour a little bit of milk in it.
And it's almost like a butter churn-only miniature.
And you just pump that side, that bad boy up and down.
You pump it, you pump it, you pump it, you pump it, and then all of a sudden it becomes frothy.
Pour a little bit in, then the coffee, and then the rest.
And it's good.
I'll have to get a picture of the throthing, the frothing frother.
It's really, it's no more than a plastic cup, like a tumbler almost.
With a lid and in the lid it's this little plunger.
And even better, you can take it even one step further.
You can froth it with the, I do 2% milk, which throths less good.
Then 1% milk, skim milk.
That froth is really well.
Froth.
What a nice word, froth.
I'll pay me touch my froth just a little bit.
If you froth it, and then you stick the cup in the microwave for about 25 seconds, it gets warm and really frothy.
And it's really enhanced the senseo experience, I have to say.
So if you have senseo at this point, remember this is a non-paid endorsement.
I just do it because I love it, because I love the coffee.
Give that a shot.
And I'll try, we're going to try out some of that flavor stuff as well, to get the perfect combination.
Hi Adam, it's Phil here to South here from Somset.
I'm calling in again.
I just listening to what you are responding to saying about some iTunes.
I had exactly the same experience.
The problem is, I think, is that because they've reconfigured it and made it so different.
Nine times at a time, it's not going to just replace iTunes.
Just index everything and it all be good.
My solution, I came up with was to basically delete everything that's not iTunes music.
You know, libraries, playlists, all that kind of Milwaukee, just delete that out of your music directory.
And just import everything back in, install iTunes, import everything back in, everything works fine.
Because it divides everything up into podcasts and audio books.
And that just got a whole new way to do anything.
So if any listeners are having problems with iTunes, that's really the way to do it.
You just got to basically take everything away.
Before I go, I just like to big up my daughter's podcast.
This baby podcast by Happy South.
And it's a great show.
She plays lots of, like, music, lots of podcasts, music.
And she's really cool, which is 2014.
Okay.
Thanks a lot, dude.
It's a bunch of you.
Ah.
The scrunchers have it today.
You should tell them what the URL is of your daughter's podcast.
Sounds good.
Is she on the podcast delivery network yet?
Pot show or where's just going to be the URL?
That's excellent.
Very, very nice.
Yeah.
It seems to be a lot of problems with iTunes 7.
A lot of people get confused as to how it works.
I have actually not upgraded myself.
Because we're doing right now, we're, I've seen it work.
Work yesterday, we're enabling, we're going to have this video.podshow.com.
Keep your eye on that URL.
Some stuff is going to happen there for sure.
And what we're enabling now is that you can subscribe to,
YouTube and Google video.
And it'll play in our dashboard in the player.
Which is pretty cool, actually.
So we'll have the top 20 YouTube videos, the top 20 Google videos.
And just a whole bunch of stuff that's coming.
And not to forget the top 20 podshow videos.
There's a lot of video content being uploaded.
Remember, you know, there's no limits if you're running into,
you know, I think with, like with with YouTube,
there's a hundred meg limit or 10 minute limit,
which I found a bit discouraging because I, you know,
I wanted to also upload my stuff to YouTube and I actually couldn't.
Or even worse, it would upload all the way.
And then it would say, now it was too big.
It's not a lot.
That's not up 150 megs.
And then they don't even convert it.
And I asked about New Orleans a couple of shows ago.
And I got a beautiful piece of feedback.
There's some great stuff happening in Louisiana.
Hey Adam, this is Patrick Richardson.
He, we're talking about New Orleans day of the day.
And I just wanted to tell you, yeah.
I'm actually into Orleans today.
They are a bit of operational and fully functional.
Monday night football starts next week in the super dome.
So it's at the interesting game.
I'm actually in town for meeting my corporation,
or corporation decided we're going to have our,
our managers meeting in New Orleans
to help stimulate the economy.
And the hammering you here behind me is,
have it set for humanity projects.
We took one day out, more actually helping go home
through musicians and musicians' village.
So the companies are interested in doing this.
They can contact habitat for humanity
and figure out how they can help soon.
Talk to you later.
Folder.
Right on dude.
Excellent.
Did he say Oracle Corporation?
Fantastic.
I love hearing that.
I wonder if they had a big, if they had a big office down there,
maybe.
That's cool.
I like it when big companies do,
you know, things like that.
No matter what, no matter what capacity they do it.
I didn't know Monday night football started from,
from the super dome on this coming Monday.
That's great.
So yeah, it sounds like things are definitely moving
and you should get your ass down there.
Spend some money.
Help out.
Do both.
If you can.
I was running.
I was getting the next set of calls all lined up.
Remember that caller yesterday on episode 464.
We said that he did not like David Epolito.
Maybe it was 463.
I don't remember.
Boy, that sparked off a lot of phone calls.
Hey.
Adam.
This is John.
That call you had today about Dave Epolito or the guitar man.
Come on.
I mean, I disagree with him.
A lot of things.
I email him all the time.
We're having quite a bit of a debate.
He's taking my button.
The argument.
But that's the side of the point.
The straight he doesn't have count is ridiculous.
He's great.
His music is great.
His players are great.
Their guitar playing is great.
He's really, really good.
And I would just love to be able to get down in New York or up to New York.
You are going over to New York to see him play.
And I don't know what this guy's problem is.
And the guy said he went to a Bob Dylan concert.
The state's there.
It was bad concerts.
I've been to three or four Bob Dylan concerts.
Every other one is different.
Some of the good.
Some of that sort of removed Bob as in.
This guy's an idiot.
All right.
Well, I guess that's not nice.
But wow.
I can't believe he would say this.
Somebody doesn't have talent.
Just because he doesn't agree with his politics.
That's crazy.
Oh, well.
And then, you know.
All right.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
He's crunchier full of scruncher.
And then our buddy Jeff Smith checked in.
Hey, Adam.
This is Jeff Smith.
Just cruising listen to four, six, four.
And listen to the guy go on about David at the lead.
And I just had to correct him on one thing.
He was saying that David at the lead was stuff is nothing but parody.
Actually.
parody is kind of what I do, which is spoofing and existing.
Song or piece and sort of doing something.
Basically copying it.
Three.
I think what he meant to say is he's doing satire, which is more social commentary.
Yes.
Right on with you thinking that he's a great social commentator.
So, hey, guys.
I was just wrong in his words.
But otherwise.
Rock and roll.
All right.
Talk to you later.
Bye.
Thank you.
Yeah.
I think what really got that guy is that I compared David at the leado to Bob Dylan.
I said, this is the Bob Dylan of our time.
You know, he's bringing us the lyrics that are relevant.
And it really is about what he's saying in the song.
But even that much about the song, and still he's got very, very catchy tunes of the time.
For now.
Well, there's one person who was bound to be really pissed off by all of this.
He hit him.
This is Bob Dylan County.
Good talking.
But I mean, that guy's fucking bitch.
It's to Dylan.
I apologize profusely.
I really do.
Okay.
I'm that was the nice version.
Here's the mean version.
Go for it.
Hi.
This is Lockjaw.
The podcast junkie.
Adam.
I just want to thank you for sticking up for David at the leado.
I hope I'm putting that scruncher in his place.
You know, probably this is guys full of shit.
He's using that scrunched up toilet paper to wipe a hole in the ground because he does not know the difference.
I challenge him personally to go to that guitarman.com download episode.
And listen to it.
And then call the DSC back and tell me that David at the leado.
Only right shallow funny songs and doesn't know what he's talking about.
Because in that episode, he plays his own stuff and he really lays his soul there at the world.
And it's one of my favorite episodes.
So do it.
Call back.
Let me know what you think.
Bye.
Okay.
I'm sure he will.
I'm sure we'll be hearing from him.
No doubt about it.
That guitarman.com is where you can find David.
David, a polito, his podcast is called.
I love the company, which I think is a very interesting title.
And I actually taught them.
I talked to him about a girl con dream to have sit.
Hello.
Hello, dear.
Thank you.
And nice shake.
Just needed that.
We come on the show tomorrow.
Okay.
It tastes good.
Thank you.
Nice.
It's a lady Patricia.
We'll be on the show tomorrow.
That was I say.
No, yeah.
He had Sid Bernstein do that promo.
Sid Bernstein.
Music industry legend.
We brought the Beatles to America.
And it looks like he may actually get some kind of show going with Sid Bernstein.
There was just a dream I had.
How cool would the beat have Sid Bernstein talking about Podsake music?
I think we could really really go far with that.
Today, the fifth episode of Shadow Falls drops Shadow Falls.ponshow.com.
It is our original audio drama.
It's theater of the mind.
It's very much in line with the audio books.
Scott Sigler, of course, being the Sultan of that.
And there's a lot more people are seeing this as a very interesting new creative outlet.
And audience are flocking to it.
That's so cool.
And it's not just about the show itself.
It's about the story, the backstory, about the actors, about the writing.
There's communities really evolving around this stuff.
And I find it incredibly exciting because this is what it really started out with for me with the iPod.
Even before I was thinking of podcasting, I really wanted to listen to audio books.
And if you want to hear a great example, listen to John Stewart's audio book version of his book.
Very well produced.
Just funny and interesting and more of a comedic piece, not just a dry read of a book.
And people are doing some very, very interesting things with that night.
And I want to support that as much of a hint.
Crap.
Do it by playing a lot of music.
I'm going to have my shake.
You listen to this.
Six months ago, the seven son potty of book trilogy began.
Seven clones were ripped away from their normal lives to hunt a ruthless criminal.
The man they were cloned from, the man who masterminded the assassination of the president.
You met John, father Thomas, killed Roy 2.0, Michael, and the other beta clones.
It was always story.
It wasn't real.
But for one night, it will be.
On Saturday, September 23rd, be a part of podcast history.
Enjoy an exclusive sneak peek of seven son, book two, deceit.
It's the first ever launch party for a podcast novel in the online community, second life, and you're invited.
Meet me, author J.C. Hutchins, in-world, and listen to my interviews about book two that you won't find anywhere else.
You'll learn about the upcoming novel and get hints of the plot twists to come.
You'll even get to hear the first chapter of Deceit, days before it's released as a podcast.
And you'll see fiction given dimension.
In-world, you'll be able to step into the warm cloning chamber from book one where the clones were given birth.
You can see the clones.
You can be a clone.
It's a new life there in second life.
The party starts at 7 p.m. second lifetime, that's 10 p.m. Eastern, 7 p.m. Pacific.
On September 23rd, at the podcast island.
Podcast Island is the second life community for podcastpickle.com.
As always, the seven son experience won't cost you a dime.
All you need is a second life account available for free at secondlife.com.
You joined the Deceit.
Now fight the deceit.
Come to podcast island at 7 p.m. second lifetime on September 23rd to experience seven son for the first time.
A second time.
For more information visit J.C. Hutchins.net.
And prepare yourself for seven son, book two, Deceit.
They're viewing on Tuesday, September 26th.
You can find it at J.C. Hutchins.net.
And at audiobooks.com.
Interesting idea, I like it.
I really do.
And as I was listening to that, I was thinking, wouldn't it be interesting to recreate shadow falls?
The place, some of the buildings, the roads, the diner, the woods.
Wouldn't it be interesting to recreate that in second life?
I would gladly relinquish all creation building rights to pod shows island.
So when we're willing to turn that into shadow falls, I would do that in a freaking heart beat.
I'd have to get Brittany Mason's approval, of course.
But how cool would that be?
Yeah.
Those of you that are really into shadow falls into the story.
If you've ever checked out second life, it could be a very interesting experiment.
Something really, really fun to do.
I'm just saying, you know.
Hey Adam, Paul Barry here from window to the magic.
And I was wondering if you could do me a huge favor.
Now I realize that this is not something that you want to get in the habit of doing on your show.
But hopefully you'll make a one time exception.
My girlfriend, Terry Woodard of the Little Reds Writing Hood podcast, is celebrating her birthday on Thursday, September 21st.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
I just want to make a general observation.
Do you remember Toby Radloth, the original nerd, who was on MTV back in the day?
I'm Toby Radloth, the original nerd.
Does this guy sound like him or what?
My girlfriend, Terry Woodard of the Little Reds Writing Hood podcast, is celebrating her birthday on Thursday, September 21st.
And due to reasons beyond our control, I cannot be there together with her.
Terry listens to the Charlie every day, and she's a big supporter of podsafe music and podcasting in general.
As a matter of fact, she just finished interviewing Mark and James about the writing of Shadow Falls,
which she will be airing on her podcast on the 25th of this month.
Anyway, I just thought we could make her day a little brighter.
If you played one of her favorite podsafe music artists, Amy Ayers, and her song One More Day on the Daily source code.
Now I love Terry very much, and I know that it would just make her day if you and I and the rest of the world of podcasting could wish her a happy birthday in this fashion.
So Adam, thank you very much in advance, and Terry, I love you, babe.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
And I need you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you,
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you,
I do it
And I need you
Why don't I tell you
And why don't you
I'll tell you my truth
To the world
Because I need you
And why don't I tell you
And why don't you
I'll tell you my truth
To the world
Because I need you
When you are by my side
And why don't I write us
I'll tell you
And why don't you tell me
And then you
Why don't I tell you
Why don't you know
I'll say my truth
To the world
Because I need you
And why don't you
I'll say my truth
by all means, I have a very happy birthday Terry Woodward, Woodward, I hope you don't take
that the wrong way, dude, I couldn't help noticing it, yes Terry, happy birthday, that's it for
today tomorrow, we'll be back with the Fubar Friday, and as of Sunday in your music suggestions,
I'm sure the music colleges will check in, then play any of his stuff last week, actually,
I'm sorry to say, his music college he didn't hit me, and as you already heard, we have
a commitment, a firm commitment from the Lady Patricia to be on the show as well.
Adam and podshow.com, send me whatever you want, daily source code.com as we can find the
show notes, links to the songs and the pods hit music network, et cetera, et cetera, talk
to tomorrow, everyone, bye-bye, another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it, on the high performance podcast delivery network
from podshow and limelight networks.