Already a hit state side now you can check out the following podcast and good old
Blighty btpotjo.com single-handedly making a men's for the Boston Tea Party one show at a time
Without a doubt fucked up beyond all repair it is episode number 511 of the Charlie good morning
Everybody how you doing is daily source code 512 the match on its Thursday
It is episode 513 of the Daily Source Code
In the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into the future
Let's check all the more she does
Living it's been Christmas here on Mars
All living it's been Christmas here on Mars
Yeah, we'll party with our little green man around the galaxy
To stand as well in your arms brings from state to the mercy
On her belly in the news now all start dancing to living it's been Christmas here on Mars
Come on now I'm living it's been Christmas here on Mars
I want to decorate it it's just you and me floating around
She from star star here we are now we're never coming down
I'm living it's been Christmas here on Mars
I'm living it's been Christmas here
Yeah, bubble
Oh, bubble Christmas here on Mars from the pod save music network hey everybody how you doing it's daily source code
Episode number 515 thanks to Andrew Grummit for the for the opening of today's show almost like let me at some wrong
Yeah, oh my goodness
Well, yeah, there's something wrong with the cable
Andrew Grummit put together the who's 515
At in case it wasn't completely clear what's going on there
I'm back at the cottage. It's a shitty outside man. It's cold, you know for as
As dark and and dank as San Francisco was it wasn't this cold and we've got the real true London fog today
Just rolling throughout the city
If I look out the window I can probably see about I'd say about 500 feet it's the entire distance I can see it's just one of those
Yeah, one of those pre-Christmas days in the United Kingdom good to be back arrived yesterday after you know
My typical 10 hour flight from San Francisco pretty un-eventful
I was completely prepared to not have any new movies on the in flight entertainment system
They pretty good about changing it every single month
I guess for some reason the month of December is not the month to change so I'd seen just about everything
So I'd purchased a couple of books including the
Let me just pick it up here for a second call
I
Want to get the title exactly right the Iraq study group report which I've seen a lot of TV host hold up on television
And I wonder if they actually read it
So I took a stab and it wasn't all that hard to get through you know
I'll talk about that a little bit later on in the show
Because there's a lot to go through
First thing that's real bummer is all of a sudden for some reason
My Nokia the the E61 that I purchased it won't send any text messages so for some reason
You know, this is in in Europe we called SMS for short message service in the states
We call it text and it I can receive I can make calls. I can access the internet through the data connection
But for the life of me I can't send a text message and it happened the minute I landed I turned it on and
And
And I and I received stuff but I wasn't able can you I always sent Patricia little message when I land saying you know landed safely
What ever airport? I've landed at that point in time and
Then we'll go out and I get some kind of error message saying unable to send message
The error code is four five five zero and of course
Singular support has no idea
No one can figure it out well it could be the the you're roaming on team mobile UK and that could be a problem so and it just I feel incomplete
I feel really incomplete when I can't send the text messages. It's bothersome particularly with Patricia gone
You know because we text each other all the time it's like a baby how you doing and love you
But you know the stuff you do as well everyone does that right and
Of course she had her second
taping last night of dancing dancing with the stars and she did very well
I'm under complete embargo. I'm not allowed to tell you how everything went because the shows aren't being broadcast until
Was it I think Christmas
Now the day after Christmas is the first show and then the 31st of December is the second show
So I'm because there's points involved and all the even though it doesn't matter because it's all for charity
I'm not allowed to tell you but she was very excited and she had a great time and I know why man because just imagine
Like a little over two years ago. She was in the intensive care unit
You know near heart attack and now two and a half years later she's dancing full-scale competition doing the
Samba
I can't well hopefully now. I'm gonna force her to be on the show tomorrow. She's got to tell us how it went
So I am
Of course going through the mail when you come back after you're like two weeks of being away
There's a fine stack of stuff
Just lovely little messages from people around the world saying I want my money. Yes, it's built time
But there was also a package and I was really really impressed with this now
You know that I've told you that Virgin Airlines is really sucking up to their top to your customers and and
I just want to give you an example of that of what what it really makes me feel good by the way
So it is absolutely working because I have a choice. I can fly American. I could fly British. I could fly
Virgin obviously there's so many different airlines. I could choose to fly
So I got a
package from the CEO of
Virgin
Where's the note here it is
ah
Adam here's the only hand luggage you'll need in 2007 happy holidays
From CEO Steve Ridgeway and what they gave me
It's really nice. It's an iPod Nano and it's one of the one of the red ones so that's
Bono and
And Tim Shriver's product red. I met him
Tim Shriver and met him Saturday night. I got talk. I got so much to tell you
It's what is it four gig one thousand songs so um, but it says on the card here
To retrieve Steve's message from your iPod
Follow these four easy steps. Well, I'm not gonna follow no steps. I want to hear the message so
Hold on a second. Let me just open this up. Let me let's listen to this together and see if they had put a person
I mean the my name on the card here Adam is in a different font and different color
The cards are definitely computer generated
Let's see if they were able to computer God. What do you need like a fucking blow torch to open this thing
How does this work? Oh, I see okay sticker here. Oh, that's actually better than the blow torch
I've never I've never purchased a nano. That's nice cute
Very cute. Okay. Oh, I'll tell you what here's we're gonna do
God this thing is so small
Let's uh, well, let's plug it in to the mixer here
I think we can do that. Here we go
Yes, it's plugged in
Okay, let's see
Music photos
Which we look under oh
What's this interesting
You're pre oh this is how do they do this? I've heard about companies doing this and working with Apple on that. This is great
They automatically subscribe me to the virgin Atlantic podcast feed which has
Well
Looks like all these are all these guides to different to how so that's guide to Sydney
What's this Atlantic off beat London? Okay, so they put a podcast in there. That's pretty cool
Where's my message from Steve? Is that his name Steve? Wait, I forgot. Yeah, Steve Ridgeway
I don't see it
Okay
So this could be potentially very disobeyed. Oh, here it is Steve Ridgeway
CEO message. All right, let's go
Season's greeting to you from everyone at Virgin Atlantic. Okay. I can't think okay. I can't think
Season's greetings Adam all right, let's try it again
Season's greeting Adam from everyone at Virgin Atlantic
I can't thank you enough for all the support you've given us yet again in the past year
It's been an exciting time for us. We've opened new routes to Dubai
Which was a major breakthrough and of course our holiday program is expanded with the new route to Jamaica
We've carried on bringing our new aircraft so there's an even bigger fleet of A34600s
Which keeps us right up there with our pledge to operate one of the world's youngest fleet
upper class suite has continued to lead the pack as far as
Business classes concerned and we're very proud that we still have the most beautiful cabin and the biggest and best bed that's out there flying
You know, they could have done a little better job on the recording
I mean what they do they they just went into his office and it's a hung a mic from the chandelier
That sounds like crap, but we are not resting on our laurels more to come next year
I'm sure you'll be pleased to hear that Chicago is back on the list
The next year we sadly came out of the Chicago market after September 11th
But it's great to be going back in we're going to give our competitors a great run for their money as usual
And I hope we can see you on our Chicago flight if you want to be a relaxation
Then there's a new program in the Indian Ocean with Mauritius starting at the end of next year and certainly everyone here
at Atlantic tickly on the leisure side is really excited about that
So enjoy playing with your iPod and downloading all the music commute should be a great companion for your trips
But of course you can watch many many films when you're flying next and once again as I said at the beginning
Really appreciate all the support you give us we couldn't do it without you and and I look forward to seeing you all again next year
Season's greetings yes
Shanting city
There are podcasts guides to other went to the podcast. Yes
Tell you
Steve. Thank you
Okay, let me plug that back in there. Okay. Well, that was nice
That's that's customer service man
That's what an all about
Hello, Adam this is Stella from Brisbane California
I just talked through listening to Hoover Friday and I just thought
I'd make a suggestion as regards your show about flying
Let's lean the fool's because it sounds good flying fool sounds really good that how about soaring fool
And it just makes me think of birds that soar so high and that's what planes do
So soaringfools.com
Well, have
Great
Thanks, darling
I don't think so. I mean don't you understand that flying fools feels better than soaring fools
Soaring now. No, no, no, no flying fools. I'm gonna keep it at that
But I played your voice moments because it's always nice to hear a woman calling on the voice
I don't get enough of
Six three
Yeah, that's the number if you're calling us from the United States and of course if you're in the UK you can use this number
I don't know if Google is just improving stuff
Cuz I keep seeing new features pop up on now. I use the docks and spreadsheets and we use the collaboration
Feature all the time within pod show by the way. That's great. I mean real
Financial models and in spreadsheets. It's way too slow too cumbersome and not everything translates and
You know we have a lot of very complex
Financial models that we've built into or I built in Excel because you know
We have thousands of people that we pay on a on a by monthly basis twice a month
That by monthly by weekly whenever twice a month
And that just doesn't really work or it's too slow or just anyway. I use
Google's calendar
religiously I love it
Of course I use Gmail
I'm such a
Google fanboy when it comes to that and I'm being using notebook and it it appears that
This Google notebook which is it's kind of meant to you know to be able to
It's more like a clipboard for the web so you see something
A page you like or an email message and it's pretty smart about knowing that something's an email message
And it'll copy the entire message and it will automatically provide the link and it's just a whole bunch of things that are smart
Except for one thing and I've talked about this a couple times when you click on the link when you're in
Google notebook it doesn't open up a new window or a new tab
It goes to the link and you know, therefore you have to
Backspace or hit the back button to get back into notepad and that takes a long time to load
Because of course I have lots of shit in my notepad
I'm using it like an outline right use it for all kinds of stuff and I'm seeing that
You know, I'm just
Maybe I'm just learning the the I'll call it an application even though it's not
I'm figuring out how to use it in a very efficient manner almost like a full blown outline or so I'm really happy with it
But I still can't figure out how to get
A link to pop open in a new window
Obviously, I can you know hit right you know, I can hit the right mouse button and say open a new tab and all that
But I wanted to react like all the Google apps because that's what I'm used to and I keep making them steak
Oh, it's
Just say hey Jamie Ross sent me an email
That would be
Our new our new executive assistant Jamie Ross you said Adam if you'd like Google to open a new tab click on preferences on the Google main page
Yeah, I did that
But it doesn't work for notebook Jamie as nice, but it's funny in that because I like didn't even know that was Jamie from our office
I just I just saw Jay Ross like a Jay Ross sent me some
Hey portions of today's show are brought to you by brand new movie
Which opens up hold on let me get all the details here
Uh
The movie is called Stomp the Yard and it opens up January 12 now. This is from the same theater the same
Movie company
Who wanted us to promote a little man and you remember that that was a very successful movie and I love doing the
I've really loved doing the the promotions for it because I hadn't seen it and they weren't gonna give me a DVD
It's the same with this one. I have no idea
However, I do know that we have a podcast all about Stomp the Yard
Which I think it's gonna be a really good movie and
It just you know, it could be one of these things that's at the beginning of January
You know, we're ready for some
Light entertainment yet
You know some serious message it's a new year everyone's in the new year's resolution. I think the timing is really good
of this movie. It's about
A troubled youth from Los Angeles attending the historically black truth university in Atlanta, Georgia and
What adapting to his new environment proves difficult
He finds solace in joining a struggling fraternity where he begins implementing his street style dance moves and attempt to help the step team
When the coveted national step show championship
So there's you know, there's some inspiration in there and and and it kind of hits home
Particularly the first episode because Stomp the podcast.com is where you can hear all about the movie
Tony cost of cost as world is is producing that nice guy by the way
I had a chance to meet him both in Los Angeles and up in San Francisco for our holiday party
On the first episode which came out on I think Friday at
Stompthepodcast.com
Tony has a can of conversation on black college life black Greek organizations and the impact that has on the culture
And of course cost as world a show itself also highlight
The upcoming movie Stomp the yard a couple other podcasts joining in this as well and I really want to see this movie
Oh, oh, shit. No, it didn't happen. Oh, sorry. I want to see this movie because when I was in college for all four months that I was in college
In West Virginia I
Pledge Kappa
Now you have to know that my roommate tie Hamilton at the time this was 1980
Was at 80 crap 81
1980 81
You know
We would have said of each other. Oh, you know my roommate is black and he would have said my roommate is white
These days of course we have to speak of African American and Caucasian and be very politically correct
But it was about if it was a mixed school about 50 50 50 tie was from
Trenton New Jersey and
You know he became buddies and and I didn't really have any friends no one
That I knew went to that school and of course he had a lot of people that he knew and
And start hanging out and we were into the same music because I came from Amsterdam at the time
It was literally the same music that that urban America was listening to so we got along famously through the bridge of music
I would say
Most importantly and I hung out you know and then and then and then said hey you should pledge Kappa
Which meant I didn't know it at the time when I said oh, yeah sure
Sure I'll do that and meant carrying around a fucking brick a couple weeks
But it was quite an experience and so I can't wait to see this movie should be very interesting
People write me here as a man of the people of the world
And nothing is as well
So this is the it cuts off there unfortunately. That's the prolific programmer from San Francisco
He's called the voicemail lines a number of times but it's been
Reasonly unintelligible what he was saying or it was like so it was such a long story
So the point here was that he appreciated me talking about to engineers on Friday's final thought of the week
Yeah, man
We love engineers. That's why I stood still for a moment to think about them
Okay, back to the how are we doing on time me? Wow talking a lot of shit here today
I see Brian and Nigma sense a whole thing about the
I incorrectly said DMTF tones you know the tones that I was playing so you can automatically dial your phone
It's actually DTMF dual tone multi frequency
He's got a whole
A whole history of where they come from
See the whole system was designed so that
Computers if yesterday or could understand what button you were pressing without direct being directly wired to the button
And you couldn't accidentally make the sound of a button press. Oh, I'm sure people can do that
I'm sure that there are people out there who can make those sounds. Where's my uh
I have a little uh a little thing
Hmm
Not gonna have to go into my computer
I'll be worth it for a second hold on let me see local disc
This is the thing that's much easier on the Mac just to get you just go to applications and you're there and here I have to
Search through a million different folders. Here it is
What is this tone dialer? There you go. So the tones we're talking about are these
I bet you there people out there who can make that noise
Okay
Try it record something send it to me
I'll see if I can make a dial and make it a surprise make it something cool that we're gonna dial
You know where to send it add them at podshow.com
Radion records interesting article PD love from love house radio sent me that
Oh shit I clicked on the link without opening a new tab
So radion records is pretty much the Bible for for the radio business and
They came to an amazing conclusion
It's the content providing compiling content wins
Says critical mass media is caroling Gilbert. Do you know there's one of the thousands of consultants
Devoting the energy to finding out what they want and delivering it is the future of radio she asserted
Yeah duh
So they go on to talk about you know the new formats the jack format which I'm sure you've heard and then there's the move in format
It has a fresh success and Seattle a thing that really got me here at the end so this was
There was some panel. Where was this panel as a panel of marketing marks in in the radio business
They underscore the importance of broadcasters using overnight to groom talent for the future and to
Prime the audience well by spending more of a station's budget on marketing and promotions
Well most in attendance seem to gravitate to the latter notion if you wondered where in these days of severe budget cuts that funding would come from
That's right your fucking host
Not that I feel good about it. You're welcome over here all of just
All of just come on over to the dark side. That's plenty to do
And got some great things we're gonna be talking about in the new year
Not the least of which is the toddies
Jersey Todd show is handing out awards. I was I don't know if I'm if I've been invited to present an award or not
I was so busy. I couldn't make a part of my commitments to the toddies and I think I've been scrapped off the list
But check out Jersey Todd show
to listen to
I think it's the first annual toddies
Yes, and why don't we close out today
Here
Well, we are getting very near the day
And if you look at the most played on the
Podcast this week it's all Christmas tunes
Oh
Nothing all the way
Bells on bug tailoring
Making spirits bright with fun. It is to ride and sing a sing song tonight
I
Or the fields we go laughing all the way
There's on both tailoring
Making spirits bright
What fun it is to ride and sing
A singing song tonight
Just go to your day
Or what fun it is to ride and sing
A singing song tonight
To go back to your past
She will only
What fun it is to ride
Or the fields we go
Dancing through the snow
Wanting a song
She will be
Under way you sing
To go back to your past
She will be
What fun it is to ride and sing
A singing song tonight
For fun it is to ride and sing
A singing song
Oh there's Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells
Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jing
I had to listen this five times before I understood it.
I'm not even going to go into that.
So Sunday, just before I left, I picked up Pacific Coast Hellway,
which was a collaboration on the heavily promoted interview with Jesus
for his upcoming birthday.
I got a tell you.
I really liked it. It was very funny.
Now I can understand, I do want to be sensitive.
If you love Jesus, you may not like this whole idea.
But I think it's all, it's all in good humor.
It reminds me a lot of Mel Brooks interview with the 2000 year old man.
Some of you may be old enough to remember that.
I only remember because my parents happened to have that album hanging around the house.
So I'm sure it's from at least the early 60s, maybe than late 50s.
But just the whole idea reminded me of that very much.
I got a promo with a couple of clips from it.
This is Brian from audio attitude inviting you to listen to the Jesus interview.
We talked about a lot of things, including what he was like as a kid.
Yeah, I was a dick, really.
What do you think of meetings?
Year 300 AD.
Minutes from the meeting.
Gabriel.
Blah, blah, blah.
Same fucking thing every year.
What the H means in Jesus H Christ?
This is so embarrassing.
I mean, you don't have to tell us what the middle initial is.
My middle name is Hyman.
Okay.
And that's the problem.
Folder or a scruncher.
Oh, you know what?
Actually, here's the beauty of it.
Every time I take a shit.
Perfect.
I don't even have to wipe.
Just like, boom, I mean, that's it.
It's just like, it's a gift, man.
It's just like one of those things.
It's just like, I don't even have to really squeeze that hard.
I just kind of like, there's a little moment.
I take a little breath and go, and you know, drops in the ball.
And I'm done.
So clean as a whistle.
You know, sometimes I'll check.
But what does it smell like?
You know what?
It smells like.
Here's the funny thing.
It actually smells just a little bit.
Just a tiny bit.
You know what?
This is going to be weird.
This is a little too weird.
I don't know if I can talk about this.
No, that's okay.
I'm curious because, you know,
Okay, it smells just a little bit.
Like Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg.
I don't know.
It's kind of a little bit that old lady's smell
and a little bit of perfume.
But it's, I don't know.
I've never smelled Ruth Bader Ginsburg.
And, well, come over sometime after I've had, you know, tacos.
Here I come, Jesus.
Jesus interview.
Attitude.podshow.com.
Yeah, you should listen to it.
It's very funny.
Yeah.
I don't know how much of the, of the interview
the guys that scripted out.
Sometimes you can tell.
I just cracking up.
It's good.
Last week, I talked about the new John Cleese podcast.
It's not a new podcast, but it's first video,
it's first video podcast.
And while I was talking about that,
I mentioned the guy who, I don't know if he's producing it
or hosting and doing the RSS feeds
or maybe he's doing all the production.
Maybe he's writing it.
I don't know.
This guy named Dean Woodbread from the UK.
And I said he was a dick.
And this sparked off all kinds of controversy
in the UK amongst the UK,
the UK podcasters association.
And I just wanted to, you know,
it's like, oh, it's unbelievable.
How important people think this is.
So I wanted to elaborate a little bit on that.
First of all, about brick caster itself.
A brick caster is run by Neil,
or was run by Neil.
And he'd been running that way before I ever met him.
And when we started talking,
when podshow, when I said podshow is coming to the UK,
when we'd be doing things,
it was all of the speculation about,
you know, Neil, you built this just for,
for BT podshow, you're going to sell out.
And you know, all of this fucking like,
you know, it's a pruder type
conspiracy theories.
And you know, what of course happened is,
as I could have predicted,
which I didn't do,
because I thought it actually might be
a little bit different here in the UK
that there might be a more sense of
politeness and consideration.
But most online communities that don't have
a real community blow up,
that's just the way it works,
because everyone's on equal footing equal ground.
And I've seen it hundreds of times.
They just explode unless they're heavily moderated.
And then of course, you know,
really a community if there's some uber boss.
And the problem is that podcasting
cannot be a community,
because it's a, it's a verb.
You know, it's an action.
It's a thing you do.
And there is no right or wrong way.
It's, you know,
yes, there are conventions for broadcasters,
like the NAB,
NASA Association of Broadcasters,
and they come together,
and they have a conference.
You know, but it's not like they have a club
where they all hang out,
because there's so many different types of broadcasters.
There's broadcasters for profit broadcasters for non-profit.
There's Christian broadcasters,
there's music broadcasters,
there's talk broadcasters.
You know,
the only thing they have in common,
which is why they can actually call themselves
some form of a community,
is that they all have to deal with
restrictive distribution.
We don't have that with podcasting.
And podcasting can mean a million different things
to a million different people.
So what do you actually a community for?
You know,
what is there actually to talk about?
Other than,
hey man, I love your show.
Listen to my show.
Hey, you should subscribe to my show.
Your show sucks, your show's great.
You know,
what's a show?
How do I do?
It's like, you know,
it just doesn't make any sense
to call it a community.
By the way,
communities in general,
I am,
I would call it more like clubs.
I don't join clubs.
I don't like clubs,
because usually,
you know, clubs are pretty much meant to be exclusive.
And even if they're completely open,
people come into the club and say something
and then it's like, well,
you don't talk that way here.
And so, you know,
immediately it's an exclusionary thing.
Samuel Johnson said in the 1700s,
there will always be a part
and always a very large part
of every community
that have no care about for themselves
and whose care for themselves
reaches little
and nothing,
if impatience of immediate pain
and eagerness for the nearest good.
And, and boy,
that really is true.
So anyway,
I knew this was going to blow up
and I didn't really follow
all the threads,
but from what I understand.
And he writes so much,
Dean Whitbread had a lot to do
with Neil and Jen just saying,
screw it.
We don't want to abuse anymore.
Just tired of it.
And,
so the reason why I called him a dick
and he still is a dick,
is he did something
that was really low-life move?
He posted,
I should probably look it up
so I don't miss quote him
because I'll be just as bad as he is.
I don't want to second watch it.
It was,
blogger.
Maybe there's blogger news.com.
Shit, I should have prepared this.
I'm sorry.
You know,
maybe I'll find you here.
which already kind of,
when you say,
when you post something on
blogger news,
crap,
I'm not finding it.
Let me see if I can,
oh,
Google,
help me out in my hour of need.
Blah,
okay,
here it is.
No, it's not blogger.
Shit.
Okay,
I can't find it.
I'll look for it.
Here's what he did.
Here's what I thought was low-life of him.
So he posted something
over at bloggernews.com,
whatever it is.
And the post said
that,
you know,
he had done some investigative work.
And it was very clear that pod show
its US operations were in trouble.
And a number of people jumped in
and said,
dude,
what are you talking about?
What are you base that on?
And he did the lowest low-life thing
that any so-called journalist can do.
He said,
oh, well,
you know,
first of all,
I have this first hand from people
who I'm not going to name.
Okay,
you don't have to name your sources.
He didn't actually,
wasn't actually able to say
what the problem was.
And then he said,
this is,
this really gets me.
If,
if none of its true,
why are you making such a big deal about it?
And that is exactly what gossip magazines do.
They'll say something,
which is completely untrue.
Regardless of whether it's true or not,
without any facts,
any backup,
any details.
And then when called upon it,
they'll say,
oh, excuse me,
you know,
if, if not of its true,
what are you making such a big deal about it?
Or as Dean would say,
what,
what do you give a jot?
And when you do that,
you're deck.
It's plain and simple.
And that's all I had to say about it,
really.
All right,
one more song before I get out of here.
Again,
from the pod save music network,
high on the pod played this week,
Al Stravinsky's one Christmas
on your daily source code.
I'm just counting the days,
counting the days.
I like the Mary's Celeste,
well,
about the mystery.
Since you abandoned me,
I'm an object I've stuck with,
without the history.
Since you deserted me,
I'm the city of trial,
I've gained a stupid wall,
with one in horse,
but no hell and a cause,
but Christmas for seasons,
if they do some day favors,
if they step out times,
I turn to the rise,
and say goodnight to no one,
to no one,
to no one who would take your love.
I've had a little weed got a sail,
but follow those own land,
and I'm too close to God,
So what? The world's getting hotter
I love to live by the sea
I'm not sure where, but it'll come to me
So be on hair creatures on earth
We'll be in the zoo
Well, I've got problem too
One Christmas for seasons
With the two Monday mornings
Respected by times I live with my head
All out of bed for nothing
For no one, for no reason
For nothing if I think you love me
So be on hair creatures on earth
All out of bed for nothing
For no one, for no reason
For nothing if I think you love me
So be on hair creatures on earth
I'm not sure where, but it'll come to me
One Christmas for Christmas
One Christmas for seasons
With the two Monday mornings
Respected by times I live with my head
All out of bed for nothing
For no one, for no one
For nothing if I think you love me
So be on hair creatures on earth
I'm not sure where, but it'll come to me
I'm just coming to me
So be on hair creatures on earth
I'm just coming to you
the blogger news network, and so we post about the Rick Haster form to close in the
15th of December. And here it is. Dixon, that would be Neil Dixon, cited reasons of having
insufficient time available to manage the forum. However, reports that all is not well in the
U.S. companies' operation continue to emerge. No link to any reports. With several notable
podcasts, there's having made an early exit. That's all presumptuous. Questions being raised
about expenditure rationale, questions where, show me a link, and low levels of revenue
share amongst pod show signies, a categorically not true if you look at the comments in the post.
Dixon has previously denied that pod show have put him under pressure to bring Brick Caster
into the expanding podcast empire. So you can kind of feel the crap that's in here. And then he
immediately hijacks the news to promote a new UK community podcast form called the National
Grid set up by the UK podcast association, which as far as I can tell is a bunch of lawyers who
want to pontificate about the world intellectual property organization. And some stupid rule they
thought that might actually happen. So that's just, that's not reporting. There's no, there's nothing
there. So it gets called on at several times in the comments. And here's what really may be
column a dick. No, but he has been falsely accusing anyone he writes. However, it is clear to see
that the UK community has effectively now been split along factional lines, which is drama queen.
It's quite reasonable to draw conclusions from the current situation. So this is what he's doing
is drawing conclusions and admitting it. This blog allows comments. Such comments are the tried and
tested way of challenging a blog post, veracity. And people are sitting there saying, hey, I'm
making money. I'm doing good. I don't know about any problems. So here comes. Why did the defense
extend into the mainly non-pod show new forum? Why the flames? If I am so far from the truth,
why the enormous fuss? So you know what? Fuck it. I'm upgrading this guy from dickhead to
ass hat. Okay. And it has nothing. Absolutely nothing to do with whether we work with him or not,
whether we work with John Clease or not. I mean, there's been so many conversations we had with
people. The stuff that didn't work out in the UK and the US. And there's no big deal. I don't talk
about it. I'll talk about one now just to give you an example. For those living in the UK,
there's a morning DJ called Bam Bam, who was on Virgin Radio. And he was fired,
a husband fired several times. He was fired before we actually started ramping up with B.T.
Pot show. He was fired from Virgin. And like, wow, this is perfect. We should see if we can get this
guy to do a show. And he was working on his own podcast, which was yet to pay for it. And so,
you know, we had several rounds of conversations with him and his partner slash agent manager.
And you know, it looked like it might be something. And then when it came down to compensation,
he was clearly looking for something that we were not willing to provide. He was looking for
I mean, we were offering a nice amount of money for him to come on board. But he wanted like a million
pounds a year, which is I'm sorry. You just not going to get that. I hope you enjoyed the coffee.
I guess it's about all you'll get from Pod Show. And that was okay, you know, and so I never
made any big fuss about him. And we parted our ways. And unfortunate. But, you know, no reason to
air out any laundry about that. And end of story. So it says nothing to do with that. This has to do
with a guy pretending to report on a story while he's hijacking a so-called community to come
over to his place. And not backing any of his claims up. And I'm quite frankly, I'm disappointed.
I'm disappointed with the with everyone who's participating in these forms. But, you know,
there's a club here. And the club is called the UK podcast. There's association. And they don't
like me. They pretend or they're civil about it. But when you really read into the boards and
you see what people are writing. Oh, man. So you guys should get over it. Really, really should.
Everyone's welcome to hang out. Have some fun. Do your own thing. Do whatever.
Just don't talk bullshit without being able to back it up. That's all I ask. What are we
adding? Now, 46 minutes. Damn it. I got to clean up the house. I got to go through the
checklist before Patricia comes home. I'll talk to y'all tomorrow. Adam at podshow.com daily source
code.com. Take care. Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT podshow
media network. Howard by podshow and limelight network. Control your part in the show at
BT podshow.com.