This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want to hear content with AdAS domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 376.
Throw your panties in the air.
It's Friday.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
We find it's always better to fire people on a Friday.
That these are statistically strong.
That there's less chance of an incident that could go into the end of the week.
So these parties are strong.
Our opening to the sets of guys.
These aren't socks.
These are some really good socks.
It's a happy day.
But I'm on a plane.
I wish we didn't shut the door.
They do it all by life.
One hundred times before.
Start as if I'm telling you scum.
Why you ain't trying to get away.
We don't have our new nation.
It's about to turn to respect both your reasons.
Don't worry, my cousin.
That type of sees on the door.
The car needs to look clear.
These are my wounds now.
It's about to turn to respect both your reasons.
It comes up to your reason.
Whew, doesn't everything sounds better with cowbell.
How do you do it?
It's Friday.
This was different from the first week I can imagine.
I don't know what it's.
Maybe because we didn't stop since last Friday.
I just kept on going through the weekend.
And we've got the weekend right in front of us.
I can smell it.
Yeah, that's going to be a good weekend.
Bank holiday here in the UK.
This is by the way coming to you from the country.
the way coming to you from the Curry Cottage. It is your daily source code. Yes, it's the
affluent suburb of Surrey known as Guilford. Bank holiday here means banks are closed and we get
Monday off. That's about all I can figure out what that means. And why do the bankers need to
day off? You know, do they really? It's probably, it's probably to delay everybody's money. That's
what it's for. Not a very nice day here. It's windy, which of course means the weather will be
changing quite a bit. Ooh, the birds are out there singing though. They're ready for spring time.
Lots of music in today's show. That first one, of course, was De La Vega. Christina would have been so
incredibly proud of me if she heard me playing that. And of course, you'd say,
yeah, I've known about those guys for two years. They're from Utah. You can find them on the
podcast music network at music.podshow.com. So nothing really too spectacular happened since we spoke
yesterday. I had a pretty long session on second life yesterday, which was cool. Oh, man, I got it.
The listeners are starting to show up in second life. And we'll talk about that later. I think I've
kind of figured out how I want to use second life in conjunction with a daily source code.
And everything else was, it was pretty routine, you know. Yeah. I mean, well, Ron was in transit.
So I knew that we wouldn't be doing our typical four, four, 30 PM. My time phone calls was usually
last the up until dinner and then typically after dinner, there's more. And so yeah, we just
kind of chilled. Patricia and I watched some TV and caught up on East Enders. And of course,
watched Boston League. I love Boston League. Wow. I wish I had lawyers like that because
I would pay because that would that would be fun, you know, we could have we could joke around
denny crane. Okay. And lots of feedback that I had left over from yesterday. We're going to go
probably about actually I promised PW trying to make it what we call a 49er, which means we're getting
two slots on the satellite window today. So for those of you checking us out on serious stars one
or two, this show will take you up until a 7 PM Eastern time. And after that, we'll we'll be joined
by the hell way. So for once, you get to hear everything. Hello, Adam. Or should I say hello, Mr.
Newman. I was fortunate enough to be down at the Builder's arms on Sunday. I was just saying
he's referring to my second life name. You can't have your real name and second life apparently.
Make sense, kind of. So you have a given last name, which is Newman, any U.M.A.N.N. Yeah, I know.
Let's spend some time talking to Patricia. I've got a question for you regarding fame.
No, what's all? What's this with all these guys talking to Patricia, man?
You know, I just said to Patricia, I said, you're getting you're getting pretty famous over here.
You know, people are digging you more than they're digging me. You better come on the show at least twice a week.
Let's see. Now, I know that you've had some pretty nasty things written about you in the past.
I wonder whether these tend to taint subsequent conversations and interviews.
No, that's very interesting. Well, you know what? The lines of blurred I'd have to say right off
the bat, the lines between what is an interview and what is someone who is media and is
isn't everybody almost media these days with email and web logs and podcasts. So I've kind of
given up on it, you know, I just talk the way I want to talk and it's actually much easier to do
interviews then because I just, I'm talking to somebody and it comes out a lot better, I think.
Now, as you heard yesterday, Patricia always keeps some things kind of to herself.
Is there a difference when some reporter is confronting you with a story that you know to be complete
fabrication and asking you questions about it as opposed to when people have been listening to
the daily source code and are talking to you as if they know you. Good question.
You know, whenever I'm interviewed by someone for publication and they start saying things like,
you know, how is your flight over, you know, around the pharaohs or if they'll say, gee, you know,
it's Patricia having fun. You know, or some little slight reference which will be dropped in,
I'm always elated. I'm so happy because, you know, there's someone who either is A,
done their homework and tried to figure out what we're doing here or B, someone who's a listener
which sometimes is even more fun. So yeah, that makes a huge difference if they're listening.
And quite honestly, I can't imagine why anyone would interview me about podcasting or any other
topic for that reason without listening to the podcast and trust me on this, it happens 99% of
the time because they've heard this information from your show. So you're questioning about it.
Well, if it's fabricated, I'd just say that bullshit. That's fabricated. Now, I've never been a pilot.
So I can't use tailwinds, but I will use a phrase that somebody else said to me recently.
Here you light up.
Here you, here you laid in. Thanks for coming to the draft and darts. I was a lot of fun.
Still jamming on it. Okay. I wanted to move the second life talk up a little bit today in the show in the program.
So let me tell you first of all about. So second life, if you're, you're listening to the show
for the first time, go to secondlife.com, download this thing, log in and see what it's all about because
it literally is something that messes with your mind if you're in it too long or if you just
all of a sudden, if you're open to it that starts messing with your mind right away.
So I sent off an email to the billing department saying, hey, I understand that if I've only been
on the system, if I've been on the system less than 45 days, there's a limit to what you can spend,
which equals $150 US, but I'd really like to spend some more and could you please look into that
form and I got a nice note back within a reasonable time frame. So they've got some good
service and good support people on the case and said, yeah, well, the problem is is that 99% of
all fraud internet and credit card fraud takes place in the first 45 days. I think what they're saying
is they want to go through one billing cycle first to make sure that, you know, I'm actually good
for it and that the account is settled, et cetera. They did refer me somewhere else. So I'm trying
to get the levels up and I pulled the, the who do you think I am dot com card? Oh, man, that's
when I got a register with GoDaddy. Who the hell do you think I am? Or don't you know who I am dot com?
So we'll see if that makes any difference, but it was so cool because I was walking around this
morning just, you know, arranging some stuff in the castle and all of a sudden I got $5,000
and linden dollars paid by Smoke Jack. And so I'm immediately I'm like, dude, you know, what's
this for? And thinking that, you know, I've got to take my pants off again, but no, he said,
no, I heard about your problems and I've been on here for about two years and here, just take this
cash and it'll tie you over. I'm like, well, okay, let's call this a loan then, all right, when I
can access funds again that I'll pay it back. I don't worry about it. So it is a loan, Smoke Jack,
but it was that was just so awesome to see that happen. You know, it blew my mind entirely.
I haven't spent any of it yet, but I've got my eye in a couple of things that I want to, I want to
complete inside the castle, because we are going to do a huge ass party. And this is,
yesterday I started to understand how I think I want to use this stuff. Yeah, it's really cool to
have podcasting and music and listening, but we were hanging out on the ground floor and I got this
great rug with all, you know, with throw pillows that you can hang out in front of the fireplace,
huge fireplace that the back wall of the ground floor of the castle. And it was me, I met this other
guy, Josh, who was, he's in the army. He comes fully dressed and combat fatigue, but he's got
some cool stuff. He gave me like a hundred music tracks that I can play. Not quite sure how that
works. Pods say for now, I mean, it's all like a metallic and some real heavy metal stuff that
he apparently goes and kills people while listening to. Okay, that's fine. I figured, let's have the
army guys on our side. So he was kind of a DJing away. Then there was two listeners, does
and Yon came in and Angie B dropped by and so we're all kind of hanging out. But when it was just
the guys, I handed out hash brownies who I'd gotten from someone else. And it was the funniest thing.
I was actually laughing out loud. It was going on as Yon and Dad's, Dad's were, you know,
putting eating these brownies and then had the trippy one, which actually is a vehicle that flies
you around and crashes into stuff. And I recorded a movie of it. Okay, it was so stupid. But it just
made me laugh. You know, it's these virtual stoneers, you know, jamming out to Metallica and
just walking around and into each other. It's hard to explain. It really is, but it's funny, man.
It just trips me out. So I think that what'll be cool is just a place to meet. You know, it's
it is literally impossible. We used to say virtually impossible, didn't we? I don't think that
applies anymore. Because it virtually is possible in virtuality. We can just hang out and, you know,
chill for a bit and chat. It's all about the chat at the end of the day. But part of the fun comes
into, you know, what new objects you have and what stuff you can share with people and new
dance moves you've picked up. And if you're really good and you can script in the scripting
language, well, then, I mean, this, of course, is who holds the true power within these virtual
worlds are the, the programmers, the developers, the scriptures. Those are the ones that really
do all the cool stuff. In fact, I got an email here. Was this from Gun for Higher?
That's a Friday since, say, oh, for sure, triple shot. Adam, about second life. If you're very bad,
apart from stopping you from accessing the game altogether, the developers have also created a
sort of prison known as the cornfield. Basically, you get stuck in a big field with nothing but an
old tractor and have to spend however much time there that the developers decide you deserve before
you return to the real world. You know what? Let's see if we can get into second life right now.
You obviously won't be able to see it, but maybe the sound effects will be worth this virtual tour
hold on. I'm just going to log in for a second. Sometimes it takes a while for it. Why is it taking
so long to boot up today? Because I'm asking for it. Is that why? Is this the watch pot never
boils syndrome? I see the little hand bouncing up and down in my dock. Not doing anything. Oh,
there we go. Probably just clearing out some caching files. Okay. Let me just connect. I'll turn
up the sound here. Oh, it connects. There we go. See if you can hear it. Oh, okay. I'm back at the
castle. What was the name of this place? The jail. Maybe we'll find it. Hold on. It's still logging in.
What it does now. It has to connect. Ah, there's the ambient sounds. Make sure I've got it all cranked
up here. There we go. Oh, that was real life, not second life. Okay. Let's see if we can find
jail. jail. Prison jail. Dungeon. Okay. What is that? Oh, that looks like a shopping area.
Okay. Let me just see quickly who's online. Oh, you know, who's who I met here? D. D. Trollup.
And in real life, D, I think I'm just going to, oh my second. You want to, you want to hear me fly?
Oh, let me, let me take you up to the roof. This is really cool. I'll take you up to the roof.
And I've got the, the Bluetooth mouth on it. Watch me teleport to my roof. Okay. I'm here.
Let's see. Oh, let me look on my, looking on my, my plant. I have a lovely marijuana plant here on the
roof whose name is Conan. Oops. There's the teleport sound. Little delayed. Oh, Conan is growing.
Looking good. See, the whole point is eventually should be able to smoke it. Let me see. Can I make
it rain? Water. Conan is in good health and has enough water. Oh, shoot. Otherwise, I could make a rainstorm.
All right. Then let me just hop into my helicopter and you'll, I'll just give you that sound effect
for a second. So I'm on the first level of the roof and now I'm jumping up to the, oops, second level.
There's Kaiser Winthorpe. I get these instant messages all the time. Okay. Let's hop in the chopper.
This is a Corske S76. And I have to start the engine first. Here we go. Okay. It should kick in just a second.
I don't know, it seems like the sound is a little delayed today. See, this is the stuff that really
blows the whole experience when that happens. No, it doesn't sound like it's working very well.
Ah, there we go. Okay. You're all aboard now. She's white with the, with yellow and orange trim.
Let's hover up a bit here. Let's just fly around here.
You don't hear much change in the pitch an hour. The sound actually I'm realizing.
Okay. I'm going to fly her back to the roof.
I can't believe I'm doing this. Like you guys really care.
Okay. Let me quit. I can always come back to that later. Let's get back to the show.
So what's really interesting is about visiting other places. Oh, so D. I was saying D. Trollip.
She's made me a pod show t-shirt. How cool is that? And she'll let me give them away to anybody. So
if you're online, look for Adam Newman, any you, a M-A-N-N, or the Curry Castle. If I'm in,
you know, come and drop by, hang out, bring some goodies, help me dress the place up because
we're going to have a killer ass, just a killer ass party. I'd say within the next couple weeks and
we'll be ready. And that's how I think for now, I'd like to be like to be using second life.
It's really just a place to meet up, to hook up with listeners of the show.
I guess that I didn't get to it. I wanted to talk about the Scientology Silent Birth Treatment,
the Tom Cruise and Katie Holmes used. Now, if you haven't, I really strongly suggest you read
Dianetics by Elron Hubbard because you hear so much mainly negative noise about Scientology.
And I know nothing about the church or the cult, but I did read Dianetics. I'm found with
to be highly entertaining and interesting and not that far out there, not, you know,
in fact, a lot of it's very, very logical. And this whole concept of keeping quiet during
birth and being careful with the unborn child and the same goes for being quiet during operations.
I buy into that, you know, your ears are open, they're not plugged up. So you got to be hearing
something and what kind of influence does that have on you when you're in an operative state?
Or if you're unborn? Ernie wrote in, says Adam, where a silent surgery makes sense,
Silent Birth or Zero Noise Birth is the full opposite and just a concoction of Hubbard's
that's not down to life at all. After the birth of my son a month ago, I and my wife had an
extended talk to our midwife and doctor about birth. This was possible as we booked those
two ladies privately for the whole birth. That's cool. It's like an escort service for unborn.
Kids. They dance for you, too. The two emitted hundreds of births together, but the most horrifying
birth they told us about was a Scientology birth. That's what they called it. Birth is all about
perfect breathing for the woman and breathing does make some noise. If you consider the circumstance
of the contractions, it is the design of nature. It helps easing the pain. Our midwife and
doctor reported that the silent birth took away longer was extremely stressful for the woman delivering
as she was of course fully concentrating on not to moan instead of directing the energy to the
right place in her body. Additional complications were coming along on top of that. Again,
birth is a lot about proper breathing. Sure enough, there's nothing against keeping a place quiet
and cozy for a birth that that part does make some sense. But hey, isn't it just all common sense?
Yeah, I totally agree. I don't know how strict that is, by the way, if the mother is not allowed
to make any noise or if the father's not allowed to make any panting noise for that reason, I mean,
Jesus, you know, it's real easy for you to start to get into the rhythm. I think I told you
when Christina was born, it was such a great vibe. It was in the operating room because she was
breech, so it was a cesarean section. And the minute she was born, when the doctor pulled this
alien out of my wife's belly, which is kind of what it reminded me at the time, but it was beautiful.
The Beatles in my life was playing, and it was, man, you just can't get it any better.
Twilight to hippie says, listen to the Charlie Herger comments on silent births and surgery
started off for some feedback. I'm a certified hypnotherapist and in hypnose school, we talk
some about this. In surgery, even if you're under anesthesia, your subconscious is still awake
and absorbing. If the surgeon says something flipping like, I'll be shocked if this bloke
ever heals up properly, then bam, that goes straight into the subconscious. Negative thoughts
affect you in negative ways. So we are taught to make recordings for our clients to listen to during
surgery. Interesting. These recordings have positive affirmations for the person things like you will
heal quickly. The surgeon performs a perfect operation. Those things will be put on the recording
and other affirmations that were specific to the person would be added as well. For birth, I think
it's similar if the delivery room is full of bad vibes that sends a negative message to the mother
into the baby who's connected to her with hypnosis. The pains of delivery can be less and in
some cases transformed into waves of sensation or relaxation. So while I don't agree with silent
births, it seems only natural for the mom to be to make noise. I do agree with what happens.
The delivery room does affect the baby subconscious. Also, what's this? I want to send you a
thank you today. When Sam and husband had to drive me to the eye doctor because I had a small
tear in my cornea. How man? How that happened? Did he slap you around? Do you just let me know?
I'll be okay, though. Antibiotic eye drops will clear up in a matter of days. But the thing is,
I have things touching my eyes phobia, which means this morning I was in full panic attack mode.
Yeah, I can understand that. On the way out of the door, I decided to grab my iPod. On the way
into town, I decided to listen to the Charlie to help calm me down. I don't know you personally
I don't but I've been a listener for months. Your voice is familiar and was quite comforting this
morning. Listening to the familiar jingles of the metro sexual moment and Trinity really helped
calm me down. Thank you Adam. The Charlie was perfect to push the panic down. Besides,
being a hypnotherapist, I'm also a telephone dominatrix. Oh, you be the good stuff always comes at
the end. So if you're interested in listening to kinky phone sex stories or liberal politics
and let's be honest, they go together, don't they? Or have you just curious sister? What two
hippies are up to in the desert? Please check out the podcast I do with my husband. No,
Twilight, let me just let me change that. I think you need to send me a dominatrix audio feedback.
Yeah, that's what I need because because I've been a very bad boy.
Good day Adam. This is Peter Bailey, a listener from Australia. Just a couple of things. I finally
got to listen to Charlie 367 this morning, which is Tuesday on my way into work. Interestingly,
I noticed that I was the only person on the train that was smiling. Although there was quite a
few other people with earphones in their ears, I wonder, does that say something about podcasting
in general or is it just me? And with reference to getting the pod show network and finally up
and running into public beta, a saying sprung to mind. It's an old project management saying.
It goes something along the lines of, there comes a time in every product's development where one
has to shoot the authors or engineers and commands production. I hope that didn't happen at
pod show. Keep up the good work mate. You've kept it at least this list. I'm pretty happy with what
you're doing. John, well mate, cool. I don't want to go to Australia. You know what? We're going to
do it. I'd say with the next two years definitely, I hope you can wait that long. Hope you still
listen to that long. So you'll buy me pints. Well, no, we don't shoot our engineers at pod show.
Only if they break their legs, you know, ten what else are you going to do? But we have kind of pulled
the trigger. We've got developers in now. As I said, we're bringing in developers first to help us out.
And create some modules and really clean the place up, I guess, to get it ready for the rest of
the world. And for those of you who have been listening to the dev cast. And of course, this is
for developers. So it's real geeky. And even if you're just interested in the geekiness of it,
you can consider yourself eligible to subscribe to the dev cast devcast.podshow.com. We're putting
in more golden tickets. So if you subscribe today, then you have a good chance even on the first show
that you'll get a golden ticket, which means you'll get credentials. You can come in. You can start
hacking away and helping us out. And we're going to do another dev cast tonight. Erano Neil
is back from her PHP or my sequel or sequel course, whatever she was doing. So I guess sometime
after dinner, I'll record that. Kevin, of course, is still back home with the family and Monday
he will be back. But I do want to get something going. We have a new past phrase. The whole
everything's all set up. We're ready to go. Andrew is a stand and buy to configure everything.
So that'll be later on tonight over at the dev cast. And some of the developers are already
checking in. Hey, Adam. Next star. Just got my ticket to the podshow plus. And I have to say,
I'm really digging it. It's really cool. I think there's so many features on there that no one
even expected. You have to say, everyone out there, when this thing comes out, it's going to be huge.
If you guys like, if you like my space and are going to the sick of how crappy it is,
this thing blows anything out there away. It's great for listening to podcasts,
great for publishing podcasts, it's great for everything. Just the podshow plus is awesome.
Keep up the great work there, podshow guys. Take care. All right. Cool, Nick. I got a look for you.
See if I can find you in podshow plus. And I'll dig you. We're doing some fun stuff. I'm really proud
of how it's shaping up and sorry, dropping the blackberry. And what's nice is if you're done any
type of development or followed along with any type of development, it's really the end where all
the stuff just, that's when it really accelerates and stuff gets pulled together and things start to,
oh, whoa, now it looks kind of like it makes sense. You know, and it's, I'm digging it for sure.
And the dashboard, the, the, the, the, the widget, formerly known as the player, now known as the
dashboard, that it is, it is changing the way you think about listening. It really is. You can build
feeds on the fly, which you listen to and you can publish and share with people. You can mix and
mash stuff together. You can set your own listening experience browsing through through new episodes.
It really, and this was all I wanted and my part of the, of the, of the spec of this because I actually
wrong drove a lot of that development. I said, I just wanted to replace iTunes. I wanted to replace
iTunes. That's all I wanted to do. And, you know, just play this stuff. Here's how I use it.
Please make it happen. Let it talk to iTunes when I want stuff on my iPod, but please just take
iTunes out of the equation and it's working. Hi, my name is Sam. I'm a person from Northern California
living in the Bay Area and I'm really happy to hear about this calm line. I think it's a, it's a great
idea. It's really just a well for me to get around to putting together an audio comment I would
never have done that otherwise, so that's a great idea. I also like the idea of making the show
around 40 minutes, that's about how long I commute every day and it's just right for my driving
to work. So, um, I'm great. Thank you. All right, Sam. Thank you very much. Yeah, a lot of people calling
in on the on the listener lines work and very well as far as I'm concerned. It's really for those
of you. I think most of you who are mobile, just if you want to, you know, record something right
then and there you want to provide feedback. That's what those phone numbers are really for. So,
put it in your mobile right now. Pre-program it. Just pre-program it is DSC. If you're in the
states, we've got that fine. Look at New Jersey number 20162563572016256357 or in the UK.
It's O2076813753. Give us a call, will you? It's nice if listeners call in too and
it's rather long comment, but it really summed up for me what listeners watch from a show, you know,
and that, believe me, this type of response is important. Hey Adam, this is Kelly from Aldi,
California. Um, just wanted to chime in now that you have the phone line which is great. I've been
listening to daily source codes since October when I got my first iPod and daily source codes
first show that I listened to and I haven't this one yet. Really enjoy it. And I wanted to let
you know why I like the show so much. It is the honesty. If you're talking about everything
is going on in your life seemingly un-sensored and just putting it out there for all of us to hear.
I love it when Patricia joins in the show, when Christina does, all the little segments,
Trinity, Metro fictional moments, the Rogers Small bit, those are actually my favorite.
I love it. This in fail, but by the way, that could not be transferred to anything else.
Love that. I like hearing about your mom and what's going on. It's just great. And last
Friday when you had that lamp, it was amazing. It could really tell that you were upset. Obviously,
I mean, you ranted for over an hour. That's a lot of outrage. And you know what's great about it?
If that had been me, I would never have done that. I can't imagine putting all of that motion out there
and sharing with the world. And you were doing that, which was amazing. And I heard another
rant, I think it was last week off. So this was Michael Butler on the Rock and Roll Indie Geekcast.
And he ranted through most of his show, we're feeding point by point just like you did,
criticisms of a fellow podcaster. And I remember the time wondering, you know, why are you doing this
much energy and time? You know, it's interesting. I heard that too. That was pretty amazing.
You should go back and listen to it. Not quite sure which episode it was, but Michael Butler
definitely went on a rampage. So when accused, yeah, it was like one of these conspiracy theory
posts somewhere that said, well, you know, based upon this action and him saying this,
it's clear, Michael Butler is ready to jump ship and leave touch. Hi, yeah, yeah, yeah, the conspiracy
theories, they run rampant. Training wheels people, we've still got training wheels on this internet
thing. So to the other thing, it just sort of keeps it going and I didn't get it. But what I was
hearing was un-censored, honest response, real emotion. And after the Richard Bluestein follow-up show
this week, which I listened to, admitting he was wrong, it all made sense in an all-came full
circle. And I thought, you know what, that was cool, but you just put the ramp out there.
And it did get the dialogue going about name calling it so forth. And I thought that was really
good. And personally, yeah, I get a fan offended by Richard or by Madge's, you see the word
kind. I feel like it's really derogatory to what he uses all around. You know, it's funny. I've heard
bricks use the word content. And it seems to be used in a different way. And I'm not offended
what it when I hear that. And it sounds more like when some people hear, use the word flag,
so anyway. But I just wanted to find a chime in and say, you have, okay, thank you very much.
I appreciate that. But you hit on something there that is quite interesting because you're wrong.
The use of the word content in the UK is probably the worst thing you could do. Now the word,
the use of the word flag on the other hand means like meatballs or some some meat dish like that.
So it just doesn't carry over. It doesn't carry the same weight. But, oh, man, the sea word,
Kant. Oh, you call someone that. And, you know, you better be bigger than another person.
It's just one of the many, many, many differences between languages and cultures
of the United Kingdom and the United States. And I think it's worth exploring this some more since
I'm in both places. If you've got any ideas about that, send it to me. We'll just call it in on the
listener line. You know what? I like this idea so much. We've got a song about a word from our
spine here. It's the yanks versus the brits. We'll drive each other crazy, but everybody knows
that it's apparent to see. That just like you and me, it's the yanks and the brits. The yanks
versus the brits. Mind the gap. Just myth that at once again. So let's talk about this.
The difference between the yanks and the brits. You know, we we breached on that. We breached.
We broached that yesterday. Just briefly as we talked about how easy I found it to flirt with
English women. Of course Patricia Meatley put my in place and said, no, that's all in your head.
There's nothing at all going on like that. Time for some more Friday festivities.
It's not pot safe. I don't believe, but man does it.
See these. I don't make it any harder. We say it and be threes about what you should
for free. I ain't gonna have to pay. And all your bullshit is why the fuck I say.
I have to give a sin and give a sin. I'll see you in the comments like a digital pin.
All for the DCA. Well, like pirates. We'll get our shit for free.
For rental advisory. You'll never fucking see. Been a couple years since I seen that FBI.
I want to cut it out because that shit is mad boring.
I'm fucking bummer than the bitch from bad boys. Except for the band and it's grandma's sex toys.
I'm a Disney. Feelin' on my drives. Don't wanna disobey it when the lawsuit arrives.
All you fucking dudes. Don't sound on the balls. Then when you get done, you run a mix and coals.
I better see some pages what sound to fight. You ain't gonna manage my digital rights.
Like criminals, pants filled up with music nerd and I'm most buying off standard left and right.
My full dozen count in this fucking fight. With a 56k head hundreds of songs.
God is my tension like asses and clocks. Now it's getting so illegal kind of tension.
If I get caught, I'm joined in the convict. What you heard? What's all this game?
It's the intro board. What I'm in a band.
I'm fucking bummer for the Disney. Fuck it and be double-aid.
Fuck it and ride double-aid.
Fuck the suit, find it, be assay.
I'm fucking bummer for the Disney.
Man, let me tell you. The other day.
All right, hey, hey. They tried to kiss me, man. Then they turned around and tried to fuck me in the ass.
Who's not a fuck as that sold us out? Like Judas did to Jesus.
For some money. Some little coins is shit. What the fuck?
Fuck it and be double-aid.
Gee, wonder what the title that song was.
Aha. Okay, that was definitely different.
Fuck the MPA and the RIA. This was sent to me via email,
came in as a bit torn hotel choral Essex. It's a whole collection, 15 songs of some internet related stuff.
It's more of that, actually. But it's pretty cool. I liked it very much.
And thought I'd share that with you for this Friday as we get ready for the weekend with a
little bit of Trinity.
Yep, it seems like we're really picking up some steam with all this biodesal stuff.
I got a couple of very interesting links in the first one from Bruce Moile about
pizza delivery cars from glass nickel pizza company. Let's see where they
they drive their delivery vehicles. It looks like they have a couple of golf
diesels, Volkswagen golfs. No, that's a polo. Is that a polo?
Yeah, I think it's a one of it is a golf, let me see.
So they've four of them. And they're using recycled vegetable oil. Very, very cool.
You see where these guys locate it on store locations.
This is in Wisconsin. Okay. Excellent. So if you want to support biodesal in Wisconsin,
there you go. Thank you very much, Bruce. Appreciate that.
A couple of people sent me this link about Darrell Hanna's, I guess she had a television show
called Love Life, DH Love Life. And it's now available as a podcast.
I'm not sure if they're doing one episode at a time. I did subscribe to it, but I haven't
looked at iTunes for a while, so I'm not sure how many episodes have come in, but the first one,
the first video is about biodesal. If you haven't seen it, check it out at DHLoveLife.com.
And I'd love to get, there's nothing on the site that explains why it's a podcast or
you know, what Darrell Hanna is, if she's directing involved in the podcast portion,
looks like a rehash of what they did on television, but still digging that.
Huh. And Alan Solomon sent me a checklist. I said, I've known about this McDonald's truck
that I see once a week on my morning commute for quite a while. Today, I finally got a picture for
you. In the process, I nearly missed my tram, so I hope you mentioned it on the show.
That's Alan from Basel in Switzerland, and he has this fantastic picture, which of course,
if you don't mind, I'll put it on my flicker page so that you don't get crushed with
bandwidth. I'll credit you appropriately, but it's a picture of McDonald's biodiesel power truck
fantastic. By the way, says Alan, I bought my domain name using one of Darrell's Go Daddy codes.
Cool. I got to tell you what the domain name was. And then finally, this is the one that got
a lot of press. A lot of people were talking about this. It got digs. It got mentioned on wire.
It got slash dotted. This is a tiny reactor that boosts biodiesel production.
And there was a cordon here that I wanted to share with you. Let me see if I can find it. Here it is.
Who's this guy? Mr. Janabek. I think he's from the Oregon Nano Science and Micro Technologies
says if we're successful with this, he says nobody will ever make biodiesel any other way.
Apparently, this reactor is the size of a credit card pumps vegetable oil and alcohol through
tiny parallel channels. It's smaller than a human hair to convert the oil into biodiesel almost instantly.
All right, Batman, that would be that would be outrageous. Cool. If we had to
imagine that, what a revolution that will be. Definitely, I'll put the link that article in the
show notes as well at credit.com and dailysourceco.com. Keep your eye on it because sometimes with
big discoveries like these that really disrupt industries, you never hear from the inventors again.
I've boring meeting. I've boring manager Robb. Rocks ain't code mom. He's very diligent,
but it's out for the stick. His code not function or elegant, what the code must be think.
Code mucky think. Baby manager, what a right god damn login page himself.
Food mucky not say it. I'm loud code mucky not crazy. Just proud of code mucky like
videos. Code mucky like to have a mouth too. Code mucky very simple math.
It's not too big or bloody secret art. Code mucky like you. Code mucky like you.
Code mucky like you. Code mucky like you. Code mucky like you. Code mucky like you.
Code mucky like you. Code mucky like you. Code mucky like you.
The lights
Code, but we have every reason to get out of this place
Code, but we just keep on working
Sears are pretty face
But try to throw a wake up either coffee cake
Take past it now
This job will fit a link and create a way
Such a load of crap
Code, monkey, thanks
Some day, eat out, everything
Even, pretty girl like you
Code, but we just win
For now, code, monkey, say some day
Don't hide our code, monkey, like we do
Code, but we like to have an opportunity
Code, but we have every reason to get out of this place
Code, but we have more money secret art
Code, but we like to do
Just screaming for cowbells
So make sure the guys and gals
A pod show are parting along with us on this Friday
Code, monkey, Jonathan Colton on the source code
Hi Adam, this is Gary from New Jersey
I thought I'd just listen listening to your latest
DSC and I thought I'd leave a message
I listened to it every day
It's my morning commute
Music, I guess
And I really enjoy listening to it
And it really makes the hour commute that I have
Go very quickly
I have a long commute to Princeton
And it's not an easy commute and listening to the DSC
Really helps
I too would like to see daily podcasts from you
And really think that you do a great job
It's a nice mixture of
Not just techy things, which I listen to as well
But it's a nice mix of entertainment
Along with technical discussions
Which I enjoy
Anyway, I thought I'd leave a message for you
And just say, keep up the good work
I really enjoy listening to your show and take care
All right Gary, thank you
That I know that commute to Princeton
That can be a bitch dude for sure
And yeah, I appreciate you making me a part of your daily routine
That's what that's what seems to work the best
Is if you kind of slip into a slot with
And everybody's daily routine
For some people on the west coast
I'm there 10 o'clock
And they actually take a break and just listen to the show
On the computer for others that's during your commute
So trying to keep it within the
Yeah within that 40 to 50 minute range
Definitely what what I'm striving for
That's for sure
And it seems to be the trick
You know to get people into
Or to get into someone's daily routine
And I can understand when things are
You know, turn out different during my daily routine
I get kind of bummed out too
I got to reconfigure myself
I got to do this a little bit differently
Oh no, he's later than normal
But you know he's here for a reason
You sound like repair man coming after you
You sound like repair man
What's he gonna do
He'll fit your misconceptions
And answer questions too
Turn nothing in the universe
And he can't move for you
You sound like repair man
Hey
Those of you listening to the show on Sirius stars 102
You know what that means
If not
It means you're about to stop listening to me
It's the end of the source code
The satellite window for for today and for this week
Of course we back on Monday
Pacific Coast Hellway is next
Yeast radio after that Dawn and Drew
And then tonight the Frank Truth with Brian Know
It's a podcast we can't air on podcasts
Because of the rights issues
But she got it here that it's a great show
That'll be at 9.930 East Coast
Follow by the Rock and Roll geek from 930 to 10
Again, have yourselves a great weekend
And I'll see you all on Monday
And for those of us still here
Just a couple more things I want to share with you
Hi Adam Curry
I just wanted to say that this voice feedback
Over a phone-in voice mailboxes
Or sent as email attachments
It's not even 1% as good
As real
Radio-phone-in
Because this podcasting voice feedback
It's not interactive
Once upon a time I have met in person
Chris Perillo
A guy who now lives in Seattle
Maybe you have had about him
Have you?
Well, under www.ChrisperilloShow.com
You can see example
How podcasting voice feedback should be done
Namely with live
Phone-in with full interactivity
And not with stupid recordings
What do you think about it
Adam and Adam see
Maybe you should establish
Once a week a live phone-in
Times when you are answering live phone calls
PS
Getting Patricia Pie on DSC
We'll not replay
We'll not replace real
Interactivity with listeners
Nothing will
So
Fuck you Adam Curry
And fuck your blackberry
Hahaha
I'm like, fuck my blackberry
I'll tell you what
Yeah, you may be right about Patricia there
But she's, oh man
The sex is much better with her
Than with the listeners
I can't be interactive with
And regarding the live phone-in
You know, I thought about that
And while it will work very well
For some people maybe but for me
I don't know it
I like talking to someone on Skype
Maybe once in a while
But I'm going to start
Exploring that with the devcast. podshow.com
But thank you very much for chiming in
And letting us know
Yes ladies and gentlemen
He is
Where are we?
He's the man
Saving the European Union single hand
Comic strip
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do
We're our flank
We believe in an internet
That's safe from viruses and scammers
We're our flank
We believe your personal information
To be just that
Personal
And we believe your internet
Should be a friend
Not a fo
We're our flank
Make this smart choice
Visit earthlink.net
And discover what our internet experts
Can do for you
Earthlink
We revolve around you
What's happened in friends
This is Marcus couch host
Of the scenes scene
And podshow music rewind
And hey, I've just logged into the
PDF and the podcast delivery network
And I'm starting to get acquainted
With the newly developed player
And the interface
And I've got to say
The folks over at podshow hq
Have really done a bang-up job
And this new
I don't like that you could call it
The portal of podcasting
And the player impresses me
The most. It's playing all the audio files
It's playing just about every movie
File I've been able to throw at it
Very, very impressive feature
But until that golden ticket
Is bestowed upon your earbuds
You can check out one of the feature shows
On PDF
And that would be my show The scenes scene
If you're into the heavy side of rock and metal
The scenes scene is the show for you
You can check it out at
The scenes scene.com
And in other news
Podshow music rewind
Number 30 has just been released
For those of you not familiar with rewind
It's a weekly podcast
It's a compilation of many music podcasts
And they're all blended together
In a multi-style mix of
Podsafe and independent music
And if you're looking for great suggestions
For podsafe music on your own podcast
You should definitely be listening
And subscribing to podshow music rewind
And we're happily accepting submissions
For inclusion in podshow music rewind
So if you've got your own music podcast
You can head on over to rewind.podshow.com
Click on the submission link
And that will give you all the details
On how you can participate
And get your own little piece
Of the serious satellite window
I'll talk to you again next week
Take care everybody
Hey Adam
This is Barbara in Palo Alto
I know you're probably getting tired of hearing this
But you haven't inspired me to start my own podcast
I have an iPod consulting business here in town
Where, among other things
I help people learn about and listen to podcast
A few months ago I had the brilliant idea
Of creating a podcast
About my adopted hometown
Palo Alto California
My ideas for this to be a weekly show
With a mix of useful information
Happenings around town
And whenever possible, historical perspectives
Palo Alto
Then around the town
Palo Alto 360
I believe podcaching will be a great way
For members of the Palo Alto community
To share stories, reflections
And items of public interest with each other and beyond
But I need your help pod father
I don't want to show just to be Palo Alto according to me
I'd like to include different voices and perspectives
Preferably from people who are already familiar with podcasting
Or satellite radio
And what better place to do a little social networking then on the Charlie
So, Adam
To the Palo Alto people in your audience who would like to do some field reporting
Or even just suggest topics for the show
Please send email to pa podcaster and gmail.com
Or visit the website
Palo Alto360.com
And for all the Stanford people
Or other neighbors who might be listening
I want with anybody who used to live here
Or is just curious about Palo Alto
Please let me know what topics or features
Would make you want to subscribe to the Palo Alto 360 podcast
Thank you, pod father
In A, let me know the next time you're in town
And I'll treat you to an ice cream soda
At that place you visited last May
And we met at a place in downtown Palo Alto
Is it downtown, I guess?
Yeah, called the, was it the creamery?
Yes, it is downtown
But that's okay
You just tell me when
And I'll make sure you and Trinity can find it
Thanks again Adam
Okay
Nope, my pleasure entirely
Okay, a little bit over my, my 55
We've been at maximum mark there
Let's wind it up at one more pod save tune for the weekend
What do you say?
Want some pills?
Victory season on the chart
When the walls come from land
Any world comes crashing down
You forget your problems
What a new friend's come up
Cut you kill at them dead home
But they won't let you out
And you need them to let out
Take one of them and take one
Get it all out
How do you understand that
Never is on and on
So you're a friend's tell you
You forgotten who you are
Yet you know you feel it
But you already come to the front
Cause you can't let them down
But they won't let you out
And you need them to let out
Take one of them and take one
Get it all out
How do you understand that
Never is on and on
So you're a friend's tell you
You forget your problems
What a new friend's come up
And they won't let you out
Don't say it's not your problem
Don't say it's not back to this one
Don't say you've got a hammer
You'll last come on and on
Don't say it's not your problem
Don't say it's not back to this one
Don't say you've got a hammer
You're not with it's not just far from home
But with the time as you rewind your mind
To the days when I've been hurt you
But it just let you out and it's not
So take one of them and take one
Get it all out
How do you understand that
Never is on and on
So you're a friend's tell you
You forget your problems
What a new friend's come up
Honestly, I don't even know that's from the podcast music never
I have no idea where I got that but I liked it
Victory season pills winding up the Charlie for this week
winding up a fine Friday
And the sun just came out so it's perfect
I'm going to go walk on the downs with the
Ports of the show also sponsored by AccuView
Check out Heather and John L's podcast
Tell your kids about it at download.accu.com
And I'm a real goof and you'll digs
And thank you very much for reminding me that
If you want the really great deal on a go daddy domain name
$695 which is only like
$3.5
Maybe even less
If you want a good deal check out with code
DSC3 not DSC1 as I've been saying all week
Dell the share Charlie three is your checkout code and you get it for
$695
Stay in home this weekend
I'm going to be total around with the girls
We're going to do a little bit of shopping
And I'll have I'm sure I'll have plenty to report on Monday
See you back here on Monday
Thanks for subscribing
Thanks for listening everybody
Adam Curry dot com
DailySource code dot com
And feel free to knock on the door
The castle in second life
Another pod show pod cast
Stick it in your ear
Get this pod cast and more great ones like it
On the high performance pod cast a library network from pod
Joe and limelight networks
I love it