The town of Shadow Falls holds a secret some more kill to protect, and others will die to expose.
He's here, and might have didn't know.
Swordle?
I'm the one that killed him.
Be monks to choose an initiative for support.com.
This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
The show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy!
Number 4-4-8 of the Charlie.
The Chacha.
Ta-ta-ta.
Ah!
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky drinks, man.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
The casting is that of curry.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe it
I think I'm about to over time, I go crazy and I don't know why and I can't believe
And I could try to give you all but it's no use, no, I don't know, I can't believe
And I could try to give you all but it's no use, no, I don't know why and I don't know why
And I could try to give you all but it's no use, no, I don't know why
And I could try to give you all but it's no, I don't know, I can't believe
I'm not quite sure who she is but paper Rogers sounds even better with cowbell
Actually
Excuse me, how are you doing everybody?
Paper Rogers played that from the pod save music that we can't believe
Just added to the PMN link in the show notes at dailysourceco.com
She's from the UK, interesting, it's from the bio growing up in a music loving family
Paper was surrounded by a range of musical influences hearing everything from the Beatles to the incredible string band to Pink Floyd
But it was always the strong female voice that caught her attention, well indeed
Hey everybody, it's the dailysourceco coming to you from Curry Cottage in the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Guildford
Great show lined up for you all kinds of cool stuff you guys have sent in to share
And you know when you come to class, we want you to share it in my ever ending quest
My never ending, I never ending quest
To maintain the 42 year old gloody as maximum as known as my ass
As you know, Amy Mac of the fitness attack podcast has been kind enough to keep me in check with yet another assercise
Amy Mac, do it for me
Save Adam's ass
Hey Adam, it's Amy Mac
Who you made it to week four
Last week was a little complicated, so I decided to do an easy one this week
You will need a wall though
Oh, hold on a second, let me
Alright, you're back against the wall
Feed out in front of you
Now you're gonna slide down the wall until your knees are at a 90 degree angle
This means that your knees cannot come over your toes
So adjust those feet out away from the wall accordingly
Great, now hold it
How much longer?
You should feel it in your legs and butt
Make sure your arms are either at your side or straight out in front of you
You cannot use them to help hold you up
Okay, that was 20 seconds, now come back up
Deep breaths and slide down again
Again
Make sure your feet are out far enough
Yeah, look a bit hurting
On the other side
I have to wait
How long?
To find out more health and fitness case or to subscribe
Check out the fitness attack podcast
At fitness.potshow.com
Alright Adam, you'll slide back up
Oh, I see this week wasn't so bad
That went pretty quick
Until next time
Oh Amy, thank you
Mr. Amy, can you hurt me some more please
I felt it wasn't so much of my asses
It was right by my knees
Oh man, they got hot
Oh man
Assercise
We should do this as we should spin this off and do a separate show Amy
I hope you're doing that
Don't we do we have an acercise.potshow.com
We need it
Oh, I always need to
Take a deep breath
Acercise brought to you by Accur
Check out their target cast about the AccurRDX
At Accur.potshow.com
Cranky
I have absolutely no condition
Yesterday, Patricia, now we're talking
As we were talking actually in the show yesterday
A KLM aircraft returned
It was on its way to Mumbai
And over Germany decided to return to Skipple Airport in Amsterdam
And it was very unclear as to exactly what was going on
Well, today I, of course, scanned all the new stories
Oh, so on breath
This is embarrassing
So I scanned all the new stories today
Apparently, now this was a flight to India
So I guess you can imagine
There could have been all kinds of people
Who might have looked like terrorists on that flight
Now this is from I witness accounts
And I'm just translating stuff directly from Dutch
Cause I haven't seen any of these reports
Translated in English anywhere yet
If I do, I'll put it in the show notes
Of course, they will source code.com
So they were about to 12 passengers
Who after take off were playing around with cell phones
Passing them back and forth
And people got really worried
Apparently, there were also three U.S. mind
You, sky marshals onboard the flight
And so it's a little unclear to exactly what happened
But the sky marshals basically took over
Command of the cabin
From the flight attendants
And at that point, I presume that they told the cockpit
They should, at the pilot and copilot
Should return back to Schipel Airport
Now, no sooner had this hit the news wires
Then I started to receive all kinds of interesting audio
In fact, I have here the audio of flight northwest 42
Talking to Schipel Tower about returning
And you'll hear some very distinct words in here
As Dutch military starts talking to the F-16 fighter jets
Talking about a scramble A or A scramble
Or scramble Deg
Anyway, listen to this
I'll translate along with you
Do that to 6-0, I'll send it to 7-0
Okay, so that's just regular traffic
We'll see what's coming now
Okay, so that's the captain of the flight northwest 42
Saying you want to touch down around 30 minutes past the hour
Okay, so what he said there is there still
Working on an escort once that they have landed and are going to be taxing
And he was going to get back to the pilot with more information
Thank you very much
Hello, sir
Good morning sir
The reporter told you are requesting whether you would like any
Flyer departments on the runway
I know sir
Okay, so in case you couldn't hear that
The authorities were requesting if northwest 42 wanted any
Fire department or any other kind of facilities on the runway
one way you heard the answer, no sir.
Nice, that was derivative about.
Now, now we go to Dutch military.
Okay, so I don't think there was an actual scramble of airplanes on the ground.
I think that they might have actually been in the air if I'm hearing this.
It sounds like she's already giving them flight level instructions.
Or she's giving them flight level instructions for when they scramble.
Okay, so they were already in the air and she's giving them instructions on where to intercept the north-west airlines.
Was it DC-10? Yeah, I think it was DC-10.
Okay, so no, so that's where she's telling me exactly where to find the aircraft.
Any get to speak to sub-point-five?
We came in from the east, possibly a quenter, and now to flying overhead, I shall be at left-back seat.
Right, and so then they had to drop carousine, etc.
So it was kind of cool to hear that. It came in so fast.
I was actually thinking of posting the audio yesterday, but I was like,
Yeah, obviously for the daily source code.
We probably would have known what would have happened.
So I guess it sounds like there apparently there are 12 people in custody.
But I don't know if this, you know, people play with cell phones all the time.
The heck knows what's going on.
Scotch on the rocks presents Whitney Steel Live of Lance.
What do you think you know me?
Sunlight told me I'd be a lady.
We need joins Lance and studio again to share her new news.
It can take your calls.
Whenever new, except for me and you,
you said no one ever will, and told me not to tell.
Call in and talk to Whitney Live, Saturday, August 26, 6 p.m. Pacific Time.
Hey, your lines show your face, but like it's for me.
Go to Scotch-dashrock.com for more information.
Whitney Steel Live in studio Saturday, August 26, 6 p.m. Pacific Time.
What are the websites, Scotch-dashrocks for more information on Whitney Steel Live?
I don't know about the name Steel.
It sounds like such a radio-chick name, you know?
It's always Whitney Steel.
We days on Z-100.
Janet Steel, overnight's.
She's the record love goddess.
She's Whitney Steel.
Now, check my Scotch-dashrocks.
I cannot believe the feedback I'm getting about this.
It's become an official controversy about me jokingly or not.
Apparently asking for naked pictures from Carmen Tyler.
You've probably heard E-Band checking yesterday saying that I was going to go,
I was not going to pass past go.
I was going straight to hell over doing this.
And you know, and Patricia and I joked about it.
I know E-Band was joking too.
But now people are starting to take this pretty serious.
Seriously?
Pretty seriously.
Kevin Reeves, who I've played many times on this podcast,
checks in in the debate.
Hey, Adam, how are we going?
This is Kevin Reeves from Nashville.
And I just wanted to continue some dialogue here regarding the naked pictures
and Carmen Tyler.
You know, the guy that sent that message in today was being funny.
And you know, said some things.
You know, regarding three things with Amy Grant, which.
Yeah, well, you know, we didn't even dwell on that.
But I wouldn't mind a three-some with Amy Grant.
I can visualize that.
A lot on some pretty interesting visual images.
But I don't think he communicated it in a way that really, you know,
illustrated the point that we're dealing with.
And it's not like an issue of somebody's soul.
I think it's more an issue of like respect for people's personal values.
Now, before I go any further, I'm on your side as far as, you know,
kind of liberal, you know, enjoy the whole ear and say things like shit, piss, fuck,
and, you know, such thing.
We're bad.
As one who used to be involved in the search and kind of rebel against the dude
and the legalism that I couldn't deal with.
So, you know what's coming here.
And I'm just not going to accept this.
That because someone believes in God or is a Christian that I can't,
we can't talk about naked bodies and naked pictures.
And sex, come on.
That makes no sense.
I'm not saying anything about God.
I'm just determined to have someone, whoever it is listening to this show,
finally send me a naked picture.
A proper one.
That's all.
How long have I been asking?
It's a matter of respect.
So, let me break it down.
Dude, hold on a second.
I got huge amounts of respect for Carmen Tyler.
Oh, please.
Huge amounts of respect.
I think I showed that all the time.
I'm just asking for a naked picture.
I'm a road of a keyword player for country paths and rock paths.
Anything goes most of the time.
And you say a bunch of crazy shit that, you know,
turning people's hair gray.
Right.
But I also do a lot of work with gospel artists and CCM artists
because it is a genre of need that I am familiar with
and that is part of my skill set.
And none of that stuff would fly.
Yeah, but dude, if you said to any one of them, hey, you know,
I'd like a naked picture.
Well, they got it.
This is not blasphemy.
They'd probably look at you go like, what are you talking about, son?
What in blaze are you talking about?
But, you know, would they be offended?
Well, that depends on your relationship.
You know, I'm a Carla or not.
Carla.
Carmen and I have been communicating for a long time now back and forth.
You know, and she's got plenty of sexy pictures on her website.
And you should see, she's got this really sheer dress on.
On her, my space page.
Come on.
Let's get a little bit of sense of humor here.
You know, what do you guys worried?
If Carmen doesn't like it, then she'll tell me.
Um, not because people are prudish or this or that.
It's just that's where their personal values are added.
And if I just started going off and saying crazy shit,
um, I'd never get hired.
Yes, I do.
I don't need to get hired by Carmen Tyler.
I don't need to get hired.
Just with naked pictures.
I would not have the respect as a musician that I have with them.
I'm not being safe.
I'm just, you know, knowing when is a good time to say certain things.
Right.
Okay.
So I guess there's no good time.
If someone is Christian or believes in God, is there a good, just answer me this?
Is there a good time to ask for naked pictures?
I think the same thing goes with these naked pictures.
You know, a lot of people on the Charlie that if you said that,
they would either comply.
Ah, but no, my friend.
No, that's not true.
I just received a picture of Michelle's sister from whispered pearls.
But, you know, it was like a glamorous.
I'm looking for the raw webcam, grainy stuff.
Oh, they would laugh it off and kind of think with their heads.
Lucky I'm not sending these naked pictures.
But it would all be in fun.
You know, I can't wait until people start sending video in
for a perversion for profit, which is my, my video podcast.
PFP dot pod show dot com.
That's pop of fucks.
dot pod show dot com perversion for profit.
Send in your grainy webcam shots, please.
I don't know where Carmen Tyler is coming from on this.
But it sounds to me like, heard the meaner on stage.
And it gives her a lot of stuff that's on the team.
And she's a very, I don't, I don't, I don't want to say refined person.
But I think has a set of values that might not go along with wanting to send
you naked pictures.
And I don't know if she would find it funny.
I think she, and it's, again, I'm assuming.
But I'm wondering if it's more of a, where she would feel
taking a back in a little uncomfortable.
Yeah, she'd cut off there.
That's too bad, Kevin, because you were on it.
You want to tear there, my friend.
Sorry, you know, if Carmen has a problem with it,
then, uh, Garmin will tell me.
I think this is just another example of political correctness
that has gone a mock in the United States of America.
Come on, guys.
You know, you're presuming all these things.
You have no idea.
Carmen's a beast.
I'm sure of it.
Hi, Adam Bryan here from Portland.
Just listening to your rant on the naked pictures thing.
This country, I don't know.
It's getting really kind of scary.
I was working at a thing the other day.
Uh, what it was talking about, uh, populations and how many of those populations
believed in evolution versus, uh, some other form of whatever.
And the United States is, like, second to last, as far as, uh,
people who believe in evolution have to be 50%.
But still, it's, it beat out Turkey.
Everybody else in the world thinks evolution is, like,
pretty much the way probably, you know, it worked out.
Well, I'm not at all surprised that there are people who think that somehow naked pictures
agree with, with some kind of immorality.
But it's like, uh, I understand your angst.
It's just disgusting.
Anyway, thanks for their chill.
And I'm still a folder, not the way to fight.
Of course you're a folder.
You know, I'm with the folders.
I'm quite sure that a lot of the evil in the world come from scrunchers.
Look at, uh, just look at your favorite, uh, head of state.
Wherever you live, wherever you're listening.
And think to yourself, does that guy, or does that lady?
Because there's plenty of leaders of state who are women.
Thank goodness.
But you know they're going to be scrunchers.
A lot of them have got to be scrunchers.
Just scrunch, do your business.
I think scrunchers may be responsible for a lot of the problems in the world.
I'm, I'm not, basically, it's not any scientific evidence.
Just a hunch.
But as you know, we're tracking it, keep letting me know.
When you call in, by the way, to the voice mail numbers.
Plus one two zero one six two five six three five seven.
Get out yourself.
Punch the number in now so you can store it.
So if you come up with a thought for later on, plus one two zero one six two five six three five seven.
It's on the show notes in London.
O two o seven six eight one three seven five three.
See how much time do I have before the satellite window closes?
Um, crap.
I'm not going to be able to do that.
Let me see.
Oh, yeah.
Boy, I really miscommunicated something the other day when Christine called in.
I understood I think what she was asking for about, you know, is there a way when you listen to a podcast or watch a podcast I presume?
After you close everything out to have.
And what she meant was the web browser version.
To have that actually remember where you were when you were playing that.
So as an example, any player that is embedded into.
Excuse me.
Sensei.
Well, when brought you by go daddy.
Use check out code DS three DSC three for your domain for the first year for $6.95.
Um, the heck was I talking about?
Yeah.
So any player that pops up into a web browser, you know,
whether it's a YouTube or garage band or pod show.
You name it anywhere podcast alley and anything with the web browser.
It pretty much can't remember where you were.
And of course, tons of people called in and said, oh, well, you know,
iTunes does it.
Yeah, of course, I understand iTunes does it.
But the question was very specific.
It was about the possibility of a web browser base player that actually could remember that on your computer,
where you where you left off playing.
And I don't think it's very simple technically speaking.
So I hope I've explained it a little bit better.
Serious stars one or two is what you're listening to.
If you're hearing the show on the serious satellite network.
It's Thursday.
So we've got Scott Siggler at the end of the evening.
I'm just going to work backwards.
So you know what's coming towards you.
East radio, email girl talk with Martina Butler.
Digital flots in another episode of The Flotsam Tonight.
Soccer girl incorporated Dawn and Drew right after Pacific Coast.
I'm going to say Mark Yoshimaru and him cough.
Bring you his stuff.
Shit, as he calls it.
That's an XPCH.
And I'll talk to you guys tomorrow for the Friday edition of the Charlie.
Speaking of bad communication skills.
So I told you about my broken indicated air speed indicator.
My broken indicated air speed by broken air speed indicator.
That's been mangled.
I said something really stupid the other day when I was explaining that concept.
A couple of people picked up on it here.
Listen to this.
Hi Adam.
It's Andrew from the Geek Farm Life podcast.
I'm a way back home from lunch.
I listened to the SC445 and yeah.
By turning away lunch hours.
A good lunch hour.
I went out to the airport.
Jumped in my long easy.
Which is a fixed moon plane.
And went flying.
Now.
So anyway.
Great lunch hour.
Up with the cloud.
It's had a beautiful time.
Let's come back.
Listening to the SC445.
We were talking about your broken air speed indicator.
And you're about nine minutes in.
You're talking about how if you've had a headwind on the ground.
The aircraft would show.
Would list off that.
Say.
Fifty knots.
The most of sixty knots.
That's.
It's completely wrong.
You're confusing.
Ground speed indicated air speed.
The indicated air speed will always show.
What the aircraft feels as the wind flowing over us.
Or is the air flowing over the wind.
All right.
Foreigners are the wing.
So if you.
If the air speed's indicating sixty knots.
It doesn't matter.
What your ground speed is.
Your plane doesn't really care.
If it's sixty knots or sixty knots.
No matter.
Any other speed.
And your craft will always perform the same.
So if you're high altitude.
With a really high density altitude.
Sixty knots.
It's still sixty knots.
And air plane will still fly the same.
I would disagree.
But your decision to take off.
With the broken air speed indicator.
But nonetheless.
You should really review.
How air speed.
Publicated air speed.
Two air speed.
Ground speed.
All right.
You know.
Relate to each other.
And I really recommend a podcast called the finer points by Jason Miller.
He's out in the San Francisco Bay area.
And I'm sure he did a podcast.
Exactly about this topic.
Just a little while ago.
And I really suggest you to check it out and review it.
Because this is something that's very important.
And understanding that it's a between.
You know.
Especially what indicated air speed and what air speed indicator shows you.
It's been a pleasure.
Thanks a lot.
Deal with.
Yeah.
Of course.
Now I'll tell you exactly what happened.
I couldn't believe I said that when you point it.
A couple people pointed that out.
You know what happened is.
I had already firmly embedded into my head.
The next time I get into this aircraft.
I have to deduct 10 knots from whatever the indicated.
I see now I'm messing it up already.
I was going to put stickers.
That's what I was going to do.
I was going to put stickers on the air speed indicator.
So there would be absolutely no confusion.
Because I still got to fly it somewhere.
It's not a.
Yeah.
It's a technical issue.
But at least it's a consistent one.
And we know why it happened.
Which also is the entire reason why I knew it was safe to.
Safe to take off.
There was expectation that the air speed indicator might not work properly.
We done our engine run ups and checks.
The proper bin cycle that's a constant speed propeller.
So we knew that that was functioning properly.
So when you look at your your your your pressure your RPM your manifold.
You know that you're you're going okay.
And when this and when this when the plane starts to take off and it's indicating.
49 or 50 knots.
You know.
Which by the way is just a little bit under the.
The stall speed as per the manual.
And it's taken off.
You know, there's a quick calculation is to what's going on.
So I still could have aborted at any time.
But the decision was split split second.
And it was a it was a fine one.
So I will stand by that.
But I totally messed it up.
Of course you're absolutely right.
Um.
My explanation really blew.
So the only thing that I have to remember, which I'll sticker.
And not you know, there's a new one on order.
And I really appreciate what you're saying.
But you're absolutely right.
It's the the ground speed.
That would that would differ significantly with with the headwind.
But not the indicated air speed.
And of course 60 knots is 60 knots worth of air flowing over your wings.
And you'll get airborne, which of course is also what told me that.
Something was wrong with my heartbeat indicator because I got airborne.
What is all this talk on the daily source code about aviation.
And actually do for you.
Hey, Adam, it's Dean and so to go for you.
The thing that DSC for four or five and you're talking about all the conversations you've had about being a pilot and all the detail you go into.
And I think it's really great because you're never really sure when you're going to be on an airplane and the pilot and the co piloter.
I was going to have the fish.
So where's this kind of come out and say hey anybody know how to fly?
And I'm going to say that all the inner whatever.
But unless you're the daily source code, I can do it.
So it's important that you do these things.
Thanks for just everything you do.
Fly.
You got to be a folder.
That's typical folder behavior.
Of course.
Hey, I'm not licensed, but yeah, I do actually know how to fly.
Thanks to the daily source code.
You just imagine that.
You got a couple of authorities that checking on the show once in a while.
Com extra blogger our European Union authority.
And boy, he was right about about the influx of about the discussion in the United Kingdom about the influx of immigrants when was it two more countries are joining the EU in 2007.
All right, forget which ones they are.
But there's a lot of talk now about you know, should we decide who can come in from where and you know, so CSB is pretty much.
You know, he has this finger on the pulse of what's happening.
We have Uncle Jesse the satellite repair man, PW Fenton, who always always has something to say.
I'm surprised he hasn't checked in yet with something about that whole moon landing debate, even though it's kind of over.
And then there's, and then there's our buddy from the financial news, from the financial aid podcast,
who always can check in with some very authoritative sounding information about any topic.
In this case, it's actually, I think.
104.
It's got to be pretty officially now.
It'll add moments.
104.
And now it's time for the 104.
You'll have moment.
Hey Adam, this is Chris from the financial aid podcast.
Time for a proper 104.
Which I should add, Christine's comment on DSE446 is about conspiracy theories, and not what's wrong with your computer.
What we're really talking about with the hair gel terrorists are binary compounds.
In the case of the most recent ones, they were according to press reports trying to manufacture TATB, or try acetone, try peroxide.
This is a combination of acetone and hydrogen peroxide requiring one other ingredient to make the reaction happen.
And it's certainly not something you can do with off the shelf ingredients from the drug store, contrary to press reports.
In chemistry circles, it's considered exceptionally unstable, and will more than likely, into the person making it before it ever reaches a capacity to be an explosive.
There are plenty of other binary compounds out there that would do a better job, and nearly every college graduate who took a college level organ in chemistry course and paid attention could do better.
Here's the conspiracy theory part.
Any time you see something in the news, you have to ask, who benefits from this?
In the case of liquids being banned on planes and through security checkpoints, here's a question for Charlie listeners.
Have the prices of beverages past the security checkpoints skyrocket again, now that you can't bring your own.
Has someone checked on the stock prices of the various airport food service companies, acquiring minds want to know.
This is Christian the financial aid podcast with a proper tinfoil hat moment.
In the spirit of the tinfoil hat moment, scruncher or folder, you'll never know.
tinfoil hat moment.
Yeah, I know you're a folder dude, you don't have to tell me.
It's okay.
Yeah, Chris following the money there in that case.
Okay, that's interesting.
I doubt that it's a conspiracy by the tax tax-free shopping conglomerates.
I just doesn't sound right.
Or the food catering conglomerates, airline catering conglomerates.
They're evil.
There's crunchers.
No doubt.
Yeah, maybe.
I don't know.
I really don't know.
I did talk to a pilot buddy of mine yesterday.
He has a command sheet between twin engine aircraft and he lives in Belgium.
He says he has been never been so busy.
He flies back and forth between the mainland, the continent, and the United Kingdom.
Three times a week now, he's doing flights.
And I think he charges, I think he charges like 2,000 euros round trips.
It's something along those lines.
So about what is that?
About 22, 2300 bucks.
And of course, you can take four or five passengers.
And he says businesses booming.
No one just wants to deal with the hassle anymore.
It's just too much hassle to get across this little puddle water.
Now, I'm thinking, there's business in it for me.
Once I get the airspeed indicator fixed.
Sorry.
That was pilot error.
The Adam or Adam, please answer this.
Are you getting frustrated?
A noise and a bit ticked.
Are you always so impatient before a fast kiss?
I've been boring, you say.
Oh, dear sir, surely your emotions are strangely amazed.
All right.
So this is the longest running promo in history.
This is the third riddle of, I don't know how many I'm going to get.
And with riddle number two, I was already starting to get a little bit bored.
Because it's basically a promo for a new podcast, which is out there somewhere.
And I've tried everything so far.
I haven't been able to figure it out.
We figured out the aviator.
You know, it's like, it's like the games too difficult.
It's too hard for me to figure out.
Please don't rush the planet and come soon.
Just enjoy the mental full play.
I've also be revealed prior to our next full moon.
Are you always as eager?
I'm so quickly bored as you said.
Production must be extra clever to keep your mental the beaver well fed.
Yeah, it's called naked pictures.
But she has all skillful performances now.
That pleasure keeps aches, explodes with added strokes that are slow.
And now you're talking my language, baby.
So we rise to your challenge of keeping you from tedium.
You are promised not to die or let disappoint in.
Think of them things.
It shall be worth it in the end.
To ease your efforts, go to riddle.procho.com.
Oh, okay.
Hold on a second.
Now we're doing something interesting.
Riddle.procho.com.
Okay, what you got for me.
Now I'm starting to like.
This is kind of cool.
By the way, if you have an audio or video comment, you know,
people are always wondering, you know, how do I get that to?
You can just open up account on podshow plus sign up as a podcaster,
which costs nothing.
It's completely free.
And then you can just upload your stuff there.
Yeah, it may get a promo or an ad inserted in front of it,
but there's always a little bit of space.
So I can easily edit that out.
It's a great way to just share files.
So if you want to send me a promo, do it that way.
So here you go.
Summary a series of riddle will be the longest playing promo.
I guess riddles.
I am the ridler.
Listen to each clue to find a word or letter.
Then assemble the words and letters into a name of a podcast.
None the better.
I give these clues to letters or words.
You determine the order of blah, blah, blah.
So they have the archive while the riddles up there.
All right.
Hold on.
This a link here.
Show producer.
You can't escape.
Show.
Okay.
It's all right.
It's going to the ridler.podshow.com.
Let's see what this is.
This is something our site is doing something dumb here.
What it does is if you go to a subdomain, then it basically recaches all the images and stuff,
which it already has.
Let's do what we got to fix that.
Okay.
Now the sites here.
I'm the ridler.
Listen to each clue to find a word of blah, blah, blah, blah.
Okay.
So nothing there.
Oh.
Here are some clues.
Shows a review.
Daily source code.
And the Elizabeth Street Brewery.
That's Richard Brewer Hayes.
Podcast.
People I dig the podpimp.
Who's the podpimp?
I thought the podpimp was Aaron Bersel, our parent.
The name start out as a joke.
CTWD.
The podpimp was always pimping podcash,
or after podshow call.
And well, the podfather hung the podpimp moniker.
I promote podcast night and day.
It's hard out here for a pimp.
Oh, the hell is that?
There's a YouTube video here.
Let's see what this is.
This is stupid.
Oh, why am I not hearing that?
Oh, yeah.
All right.
Whatever.
I have no clue.
I don't know what this is.
And quite honestly, you better start sending some naked pictures.
Winding up the charlotte with some charge.
Start a good end of the destroyers.
The pod save music network.
Where are we?
Any town?
New S.A.
Take me back, leave it.
From the blast to Jacob's been.
I forgot I go to sit and feel.
They got the house of blues on his face.
And the rocker on the face.
Take me back, leave it.
I'ma get it and attack you with me.
You gotta take this back, Detroit.
I think they're missing it.
I'm going to the motor set.
Cause I'm a lambland game with mine.
But be sure it wins, keep turning.
Yeah, baby, I'm alive.
Take me back, Detroit.
All right, get it and it's filled you with me.
Nice.
But every time I play this town,
The people train me so right.
Every time I come to you, I'll sit in.
I will run home then.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, today, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey hey, hey, hey
Take me back to Pittsburgh
Off in your mouth
All the way to Tulsa
Now I'm a sin and tone
Take it's the fact that
I laid a Georgia tune
We got a man
Up to my own little soul
Take me back to LA
That's what you see me
George Thorough
It sounds better with Calville
Any town USA
From the Podsame Music Network
You can find a link
To show notes for today's podcast
DailySourceco.com
To the Podsame Music Network
Right to Georgia's page
I realize it and actually finish the
The Riddle
Let's just do that
There's like 40 more seconds left
Take on our cut
And there can review
Each Riddle as we reveal it to you
On that page you will find these riddles in print
Some visit your listeners' assistants
And together you will decipher our hints
So they add them
Here is the next clue
People call it the Chacha
The Chali, the Chak
But it's acronym contains the clue that's a mark
The first of your three is the first of our second
So one
Then the solution
You shall reckon
TK of them
Daily
Okay, I got that
I don't know
You show better be so interesting to me
I'm gonna be really mad for playing along
This is no good
All right everybody
I would really love to have some suggestions for the
Football Friday
That's what I'm gonna call it now
Since we have a football at the office
Football Friday
If you don't know what football stands for
Look it up, FUBAR
So send in some suggestions for stuff for me to play
That means the weekend is almost here again
Gonna go flying again this weekend
You know it for sure
Airspeed indicator or not
As the wind commander would say
I see a lot of birds without an airspeed indicator
So have a good one
I'll talk to you tomorrow
DailySourceCode.com for the show notes
And of course Adam podshow.com
Free feedback
Take care everybody
Bye bye
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
Yet this podcast
And more great ones like it
On the high performance podcast
Delivery network from podshow
And line-white networks
So I love it