For the first time ever, the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr. in one action-packed DVD collection,
own all 27 episodes, the cult hit, including all new interviews with Carlton Koo.
First thing that Brisco did that impressed us was, we're not only to come in and really read the dialogue well as an actor,
but he also did a standing flip in our office.
You flipped too for Brisco County!
If you like the kind of TV you can't get on TV, get your copy of the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr.
Available now on DVD.
There's nothing that they both can't do.
But make you wild as dreams come true.
So grab your ear buds and jam them in.
And let the fabulous show begin.
It's Adam and Patricia.
Yes, Adam and Patricia.
Adam and the Lady Patricia.
I don't know.
It's the sign of the time for the New Year.
Like I'm going through today.
I don't know.
If I'm losing my mind, but I'm lost and blind, I don't take it.
Is there any way I wanna hear?
Is there some way to make this really hear?
Because of you, I can't sleep anymore since you walked up the door and you left me.
All I do is stare at the wall,
I think you know, thoughts at all, sempre memories.
Why do you wanna try to be insane?
Why do you wanna cause me so much pain for me?
I don't think I can't make it on my own.
If I'm losing my mind, but I'm lost and blind, I don't take it.
I can't feel.
Don't know darkness from light, don't know daytime from night on this recent.
Is it real?
Or will I wake up from this and the midst of your cares and embrace it?
What they're gonna miss both the two.
I don't think I can make it without you for me.
I don't think I can't make it on my own.
Don't think I can't make it on my own.
Why do you wanna try to be insane?
Why do you wanna cause me so much pain for me?
I don't think I can't make it on my own.
If I'm losing my mind, but I'm lost and blind, I don't take it.
Why do you wanna cause me so much pain for me?
I don't think I can't make it on my own.
But I don't think I can make it on my own.
But I might die here on the long way
Show me size
They'll need that you're still in the way of me
What's going on?
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So many times
It's our life
I don't think I don't like about that song as the windy fade out.
That's a bummer, isn't it?
I just want to...
Kevin Reeves, just throw me a line.
You like that song, don't you?
They still fade out these days.
Apparently.
Kevin Reeves does.
Yeah.
I don't like that anymore.
No.
I like songs to end.
Yeah, but jokes don't like that.
Jocks?
What do you mean Jocks?
I always...
Very confused.
I would fade out.
Yeah.
Man, you really love Terry Wogan, don't you?
Oh, I love him, yeah.
He's sweet.
What does he...
He makes like...
Such a gentleman.
I like that.
He does like a million pounds a year at BBC.
Oh, yeah.
And he works an hour and a half each morning.
Yeah.
And goes on vacation.
Yeah, was it?
He...
Was it from 730 to 9, I think?
Is that what he does?
Not more than that.
And sometimes, suddenly, he's gone in the morning.
Oh, yeah.
And then they go on vacation.
Johnny Walker or whatever the hell he got his name is.
They don't like Johnny Walker.
No, I don't.
No.
Well, I mean, I don't know the guy.
I just...
I miss Terry.
If you're going to have to listen to Terry Wogan,
then at least get used to it.
Yeah.
Better listen to the real one.
Hey, everybody.
How you doing?
It's a daily source code coming to you from the curry cottage
that's already known as Guildford episode number 470 already,
which, uh, hey,
Honda you've heard about 10 of those.
Haven't you?
What?
Well, I was reading.
Yeah.
He's not even listening to this show.
Hey.
Yeah.
Good.
Are you reading through the...
I'm reading your show, perhaps.
It's something very interesting.
It's sex myths.
Sex myths.
Yeah.
I was very curious about that.
Okay.
And give me a sex myth.
And what is the form out of the story?
Same sex fantasy.
Must mean I'm gay.
Um, hold on a second.
Let me answer the questions.
Um...
No.
It's totally normal.
Okay.
Next.
I'll do this.
Sex is bad for people with a heart disease.
No. It's very good for people with heart disease.
Exactly.
Then don't worry.
Next one.
I'm good at this.
This is really easy.
This is almost insulting.
To my sexual intelligence.
If he pulls out, I won't get pregnant.
That's one young girl's thing.
No.
Obviously, that's not true.
Obviously, that's a myth.
Obviously.
Give me a hard one.
Isn't there something better?
Get back to the gay stuff.
I was funny.
Let me see.
Not all women have a g-spot.
All women have a g-spot.
Not all women have discovered their g-spot.
Right.
And they might be on a different spot.
Yeah.
Just email adamantpodshow.com and I'll point it out to you.
Happy to send you graphics and instructional power points.
There's something gay about Adam.
There's something you have to admit to.
But you know you like it a bit.
Adam's got a great big house.
Adam's got a pretty life.
Adam's got a daughter who cares.
Adam's got a pretty good life but you know.
That he's kind of a mow.
There's something gay about Adam.
There's something you have to admit.
But you know you like it a bit.
Adam used to have really big hair.
Adam used to have funny, bowloat ties.
Adam used to have assholes like the chaps.
Adam used to have photos of Kurt Loder and him trying on bikinis.
Some are house and fire Island but as far as I know it's just a rumor.
But you know that you like him so.
There's something gay about Adam.
I think it's a hit.
There's something you have to admit.
There's something gay about Adam.
But you know you like it a bit.
Does he swallow a spit?
How?
The song is sounding like shit.
Yeah.
Thank you Mark Hiroshima to them, Carl.
Isn't that great?
We've built a company where I can actually pay people to do that stuff.
And I didn't ask for just, you know, people just sit around all day and say,
What could I do for the boss?
You know, let me write a song about him being a bit gay.
Oh, nice.
That awesome.
Yeah, fantastic.
I think it's a hit.
It's kind of the mellow yellow.
And isn't it true?
What?
But something gay about you.
But I spit.
I'm just in touch with my team.
Don't we love that?
We women love that.
Last night we were watching a documentary about Courtney Love.
From rehab to re-recording.
And it wasn't a really good documentary.
No.
But it was done with a, you know, with a DV camera.
So it was a very private private documentary.
It was a close impression.
And I think it was difficult to taper, to actually.
Well, I think I thought that the guy who did it got really good access to,
to Courtney.
And he was, he's literally everywhere.
But at one point, she talked about what really turned her on.
And what did she say?
She said, the nerdy ear, the key key ear, the more genius.
What I always say.
She said, if you got glasses, if you wear and shit,
shit clothes, you look like door aliens.
And I can learn something from you.
She said intelligence is intelligent.
Yeah.
It's sexy.
True.
I got to get the insight for PDF and start learning.
I love people with talents.
And she said, I don't even, I don't, then if I'm impressed with the talent.
And, you know, if they're brilliant, I don't even look out.
You know, the way they look.
I don't think it's, it's important.
It's funny because I was talking to Christina about that this morning.
Oh, yeah.
On our, you know, that's why I take it to school.
It's because she could take the bus, you know.
But it's fun because we chat and we talk about shit.
And this, this came up as well.
She was your quality time.
Yeah.
First that's our quality time.
And this conversation came up again.
And then she actually concluded herself, well,
you know, usually all the ugly, stupid,
doorky boys turn out to be the best husband.
And I said, that's right.
Now go take a look at Dan and Ferguson.
You tell me, boy, that I fuck up with Liam, huh?
Yeah.
But I think she's, she gets very easy bored with, with guys, which is good.
Yeah, very good.
Yeah, no, because you don't hang, you know, with one.
Just hang out with one.
No, she hangs out with one.
Yeah, she has a lot of friends.
Yeah.
So I thought here I was super dad.
And Liam and Christina are in her room.
And I come by and I say, hey, I got a ticket for digital music awards.
So you both can go.
And Christina said, you know,
I really, and you thought, you know,
I thought it was being a great dad.
Look what I'm doing.
Yeah.
I'm inviting her boyfriend.
How cool.
But she wasn't quite, because she, what did she say to me?
She said, I want to make sure he goes as my boyfriend.
The notice, you know, some guy who's just looking around
at how to get into the music business.
I'm going to be in trouble.
You know that.
I don't know.
Because she's going to say that to him.
She's going to say exactly that.
Yeah.
So I'm going to tell him that.
Well, what we didn't know is she was actually.
She already invited one of her friends.
Cool friends.
Yeah.
That was the big mistake.
You didn't know that I haven't heard a talking about it.
So you thought to do, you know,
I'm doing something cool.
Yeah.
Well, we worked it out.
Because now we have an extra ticket.
So the entire curry entourage is five people in total.
We're taking a half a table.
They're totally welcome.
Yeah.
It's kind of interesting.
This digital music awards.
Yeah.
Sounds very nice.
I really don't know what to expect.
I don't know what to expect.
I don't know all the names that are performing.
And it's going to be on channel 4.
The airing it after the awards, which I think is a shame.
So the award show is on.
And then I think two weeks later, it airs on channel 4.
Yeah.
Isn't that kind of a bar?
Yeah, it's a bummer.
It's not important to know for something.
I don't know.
I really don't know.
I guess not.
Who knows?
Sometimes it's very hard to get.
This is the only the second or third year they've done it.
Sometimes it's very hard to get the venue and the broadcast time schedule.
It's exactly the same moment.
Okay.
Sometimes that's hard.
But what we're going to do is we're going to have our own little mini streaming
studio.
The Grammy is when Ron and I did the Grammy Awards from Los Angeles.
And we know it ever done a cybercast.
Well, maybe someone had.
But I think we were the first ones that did it on that scale.
So we're going to do something very similar.
And we're going to have, I think we have like four cameras, backstage.
We have four cameras roaming around.
And we're just going to open up a stream.
So you can log in to btpodshow.com.
Are you going team five to start?
Yeah.
No.
It's even better than that.
After they've done whatever they've got to do.
Then they first walk through the press tent.
If you will.
It's not really a tent.
It's in the press room.
And then they're taken from the press room.
The only way to leave is through our room.
Where we have, so we have all kinds of beautiful people.
Free open bar.
You know that.
That already looks very invite.
Yeah.
We're going to light it.
It's going to be.
Oh, where am I?
Exactly.
Oh, this is cool.
We're going to sit everybody down.
So it's going to be.
It's going to be raw.
I'm sure.
But you know, people will be able to watch on podshow.com.
And just have open window to backstage.
So that'd be kind of fun.
And you're going to be there.
What do you mean?
I'm going to be there.
You're going to be there to hang out with them.
Well, you know, I have a very important job.
I've got to smooth with everybody.
I've got to smooth with the British telecom people.
Of course.
It's going to be there.
We want to sign people, too.
Yeah.
In fact, we're doing kind of like auditions tomorrow.
Oh, yeah.
Tomorrow.
Tuesday afternoon.
Yeah.
Where people can come in.
And just, you know, whatever they think they want to do.
For the show.
Yeah.
Very busy.
We have three or four hosts already that we signed up.
No, it's going to be good.
Yeah.
Of course, I'm going to be busy.
What do you think?
It was just going to be more good.
Oh, thank God.
You daughter is there.
You're going to be there.
Yeah.
We'll be busy running around.
But that's what it is.
You know, we want to, we'll be producing.
Well, I'm excited.
Yeah.
I can tell.
I am.
I know you didn't listen yesterday.
But this is the, uh, I thought you were going to be on yesterday.
So, for 69 was the episode.
Swass on Nuff.
Mm-hmm.
I should have been there.
You should have.
Hi, Adam and Patricia.
This is Ali from Swingercast.
From Swingercast.
I've been thinking, you know, 69 is always been my favorite number.
But for 69.
Mm-hmm.
That's even better.
That's my new favorite number.
That's a hot combo for 69.
That's a proposition.
Don't, that's a proposition.
John tells me you like to have people's in unique pictures.
Yeah.
Check your mailbox.
Folder or scruncher?
I guess I'm by.
I do them both.
I fold and scrunch.
Mm-hmm.
How about that?
Do you have the Sierra Charlie number?
What was that?
Well, that was her partner from the Swingercast.
Oh.
I think they're basically inviting us to go have a 4.69.
See, what's so unfair is you've done all that stuff in the 60s and 70s.
Oh, it's because it's done that.
Because you, yeah, but see, I didn't get to do a lot of that.
Because in the 80s we had like AIDS and death, you know, like 80s.
You're going to die.
No.
The 80s and 90s.
It was hard.
I don't know that.
There was none of that free love and all that groovy stuff.
Yeah.
We didn't get any of that.
What a flower in your hair.
I'll stick a flower in my ass, as long as I can have a group sex.
Okay.
Maybe that guy who called in about his sister-in-law?
No.
Yeah, you do.
Oh.
The abusive relationship.
Oh, yeah.
Can we talk to about that?
Yeah.
Let's hear the comments about being with my sister-in-law.
And what I did with your show on Friday.
I made her a listen to it.
And God thought, what happened?
She passed her 3-key bags.
That's incredible.
God.
I kind of breaks up at the end, but he says,
She packed her freaking bags and left.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
So he's helped.
We saved it.
We saved two people, I think.
Uh-huh.
Because you never got to change.
You could make a career out of it.
Oh, yeah.
You should do an advice show.
You're really good at that.
Yeah.
You can be fantastic.
Great example.
I'm married to you.
Uh-huh.
How are you doing, man?
Thank you.
Uh-huh.
You feel much better now.
Yeah.
So I told everybody yesterday that yesterday I played an emo song to start off
the show because I was an emo.
Because we got some horrible news yesterday.
Oh, please.
You know, I can't even be sad about it anymore.
I get an email and phone calls from around the world.
People saying, really, I hope you get a house.
You know, really sorry.
Oh, we're so...
I mean, look at the quality of the problem.
Yeah.
You first of all, this is not a horrible thing.
But can you believe that of all the houses we pick?
Let's say we feel very lucky.
Oh, we're very thankful.
Very lucky.
Every day we wake up and open our eyes and we're still alive.
Yeah.
Yes.
Now, fuck this shit about the goddamn covenant.
Oh, this is me off.
Yeah.
So we haven't...
I'm a little worried because I haven't heard back from the real estate agent yesterday.
Yesterday.
It's very quiet.
Yeah.
So it's too quiet.
Definitely.
Yeah.
Well, I did kind of yesterday.
Oh, you did.
Yeah.
There's a covenant which means you cannot convert the garage,
which the house is almost perfect for us.
If only we could have the kitchen in a different spot and make the current kitchen.
Yeah.
Which is perfect.
Because, you know, we've agreed that we really want to spend the most of attention
to the places where we are the most in our lives.
Which is the kitchen, which is the bedroom.
And you.
And the bathroom.
No, no.
You know, I don't really give a shit.
I mean, just give me...
Yeah.
I'm willing to sit out in the garden.
Yes, you know.
That's fine.
I don't care.
But so the garage, the garage,
cannot be converted.
I'm going to figure out this covenant.
At least the seller, the vendor.
Well, because it wasn't figured out.
They came up with the covenant 30 years ago.
Yeah.
I don't know why.
But I think a covenant...
There must have been a reason.
Yeah.
But to me, a covenant is pretty much a legal agreement that you can't...
But they must have...
I want to hear the reason.
Yeah.
I'm very curious about the reason.
Because these days, people want to do something with any space they have
with their houses.
And, you know, we don't drive our cars in the garage anymore.
No.
Because we're in a hurry.
Well, there's...
Obviously some reason.
And if we find out the reason, maybe we can turn the covenant back.
I don't know if it's for all of the houses or just that one on that particular road.
But, you know, it's so messed up.
Because you get everything all geared up.
You get lawyers and everyone's involved.
Everybody's already going.
Everyone's ready to rock.
And I gotta leave in a week.
You know, it's like...
Yeah.
And then what?
Then we're...
If nothing happens, I'm going to be gone for two weeks.
What can I do in the two weeks time?
Telephone calls.
Yeah.
I think we want to start looking again.
No.
We'll just wait.
Wait until we got some answers.
And then I'm just going to switch my...
You know, my house knob.
I thought I was your house knob.
Because I don't think about it yet.
Okay.
We love here.
Because we were very happy with house.
Yeah, well.
I've also switched to neutral baby.
I'm like, okay, whatever.
But, you know, I hope something...
You know, it's going to be so fucking busy.
It's going to be next week.
Everyone in town, I mean, I'm not a lot of bandwidth to do much.
So they, you know, Bruce Bruce Simon.
He's got to really fix it.
Yeah.
You know, figure it out.
I know.
But there's nothing we can do anyway.
It's frustrating.
See, I get all flush and I get all sweaty when I think about it.
Yeah, it's kind of harsh.
But people remember the phone number when I play that.
Plus one two one six two five six three five seven four.
The New Jersey number in London.
Oh, two oh seven six eight one three seven five three.
Yeah, Christina show is out.
The BG blast.
Oh yeah.
Let's just do it with Martina and Shme.
Okay.
You want to hear something incredible?
Yeah.
Listen to the promo.
Then tell me this is not...
She is not my daughter.
I mean, let's see this.
Okay.
Hey there.
I'm Christina Curry.
One of the hosts of the BG blast.
Be sure to tune into this week's episode where I showcase new music by Melo Bright Van.
Sean J and more.
Listen to hear about the exciting how low-screen promotion where one lucky listener will get a free trip to Bush Gardens.
We even learn about hippo camps.
And I share the star in my most recent drama in the dressing room of London's top shop clinic store.
Toon in this week and check it out.
What do you think?
She sounds a little bit higher.
I think I think the whole spot was spun up a little bit.
Yeah.
Just a little bit.
But do you hear the puke and quality she has?
She's really cute.
She does.
I'm just waiting for to say everybody.
Toon in there and everybody.
Yeah.
Very cute.
Good timing.
Yeah.
But she sounds a little bit lower.
I know.
She does.
Yeah.
But it's the high tempo height.
More teenager.
They needed more teenager.
No.
I think that the music was so long.
And they had to squeeze her track into it something like that.
Wow.
She likes that.
Well, that's Dr. Dave.
Dave Fox.
He's putting the show together.
He's a profession.
He sure is a profession.
Yeah.
What else you got, baby?
Anything else you want to talk about?
Well, I was just.
I said it this morning when I read the paper about that judge here.
Yeah.
So there's two judges who had it in a fair together and they had the same housekeeper.
And I think they were both screwing the housekeeper.
It was his housekeeper, I think.
But it wasn't she having sex with her as well.
I think he had sex in the beginning with her.
Yeah.
But didn't.
So she probably was jealous.
Yeah.
She had made video or stole video.
So he had the two judges, male and female.
See, that's having sex in the end.
Let me finish.
Let me finish it.
Okay.
Yeah.
People didn't read the fucking story.
This is a UK story.
Only when America don't understand.
Then you just.
I know, I know your point.
Just let me.
Yeah.
Ready?
So the two judges that was video tape of them having
sex and doing coke.
Doing coke.
I didn't hear that.
Well, why don't you read the paper?
Oh, it's in there.
I must have missed something.
That was, that's the big deal.
That's the coke part.
And so she then blasted.
And she was here illegally.
Because her visa ran out.
Yeah.
And then she blackmailed.
The judge for 20,000 pounds.
Otherwise, she'd release the video tape.
Yeah.
And so that.
So they sued her for blackmail.
Or she was charged on blackmail charges.
And now, of course, the question is, how about these judges?
Are they fit to be judges?
And 20,000.
It's not enough.
That was stupid.
She should be thrown in jail for being idiot.
Idiot.
Yeah.
She's done it like that.
Now you're pointing about taping yourself.
Well, dude, that's what I said.
And I said it to you once.
Because you said a couple of months ago.
You wanted to tape something or I don't know.
Or should we?
What?
Ask me to tape it.
Or I'll try 15 years ago.
15 years ago.
And every year, every year, maybe you're asking a show show.
That is so not true.
Because I know that I look horrible naked.
I mean, I'll tape you.
But I'm not going to tape me.
Are you nuts?
But I always say it's like, no.
Faces of death far free.
If it's my husband for 20 years or anything,
I would never ever do that.
Because you never know who finds notes.
But that's part of doing it.
Is the excitement of knowing that you have this illegal thing.
That if it got out, it could destroy you.
Yes.
Look, you can become a really big star.
You can be a little bit.
Look at Perisilta.
Absolutely.
I think Pamela Anderson didn't hurt her either.
After we all saw Tommy's trauma.
I think.
Yeah.
That's what I'm doing.
That thing is enormous.
He was the starring there.
Well, that's what I mean.
So if you have, if you have that kind of penis.
Oh, you shared.
I think you shared.
I think that's your obligation to mankind to make a video.
I've seen this whole thing.
He's steering the boat with his dick.
Ah.
And he's honking the horn.
Oh, no, I'm with it.
It's amazing.
And for Pammy.
For Pammy.
It is big.
You know that I've never seen it.
But I've, there was a program on me.
Believe me.
And actually, I had a glimpse.
A glimpse.
And then I couldn't believe it.
They can't show that on English TV.
No.
I can't show it.
You see the little bit of penis.
And I couldn't believe it.
Yeah.
So yeah.
Then you should tape it.
Yeah.
I point exactly.
And he was right to sell it.
But I would never do that.
Well, that's a shame.
No, because I'm such a smock.
Oh, you're such a white.
A smock.
Somebody will find it.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah.
Well, but, you know, we've exposed ourselves on television.
But we, you know, we checked it.
And it was okay.
Yeah.
Certainly was okay.
I thought what, what actually fluked out and escaped of my penis.
Yeah.
You know, no one said, hey, Adam's got a small penis.
Right?
Everybody was angry.
Lots of men were angry.
Very angry.
Yeah.
I know.
Because they were jealous.
I guess.
Yeah.
And see, this is my point.
It's like, I'm like, man, all right.
It's okay.
That's good.
You can Google Adam's penis.
And it'll probably show up.
Oh, God.
You'll need to expand your browser.
Hey.
Now you did it.
That's been seen so many times before.
Yeah.
I really don't care.
I wish we could put, I investigated if we could put out the Adam's family.
Yeah.
Very difficult because of all the music we used.
Oh.
Yeah.
You can't make it available for a download.
Oh.
Yeah.
Because we use all kinds of hits and every greens and stuff like that.
And it's a nightmare to license.
Oh, shit.
Sox doesn't it?
But we could put it on the stream.
If we had a live stream, then we could do it.
What is that?
I mean, you can't download it.
But you can only watch it at a certain time.
Or it has to be streaming.
Yeah.
There's all different laws for that.
You could do that.
But I want to sponsor.
Yeah.
Because you probably need to pay for it anyway because you're using the music.
Well, yeah.
If you have a stream, like we'll have that at the digital music awards.
Yeah.
There will be all kinds of music licensed music as well.
But with streaming, you can pay Ask Cat BMI because you can't download it.
So there's no other organization.
The record companies can't do anything.
You do have to pay Ask Cat BMI, which is okay.
Yeah.
I don't want paying for it.
So I don't know who to pay.
But then if people want to watch the Adams family, they have to pay then.
No, we could do it anyway.
We want.
We could have it sponsored.
You get a sponsor.
That's what I mean.
Yeah.
So indirectly people are paying, of course, because there's a sponsored message.
Or yeah, you could draw.
I don't know if any.
You know, I don't believe in the pay.
You know, a dollar 99.
I just hate it.
I don't know.
I don't like it.
You know.
I'm not in custody anyway.
Yeah.
I'm just not interested.
I'd like I wish more people could see it.
Yeah.
Rather than making.
Made potentially more money by restricting it.
And then, you know, you got a copy right protected.
So so people.
Yeah.
Fuck it.
My sister was watching it with.
With her daughter and her new friend.
She was watching the DVD.
Her partner.
Yeah.
And they were watching it again.
And then she said it was very funny.
It was a funny thing.
Better when you watch it now.
And it's Christina was so much smaller.
Yeah.
And there's a lot of English in it too.
So it could be pretty international thing.
I mean, it's not hard to understand that you're based on watching your life.
No.
You actually have to see it.
And you will understand it.
Yeah.
So would you consider that?
You being the co-co-executive producer?
Yeah.
You put it on the pod chest.
No.
That might be fun.
Yeah.
Because it's a pity.
It's just laying you.
Yeah.
I mean, even if we didn't make any money.
I have to think of it.
You know.
I mean, we are naked here in there.
Yeah.
Hopefully.
Now, I like that.
I like having a historical record of my nakedness when it still was okay.
Hmm.
Don't you think?
Don't you love having your playboy picture?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Been in there for a couple of times.
And.
But isn't it nice to have that to look back at?
Yeah.
Especially.
Well, you actually look at it.
Like, I don't look like that anymore.
That's a pity.
But it's photoshoot.
Yeah.
It's pretty.
Layout and lighting.
Yeah.
A million of those shoots today.
Well, no, the days that in the days that I did it, we didn't photoshop.
Get airbrush.
Not, not even the first one.
The first one.
First one was nothing done.
Untouched.
It was all lighting, wasn't it?
You have to do it with light.
Yeah.
These days for photographers just put you in front of a screen.
Change the background.
Oh, they can make me look like 16 year old.
Yeah.
I mean, it's enough fair.
Cool.
It's not fair.
That was not fair.
You know, this is not real.
All right.
I'm going to play a song that is nominated for the Digital Music Awards, which is now available on the podcast music network.
Mm.
Okay.
I don't think it's going to be your style.
It's in the electronic category.
Okay.
So you may not like it.
Who is it again?
The future.
That's right.
This dream is a beautiful night.
Yeah.
The falling sun, the faded light, the rolling ground, different sky.
I'm going to slide, because I'm good.
I think I might go mad instead.
It's a dream is a beautiful night.
Yeah.
Oh, the sun is shining.
It's a dream is a beautiful night.
It's a beautiful night.
It's what it seems.
The smoking done.
The second chance has just ruined.
This dream is a beautiful night.
Oh, the sun is shining.
It's a beautiful night.
This dream is a beautiful night.
Oh, my man, oh, so good night
Just feels like a bullet from nowhere
And so good night
This dream is a beautiful night night
Oh, so good night
Just feels like a bullet from nowhere
And so good night night
This dream is a beautiful night night
Oh, so good night
Just feels like a bullet from nowhere
And so good night night
Insight has a physical meaning
And it drives me insane
Too blind to be up to my fear
Such a feeling for pain
Insight has a physical meaning
And it drives me insane
Too blind to be up to my fear
Such a feeling for pain
It's called a bullet from nowhere
The future
Nominated in the best unsigned band category
For the channel for BT Digital Music Awards
London October 3rd
Beyond the lookout for live video at podshow.com
I liked it
It's not bad, isn't it?
It's very interesting how they made one of the harmonies
Became the melody
Yeah
Like I know what the fuck you're talking about
But I can imagine where that bass line
We're pretty good in the club
That's actually the harmony
And that bass line
Right?
I liked it
So I guess they'll play
I'm not quite sure, I don't know who's coming
Oh, I know who's also name
You're going to laugh
Sandy Tom
I wish I was a punk rocker
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
Doesn't she play all that shit herself all the instruments?
No, that's not her
Well, maybe it's not her that
I thought that she was coming
Oh, yeah
Yeah, I think so
I think she's performing
So as you noticed, I was planning on being out here
Out of here by noon, it's almost one
Yeah
The reason being
After a year and a half of
Telling Ron that he should try
Virgin upper class
Instead of he always flies American airways
Or British airways
So they decided to do Virgin
Yeah
And there was a
Mechanical difficulty
Oh no
And they had to go to
They had to go to LA
And then from LA to London
So they're not rising until 3.30
And you would you great idea
I've never had a problem with a Virgin
Never, never heard
What do I say when I come back
What do I always say?
About a problem, never
No, what do I say?
I love that airline
I love it
It's fantastic
Oh
Isn't that always like that?
Mm-hmm
There you go
Oh my god
So I won't see you until tomorrow
But they will be comfortable
And later
Yeah, they'll be comfortably laid
Yeah
So I'm going to stay overnight
In London, I'll have to do the Friday show
From the hotel room
Okay
And I'll see you tomorrow night
All right
Something like that
Yeah, something like that
Yeah, okay anything else
Well don't let him line up tonight
What?
All my friends
Oh, don't come to the don't come to the cottage
Should I tell Jimmy?
Just to keep an eye out
Cross the street
Yeah, thank you
All right, baby, thank you very much for being on show
DailySourceCode.com
Adam at podshow.com
Almost
I think it's a nice thing
I love you baby
I love you too
Bye-bye
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
Get this podcast
And more great ones like it
On the high performance podcast
Delivery network from podshow
And limelight networks
I love it