This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Atm Curry and the daily source code is on the air.
For sixty-eight?
For sixty-eight million dollars worth of air playing strap to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
With you, they take your hand, they tell you that they understand it's true.
What you know is that when I tell you to run all right, do we not care?
When the world comes out to greet you, do we not all right?
When the world comes out to greet you, do we not care?
How shall you place where you can walk in the sun?
When the world comes out to greet you, do we not all right?
When the world comes out, do we not all right?