portions of this podcast are brought to you by EarthLink Internet.
$60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I guess it's a battle curry.
Delta Sierra Charlie 309er.
Hey, we're halfway through the week everybody.
Let's celebrate that properly.
Let me go!
Big story aside but true...
You would believe you if only you would say goodbye
Sit here on this break you've made
Stair up the ocean in a haze
Come bread and name alone
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Come bread and name alone
How are you and I
All hope are we?
Walk as long as our rain
I'm gonna talk about it, ain't it obvious that I need you?
I need you.
And if you love me stay in town, with you here I'll stick around and to threats, don't matter.
How you saw it in this way, too many dreams into many days,
After thoughts they made nothing.
Oh, whoa, you could have told me,
Now the days of summer, I guess much longer with you.
I always didn't believe it.
Now I can't accept that the night's all longer since you've seen this through.
Don't wanna talk about it, ain't it obvious that I need you?
I need you.
Days of summer, now is now, I'm such a sucker for power cords and power vocals and choruses.
So in the pod save music network, thanks to Kevin from firstperson show.net for sending me a link to them.
If you took out the website as well, they've got a couple of videos.
Hey everybody, how you doin' is Wednesday.
We are halfway through the week, whether it's shit over here.
In preparation for my San Francisco voyage, hopin' on the oil rig for another couple of weeks.
Patricia, hold on a second.
But you should drag me to the hairdresser today, and I have a perfect coop emo at the moment.
My daughter is gonna be so proud which she sees in my hair, just like all the emo guys wear it.
Let's see, got lots to talk about today.
Interesting stuff that people basically emailed me. I'd love to get more of this stuff in audio comment form.
I'll see Patrick Mylander sent me a link to a German website, a page and a hoita.de, and he actually gave me a synopsis in English of what the page says.
This is about what's going on in France. Apparently they're about to legalize file sharing, and from what I gather for a 7-year-of-fee, so about a box,
that'll be added to your monthly internet bill, the legalize copying of music and other media.
Patrick, thank you very much for sending in that link. My Germans are a little rusty, but I was able to kind of get through it.
Some other people sent me information about this.
If you know what's going on, and I know we have French podcasters tuned in, the pom pom pom pom pom pom podcast.
Give us an audio feedback. Let us know what's happening over there, because that sounds pretty exciting.
Another thing that a whole bunch of people have been emailing me about, this is something that, you know, if dig.com hasn't jumped on it yet, they certainly should.
This is about the Coldplay CD. I don't know if you've heard about this, but the new Coldplay CD, which I believe is on Sony records. I'm loading up the page right now.
Let me see, are they on Sony? Yes, they're on Sony.
It comes with what we call a Yula, an EULA, the end user license agreement, and there's lots of information now on the net about this, but it's really, it's pretty funny. So this is insert.
And they have pictures of it, and have actually listed out in plain text exactly what it says. I just want to run through some of these things.
The most important part is the title. This CD is a copy protected CD, and it goes on to say, thank you very much for purchasing this CD in helping the cause of anti piracy.
The recordings in this CD have an anti copying function. They cannot be copied into a PC.
In order for you to enjoy high quality music, we have added this special technology, so they add a little player, so you can play it if you want to roll it out on your PC.
Listen to all of this stuff. Here's all the disclaimers. This is, it's exactly like the opening up a copy of Windows XP. You know, there's all the fine print that you just rip across, but by opening that you agree to the end user license agreement.
Here we go. Some CD players that have the capability of burning into an MP3, such as portable players or car stereos. Oh, this is the list of devices that won't play the CD.
Some players that possess CDR or RW functions. Some car stereos with satellite guidance systems. Some CD players or car stereos with hard disk recording capability. Some CDR RW recorders use from music.
And it goes on. It won't work on some portable CD players. Some DVD players. Some CD LD convertible players. Some game players.
It's amazing.
Oh, yeah, so they, they add this little application. Although you can use your Windows program to listen to certain tracks. This does not mean the CD can be played in all PCs.
The first time this program is used in Windows automatic starter software gets registered in Windows file.
Is that what they said? That's horrible English. Those programs already registered to not affect Windows. This is, that's not even English. That doesn't make sense. Anyway, the final one there is this CD does not support Macintosh PC software.
Hey, why don't we just not buy it? Oh, it's going on. That's nuts, man. That's totally nuts.
And then I'm sure, you know, we've getting more and more stories just pouring in about how wacky the RIA and affiliated organizations are. And a lot is coming. It's kind of bubbling up as to how they've been growing their market share, not by necessarily selling more records, but by taking money from other places such as
the story from Fradrico Avers.
According to my physician here in Belgium, he only plays classical music, which is royalty free in the waiting room.
Because otherwise he has to pay the Belgian ASCAP equivalent.
Is this how elevator music got started? Well, I don't know if that's, I guess it is true.
Wait a minute, I know, wouldn't they technically, it depends on who the recording is of. I don't know. I guess maybe there.
I'm trying to think if you'd have to pay ASCAP EMI in that.
Anyway, doesn't matter, just some of the wacky things that's going on.
I had a great conversation yesterday with Steve Gilmore of the Gilmore gang and Gilmore daily.
And we were going to do, we actually wanted to do this before the New Year's, but he was sick and I had a lot going on by parents.
And so we decided to do it in the New Year. We had a great conversation. I don't know 45 minutes or an hour.
It was, I thought it would be a really good Gilmore daily. And I like having conversation with Steve because he can be such a dick.
And I really get you fired up.
And unfortunately, something went wrong with the recording on his end.
I should have had the presence of mine to record my end of the conversation at least.
But of course, didn't, so we're going to have to do it again.
But we did talk about this Google PC. I don't know if you've heard about this.
But the rumor is now out that Google is going to be launching a cheap PC.
And we had this conversation. I thought, you know, the only reason I'd really care about a device like that
is not if it was 200 bucks or 100 bucks. But it was free.
It was free and it returned for that.
So what is it? It's a computer and it hooks up to the net and it gives you Gmail.
And maybe it's some kind of online office, sweet stuff. You know, I could totally see that being something that in return for advertising in your attention is Gilmore would call it that that could be an offering.
But anyway, the word is is that where the rumor is, the Google is going to announce something big at CES, the consumer electronics show in Vegas, which I'm just missing.
I guess is it this week that it starts up or this weekend or something?
I was supposed to be on a panel, but it just everything kind of worked out a little differently.
And it's a bummer because the same time as CES is the adult video awards.
And I had some connections to get in. So I'm bummed about that.
Adam says Alan Wage is after being marooned in a non Howard Stern city in Atlanta, all my life.
I'm anxiously awaiting January 9th when Howard goes on air at serious.
I got hooked on him was spending a lot of time working in other cities during the past few years.
I got my serious radio at best by last week in anticipation.
I got me thinking though, once I start listening to Howard during my morning drive,
it's going to climb into my podcast listening time.
So my plan is this morning drive, Stern afternoon drive, DSC, other podcasts on days when you don't do the DSC.
Wow, I'm sure others are struggling with this dilemma. I love to hear your thoughts.
Well, I think the good news about Howard Stern on serious is that he'll basically,
I think the way it's going to work is the show will just be on a repeated loop.
So very much the way it would work east coast, west coast.
I don't know, yeah, he has three channels.
So there's going to be some repetition.
So you could listen to Howard whenever you want to, I guess.
But I think he does work best in the morning quite honestly.
And there is a lot of, and we talked about that yesterday as well.
Gilmore and I did it. Well, we'll try and resurrect some of that conversation,
because actually I thought someone was pretty, pretty good, but it sucks man.
I used to happen to Dave Winner and me a lot when we first doing trade secrets.
And then, you know, the recording stuff wasn't quite fleshed out yet.
And the backward freeze up and all the entire recording would be lost.
And it just sucks. And then to pick up the thread, you know, sometimes you say,
forget it, we'll have to do it another day.
Quite a conversation going on online here in the daily source code.
And offline at the pod show office is about advertisers.
And how we want to change what advertising is in this new type of media mashup.
In this particular version, which we call a podcast, not all of it.
I will definitely be talking about stuff as we can bring stuff to the surface.
Because, you know, we got advertisers involved in the conversation.
So it's pretty exciting stuff, but we definitely definitely are working on changing what advertising is.
And one of the ways we do that is through these subliminal senseo vulgon mind tricks.
Greg Mason got a senseo machine with a gift card for the holidays.
He opened up the box, plugged it in, flushed the machine the next morning.
He says, I made a mug of coffee to my surprise.
The coffee wasn't as good as I was hoping, but more alarming, I had zero froth.
Oh my god.
Well, you know, I don't know if the, you guys send this whole long email about not having any froth.
Okay, I'm just going to tell you how I do it.
How I make my senseo coffee, because that does give me, it gives me good froth.
So, usually the water tank is filled up.
If not, you got to do that first.
And then, you know, you hit the on button so it can warm up.
In the meantime, you get your pod, you put that in.
After throwing out the old messy gunky wet one, right?
Because of course, you never take that out right after you're done with the coffee.
You leave it in there for the extra aroma.
And then in your coffee cup, I put first sugar and then I put my milk in.
And I put a liberal amount of milk.
I like it that way.
And then by then, the senseo machine is ready.
I plop the, the coffee cup under a hit, a press play.
And then it comes out and it does.
And then when you stir, you know, put your spoon down in deep and make sure you're stirring
more near the bottom.
And it's really frothy.
It is. It's just fricking frothy.
Hey Adam, Kevin Williams here from the middle management lobotomy podcast at mml podcast.lipsen.com.
I listen with interest to Delta Sierra Charlie 307 and the idea of a senseo conspiracy.
I am a fellow podcaster who has also heard your dulcet tone,
singing the praises of senseo.
And as a result, added the senseo product to my Christmas list.
Low and behold underneath the tree was my brand,
spanking new senseo machine.
I could not tell you how excited I was to have the device open it up
and try my first cup.
And I do have to admit, it is very impressive.
The dui eegbert's medium roast product that comes with the senseo machine is very tasty.
And just the way it's manufactured is incredible.
Now onto the conspiracy part, however.
The concern I believe of the listener was that senseo,
in teaning up with dui eegbert's, has formed basically a monopoly on the coffee product itself.
In essence, the same thing as Dell making money one time off a piece of hardware
and Microsoft making repeated money off of software sales
that are built into the same device.
I would say it's slightly different with senseo.
In that if you do enough research, you'll find a number of coffee producers
that make pods for single cup brewing devices.
Now they are not officially branded as senseo nor will they be,
because of the marketing deal that's senseo.
And senseo, yes, senseo, I believe owns dui eegbert's.
You'll find it on the senseo package.
Have cut to work in tandem.
However, at least in my own local independent grosser association supermarket.
Yes, I use an independent grosser and not one of the big chains.
I found not one, but two brands have produced single pods
that are available in those supermarkets.
Maxwell House has their branded.
I'm not sure of the exact name.
Folders has created a branding called home cafe with single pods
that will fit the senseo machine just fine.
Their French vanilla is very tasty out of a senseo machine.
I've not tried their columbium roast or their regular house blend yet,
but we'll be going those to try in the future.
Both those products sell for a price point lower than the dui eegbert's price.
So if cost is a concern, yes, it is more expensive than buying a pound of ground coffee,
set for a standard paper filter.
However, I'm not wasting as much coffee and I have to think of the environmental impact
of the waste of the beverage and the water as well as the product itself.
So I am one satisfied senseo owner and thrilled that you made the recommendation
as for a conspiracy.
Check the web folks.
You'll find plenty of coffee pod producers that make pods for single
cup brewers that will work just fine in your senseo machine.
Thanks and appreciate the shout out.
Take care.
Bye bye.
Kevin, so I'm really digging this conversation that we can have about products.
I don't get paid for this senseo mentions.
We did get compensated for eye dog.
I've got a lot of positive response on the eye dog stuff.
And I'm wondering if maybe advertising on podcast is an ongoing conversation.
Arguably, you're going to get more people try something out.
If they hear feedback both positive and negative, they're more inclined to check it out.
And of course, that also depends on price point.
You may not do that with a car, but certainly on a $50 coffee machine.
So interesting.
Thanks for the feedback on that.
I'm still loving it.
Still loving my senseo.
You know how I love it?
Because I don't have one in San Francisco at the condo, but for sure, I don't know why.
But she bought me a cup of chino maker.
And although I do like the cup of chino, whenever I get home to the cottage, I was like,
oh yeah, there's my girl, there's my daughter.
There's my senseo machine.
I'll be there.
Congratulations to Julie and Smith in over your head podcast celebrated his 100th episode recently.
CC Chapman, accident hash, same deal.
Oh, I mean, that's what an achievement.
100 episodes. Congratulations, guys.
That's fantastic.
I wonder how I haven't spoken to Don and Drew in a long time.
I wonder how they're doing.
Actually, I saw the Drew is sent me an instant message the other day.
And, but I missed him.
He was gone by the time I got back online.
I'm going to see what my other girlfriend is up to.
Quick mention, let me see.
Hold on here.
About LibreVox.
There's actually a request coming in for people to say,
hey, I'd love it if if this book were available in audio book format.
And you should definitely check out LibreVox.org.
Just see what's going on over there because they got some really cool.
And they've got, essentially, they've got open source audio books.
Oh, sab.
And nice acronym.
So, two, uh, alto, I think.
Uh.
He writes, you said on the show that you've chosen some works already to submit into LibreVox.
Am I totally wrong if I wish that around the world 90 days might be one of them?
Yeah, that's not one of them.
But that's a good one.
Someone should definitely do that.
And the two guys from Helsinki, Finland.
Make sure you, uh, add a link to the Frapper map.
Make sure you put your little flag in there.
I'm a demon in the rack and throw.
Plan 9 Rock Show.
Choose a show that comes out of the chart.
I'm a demon in the rack and throw.
Jasper from the Plan 9 Rock Show.
That really might a cup of teasers and music goes.
I'm a demon in the rack and throw.
The Plan 9 Rock Show.
I don't know why it's because I've got enough of my new favorites.
So I'll probably be ripping Jasper's show off.
Plan 9 Rock Show.
Just rack.
Plan 9 Print.com.
Welcome to the Switchers Podcast, where we introduce Switchers.
You know, Switchers are full with those users that come forward on this platform, and now
only use the Apple OS and hardware.
Welcome, my dearest off-laping from the Switchers Podcast.
And as you both cast away into your comments, I forgot now I was going to edit this
piece because the whole promo is in Dutch, but the payoff actually kind of makes sense.
Let's start the new year right by learning how to go to college for free with the financial
aid podcast.
Every week day we feature daily scholarship updates, financial aid and student loan news, and consumer
finance tips to put more money in your pocket.
File your FAFSA, get a student loan, find a scholarship, and learn about the latest trends
and personal finance.
Did you know, for example, that US students in 2006 will face a 35% increase in their student
loan interest rates?
It's true.
Learn how to protect yourself from this by tuning into the financial aid podcast.
Subscribe to date to the financial aid podcast at www.financialaidpodcast.com and make an
affordable college education the easiest resolution in 2006.
So this morning after I dropped Christina off at school, my phone rang, my blackberry,
and it was really weird.
It was like a bad Skype connection where the speech was all kind of drawn out, and it
was my dad.
He was calling me from the hospital, and as you probably know by now he had a TIA followed
by a minor stroke, and the outlook looks good, but he definitely asked to stay in the hospital
for at least another week and they started the rehabilitation process, and he now has
40% lost 40% of the use of his left side, and he was really weird because he's so
typical.
He started talking about podcasting and about opportunities, and he had, it was really,
it wasn't what I expected at all.
Actually you know what, if you are listening to us right now on serious satellite stars
103, I'm sorry you're out of luck, we're going to continue this story on the podcast.
You'll have to go to dailysourceco.com to download it later on if you want to hear the rest
of the story.
Pacific Coast, Hellway, is up next for you guys, and I'll be back tomorrow right here on
the bird with y'all that everybody, and we're going to continue here with a conversation
about my dad, okay?
So it was, it's just us now, you know, I was like, you know, how are you doing?
He's like, well, he basically told me, but his speech was definitely, you know, not
slurred, but drawn out, and he was making sense, it was just really slow and exactly
what you'd expect from someone who, in that position.
But then he did something that he, that he's done before, you know, or always does,
really, starts talking about business and like, you know, dude, you shouldn't be worrying
about this.
He says, no, yeah, but I've, you know, I've got to survive, and like, yeah, well, of course
you've got to survive, so we've got to work on your health, but I think he was really
just talking about making money and business, and I couldn't believe it.
It was, it was surreal almost, and I kept saying it over and over and over, you know,
how are you, your health?
That's what's important.
And it was, anyway, it was a weird conversation.
He said something very, very cool, though.
Of course he, well, you know, he continued to talk about business, so, you know, I was listening.
He said, you're paving the goat path, I was like, what, he said you're paving the
goat path, and I asked him what that meant.
He said, look, you know, Howard Stern was able to, you know, cash in for 100 million
a year, and he measures everything in money, by the way, my dad.
But, you know, the, the possibility of this podcasting stuff is, you know, could, could
change everything, but not if you are out to, to pave the goat path, radio being the
goat path.
And I thought that was really prolific.
And, you know, and so I said to him, well, you know, that's exactly the way I feel about
it.
You know, there's so much more, and, and really it's about, in the, in the bottom layers of
it all, it's all about subscription, about publishing and subscribing to, to data, right
now we've learned how to, how to shuttle big pieces of, of audio around, but it's just
data.
So anyway, I said, you know, I didn't get much further with him, but he's doing okay, and
he's in rehabilitation, and he has to stop drinking, stop smoking, and exercise more and
take care of himself.
And, uh, I'll support him, however I can, but he definitely also has to stop worrying
about other shit, because that, that just can't help, you know, I think he needs to slow
down.
Okay, uh, a couple of things, let me see, oh, we actually have something really cool
coming up in a minute, uh, something that, uh, actually won't even work on, uh, on anything
but on headphones.
So if you've got some headphones, uh, you might want to grab them and, uh, jam, jam your
buds in now, um, coast, fun.
How to respond to, um, my, uh, parsing of weather, aviation weather, maytars and taffs.
Uh, he says, parsing maytars in any programming language, isn't as easy as it sounds.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to make it sound easy.
Since there are a lot of maytars standards, Jeremy Swadney started a purl parser for
maytars years ago.
Yeah, I've seen that actually, um, it's, uh, it was on, uh, there's a fresh meat project
page for it, uh, the GO maytars, that what it is, um, yeah, well, the service that I'm using,
I don't remember what it's called, uh, they seem to, maybe they're using a version of it.
That's very possible.
Let me see, what I use is, uh, so that's just, it enables me to put in the
aviation, uh, code for the airport that I'm looking for and it gives me the aviation
weather.
What is it?
TMG TMDG.co.uk interesting.
That's where that's where I get it from aviation information and weather, right?
Yeah.
www.tmdg.co.uk.
Okay.
So, um, I don't know if you've seen this thing, this, um, dig spy page, which to me is like
the ultimate aggregator if you're looking for, you know, slash dot type geeky type stuff.
It's, uh, an Ajax based web page and you, you put your browser on that page and it just
starts to scroll with just all these digs that are coming in of stories mainly technology
related.
And it's fantastic, you know, that is truly the river of news.
Um, and it's, and I like it because it's, you know, when I'm interested in tech news,
I can go there and it just kind of flows down my screen and I can click on something
when I think it's interesting.
I'd love to be able to have, you know, dig sites for all different types of topics.
I know that dig has categories and stuff, but it's still mainly a tech oriented community.
Um, but something, excuse me, I'm not even drinking this and say, I'm drinking tea.
Something that showed up multiple times is, uh, this Hallophonic MP3 sound.
Apparently, um, there's this file done by, uh, uh, a company and out there, I think, in
Switzerland, that has made a Hallophonic sound embedded into an MP3.
I don't know if there's any technology behind it.
I was, you know, I was rushed and too lazy to figure it out, but I figured we would
listen to their example file together.
It's supposed to give a complete spatial effect.
Um, so you can even hear sound above and below you.
So I have not listened to this myself yet.
Let's just listen in.
Okay, good, good left and right separation.
There you go.
The matches flew over my head.
That was kind of cool.
Cool, that way, I'll be over here, well, the guy with the matches comes back this way,
we're in across each other in the middle, come on, come on over here.
Okay, stay over there if you want.
Okay, if you're going to walk that way, I'm going to step over here.
Okay, okay, it's driving me nuts.
Yeah, my God.
Uh, all right, where are we, pod safe music video stuff?
Oh, yeah, apparently this kind of sucks, apparently there was a video was made of pod safe
for peace, but I guess it didn't work out, you know, and the reasons being that it all
had to be worked out was slow in Orlando who wrote the song, which is, of course, you
know, when I said, hey, you know, I'm looking for people to start creating music videos
of pod safe music, maybe I should clarify that, this all does become a part of the unlabel
if you will, which we've talked about before.
What I think will happen, or what we're actually, you know, designing and building right
now is let's say you're a video maker, a music video maker, you'll just call yourself
that, pod safe music video person.
I believe that there should be able to, you know, we should be able to come to an agreement
between artists and the pod safe music video makers, so that you can, you, you can basically
put images, synchronize images to their soundtrack.
And the entire point being that you would have an affiliate and an affiliation with that
artist, so that when someone watched the video, the concept is, of course, they will want
to go and buy something from that artist.
And just like Amazon, you would click into their store or whatever, and you'd get referral
fees.
And I think that that's part of what the unlabel is going to look like.
Everybody should be able to have a record label because what is a record label?
It is promotion.
Now that we know the technology is not important.
Of course, you know, the record labels have an art department and they can connect writers
with these musicians.
You know, that's, that's really when you're trying to, you know, you, that's like a laboratory.
I don't believe too much in that, I think it's much better to have a community of people
who hang out and meet each other, which, of course, the pod safe music networks should
also turn into that if we put some, like, forums and stuff, but there are ways to make
this work.
And at the end of the day, I think everyone will be able to benefit.
So, I don't know, just brain farting here.
What's this?
That's a video feedback which I want to share with you.
You won't be able to watch the video, but the audio will be sufficient.
So, Guy and his kitchen, and in the background, a sense out.
And this is a response to the endless source of throughout the 6th and seems to about
a port safe music, let's give him some cues.
You've spoken about video drivers making videos for artists.
Well, I got into folk broadcasting for the other way around, I needed some music to go with
my skateboard videos.
So, I want to join you, the pod safe music network, and see if you need your feet.
I just started my own feet, got my own domain name and name, what a good way to start
2,000 to 6th.
So, if I can help some artists with names on video, I'm very glad to do so.
Now he's making a couple of sense sails, nice close up with a machine.
You can find the more info about my video project on www.yolo.com.
Cheers, and people to do the work in 2006.
Music I use is MinWitDrop from Bang Out Production, which I found the pod safe music network.
So that's YoDo.com, J-O-H-D-O.com.
So that's exactly what I was talking about.
He wants to help out artists by making cool music videos.
I think he should be able to do that, and yeah, I told you that people who are working
really hard between Christmas and New Year's, not includes work on the pod safe music
network to get the sails generation.
Thank you, by the way, for all the feedback you've given about means of payment, I can
tell you now that we definitely want to use multiple forms of payment.
So cell phone will be one way, would of course a credit card or PayPal will be another way
to purchase from the pod safe music network.
Working on the licenses, the agreements that the artists, because they'll be able to
opt in whether they want to sell or not, they won't be obliged to sell.
We have to put in some technology for that preference, they say, you know, make this track
available for sale, all of that stuff, and it's a lot of work really is.
I think that as I said, you know, going out to San Francisco, this coming weekend will
be testing in the next week.
So, well, hopefully we'll see some features come online in about 14 days.
Hey Adam, this is Sean J from Shakespeare Cast, calling actually for a couple of reasons
one.
I'm trying out this whole listening to your broad cast and having an idea and popping out
my eye talk and popping it on there and leaving a comment, so we'll see if that works.
But the second reason I'm actually calling the main reason is that behind schedule on
you, I'm listening to 303 right now.
And you were talking about some more of the, you know, pay-per-song stuff on a pod show, music
network.
And I got this idea, if there's a way that you could set it up to have people who are
purchasing, let you know which podcast they heard the song on or that referred them
there.
That would be just another thing, a way to collect data as far as, you know, where people
are here in the tunes and who's recommending them and that kind of thing.
We only do one song in episode, just kind of tagged on at the end there and it's mostly
the popular stuff that you guys are playing.
But I thought, God, how cool would it be for people to know exactly where these revenues
coming from, you know, accident ashes is drawing so many listeners to purchase this song
or your show, et cetera, et cetera.
And then you could even throw, you know, maybe a penny per purchase to that podcast.
And you could do it all, you know, we have to be registered with the Pod Safe Music
Network.
So we've already got accounts.
So you could just link it up that way.
Of course, that means that money for you to buy a new guy.
Oh, sorry about that.
The hell was that all about?
Sometimes when Mac does that, it goes into this audio loop for no reason.
This is something I noticed with this new power book ever since I got it.
It hasn't happened in a long time.
Anyway, I think it was really clear what he was saying.
Brilliant minds, think like, there you go.
It's exactly what it is.
It's a referral program and I think it will work that way.
And I think, in this case, we have a basis product which is a music which people are
used to paying for and artists are also used to understand that there's a chain, a sales
chain and if we do it based upon the principles of Amazon, you know, there's an affiliate
relationship.
All of that stuff comes into play and I think everyone, as I said, everybody can benefit
and listeners should be able to do that as well.
And the way you do this is by creating a network.
And the network means that, you know, we all agree to certain things and obviously with
any network, I'm going to be involved in there's going to be a great amount of control
if not actually I should say this one thing we've always stood for is I don't care what
you're doing on your podcast as long as you're keeping your audience growing your audience
and having a damn good time, a skipy good time, a CC which it would say.
But that's what it is.
It's putting a network together and the network includes parties who all have some
equal say in this and it's the creative people who are consuming at the same time.
It's listeners, viewers, readers and there's also people who want to market and advertise
to these groups and we have to have this dialogue ongoing to figure out how we put it
together.
I tell you what, you know, people listening to this show, you've been really vocal.
You really help me make a case towards some major advertisers about how we talk about
products and how we sell products and even if we're interested in selling products.
So it's been great and I really appreciate it.
And this was a big hit.
On the other night, when I drove, when I picked up Christina from a party and drove her
friend of hers home, I cranked this one up in the shaggy one.
Farts are so fragile, they're fashioned from gas, why must we squeeze just to help them
to pass?
If parts are so strong once they break in the air, they're a shall-bye away, over a room to get
cleared.
But, Farts were made out of super ball stuff, they bounced right back when they fell
from your butt, they keep that sense of the smell would be rough, if Farts were made
out of super ball stuff.
Farts are so friendly, they follow your tail, although we can't see them, they leave.
They leave quite a trail, Farts are in color, they're so hard to find, they're so fun
to light, as they leave, you'll be hiding, but if Farts were made out of super ball stuff,
they bounced right back when they fell from your butt, they keep that sense of the smell
would be rough, if Farts were made out of super ball stuff.
Just imagine the free time, it's always they would be in my pocket, I'd keep on the
throw at your feet, if Farts were made out of super ball stuff, they bounced right
back when they fell from your butt, they keep that sense of the smell would be rough, if Farts
were made out of super ball stuff, if Farts were made out of super ball stuff, they bounced
right back when they fell from your butt, they keep that sense of the smell would be rough,
if Farts were made out of super ball stuff, if Farts were made out of super ball stuff, they
can understand that teenage girls were totally into this, right?
Cookie Cutter Girl, aka Lynn Julian, if Farts were made out of super ball stuff, that's it for
today's Daily Source Code, I'll be back tomorrow, and then we wind up the week just before I
head off to San Francisco, thanks for listening, thanks for staying subscribe to DailySourceCode.com
and your feedback to AtaminCurry.com.
Bye now!