A domain registration is a gift that keeps on giving.
For all the cakes in your life, do your shopping at godaddy.com.
Listen to this podcast for a special code that you can use to get special discounts at godaddy.com.
This is Delta CR Charlie, 511, and for God's sake, don't buy Sunfeld DVDs.
Because my carry-chat is a racist, don't watch when it keeps on moving.
Because he's a racist too.
You can listen to this podcast, however, because Adam carry is not a racist.
Adam carry doesn't hate anybody.
In fact, Adam carry loves you, dear listener of DSC.
Hey, I don't know where that is.
But Adam carries the power to the other side.
Oh, I've lived at 54 feet below the ground.
I've traveled westbound.
I have to get to get to get this gift on my wish list.
But the limits tick with the quickness, and still no one's solving the business.
No one hears speaks my language.
No one here has my currency.
I'm the founder, and the wise man, so this song is a one.
I'm going home.
I can't feel my legs anymore, I'm so far from the shore.
Behind the lift and girl with the face cast, so live in the cramp of the candy dance.
This can't be half for the move any faster, so I'm stopping trying at the air.
Like an asshole.
There's no one in big for language.
No one here has the currency.
I'm a thief under and the wise man look me dead in the eyes and he's the power.
I can't use the pay for all he can't use the two bucks and the wonder.
Oh no!
I remember the days when they got to you all and I can't live today, for let me know the chase from all of us.
I remember the days when they got to you all and I can't live your whole journey.
I can't live today, for let me know the chase from all of us.
Oh my God!
It's too big and you're busy staying true.
But my heart will break into you.
raste!
Well, it's definitely different.
Johnny Sonic Pesso's Euro kicking off the daily source code for your food bar Friday.
We are without a doubt fucked up beyond all repair.
It is episode number 511 of the Charlie Good Morning, everybody from Northern California.
San Francisco in the Curri condo, beautiful morning.
The sky is completely red.
The sun is just coming up over the clouds in the distance over the day.
And even though, in fact, I'm going to actually put down the shade here.
So I can see what's on my screen.
You know, there's an old, uh, damn, that's loud.
There's an old sailor's, uh, Ryan that says, uh, uh, reds, uh, reds guys at night.
Sailors delight reds guys at morning, sailors take warning.
I don't know, though, because I've had some really nice red mornings here in, in the Bay area.
And the days have been just fantastic.
Although yesterday did you hear what happened in London?
They had a typhoon run through London?
Now Patricia called me about that yesterday.
She said, you have no idea what happened.
I said, why?
It was like a typhoon.
It was the weirdest thing.
And of course, we're south of London, south west of London.
And she said, it was tremendous hail.
And, you know, the cats actually came running in before the hail hit.
They were just like, boo, like bullets out of a gun.
Because, of course, they felt something weird was up.
As, uh, as pets often do, I guess, with, uh, with these natural, uh, phenomenon.
And, uh, and, and apparently, it's not all that uncommon for that to happen in, uh, in the UK.
Okay. So, uh, had that one to the list.
We've got typhoons.
I want to thank, uh, let me see, who was at Jason Smith who sent in that song, uh,
Johnny Sonic Pacell's Euros.
And you could find that on the Podsafe Music Network.
Of course, links to that in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Oh, man, I'm telling you.
So it's, uh, even though it's been a short week that I've been here since I didn't
even tell Tuesday, it feels like I've been here for a month.
Cricky, really, really busy. Yes, I, you know, I was so tired every single night, uh,
when I get back, um, there's a stuff that I, that I do for, uh, for serious.
Because, you know, we have, uh, four hours every single day, and, uh, we do promos.
And all kinds of different stuff. And so I typically do that last second one.
I just stir my, uh, tea here.
Uh, I was so tired that I recorded them last night.
And I was convinced that I had transferred this file onto the server for Peter up to get in the
morning, because he gets up around six o'clock, uh, a, uh, Eastern time, uh, because he's in, uh,
in Florida. And, you know, he starts to put in stuff together. And, um, and so I woke up this morning at
630, uh, Pacific Standard Time. And, uh, the first thing I do is, you know, my eyes open, okay,
it lights on, uh, let's see. And then I usually, literally, uh, not within, uh, you know, within a minute
of waking up. I start checking email, because I've just, you know, the engine runs. The
brains go and I'm, I'm moving while I'm getting my first cup of tea and all that. I see an email
from Peter up and he says, wow, it'd be really cool to be starting on stuff. But, uh, he'd been
waiting for like two and a half, three hours. Uh, I, I, I thought I had transferred it. It literally
was just sitting there. The, uh, the folder of the, of the server, the FTP server was going to send
it was, uh, was open. I guess I just never made the drag. Oh, man.
Uh, really exciting stuff to work on this weekend. Now I'm going to go to Los Angeles Sunday
afternoon for a couple of days, Ron and I are going to go because we've got, uh, uh, and now we've
got some meetings in Hollywood, baby. And we're going to hook up with, uh, you know, with people
that who've been working with in the LA area, uh, Mark Giorgio Motornemkov. I, I hope you're going
to have time to see Marcus couch as well. You know, we're going to, it's really, really busy.
So I'm sure we'll never even get, uh, three quarters of the people that we're supposed to be
seeing, but, uh, I'm going to be there for a couple of days coming back Tuesday night, uh, but
this weekend Saturday, I have all Saturday planned because Cas Blaster Mike, uh, who, as you
know, is the, uh, is the developer of Cas Blaster. And it's the, the program that I've been using
for. I should tell you that up, I must be several hundred episodes at this point. I've been
using it to, uh, to produce the daily source code. He has created video blaster. I'm not sure
I like the name, by the way. I, I, I still like Cas Blaster video, but it doesn't matter, um, and
it's essentially the same concept only for video. And he sent me an alpha version yesterday. Dude,
I got to tell you, this is like a fucking revolution. It is exactly the software that I've been looking
for. Um, now I got to play with it some more, but, but really what you fire it up, it's just like
Cas Blaster, where you can load in clips. And by the way, it can be Windows Media, it can be quick
time. It can be an MT4, even flash. You load that up into little players. And then you, you know,
you can select cameras. You can have multiple cameras. Uh, now I have a built-in camera on my Sony
via, uh, it founded immediately, but you can also switch between cameras. If you had another USB or
Firewire based video device, or any other type of video input I presume. And, and you just switch
back and forth. And, you, you play a clip and it automatically plays the clip and it switches the
camera off. And, and, and, and at the end, it poops out an MP4 file. It's like, yes, this is exactly
what I've been waiting for. And of course, you know, the, the step after that will be, uh, direct
upload to the, uh, to the podcast delivery network. Uh, so I can't wait to tell you more about that
on Monday. Uh, and Mike said I could talk about it as long as I didn't give out the link to the
alpha version. Yeah, duh, that makes sense. Uh, let me see. Yeah, thank you all so much for sending
information on, uh, on the, uh, the road tax thing that I'm trying to figure out in the UK. Of course,
I'm, I'm here. So there's not much I can do about it. And, um, and Patricia doesn't know where
all the paperwork is. And it probably honestly, that's not her. She shouldn't have to worry about
that. This is my crap that I have to deal with. And, uh, and, and, and as simple as it should be to
be able to essentially pay road tax, I can't even get a straight answer out of my friends in the UK.
Hey Adam, Mike here from Fishball Acoustic. How's it going? Logbooks. What are they? Well,
you don't need to worry. There's nothing too complicated. You don't have to keep a log of how many
hours you drive and what you do with the car and all that kind of rubbish. All it is, it's a, it's a,
a name for the vehicle registration document, which is a document that, uh, every car, every registered
car has. Um, I think that the number of it is V5C or something like that. But basically, it's a
registration document that just says, uh, your car's make it's color. It's, uh, year registration,
registration number, chassis number, you know, stuff like that. And, uh, that's it, basically. So you
should have one of those for your car. All you need to do is to pop it in the envelope with the rest of
the crap that you sent to the vehicle registration, um, people and then Bob should be your mother's brother.
Tailwinds, right? Yeah. I don't, I don't know if I want Bob to be my mother's brother.
That doesn't sound right. Okay. Now, first of all, I, no, and I don't, I don't want to delve
in it too, too deeply, but a log book that doesn't sound like the description of a log book
what you did. Sounds like a, um, a registration is not what that is. It's a registration document,
which, as far as I could tell, was not required as for the documents. I even know what the
fucking registration thing looks like. Now, listen to Adrian Pegg, who's, I think a guy who's pretty
much together. And he tried to explain it. Hi, Adam, it's Adrian Pax from London. Uh, without going into too
much detail, I'm boring, everybody rigid with a road taxi in the UK. I just thought I'd try and explain
you very quickly. Um, the taxi represents the, well, it's actually called a road fund license.
It, it, uh, it's, it's, it's effectively the money to go to the government, to pay for the
upkeep of the roads in the UK. And, uh, road users have to have, um, uh, a taxi in order to legally
use the road. So, uh, simple really. In order to buy a taxi, uh, you have to have a couple of things.
You have to have a valid insurance for your car. And if your car is more than three years old,
you have to have an MOT certificate, which is, which is, as you, uh, correct the guest is a mystery
of transport test, which is, um, uh, only applies to cars of, of vehicles that are older than three
years. Um, and this is where the vehicle is tested for those things, including, uh, you know,
like some breaks and tires and stuff like that. Um, so the whole thing is tied together so that
you, you can only buy the taxi's completely on the road if you've got those other two bits.
And I think the, um, there might be some confusion, but I thought your Jag was in New Jag,
which case it won't be needing an MOT for another couple of years. Um, so that's that, um,
um, and the other thing that you mentioned was the, uh, logo, would you actually, uh,
like a receipt for a car release, sort of, it's a document, a little document that goes along with
the ownership of that vehicle, uh, have all the details about previous owners and, uh, uh,
where the cars, the, you know, and, uh, and so on. Um, why are you being up sending the logo, uh,
I can't imagine unless there's some confusion as a Y, um, over the MOT thing. That's, um,
I'm not sure they're confusing. It's typical British beer. Oh, yeah, yeah. Anyway, take care,
keep on the good work. Exactly. This is what I don't, I don't understand. Why do I have an MOT certificate?
The car's not three years old. I've had it for a year. Yeah, uh, uh, uh, my dealer, um,
you know, it was time for the annual on the car. So I, you know, they picked the car up. They
pretended to do something. They throws, you know, they take the older oil out. They put new oil in.
They charge a 200 pounds. And I know how that works. And, but they also gave me an MOT certificate.
Why are they testing the car? It doesn't need not to be tested. Why does, uh, motor vehicles,
or whoever, whatever the department's name is, why are they asking for this stuff? And, and if,
if I'm the original owner of the car, do I even have a logbook?
Ah, thank God we have this song. And now we're from our sponsor. It's the yanks versus the brits.
We'll try to be sure the crazy, but everybody knows that it's a parent to see.
Let just like you and me, it's the yanks and the brits you to add down. The yanks versus the brits.
Mind the gap. If you're sitting there in the UK thinking, oh, I know what the answer is.
Please feel free to use our UK-based phone line to leave your message about the case.
That might as well do the US numbers. Well, uh, because, uh, I think the brits have the
yanks this week on phone calls.
David Longley sent something in for today's football festivities, which I thought was a very
interesting idea and good experiment. I want to try with you right now. So he says,
yeah, you know, sure you have various jingles that that help people remember the phone numbers when
they want to call in to the daily source code. However, he says, I've got something that could be
even better. Now, this will only work as far as I know for people, uh, senseo. Excuse me.
It's will only work for people who have, uh, are listening to the show on speakers or on a
headset that you could wrap around the mouth piece of your phone. He said, why don't we try and, uh,
and give out the actual DMTF tones. So instead of you dialing, all you have to do now is now pick up
your phone. If you need to get an outside line, you want to hit the outside line code first. Now,
put the mouthpiece of the phone up to the speaker or into the headphones if you're listening on
headphones. And let's see if this works. So that would be the UK number. Did it work? Okay,
yank, standby. Put your phone's mouthpiece right up there to the to the speakers. Ready?
Let's see if we can dial into the Jersey number.
I think, and if this works, I have a great idea. If this works, we can do the
surprise phone line of the day. And, and I will, uh, I'll give you the tones and it'll dial and
you'll see what it is. I mean, something that we should, uh, experiment with. Now,
I'm not going to tell you who this is until after the song, but it is from the late 60s,
early 70s, and you do know the artist. I wish you were the fisherman. I wish you were a king.
A fisherman's mom has a good love. She keeps the cabin clean.
And there is nothing wrong with you, they love you.
The queen is a hover. She has changed.
She keeps the jay money. She keeps the jay money.
I am for the man who walks in the sun to let's die.
And there is nothing wrong with you.
I wish you were a fisherman. I wish you were a king.
King's what has a good love. She never does a thing.
And there is nothing wrong with you.
Now, it's not possible, but I think we can get this song on the pod save music network.
If anyone was interested in it, which I like it. I have not heard this song in, uh, I got to say at least 10
years. This is that. I think it is 30 or 35 years old, as you can tell from that real 60s kind of echo chamber.
You know, I'm not going to tell you who that is. Why don't you, why don't you give it a guess?
Call into the phone line number in the voicemail. Let's see if you can figure it out.
Some of you may already, I've given enough clues and hints already, but I have not. That is, I love that song.
It's just as good as the first time I heard it. Hello! Hello!
Hey, tractor two times! You got way too much time on your hands, my friend.
Yeah, what's up AC? This is Jersey Todd, the official nighted music college of the
Chacha. Dude, did you spend some time in West Virginia a few years back? Well, you know,
when I used to think about West Virginia, I used to think about coal miners, some beautiful
country, maybe the Appalachian Trail, a C++ college football team, except not anymore did,
not anymore, and neither will you, because today on the Delhi source code, I'm bringing
you a band that from now on will make you associate West Virginia with the best cleavage on the
pot-safe music network, and some kick-ass rock and roll. The band is hydrogen,
now West Virginia, their song is blind, and oh my god, she can sing to check this out.
I'm a fool like you want to fame, I just do the thing, and you know that it's too
I want to want you want to, when you want to, it's just another day.
No more time, I can tell, break my plans and I'm in the end, cause I'm giving in.
I'm gonna say, couldn't be just the same as the same thing, we will wait to see you.
I'm gonna follow you in the night, but will you just go by my grind?
I'm gonna go by my grind, and if you want more now to lie,
I'm gonna go by my grind, and if you want more now to lie, and if you want more now to lie,
what am you doing?
When you're kyooing 23 when you say am I listening?
I'm not listening!
Take the ball, take the place, take it all, just prepare to pay,
cause you don't go.
Now more, follow you in the night,
and, most importantly, just customize.
I want my love you will find
I want you just to find my grace
There's no one more right on the other side
God I think I'm so weird
Oh, time man
Now that's football, stop
It's food for the football
I think I'm going there
Damn, hydrogen from West Virginia
Fly high, fly blind blind
Her name is Julie Todd
I'm looking at the picture right now
at
Potshow.com slash music
Oh my god
Dude, you are so rough
I think I'm in love again
I don't know who this is
but stop fucking calling Disneyland toll
Yeah, I did go to school in West Virginia
and West Virginia is pretty cool
You forgot to mention moonshine
There's another thing West Virginia's got going for it
Yep, now I've seen this, I've seen this type of specimen in West Virginia
Mm-hmm
Damn
That's the read from the bio here fortified with cutting edge riffs
Intelligent lyrics and massive hooks delivered by Julie
Just Julie, a stunning front lady with a multi-active range
The result as a formula set to conquer everything from alternative rock to modern hard rock
To timeless metal without sacrificing credibility
I don't know what all I mean
Is man, you guys kick ass
Damn, they have another song on P.M.N.
Hold on, let me see
Break and be down, let me listen to that one for a second
They were both uploaded two days ago
Let's see if that one sounds like for a second
Oh, it's the ballad, of course
Do you mind if we just listen for a second
Because
Is Julie is very talented
I bet you this one kicks into it
I'm like a major fucking overdrive
These guys are great
It does take me back to my days in West Virginia
Only about three months worth of for I quit school
I didn't know what the hell I was doing there
Oh, she's seems beautiful
I just gave the illusion
Oh, oh, oh
Shit, okay, we'll do that on your own time
Go listen to that
Links at the show know it's a daily source code dot com
Last night only in America ladies and gentlemen
No Gibson was on the tonight show
And he got nothing but applause
It was great
This is what a great country America is
First you can get kicked down, stomped into the mud
Whether it was deserved or not is is
You know, I think it was of course it was deserved
But it has nothing to do with it
For whatever reason you get stomped down kicked in the mud
Drag through it
And there was talk of Mel Gibson never working again in Hollywood
And yesterday he comes in this night show
And it's like, you know, I said, man, I fucked up
He didn't actually actually say that
But I fucked up, you know, I straightened up, I moved on
And I've got to face it
And that was, it was such the right thing
He said the audience went wild
And his new movie opens up tonight, how convenient
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
All right, let's see
I see there's anything else like a talk to you about stuff that we're doing
You know, you should definitely be on the lookout for changes
On the plus podjo, plus podjo.com
Because every single day there's new changes coming out
The dashboard is now functioning
The collection stuff has all been cleared up
The program guide is about to change
There's so many, so many things that are just now just rolling out
One after another
Now that we kind of have a shit together
And I'm really feeling damn good about it
Also, yesterday I got a demo of
The next version of our IPTV interface
This is the stuff that will work on the set top box
Oh, man, it's so awesome for video and for audio
And not just that, but it's, you know,
Imagine if you imagine if you will
In a world where you could take
You know, your, your hot people, your hot music, your hot videos, your hot shows,
All the stuff that you like, your channels
And you could have those all in your television
But really could navigate it with a remote control
Easily
Oh, man, you're going to love this
I know you are
Coming soon to a set top box near you
Adam, it's Bernie from Bernie's world
And I haven't sent you a tune in a little while
For just the right tune for a food bar Friday
And I think this is the one
It just hit the pod save music network
It's by a band called WW3
I'm not going to give up the title because you're going to get it from the tune
But trust me, it's a lot of fun
It's perfect for a food bar Friday
Sabrina, it's Sabrina, check it out
My new t-shirt
Oh my god, am I got you?
Look, right
Like I know, I know
Yeah
Wait, what's going to wreck
Oh, I don't know
I think I'm going to rip the collar off it
Oh my god
I cut the glass
I skipped school
I hold that
To sleep out
In the parking lot of coconuts
Where they had the tickets on
Downward two of struck
Didn't view us on the show
The tape I like but I get knocked
Take the sounds
Take off your t-shirt
Miss Montelica
You were two years old
When ride the lightning came out
You felt no pain
My birds and dad
But she tried when they canceled
Baby, what's that?
You mess around with my pants
Take off your t-shirt
Miss A, C, D, C
You don't even know
Hell's bells from a hate brain
You got that shirt
It's urban stuff, it's so cool
We've loads of bells
Just like we saw lunch
Take off your t-shirt
Do you remember the badminton guideLaughing
Hey, Lou
I mean you know they did not sing every rose as it's thorn
The sheep must be short, take off your day shit
Or you're in me, the number of the beans was not six
Six, seven!
I'd like to learn about what's happened from you
But they can't play them all in TV
Time to take off your day shit
Take off your day shit
You can't hear me song for the band
That's on it, take off your day shit
Take off your day shit
To the waste they get off beyond
It's you can't hear me song for the band that's on it
Still so crisp from the hanging on the rack
This t-shirt stretched across your back
It says nothing of the sacrifice
Through a thick end then
When snow and ice did I throw at the last lens
This one on the red of our sand cotton shield
Now face the face
And shard to shard its revamp
Your act on red song's weight rack
What you let them be
Cause they belong to mine
Take off your day shit
Can't hear me song for the band that's on it
It says molly hatch人
Show your feeling
This is a waste they get off beyond
Is you can's some for the band
That song you don't know the guy is printed on your garbage
Take off your T-shirt
If you can't name a song but the band that's on it,
duh, Bernie, thank you so much, man.
Awesome song to wrap up a football Friday at least
in the daily source code.
And of course you can find out one on the Pot tape
using them, Seanout, say that is rosecode.com.
I'm not saying it's a today.
It's Friday!
Monday Tuesday Wednesday Thursday,
football Friday and a spinal fun on the week.
Nothing really, uh, all that pro-found for you today.
Other than I've just been thinking about the world in general.
You know, nothing too heavy.
And I'd say, uh, the, uh,
there are two things that I'm really noticing.
The one thing is, if you look around, uh,
and everywhere in mainstream media, people are being laid off.
We're seeing this happen at clear channel now that they know
they're being broken up and, uh,
and take in private, which of course is basically the end
of that company.
It will be split into little 80-bitty parts.
Um, we see journalists being let go.
But in our world, we're hiring.
And it's great because there's a total,
I can now almost visualize the talent as it just flows
from mainstream media into the next wave of media.
I'm not going to say we're new media because we're here
and we're kicking ass.
And along with that goes, um, and this is, you know,
I just been thinking about the, the zoom a lot.
Thinking about, wow, you know,
what, why did Microsoft make some of the decisions it's made?
I think probably the most promising thing
that we were all, we collectively were probably the most
upset about those of us who really care is that, uh,
although the device has Wi-Fi built into it,
it doesn't really function the way we expected to.
And I think we could take that a little bit further
because what I'm seeing now with all these different networks
providing connectivity from the cellular phone companies
to Wi-max, uh, to some version of universal Wi-Fi,
which of course doesn't really work.
That kind of got fucked up somewhere along the way
in all the, all the agreements of how Wi-Fi is supposed to work.
I think that we're going to see handheld devices
that'll just be like radios that will just pick up a signal.
Now we still have some work to do on battery life.
This, this Wi-Fi shit really can drain your battery.
Although I gotta tell you that Nokia E61, I'm still loving it.
It's holding a quite fine with Wi-Fi being on and used all day long.
So it, it does get me through an entire day.
So I think that, you know, if you just take away the knowledge
of how all the protocols and how all the wireless should work
to the, you know, on the back end and just think about, you know,
normal folks, just joblo picking up some device
and all of a sudden, you know, there's like television on it,
except it's not a network that is like ABC, NBC, CBS or Fox
or is there another network?
And, you know, there's like radio on it,
but it's not really radio.
It's, well, hold on, you can listen to stuff live
and you can also make sure that show is always ready there
and waiting for you.
I think we're going into a fantastic new world.
And I'm seeing devices coming out now,
it's gonna be in 2007 and I'll probably do a whole year wrap up
and oh, let's do some predictions as well before the end of the year.
Because I think that we're gonna see some really radical changes
that will actually take us back 10, 20, 30, 40, 50 years in time
and what the most interesting thing will be
is to see how legislation is going to be adapted to that.
It's not much, but it is my final thought for the week.
I'm gonna do some mistakes.
There's a fool about Friday and I'm spinal thought on the week.
Oh, okay, everybody.
Well, I want to thank you so much for listening
as I said, I'll be playing this weekend
with Cas Blaster video or Vitt Caster.
I can't, Cas Blaster, I see V, I just, it rolls nice.
Cas Blaster video.
Please send in your openers.
Do not send a five, 12 for me
because I've got one from Pdo,
which is a very good one.
It's a real tin foil hat moment opener.
If you've got other openers, send them along.
Starting at five, 13 as far as you want to go.
Even if I get duplicates, you know.
I pretty much always use them.
Adam at podshow.com is where you can send email.
Don't send it to curie.com, please.
Please, get solved fucked up.
So, Adam at podshow.com is the place to send comments, emails.
Even if you have a small file, you want to touch.
I've also started scanning promos.podshow again.
And show notes for today's episode can be found at dailysourcecode.com.
Hey, I'm off to the office.
Gotta go do some work.
Have yourself a great weekend, everybody.
Take care.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best and the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery.
Podshow and Lime late.