Delta Sierra Charlie, three, two, three.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped my ass.
Today's news!
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't mean us thinking crazy.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding.
It's so curry.
Today's source code is on coming here from the Curry Connage and say a cold.
And someone missed me foggy today.
You're in Surrey.
It's like a back of the 60s, by the way.
It's hard to confirm it on the week show.
Turned out by so smokey as I waited on the corner.
Not watching over the people passing by.
Played up my way too for the girl.
It's special.
She's a girl in life.
It's like a giant.
It's like a giant frog.
Love that you are smarter than me
I can't love this because I don't speak your language
Love feels it fun, no, what you want to say
I've never faced a high cause I don't speak out of my way
But I feel as if I know what she wants to say
I've never had the sunshine in her eyes
It's run the dawn and I hope that she won't smile at me today
I've never faced a high cause I don't speak out of my way
But I feel as if I know what she wants to say
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
So, actually a very interesting band
I was a hunting around the Potsay music network
Actually, I think it's not a band. It's a guy
He'll reach from the buy on the Potsay music network
The cinnestrels is a project from Steve Dix
A British musician residing in Colone, Germany
Steve's music harks back to the British sound of 1966
Do I hear it like an echo or something?
What is that?
He's got an interesting website
Interesting story about this guy
And I heard the song was like yeah, that's kind of like a kinks dedicated
Follower of fashion type vibe
I'd decide to play it
I got a lot to do today
A lot to talk about
And as I was putting today's show together
I had a whole bunch of mini epiphanys
I'd have to say, well there we go
Now it's gone
I think I had something misconfigured
Sorry about that
Oh, I know what it is
It's the other headphones we're feeding back
What do you get when you're doing it all in your own studio
But still running on cast blasts
Here on the Tashiba portage
Loving it very much working perfectly
We're gonna stick it to the man
On today's show a couple of promos
New announcement of a new show
Join the network
We've got more pod safe music and a whole album you can download for free
I'll talk about that
I also want to talk about my pod show
And
If that's not enough
I don't know what is
A lot of people ask me
How do I prepare for the show?
This is one of the first things that really hit me this morning
The way I do it actually is throughout the day
Whenever I receive an email that I think is interesting
Or I want to talk about it
I just want to put in the show
If I'm in Gmail I'll tag it with a label with a DSC label
And so it's shuttled off elsewhere
I don't see it anymore until I need it
If I'm on the blackberry since there's no direct communication
I actually have a way to forward it to my Gmail account
And through a whole bunch of rules that then shows up in the same DSC folder
And then what I do basically in the morning is I just start at the bottom
And work my way up towards the top
And I realize that
Well over 70% of this show is put together by the people that listen to it
And it makes so much sense
You know this is
Okay, so let me just follow on that for a second
This is a tremendous opportunity
Remember when when we were talking about mashups and how they were put together
And the problems with mashups the rights issues problems
You can't really even create a mashup and sell it on a CD
Because you know a mashup often consists of so many different songs
That it's almost impossible to clear all the rights to it
Now that's not a technological problem
That is my gosh when songs are played on the radio
There are actual computers that are registering that sound
And it's called BDS and what it does is it takes off the number of airplay
So that basically the whole music industry
Which includes the broadcast industry knows which songs have been played
How many times at any given moment
So the technology is there it's just the licensing has been difficult
But now I'm podcasting now that we're in this digital realm
I'm thinking you know there's there's an opportunity here
To create identifier
So basically if you sent in an audio comment or if I played one of your songs
You know pod save music network
Then you would automatically be notified that your audio or your video
Even for that for that matter had been traced to this
You know let's just call my podcast a mashup for a moment
To this mashup and it would be you know identified
And this is something a lot of musicians ask me about who upload their tracks
The pod save music network they say well if someone uses it as a promo
How can I be accredited for it?
And of course you know I'm sure pod castle will put that on their show side
Or you know the put some permanent link
But you know it is of course not you don't get credit every single time
That someone plays a promo particularly not if other pod castes are playing
You kind of get my drift right?
So this is one of the things that
George's Russian scientist is working on and I'm very excited about about the really the endless possibilities of this again
I don't think it's tremendous science although there is definitely some science in it to get it done
But I think the technology is there to make it all work
Excuse me
Yep, I have a fresh cup of it right here
George's mom listens by the way too
She's I think his whole family a Russian scientist living up in Canada
Hey George is mom glad you tuned it in
Okay, as I said a couple of promos and this is a project that I've been keeping my eye on just because I've heard the first two episodes
Love this stuff to death and it's also kind of in the family you know six degrees of separation
This is a Jaymax brother. Here's his promo
Hi, I'm Mike Pico. I'm not really the first wing commander in the Nova Squadron
But I play him in an original podcast production
I'd like to invite you to check out the podcast with a little something for everyone
It's a sci-fi story so 90% of the folks on the web. Let's know from understanding what's going on
The next time you get the urge to buck orders and save my tail section don't
Plus, we have great writing. Well, don't look at me. I'm just some dude with too much time on his hands
The children we got podcasts located at WWWW. Showing the guys I'd have this problem
To be a family and all podcasts so much Christians may apply offer where we're prohibited
Results book I win China and our media families are not at home before wait what I'll never mind just check it out
Join the fight for survival
Do you believe anything is possible? We do where are flink?
We believe in an internet that's safe from virus hidden scammers. We're earthlink
We believe your personal information should be just that personal and we believe your internet should be a friend
Not a fo. We're earthlink
Make this smart choice visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you earthlink
We revolve around you
I'm a guy so I'm a trist in the jail
Of course it's got cats performing live ass or you hear me burning burn
It's all to be binding on it because you're gonna be all an MP free form
In the shed we be known to keep you see one only bonds from the deep form
Sweating lyrics over in and that speech form
You're in the computer for some other than free form
And the son of each week keep you on it for teachers whatever you can post up drop a letter
Hey, what's up guys and welcome to guycast
This is the show we talk about cars sports drinking sex drugs rock and roll and whatever the hell else we feel
You keep listening we'll keep talking
My name is Tristan and as always the ugly guy sitting across your meat is Jeff
That's right. You can hit up a brand new website at guidecast.net
Where you can check the map to see where our listeners are listen to past episodes
Get the dirt on who we really are read the latest comments and vote on our weekly topics
Topics like our top five favorite cars are most memorable sporting events and hanging out at the bar plus every week
We bestow the honor of ultimate guy of the week on somebody who deserves your respect
By the way guys, this show is not for the faint of heart or people are sensitive ears
That's right. This show is like hanging out with your boys
So don't expect any lame
So just hit subscribe and iTunes or check out the site every Monday night through latest episode new content
Join us next week for a new episode until then my name is Tristan and I'm Jeff this is guycast
Hey Adam this is Dr. Dave of the shrink wrap radio psychology podcast saying
Thank you for inviting shrink wrap radio into the pod show family
I'm a regular DSC listener and I'm definitely on board with all the big dreams that you and Ron are bringing into reality
shrink wrap radio features interviews with interesting people in and around the broad world of psychology
The format is a weekly show that runs around a half hour in length
Ending with a piece of pod safe music that ties into the week's topic in our first 20 shows
We have covered such topics as the meaning of dreams psychedelics developing intuition Islamic psychology
Consumer research
Gestalt therapy
Buddhist meditation mythology
And we've even touched on the inner workings of the infamous zodiac serial killer
We've got a lot more interesting topics planned who knows?
We might even get into the psychology of the trans oceanic metro sexual
Free wrap radio is must listening for anyone interested in what makes us tick
This is the show that brings you all the psychology you need to know and just enough to make you a little bit dangerous
So Adam thanks again for bringing shrink wrap radio into pod show
This is Dr. Dave saying it's all in your mind
Yeah, no kidding back
And I like these types of shows
Just like the skinny on sports you know fastest ten minutes on your iPod
This is like just no enough to be dangerous, you know, so you can be a cool guy at that cocktail partay
Welcome Dr. Dave great to have you on board. Welcome to the pod show podcast network fantastic
Um, and as you heard Dr. Dave could be our guy. He could be the guy that would actually help us out in our metro sexual moments
Metro sexual
It's Adam Curry's Metro sexual moment
And Curry's Metro sexual moment
Yes, indeed. It is time for the Metro sexual moment
Try to move it up a little bit in the formatting of the show
So that we can have our friends on the serious stars one or three
Participating all the joy
Adam says John Dwyer in regards to the Metro sexual moment from DSC 321
There was a question about moisturizers and acne. My dermatologist highly recommends moisturizing every day
This helps reduce the overproduction of oils in the skin that cause acne
The key to this is getting a moisturizer that's oil-free. There are many brands available all at any surprise
I use Johnson of Johnson's purpose. It's oil-free fragrance-free high-poilogenic and contains SPF-15 sunblock
This way you get all the benefit but no girly smell
For you or UK listeners when I lived in England I used a moisturizer from Nutrigina that I got at boots that did the same thing
If you're wondering what the hell this is all about
The Metro sexual moment is where us guys huddle around and just kind of talk about stuff that we normally
Wouldn't feel comfortable talking about in the locker room or around the water cooler, you know, but it's a and by the way
To Chris Rockwell dude, I'm not taking away the man out of us. It's important stuff
Become a little bit more Metro sexual my friend
And you might actually get laid
Bob Brown says hey Adam first off damn you
Due to your constants and sale references I went out last week and bought one
I have to say for the most part systems great simpler than making regular coffee and faster than making instant coffee
And then it goes on to complain about pods, there's a Germany
But what it be prudent he says to add to the Metro sexual moment is and say oh minute or something
I'd love to get advice as to what I could drink
And it could in turn beef up sales of particular coffee product
God knows I had that sales since I opened my air for six months
I'm sure the promoting your coffee pot would be just as effective
Okay, well you mean so like what to drink and how to be swive and what to serve
Is that is that what you're talking about?
Yeah, I'm okay with that
Send me some stuff audio comments by the way what I really need to the Metro sexual moments
Little tired of just reading a G-mails
Back to our shaving topic
Shoot, I don't have the name of the person who sent this to me
But Gillette has a new razor that will likely replace the mock three five blades instead of three
Also available in a powered version
Excellent
Well, we will try it out of course and I'm still working towards
You know trying to talk to the Gillette people see we can get every registered listener of the
Daily source code at least he wants one a a mock three or who knows maybe a mock five power razor
I'll talk about registered listenership and a bit and then finally Kevin Shelombog Adam
I was listening to DSC today while walking along Michigan Avenue in Chicago
Oh man there's show reaches doesn't it
During the Metro sexual moment right about the time you said something about women digging a well groomed man
A gorgeous woman walked up next to me at the stop light
I could not help but take a look
She was absolutely beautiful with long blonde hair and sexy high heel leather boots
What's more?
She glanced back at me almost with a giggle
Just then I realized I'd been humming the Metro sexual theme song
Well, was there any continuation to the story my friend?
Inquiring minds need to know
Quick update on developments back at Pod Show HQ
I know I have my extra long days now that I'm in the cottage where I can do everything I need to do
Until about four o'clock. That's one San Francisco wakes up
And then we continue until about 11 or 12 o'clock. It's double duty
But I somehow I really am I get to stay on top of things
And I get to listen to so much more during the day undisturbed. It's lovely
I got an email from Rockstar Kevin
He really has a lot of the lead development on the what we're actually what we're calling my pod show because you know
Besides creating the pod cast delivery network for the pod casters
Which and with that comes a shitload there's you know show sites and all kinds of modules
You can put on it with the you know the last top the last just an example
Last five song pod safe music songs you played from the network
It's very simple system cast blaster integrates into a beautifully
He sent me because basically I think the beta is starting is starting getting ready to roll
And it's out of my hands you know yesterday of Brian from operations
Sent out an email is like okay we're moving people and I think a girl a guy in the bottle of the first ones
That are going to be migrated onto the podcast delivery network
So when you think about you know just some of those modules I'm talking about it
Makes a lot of sense to give listeners a lot and you access to a lot of that to and by the way
Is there difference between a listener and a pod cast or maybe not in many many cases
And I'm so excited about what actually so I want to say you know
The whole team but definitely wanted to sing about Kevin for a second because in the past couple of months
He's just
He's gone to kind of a and I've talked to him about this personally
So I don't feel like I'm revealing anything by saying it but he went kind of from an introverted guy into just a superstar
He'd like like a switch went on
And he's you know now he's he's managing all these other developers and just this shit is really coming together
And it's very very exciting and I think we get our maybe I guess we get our logins today or whatever
So I'm just you know it's just an excitement thing for me
And you know that means that a lot of these podcasts that are joining the network
You've been hearing announced on the daily source code
They'll also have access to that portion
So you know as we grow we're going to grow this beta and then of course the point at the end of the day is that everyone can come in and use it
So but we're just taking it safe and rather get some you get some stuff out now and let it break and work on it and continue because
Like almost like the pod safe music network sales system which I'll talk about later as well
You know we're not building a store we're adding functionality and we're doing it as a part of the unlabel concept
If we just want to go and recreate a store then you know why don't we just put pod safe iTunes on the front door
You know I don't think that's what we want to do anyway excited
And I got the tickets for Christina's show
I think I mentioned that she wanted tickets to go to panic at the disco
Which is essentially an independent band that just recently got signed and they're really catching some fire
It's pretty good band and so she found two tickets on eBay
You know the sales prices like 20 pounds
I think she wound up buying them for 60 pounds
Fucking scouting what a scam that is
I'm so not used to it because you know always used to get free tickets or backstage passes or whatever to get to almost any show
And I probably could still do that if I wanted to
But you know you forget how you know what an industry has been built up around all that
Including people who buy tons of tickets and then auction them off for three times the price on eBay
You know it's just the way it works in fact make no mistake
I know many many artists
Who as a part of their contract with any venue will demand a certain you know blocks of seats
And they literally turn around and sell them off to scalpers
It's and usually the artists themselves don't do it, but their managers do famously accused of this was
Ah, was it Arnold?
I want to say this is a fool or was that the pig on green acres?
Uh, Rod Stewart's manager was accused of this in New York
I don't know if he was actually convicted but
So I don't want to say that it's true for a fact
But trust me when I say there's a lot of money going around in that business
A sheet load
Let me see, I think I've time to do this before the satellite window closed
The creepy sleeping show podcast
Intensive music
Inturn to the parts of us
And now a message from the president of the United States George W.
Good morning
This week members of a House and Senate Conference Committee
The police and agreement on reauthorization of the Patriot
Art of victory is able to
The Patriot acts tougher criminal penalties and increased resources to come back
The dangerous spread of facilities
Creepy sleeping
Judge Carl
I wanted to mention that
Although I've said it before and I will say it again for a few more weeks
We're very happy to have a review sponsoring a podcast
Heather and John L.
This is an exciting development in advertising in podcasting
Where you have a company that understands what its audience is
Basically supporting its audience
Of course in exchange for
For getting young girls to switch on to active use
I like the product myself. I've used it ever since I've had contact lenses
But the show is pretty cool
It's Heather and John L
What is a tagline here
I think it's like two girls
Let me see
I'm actually looking at the banner for a second on the site
Two friends get a microphone
Will they get an audience?
There you go download.acuview.com
Those of you listening to this on the series stars
Thanks for listening
We'll be back tomorrow
Pacific Coast Hellways up next for you
If you want to hear the rest of what we talk about here in podcast land
You gotta go download it
I
Actually got an email from Mark Szeeda
Hey Adam just wanted to give you a comment about your sound
Or to win your satellite window closes
And yes, it's kind of related to sound
Virtising
Apparently it's a TV show in Australia called
Rove Live
It's a Letterman type variety show. He has a segment called
What the
I guess isn't what the fuck
Where people send in pictures of funny signs
Newspaper ads and stuff like that
They don't make sense or give a different meaning
To what it's meant to me and you understand
It's like headlines so I'll jail and I'll call it
He uses the same musical signature to introduce his segment
And as a regular viewer of the show
I'm accustomed to hearing the sound and associating it with
What the?
So every time you announce that your satellite window is closing
You play that sound like get the natural reaction of saying what the
Interesting
That stuff works man
It really does
And you just can't deprogram people profit
Which is the beautiful thing of the Vulcan mind trick
It came standard with and that is kind of interesting
It came standard with this application called Countdown Clock
Which I think I have another 20 days to use before
I'm going to I'm probably going to buy it
It works well
I like it. It's very simple. It does everything I wanted to
And so the question is
Is the sound
Clear or the rights cleared or is the guy
Is Rove Live using the sound of the countdown timer
All these questions and more will not be answered
Oh
What was that?
That's weird
This is the first time I've seen this happen with cast blaster
What is that?
Well, maybe this is just a cropped sound file
Hold on
Oh, that's not right
Let me try another one
That works
I do want to play that jMac thing
Hold on, let me just open it up then
Try a media player
Oops, so that would be today
Oh, man
Okay, so this is where windows breaks down for me
Find it so difficult to navigate through the file structure
Here we go. I mean the folder I want
Where is
Oh, man
Tell us this
Oh, here it is
JMac. Okay. This is going to come through on the other sound
Mr. Curley to jMac
Out of light dot com
I wanted to say thank you very much for playing that promo for us
We got a lot of great feedback
And sort of the artist megatron
He's pretty excited about that
We put a lot of hard work into it
So it came out really good and we're really excited about it
And megatron wanted me to say thank you very much
for sending that off to your buddies over a series
So he's really geeked about that
Another thing I wanted to talk to you about was
The pot safe music network
We're really really excited about the pot safe music network
Being able to sell artists tracks
Because a lot of artists we work with will be really excited about that
They'll be able to make money off of people here in the music
But however it's hard for us to keep up with the latest and greatest
That you guys have had submitted to you
By artists so it's hard for us to keep up on the latest tracks
And being a producer I never realized how much work it is
I'm sure you already familiar with it
With all your experience in the in the radio business
But I didn't know it's so busy
I mean I'm constantly busy
I'm constantly doing things research and looking things up
So it's really hard for me to keep up with new submissions
On the pot safe music network
And get them over to our reviewers to check out
To be put on the show
So here's the deal
My idea is to maybe place an RSS feed
For each genre of music
So that we can add and remove whatever genres we would be interested in
To our feed readers
That way we can stay up on the latest and greatest tracks
That have been submitted to the pot safe music network
And maybe in that feed you can supply a link
Rate to that artists pot safe music page
Now I think that could be done with relatively little effort
On your guys' sights since you guys have some world-class developers over there
So I think it would be a great thing
I think it would be really great for me and other podcasts too
So we don't have to go search in a mile all the time
It's conveniently there if we need it the RSS is there
I'm sorry there I apologize
I guess I haven't done my homework and it's hidden in the site somewhere
And I didn't see it
Otherwise thanks
And I look forward to hear your feedback on this
Thanks for taking the time
I'll be in touch
Thank you
Well the good news is this whole site is completely RSSified from the ground up
So actually let me just check for a second if you go to
I'll check for you
I'm pretty sure it's what you're asking for is not there
But I know it's very easy to do
So I'm looking at the new submissions
No
Okay
Doesn't I don't think that'll be a problem
As you know there's an RSS link for your most recent
Shows played there's an RSS feed for
I think the top 10 songs
So I think it would be relatively simple to create an RSS feed
For new submissions and do it by category
And I'll ask Chris Rockwell if you can if you can put that in
It may have to wait
You know a week or two before we can implement that
Because it got like Jersey Joe
And I think Dan going over all the code
And we're tightening everything up again
We're about to do credit card transactions
And we definitely found a couple things that we wanted
Different done differently
So I apologize it jumped a gun a little bit
Although I have made the purchase
I have made actually a purchase pod say for peace
You know we brought slowing to the mix
Just for testing purposes
And it works fantastically
And again we'll talk about pricing in a second
But a lot of second I'm rolling one up here
Remember this is just us podcasts is not on the satellite
You know I can do whatever I want to do
Yeah, let's definitely get that going
That's a very good idea
And it would be I mean obviously what we can do is we can do
An RSS feed within closures
Because then you know at least not
No that doesn't I mean that's just not a good idea
I don't think that
Well maybe it is a good idea
Hmm
It's just you know because it's such an open honor system
Where you know you can download all this stuff if you're a podcaster
And by the way with the system I was talking about Russian
Russian George scientist George
You know we'll be able to keep a little bit better eye on that as well
If we see that you're only downloading and it never reappears
And a mash or something that you know you can put back into the network
Then you're not contributing and you know the way you should be
You can't just all be taken not give
Oh man I can see this so clearly
I can really see it happening
And it's going to go beyond audio for sure
For damn sure
Lots of comments about the sound quality of the show
And I had some thought about that as well
There are
You know since I started using cast blaster
I think that
There's a difference in MP3 encoders
I used to use the lame libraries
Which I think are probably the best
But it really adds a whole extra step to the show
So I didn't feel like doing that every single time
But I basically reencode
Either I'd make an AIFF
Of my show on the Mac
I'd do it with
Audio hijack pro
And then I'd encode that to MP3 with the lame
And I had some custom settings
And it was really really good
But it's just too much of a hassle
Now I'm using cast blaster
I think cast blaster uses the windows media player
Codec to create the MP3 files
I'm not too sure about that
Since Mike did the whole re-writing
By the way
I think he just released another re-writing
The problem that you just witnessed
And I'm using beta 51
Is now gone
And there's some other little buggies that are gone
So I just haven't had the time
Yet to back up my files and switch to
To the new version
But I'm sure it's working well
Along those lines
This is interesting from Finland
Verve
Victor India
Victor India Romeo Victor Echo
Greetings from Finland
From Finland Adam and listen to your show
Since last summer
I've been somewhat addicted to it
I'm not a Mac user
Don't have an iPod
But I've enjoyed the world of podcasting
With my creatives and micro
This is what we're talking about yesterday
You don't even need the portable player
You can just listen to it on the
You know through the website
DailySourceCode.com
So I bought that in August
I've been very happy with it
And I, of course
I have to use Windows MediaPlayer
To put my MP3s into it
After downloading them to iTunes
Yeah
That's a pain in the ass
But now I have a problem
Since you started using Cast Blast
I haven't been able to transfer
The DailySourceCode files to my Zen micro
With the Windows MediaPlayer
I get an error message reading
Quote invalid access to memory location
And then the MediaPlayer just crashes
This is strange because all the other podcast
Transfers with no problem
Including the earlier episodes of DSC
For instance, 316 works
I did some testing
Open322 audacity
And saved it to MP3 again
And I worked fine
So I'm thinking the problem could be in publishing
Or in the ID3 tags
I don't know
I'm a girl
It's too technical
The hell is that
I know lots of girls who are very technical
But it's cute anyway
This does sound like a problem
And I wonder if it's a problem on the encoding side
Well
That wouldn't make sense
If what I just said is true
That Cast Blaster uses the Windows MediaPlayer in Coder
Then I should make any difference
So I guess I'll have to hop into the Cast Blaster form
And find out what that is
Ver if I'm sorry about that
We'll work on it
We'll figure it out one way
The other that is pretty critical
That it works on Windows MediaPlayer
Here's a question from Mike from West Fargo
North Dakota
Oh, this is about making videos
He says he's a little bit behind on his
See, listening to the conversation we had earlier
He'd like to make videos for Podsafe
Music songs
Is any way I can do this and report back
Mike, yeah
I think this is exactly what we're working on
Where it will be automatic
And this is going to be a part of the unlabel
It makes so much sense for
You to create a music video
And then help the artist sell
Some music
I thought somewhere I had a question about
Podsafe
Music network
What was that
Shoot, you know what?
I think that's I probably saved that for tomorrow's show
About the pricing
Well, there was one thing I wanted to say
When we do put the unlabel pieces in place
Of course
If you help sell
A song by the artist
But you don't want to take any commission
Of course, we will enable it so you can give that to the artist
That's just the one thing
And I think we will bump into this again tomorrow
When I play that, when I play that audio comment
But that's a given
I just want to make sure
And again, as we roll out testing
We don't want anything
Let's just get this thing rolling
Let's get it all working
Before we even talk about what Penny's pod show
Would like to have
Um, okay
This is very fun
I'm so excited about this
Hi Adam
My name is Mark
And I'm from a small town in New Hampshire called Cornish
And yes, it's named after the town of Cornish in England
I've been listening to your podcast for quite a while now
I just finished listening to DSE32
And I'm sorry to hear that you had to go out and buy a windows computer
In order to solve the audio looping problem
I even more sorry to tell you that I have a windows computer
I've always had windows computers
And I've experienced the audio looping problem numerous times
When playing back audio files, especially MP3 files
In Windows Media Player
And my favorite player called BS player
When playing back recordings that I made in audacity
Which is what I'm using to record this comment
Hopefully this is just a quirk of my system
And you'll never experience it with your brand new to Shiba
Anyway, I just want to let you know that it may not be that easy
To get away from the looping problem
And that I think what you're doing with the pod show
And the pod safe music network is really great
How do I become a registered listener by the way?
Thanks Adam, take care
Right, so that's going to happen through my pod show
And it's going to be a really cool interface for listeners
To keep track of their shows, to share the shows, to share episodes
That they like to connect with other listeners
And to get free shit, I hope
If you're registered to listen to this show, that's what I'm going to do
I'm going to try and get you free shit
So about the looping thing, I don't think
These problems are related
In fact, yesterday and I posted this at curry.com
A new site was brought to my attention called
PowerBookDefect.Info
I'll just read a little bit from the site
We are power book owners that are experiencing a sound defect
In the latest PowerBook G4, the problem occurs on the high resolution
Models 15 and 17 inches
Update, also on the 12 inch
And probably on all the new PowerBooks being sold in shops today
A lot of people says that the say
Oh, this is interesting, a lot of people says
That the echo slash loop problem disappears
If you use an external sound card instead of the internal one
This insulates that all new PowerBooks have some sort of damage
On the internal sound card that provoked this error to happen
This of course is exactly the problem you've heard here on the daily source code
So far Apple's official statement is
No multitasking, only use one sound app at a time
And this is a lesson for me as well
You know, this is like
You can't do this as a big company
You know, with such dedicated followers
Look, I got wronged by my partner
By 17 inch, the new G4
He's got all kinds of audio shit and he bought logic
And he's got a different problem
Where logic just overloads it overloads the CPU
When you use like three tracks or some MIDI tracks
It's just fucking crazy
It's something's wrong with these machines
I can feel it, you know
And it seems like tens of thousands of people are having this problem
And all Apple really has to say at this point
You know, hey, we take you seriously, we're working on it
I'll be good for another three months if you tell me that
No problem at all
But just tell me, don't tell me that
You know, this is a problem we'll update you
And in the meantime, I'm only used one sound application
What do you think we use these things for?
We use them for sound applications
I've been the biggest promoter of this platform
Guy, yeah, yeah, yeah
So powerbook defect.info, okay
It's still going to demand
Taking the lawn to our own hands
Something like that
Let me see, I'm not going to do this next
Let me just see
Shoot man, yeah
These shows are getting too long
There's too much for me to say
I'm just skip this next bit
I'll move that over to tomorrow
Hold on, we're going to do Trinity tomorrow as well
I think
You know what?
I'm going to skip all the rest
I'm going to leave that all for tomorrow
So we have some other things to talk about
Except for the financial aid podcast
I was, he's got, oh, he's always has some good stuff to say
So check this out
This is Chris from the financial aid podcast
Here to talk to you about money
Specifically the money from the pot safe music network
Music store
Maybe the pot safe music store, I guess
Regarding what I as a podcast
It would be looking for in terms of revenue from
What you call the splits
Not a whole lot
Because I'm already getting the music for free
I'm getting the license to play for free
It's really very generous
Of the artists to share that
To be willing to take the risk of that
A podcast doesn't go just fling it up
On one of the peer-to-peer networks
And completely undermine the AD artist's efforts
So I would say at most
Maybe a penny
Or another idea which I'd be hugely in favor of
Would be credit
A song credit
So for example
Let's say I refer 80 people to play
To a buy a drive away by Matthew evil
Hey Matthew, that's a plug for you
In return for that I would get maybe 80 credits
That I could use towards
I could give them out to friends
I could say, hey, why don't you pick up
A free song on the podcast
Music network courtesy of the financial aid podcast
Here's a free credit
Or you know, it wouldn't have to be one one
It could be 10 to one
10 credits
Give away one song
Something so that people who are not
Not, you know, not podcasts
Just can get a piece of free music
That is unencumbered and unrestrict
Anyway
Just an idea from the financial aid podcast
It's financial aid podcast.com
See you around
Yo dude
See I knew I was right
And actually I was better prepared
Than I thought I was
This is what I should have played when I was talking about
The pricing thing
This is the comment
From that I thought was going to be played tomorrow
So I'm sorry about that
Absolutely
And I love that thinking
I love the idea of the credits
And you can give credits away
Fantastic
And we should be that flexible
At the unlabel
To be able to make those choices
Like that very much
We'll definitely work on that
Finally then
I got one more piece of music
I want to share with you
And the reason why is because of this email
A reodrebica
Says
Adam I manage the San Diego band Bill
You played their song
Sound Scientist
A while back just wanted to drop
You line about a promotion
That we are doing this week
This is cool
As a bit of a thank you to the podcast community
We have made Bill's new album
Birthday Suit available for free
Download for this week
We spent over six months on the
In the recording studio
And we put everything we've got into it
Really look for people to hear the music
We thought this would be a good way to accomplish it
Being played on your show and the pass gave us a big swell
In listeners in the past
We're hoping the same might be true for getting the album out there
If you think your audience would be interested
Please let them know that the album is available
For free at billmusic.net
Through the podcast play
Back banner
Or directly the download page
Bill's music.net slash podcast playback
Dude
I love this
Man and you know what?
I think this is so smart
I really really do
And I downloaded the album
I've loaded it into my iPod
Love it it's all kind of the same vibe
As a sound scientist
And well obviously
I want to play
I already had a copy of course
Since I played it on the show
But this one's from your download
This is Bill
I'm the source code
On a girl's case
Highly classified confidential
Interface against the guy
You look like you could use a brick
Said as I lived in my head
And I'm a working from a dead tree
Not sure how long I was on foot
Looking for the cloth on a star
On the show when I look together
Thought I had been mistaken
Lookin' in the wrong direction
And I can question David
Just do the answer
Again a chance
Cause when I hit the wall
Just come to the back
And send me up for the ball
Love a lab test
And some men too go
I love a lab test
Mix it up, mix it up
Stir it in a cup
And turn it into
Mix it open to the double tree
Step on the glass
And we're catching on here
You better act now
And I'll think you might have lots of you
A trick, trick, trick, trick, trick
See the wind's all the medicine
Baby, little something
Take the edge of while you wait and don't come
But I'm out of blood
It's kickin' hooked on us
Hopin' up your hands
Let me get you into
I'll just stop
We're just somewhere
To go
And I know
I've got this day
Yeah
In search of the truth
I lost
For ever better stay
I've got this day
That's just a nice piece of music to listen to
You know what I mean?
Sound scientists from Bill
Check out their album
Downloaded for free
Very cool guys
Outstanding
Thank you for sharing
And that's it
I'm trying to keep these shows
A little bit shorter this 60 minutes
Enough is not working for anybody
I'm sure
So we'll cut it for now
I'll be back tomorrow
With the Thursday edition
Of the Daily Source code
Bye bye
Another pod
Show pod guest
Stick it in your ear
Thanks for watching