This podcast is brought to you by Potcho and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Okay.
Deltis here are Charlie 3, 9 or 3.
They pack the bags and off they go.
Though they might be quite far from home.
The world is their oyster and she is his pearl for sure.
It's Patricia and Adam set out for another world tour.
New Yorker's San Fran without her just wouldn't be right.
Yes, she's the real reason for Adam to come home tonight.
But when they're away and they both want to play at the flick of the wrist or a puff on the split,
they can find their way around, paint their whole town for sure.
It's Patricia and Adam set out for another fabulous wonderful,
filled extravagant happy ever after world tour.
Yeah, the part time I've seen her.
I said, oh, what a scream.
Oh, yeah.
She wasn't nice and sweet.
Well, she was pissed.
I've had me.
Who I had a teller.
Yeah, it's the way to love.
Well, honey, you're out of sight.
She lost me in the eye.
This is your goddamn fucking great love for us.
And do your life how it feels.
Run in the back seat, baby.
I will burn up the road.
Oh, yeah.
So look out.
Because I'm going to go to go, go, go.
Oh, I got a feeling.
Yeah, I got a feeling.
That you are a driver too.
And come on.
This edge is rampant down in just for you and flight.
And do your life how it feels.
Run in the back seat, baby.
Run in the back seat.
Who is that 我們?
Well, I'm in the back seat, baby.
Run in the back seat, baby.
Don't see me, I never get up and down.
But I know, in the air, what you wanna be, oh, right
So never, never, never, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever
Don't me again, come on, don't you know you gotta hurt
What you've had, and you're like, how it feels
Running in the back seat paper, running in the back seat paper
the massachusetts it's the gentleman and riding in the back seat kicking off
Chuck Chum three nine three come to you from New York City nice contrast that song
with the canvas and tool what stick stick it in your room stick it in your
baby it's early you know yeah just after breakfast there you go oh man the sucks so bad
are we have an incredible headphone problems today you hear me now yeah okay there we go
hey everybody Christ the sucks hold on honey yeah I'm I have to I have to let me unplug you
let me unplug you on so you can't hear anything hold on can you hear at least one year now
yeah yeah okay I'm sorry so apparently I I'm so stupid I left
I left the cottage and I brought a half the equipment with me I brought with me no headphone
extender cables so Patricia has to sit really really close now I brought two microphones but I
forgot that this I wish you can you move that microphone up a little bit because you're a little bit
soft yeah yeah there you go so you have no place to no I'm not there you go speak speak speak speak
yeah it's okay very good I forgot that the power supply I have for the for the mixing board
is it's a UK power supply but it's it's one of the only ones in the world that only does
220 volts doesn't do 110 volts so you plug it in no 110 and it powers the mixer enough for it
to work but if you want to actually plug in the second microphone then you then you get that because
it doesn't have enough power so we'll fix it when we get to monitor it yes I think that the story of my
life what and home it always sounds like that I always have shitty sounds no what are you talking
about the studio at the cottage is great what are you talking about equipment I'm talking about
equipment I'm talking about equipment now equipment that I should have you know listening to music
and also it's always half half it doesn't work or is that my fault yes no I mean yeah I have
that because we move and then you say I'll do that later yeah I say that right yeah that's true
say I'll fix it up do the wire later now I must say it's such a mess look at this you know
and it doesn't even work I do that later and it's just never happens well I promise you
when we if the Patricia's palace actually comes to fruition or any Patricia's palace for that
and for that I promise you that I'll do all the wires I have a good music throughout the whole house
yeah we'll get so we'll get so into we'll get some of the do it properly now I will say
that you know of course I have a lot of wires and it's very difficult to find enough plugs
in any hotel room and what do I have with me is my trusty gaffer tape yeah so is it so we have a
very professional gray strip of tape hiding a wire that runs across the we moved hotels we're in
yeah yeah that's what I want to say yeah we're in the Waldorf Astoria tower yeah this is more my taste
this is definitely yeah this is my taste no kidding we're on the like the 38th floor beautiful
we checked in yesterday let me just give you a recap first I don't think actually that not just you know
not that I don't like modern or you know 20 hotels but but they have to be functioned yes exactly
until now we notice that it just doesn't function it all and it falls apart yeah that's not fair
yeah because I actually asked Ron a pay a lot of money yeah yeah I said Ron I said where did you put
your your shaving kit you know every guy has a bag with shaving kit and stuff you said well I
had to put it on the floor and if Marta would call him while I was peeing in the bathroom you would
actually turn around and peeing to his it was shaving kit I could just see him doing that no it's
not not if you have a shaving kit it's not fun you're totally wet because the shower leaves
because you take a shower and the thing is a little bit stupid you know so we recommend not
staying at the W Hotel that is not not high in Patricia's recommendation no no no we just do a list
actually yeah I'm very good at it because and I'm not talking about you know it doesn't
need to be always classical it's my taste but I do understand that sometimes people like to
have a very nice and trendy hotel yeah but you know if it doesn't work it doesn't function
and you're not getting what you actually should have for your money what you're paying for
you're paying for no crank up a little bit no little more power there thank you Jeff Smith by
the way for that fantastic opening jingle yeah Adam and Patricia's world tour in that in that
so that's so sweet because he's on the road himself he's in some hotel room
so quick he just writes the word just like that yeah well he was he was listening to our show
he's on the road performing I don't know where he is right now but he just sent it off and
and actually as I was thinking about that I wouldn't mind doing that with you in a couple
years huh when when our daughter's grown up and doesn't give a shit about us anymore I am now
well she doesn't right now I just spoke to her and I have such a nasty feeling in my stomach what
you mean well I just I was just talking to her first I was talking to my mom I have to say
the both 80 let me say that again so I'm all the 80 with power tools I mean very good you know
very they look very young and they act very young but still you know leaving with um with your
teenage daughter so I'm I'm calling every day and so it took my mom and my mom starts right away
all the things that that happened it's happening over there not even asking what's going on
but doesn't matter who gives a shit about you let me tell you what's going on here with me with us
we were doing this where we're doing that I appreciate you mom and she's not feeling well and so she
stays home after all she did it again yeah she's home yeah but you know so what's the bad feeling
about then well no I was so I said Christina I said my mom come to the phone so I talked to her
I said hi honey how are you doing yeah fine she was talking about big brother and uh so and how are
you and you have to take your medicine you have to do and be careful be very nice to you
grandparents because daddy you know and when he comes back and he gets he's getting a bad report
yes right you know you know and she throws the phone down and walks away and it's teenage or
stuff oh and I'm miss her so much it's teenage or stuff of course that's the being so tough you weren't
that way to your parents ever I was I was but I was gonna say that I wouldn't mind in a
couple years when our well maybe it's already happening then when our daughters and care about us
anymore I wouldn't mind doing world tour with you going around and doing shows from different
luxuries hotel rooms you wouldn't want to do that no well thanks I thought you were the one that
wants to travel I want to travel with you when I don't want to show it's okay well how
travel that's the whole point we got to do shows to pay for the travels we're coming to
your luxurious hotel and we will give you Patricia will give you a review on our show okay well it's
okay honey I'll find someone else do the show with me I'll find someone else to do the show with
me on the road I'm a world tour Jeff could you please do a new jingle for me it's uh it's uh
I'm in somebody Adam and Angelina Jolie anyway so I'm just teasing you you would you show
so we're in New York for a couple of reasons and we're actually leaving in a couple hours going to
San Francisco and we go straight from the airport to Monterey to put Pebble Beach for the
conference so we're gonna be at for two days yeah what a bed life yeah horrible but actually
Ron and I were speaking at the barestern's uh internet conference yeah barestern's actually some
of the people who work at barestern's helped us sell our previous company then when they were
to Solomon Smith Barney it was actually pretty cool um this was the first time we really showed
anyone in the in the business community um what we're doing when we gave a demo and showed some
stuff and uh it was it was it was good we had a good good couple of days um and of course Patricia
I also had to get my paperwork sorted out you know um I got an email yesterday first of all there's
a lot of confusion about um uh if just reading the comments at curie.com come extra blogger of course
has a lot to say about immigrating uh into Europe oh yeah of course he knows everything hi uh um
the issue so and I got an email yesterday from meno meno smart from uh show news in the home he said
so I've been listening to the show and uh and reading the web blog and so I understand you're trying
to become a British citizen I'm like no you know I'm not trying to become a British citizen no I
have to I have to have new paperwork because you can't have a marriage certificate that's older than
five years to prove that you're actually married to a European national and because we're opening
up an office watch show UK in June actually I mean we're just talking like a couple of weeks to a
month of opening an office I have to have working papers not just hanging out papers but working
so that's why we're here in case there was any further confusion we got everything yesterday we went
let's see we went down to uh center street yeah and we stood in lots of lines yeah um had
look money orders and cash payments and black pen only and the only thing I heard
constantly was that's $3 that's $3 that's $2 that's $20 that you know from well for as much
we had to go to four offices four offices to get this done because you have to get you know
first you have to get a copy then the copy has to be signed and the signature has to be
notarized then the notary has to be uh for scene of an upostille yeah which is a French word for
another piece of paper with a signature and a raised deal but we got it all so now we get back
uh lots of foreigners actually what we did and so we were in line at the marriage bureau to get into
the building um just that was the first the first step um and and and that's where you go if you're
getting you know if for any marriage stuff I guess and well we have to actually be honest we lost
our American certificate who's who's we chemo sobbe who's we so that that it goes it doesn't matter
it doesn't matter it it would it would have been older than five years anyway it doesn't matter
we needed a new one anywhere it can be older than five years so we needed a new one yeah but you
can be honest about you losing the marriage certificate. No it is somewhat but you know if somewhere
in three house somebody moves so many times like we did and we have so many boxes and still boxes
somewhere who knows what's in there so we're waiting in line and uh the guard says uh oh you're from
Holland because he asked that he was checking ID member the guy yeah it says you're from Holland
well congratulations welcome to America that was really he didn't know that we've been married for 20
years or whatever he said welcome to America that's so sweet and then he said hey by the way is it true
what they say about Amsterdam or Rotterdam you can get you smoke get you smoke yeah dude I'm hammered
right now can you tell let me into the building yeah we're very happy looking aren't we so that was
pretty cool and as I said but we did it it's it's done we did it we did it everything is okay now
and so then after we were done with all that and we actually made it on time we made it before the
330 deadline when all the offices closed and then because we could I was so unfortunate we couldn't
stay in extra night in the W Hotel I really tried to get an extension on our style I miss Emily's that
bad I miss the beautiful bathroom so I was able to get us a beautiful room in the in the
story tower so in the room and I said you know what because American Idol was going to be on
we were going to you know Yvonne was going to come over and have some tea your sister who's in town
on business so you know what I'll set up the studio now so we'll have good sound then of course
you know again apologies that I messed up half the wiring but you left your phone charger
and the you left your own charge but it was on your excuse me you brought the phone
charger was never in my possession it's your own phone look you have to be responsible for your
own communications infrastructure it's true that's true but attached to that phone charger was my
adapter and that of course I should have my phone charging your adapter you've got the
adapter and my phone charger was in there so so when we arrived here and we said we were very
tired take your hand away because you're covering them all right and well couldn't say anything anymore
I mean I had to put my my feet up because you're walking a lot here you know and you walk fast
it's very hard for me you're like there's so much longer than mine so when we came here we were
tired tight tight tight tight tight and I said well you know I'll go outside and I'll find our we
I'll find my a new charger and a new adapter and an adapter for you because I felt very very
you know bad about it so we went outside first I went down stairs in the shop didn't have it went
to the next hotel didn't have it and so I walked on Lexington Avenue and finally as I found
sort of that foreign electrical stores that they had like a fifth of a new camera size screaming outside
hey one of my GPS yeah but actually when I was walking outside I thought oh my god I forgot my
piece of plastic in my mouth because I told you I told the the peeps
yeah a couple of days ago that I went to the dentist and he took everything out on one side
so you have a little snap-in plate with some of my 10th temporary things and it's not teeth
it's actually mullers you know well but but if you don't have them in a smile or the canine you know
the canine the the hooked on yeah so and went whenever you smile now with the other day
at the end of the day just let me explain so people can get a visual okay yeah when you smile smile
for me and I have a smile smile you look like a pirate yes a pirate and I have a big smile yeah
with a big baby holy yeah you see a hundred teeth when I smile yeah and so while I was
walking on Lexington I thought oh girl I have no teeth I doesn't matter because no I don't need
this smile to anybody anyway so and when I speak you don't see it only when I give my big smile
so I'm walking and so I found that store I got it I walked all the way back I came to the hotel
stepped into the elevator and halfway the elevator stopped and I thought shit I want to be upstairs now
the door's open and a bunch of gorgeous I mean you know very well dressed men step into my
you're the only one on the elevator the only one in elevator so I go back a little bit and
everybody steps in and in front of me how many guys how many guys like i think five six guys
four five guys with a very tall guy the tall guy standing front of me and I see Bill Clinton
president Bill Clinton president Bill Clinton steps in front of me and you know I like him oh yeah
you always you'd have a lot to say about him yes I think his package is big he'd it must be yeah
yeah now he's very popular with the name he said he's a big guy he has to say I was very impressed
the moment he's tall he's he's very impressed he was standing in front of me and I thought whoa yeah
you know your whoa but he's whoa he's more whoa than me well he's more whoa to the outside
more I mean wider wider he's you know like you are tall and slim yeah he's more you know
he's about my height is good I have to say so I'm looking at him and in my you know
because I your nature I was in shock yeah so I said I said something like hello
hello because five guys jumped in you know what's coming there was just it came up hello
and he said to me well hello hello hello and I give him a big smile
and while I'm doing that I think oh my god and so you were like hi mighty hello
and so oh man that's horrible yeah that's horrible was not wearing teeth and what did he say
after that well he didn't say anything but he was very very very charming and if learning
and what did he say don't just say that I mean so you said hello and I gave him the big
did he immediately go on shit I bet I said hello that's what he said hello and now he was
just talking to him and everyone know not to say because I turned around I thought oh my god
I turned hang my head down and I thought I'm not going to say anything anymore so you didn't
hear what he said I was very I was just I was just well you're just you're a chance you're a chance
normally I would have said well you are very good looking you're Mr. President I have to say
I understand now what it was going oh big then you would have said that but I thought better not
say anything okay so what have we learned what have we learned from this well don't
don't forget to forget your teeth because you never know when you're going to run into a
former United States president that is just yeah that was my chance yeah we don't go go I think
I if I was into it and I was married to you you could have gotten them with your teeth
probably one second let me just tell the folks who are listening to us in stars a
serious stars 102 that more adventures of Patricia can be found at dailysourcecode.com
and Pacific Coast Hellway is up next followed by a yeast radio well man I can't believe you must
that up yeah but but but so let's just say we weren't married and it's just you and you had
your teeth in would you have gone for for drink yes just for a drink yeah or you're such a
tease yeah yeah I would have go for drink yeah I would have to hold for me yeah that's right you
like you like the young kids you like the young kids don't you well yeah oh man that's funny
of course you I mean he's in a nice story of you I had a drink with Bill Clinton and who knows you
know he might you know charm the depends off I don't know well apparently he's very good
the charm of the pants off didn't he? you probably have something there I'm very curious
all right do we have anything else we we necessarily need to talk about because I got a couple
things we can there's just one thing Michael but remember we're talking about death cab for cutie
yeah about how did it nominated for a Grammy and they're on the pod safe music network and and so
we were talking about that Michael Butler sent in a he actually called the the the listener the listener
line to leave this company yeah check this out hey Adam this is Michael Butler calling from the
world rig in San Francisco so let your listeners know death cap retreat he's not the only big
man on the positive music network let's say I'll name a couple more co-heating cambria macuna coil
make a state subway landed danger doom yellow card nick caves motion city soundtrack alcohol
interior they might be giants I could go on but the satellite window would probably close so one more thing
all right so there you go whole bunch of big bands on the bod said yes yeah it's cool that's you know
what's happening is a lot of independent record companies are figuring this out and so they're
they're understanding that and this works this is only the beginning you're so right so today we fly
to San Francisco we get picked up the airport we don't actually go to the condo since we're here
day longer than we expected in New York that we go to pebble beach for the cleaner perkins CEO
weekend it's basically a whole bunch of a whole bunch of guys who have companies like Ron and Adam only
well you guys are a hit yeah but they'll be boring most of them I don't know how do I know you don't know
that no I think it's gonna be a whole bunch of guys with trophy wives walking around you know what a
trophy wife is yeah yeah so I'm bringing my trophy wife as long as you bring your teeth
yes I know darling so that'll be fun and then because it's I'd forgotten it's Memorial Day weekend
which means the office is closed on Monday but but there's a lot going on and I don't know
how these things happen but apparently there's a why I knew about it a week ago but this is a big deal
there's a it's called the pod safe rock show is being held on Saturday the 27th at the red
devil lounge and I'd have to say there's a three of my favorite bands are are playing and pod show
was sponsoring it and you you want to go to right yeah sure so we have a we have a promo for the show
Memorial Day weekend is just around the corner a huge epic decision to make are you ready or rock
Saturday, May 27th in a heart of San Francisco the rear del loud just be pleased to be
hot Joe in the pod safe music network present three bands in a same three rock and bay area bands
with killer life performances San Francisco's favorite site, pod pop or sir Corneville
uh for the galaxy featuring rock spot in mind for the extra super action show
why you're not really more I'm in a Chinese place and Michael but there's a rock band of
American heartbreak
so get ready a rock and kick off summer in the city where rock lives up the really hot band
one red hot night American heartbreak for the accident and grittled three bands in a same
Saturday, May 27th a red devil lounge in San Francisco for stickers and full details visit
events.pot show dot com more red devil lounge dot com be a superhero and be there presented by
pod Joe in the pod safe music network. how cool is that yeah I can be like Bill Graham
hello everybody please welcome American heartbreak yeah it's gonna be it's gonna be a great show
it's gonna be a great show no I think it's gonna be a great show what about uh just a couple things before
wine that remember we were talking about how I felt that when I was at British telecom we had
our big big meetings that I always had a lot of fun with the uh with the assistance there
I ended up so convinced it's my accent that that makes it work so I get an email
from Lisa yeah and she says hi Adam and she says she's one of the one of the assistance
that that I've been working with says listen to your podcast pretty impressive but the accent
wasn't quite doing it for me despite you thinking that it was a big hit with us PA's I almost fell
off my chair laughing when I heard that you cheeky bugger but even when I said you know
Patricia will probably think I'm so full of myself apparently apparently I am well
you I know you for years and well I'm a cheeky bugger now you are she's absolutely right last night
we watched American Idol anything you want to say about that the two finalists you being the
the musical despair wow they they're both great singers yeah he's moved your hair away from
some of my yeah I can hear all of New York I can barely hear you yeah it's kind of so
okay like this much better can you just yeah and I can see your boobies now too that's good yeah
do that just keep like that I'm very good the very good singers both unbelievable I mean
I think that the singer's equality is so much better than in Europe I have to say well the
I mean I mean of of the idols competition in Europe oh yeah blows him away you kidding me
I mean unbelievable and I don't I don't see the guy what's his name Taylor Taylor
nice nice guy but see him is an idol I'm sorry I'm sorry I don't think it's a time with more
I have to say vocally I thought what's your name Katie I think she has a much more
interesting range there's more things she could do she could be musical she could be
recording star she is beautiful maybe she she X I don't know everybody X anyway in America
but I think that she is multi multi talented and multi-aggressive so beautiful stunning stunning
but the only thing I noticed is she shouldn't wear shoes with ribbons on them no no no that was
not it notice that she doesn't know what she's singing yet the the words doesn't weigh anything
right she hasn't had enough sex life she hasn't had no heartbreak you know that's the only thing
she doesn't it doesn't it's not together with her heart yet
right yeah she has my dad stick around the in the in the mainstream music business for a while
she she she she'll get her heart broken enough time she she'll get that soon enough and then we'll
welcome her with open arms to the pod sick music network that's really fabulous but yeah and I
think she should be the winner okay well I guess we find out tonight is that tonight although I
hear that the voice of the guy is is fantastic yeah but he it doesn't go with his body and
everything I don't know it he could be this jockey something wrong and I'm not don't mean that
you cannot be fat or I don't know what because you can be fat up there's a disconnect and we've
no hair and be a great idol yeah but I don't see it you know what I mean I have a feeling he might
win though for some reason because he it is such an American he's such an American regular I don't know
it's just like it's I don't know I got a feeling that that Americans might really vote for him
yeah because they can also justify with him maybe and we're tired of chicks winning you know
pretty girls with great voices that they keep winning American Idol you kidding me Kelly Clark's
and yeah and we had like maybe we were better yeah maybe you know and well just before
American Idol started I checked into second life and you know that Brittany Mason and Magic
Star and they've all been working on on the pod show palace and there was a pajama party
yeah which was fantastic I mean I know you looked over my shoulder and I went with the hell
you do but it was really cool there was like 50 people in pajamas hanging out and I'm looking at
your face like maybe I should just stop right now maybe maybe I should just not say anything anymore
I'm probably not a good idea I'm sorry okay baby I'll tell you what we'll play one more song
we'll play one of the one of the bands who are gonna be at the big Saturday night to extravaganza
this is uh griddle
I love you by dear at least I'm sincerely love with what I love and if you question my intentions
affectionate man I sometimes know they do what they're so I'm told to sincerely question what they love
I wish I could be the one my side I will see you meet up till I try to raise you
I'll try to love my mind but I'm falling
I'm trying to run my mind I'm trying to run my mind
San Francisco's very own griddle for preoccupied from the pod say music network available for sale now
free and clear no DRM MP3 you can buy it keep it forever go download again if you lose it
give it to somebody the new Beatles I don't think anyone wants to be called the new Beatles dear
but we'll sell and I presume the show will also be recorded the the Saturday show the pod say for
auction so that'll be cool you got your rock close with you bed I'm always ready oh yeah I am
all right hun so I suggest we get pack up our shit we got about two hours and two hours
and that's that's perfect right two hours and in that two hours I will put the equipment back and you'll
pack everything else
oh boy okay it's a beautiful day it's certainly a blue sky maybe just get it maybe we'll have
enough time for a quick walk around the block before we yeah before we leave yeah a little bit fresh air would
so the next time you guys hear from us will be tomorrow at some point from Monterey California
from Pebble Beach I'm not quite sure what time the show is going to be up because now we're on
west it's going to be on west coast time so in order to actually make the satellite window we'd have to
get up at six and do the show I have a feeling you may not be into that I don't know you never know
okay I'll have it ready I'll have the same shitty sound ready for you all right everybody
well I'll talk to you tomorrow thank you very much hun you're welcome I love you baby
I love you too okay bye bye the pack the bags and off they go though they might be quite far from home
the world is their oyster and she is his pearl for sure it's Patricia and Adam said I'm for another
world tour New Yorker's San Fran without her just wouldn't be right
yeah she's the real reason for Adam to come home tonight but when they're away and they both
want to play at the flick of the wrist or a puff on the split they can find their way around
paint the whole town for sure it's Patricia and Adam said I'm for another fabulous wonderful
filled extravagant happy ever after world tour another pod show pod cast stick it in your ear
yet this pod cast and we're great ones like it on the high performance pod cast a
livery network from pod show and line-white networks I love it