This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 3-8-7, portions of this podcast are not family safe.
You want answers?
I think I'm entitled to them.
I want the truth.
You can't handle the truth.
Sun we live in a world that has artists and those artists have to be promoted by other artists
with podcasts.
Who's gonna do it?
You?
You, Mr. Record, exact?
I have greater responsibility than you can possibly fathom.
You weep for the old days and you curse the internet.
You have that luxury.
You have the luxury of not knowing what I know that the ability to play music in podcasts
while tragic in your view.
Probably sold back catalog and in my existence while grotesque and incomprehensible to you
still sold back catalog.
You don't want the truth because deep down in places you don't talk about it parties,
you want me on the internet.
You need me on the internet.
We use words like free and download and pod safe.
We use these words as the backbone to a lifespan promoting something.
You use them as a punchline.
I have neither the time nor the inclination to explain myself to a man who rises and sleeps
under the blanket of the very revenues that I create for you, then questions the man
or in which I provide them.
I'd rather you just said thank you and went on your way.
Otherwise, I suggest you pick up a domain name and produce a podcast.
Either way, I don't give a damn what you think you're entitled to.
Did you order the song play?
I did the job you sent me to do.
Do you order the song play?
You're damn right, I did.
My favorite sits waste, I run with the kick eyes, I'll be forced to cast those.
I don't think we picked up a song, I'll sing it from the mountain, just take it to the top.
I'll scream it till my left heart, I'll stand here till I drive.
The feeling is leaving, it's so cold, it's the sleeping, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice.
I know you're hating me, and you can't shed it, you'll make a rush out of my body, no matter how I can seek you, you'll be so special, now I hold all the time.
You think the same of me, just take it to the top.
The feeling is leaving, it's so cold, it's the sleeping, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice.
I know you're hating me, and you can't shed it, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, if we don't stop, if we don't stop, if we don't stop, if we don't stop, if we don
do, if we don't stop, we'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, you'll be in a cup of juice, and now, if we don't stop, if we don't stop, if we don't stop, if we don't stop, if we don't stop, if we don't stop, if we don
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah controls,
And of course you're gonna be along for the ride. I've been waiting for for a new Danko Jones song to go pod safe and here it is
Came on the network May 12. These guys from Canada didn't actually realize that
I just I'm sorry sorry, but it's the cowbell is kind of my version of DRM actually
You know if I put that in there then I'll know if you copy the song illegally
Jeffrey Sheafer says Adam and Joy Thursday show and a previous show you were talking about subliminal programming or was it micro-programming?
Using the sense sale moment as an example a new-old linguistic programming actually NLP
I can totally see where you're coming from but have you ever stopped to think about the results of unintentional programming?
After you show I was listening to Jethro Tulls, Minstrel in the gallery and a cowbell kicked in
I kept waiting for you to chime in with oh yeah
Oh yeah, I was completely disappointed with Tulls lack of foresight
Where are you when I need you man? Oh, maybe I should create a special little cowbell
Jingle you can play next thing you know I'll be talking with the boys when I come home from work
Okay, well you'd have to talk to Patricia about that first obviously
A little weekend update. Let's see
Rather well kind of un-eventful or
Expected Friday afternoon I had a date with Captain Dan
You know we've been we've only really seen each other flying together and we decided we'd go up to
Dunsfold airfield which is about 15 minutes away from the cottage and ge offered in the lovely United Kingdom
This is where they filmed top gear and apparently they've a hack well the it's an old airfield
It's where the harrier jump jet was developed and built and tested and the airfield is still used and so we decided to go up there and check out see what's going on
And indeed there's a huge hanger with
Probably about 25 aircraft in it
Plenty of space of course no services no fuel no, you know no guy to pull the cut the the plane out of the hanger for you
We'll put it back in which I enjoy so much at Fair Oaks
That's it's there early in the show. Excuse me
But you know we walked around and it's a huge development this Dunfold park estates
Where the 80 companies there but I really got the impression they were quite straightforward about it actually
That they don't intend to uphold the aviation nature of the airfield in fact
McLaren tests their their cars there
Mercedes has a test unit that's on on base
They use it for the most recent what they use it for
Da Vinci code they shot several scenes there and they were actually preparing for the new James Bond movie
So they had an old cop car
a New York cab car
a couple of what looked to be like fuel trucks with
You know explosive devices on the side to you know give us a certain visual effect but not really destroy the cars themselves
And so you know nothing and and besides some restriction like you can't fly in
On Saturdays after a 3 p.m. or Sunday at all like well, that's not gonna work because of course the next day
Saturday Captain Dan and I hopped in 9 a.m. wheels up
Off to Rotterdam go see my mom my two sisters were there
So the flight itself was pretty unadventful although I must say
I must say that I'm getting pretty damn good at the instruments shit is really starting to come together for me
And since I still didn't have the GPS updated properly
I'm pretty much flying on the VORs which are these radio beacons
Which it's very old fashioned but it works so well you tune it to a certain frequency and this thing this
Beacon this VOR is sending out a signal and then basically a needle points to where the signals coming from and so you know exactly
Which direction you're headed sound simple enough right?
Except you got to do a lot of changing of frequencies and talking to control towers and really I'm flying instruments
Which is pretty cool. Yeah, I mean I don't have the hood on or anything and I'm and I'm still looking around and enjoying a little bit of the view
But yeah, pretty good. It's I'm improving and once again I I can safely say that
It'll be a long while before I finish the book of aviation
Cranky that is it's one big ass book
So Rotterdam
Tuxi Core was there to pick me up
Who was I has told you he's my my ground services unit now takes care of everything for me
Drop me off will I was in from Italy Tiffany was there
Mom not doing too well, but she she knew she had to go back into the hospital
But she was gonna go for today from Monday
But she definitely just wanted to be home when all three of us were there and it was nice for us
We hadn't seen each other in several months all at the same time
It was pretty funny, you know because we're all sitting there going like well you know well
Where are we at we're standing in the kitchen and
It was just it was for the first time in a long long time that you know
Here are my two sisters, you know the 38 they're 40
Once 38 once 40 I'm almost 42 and I like dude
We're like all grown up now and we have all this grown-up shit and yeah that things happen to our family too
And what was and so I'm the I'm the the oldest of the three and so you know
And I'm trying to come up with some very something very profound and
I got off on the right foot and I had their attention and then I kind of wound up with so
What the fuck
And the and it's hard to you had to be there, but it was a moment that the kind of work and so now our family slogan is what the fuck
Sorry if I offend you with that we don't use it in public all the time
But mom was a definitely has pain and and they've got to figure out some way to manage that in the best ways to do it in the hospital
So she went in yesterday Sunday on Mother's Day go figure
Willow broader into the hospital and so they're gonna do a blood transfusion today
I believe which is really good because that'll make that you know
Look people go to Switzerland to get these all the time it makes you feel really good and refreshed
And then they're gonna work on the pain management and they hope to have her home in a couple of days and we hope so too
Okay, now
Anything else? Oh of course
So a flight back of course
Unadventful as well lots of
Cameo's name was cloud so we had some bumpy weather, but it was fun
It's always fun when you have to switch frequencies when you're bouncing up and down. It's a good workout
concentration hand-eye coordination
Um, I got home
Chilled out and I finally figured out the GPS stuff. I was able to hook a I post it a note on curry.com
And I was able to get my aviation GPS loaded with European nav data
Although just for the geeks amongst us for a second I definitely boneed myself because I bought this
It's one of my favorite GPS units
It's the the 195 by Garmin, which is it's old fashioned and it's black and white, but it's sturdy and you can drop it
You can haul it a long it just feels really good, you know, and you can also use it as an anti-terrorist device and wax them over oh someone over the head easily
And I I bought it off of eBay and I was really happy with it. Remember that a couple months ago, actually
And I was just waiting for a ticket to get over here and have that have the yoke mount installed and everything
And it turns out that the actual the the land data so the late, you know the actual mapping data
You can't use or configure that you either buy a European one or you buy an American one
So of course I got an American one because I got it off of eBay and you can't change that so I have nav data in there, which is good only I can't I there's no map data in it. So
Frustrating I'll just have to wait until
Until we really have something to celebrate and I buy a
430 and tied into a super luxurious
Autopilot system
One day always have something to look forward to
Speaking of flying
Here's a first from the divorce mail phone lines
Hello gentlemen from the cockpit like take a moment now and welcome you aboard
We have live a lot but 1,000 feet flying time today is four hours 21 minutes to Ontario, California
Oh, and speaking in the wrong microphone here. Sorry Adam
Yes, I'm sitting in the cockpit here and I know you had to comment earlier about being the first of everything
So that's how to be the first to give you a call from the cockpit
Sitting in my trusty speed the 757 on my way to Ontario, California
Long flight today. It's gonna be beautiful though. Did want to call and say hi?
We'll show you listeners all the best. This is Robin from Insightworks.com. It's IN has YTWLRKS
I've got Com. So long
And tailwinds dude. I think that is a first
Actually to do a promo from
From the cockpit. Yeah, and did you hear that by the way now? I met Robin and this is a true true avator
Real arman listen listen to how he says just listen to the inflection in his voice when he says
It's gonna be beautiful because he really means that and then and there's something about flying above the world
That that does affect you emotionally. Let me see if I can find it
Find it
The 757 on my way to Ontario, California
Long flight today. It's gonna be beautiful though. Did you hear that? Yeah. It's gonna be beautiful though. Oh, almost like it was in love
All right cool well if you're at
37 38 thousand feet you can give us a call. That's real easy
Voice mail numbers and there's no greeting so don't be surprised if you get the tinny mechanical voice saying leave your message or send your facts
In New Jersey 201 625 6357 or in London
O207 681 3753
And that by the way I've been told by many is the correct way to separate the digits in the UK
O20 for London 7681 3753
Kind of really interesting one this is this is where
This is where the show is gonna get pretty interactive for a moment here and I'm kind of
Joining you know
This is already a track in progress, but I felt like when I got this next comment
I listened to it. I'm like oh, yeah
I think I think the daily source code listeners will want to get involved in this and maybe just maybe we can turn it into a feature check this out
I Adam I've been listening to the Charlie for about three months or something
I'm from Alberta Canada
Listen, I had to send you an audio comment. This isn't for me
Although I wish I hadn't a good excuse to message you about my boring life
There's a fellow who
A virgin no less who has a website called a virgins plea.com and uh
He's got a hot friend who's gonna like sleep with him if he can get five million hits in 30 days
I'm thinking
Daily source code those guys will help him out
So anyway plug him put this uh put my audio comment on your in your next uh Charlie
Help this guy get laid all the details are on a virgins plea.com. He seems like a really nice guy
Help him bust a nut
This is Jordan from Grand Prairie Alberta Canada
Be so I mean sea crest. Oh, oh no
Well, see now this is a true friend
And I'm listening to this and I'm like okay, let me go check out this website
A virgins plea.com by the way. This is what my day consists of here at the cottage, okay?
So you have to have gotten up and have taken Christina to school actually when Christina is is called to the fund of the class and says
You know, well, what is your dad do? What does your father do? What's his vocation? What's his occupation?
And then well, he helps uh virgins 25 year old virgins get laid. Yeah, I need listens to
People talk about that all day and there's big green chair. Yeah, that's my life
So like I go to this page
Hey guys like you know 25 he's not bad looking he's not hideous. Let's put it that way. He looks clean and and fresh, you know kind of like a
He looks okay and his girlfriend the
The girl who promised this wonderful gift the gift of of a first-time love to a man
Is she's hot definitely
Definitely and he's already at 2.9 million hits within seven days. So I think he can actually get it made and
Get laid get it made and we should help him out
Yeah, so I went to the site and I'm thinking well, what's the background on this and well luckily enough
He's uh started what he calls audio blogging
So he doesn't quite know that he's really doing a podcast or that we're gonna force him to do a podcast because I need more of these
This is something simply called update one. Let's just listen to a little bit and you hear some of his reasoning and I thought it was pretty touching actually
Hi everyone and welcome to the first audio update from a virgin's plea.com
Okay, now you know take a second to get a custom to the voice
All right, he's a little hyper in the beginning it it drops down about half an octave later on
So he's still not an unattractive guy my name is Jeff and I'd like to thank you for taking the time to listen to my
audio blog
I'm the star of the website of virgin's plea.com and
The whole goal of the website is to get me five million hits in 30 days so I can lose my virginity
But why do I want to lose my virginity so badly you might ask?
Well, the whole story goes back a few years. Well, I don't think that's a hard
That's really not the question is why you're doing it in this man. Oh, that's the question when I was 21
Four years ago to be exact and I was engaged to be married to a woman
I thought I would be with for the rest of my life
Six months before our wedding she decided to cheat on me
Was
Those were just some dark days for me
The shit I went through back then was just nuts
Needless to say I really didn't date much for the last three years after the pain and suffering caused by that
I just couldn't bring myself to date a woman again. Okay, so so he was holding out
For his one true love. He was going to have sex on his wedding night. How beautiful is this?
Old fashion, but okay beautiful
And six months before their wedding day
He finds out she's been cheating on him which is the cheating is one thing
But you know if you were saving yourself a presumably she was saving herself as well
That's quite a blow that so that would freak me out to so for the last three years
I've been single alone and was that any real drive to want to get laid?
Is it coincidence that this is national masturbation month at all you think?
Well a very very hot putonic friend of mine said that if I could get a website with five million hits in 30 days
She would have sex with me. Okay, so first of all dude you're in okay you're in no matter what I think in less
She's a real bitch
She will eventually take pity on you even if you get close. So I'm not worried about it
But it's interesting. It's an interesting experiment now it may not be the best way to lose your virginity through an internet bet
What do you mean at 25 having never been laid the overwhelming urge to have sex is just starting to get too much to handle
So I decided to do it and so far
I've gotten oh, yeah, we had to wrestle you to the ground for it one million visitors in about seven days
So I'm well on my way to actually making the goal
But I mean it begs some bigger questions, you know, is the internet right to use for things like this?
Yes, I don't know. Yes, I mean the support I've seen out there though is just amazing. I think maybe you should do a little prep course in
Second life, you know, so you know all your moves and you kind of get some feedback on on your sequences and you're and you vibe
I've gotten hundreds of emails from around the world including some from soldiers in Iraq
People in Australia
You know Romania
Started a my space profile a couple of days ago that got you know 500 friends afar count messages
emails the support from you guys has been amazing. Okay, so I think the daily source code listeners should definitely provide
their resource and their help by hitting this page
Virgins plea.com and
Maybe you know there's more people out there who I think at 25 if you haven't gotten laid by 25 you need some help
And I gladly gladly open up this podcast to help anyone because I know that we have
listeners out there of all preferences ages races religions Creed backgrounds upbringing
Who'd be happy to help no hits necessary. I'll just connect you now of course what I am expecting
25 year old virgin I am expecting you to podcast really podcast your experiences
So including your you know the first time. I'm not interested in video
Yet he says later in this comment which is really long this video of this audio blog video does
It was like another two minutes left on it. He says that he's going to write up all of his experiences
But that's not gonna cut it. No, you've already stepped into our realm into our world into the world of audio
You owe it to science actually science and progress you owe it
To record this in audio and and you and you should let your platonic friend your
Friend formerly known as the platonic friend you should let her know about it lettering on it
She's already given up her identity freely so I guess that's okay, but just the audio that will be fantastic and I guarantee you
I guarantee you it's gonna do something. I'm not sure what but it's definitely gonna do something and I really hope you hear this
Because that would be cool and you should podcast
Maybe once a week for the next three weeks since you're only into week number one and then wind it up, you know
She will I'll give you the bandwidth no problem. We'll put you on the network. It'd be awesome. Completely awesome
And I think we should have more of this this is fit. This is good. This is a very good public service
I wish this was there when I was 15
Folks listening to us on
Serious satellite stars 102 here's what you can expect for the next couple hours
The next three and a half hours to be exact on
Channel one or two you should keep it here because specific host hellways up next it's there on five days a week
Mark Yoshimode Namcoff and the Pacific Coast Hill players
Follow by Mads Weinstein full hour of
Bloated geist radio dawn and drew after that half hour for them then to go more daily for your tech injection
DVD weekly on it nine o'clock eastern time and that'll be wound up the entire evening with some music from
CC Chapman from Boston those are all eastern times
All right everybody so I'll see you tomorrow right here or go to daily source code dot com to download
The rest of the show for today
Those you still hanging around
Let me see
Gosh, I couldn't have gotten more links over the weekend about the BBC
Hoping to second life that was pretty interesting, huh? I woke up Saturday morning
I said the Patricia said oh man the BBC they're doing exactly what I was thinking of doing
BBC has staked acclaim to a
Virtual tropical island where it can stand on stage online music festivals and throw exclusive celebrity parties
So I listened to the radio one portion of this
They had their big event the the one big weekend event which is held in Dundee
So that was on Saturday and it's something the BBC is very good at doing a live concert carrying the live music
Doing the background interviews backstage in the dressing rooms
We used to do this stuff in Holland all the time and it did it's incredibly expensive to do this type of radio programming
But so appreciated it's so good and
Then in second life they did indeed get themselves an island or what is known in second life is a virtual world by the way
That a lot of the source code listeners have been turned on to and starting to check out and actually meet each other through second life
Maybe it's a whole misnomer, you know, it's just extended chat
It's what it is but it's good because there's there is a physical aspect to it
So what's known as a sim now here's here's where what I don't understand and here's where
Pod Show is going to do something a little different. I love the the whole idea of using it as a collaborative environment to
sample music
or video or any other type of audio of actually
At the Pod Show Palace which is a virtual palace not for real. It's it's just a place where we're gonna be able to get together
I've built a movie theater and it's great, you know, instead of
Being on for instance Skype and saying okay, here's a link everybody open this up and look at it
You can all basically sit down and chairs and
Position your view and it plays on the big screen. You see it at the same time. It's it really is a mind trip that kind of stuff for me is very exciting that you so that
But what the BBC did is when you have one there's there are technical limitations actual computer
Processing limitations to what you can do in this virtual world and this is a real tinfoil hat moment isn't it
But you can really only have about 50 avatars which are representations of people
On one sim at the same time before it really starts to slow down and so I I figured this out a long time ago and when we open up the palace
We'll actually be teleporting you to other sims where we've also purchased
Well, we call it land, but it's basically, you know computer space
to build stuff so that we can have a much larger
amount of people having and also people to be able to be able to be have private conversations and stuff like that
And if you don't think it happens it really does forget all the you know the the
Castles and the palaces and the clouds and the and and the weather and all these life like things just
What is actually happening is people are getting together. Hey, I don't this is your war from second life
Just sat at table right now on second life and we've just found out each of his locations
And it's just made me realize how great second life is
There's someone from Hawaii two people from Holland and two people from UK
It still just shows how great second life is because we like in real life we would probably never meet
And because we like separate it for thousands of miles here we are just
Sitting as a table
Talking like right there like meeting each of it. It's really amazing and
Like to thank the island for introducing many of us to second life
And rather abruptly
See see what I mean so what what what is it? I mean how how else are you gonna discover people
That's the thing it's it's critical. Just look at chat and we use this all the time you use MSN
But where do you go when you want to find just a particular group of people who are interested in a
Certain subject or topic or just a community?
You know, is it that simple is it that easy? I think second life is in the interface that everybody understands
You know, here's my shack here's where I live come here if you want to talk about me and my shack and whatever
I represent and so it's very easy for people to find each other and
Just sit around and chat, you know, and I drop in at least twice a day
I'm not always interested in all the you know, there's a lot of podcast chat which I like
Okay, but just you know stuff about life. I love it, man. Oh
Oh, forgot to tell you yesterday picked up the in-laws
They're gonna be here with Christina while Patricia and I are in on our on our jet setting tour
So the place is kind of busy
We could have more people here. We could have more guests, but not with those two
Just busy
They're off all off and town by the way. They're out shopping on the high street
So I have a little bit of peace and quiet while I'm while I'm doing the show
So anyway, I just thought of a couple people that I met
Since I've been using the second the virtual world second life is an interface to listeners and other people who are interested in
Extending the experience of the podcast and and just like the BBC yeah, man
Definitely gonna get some potsafe music artists in there and now the BBC didn't have any
any avatars of
The artists who were performing
But we will
I think they'll make it much better on it
Yeah, they had an at Christmas and I'm not laughing at the BBC. I think it's fantastic
They really jumped on this very well and really brought
Second life to the forefront and also
Harvard Law School the Berkman Center
They had a
Conference on was that Sunday as well. Yeah, I think it was on Sunday and they also had a virtual conference center in second life and I just checked it out
You know teleported over there sat down and I was watching the video. It was but I could whisper to someone next to me. You you can't do that
It's interesting stuff
So the people that I've been I just want to thank a couple of people who've been working really hard on getting this pot show
Palace X I've been doing nothing but just kind of
tutoring around figuring stuff out and and paying for all the work
But my partner in this is Brittany
You've probably seen her around the castle. She's really she's doing everything. She's doing all the and I don't know who she is in real life
I don't care she's Brittany and she's doing just a kick-ass job
of coordinating
Getting stuff done
She knows a shitload about second life then there's master Q who she introduced me to now he is
Master Quattro he actually posted a comment on
Charlie 386 he works with the and she chung
You probably heard about her she was in business week so he's kind of my virtual real estate consultant
There's ex-dark ex who's who's been building the the palace and the the casino and and allora he works with her magic star doing the
Interior bow-twang working on some pretty interesting scripting stuff
Detrol up working on logo and she's a she did the pod show t-shirt. She's working on something for the palace Melissa
And I'm sure I forgot people, but I'm just like wow, you know, there's a lot of people I've met and
You know what it's making a difference we're seeing audience
interaction we're seeing all kinds of I don't know
Just a few than I got
All right, I got them crazy
You say you want to see me run or now you have your wish
You know I will not come over to your castle in second life. It's not because I do not have invitation
It's because
Even your avatar is gorgeous
I cannot stand to look at
I'm sick of it. I don't cry
I know that if we met that I would feel like a glass and penis on our windy day
Next to your manly good looks
So I've taken on a whole new fitness regimen
I'm running five miles a day in fact. I will no longer be known as comic strip blogger
You can call me comic strip jogger
And with my hair transplant surgery, I will soon have long flowing blonde mane like you're on
And then with my four inch platform heels
When we finally do need that I'm curry. I'll be able to stand face to face. I look you straight
And the eye and tell you
When I get out of hospital Adam curry. I would I
Oh damn you don't have Adam curry. I got to tell you just on the pod show stuff
We got you know there's so much
Interesting stuff happening. We're starting a running channel
I actually we've been developing one for the past couple of weeks and we and it was we're very quick to
To be secure sponsorship of the channel
You can look for that very soon and it fascinates me every single time it's kind of like
It is a sound seeing tour but it's a very focused sound seeing tour you know and
I followed along with Steve runner doing his his marathon podcast and there was a little bit of technology involved there
You know the RFID chip that's attached to your shoe which then triggers off an email message to tell
The world whoever is the recipient you know where that person is what point they just crossed I mean this there's some cool stuff
Not only that
There was oh yeah, oh man
So let's see the earthling stuff is coming the emails went out to the podcast network for
Folks who want to participate in that promotion. It's gonna be awesome
And and this is where the audience you guys really get to participate
You can make a jingle or endorsement or you know, let's make advertising better, right? We've all bitched and moaned about
The Earthling commercial
Well, here's your opportunity and you can win valuable cash prizes in the process
One more thing that pod safe music summer
Well, I'll just call it the showcase. I don't want to confuse anyone with the Nashville gang that's going out there
And we hope to involve them as well, but we've got some excellent excellent stuff coming up
Over the summer with a big sponsor getting more pod safe music out there. It's gonna be a great summer. You know that it really is
Sing along, if you want
Well, along with the BBC using second life for their
Simul cyber cast this was the number two link email to me in the past week and a half
Comes from the New Zealand her Harold and it's from the fine New Zealand company that is successfully turned sewage into modern day gold
Mollboro based aquaflow bionamic yesterday announced that it produced its first sample of biodiesel fuel from algae in sewage ponds
It's believed to be the world's first commercial production of biodiesel from wild algae outside the laboratory
The company expects to be producing at the rate of at least one million liters of the fuel for each year
From blenheim by April today algae derived fuels only been tested on a controlled conditions with specially grown algae crops
Aquaflow's algae however was derived from excess pond discharge. I think that means shit to you and me
From the Mollboro district council sewage treatment works algae takes most chemicals out of sewage, but
Having too many of them taints the water and produces a foul smell. Yeah, it was right. It was shit
So we are so close to pooping in your tank. It's not funny
This is just that with the reactor that was developed just recently. I can see these two technologies converging and we may actually be able to make our own fuel to power our
Automobiles and even even our aircraft
Just by cropping in the tank. You got it love it. I had a period in an early story over here
Not shit. You can't hear that. Can you? Let's just do so off
next time I promise I'll
I'll do the
The charity music on the other computer. This is just not working hold on. I had him here's an interesting story for your
Trinity moment
And the main issue of wired magazine page 33. They have a story about a guy
Peter Bethany from New Zealand that actually had his butt liposfection and
Is going to convert it to biodiesel to power his speedboat, which he's going to try to take around the world
I'll get to it. I love the show
Now that's what I call a true hero. You know what I mean?
How much fat can you get out of your butt though?
From the biodiesel industry
We're getting close the technology's really our converging here. I'd say invest in diesel and biodiesel stocks as soon as you can
Links to the story of course provided in the data source code dot com show notes
It's the Roger Smalls impersonator here. So talk to you about go daddy. I was listening to the show yesterday
And I didn't really hear you mentioned them except for the added beginning and well
I just thought that they pay in money which supports you show so maybe you might want to give them another mention or two
Well, far for now. I've got to go Russell through your trash for a bit
Two dogs
You know it's bad when the stalkers have impersonators right
But while we're talking about it great deal go daddy dot com on any domain name use the checkout code promotional code
DSC three and only cost you six dollars and 95 cents
And thank you very much Eric Eric and Sarah do the alternative music show another fine pod show podcast network program
Please
doesn't print to try and see you though
So we're playing it as a herdehyde who's record company just as much as everyone else
Not a good idea Roger not a good idea
But yeah, if you haven't heard it check out Kevin Reeves with mother on the podcast music network
You can buy the MP3 free and clear of all digital rights management for you to use as you wish and buy a copy for your friend and buy a copy for your mom
That is
From tomorrow
The member ought held a minion over flightless birds and comedy
This is the story of a super force of extra beters brought back their team's pick to reclaim
Comedy my job is on the internet my recreation is on the internet
There's no internet in my life my life has disappeared
Screw you Tennessee fifty six. I hate you your stupid Tennessee icon
I think an optimal time for you to go out a date and have sex with many women in
There's a line that they agree that every girl in the world would fall in love with the
Boo, it broke out before me, John
You've never pulled
MP report
.com
Get out of this is Mark from the small room podcasting at a Brisbane Australia
Behind me you're listening to deep down under from Australian band visions of a no mad
They're among the many Australian bands and artists who've chosen to be part of the pod safe music network
I got to tell him mate we love the PMN and we're gonna push it as hard as we can man because we think it's a great for Australian music
Anyway, when you and our aim is to provide our listeners with a uniquely Australian view of things from home and all around the world
We're not gonna limit it to just here
And we're gonna try and prove once and for all that all Australians aren't crocodile hunters here in Australia
They call me the crocodile man
Steve can you give us a minute please
Anyway, I heard you mentioned on Charlie three eight four did you like to get down to Australia some time
Made by them there for it
We'd love to have you down to where own little five acre property, which is just that side of Brisbane
We're only 35 minutes from the beautiful beaches of both the sunshine and gold coast of Queensland
Mate beautiful one day
Perfect the next anyway
Feel free to drop me a line and please visit us at www.thesmallroom.net
We'd love to hear from you and guess what mate
We've even got cowbells
A trans-Pacific
Cowbell moment
All right, gonna wind it up with one song
You know, I love getting recommendations through email for songs and just because I don't play it now
doesn't mean it's not on my playlist please keep sending them in please do I really appreciate it
Stacey says Adam always I know you're always looking for new music to play on your show you got to check out Sean
Halikoff
Halikoff you gave me a phonetic pronunciation there. He's Canadian and he's
His demos are definitely D.C. D.S.C. worthy
He has four songs for download love your show. It's also so educational. I like the music. Thanks for the great new artists
When you're going to get some D.S.C. Schwag a girl's wardrobe just isn't complete without a big D.S.C. on her chest
Stacey I agree
I agree I think you should send me a picture of your chest and we'll make sure that it's exactly the right size
And please and uh
May I thank you for the excellent suggestion
This one's titled what
I'm pissed off. I'm a female. I'm wrapped up. I'm a cream. I'm tired. You've got me while you're
Am I not good enough to be the only one?
How do I?
I can't watch you dead.
Before give I can't go back to the one that's worth her
How do I forget what you did?
I will never know
He's my, it's he nice, it's he then
When you'll try, cause I won't write there, I care
And I'm not good enough to be the only one
How do I, how do I forget what you did
How do I, how do I forget
Can't go back to the place where I'm her
How do I forget you did
Yeah my God in her took me the only one
How do I?
How do I forget?
What you did?
How do I?
A four gift
Can't go back to the Wednesdays
I told you that I wanted to sacrifice my life on the ground.
But all those
today went on.
Sean Holocoff, whoo, that's a kind of weird chord there. And that wraps up this Charlie for today from Monday.
Of course we'll be back tomorrow as I said for a week, exciting stuff going on Thursday.
I'm doing an interview with the BBC, so I'll be Thursday morning, right after I drop Christina off.
But before that, Wednesday, hey, Wednesday is going to be cool.
I have a, I think a 130 meeting with Ben Fervayan.
And I, that's a Dutch name. I, I presume that he is a Dutcher of Dutch descent.
I don't know if he actually speaks Dutch or not. He would have to think so, though, with that first level surname.
He is the CEO of British Telecom. We're getting very close to working some self out with these guys.
I can't tell you how excited I am because that would mean the pod show UK actually will become a reality.
And I'm so happy that we're going to get all our paperwork straightened out in the next week or do in New York.
At our curry dot com, dating source code dot com, I will talk to you guys tomorrow.
Bye bye.
Another pod show podcast, stick it in your ear.
Get this pod cast and we're great ones like it on the high performance pod cast of Liberty Network from Pod Show and line-light networks.
I love it.