In July, Pacho asked you to declare your media independence for the unleash of Pacho Plus Beta.
Now, we're insisting, system, in just days. The number one new media network in the world will get even better.
All new features, advanced functionality. And now, we're proud to deliver the following show on the network that guarantees complete control of your media. Pacho.com.
And an ex-generation distribution data with BET, under my belt, we don't need my freaking boots left.
I'd rather be flying my Cessna 182R beam into the future.
August 1st, Delta Sierra Charley, 491.
D.S.C. Academy.
D.S.C. 490.
Is the time tonight?
It's the way she walked behind us that back. It's the way she looked down.
I can't find what did establish it. You got chopping up the mail.
D.S.C.D.S.C. 390.
I know the love is going to never get it down.
A bad idea.
Lurses so sweet when you can't be as small.
Looking so sweet when you can't be as small.
Lurses so sweet.
Winter, fish and tap it.
Loaning round four days.
You got the best of everything.
You got the one in.
When you make what you can't get.
And before the best of this, we have to give this one more try.
I can't believe it.
Lurses so sweet when you can't be as small.
Looking so sweet when you can't be as small.
You got the best of everything You never want it
Let you think what you can get And afford the best of this
We have to give this one more try
She's had a feeling for a long time now
She's had a feeling that she wanted more
She's had a feeling that she hated or so
I want her way back
When you're with mine
I want her way away
You got the best of everything You never want it
When you think what you can get And afford the best of this
We have to give this one more try
Let it go
Rory
Tonight I don't care
I'm having a candy dinner from the pod save music network
I see they put that up
It's a couple months ago actually
Of course the minute the song ends
The minute I start to talk that's when the phone starts to ring
No one else in the cottage
So we'll just have to bear with it in the background
I should actually hook that up to the mixer
So we can just answer these phone calls in the show
Find out when people really want
Rory's from Florida
I discovered the song not by
Proosing through the pod save music network
But actually I produced a BG blast number
Rory's seven
Well produced I hit record and like Christina do the rest
She's hosting episode number seven
And that was one of the songs they played
They're going to play on the show
So I love it when the young ones can just teach me a little bit
No I'm saying
Okay
Let me catch up on stuff that happened over the weekend
Was extremely busy
Because we have a big demo coming up
Tuesday morning 7 a.m. in London
So I'm scooting out the door
As soon as I'm done with the show today
And I'll be staying in the city
Which means, well you know what that means
And the show will be late tomorrow
Not for you satellite listeners
But for those of you who kind of have gotten into
Sync with me and are expecting the download to happen
So what was the big thing that we were preparing for Saturday night
I'm sorry Sunday night of course
Was Guy Fox night
Bonfire night
I remember the fifth of the November
Jump out of trees and them flat
I see no reason why I jumped out of trees
And should never be caught
And well
Around three o'clock I called it
We they were expecting missed
With fog rolling in
And we were so busy
You know because we have our
BT podshow.com
Unleash coming up this week
As well as podshow plus 2.0
Maybe we should say 1.9
Sounds better
Podshow plus 1.9
And so we have Chris Rockwell
He was in London and he was going to go with me
And do the video photo
Do the videoing
The videography
And I talked to Captain Dan who said
Well you know we can always do it
We can always go and wait
And if it sucks then then too bad
And then we won't do it
But what we don't want is to
Go up flying and not be able to see the field
Because then you basically can't land anymore
And then you fucked
So
Out of safety concerns
I call that probably
You know in hindsight
And of course it always is hindsight
Now I'm not at the airfield
Then if boy if missed comes in to Farrow
Echo golf tango fox trot
It really does come in
So where I am and what I was seeing
From my window and Gilford is not representative of the field
But it looks like we probably would have been okay
And it's too bad because the fireworks
From Stoke Park were just unbelievable
I could see them from my studio window
You know that's the guest bedroom
In the cottage
And it looked fantastic
So it was a bummer
But you know it was a full moon
And you could barely make out the full moon
So I'm not quite sure if that was cloud cover up above
Or if it was indeed already the missed rolling
And it's hard to say until you
I'm actually at the field
And someone else is landed
And said well here's what I saw upstairs
So sorry about that guys
But it's afty first
I hope you'll agree with me on that
Hi Adam
It's Mike here from the fishball acoustic podcast
At fishballacoustic.podshow.com
Yes, we're positive family now
Speed cameras
Bastards that they are
I just wanted to explain to you how they work over here
As someone who's had to pay a few of these things
In the past
Basically the reason they want your license
is because they want to put penalty points on it
Yes, they give you an endorsement
With three to six penalty points
Probably three if you just over the speed limit
Now as you build up your points
If you get done for speeding a couple of times
Or three or four times
Once you get to 12 points
Then you lose your license
Now I'm not quite sure how that would work with a Dutch license
My wife is Dutch but she has a British license
So I don't know whether they can actually put endorsements
And penalty points on a Dutch license here in the UK
But I guess you'll find out
Anyway, just thought that might be useful to you
Tailwinds all the way mate
But not when you're driving
And folder
Yeah, I appreciate that
And there's more that came in regarding that
So here you know this is the two speeding tickets
Patricia got snapped on the camera
I'm doing 40 in a 30 zone
And of course I said I don't worry about
I'll just say it was me
I'm starting to regret that now
But this point thing
I have a Dutch license
I'm sure here's what's going to happen
They're going to say
You need a British license
And we're going to take the points
They're probably going to give me the license
Take the points off and take the license
Right away immediately
So I'll be completely about driving credentials
Hi Adam, it's something clerk
After Odin asked us
Welcome to the busy time
It's been speeding, fine procedure
It's fun, isn't it?
First of all, you get to let it tell me
But your car was stopped speeding
And asking me if you're the owner
So you've been in the form and send it back
And they didn't send you a letter saying
We have evidence that you were speeding
Yes, of course they do
You bloody well gave it to them
And then comes the fine bitch
If you don't want to go to court and fight it
It was a bit irrelevant because it's not just a fine
It's three points on the license as well
And the way the system works here
Get 12 points, they take your license away
But that's why they want the license in the post
They've got a stamp in
Literally points
And after four years
The points are considered white
You can send the license off with another check
And nothing, you're back a license
No point showing it, you're going to clean license again
Ask the way the system works
Isn't it fun?
Yes, thanks
It's a scam
It's a fucking scam is what it is
And in the Netherlands, I have to say
And a lot of people complained about
About the traffic
Speed, what would you call it?
Speed insurance system in the Netherlands
Which is fantastic
I really, really like it
Now of course it's very big brother
It's completely messed up
Here's what they do in the Netherlands
They have several different strips
You know, pieces of roadway
And what they'll do is they'll clock you
At the beginning of this length of roadway
And it could be several kilometers
And they know that you cannot reach the other end of the roadway
Any faster than X amount of time
Any slower of course is okay
But any faster they say, well, you're speeding
Because there's no way you can go that distance
Without going over the speed limit
And then they send you, they don't do any of this
Do you own the car?
They just send you
A bill, basically
And what's nice?
And so there's no points off the license
This is something I do in the states as well
Which, honestly, I think works quite well
Because it is a deterrent
Because it sounds like if you got four
Four speeding tickets
That would be four times three is 12 points in your license
It's gone
So that definitely is a deterrent
And of course your insurance rates will go up
The states does that in many states at the same way
I remember New Jersey was that way, although
Yeah, your points got deducted much sooner than four years
And you didn't have to pay for it and it was automatic
But what's in the Netherlands
I really like it because it's basically just
You know, it doesn't stop people from speeding at all
It's just like, well, you know, you take your chances
And if you got to get somewhere fast
You know how much it's going to cost
That's it
It's like buying a first-class ticket
So for people like the speed it's fantastic
Again, as a deterrent for speeding
Then not at all, it doesn't work whatsoever
Oh, parky sent in something about Guy Fox
Stay home and say
I had him as parky just calling in
The bit more on this flying on Guy Fox night
I came back from Amsterdam on schedule flight
Into London Heathrow
On Thursday evening
And then the fireworks even then
We're just amazing as we flew in
It was quite late and we're coming in low and low
And kind of on so sure
There's a lot of fireworks going off
And it just looked awesome
So if you can get up over the weekend
I think it'll be just going to be absolutely awesome
But my Saturday will be the best day
But there will be stuff going up on Sunday
All the organised displays will probably be on Saturday
But there's still plenty of private parties going on on Sunday
So you should get a decent view of what's going on
Take him and cheers back
So as I said earlier, I did get it up over the weekend
Just not flying
Apologies once again to Lady Patricia not on the show
She's at the cardiologist today for her
What is it to her quarterly check up
So they put on the treadmill
And make her generate electricity for guilt
And I said, I'm really going to miss you
I haven't been in the show for a long time
She says, well that's what it is
The families don't like it when moms are working
It's only fun for the moms
Because she's not just doing it
Doing this quarterly check up stuff
She's working on the house
Which looks like a second week of January
Is moved day
So, bye-bye
Very, very busy
A poor city PD is a new show that we're debuting
Today, in fact if you go to podshow.com
You'll see it a trailer on the homepage
This thing is fucking amazing
20 minute episodes
It's a cop show
But made by independent producers
It just made completely independently
Actors, producers, writers, everything
And it just blows me away
The videographer of the cinematography
I should say the script
The sound effects
Good sound effects
Because when you fire a gun
It never sounds like it does on TV
And I'm really happy to have these guys on the network
I think you'll like it a lot
Or at citypd.podshow.com
And Google has done it again
They have enticed me to go and buy some new hardware
I told you that they had this new Gmail application out
For Java phones
Which I've been looking at the Nokia E61
For quite a while
Chris Jacob
Our head guru sales weasel
Has won
And I've been kind of looking at it a little bit jealous
Because it basically has everything in that N91
And it likes so much like Wi-Fi
And the ability to store tons of podcasts
And the only thing I didn't like about the N91
Besides the fact that it's like a brick
Is the keyboard is little
Itty
Just teeny little slivers of keys
And it's only a numeric keypad
So if you want to hit the F
You have to go D-E-F
If to click three times
And so the E61
Kind of looks a bit like a blackberry
It's about the same size
And I finally bit the bullet
And went out and got one
Specifically because I wanted to try out the Gmail application
Instead of using mobile Gmail on my blackberry
Which works fine as well
Let me tell you this thing kicks fucking ass
It is so incredibly cool
Besides that this Gmail application
Is just the cat's meow
I mean really
I mean everything
I think yeah everything you can do
In a web browser you can do in this application
You have shortcut keys
That you can use
You can access all your different
Well for icon folders
But I guess your labels or whatever they call it
Really incredible
And of course the phone has built in Excel
And word and even power point
As tons of applications
This one came with a GPS application
Remember I still have a Bluetooth GPS receiver
Fucking works
It's like it's as good as a Tom Tom Go
It's unbelievable
I'm really blown away
And just want you to know
The Google Responsible
For me shelling out like like like 600 bucks or something for this thing
But it's amazing
Already I'm completely transitioned
I was able to synchronize my address book
So all my contacts are in there
It's cool
It's great
Get out of it
There's a lot to call it
Subministraria
I'm talking about the little Java Gmail client
For the mobile fund
You mentioned it in the episode
For nausea
I think it was on the product
I'm just putting it over
That's as with your experience
In the case
The little app does work here
With the mobile fund
In Australia
I'm using it on my
And it works from the absolute treat
As you mentioned
It's at right the left
So
Yeah
Just thought I could get up into feedback
This is just from the personal productivity shows
On the podcast it works
Cheers
It's ready to go
There's only one spot
You can do that
It's pod show
The game is shut down
Other companies lay down
Who change the rules
And things to stay sane now
We're pod show
To it
Others want to copy us
These catches like old hamburgers
They need to catch up
Wack shows
Wack shows with no spine
They needy
They're drowning in the sea
And thirst for originality
Pod show
Poca tsunami
A nerve quake
The wave at the futile
And y'all are just in our wake
Pod show
That's where it ended
Oh, those guys are happy about the new pod show
Unleash
This is going to be great
It's going to be a wacky week
It really is
As we unleash BT Pod show dot com
I think that will be around Thursday
But you'll probably see some stuff happen
In fact
Tuesday
Around
I think it's 130
PM
Pacific time
So that will be 930
PM UK time
We have to bring the entire site down
All of Pod show dot com
Has to come down
For several hours
Now we contemplated doing this
In the middle of the night
Of course
This is you know
It's so traditional
It's like you do an upgrade
It's like everyone gets up
A three in the morning
And does that shit
And then you have to give a very tight window
And we know it's going to take several hours
Because it's all kinds of database
Which shows we got a lot of people on the system
So we have to do this with extreme care
So not only are we launching
Launching BT Pod show dot com
But also
Unleashing Pod show
Plus 1.9
As I explained earlier
1.9
Which
I think you're going to love this
We've really taken all of your feedback
To heart
And have created something amazing
And really opened up a whole new avenue for videos
And not just video podcasting
But also if you just want to upload your one video
Very analogous to YouTube
I would say
But then you can you can with one click
You can then add that into a show
Also your collections will change
You can instead of adding just shows to a collection
You can actually create your own RSS feed
Right within the system
Your own feed of just stuff
So whatever it is it could be a picture
It could be a series of pictures
It could be a
One particular episode of a podcast
It could be a video
Or a couple of videos that you like
And someone can subscribe to that
And we'll also bring you the ability
To create private feeds
So instead of email
You know
I'd detest when people
Send email
With their media
It's like hey you got to listen to this song
Check out this video
It's like I want a different way of receiving that
Also something that definitely assures me quality
So if you send me a feed
And that'll probably work the first time you send someone
An element
You know say hey
Let me just set up a feed with you
You'll say yeah okay
I'll take your feed
It'll show up in your collection
So let's say it was from Michelle
From whispered pearls
Because I'd love to get some feed from her
She would
Then add anything into that feed
That she wanted me to have
And that would show up automatically
And pod show applause
And of course if I subscribe to it
With my Nokia E61
Or the iPod it would show up there as well
And also of course on television
Now that we're getting close to
Some of these IPTV projects
Which is that's a story for a whole
A whole different episode
Right
Hey don't forget a voice mail number
One, two, one
Six, two, five
Six, three, five
Seven
One, two, one
Six, two, five
Six, three, five
Seven
Oh it's so well known
This phone number
Of course
On mobile phones worldwide
Which you're supposed to plug it in
That's why we have plus one
But the plus in and then two
One and then two
One, sixty, five, six, three, five, seven
Because then whenever you're driving somewhere
You just give us a holler
Even if you're driving through the hills
Of Florence Italy
Tell Adam
Checking him from the hills of Florence
Literally
This is almost so understandable
That's my sister Willow
Calling in from the hills of Northern Italy
Oh
Cool
That's that service that I've turned Patricia on to
Jaja
And I guess she's download
They have a mobile application
Which she's I guess she's put on her phone
And calling from Italy sucks
It really blows
It's very expensive
And so Jaja is a great
A great solution to lowering cost
Not getting paid for this by the way
I just love the service
And we had another
$800 phone bill
From previous month
Patricia just calling once or twice
You know a day
It's a lot of money
I can use that for something else
Now she's using Jaja and she loves it
She totally loves it and Willow's using it now as well
And they have an application which I tried to download
On to the E61 but for some reason couldn't get it to work
But I guess she's calling with it now
Of course she's on a mobile phone
The driving through Italy that's why it sounds so crappy
It sounds so crappy
It's really cool
It's another show set of supporting that one out
And I hope you've been on fire
Saying remember to remember
This weekend
I'm looking forward to meeting
Back to that
And I'm sorry about the student ticket
And they're with the hospital
But I think I don't have a bit more pressure
So they're actually going to grow
I think that's what happened in the back
So I'm going to see what happened to that
I'm doing it in 65 euros
And
And let me call it
More stuff
I'm going to tell you about
I have a nice week
And that's it
Bye
I will
I wish I could understand
More than 40% of what you send in
But I think that's just the cell phone
And maybe you have the window open or something
Oh well
But still that voice number sure does work
Doesn't it?
And I fucked up a couple times
On food philosophy
Jennifer's really angry at me
Hey Adam
It's Jennifer from Food Philosophy
So there it was
Climbing the muddy treacherous hillsides of Italy
Striving to get perfect footage from my podcast
A great personal risk
And I finished the day feeling great
Satisfied with my success
And then I returned to here
This
Serious broadcast
Coming up next is two for Tuesday
Jennifer and Aloe tells us why food
And sensuality are the perfect pairing
Seems you're pretty good at
British pronunciations like
Controversy or
Actually
But your Italian sucks
Oh
That hurt
So let's try that again
Shall we because you're making my ancestor spin
In their graves
So repeat after me
Yanolo
See?
It's easier
Yanolo
I think you can manage
Of course
At least you remember the name of my show
For that broadcast
Which you seem to have forgotten
A few days later
In fact our insertion technology
We really use for golden tickets
Which we'll be coming out with
Actually there was one on
Ah, what's the Jennifer show
You're going to give the fork
Yanolo, is that it?
No, it's going to kill me
Slap me, slap me with a wet towel
Adam, sweetie
We just can't have these malfunctions
Okay
I thought that having the first golden ticket promotion
Since yours
On food philosophy
Actually had some meaning
So I think you need to make that up to me
Oh
And you know I want to throw a little challenge your way
I know it's going to be scary to you
But hopefully you'll face it with some dignity
Okay
Because you have three handy little flavors
Of splendour over there
But I have eight flavors
Of filtrous gourmet selections coffee
So I am challenging you, my friend
To a cook-off
Let's see who can come up with the better recipe
Now for you I have a feeling
That your listeners might need to help you out
Because well
You can't even boil pasta
But you know that's your problem
So
I can boil pasta
I just didn't have the right tools
And it slipped out of the thing
And down the drain
Hey
You're stuck in the kitchen
Burning and mangling ingredients
They can come over and visit me
And have a chance to win a golden ticket
At foodphilosophy.podshow.com
And see what we're cooking up over there
So bring it on
Big hard boy
I've got a wet towel right here
And it's got your name
All over it
Oh and I'm a folder
I know
I know you wouldn't talk like that
If you weren't a folder baby
Ah
Mr. Nola
I'm so sorry
So incredibly sorry
Tell me that you think you knew it
Oh
Yeah
Yes
Oh
I just think you know it's
Oh, oh, oh
Yeah, you feelin' the need to know it's
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Do I know I feelin' the need to know it's
Yeah, you feelin' the need to know it's
Yeah, you feelin' the needs to know it's
Now we're all for now
Now you're here and you're here
So now we're all for now
You're all for now
Why rapes?
The pod save music network
A lot of people playing hey Kate
It's getting major pod play
But this is another one of those that I discovered
Viad and BG blast
It's over
From South Carolina's favorite sons
I realized I gave it a whole wind up about
Taking everything down
Tuesday
I didn't tell you exactly what we're going to do instead of it
So I will right after this
Is your computer a hacker magnet?
It won't be anymore because Earth Link is here to save the day
With Donald's faster than speeding boat
And far all it is more powerful than a locomotive
It has an anti-virus system that cleanses your PC with the click of a mouse
It's a blur
It's a plane
It's Earth Link
Perfect internet from outer space
It linked to Earth with powers and abilities far greater than those of normal high speed
And price is so low that it will blow you out of this world
So make the right decision and turn to Earth Link as your internet provider
The last time somebody drove
Right so here's the piece that I forgot which is pretty damn important
So instead of sneaking off in the middle of the night
And everyone being tired and rushing and trying to get stuff done before people wake up
And of course that doesn't work anymore since we're globally
You know people in Australia rely on us people in Europe rely on us people in the United States rely on us
It's like you can never be a hide that from anyone at any given moment
It's happy our somewhere right
So what we're going to do instead is we're going to do a dry run of something called the plus
Now the plus is a 24 hour 7 day week video station
That we've been working on covertly for
Not from here right like I haven't talked about it here covertly for a number of weeks
And it's going to be interesting we'll have all the coolest videos
Not just music videos but all kinds of videos
Video shows you know all scheduled
We're actually we're going to start off with one feed
But we will have a feed for Europe a feed for the east coast a feed for the west coast
And we'll have you know live breaks coming to you from Pacho HQ in San Francisco Los Angeles
New York and London
But for Monday as I said 130 pm eastern Pacific time is when we start
We're going to do a dry run of the plus and I believe the lovely intel is the Amy Mc'll be hosting for us
So you'll actually see the engineers sweating away as they're working on getting stuff up and we'll bring you updates
You know we've always done fun videos and stuff during downtime
So that's what so nothing will be accessible except for one page with that
And obviously we're going to work as quick as we can to keep everyone's podcast rolling
Nothing else should break
Even iTunes should resume perfectly after we come back up in a perfect world of course
So look forward to that on Tuesday
And that'll be just before the unleash of Pacho plus one dot nine and BTpacho dot com
It's a lot I know
Before I get out of here remember if you want a great deal of domain name use check out code dsc3 at godaddy.com
And right I'm off to get this show up on the system and I will be back with you
Well, if not tomorrow because we may I may just not do a show because of well, you know
Because of our our our switch over
If not tomorrow then it'll be Wednesday
Thanks for listening everybody take care yourself bye bye
Another Pacho podcast stick it in your ear
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from Pacho and lime light networks