This is Soccer Girl. I just listened to the first episode of Shadow Falls and it's scared me
crapless.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I don't know.
It's the sign of the time for you to come.
If I'm losing my mind, but I'm lost and I'm blind by the chainsay.
Is there any way I wanna hear?
Is there some way to make this really hear?
Because of you, I can't sleep anymore since you walked out the door and you left me.
All I do is stare at the wall, thinking no thoughts at all, step to memory.
Why do you want to try to be insane?
Why do you want to kill me so much pain?
What threw me the sign?
Don't think I can't make it on my own.
Why is it crazy?
I'm just wondering if what I'm doing in my eyes.
I can't feel
Don't know darkness for light
Don't know daytime for light
Honest face and he isn't real
Oh well I wake up from this
And the midst of your cares and embrace
And one thing that I'm in my sports to do
I don't think I can make it without you
I don't think I can make it on my own
Don't think I can make it on my own
I'm trying to pray better
My dad's in the long run
Show me size
Tell me that you're still in love with me
Will you be mine?
Show me that you're still in love with me
My dad's in the long run
I don't think I can make it without you
I don't think I can make it on my own
Don't think I can make it on my own
I'm trying to pray better
My dad's in the long run
Show me size
Tell me that you're still in love with me
Will you be mine?
I know I've played the song before
I've played the song before
I've really reliant on that shit
I've really reliant on the podcast
music network
Every morning it's like
I listen to the new songs
and then I compile my playlist
The one of two songs I'm going to play
and I couldn't do any of that
So I just reached back into the bin
I had to look at my hard drive and pull out Kevin Reeves
What a great song that is
Of course there will be a link to the
podcast music network page in the show notes
Once it's all back up and run
I finally got my touch and go practice
You know I really want to get my landing skills
even better
I used to be so good with the helicopter
I could put it down
I could put it down better than my instructors
There's something about the way you land a helicopter
being so completely different
even the concept of a flare
being so different in helicopter
versus a fixed wing aircraft
that it's just taking me a little bit longer
to refine the art
Captain Dan and I suited up on Saturday morning
It was about when was pretty significant
or pretty significant
it was 15 gusting to 20 25 knots
which is great because what you want to do
is you want to practice your crosswind landings
and the best place to practice landings
is on the grass strip because
well if you if you muck one up
it'll definitely diminish your tires
as we know I'm pretty good
and it's smoking them out
So we flew to Goodwood
which I just love the name Goodwood
which is this fantastic complex
it covers an acre's owned by a real Lord
who has a castle and he has a polo pitch
and he has also he has his airfield
which has four runways
which is fantastic
we're actually not that good for practice
because you know if the wind shifts
and they basically shift the runway
but we were able to get some pretty good crosswind landings in
it's got a race track around the whole thing
classic cars racing
just really really nice operation
so it went there it's only maybe 15 minutes or so
now the minute we took off
from Fair Oaks I noticed something was wrong
because basically you do the call outs
the minute you push the engine
the throttle all the way forward
metal to metal as we call it
so the throttle is against the metal of the dashboard
or the control panel
you call out power pressure
check temperature again
and then you're looking at your airspeed indicator
which is basically telling you what your airspeed is
how fast you're going
and you're constantly checking that
and of course looking out to make sure you're kind of on the center line
and not veering off the runway
and so the real thing you want to call is airspeed indicator is alive
you've probably heard this if you listen to any of my flying charlies
and so I call it was alive
but I immediately said something's not right here
now it just was indicating too low
typically we'll take off about
about 60 knots
that's about the speed you have when I can pull her up
you wait for a positive rate of climb before you actually bring the gear up
well I'm giving you quite a rundown here aren't I?
so it was only indicating about 40
but I could see that the manifold pressure
engine power RPMs everything was good
so no reason not to lift off lift it off fine
now of course if you're taking off into the wind
which is we were pretty much had the nose right
just a little bit off the left of the nose
that we had the wind off the left of the nose
you have to subtract the wind speed from your airspeed
okay that'll give you your actual ground speed
so the indicated airspeed
if it was 10 knots
headwind would probably say about 50
and that's when it would start to come off the ground
but I knew it was not gusting at 20 knots at fair oak
so that very moment
but anyway so we went up and as we're flying and you know
there's a lot going on where I immediately have to talk to Farmer or radar
because we're within the airs
we're literally within the Heathrow's airspace
when we take off from fair oak
so our fair oak is within Heathrow's airspace
so you're pretty much controlled as we
bopped out to go to midhurst down to Goodwood
and I said to Captain Dan I said
you know something's not right with the airspeed indicator
but we kind of thought nothing out of it
because it really can make the difference
you know if you've got the wind
if you've got a strong headwind
your indicated airspeed will be much lower perhaps
the ground speed and it can be reversed too
obviously depending on where the wind is coming from
so no worries
so we go to do first we landed Goodwood
and have a cup of coffee
and then alright we just plan everything
look at the circuits which is a little funky there
for runway two four because you don't want to fly over some houses
and so we start doing our circuits
and landing really is all about attitude
and power it's really about speed control
because just as the aircraft wants to take off
it around sixty six well between sixteen seventy
knots probably sixty five
it also will not land above that
so you have to kind of know how fast you're going
and so on you know as you're coming into your final
turning on the finals for landing
you want to have it about
seventy five reduced to seventy you want to go full flaps
which is something I really had to practice with
you know you've got your just it's all a matter of all these things
coming together
and and you really want to be just about to touch down
obviously around sixty five sixty knots
which is just about the speed that it takes off
and so this is your indicated air speed
and as we're you know I couldn't I couldn't get it
you know we were bouncing and you know yeah I could get the
thing on the ground but it was anything but a good landing
and it was just it was freaky me out
and like I can't understand this I've been flying for hundreds of
years I can't I land now
and then so Captain Dan says well let me give you
you follow through in the controls and I'll do one for you
and we come in you know and he bounces that sucker
and off the runway
and then we we kind of figured it out hey wait a minute
the air speed indicator really is busted now this of course is from that
hard landing I made with Patricia which wasn't all that hard
because you haven't heard her complain about it
but that's when the needle got stuck while apparently it screwed up
some other pieces inside the air speed indicator
I'm sure my sucking on the peto to might not have helped but that
doesn't seem to be the problem all the all the two
being is all fine for you pilots out there
so there's a very simple test you can do
in the air actually to see what the deviation is of your air
speed indicator basically you're going to fly into wind out of wind
and then you take the the differences in chopmen two and take two
percent difference whatever and you come up with
what you're what you're with the actual indicated air speed
should be and so it really is
indicating 10 to 15 knots too low
so once coming back to ferrox man I just
greased the runway because I basically just took the you know
just deducted those those knots
from the from the indicated air speed am I born you yet
it's just so happy to tell the story
but you know the whole reason why you know you're really careful
about seeing an air speed indicator drop down to 50 knots
because that's your stall speed and then basic it's not the
engine stalling but the the wings will actually stall and provide no
lift and you fall out of the air so it's a little
little another chapter in the in the page of aviation
and of course I call the wind commander about it and say they
oh dude you got to get this fix you say yeah sure no problem
you come on over it's not all that expensive to replace it
and we'll put a new one in next time you're over and I say what
can I just you know fly without the air speed indicators again
you know I still lots of birds flying around without an air speed
indicator which I guess is his way of saying you're an airman
okay then Saturday night Christina had a sleepover
maybe should say that to store I'll say that story for tomorrow
when Patricia's on uh it was a real parent moment
now I'll ask her to come on tomorrow and talk about that
now I have a couple of topics lined up for today's show
if you hear a Skype a bleep that's because I am monitoring what's
going on with uh with the server status right now
the first topic I wanted to just kind of pull together
is all the information that I've been collecting and you've been
sending me about this nasa footage that has been lost
and of course my I would have to say easy belief in you know the
fact easy belief that we may not have landed on the moon
so I've been receiving all kinds of amazing
just absolutely amazing links one was one thing I've put here
that I didn't actually put in
putting into my show notes now
I got this awesome link to a documentary a French documentary
which is an English made by French television company
I'm going to make sure to put a link to that in the show notes
I'm going to spoil it by telling you what's in it
but you know you got Alexander Hague in there
and Donald Rumsfeld and it will blow your mind about this whole
controversy but you've been talking about it as well
and I wanted to share some of the comments that have come in
hello Adam it's racist and you can
I'm sitting in traffic at the moment
I'm in my home just going to have a result
I'm sorry about that
hold on a second
let me I can't believe I can
I've done the wrong one in there
I'm so idiotic
okay try this
and it really does a great job
but
Adam this is Tom from Michigan
after these last couple of charles about the skepticism of the
Apollo landing had to leave a message
you know you're right that the grainy pictures don't prove that we went
but the grainy videos don't prove that we didn't go either
there's an overwhelming amount of scientific evidence out there
that we did actually land on the moon and we landed on the moon six times
and a great website to check out if you're interested or any of the listeners of the Charlie are interested
is www.dadestronomy.com
put together by a guy named Phillips Flight
I think that says it
he works with the astronomy department at Sonoma State University
as he says on his website
I'm an astronomer, a writer, a skeptic
I like reality the way it is and I aim to keep it that way
so he takes apart the
the skeptics and the
the conspiracy theorist series
point by point and he really does a great job at it
and really shows how their
so-called proof is not proof at all
and the fact that they lost the tapes
doesn't really prove they're hiding anything
it just proves they're another big government organization who doesn't know
the left hand doesn't know what the right hand is doing
and in this place the fact that they did that
really to me makes it more believable that they just bungled it
I mean how would they be able to keep six
landings quiet for 35 years
if this whole thing was a big conspiracy
now and it's just my two cents
love to show
an atom
folder
later
okay so I'll take it very seriously
I don't know that you're a folder
uh...
I totally reverse two segments on the show here I'm sorry as well I got messed up
so I thought long and hard about this in particular after seeing that that
documentaries about fifty minutes five zero
so you please take a look at this it's a it's a Google video so you can
pretty much watch it on anything and just click on the link in the show
notes
but I I
you know I really went through all of my thoughts about this over the weekend
you know and I don't necessarily think
that none of the moon landings might have happened
uh... it's just well here's the three pieces in the row that really
led me to my certainly initial conclusion first of all
the rumors
just like anybody else
where there's smoke there's fire you know you want to believe all the
all the nasty things you know it's very much like evil pod show
I'm sure you know there's so many people out there who hear rumors and
there's no conclusive evidence or proof of of
said evil doing you know
so they have a they draw conclusion rumors are that's what happens and some people
stick to their guns when it comes to that
and you can in its very easy to build your own truth certainly over time you know if you
have certain pieces of information which may or may not be fact
you can you can build your own truth in that
now secondly
is my my television background my broadcast experience you've probably seen
wag the dog with dust and Hoffman
same thing when I saw that movie is like yeah it's exactly how it can be done
and in fact as I told you I think on Friday I've been a part of a lot of
television illusions and trickery
not you know not necessarily bad or or meant with any malice
certainly meant for ratings
and television does that all the time now this was not for ratings but it's
highly believable that
the US government wanted to
you know have some kind of leg up on for instance the Russians
and again I refer back to this documentary it'll blow your mind
but when I really thought back to it my skepticism comes from one experience
and it kind of hit me
all of a sudden over the weekend when that when I was young
when I was young
I listen to the radio
I guess if only mama cast had any that ham sandwich
Karen Carpenter had
Aunt Meg who is Uncle Don's wife and we'll talk about Uncle Don
in a second
we were I don't know because you know of course they live in in Washington
they took
I think we're probably about five or six
cousins
I don't remember why we were there with her but she took us to the Smithsonian Institute
and of course you know what I was most interested in
is the space exhibit so they had the capsule there
I think the Gemini
I don't know Gemini
I think that's the one and and
and that was it was almost disappointing
in fact that's where this is where it all started
I looked at that capsule like this this thing you know what happened to the
you know in my mind it was almost like
having listened to a
a radio and old fashioned radio drama
or even listening to a disjockey
on the radio and you have a certain image of someone
and then all of a sudden you see them
and it can really destroy your image of the show
if you see how a show is done that's why I don't like people taking
video or pictures of me doing a show because you have a certain image of that
that's the theater of the mind
and somehow this little
dinky thing which had
didn't have all the knobs and buttons I expected it to have
blinking lights and all the excitement it just wasn't there
and then they had the moon rock display
now that I look at that moon those moon rocks I went like
the crap is that man looks like a friggin rock
it's just rock
he went a lot of touch it or anything
I think even remember saying
I can't touch it I want to feel it
you know and of course my I think on Meg probably said
oh you know that could be contaminated
like that it was in glass
you couldn't have touched it even if I wanted to
and I think that's where this all came from
if you combine all of that throughout the years
and the rumors of course with the introduction of the internet
just grew stronger and stronger
I think that's what made my disbelief grow stronger
do I really technically believe
that all these landings would have been hoax is no
now I don't think that's possible
and quite honestly I hadn't even really
stopped to think about there being
it was at six or seven moon landings
so that's first one still possibly could have been
not hoax but it could have been oh man
I don't want to spoil this documentary for you
you're going to see it and you're going to understand
where I'm coming from so I think you've changed my opinion
without a doubt
is there nothing left there do we have to
readjust these reflectors
what I will do
and I'm actually thinking of planning a trip to New York
I want to talk to Uncle Don about it
because he was definitely around the administration
well right after Nixon
I'm not sure if he must have been doing something in there
around then but if not he knows all these guys
he knows Rumsfeld he knows Alexander Hague
so I'll just ask him who gave me a real-on stance
and of course I'm going to ask him about a lot of other things
including Korea
but what happened to the morning is a fantastic
fantastic story came out
I'm just going to click on the link here for you
which as always we'll be in the show notes
a daily source code dot com
this is really cool
the director of Pink Floyd's video clip
for dark side of the moon
Australian film producer Peter Clifton
in 1979 when he was making the movie
or making the video
he wanted to have some space footage
and so he contacted the Smithsonian Institute
and they sent him a tape
and he actually is a picture of him holding this tape
it's not like you know some wanky video tape
it's like a professional
I think it's a one inch B
what they call those BNC
or type C
a professional studio video tape
probably don't use those anywhere now
digital
so that's a proper proper copy
and so he essentially when he read or heard the story
about NASA losing the video tapes
how am I doing on time
when he heard all the story on television
he went to check the tape
and it turns out he has 30 minutes of footage
he only thought that there was just a couple of
just a couple of shots that he used for that video
but it includes the entire moon landing
so now there is apparently
a high quality copy of the moon landing footage
which I think if he's got that high quality
it wouldn't be awesome to put that out on the internet
now that we have it anyway
let's just do that
if anything it'll make this conversation
even more interesting
so
there you go
I have to say I'm pretty much on board
that we at least landed a couple times
maybe not that first time
and it doesn't really matter
it's been fun talking about it
for those of you listening to this podcast
on a serious stars 102
this is just the beginning of pod shows podcast line
up every single week afternoon
but if it coast hellway is next
now let me get back to
I'm gonna get back to some of the stuff we were talking about
in the comments that I wanted to play earlier
about
well it's a couple of topics locked into one
you know these terrorist threats in the UK
out
scared the shit I mean the door just slammed shut
so there's a couple of
topics interwoven here
one is about what kind of liquid bombs
can you take on an airplane
and the other one of course
has gotten into this
rather heated debate
certainly in comments at daily source code.com
about whether business class travel
subsidizes
economy class travel
or not
hello Adam it's racist
UK I'm sitting in traffic at the moment
but in my home
just go ahead
without you very well
and
I'd start laying out
on this thing too
a day before full floor
no
and he was talking about
this is trash
and that's the starting
economy class
that's certainly coming from on this
I agree
as to
out to the point
and I agree
for him
I just prefer
than
you're all the others
and they're the crisis
and they're not in the juice
but
to take them low cost
airlines in UK
and they've got
the easiest
right now
they're my baby
flyby
all those real cheap ones
they don't have a business class system
they only have
what happened
especially
have a company class
so let's see
how you're subsidizing
that
the crisis
they are the real cheap ones
don't know
so I think you get the idea
about what he's saying here
is
yeah you may
you may think you subsidize
economy class travel
but how about these
budget airlines
that don't have an economy class
well duh
I'm not talking about
all air travel
you know
I haven't seen a lot of real budget airlines
flying from London
to San Francisco
these are short little hops
and they use the same plane
to turn around
and go back again
which has a lot of cons
and some pros
one the big pro
of course is price
and I've
travel with easy jet all the time
I never said
I subsidize
any of that
rather than just paying for my ticket
and showing up
but when it comes to
transatlantic flights
or flights that are not flown
in a
one class
there you go
in one class
operation
obviously you can't
subsidize it
but you know
the
the subsidize
subsidize
subsidization
I did it
comes from the fact
that the only
operated with one aircraft
so you can
have a significant delays
if the first
the first trip of the morning
doesn't go well
or if there's a hiccup
anywhere along the line
then it'll delay everything
the huge drawback
which doesn't work very well
for business travelers
and of course
there's no amenities
but these are usually
on very very
short flights
probably up to
you know
no more than
three and a half hours
four hours
something like that
or maybe
there must be a budget
airline from New York to LA
I'm sure there is
I'm sure
or jet blue whatever
is but you know
I think jet blue
is owned by
American
Delta
you know
so that there's all kinds of
subsidization going on
everywhere
but I think we pretty much
close that topic
a lot of people
sending me comments
and email
and I ask
I'm always to send
the to me an audio
but
they don't always do it
now about
about the explosives
that said terrorists
may have been planning
to bring on board
I've been trying to find out
not that I want to
make a
make some kind of explosive
device but
just like to know
is it really possible
you know
it isn't all the stuff
that can really
cause an explosion
isn't too
unstable
you know
to
to take along
and mix in the bathroom
or something like that
and this is
this is got some pretty interesting
feedback
hey I'm a chicken top
of the
six not just got
finished listening to the
DFC
I'm not a way to picture
there is a little bit
scary
so
be careful
using the
I can
also
at the car
just one of the
comment on
the
anarchist
cookbook
which you may have heard
I used to actually
check that out in the library
in my high school
but it had
like three different
sections on it
that
talked about
one of them was making
bombs and things
that's one of the things
you want to do
know about your show
and just reading that book
you can make a whole bunch of things
one of the things we used to do
was make a
calcium car
by bomb
when we were kids
now
we were kind of
gentle with it
we would take milk jugs
and drop calcium car
by but you could pick up
any
oh gosh
army navy store
things like that
calcium car by
a little rock
they put in the minors
elements to keep the light
going
among other things
but drop the rock in there
and we would take the cap
of the milk jug
and we drill a little
hole in it
and then get some fused
some like
similar to the fuses
so they could get wet
and put a little
dumb around them chips and gums
get the fused in there
seal it up
around the cap
then shake up
the mixture
a little bit
to build up the gas
and light the fused
and then it would
expand
the plastic of the milk jug
and it would make this big
fan
like a shotgun going on
now the version that was in the
anarchist cookbook
was to use something like a wine bottle
and you put a
a fused in the cork
and we did that only once
and we look a fused in ran
and hit behind a big piece of plywood
and the shards from that glass
shot so hard
that they actually went into the plywood
and on our side
there were pieces of the glass
starting to stick out
so it scared us so badly
we never did it again
but you said you wanted
some information on how to make
bombs easy
go check out the anarchist cookbook
it can be gathered up anywhere
there's also a little
chapter if I remember correctly
on how to make like
things with pots
like pots
beginning and pot brownies
and stuff like that
so hey
you know we're not in my pocket
um
did I say pot
cannabis
whatever you want to call
up
then also
just wanted to mention
whatever happened to your
it's your uncle
I thought you had somebody
who was in the services that would be a really good person to have on your show right now
and last night at least
I'm a scruncher
have a nice day
bye
all right so obviously not an endorsement
to go learn how to make
explosive devices
although I like the
the brownies part I might go check it out for that
all right so yeah that's possible
and I'm very familiar with carbide
I lived in kind of near farmlands for a long long time as a kid
about 20 miles south of Amsterdam
and we would we would take the the actual milk cans
the you know the big heavy metal
milk cans
and we throw some carbide in there
in fact we call them carbide cans
and you'd heat it up
to a certain you know on an open fire
or whatever
and you kind of point the can
and it would eventually would blow the top off
and of course it would blow at hundreds of hundreds of yards
it seemed like
or what I can remember
and of course you know this kind of stuff
absolutely is very dangerous
it won't blow up a plane
and it seems like it's a little tricky to detonate
and it just doesn't seem like the kind of PR
terrorists will be looking for
and you know there's a time factor in it
unless you have
I don't know how do you fit the iPod into the bottle
to detonate it
or maybe even I love this one
core core peaterson
sent in a email said
you know how about the old
Diet Coke and Mentos trick
yeah that would work too
all you need is a Diet Coke and some Mentos
and you too can explode at least something on the plane
so so far I'm pretty dissatisfied with what I've heard
although barren secia
I hope that's the right pronunciation
says he's got the solution to airline terrorism
it's really really simple
check this
get both the Shiite and a Sunni Muslim cleric to bless all airplanes
blessed
this is crazy
bless them in a way so it's clear that if a person causes harm to the aircraft
they don't pass go don't collect $200
and don't get their 42 virgins and they go straight to hell
it's either that or we have to fly in single-engine planes
like the Delta Sierra to minimize any terrorist attempts
yeah
no it's maybe not that crazy
portions of this podcast brought to you by go daddy
you can get a domain name for the first year for $695
be using checkout code dsc3
when you check out go daddy dot com
if you want to leave a voicemail comment
here's the number plus in your cell phone come on
grab your cell phone put it in now plus
201 625 6357 you want to use that number for Skype
or if you want to use our UK number in London
020768137
five three
let me just play a couple of comments that came in over the weekend
hey Adam this is Audra
also you played my list of survey on show 440 so I played it for my girlfriend
of five and a half years
and yes that's correct
okay all right so you're a girl too I got it
and she said that I am just I'm hearing this for the second time
what is that I played this for my girlfriend to five years I think
what you're trying to say is you're getting
half years and yes that's correct
okay so you're a girl too I got it
and she said that I sound like a 12 year old boy so I was
wondering if you could maybe tweak it
change my voice a little bit so I sounded like one of those
sexy women that day all the guys who go over just because of their
voice so you could do that that'd be really cool
oh and can you have your people head on a word to
croncast that's crl and c a s t dot com
because that's one of the shows that I would do when I'm not listening to
the d i c I don't have my own podcast I'm just a
listener so I have to have to put my own listeners
shows anyway if they go to croncast they can tell that
I'll just send them and maybe we could both win
iPods because croncast is giving away iPods isn't everybody
say I don't make some show and by the way my girlfriend's
this country and I can't change that
I don't know what to do thank them
okay well I'm happy to help but not with trickery
not with vocators and electronic gadgets
it's not about how you say it
well actually it is it's what you say and the intent behind it
so you know only have to do is is think sexy you can think sexy
for your girlfriend so you know you haven't been these aren't really sexy
topics some some contest touring thing you're doing
and talking about you sound like a 12 year old boy you know I can help you
absolutely first you know call back in and say something sexy
the way you say it to your girlfriend and slow down a little bit
and then naturally your voice will come down a little bit
and draw out your word somewhat call back and I'll write it
and I help you we can get through this together so that you can actually have this
in real life and not just you know not just on the daily source code
I do want to help you speak sexy
oh and send me a naked picture please
hey Adam this is tap from Houston so I totally get the whole correlation
with some sail and burping
in fact I've made the transition from you bird by think
Nana coffee sure would be real good night now because my office didn't allow us to have some sail machines
I totally understand the correlation it's really great
what I don't get those the correlation with folding toilet paper or
the other day I sat down with the toilets take a crap and I thought
man I ought to listen to the daily source code
so just find a leave a comment and all the way
folder
well
I have to have to be honest with you this in sao thing was totally an experiment
and the folder scruncher thing I was done with it a long time ago
but people don't stop you just want to stop calling in about it
and if I played some of the stuff that people send in
you know we've gone totally away from the scrunching and folding and into all kinds of other things
that I'm not interested in I'm really not interested in all your personal habits
but the folding scrunching takes place before you do anything you know it's
it's a
I'm just interested in that and when I'm finding now indeed is that whenever people
and Patricia just yesterday that's last night she said
hunt it's official
I really am a folder
you know it's because now people are you know paying attention to these little things we do
on a daily basis
so and of course I love the fact that you know you're thinking of me and thinking of the show
that part is is
wow talk about
Vulcan mind tricks and getting people to
continuously think about the show and hopefully listen and
be part of the audience and interact and be involved
yes the next step I guess is
well I guess the next step is
getting into your dreams
maybe when you go to sleep and you know you know the old
count sheep thing
maybe you see little DSE logos jumping over a fence
doing touching goes
I hope I programmed you now
Hi Adam my name is Jason I'm a family physician
and Ohio I'm 35 years old
married two kids
give up the rest real radio just about a year ago actually
after reading an article in a wired magazine
that you had the interviewing you talking about podcasting
I got my first iPod
and the news is on there started listening to some podcast
ironically I didn't listen to yours until about a month ago when everyone on
podcast full on one
kept talking about how of course I listened to the
David source code period
I always think that
this kind of podcast was more for
people in the podcast and I listened to it
I realized it was in anybody who likes
good commentary and good music
and I really enjoy it and I'm a
David listener now
I
need to say that
I am a folder
I do teach a folder
and I think really that's about the only way to go
if you're scrunch of your missing coverage
got to watch your hands afterwards
just to get the crap off
I watch my hands anyway
be sure but
don't like the crap on my hands
always been a folder always will be
thanks a lot Adam
isn't it great to hear a family physician
talk about not wanting crap on his hands
yeah
there was a thread over
a podcast pickle which was
which of course caught my eye
daily source code has jumped
the shark was the title of it
that I no longer talk that much about podcasting
and that a lot of people used to listen to it
well yeah I mean before there was podcasting
per se it was really technical
and it was basically me getting feedback
to developers
who were creating eye potters
eye potter lemon
so you know of course my interest
change things I'm talking about change
I just did what I did like eight minutes
about flying at the top of the show
which you may not have liked
and you could just fast forward
right over if you want to
but yeah I'm not interested
in only talking about that
and I've expanded
a lot of podcasters
you know don't listen anymore
because they don't get the information
they used to get out of it
and then I'd interested in other things
I have to say which is perfectly okay
it's all right
you know and hey you know if you want to stop listening
stop listening you know you might come back
you might not that's cool
I used to have that with Howard Stern all the time
after certain what you know he he going
rants for weeks
and as much as I like lesbians in the studio
sometimes even I'm like okay
I got to listen to something else
and maybe I'd come back a couple weeks later
certainly the best of stones
I could rarely listen to those
I like the whole live aspect
and and I'm just saying that
because that was a big influence
on stuff that I'm doing now
so
yeah I'm interested in other things
I'm interested in people other people
talking about other things
you know okay so it has to be for a folding and
scrunching and it's folding and scrunching
uh this is all a test
nothing but a test
every single piece of what we're doing here
is a test you know it's all going to start
melt together
um even the whole concept of
uh subscriptions
well
not the subscription but the the delay downloading
that's going to go away so we're already seeing
that disappear
every device will be connected
with high speed to to every piece of content
you know it'll come in in real time
what we used to call streaming
it'll just be there you know
this is what we're already seeing
that's the pod said music network
you know I don't have the whole library
the pod said music network here
at my
at my fingertips you know
I'm I'm getting that in real time
from uh from the pod team music network
it's completely feasible
that I'll never have to download
and load it up into cast blaster
ever again in the near future
I'll just select it from a list
I want to click play
it'll just play
straight from whatever server
wherever it's coming
you know that stuff is going to happen
and everything all lines are going to blur
whether it's
quote unquote mainstream content
or not all the media companies
and pod show is a media company
um
although I think we're approaching it from
180 degrees in basically the opposite direction
media companies will see this
they'll change
once uh
the way advertising
is is quantified and measured
really changes we're already
you know pushing that
everyone's going to be everywhere
so I want to I want to
broad experience I really do
if you got some other cool topics
to talk about that I know nothing
about or it would not think about
bringing up let's do that
it's totally your show
in case you haven't noticed
70% of the show
is
your your contributions
I am this is Brad
I do windows dot dot show dot com
and I was calling about the Sebastian
box story
still haven't heard that story
and you kind of peaked my interest
I love the show
I always listen and keep it up
and I'm a holder
so I uh
I thought I'd already told the story
and that's what I was kind of surprised
that you sent that comment in
and now I realize I told it a couple
weeks ago on the um
I love the 80s podcast
who asked to interview me about the 80s
which of course you know that was my
certainly a huge high
high point in my life in career
was working at MTV
so I'll put a link in the show
notes of that particular episode
I think they put it up last week
maybe the week before
and I actually tell the a couple of stories
but also the Sebastian box story
which took place in Moscow
I realize I'm taking up a lot of your time already
I'm going to play one more song at the end of the show
of course another one that I've played before
but first
here's
I really like this idea
so I guess two or a group of girls
have a podcast and they're promoting it
and instead of sending a typical promo
they're sending me a promo
and individual riddles
and on Friday I played the first riddle
or maybe it was Thursday
but at any rate today
I've got the second piece of the puzzle
and you know what?
I'll just play along
I think it's kind of cool
The Adam O. Adam answers this
Are you ready for the second clue
with an express me for you?
You won't be disappointed
as you mentioned on show
these juicy riddles are a promo
and perhaps a little bit more
need certains aren't necessary for us to reveal
that the missionists of our surgeon podcast
and how they will make you feel
Three words makes from 11 letters
thus this mystery spell
we hope you will figure it out
because we may never tell
Adam O. Adam
we know you're a clever boy
be at this your playground
and podcasting your toy
your goals, carefully measured
and destination offset
your concrete new territories
all on our calculated bet
with evidence you see as a new
fly forth
keen on selling podcasts
the Wall Street
as you seek their support
Adam the Adam
here's your second clue
by the way we're being nice
studying one clue for two
use the first letter of the word
that is spoken often of you
just the old names of fly boys
and the name of the popular movie
too
if you need help
ask your listeners to make it easy for you
TTFN
okay
I was writing along as that was
coming down so three words 11 letters
I believe now the first one
the first word started with a P
so I'm just going to say if we group that stuff
it would probably be
three I'm just going to take an average
three letters for the first word
four letters for the second word
and three letters for the third word
and the first word
here's just roll that back
what did she say now was
a different word for fly boys
or a popular movie
that is spoken often of you
spoke a word spoken often of me
the old names of fly boys
and the name of the popular movie too
the old name for fly boys
wow
I'm not sure yet
if you have any ideas you know how to get a hold of me
send it to adamantpotshow.com
or call it in plus one two zero one six two five six three five
five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five
five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five five
You can't show me something new on the door stand for me or him or her
You're a super natural girl
You're out of this world
I ain't like
With you too light
You're a light
You're out of sight
You're a super natural girl
You're a person
You're out of this world
You're a super natural girl
Jimmy Golding you're a super natural girl
And I guess I will have a link to that in the show notes as messages just coming now through on the instant message that the sights back up
So the pots have music now works should be back up as well
Apparently
The trigger that was making this happen was an auto updateer
At Rackspace that runs in the middle of the night and it apparently is screwing up a whole bunch of infrastructure for a lot of people
Okay, so I guess we found the big problem
Haven't actually resolved
What it's doing but we can certainly pull that part out of the mix not haven't happened
Cool, all righty
Well that's it
I'm done for today
This afternoon Patricia and I are looking at another house here in Guilford
Putting it in offer on yet a different one
We'll try and get her on the show tomorrow and talk about husband and wife crafts
By cast master
Talk to you tomorrow everybody. Bye. Bye.
Another pod show pod cast
Stick it in your ear. Oh, yeah, by the way
For a perversion for profit. We should have a new one out today as well. Bye
Get this pod cast and we're great ones like it on the high performance pod cast delivery network from Podshow and line-white networks
I love it