Hey, this is Dan Patterson from the Creepy Sleepy Show.
You want creepy without the sleepy?
Check out Shadow Falls, Pod Show's brand new audio drama series.
It's terrifying.
terrifying.
This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Doc, let's go and go to see if I can see it.
I was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
I'm flying into the rising sun.
She is a whole different generation of how.
Feel it in my arms.
My American tank came up.
She needs to see.
She's so good to me.
Talk about her life before you.
There's literally this thing changing.
It's my fear of the weather.
My American tank came up.
She needs to see.
She's so good to me.
I'm a whole kids now belong.
So far away from the garden in love.
She is one new generation of how.
So I will see just how black was my life.
When we're alone in the city of light.
Yeah.
Yes.
Thank you very much for watching this video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the
next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see
you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next
video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video,
six, two, a desk, three, two, three, talk, then, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video,
see you in the next video, see you in the next video, come back and kiss!
See you directly, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, and don't forget to subscribe to my camera.
Thank you, see you in the next video, bye bye, click!
Well, in the next video, see you in the next video, please, click, n fragrant and check them out!
You, pity, Fun!
Easy, fast!
Oh, man.
What a way to kick off a week.
Love it!
Over for Tokyo, live coming to you from the Podsafe Music Network, thanks to Michael
Butler for the tireless effort of getting DP on the PMN.
Man, that really, and did not go on notice, by the way.
All weekend, long podcast, all over the world, we're playing Deep Purple.
Why?
Why were they playing Deep Purple?
Because they can.
Man.
Hold on a second.
What?
Don't interrupt me with you.
It's the Daily Source Code.
It's Monday coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey in the UK known as Gilford,
shit weather today, or should I say, shite, but this really, really made me feel good.
So happy to play this for you.
It's from a brand new album.
It's called Rapture of the Deep, the lineup, which, of course, has changed throughout
the years on this double CD set, consists of in-gill on vocals, in-pays on drums,
the Roger Glover on bass, of course, oh, man.
What I love to have love is all on the podcast music network.
Steve Morrison, guitar, and Don area as a keyboard, it's chock-full, and this is what's
so cool.
Obviously, women from Tokyo probably belong to some record company somewhere.
And these guys would never be able to put it up on the podcast music network, but what
a concept, take a live version, record that.
You own the master, you already own the words and the music.
So bottoming, put it up on the podcast music network.
So there's actually, there's another live version on the track, although not on the CD,
not on the podcast music network.
What is it to smoke on the water, another live version?
This CD is just chock-full of great stuff, and I'm going to play another track from
it later on.
They have another, one of the track, which I won't play today, called MTV, nice little
slag at them, check that out.
Links, of course, in the show notes at dailysourceco.com, so you can find deeper pull
on the podcast music network.
Wow, I'm so happy.
It really, really makes my day great work, Michael, and there's another artist who popped
up over the weekend.
George Thurgood, now also on the podcast music network.
This is exactly what we hoped for.
We knew we were so sure that artists who have an established name just won't be able to
make it in today's music business, because it's all about the quick pop, the big hit,
the rake in the dough, and fuck the artist.
I'm sorry.
That's just the way it is.
Now that these artists have some stuff under their own control, such as recording their
own live concerts, releasing new songs, releasing new records, and putting stuff up
so podcasters can share them with you on the podcast music network.
I've said it many times.
There's nothing as powerful as someone saying, I love that fucking song.
No recommendation engine can top that.
Who?
Hey, was a lightweight weekend, otherwise you probably followed along on my weblog, maybe
didn't, but I was planning on doing a touch and go landing practice all weekend.
Actually, all Saturday, a Saturday, we had cloud ceilings of 400 feet, so that's a non-starter
regardless.
Sunday, we had thunderstorms, high gusts of winds, which is perfect to fly in, but not
very convenient for landing practice, because you're basically fighting the elements
more than you're learning anything.
So that's been postponed to either this week or the end of the week.
You know, we had to do something else.
You might have seen perversion for profit, my very first video podcast show.
Well, it's not the first test I've done, but I think I'm finally, I finally found some
software from serious magic.
They have a package called vlogger, which I hate as a name personally, and it doesn't,
it is basically the same package, but doesn't have a lot of the things in there that
I would need.
So I went for the $498 version.
It's to be delivered on CD, so I still have that big demo written across the screen.
But once I get the software in, I'll re-render that show, and we'll continue.
I don't know if this is going to be a weekly thing, or maybe a couple of times a week,
it just kind of depends.
It really depends on how fast I can produce stuff, because that's what really cuts in.
Even producing the source code from start to finish, from prepping the show to actually
being done and walking away and it being up and checked in everything rolling.
It's a minimum of three hours.
It takes about the same amount of time for one of those three-minute video shows.
Anyway, if you're playing the show in iTunes, or perhaps in Windows Media Play, or any
other player, or even on a portable player, you might see a fantastic new artwork, thanks
to NeckDrek for giving me some custom icons for Daily Source Code 441.
The intro's coming in fast and furious as well.
That was a Dutch intro today, introducing episode 441.
Send them in for me, please.
I need 442 all the way through a thousand, if you know mine, so just send them in.
Just a short little thing, something creative, something fun.
I really appreciate it.
It takes a lot of the tediousness, and I think just the boring tags out of my life and
put them back into your creative hands.
Quite a show lined up for you.
We've got all kinds of cool stuff to talk about, including some corrections.
Hey Adam, this is Manu, aka Spuds, the producer of the Hamister Jesse Podcast.
I was listening to DSC 434 when you played this song.
I'm confident and reforming to feel all right.
Yep, it's coffee and refer by my buddy Ron Sunshine.
I just want to clear up a couple of things.
First off, you mentioned that you found the coffee and refer song from the podcast called
The Jazz Sweet.
Now, while that's a great show, I'm pretty sure that's not where you've got the song.
You see, the song isn't quite hot-safe, at least not yet.
The tune was featured on a different podcast called Hamister Jesse.
Hey, I'm Mr. Jesse.
You show of gaps in fine, Bobby Coo.
Hosted by Jesse Miner and Produced I.
Well, me.
It's a show that features swinging jazz and blues, you know, the good stuff that Patricia
thinks.
Well Ron Sunshine gave us permission to play coffee and refer on our podcast, because
he happens to be a personal friend of Jesse and I.
We also have an interview with Ron and even more of his great music.
Go to potshow.com and search for Hamister Jesse and my S-T-E-R-J-E-S-S-E to get the show.
And you can also get more of Ron's great music at Ron Sunshine.com.
Also, we noticed that I'm that you subscribed to Hamister Jesse.
A little bird at Potshow HQ told us that you heard it and jumped on board.
Thanks a lot.
And I think I can answer your question, you posted on Potshow, what's a lindyhopper?
Basically, a lindyhopper is the old school term for swing dancer.
So now, you know, I wouldn't normally send in a comment, but Jesse Miner is the host
of the show.
And he just got married and he's on his honeymoon.
So I thought a cool plug for a show on the Charlie would be a great wedding gift.
Thanks to Tanya Adam, oh and a scrunch scrunch.
I do thank you, sorry for the mix up there, but I really do love the show.
Yeah, I'm subscribed, absolutely.
And I'd already found out from our financial wizard extraordinaire, Cindy, who is a lindyhopper.
Exactly what it was.
It's coming back, man.
The big band, the sound of the swing, it's all coming back.
While I'm on the apology path, made a mistake on Friday's show, I falsely accused
Podcast Paul of leaving a snooty comment at acure.podshow.com, without having actually
listened to the show.
It wasn't podcast, Paul.
It was Paul Pinfield.
There's too many Pauls in the UK in podcasting.
Anyway, so I'm sorry, Podcast Paul and Paul Pinfield, well, I've already been talking
to him over the weekend, so everything's all pretty much straightened out, but I did have
to do a public apology.
Something interesting that I read on Valleywag.
I don't know if you are aware of Valleywag.com.
It's basically, it's kind of like a tabloid for Silicon Valley.
And sometimes some great nuggets show up.
For instance, if you are a content producer for Verizon and you produce content that is
currently delivered through the Verizon Wireless Network, which basically means cell phones,
there are some restrictions you should be aware of.
Oh, yes.
Valleywag posted this, so I'm going to presume that it's correct.
This is guidelines for publishing content on Verizon.
No content provided to subscribers of Verizon Wireless from content providers, where
then the form of text audio images, video, or otherwise may contain any of the words listed
in appendix A. This includes any variations in spelling of the words, e.g. fuck, fuck,
Ph.h. fucks, fucker, fuck, fucking, et cetera.
Oh, I should have mentioned this shows definitely, and this portion certainly not family
safe.
So basically, I mean, it's all, it's their right, it's their network.
They can, they can tell anyone to do whatever they want, but it seems like we won't be
having podcasts freely and openly available on a network like Verizon in the near future.
I just like to run down the list of words they have.
Some of them, I feel are completely out of order, are part of the daily vernacular vocabulary
that we use, but you won't be able to do that if you're producing content for Verizon.
Listen to the list.
I'll just run down really quickly.
Anal asked bastard beat off bitch B.J. camel jockey, chink, circle, jerk, clit, cock,
cooly, cune, cornhole, cunt, dego, deep-throating dickhead, dickwad, dildo, dyke, eat me,
fag, faggot, philasio, fisting, flesh, flute, flesh, popsicle, forticate, fuck, fudge, packing,
gang bang, genital, get laid, gobb the knob, golden shower, gook, hair, pie, hard on, homo,
honky, jerk off, juboy, jizz, five, kike, lesboh, limey, man loaf, masturbate, muff
diver, nigger, nut sack, packy, pan, face, pwn, tank, pubic pussy, queef, queer, raghead,
rim job, ruby, red bag, scrotum, shit, sit on my face, 69, slags, slants, otomize, spank
the monkey, spear chucker, spick, spooky, tea bag, and testicles, twat, vagina, wet back, whack
off, whip it out, white swallow, and wop.
Some of those words, I don't think are that offensive.
What is up with the number five?
We've banned the number five, holy crap, I'm sure now I'm guaranteed to have no spot on
the Verizon wireless network, that's for sure, oh, big shake up in second life, I said
that if Durandran was coming into second life, I think this is Friday's show, I said,
that's it, I'm out, I'm done, and I do kind of mean that, but that doesn't mean that
the pod show island is going away, not at all, doesn't mean that I don't stop by to hang
out in meet friends, I just don't see it, second life just became a non hit place
from me, it just did, stop, I am in Brittany Mason, who of course is running the whole
pod show island, stop, I aming early, is the island going away, the island is not going
away, I'm not going away, but I just don't think that if second life is promoting Durandran
and that's their big claim to fame, I don't want to be a part of it, as much as I'd like
Durandran, I don't want to be a part of 80s has been, I'm already enough of that,
thank you, so today is August the 14th, I don't know when you were listening to this
show, but it's actually one day after a pretty historical event for me personally, Adam,
I just want to send best wishes for August 13th, the anniversary of your first pod cast
two years ago, and thank you, my name's Len Edgerlee, I live in Denver, Colorado, and
even inspired me to try out pod casting, but mainly just to be a loyal member of your audience,
and what I think accounts for why you're a must listen to for me is you're open as an
honesty, you're consistency, incredible way that you keep doing this even through things
like the death of your mother, and you're always learning things, like playing around
a second life, so these are things I try to bring into my own experimentation with pod casting,
and you know, I think I'm either a culture or a skrunder, because I sort of fold the toilet
paper, but in a real loose way, so it's almost a skrunch, so I don't know, I've thought
about this, and it's amazing the things that David Sorsko gets me thinking about, including
that most intimate act, anyway, happy anniversary, a great day, and I hope you have lots
of celebration of it, thanks Bob.
Thank you so much, that's so kind of you.
I have, of course, you know, me and Adiversaries, I completely forgotten about it.
That was August 13, 2004, was indeed the first daily source code that had been doing
pod casts for several weeks, if not two months prior to that, although they weren't
really named as as such, I think it's so long ago, and of course, all those files of
lost, or they're sitting on a dot mac account somewhere.
Yeah, this whole scruncher folder debate is, is big.
It's amazing how every single person of all walks of life are interested in passing
on the information folder scruncher.
I think it's the mystery of it all.
It's why do you scrunch?
Why do you fold?
Is it something you brought up with?
Is it hereditary?
Does it say something about your personality?
I think in the next presidential elections, boxes of briefs, who cares, folder or scruncher
Mr. President?
Hey, Adam, this is Will, it's stranded in Cleveland.com, and I'm running a little bit
behind on the Charlie, and I was just listening to episode 415 on August 13, 2006, and
the affluent suburbs of Mayfield, Village, Ohio, near Cleveland, and the podcast, stranded
in Cleveland.com, not a plug there or anything.
Anyhow, I just wanted you to know, I just listened to you instructing everybody to plug
BSC into their cell phones and want to let you know that that is exactly what I did.
I stopped picked up my cell phone, put in DSC, and put in the number.
So now you're stuck with me even here in front of me.
Hey, love the show, and check out the stranded in Cleveland, and especially check out
my art.
Thanks, Norma.
All right, dude.
Thank you.
Probably about the same as Guilford sometimes.
So that's exactly what you should do, because, and I recommend you do this for any podcast
that has a phone number, because it's the perfect way to get in touch with the show that
you're listening to during your commute, if you commute, if you listen, whenever
you're listening away from your computer, program the name and the number of the show's
voicemail into your mobile cell phone.
For this show, it's plus one, two zero one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven,
or if you prefer it in the United Kingdom plus four, four, two, zero, seven, six, eight, one,
three, seven, five, three.
Hey, Adam, it's Kevin Crossman from the Frap Pack podcast at FrapPack.com.
Two questions, number one, what's this plus one thing with the phone number?
I've never heard that before.
Maybe that's a young versus Brits thing that you're picking up from, I'll living
over across the pond, I'd be interested in knowing, and then I'll go home, let's get to
that one first dude.
Okay.
Yeah, of course.
You're a young.
I'm a young too, but I'm a worldly young.
You see, the GSM protocol was developed specifically so you could roam around the world
and not have to enter in different country codes, as you may or may not know, in just
about every single country in the world except for the United States.
If you want to dial an international number, you dial zero zero and then the country code.
So that would be, if I was going to call the United States from anywhere but the United
States, it would be zero zero one and then the area code and then a number.
In the United States, if you wish to call overseas, you dial zero one one and then the
country code and the number.
So you see this is particularly when you travel between the US and anywhere else in the
world, it sucks because you want to have those numbers ready to go at the price of a
button, particularly if it's the daily source code number, right?
So a little trick, and this is a part of the GSM protocol, which is what we use on mobile
cell phones today, is to enter a plus, sometimes that's, you have to hit the zero key twice.
This plus basically tells the cell phone network, attention attention, standby for country
code.
So the US being one country code one and my number, my main number being a new jersey,
you do plus and then one and then the two zero one, sixty five, sixty five, seven.
So no matter where you are and it could happen that you travel outside of the US,
it will still work and you won't have to reprogram anything or re-enter the numbers or write
it down and then you know go back, it's just the way to go, enter a plus, it works a
universal.
Secondly, I want to leave you a folder scruncher, but I'm not really a folder, I'm not
really a scruncher.
It's sort of a folded scrunch, I don't know what to call that.
Anyway, if you have a term, I'd love to start using it, anyway, blow jobs, bye.
Oh, I feel so bad.
I feel so bad for the people who are listening to serious stars one or two right now.
I mean, in a way bad, because one way not bad, because of course, you still have three
and a half hours of fantastic pod show podcast coming at you on stars one or two.
I feel bad because you're not going to hear the folder scruncher song and another comment
about the big folder scruncher debate.
Inore will you hear brand new, deep purple, but if you go to dailysourcecode.com, you
can download the show, listen to the rest of it, or at the office, just go to dailysourcecode.com
and click on play it and it'll start playing for you right away.
On the way today, Scott Siggler, East Radio, CC Chapman, DVD weekly is coming up, Jersey
Todd Show, Don and Drew, right after Pacific Coast Hellway, which is next here on serious
stars one or two, I'll be back tomorrow with y'all take care and have a great day.
Okay.
So you're still here, which means you're in luck.
Hey Adam PD love from localsradio in thedadicast.com, so the folder scruncher debate.
Well, I admit I'm a scruncher, I know that distance me to be a surf in the folder lords
and bearings, but that's what I am.
When helping my kids clean their bottoms, I was a folder.
So with the phoning example, but daddy being a scruncher, what would they turn out to
be?
And I know you've talked about this being a hereditary thing before, so yes indeed, they
are scrunchers.
Perhaps folding is something that is just learned in kids, they don't get it because
they do scrunching because it's faster, I don't know, they're always in a hurry, so
that would explain it.
Frankly, I would just be happy if they stop missing the toilet, but anyway, by the way,
I just loaded up a new virtual mixtape on Lovehouse Radio episode 105 and episode 104
included a skit called Podsafe Idol.
Check it out and let me know how goofy you find it, because it's pretty goofy, but I
want to head and register Podsafe Idol.com on GoDaddy just in case it evolves in
anything.
Tell me what you think.
Anyway, enjoy your show every day and like I said, scruncher.
Alright, dude.
I hope you used the Daily Source Code DS3 code upon checkout to get your domain name for
only $6.95 a pity love, a outstanding citizen of Podsafe Idol in the second life.
Okay, scruncher folder, I was waiting for this to happen.
I came kind of from an unexpected, unexpected direction, I thought it might have come from
Jeff Smith or from someone else, but no, Slaw.
Do we remember who Slaw is?
Slaw is big on the Podsafe music network.
He was instrumental in the Podsafe for peace song, which of course will start cranking
up in a couple of months and he sent me an intro to the song, which unfortunately got
hoesed out somehow on the transfer, but it was like the middle of the night.
He was just finishing up the song and he just decided to crash.
So I'll do the intro here, that this is Slaw, it's a parody, so it's kind of iffy as
to how Podsafe it is, maybe under the guidelines of fair use, it's a parody anyway.
I present you the ultimate folder scruncher song.
We don't you worry baby, don't worry, cause I'm a wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe
in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-wipe-in-
we are the divas at the divacast.com we are five fun what do something fabulous friends
and this is Suzanne this is Carrie this is Amy I'm Julie I'm Sharon and we talk about things
like motherhood marriage friends careers that dreads rock and roll whatever the mood
hits us said grab a glass of wine and join us find us at the divacast.com the divacast.com
the divacast.com
yeah I subscribed to that show I just heard about it I believe Robin from inside works
produces it a fellow pilot airman and I sent a little a little link over to to myself
and a couple of the people of Podge on like oh yeah this is cool the divacast
it could also be called the milk cast quite honestly just listen into it you should
check it out oh I'll put a link in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
let me see I talked about it earlier about acura if you haven't checked out the acura target
cast yet and you want to find out about the acura RDX SUV and particularly about its
surround sound system which they they actually developed with musicians and with a
Grammy award winning producer then check it out it's obviously it's intended to be about their
car so it's not a podcast you know it's not an advertisement going under cover as a podcast it's a
target cast it's if you're interested and if not then please don't listen to it it's literally that's
simple acura.podge.com hey Adam can you hear me it is pandemonium here at top of the pod
safes to celebrate the 50th episode of the show we're putting on pod of balloons a virtual
concert featuring live performances of artists found on the pod safe music network tune in for this
week's episode and hey Adam bring your wider well I got to go because the shows about the
start and I'm the MC tune in at topofthepodsaces.com and the link will take you to my new pod
show site check it out that was right out I want to thank a couple of people actually
quite a right amount of people over at pod show hold on let me just open up the open up the Skype chat
we had open all weekend Chris Rockwell Joseph Engo Jersey Joe X98 Mark and Steve David Gavin John
thank you guys so very much for giving up a lot of your freedom over the weekend so people who are
registered with pod show plus could have more freedom more functionality more speed more freedom
that I already said that but that's really what I felt like these guys worked their ass off over
the weekend and really really appreciate it okay it's unavoidable first of all the reason
my lady Patricia's not on the show today is because she's visiting the British Museum with her
sister you've on today in the city so no time for Charlie no we've got to go look at the crown
jewels I said baby I got crown jewels right here they weren't they weren't bling enough apparently
so we just cannot avoid talking about terrorism because I just wrote the topic lightly on Friday
and got plenty of responses via email and of course voicemail as well perfect place to
to let your voice be heard I was trying to be as um how should we put it as careful as possible
because senseo this senseo moment brought to you by the diva cast calm trying to be as careful as
possible because when you get into discussions about religion man if that's shit can just go on forever
you know and at the end of the day there's no real proof of any religion of a lot of the claims that are
made I don't think you know once in a while we might see you know Maria in a cheese sandwich but that's
about as close as it gets um of course you know my main point is that here we go again now
now we're we're down deep into all kinds of new security measures already on the BBC they were
reporting that the airlines in particular the budget airlines like Ryan air an easy jet we'll not be
able to bear this pressure these guys fly with one plane on their routes so you know if you
go to Amsterdam the minute you get off that plane new passengers are loaded on that
fucker flies right back and it does the same thing all day long the the air crew often don't even
get out to to go to the bathroom they just sit there and just so it's the minute you delay anything
by little bit it all it just has a complete domino effect and so it's very very difficult these
new security measures obviously we understand why they're being put in place but I got a lot of feedback
about my comments in general and also listen to this one hey Adam this is Bill Geltner
Austin Texas calling about daily source code 440 and your comments about terrorism I'll keep this
short I'm pretty sure you won't play this I'm not even sure you bet I want you to play it all
I won't do it don't call into the voice mail if you don't want me to play it okay
I just want to tell you I'm just speaking from the heart and speaking honestly from somebody
who's a American citizen who knows that there's a lot of lies lying out out there about 911
lies about terrorism a lies about Islamic fundamentalism you act like that you know everything
you're being told about these wild Arab Islamic fundamentalism deep all is is really what the
problem is and you're just totally incorrect you really need to read books again I explain it to you
nobody's gonna believe it you'd get into it deep enough to understand just how wrong things have gone
but you'll read David Ray Griffin's books they're freely available what's to
tire play and know there's lots conspiracy theory and know that a lot of it it's it's supposed to look
outrageous you you post it Alex Jen's video about 911 a long time ago when I can understand why
you don't want to touch a lot of it but for you personally if you don't talk about it at all on
your podcast for you personally you really need to get up speed and quit spouting this crazy
stuff you're spouting it it feeds the whole pair of things and the psychological operation
that it is so read books get get informed and stop spouting the nonsense that you're going with
that this is not Islamic fundamentalist here this stuff is trumped up it's manipulated in your right
it is it's the reason you rightly say that they make all these claims that they need to support
is because yes it is meant to instill fear in the population and it's a matter of social control
for things that the public won't go for unless they have these terror effect terror attacks so
thanks for letting me talk yo dude of course that's what the church has all about well you know
obviously in your short two minute and twelve second rant there you didn't prove you didn't prove anything
okay and thank you I do read books I've read plenty of the conspiracy theories I think the only
thing that I really said that was one hundred percent true that just about everyone in the world agrees
to is and I incorrectly attributed it to JFK of course it was FDR Roosevelt said the only thing
we have to fear is fear itself and right now that's exactly what's happening we're fearing we're just
fearing we're afraid so if that whoever intended to instill that fear that part was very successful
that's working however you know I live in the United Kingdom I work in the United States and when
I'm working there of course I'm you know I'm staying there and I'm an American citizen I feel
very safe I think it's one of the best countries in the world still nothing wrong with it I feel
free when I roam the streets you know there's a lot of pros and cons and all different
countries around the world and I still think the United States is a great country and if indeed
if indeed there's all kinds of bad forces at work well then I have belief in other American
citizens that they will actually come to task and they will take on whatever bad and evil powers
look out there excuse me terrible so if if it's the administration dude if it's bush start running
for president start getting into politics that is the American way absolutely the American way to go
we only have two years shit's heating up now you got a hurry for sure hey and this is Mike
Will's I have just listened to your latest daily source code here and people concerned about flying
and stuff you know what I'm kind of with you I'd hop on a plane and just go along with the flow
and the terrorists with them I'm bored you know I'd say FU and I won't have in you late and that's
what I'd say because you know what if it's my time to go it's my time to go and there's no
controlling over what happens but yeah it is kind of freaky but you know what you're like to say
it's a dangerous world there have been podcasts.com my podcast if you want to listen to some great
music and folder and scruncher thanks man absolutely no matter what I don't care if it's our own
government or if it's someone from some cave somewhere or whoever the hell it is you're not going
to scare me I'm getting on airplanes I am flying and I'll take I'll take whatever lumps I have
to even if that means flying naked. Hey Adam on today's DSC you made a comment about the next
time they'll find some guy with dynamite up his ass and we'll all be subjected to body cavity
searches so soon we'll have to fly naked that might not be a bad thing but we guess it is Adam
keep in mind when the rest of us fly we usually don't get to fly on a plane full of super
models like I guess you wow I know the last few times I flown I've seen people I don't want
to sit next to little ones they make it this is sac from the dirty jokes podcast keep safe yeah
what happened to good looking stewardesses I know you're supposed to call them flight attend
that's what happened to them at least virgin makes an effort you know they make they make all the
girls pin their hair up and and wear a nice little cute kind of old fashion like 50s uniforms
you know I wouldn't mind that you know why that's going to pay in for and I heard the support
on the NPR over the weekend in all things considered I'm going to play this report for you
because it really got me going and I want you to and you you may have no sympathy for me on this
but it really got me going I heard this and luckily the reporter says he's biased right up front
but have a listen I'll admit it up front on this story I'm biased I've been standing in
long security lines for years now watching first class passengers cut to the front first class
there's this class airline trust I don't mean the first class line at the ticket counter
and this isn't about the government's program for pre-screen flyers either but we're talking
about here are the special short lines leading up to security that are reserved for first class
passengers or even coach passengers who hold the airlines elite club cards I've been grumbling about
this for years mainly to myself like some kind of old crank but all of a sudden I've got company
that's outrageous everybody should be equal whether you first class or you're up
up of the coach in America's long airport security lines class resentments are simmering
they said let them in case I felt like with her lateria it was very frustrating
on Thursday Bridget Gargan waited in a line that snaked all the way back to the airport parking garage
and after two hours she missed her flight trying again on Friday she was ready to
storm the barricades you know what I think in in times like this we should all be in this together
and if it really is for the good of the country it was frustrating yesterday to wait two and
half hours in line to watch people because they had a little more money be able to walk through
first class flyer Ryan Schull hardly notices the indignation brewing in coach as he's
waved to the front of the line if you travel every week it's nice little benefit so
just see this a little bit of time you don't hear any grumbling from the poultry at
back there but just walk right by and don't listen to it and whom does Schull and the other
first class passengers have to thank for having their own line the airlines or the publicly run
airport as it turns out a little of both standing at a railing and looking down at the
rat maze of passengers waiting for security airport spokesman Bob Parker explains we may actually
control the shape of the line as the airport operator but if the airlines choose to have a
special line for a special category of their customer they can't Parker says many airports have
similar arrangements the airlines are tenants in a public facility but they're traditionally
allowed to arrange for special treatment for their best customers even in the airports public areas
it's really no different than buying the first class seat on the airplane at the front of the
airplane with your own restroom and a nicer meal and that explanation seems to satisfy a lot of
the people standing in line truth be told even as bad as things got on Thursday a lot of the people in
the economy class line shared the view of these gentlemen from Texas Herbert Hasket and Larry Lewis
I get they paid to give a to be for a class so she should stay to give for a class service
if I pay for the ticket I don't want to be the same thing yeah so things don't look too good for a
revolution in the departure lounge anytime soon they say we Americans don't resent rich people because
we're all brought up to believe we have a crack at having our own fortune someday could be the same
is true about flying first class they did Martin costume and PR news Seattle I'm aren't costume you should
be kissing my ass you should be licking it are you stupid this really got me so angry
I fly the equivalent of business class I could even fly first class if I wanted to but I
fly the equivalent of business class between London and San Francisco I fly this on virgin Atlantic
because I love their service and their flight attendants are I have cute outfits on
upper class is the equivalent of business class on British airways the price of a ticket is 12,000
dollars for a round trip be here me 12,000 dollars now why do I take this expense why does
pod show pay for this because when I get off the plane in San Francisco I drop my shit off at
the condo and I go straight to work why because I can I feel fit I'm rested I was able to do what
I wanted to do on the plane they've got fantastic movies I'm playing paying for all of that I don't
get a chance to go to movie theaters I didn't get a chance to go to movie theater and being paid for it
to see little man damn I should go see that anyway I pay for that I pay to be able to fly back on
a moment's notice and change my tickets I pay extra money for that and you know what that does Martin
that subsidizes every other class of travel below business it subsidizes the reason you can fly
for 50 bucks it's because I'm paying 12,000 proletarians fuck you the oh man just piss me off
and what is this look it's security you have to go security through security if there's a
shorter line you can pay for it fine this has nothing to do with we all have to be the same
we're all in this together you wouldn't be in the fucking excuse me I shouldn't say I shouldn't
use that word you wouldn't be in the line as many times as you are if I didn't subsidize your travel
and let me tell you airline bosses you better go talk to somebody because it's very look I know a lot
about aviation we're very very very very for you dangerously close to the point where it makes a
lot more sense for a private airline to fly two planes back and forth between New York and London or
London and San Francisco or to New York and San Francisco back and forth because for the same amount
of money you can fill up a plane with 20 people in a nice BBJ Boeing business jet and we have
great we have no freaking hassles with security you walk right through you check right in
your hop on the plane you're back and forth of course the flexibility may not be there
but the flexibility of not having to go through the airports is what's going to happen you're going to
lose you really are and when we don't when business traveler stop flying everything goes everything
stops dead in its tracks so you guys gotta go talk to whoever you talk to whenever you need some
you really do and please please stop with it just because they have a little bit more money they
don't need you would not be in the line most likely if I wasn't subsidizing your travel man
no just a personal thing you may think I'm a dick for going off about it but
man really got to me as promised uh want to wrap up put today's show with something new from
depurple who have just joined the pod safe music network this has a riff that will kill you
even Christina liked it oh no could it show up on pod safe the queen to be reported tonight for
release on pod show applause never know girls like that purple on the podcast
i'm gonna bounce my face i can't be what you say i love to stop and talk you keep
fat in the region just the way she said something at all is so convincing but she's good on the phone
i wait until she's ready that could be a while but she always takes a time that she turns up and starts
up and up but didn't recognize a car when man he has to be in the field
he has no sense of reason and a reasonable one makes any sense at all
for a reason well guys she said you know what i mean but i get to understand
no one she may have a reasonable man wasn't meant that way i was only having fun
she didn't appear in the yard damn it just found i got prepared to present she was on my phone
but i don't be the other way in the head since you come
girls like that
purple girls like that from their double CD set rapture of the deep links in the show
notes of daily source code there on the pod safe music network proud to have you
mates and that's it for the show for today a little bit long but man we had a lot of stuff
to do and it's the start of a new week so i'll be back tomorrow uh again probably
a pod save the queen coming up tonight and uh who knows what will be happening on the video
front take care everybody have yourself a good day out of it pod show dot com and daily source
code dot com bye bye another pod show pod guest stick it in your ear