From the Curry Cottage Hillford UK, from the Curry Condo, San Francisco, or from the Curry
Cockbidders, guys above, wherever Adam might be.
There's always the Daily Source Code, this is episode number 483, with Adam Curry.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Welcome to the robot weather in Celsius for the Guildford region on Monday to 23rd October.
Today, chance of righting with the maximum temperature of 13 degrees.
To not chance of righting with the minimum temperature of 11 degrees.
Tomorrow, chance of righting with the maximum temperature of 12 degrees.
My favorite situation is, I'm always the kick-ups.
I'll be first a cast.
I don't need to sweep it down the line.
I'll sit in front of my turn.
Just take it to the top.
I'll scream in till my lunchbox.
I'll stand here till I drive.
The feeling is leaving.
It's so dark.
It's the sleeping.
We don't stop.
I'll be in the cup with the suit.
And now, I'll stand for the wind and nothing coming.
Baby that.
I know you hate me.
And you can change me.
You make the watch so fine.
But it's no matter I can see you.
You used to be so special.
Now I want all the time.
You think the same will meet.
Just say, don't decide.
The feeling is leaving.
It's so dark.
It's the sleeping.
We don't stop.
I'll be in the cup with the suit.
And now, I'll be in the cup with the suit.
Now I'll be in the cup with the suit.
We just say, don't stop.
It's just a maze where I don't want you
You make a much better fun
But we don't matter what you think
Oh, what?
It's been a long time ago
It's just a way to get me
But I know this isn't one thing
One thing we won't mind about
You can put my name on the top line
Yeah, baby
I don't need to pay me
I don't want you
You know what you're doing?
You're just a maze where I don't want you
I don't pay me
I don't want you
You make a much better fun
But I know this isn't one thing
I don't want you
You make a much better fun
It's a way to get me
Danko Jones
Baby hates me
Kickin' off another week of the Daily Source Code
Can you hear it?
Can you feel it?
Can you feel the sound?
Yeah, I'm back at the Curry Cottage
Everybody
It is a Daily Source Code episode
Good to be back home
It's, well, you already heard the weather
So, you know, it's kind of crappy
That's something new we're going to be launching
In the next week or next couple of weeks
There's the robot weather, fill in your zip code
And automatically automatically
Apodcast is created with your weather
I think it's twice a day
So
Yeah
It's good to be back
You can tell it's still a little bit of
Hairball left in the throat
Oh, it's so nice to have my two
Processor back
Oh, I just love it
Really, it makes such a difference
When you've got a particular sound
That particularly when you can just talk
As loud as you want
And everything jams into the
Compressor, into the whole sound system
It's kind of driving a car
You know, it's like
Your own car always drives the best
You know how to drive it
And then setting up a buying a new car
Has always little takes a little getting used to
So that's kind of what I got going on at the condo
I got to get me another one of these TLAs
Though for over there
Just so much better
I'm kind of missing that noise gate
Though you know you hear
So much more noise in the background
You can hear
It's just a lot of noise here
I've got the
The mini fridge running
I've got the fan on the
VIO is probably kicking into high gear
And there's a couple of max
That are still on
Anyway, so here's something new
I get back yesterday
Patricia, you know, let's me like
Bring my suitcase upstairs
She says, okay, let's hop in the car
I gotta go show you something
Of course, a house
And it was pouring rain
It was absolutely pissing out of the skies
I mean like we took took umbrellas
Went to the place
I have to say she is found quite a gem
Really, very nice
In Guilford
And with more space
More rooms, more garden, more view
More modern
Fantastic
And we just got back about 20 minutes ago
And guess what?
We'll be moving in
In January
Can you believe it?
After all this going back and forth
All this crap that we've been going through
Within three seconds
We take care of business
I'm so happy
So there's going to be a lot of
A lot of interesting times in the next couple months
Traveling back and forth between here and San Francisco
Getting the whole second
Sorry
Not used to
I forgot about the blackberry
Doesn't work on this setup
Yeah, moving, packing
Oh, how about this?
How about trying to get broadband
And installed before we move
Oh, yeah, it's going to be very, very interesting times
And of course, you'll be along for the ride
Okay, Adam, I'm slightly grossed out now
I'm listening to the DSC
On my pay for him
And
Listening to the story of our woman touching herself
And the sound of your voice
That's it
I'm listening to the show
The woman touches herself
Right
So really grossed out now
And appreciate it
He didn't play anymore comments like that
It's sparkling in the morning
To think about it
Thanks
Bye
Of course we're referring to Giselle
If you didn't hear Friday show where Giselle called in
You've got to go back and check it out
I'm really full of my Friday
Dude, I'm sorry, maybe you should not listen to the show on your paper
Around early in the morning
Maybe if I get her to talk about you
Would that make a difference?
Would it make you feel a little bit better?
I think so
So please don't take away all my jalis
Made a super big mistake last week
And I was thinking I didn't want to make this mistake
And somehow it slipped out anyway
I played the, actually I'll do it
I'll play it for you again
The folder scruncher jingle
And for some reason I don't know why
I miss identified this as being something
That was made by Jeff Smith
You know this one right?
People talk about it baby
Of course it's fantastically done this
I'm doing it wrong
Doing it wrong
Don't you worry baby
Don't worry
Because I'm wiping, wiping, wiping my book
Of course not pot safe, but shit
I'm a roller
I'm a scruncher
And I'm a buncher
I do my business on the throne
I'm a sitter
I'm a standard
I'm a left-right tender
It's nice to know I'm not alone
So of course I was pretty stupid
Because the person who made that is none other than slow
Everybody's slow
And he sent me a really nice email
He said you know I totally understand where you
You probably forgot and was thinking of Jeff Smith
I've done that because he does all these great jingles
Not just for the daily source code
He doesn't afford it
I think everyone in podcasting now
He stopped by Jeff Smith
The Jeff Smith dot com
At one point or another
And then slotted something really cool
He said if anyone really deserves a jingle
It's Jeff Smith
And that's an interesting point
Because you know it's hard
I don't like making openings
And jingles and imaging and sound bits
For my own show
It sounds weird
You want someone else to do it
Which is why I'm always begging and pleading for more new intros
I need a
484, 485, 46, 47, 488, 49
I've got a 490
And so what slotted it is he created a jingle for Jeff Smith
And I was blown away by this check it out
Jeff Smith, Jeff Smith
It's another jingle from Jeff Smith
Just give him a subject and he should've come up
Please
Yeah, I'm another jingle from me
Jeff Smith
Crap
I want one of those
Dude, please
I want the lady singing harmony
It's fantastic
I love it
Now bring up
This is Angie B. Hostess of the Chill Count
Special guest Moshing in the studio this week
Hello Angie and hi to your listeners
Moshing and I got together to talk about
It's brand new self-release city chill dynasty
And a whole lot more
The internet is really allowed
And in the musicians a platform
You know before the internet
You know who is going to play your music on the radio
Just really excited about
The idea that one can do it like this
You know, rope with someone who you've never met in person
And endowed over the internet
It's a great way to meet people
It's a great way to see how other people work
Come check out this half hour special feature
The show counts with Angie B
At showcans.podshow.com
You can tell that I check out promos.podshow.com
This morning is that was prepping for the show
Lots of great promos rolling in there
If you're ever looking for some cool shows to listen to
Just check out the promo feed
Promos.podshow.com
You can subscribe to it as well
In podshow plus
Angie B
I have so much that still want to do with Angie
We still have that soap opera
Which she's already done her half
And it's been like four weeks
Maybe even five weeks
If I had the opportunity to do my side
I promise you I'm going to get this week
It's just has been crazy
And I didn't have the right set up
The right sound and everything in the condo
There's another promo that I found
That was very cool
Jay Donnelly is always working on stuff
He's got like 18 podcasts
It's unbelievable to be on stuff he's doing
And I think he got Joe Klein to cut this form
It's of course, you know
We got Halloween coming up and
Well, special programming on its way as well then
With a regional Emedyville homeowner George Lutz
Since 1969
The first ever interview
With convicted murderer Ronald Defeyels
wife Tracy from Greenville, South Carolina
Nightmare in Emedyville
The Ronald Defeyels story
Death in the family
Which shall steal
Yeah
Coming soon
To mad pod
Come
Oh
Joe Klein the announcer guy doing his thing there
Very nice nightmare in Emedyville
I
Didn't get a lot of responses
To my question about French vanilla
We were talking about Splenda last weekend the last week Friday whatever
And there was a question that came in why why is it always French vanilla
What are the French known for and low and behold
John Glass Cox sends in an email
French vanilla contains egg yolks
Or an extra fortification of egg yolks
The term here comes quote
The term French vanilla
Has often used to designate preparations that actually have a strong vanilla aroma
And possibly contain vanilla grains
But originates from the French style of making ice cream
Custard base with vanilla beans, cream and egg yolks
Voila
Seto
A little lesson in French vanilla
And all you got to do now is mix up with some hazelnut
I can't get it over here
I can't get the Splenda's
I wonder if they're going to go international with that or not
They should
Shit they've got enough people talking about it now
There's a link on the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
If you want to phone in your best makes your best recipe
Your best use of Splenda
And of course you can always go to destinationflavor.com
Tell us about your flavor
More videos about why the food and food come in
Okay, so let's subscribe
Where the Why the коммент.ail
Nice to meet you
Next time
Cheers
Fuck the toast
Here come the Interest
Of the drinks
Come on son.
Ok, I'm gonna talk about the tunes you know...
Okay good go.
so alright, and etcetera that you did.
Its the left.
It's upper club e Walletable.
That's the new...
.. something new scene collaboration...
....the music Today a part by Isaac Nott
And I came to see Girl
thevert to be a part.
stay.
I'll find Mega🜰파Kats that held your club it's
experience from beginning to end.
So be sure to check us out.
Alpha, Mega inverkats!
You want some crunch you want to listen to that, the
alpha megapodcast from HotLana. You can find that at podshow.com, of course.
So I want to tell you a bit about what you can look forward to in the next couple of weeks.
I've been more than hinting about the official unleash of theBTpodshow.com, which will
kick off the end of the first week, the beginning of the second week of November, which
means, well, excuse me, be opening it up, wide. And of course, this will be a very UK
centric, but all a part of our original system and platform. And at the same time,
this is where it gets really exciting. We're also going to be releasing a new version of
podshow.com, podshow plus it's for really going to be adding a whole bunch of features,
room-moving a lot of things that didn't make any sense. Whole new layout, whole new graphics,
and we've been working on this for quite a while, obviously. And so we're going to have,
and we're integrating the pod save music network, it'll stand on its own, so nothing is
really going to change if you go to music.podshow.com, however, now pieces of that will be
integrated into podshow plus itself. So you'll have music, podcast, and video. So we're adding
a category there, even though you can create a podcast out of anything you want, including videos,
which a lot of people are doing now at podshow. You'll also be able to upload videos into
a separate path, which will allow you to publish something quickly. Very much the way YouTube does,
it only there will be some very cool ways to integrate that into a podcast if you want to,
it can stand alone. It's a lot of thought, a lot of hard work has gone into this. So you'll see
that showing up, probably around the same time as we launch btpodshow.com, and then there's something
else called the plus, which we haven't really talked about, but I think I've been hinting about
that as well. It's an additional video project that anyone will be able to participate in,
and I think you're really going to like it. I don't want to say too much about that right now.
I want to concentrate on the btpodshow.com launch and the new version of podshow,
with new modules for, it's going to be so different. It is a total mind fucker when you see.
It's like, oh, wait a minute. Now starting, nothings are starting to come together. We've been
releasing features and fixes and stomping on bugs for, well, since we launch, which was August
September three months ago. That's when we unleashed. So you're going to, I think, I think you're
like it. There will be a lot of changes, a lot of things. Hopefully, I'll be here for the next
couple weeks, and we'll be able to be here for podcastcon UK that I believe is on these and on the
18th. Yeah, I think it's the 18th of November. There's also some other stuff that's been going on
and luckily enough, you folks are nice enough to keep me updated while I was away.
Hello Adam, A's GD from GD's by size bonus here. I just give me a gig report and what's been
happening in the UK while we've been away. As you know, we had podfests down the purple turtle.
Yes, gone safe and the purple turtle. And it was a nice, absolutely fantastic. This was last Thursday
the 19th of October. We had four great brands on the bill. It worked wonders for the UK music podcasting.
So many people coming into the place and knowing who we were basically saying, yes, I listened to
your podcast, which is tremendous. As you had one girl, a New Zealand girl who works for BT and
came up to me and said, ah, I know all about podcasting because BTs involved with BT podshow,
which I thought was brilliant. She said she's going to spread the word about the gigs that we're
doing at podfests. Now you missed this one. No problem mate. No problem. We're doing it all again
in November the 29th. I hope you're in the UK then and who come down. I would love to see
there and show you how was Brits know how to rock out and have a good night out. Make sure
it's a date for your diary. Purple turtle, 29th November, it's podfests. More details at www.podfests.co.uk.
Another purple turtle extravaganza podfests UK. All right. Yeah, I think it'll work out perfectly.
I may be able to hit podcaster car and then go to the San Francisco and come back and be in time
for the purple turtle extravaganza looking forward to it. What else was it going to say? There was
something about it. There was a crap. Screw it. I don't remember. Maybe it'll come back.
Found that Howard Jones is on the pod save music network Howard Jones of course have been
playing his records ever since I was 19 and looking at the picture of him on the pod save music
network. It's and he's lost a lot of hair since then. It's like receded all the way back.
But it's great. And there's a little blurb up here. He has released one track,
which he put up on 20. He put up yesterday. Released for podcasters to promote the forthcoming
UK hit makers tour with ABC and Toya. A world tour is to follow in 2007. When playing this track,
please include tour details and this link. Oh, hold on. podcast live. Oh, I see. There's
no interesting. Let's see if we can open this up. What is this link? That's an interesting
way to do that to promote something. The pod save music network home on this link is a little
messed up. We'll fit tour dates dot pdf. Cool. Oh, we have a 404 arrow at the
fuckers. That can't be right. Hold on. HJ tour dates dot pdf. Looks like I'm
shithead. Let me just go look at that home page and see if there's anything there about how
a Jones tour dates. Well, there's a link to podcast live dot code dot UK. But the link that
how a Jones put in the pod save music network is not working. I'll have to look into that. Okay,
so we'll find out what the tour dates are in the meantime. I wanted to take a listen to the song
because it's I really liked it. It's kind of like classic Howard Jones, but
modernized. Oh, no 80's vibe. Just rocking. Building our own future. From the pod save music network,
Howard Jones on DSC or 83.
What we feel in the morning to meet this song between the live and the dark song.
So take a step in this place. God have been building our own future. Just for now,
day by day. Three, two, two, a life. It's been for more of us.
Putting people's lives at the top is the first consideration.
Changing in the heart of just one of the world of things and timing sounds.
Don't give it up to the free table for us around this way. It's a song between the
in and the outside. So take a step in this place. God has been building our own future.
Just for now, day by day. Three, two, two, a life. It's been for more of us.
So take a step in this place. God have been building our own future. Just for now, day by day.
God have been building our own future. Just for now, day by day. Three, two, three, two, a life. It's been for more of us.
So take a step in this place. God have been building our own future. Just for now,
day by day. Three, two, two, a life. It's been for more of us.
So you got to hold it, rock? Our Jones has that great way of producing the, you kind of
like that snare back, back, back, very typical for him. Sounds lovely. Building our own future,
how are Jones? You can find it at music.podshow.com or through the show notes at dailysourceco.com.
I found it. So I'll put that link into the show notes for the PDF. There was a little space that's snuck in there accidentally.
How it will be performing at the Historic Avalon Theatre in eastern on the 26th of October.
The Oakville Center for Performing Arts in Toronto on the 27th, the 28th. Let me see.
Then he's coming over to the UK on the 2nd of November. That's the hitmiggers tour with ABC and Toya.
That could be kind of cool. So he'll be at in Bristol on the 2nd,
Ipswich on the 3rd, Reading on the 9th. He's coming to London, Birmingham on the 11th. Let me see.
So okay. He's going to do Folkston on the 23rd,
Portsmouth. Okay. Portsmouth is on December 1st. That's, well, we might go there. I think that's
not where we saw Jones call it. Before I forget, I could use a couple more phone calls.
You guys have gotten a little bit lazy. I'll give me a call. Let me know what you're up to,
which is thinking of Friday. By the way, I spoke to the wing commander this morning.
The Delta Sierra, my aircraft has been completely overhauled.
He really went from front to back, top to bottom, took everything off, opened everything up,
re-adjusted all bits and pieces. Remember, I did have a hard landing, which bugged the ASI,
the air speed indicator. And so he figured it was a good time to go and check everything.
So apparently, she's completely ready. And what he said to me was, I look at Friday's good.
I'm coming over Friday. I'll pick you up. Then we'll fly back. Then we'll do a couple of circuits.
We'll fly around a bit. It's always good to get some extra instruction from the wing commander.
And then he'll pack me off solo on the trip back home. He says it's time. It's time you do this.
So that could be a very big adventure for me. And of course, I'll be recording every single step
of the way. At least we'll have something for prosperity, right? Okay tomorrow, I'll get the
lady Patricia on. We'll talk about the new house and have an update from Pod Show HQ more
about the launch here. Yeah, the typical stuff. Take care yourself. Adam at PodShow.com. Thank you.
So much for listening. Bye.