Already a hit state side now you can check out the following podcast and good old
blighty btpotjo.com single-handedly making amends for the Boston Tea Party one show at a time
at him curry and the daily source code is on the air
delta Sierra Charlie 5-0-6
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass then the next generation
radio content in my ears I like to think I'm flying into the future
I'm not going to get it my way
I'm going to get it my way
I'm not hiding my way
oh yeah, that's why I'm talking about
around
the
balance
The show notes at daily source
So number five, zero six of the daily source code coming to you from the affluent suburb of
Surrey and Gilford in the United Kingdom, still playing Mr. Mom Patricia still in Rotterdam.
I gotta tell you, man. Why I'm told you this before? Ah, so much respect for,
for basically any parent who stays at home and makes the house run.
Particularly if you got kids and animals and crap like that.
Oh boy, there's so much to do. And you know what?
I've got to do everything just right because you know this right whenever she comes back,
the first thing she does is investigates everything.
To see if everything has been done properly and if everything was done on time.
And of course there's the the obvious stuff, feed the kid, feed the animals.
Ah, but if you don't open the curtains in the morning, well, then the Mary and the neighbor on the other side of the street,
you know, she'll see that and then she'll wonder if something's wrong and she'll report that.
And then of course, I'm in trouble because I didn't do exactly as I'm supposed to do.
So I'm creating a checklist.
As a as an aviator, I believe strongly in checklist because they will basically keep you alive.
You can't think you know the checklist. You can't think I, you know,
I'll remember and I won't forget any of the items because of course,
there will be a day when you do forget an item and that could of course be what we call a day record.
So I have this checklist man. It's like first, you know, the first part of the checklist isn't even really my checklist.
It's the dog. Now, now I sleep through this, but every single morning, the dog comes up to Patricia.
This little Yorkshire Terrier. He's very sweet and we love him dearly.
But you know, he comes up and he'll make these noise.
It's like it's not really a bark, but it's kind of like a half bark going.
Well, you know, and this little dog, right? And he makes this really, this, this really big sound.
So I've learned to sleep through that, but that of course is the signal and that comes around 630 a.m.
That the dog wants to be put up on the bed.
So now, of course, that's part, that's the first item when I checklist in the morning.
And then, you know, it's seven when I actually, when the alarm goes off, because we've got to get Christine off to school.
The other check start and that includes folding the covers back on the bed.
It includes opening up the curtains and the blinds.
Then, of course, I have to carry the dog downstairs.
Make sure that he goes out into the backyard to do his stuff.
Then, I have to pour a little special glass of cat milk for the, for ginger for our, our tabby.
I mean, it just goes on and on and on and on.
But let me tell you, guys, if you, if you're serious about not getting shit,
you got to make a checklist.
And my checklist is longer than that of a fucking 747 unfortunately.
What are you going to do?
Ah, she's back.
Amy Mac.
Here to get my ass in shape with some real work.
It's week 17 of our quest to save Adam's ass.
What are we doing?
Adam, how are you?
I'm good, Amy, how are you?
What's wrong?
We're getting fancy.
We're going to need a chair and your wireless because we're on the floor.
Oh, shit.
Okay, let me turn on the other one.
You're a folding chair would be great.
I wouldn't really recommend a chair on wheels.
Okay, I got it.
I go collect your goods.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
I got it.
Okay, I'm on the other mic now.
Okay, I'll face the chair seat toward you.
The chair.
Oh, face it towards me.
Now, play on the ground and pop your feet up onto the chair.
Oh, hold on.
You want your feet as flat as possible on the chair seat.
All right.
Okay.
Now lift your butt and make a bridge.
Lift it on the floor.
We're back in the day.
Take it to the bridge.
Okay.
Now you're going to go up and down 10 times.
Ready, go.
Up and down.
When you come down, you want to come close but not all the way to the floor.
Oh, okay.
Oh, my God.
Keep it slow and control.
All right.
Your hands are going to lay on the floor next to you.
Two.
The button free.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now on 10th one, hold it up there.
Four.
Squeeze your butt as high as possible.
I make my clients use this ability, but for their feet to create an unstable surface.
So you lucked out with the chair.
Oh, thanks.
All right.
You can come down.
This works.
Your butt, legs, stomach, and even your calves and back.
I'm sure you felt every single one of us.
Oh, yes, I did.
Every single one.
I'm out of touch.
Say nice things about me.
Until next time.
Thank you so much.
Amy, how could I not say nice things about you?
Get rid of the other mic there.
Wow.
Yeah, I did feel that one.
Well, that one in my ass.
You know, you could actually do that with two people that exercise.
Just to make it a little bit more challenging.
Go ahead and visualize what I look like doing that.
And you'll know exactly what I'm talking about.
Let's see.
What am I hearing now?
How was that?
Something's, oh, I see.
Okay, there we go.
The other mic was still on.
Let me see.
I have a whole list of things to talk about here.
First of all.
On pod show plus if you go into your collection and you add a show.
The RSS and OPML importers are live and they're back and they're working.
So you can literally take an OPML file of subscriptions.
You can upload that into your pod show plus account into the collections.
And it will load all of your shows in.
You can actually create it into a single channel if you want to.
You can add an external RSS feed to get to put a show into your collection,
which is not currently in the database.
And of course it's automatically then added to the database,
so to show up and search.
And I'm quite, quite chaffed with that actually.
Yeah.
It's working.
Big story here in the UK.
This is unbelievable.
You heard about this Russian spy who was poisoned to death.
Now, of course, you know, that's the story.
And it sounds very plausible.
It's one of the definitely sounds like one of those kind of cold war era.
James Bond asked type scenarios where Russian spy is poisoned by.
What is the.
Let me find out.
I'll put a link in the show notes to the CNN story.
The actual poison is.
Polonium to one zero.
A rare radioactive element usually made in specialized nuclear facilities.
So this guy was riddled with it.
And he died.
And he looked really shitty at the end there because they have all kinds of footage that they run of him.
I presume that's the end of his life that they're showing in the hospital bed.
So they they checked out hotel rooms where this guy was restaurants,
office buildings, and they're finding traces of this polonium to one zero everywhere.
And and someone thought, you know, maybe we should check out the airplane that he flew on.
So now two seven sixty sevens at Heathrow British airway seven six sevens have been tested positive.
And a third was grounded in Moscow awaiting examination for contamination of polonium two one zero.
British airways now trying to contact 33,000 passengers who have flown on these jets since October 25.
That's an interesting statistic right there.
Two hundred and twenty one flights in two months, I guess, or less than two months.
Three thousand crew and airport personnel had contact with the planes.
And let me see apparently.
Sixty eight have been referred to specialists health authorities.
Test take about one week.
I mean, you know, we were all freaked out and we shut basically shut down the air, you know, the air or the aviation industry.
For for this explosive so called explosive liquids that terrorists were planning on taking on board.
And when he's that shit.
Yeah, we got to have it, you know, got to have another scan now.
We've got to have radiation scans while we go through to make sure that you're not trying to kill you to fill up passengers.
And it is quite serious, though, and I'll bet you that a lot of people are going to get quite sick from this, even if they.
Yeah, this is basically if you ingest it or inhale it, you're fucked.
Lots of feedback about yesterday's story about Cliff Richard, sir Cliff Richard.
Who's some of his songs that he wrote and and of course also they were hit songs that he has copyright on.
About to expire in 2008, actually, and Sir Cliff is making a big issue of it and saying he's one of the instigators of trying to extend the copyright.
Lifetime from 50 years to 95 years because essentially in 2008 hits when his songs start to become public domain, which means anyone can use them for anything without paying a license to Sir Cliff.
And understandably, yeah, he's upset.
There are some opposing views.
Don't work in Ask Up. I just thought I'd like to weigh in on the 50 year copyright and plans for extension or please for extension right Cliff Richard with a couple of thoughts.
The first one is that in this country, UK, can reach school at 16 and get a job and make you weigh in the world and work at 165.
That's 49 years in which you have to provide for yourself and put enough money away to provide a pension for when you retire.
So I don't know why Cliff Richard didn't get any difference.
He's got 50 years living off the year, the world sees some of his songs.
And now he should have put enough away to keep him for the rest of his days, he doesn't need a copyright extension.
And it's a copyright extension to a longer term with right is right.
And how come he's got any staff to decide it's important at the 50 year barrier starts to arrive?
There is really that important. This should have been agitated for this 20, 30, 40, 45 years ago, maybe even 40, 90 years ago.
Say that the 50 year copyright was wrong.
And now it doesn't come to the attention now, it's about now the gravy change about the cost of the rails.
Well, good luck to him. I don't think he deserves it.
I don't think many other people will either, but for now.
Well, some interesting things there.
It sounds a little bit like you're throwing some of your own unhappy dark baggage onto Sir Cliff.
And I had a good think about this.
I'm a copyright holder myself. I do lots of stuff that has that I own that has copyright over it.
I think the first thing is you should not presume just because Cliff Richard, Sir Cliff Richard, I really should say that all the time because it's proper Sir Cliff.
Just because Sir Cliff has made millions over a 50 year time span.
Don't think for a second that he's still gotten money.
I think this is one of the biggest misconceptions of people who are famous is that they actually famous and rich at the same time.
Those two increasingly do not go hand in hand really they don't.
And it's very difficult to sustain a lifestyle once you hit it big.
You know, you got to kind of keep hitting big records hit records and over time, you know, royalties on some of his songs, you know, they definitely dwindle licensing.
I'm sure if someone wants to do a commercial and license his music, you know, those are nice little hits interim hits.
But but don't for a second think that he's made or that he still has a shitload of money.
So I think that he, he may just, you know, he very well may want to keep that income.
You know, it could easily be, you know, what about, you know, so think about it. He's got to living dull, which is, you know, worldwide very famous hit, you know, got myself a cry and walk and talk and, you know, whatever live in dull.
So, Mattel will be able to use that for their Barbie commercial and Sir Cliff left the sit at home agitated watching that song.
The creation, his art, his work sell plastic dolls with no genitalia.
And that could be very frustrating. So I do see the other side of the coin on the other hand. I think it's wonderful.
That creative works coming to the public domain and can be used by others.
But you know that really what's going to happen is going to be used commercially. So I don't know. I'm kind of on both sides of the fence.
I feel, I feel his pain in a way. Now there's lots of shit that I've done that people re broadcast on mainstream radio and television stuff that they would all definitely have to ask my permission for and they never do.
You know, you can spend all your lifetime, you know, running around trying to track down money for that.
But as an example, my official biographer, the official biographer of curry of my broadcast career, Tom Scooting.
You can find him at clockwalk.net. He lives down under. He's been collecting a lot of my radio shows from the past and he put up three clips through YouTube clips.
I got to tell him that he's got to put the shit up. He's got to use the the new Potio video uploader.
You know, we also do the flash video thing now and you can put it in your collection. You can share it and do all kinds of cool shit with it.
Potio plus.
So he found three clips, which I've put on curry.com. You've got to see these.
One is well, two of them are me on stage with famous people performing with them. Well, famous.
Let's just say meet loophus famous and there's some other guys.
And another one where I pretty funny interview I did with Grace Jones in the very early 80s.
And, you know, that's all stuff that, you know, obviously I have certain rights over that material.
You know, now it's on YouTube, you know, what are you going to do?
That's just kind of a fact of life and I'm actually I'm quite happy that it can be shared and people can enjoy this crap from 25 years ago.
And maybe get a good laugh out of it or just the laugh out of my, my hair, you know, either way it's okay.
Hi Adam, it's Mark. I'm talking to you.
It turns out the BBC held and you suggested that Potio squaps cast my ears for me.
So guess for her.
Yeah, I know worked for a radio one.
And I'll be doing the back for sure as of next Monday.
I don't know if that is all we've said about it.
But, you know, you'll be taking over at TomPotcast.com.
And we're not going to say in Oxford Beauty, Potio, he wants to remain independent.
He told me as he was clearly noticed.
But, good news all around.
So thanks for suggesting that to the BBC.
Hey, I don't know who this is.
But stop fucking calling the Daily Source Code asshole.
Mark, on Jerry Buckley.
Plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3, plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3.
And this Jousel thing has really gotten out of control.
People sending in all kinds of, all kinds of fun audio.
You heard that one just came in.
Not particularly aimed at you, tartan man.
Thanks for calling it.
I was kind of funny actually.
Check this out.
I think you're like it.
So, you know, what's kind of like it?
And I just, she's so cute.
I thought it was a joke.
She sent me a picture by the way.
Okay.
I don't know who this is.
But stop fucking calling.
Is Alan Paul.
She's Alan.
Getting so much trouble.
And he's sound like 7 feet tall.
Like he'll beat me so well.
I think I'm going to hang back on this one.
Oh, oh, man.
He's such real stuff.
I will give you a little advice.
Oh, wow.
Thank you.
Oh, man.
Hey, Adam.
It's Jousel.
I've been thinking about it.
And I realized that you had to see those things because of your wife.
So, I forgive you.
And I was also thinking that since you're going to be back in San Francisco next week,
I'm going to try to put some money together and come up and see you again.
Or you know it'll be really cool.
Is this you could hop in your plane and come down to San Diego and pick me up.
That would be very, very cool.
So let me know what you want to do it.
Talk to you later.
Fight.
Okay.
I guess everything's still up up in the air with Jousel.
This is the weirdest thing I've ever witnessed.
Is this girl from San Diego?
I don't know, Jousel.
I think we should just stop because this can only end in tears or something really, really bad.
And hanging out with you in San Francisco.
Let me just check here.
Hold on a second.
It's.
Nope.
It's not on the checklist.
Yeah, I don't encourage such it.
This is James from the UK.
I am.
It's.
Let's all listen as enjoy this lovely voice mayor.
The one who listens to his podcasts at one third in the morning while walking his dogs.
Yes.
I do.
Thank you.
I am drunk.
Then it's Christmas.
Is a one cat.
It's too good by it.
I have to say there's a very high proportion of drunk calls coming from the UK versus the US.
Yanks are really, really lagging behind.
No one calls when they're when they're stoned though.
I always look forward to those calls and I get the drunk calls.
Yeah, you should call Chris Moiles man.
Get on the air.
Get on the, get on the Chris Moiles show and.
And then and then plug the daily source code.
Do something like that when you're drunk.
I'll be very cool.
Hey, Adam, it's Sam here in the UK.
I just got our drink and.
Tell me about this crazy thing.
It's just been going on in the UK just recently in London.
And on the 28th of November, Liverpool Street Station in London.
It was the last mobile clubbing event.
And just the later people turned up on the train station.
It started dancing a specific time.
And it's happening again tomorrow on the on the 30th of November.
And the instructions are as arrive at panning station.
Good time.
Walk around and get into your groove.
Spread out throughout the whole station.
No dancing before night or seven 18.
At the instant the clock strikes seven 18.
Dance like you've never danced before.
Try not to dance in one place and always leave without a trace.
No letter please.
If you don't dance as long as the need takes you.
And I thought that was actually fantastic.
So I'm going to be turning out for panning station and seeing what the hell guys on.
And I suggest you do it too.
Oh, that's it.
All right, dude.
Folders.
Of course.
All the folders doing all the wacky things.
Make sure you shoot some video.
A bomb man because that would have been perfect.
Because at Liverpool Street Station is the station.
I get off.
I get out of the tube to go to our shortage office.
It's about a seven minute walk from there.
I could have witnessed that.
Of course, I didn't go into the city yesterday.
I was supposed to be on a panel of digital Hollywood London.
And obviously more.
And I've ever heard one.
But I was still running today.
It's okay.
I was still running that fever three days in a row.
I'm pretty convinced that it's it's related to jet lag and and the checklist.
But I just felt like such shit.
So I apologize.
Adam.
First to do it to Jezelle.
Stand her up.
Stand from Cisco.
Stay to it to me.
Put me up here in London.
Digital Hollywood.
It's looking forward to seeing you.
You were wrong.
Because it helped a rather bland presentation.
I need to have to shake it up here.
Take it easy.
There you have it.
Report from London.
A rather bland presentation.
I'm sorry, man.
Chris Jacob our head sales.
We'll be appearing on a panel on Friday.
I believe he's in town for just one day.
Guys, if I can animal.
Is it going all over the world?
Make it podcast or money.
Congratulations to Kelly Lewis.
Episode number 100 of geek brief TV is up.
Nice little compilation of.
It's it's really amazing.
The she opens up the show with a compilation of a whole bunch of different openers.
Basically geek brief one geek brief two geek brief number nine number nine number nine.
And it's like one of those.
You've probably seen these these videos.
A picture a day for a year.
It's like that.
And it's fascinating to watch how Kelly has.
In some ways matured.
In some ways gotten.
Really really sexy.
I think she lost a little bit of weight over the over the years as well.
I can't quite tell.
Anyway, she has a.
She's a t-shirt on today that.
It looks very good.
Or Kathy looking good everybody.
Those of you who follow the entire apple trademarking the word podcast.
Big blogger's for your vibe.
Yesterday.
Let me open up the email.
Okay.
This happened to.
What is this global geek the podcast network?
What's his name?
Hold on a second.
It's just loading.
Takes for a second here.
Great.
Yeah.
Is it great Davis?
Is that what I'm thinking?
Let me just see.
No.
Dave Gray?
Yeah.
Dave Gray.
There you go.
Dave Gray host of the global geek podcast.
Okay.
So apparently.
He sent one Australian dollar.
To Apple.
To use the term podcast.
Which I think is pretty funny.
And so he scanned in a reply that he got from the Apple trademark department.
Dear Mr. Gray, apple is in receipt of your letter.
Your date at October 3rd, 2006.
We are returning your check for one dollar.
Apple does not object to third party usage of the generic term podcast to accurately refer
to podcasting services.
Apple does not license the term podcast or in regards the Apple trademark department.
So everyone's like jumping up and down and saying, oh, this is great.
You know, it's confirmed.
You know, Apple is leaving the trademark alone.
I see exactly the opposite.
And in fact, I think we should shut up and not be so euphoric because what you.
This is setting a precedent right here.
Apple is setting a precedent by saying, we do not object to third party usage.
In other words, they're saying that they own the word podcast.
And because they said Apple does not license the term podcast in no way.
Does that mean that they don't claim to own a trademark or some.
Type of, you know, service mark or whatever on on the name podcast.
So basically, you know, we just became Apple's bitch.
I'm not happy about that.
I would reject it.
I would say you have no right to object or not to object.
What's that Steve Jobs pulling the tank up front?
I don't know, man.
I find that highly suspicious.
Presidents is very, very important in law.
So I'm not too happy about about what I saw there.
And I finally figured out what I want for Christmas.
The other day, I was saying that I really had no idea.
I have everything.
All I want is health and happiness.
Well, there is one other thing I have to say.
It is a flight simulator.
Actually, I thought, and I was looking at Google for flight simulators and you get all kinds of stuff.
And I downloaded a couple of the free ones.
And actually, when I bought a little joystick to see, you know, to test some of the demo versions of flight simulator 2004.
But I'm looking for something.
You know, and I love the open source ones, by the way, because a lot of cool shit does creep in because anyone could contribute to the source files and the data files.
When I'm talking about, you know, I want the hardware, man.
I want the real panel.
I want the enclosure.
I want the 3D view.
And I found out that these are not called flight simulators.
I know they're called FTDs.
That is Fox Trot Tango Delta flight training devices, which is a stupid name because it so easily can be confused with an STD.
And I found this company elite.
Oh, man, they make some fucking amazing, amazing flight simulators.
Complete enclosures, 3D views, real panels.
I can't wait.
I can't wait to install one of these.
After we move, after we're in the new cottage, and I have a third floor all to myself, let me tell you.
I'm going for it.
And these are like certified.
You know, you fly for five hours in these things.
And you can actually count it towards your, your instrument rate license.
I mean, it's like apparently the experience is so real that they are counted as real even on the,
on on the application and what they're, they're counting.
I'm losing it.
I'm totally fucking losing it.
We've got about it.
Humans in the parking lot, arteries covered blood clots.
Push you through the arms of the apartment stores.
Me on crosses in Christmas lights, credit card debts and brand new bikes.
The holidays are here in this year and more.
The rabbi reads from the test to me in the bank accounts.
Is it the easement, salvation, Santa, solicit for the poor?
Disception of democracy, the planaries of folk foreign policy.
The holidays aren't here in which they're at war.
Smoky skies and fixed elections.
And just distracts from all directions.
People with their backs against the floor.
Looking for someone to set us free.
A king with fists like Muhammad Ali.
The holidays aren't here.
And we're still at war.
The holidays aren't here in which they're at war.
Cris the fur, Columbus knew.
Let's go, they gotta imagine too.
The profits of oppression grow like never before.
I'll hail to the capitalist thief.
The moon get lost once and cover it off.
The holidays aren't here in which they're at war.
A king with fists like Muhammad Ali.
Jesus shares another tune into a sea of 2,000 years into the eve of a new year once more.
The season joy resolution sorrow toasts the hills and waves to my road the holidays are here in this game and war.
Religious wars and domination were all trading globalization the prices of patrol beyond control.
Those from churches are backwards to those known believers in you beginers the holidays are here and we're still in war.
Say a prayer for the last fault you need.
Prisoners and soldiers you never have met understand what it is they're fighting for.
Say a prayer for your enemies say a prayer for the victims and the families the holidays are here and we're still in war.
You know you take that record you take a Leonard Cohen CD and draw a nice warm hot bath and throw in the toaster and you've got the perfect holidays.
Everybody that's it for the daily source code today tomorrow will be all food bar fucked up beyond the repair for our food bar Friday hope you join me then.
Thanks a daily source code calm email at podshow.com. Bye bye.
Another podshow podcast stick it in your ear.
Okay, I don't know who this is but stop fucking calling to tell you at home.
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT podshow media network powered by podshow and limelight network control your part in the show.
And be the podshow.com.