This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charley, 399er and Iner.
With $16 million worth of airplane straps to my ass.
Transmeters?
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need noss.
Thinking transmere?
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Podcasting is an Adam Curry.
And so I've had a way that I only want the stars to give.
And she goes high, baby, cold.
And I want the wife, baby, here.
And some girls are on the face, and I know just how to be here.
And so I've found my days that I only got more cold here.
And I'm thinking to be so much more than I hold on me.
Ready?
How much more can you take?
Let's go!
And so I've got my way that I only want the stars to give.
And she goes high, baby, cold.
And I want the wife, baby, here.
I think in today, it's so much more than I hold on me.
The way how much more can you take?
The way I much more can you take?
I think in today, it's so much more than I hold on me.
Ready?
How much more can you take?
Let's go!
And I think in today, it's so much more than I hold on me.
The way I much more can you take?
I think in today, it's so much more than I hold on me.
I've got to get on something like cowbell action.
The cowbell song brought to you by years of static kicking off another week of the daily
source code.
Hi, everybody.
Adam Curry coming to you from the Curry Cottage in the affluent suburb of Surrey
known as Guilford Beautiful Day today.
Start off a little bit hazy, but of course, can't complain because we had an even more
beautiful weekend, which I'll tell you all about.
It was jam-packed somewhat hectic at times and involved a lot of travel and lodging stuff.
Always something interesting happened, I'll tell you about that.
By the way, thanks to Yifthach Levy, who said, I don't hope this message finds you well,
we're searching for music to add to the first episode of my own show today.
I came across the cowbell song by years of static, which I think you'll love.
It seems like Yifthach is getting ready for his own podcast, which will be located
at HowDueJew.com.
I think I've talked about Yifthach before, or maybe he sent an audio comment or something,
but I recognize it.
Oh, man, I've got a whole new set up, so I'm a little bit distracted, a little discombobulated
if you will, because when you've got your studio and your set up or studio, we've got
all your gear set up and everything is just so, and then you change stuff and you have
different boxes and different devices, it gets a little harrowing at times.
I'm not going to tell you exactly what happened.
I just want to stay with a wheel, of course, but now, right now, I just want to stay with
the cowbell vibe, because it seems like people are back on a cowbell trip.
I wonder if my cowbelling has anything to do with it.
Tom Morris sent a track that he thought I might want to add to my cowbell predilection.
Yes, what?
What?
I got a fever.
Yeah.
It's, uh, what is it called?
It's, uh, who does this thing?
I'll put a link to it in the show notes.
It wasn't exactly the kind of track that I would go for, but it had, of course, the required
cowbell voice drops in there, so, very cool.
Thank you very much, dude.
Before the weekend, we kicked off, uh, really here in the, in the cottage, we kicked off all
of the festivities, if you will.
With, uh, Christina's very first podcast, pod save the queen.
And, uh, I have to say, it was phenomenal.
It was absolutely, I was blown away.
Not just so you have a little bit of, of history as to how this came about.
I've been asking Christina and people, you know, listeners to the Charlie been listening,
Christina, I haven't asking Christina if she would ever start her podcast, which she alluded to.
Now, she's, um, 15 going on 16, and this is the, uh, the year I think around October.
So, actually, when she's 16, there you go.
She can actually start doing part-time work, and very typical for, um,
15 to 16 year old girls here in Guilford is, to go work at, uh, the barber shop or the
hair salon, Tony and guy, uh, or maybe work at top shop or just anywhere you can
get a Saturday in part-time gig.
And, uh, so I, you know, kept here in Christina,
talk about her friends who were where they were working.
I said, you know, there is a real opportunity for you if you want to make some money, uh,
by doing a podcast because I'm pretty sure that it would be, it would work.
It would be popular, it would be successful.
And, uh, somehow the, the quarter finally dropped and she said, okay, I'll do it.
And she said that, uh, was it Friday when Patricia and I were doing the show.
And she came up and she was ready right after we were done.
She had her MP3 files, which she'd emailed to me.
She had all kinds of notes, which were bullet points, because I did kind of
cheat a little peek there, but it was all bullet points.
And, um, and, you know, I just hit record and off she went.
And I could, and a lot of people actually emailed and say or left comments and said that,
um, I was, my presence was too prevalent, but I couldn't help it.
I was just sitting, I was, I, I, my mic was not on.
She had the mic that Patricia normally uses.
I just couldn't help laughing.
I was funny.
And I was just blown away by how he, how, how easily she slipped right into it.
It was fantastic.
So podsavethequeen.com is where we can find Christina's podcast.
And I guess she'll be doing one, um, once a week, you know, to kind of ease
into it.
Although she was already talking about, well, maybe I could do a different show with
this person.
Why don't we just take it slowly and she's already in contact with the,
with her listeners, with her audience and helping her on the website and getting everything
set up podsavethequeen.com.
You know what?
I'm a proud popper.
I got to tell you it very proud.
So then Saturday, um, had a trip planned to go see my mom.
As you know, I think, you know, she's in the hospital.
She's been there for two weeks.
Um, and the main reason was, she, her, her general condition,
a, a interior, a deteriorated significantly.
So they need to do a couple things.
And the main thing is pain management.
And you just can't do that, you know, with a visit to the doctor and then coming back
two or three days later and saying, well, this work, this didn't work.
It really has to happen under supervision.
And so she's got a team of great doctors, um, who are on the pain management team,
led by this one guy, uh, who, uh, my mom calls a Pablo Escobar.
I call him the candy man.
And, uh, they're doing it.
They, they figured out the right mix of, gosh, I don't know what the hell it is.
I mean, variance and pretness on and caution is what.
Uh, but it's working because I saw her on Saturday and she looked phenomenal.
She's ready to leave the hospital now.
Um, of course, now she's in this, in this very interesting fight because, you know,
they have, uh, detected more cancer that has to be, uh, that has to be
new, essentially.
But since she just, you know, her most recent radio therapy was, was pretty recent.
Uh, they just have to wait.
You know, otherwise you fry someone up if you just keep, keep blasting him with radio therapy.
So the only way that clears up, of course, is through a natural process.
And if your general health is, is good, then it, of course, the healing goes much faster.
So she's in this very interesting race where, you know, she feels much better every day,
yet she knows that, you know, on the inside, uh, there's deterioration, deterioration.
Uh, the shit is eating her up.
Just put it that way.
Um, but to man, she was in great spirits, um, eating like a dock worker.
We even sat outside on, uh, on the hospital balcony.
And yeah, it was just good.
Of course, the visiting hours are much later than normal.
So I booked the, the Rotterdam Airport hotel.
There's one.
Only, it's not a very big airport, but it's an international airport.
Uh, for, um, I think they could take, uh, the, I think the 737 is the biggest,
uh, aircraft aircraft they can take.
So we left, uh, the Delta Sheriff there overnight had a great flight, by the way.
It was, uh, man, even though, because the weather, when it's warm, you get a lot more
thermals, and you get a lot more turbulence when you're, uh, see below, below three and a half
thousand feet.
It was pretty bumpy, but then we went up over the channel, flight level 555, five and a half
And it was like the, like the plane was on rails, man.
It was just smooth, gliding, and the weather was beautiful.
So that was really nice.
Um, now I, uh, so I, I booked the hotel.
I booked the hotel for myself and for a captain Dan, who, of course, still flies within
the all the time, as my safety pilot.
Um, because otherwise, you know, we would've had to come back after hours.
It could've gotten dark, you know, you know, it's just, what differences
to make?
I figured we just leave Sunday morning.
So of course, Saturday night, we had the grand opening of the pod show palace
and the casino in, uh, second life.
And now as you know, my Mac fried, my power book, which was my primary
machine, which I had really run everything off of.
So the only other machine I had that, uh, that I could take with me was the, uh,
to sheep, a portage a laptop.
Excuse me, since I'm, which runs, uh, cast blaster, which I use all the time,
basically just for production purposes for the show for you running cast blaster.
So I loaded the second life on to it.
Interestingly enough, and if you don't know what second life is, go to secondlife.com.
But if you listen to this show, if you're listening from more than four episodes, you do.
It's, uh, I guess it's a game.
It's a virtual world.
It's, uh, it's a place to go.
It's a place to do things.
And basically hook up with people.
That was the whole point of the pod show palace, uh, and the grand opening.
So I have to say that second life runs a hell of a lot faster.
The, the resin and just everything works seemingly much faster, which is pretty,
pretty interesting to me.
Now this hotel, which is a golden tulip, the Rotterdam Airport hotel.
Um, it's small, you know, it has, I think, 90 rooms.
In fact, before it was a hotel that was used as a, uh,
asylum-seeker detention place.
So it kind of has a whole bunch of smaller rooms.
Um, and what they, even though the rooms are fine, you know, it's, uh,
it's, it's perfect business hotel.
They don't have Wi-Fi in the rooms.
In fact, there was no connectivity in the rooms.
But in the bar and in the lobby, there's Wi-Fi, which is that Swisscom crap that,
oh, man, which cost you like 18 bucks for an hour or something,
totally ridiculous.
But so no problem.
I figured I'd go downstairs.
The lobby's really is quite nice, and I kind of sat in the corner,
so I had power for the, for the laptop, and, you know, I hopped on.
And, and now, uh, earlier, because we had, we had dinner in the hotel.
We noticed that a whole bunch of people were going upstairs,
and it sounded like a wedding or some other kind of party was going on.
And so now around, I don't know, one, thirty, one, forty, five.
You know, I'm popping back and forth, talking to people.
I've got my virtual Tuxedo on in second life for the opening, and, you know,
there's just all kinds of stuff going on.
So I'm pretty much focused on the screen, but of certain,
I can, I can feel, I can sense that people are, like,
near me in my vicinity, if you will, like, had a, a radar,
and I can, you know, kind of sense that, and I think they're looking at me.
Now, remember, Patricia and I are pretty well known in the Netherlands.
So even though I had my head down, it was kind of buried in my work,
I could tell that people were recognizing me, and, you know,
then, then, of course, they'll start to make comments.
And I even said, hey, you know, I'm, I'm just working here,
you know, trying to give them the hint that I was actually doing something
that was productive, and I didn't really want to be disturbed.
It didn't matter, because the people who were there had come from this,
what I thought was a wedding party upstairs.
It was a 55 plus singles night.
So you can only imagine that around 130, quarter to two,
everyone was pretty tanked up and horny, and it was quite frightening.
Let me tell you, because as a whole bunch of old horny guys,
and I'll just say that they were well over 55.
And then there was, you know, some spring chickens probably around 55.
And they saw me, and they were like, very interested in me,
and it got, I actually almost had to run for my life.
And it was like 100 of them.
And, you know, as soon as I could, and, you know, they want to take pictures
and rub my ass and whatever, and I ran back to my room,
and I figured, you know, I'll wait for a little while.
And I checked it, like, at 2.15, 2.30,
and was still jam packed down there, so I like screw it.
And then the next day, we had to fly back,
so, you know, off to the jet center, where the lovely Delta Sheriff was standing,
waiting in the flew back, and there was an air show,
big and hill, so it was just a very,
a tiring weekend, let's just put it that way.
But it was fun, and it was great to see that my mom was doing so well.
So, at all, be able to visit her,
want to visit her Saturday, and then I think Tuesday,
it's off to San Francisco again,
this time probably for two weeks.
So, due to the crash of the power book, and yeah,
I'm going to take it back, or send it back.
I haven't decided if I'm going to send it, I think goes to Ireland,
or I'll just take it back to the store in San Francisco.
I, of course, I had my outline, my omni outline,
where the whole bunch of voicemail feedback,
and promo is all kinds of stuff.
And so, it's still on the machine, it's on the drive,
I just can't get to it.
And so, if you want to hook me up,
and give me some more good feedback,
or repeat whatever you sent in over the past week.
Voice mail numbers for the US in New Jersey,
201-625-635-7, or in,
or our number in London,
with someone correctly pointed out,
do you only want people from London now,
is for anyone to call, of course,
I'm just giving you a choice of numbers.
O2O-7-6A-1375-3.
Hi, Adam, Kelly Muller.
I just like to thank you for playing my song
on your great pod show.
It means an awful lot to me.
Thank you.
It's an honor.
Thank you, bye.
That was, it was Kelly Muller,
that was a demo song.
Was it, would we play that?
Did I play that?
Shoot, let me, let me just see.
I wasn't expecting that one to pop up,
actually.
Hold on, let me just see,
when did I play her?
I think that was actually,
it was something that was listed as a demo.
See, I'm now in the pod safe music network,
and it makes it real easy to go find it.
Kelly Muller there it is.
You're a word.
Let me just remind ourselves
what that song was like,
since she was so nice to call in.
Yeah, she's from the UK, right, right, right, right, right,
or was it.
It was,
it's not me now.
More than a dream,
crap.
Sorry, bear with me, let me see if I can,
okay, at least the computer's working.
Your words, that's what it was, okay,
I'm looking at my playlist now
on the pod safe music network,
here we go.
So I guess we can just play this straight from the page, right?
Here we go.
Let's just see what that was again.
Is it working?
Anything?
Any sounds?
Yeah.
Oh, that's right.
Oh, man.
Yeah, that was the drip drip drop drip drip song.
Awesome.
Very cool.
Okay, I guess I should tell you why it sounds
a little disjointed today.
So I've made a decision.
First of all,
thank you all so much for trying to help out
with the power book.
I have no idea what it is.
You know, people have given me the power
management unit reset sequence.
I actually tried to boot from the CD
or the DVD I think it is.
That's always a good one
because if you put it in
the CD, it will try and boot up from.
But now of course the keyboard doesn't seem to be working.
So it's not recognizing the DVD to boot up from the drive
and the only way to have it eject upon startup
is hold down the mouse button, which of course
also isn't working.
So now it's, I'm even further from where I was when I started
and it's not booting up at all.
And you know, and I have to work.
I just need to, I need to get my stuff moving.
And some theories about why this has happened.
It's my third fried power book in any year.
Wants me left something on the on the curry.com message
boards.
Maybe it's the voltage in the UK,
which apparently is significantly higher than the
listed 220 to 230 volts.
I don't know.
It doesn't sound right to me.
I think it's going through the transformer
and the transformer's outputting.
Not AC, but a DC power supply.
So I don't, I don't think that that's it.
But it was getting really, really hot.
Particularly when I was using second life.
And so, you know, I fell asleep with the,
when it was still working.
Right after we got back from San Francisco
and I woke up and it was frying.
It was roasting my nuts.
Michael Musiel says,
what we often do to save the old jewels
is to use an old bean bag.
Was it bean bag backed lap desk?
The flat surface of the lap desk
was ideal to set the lap top on.
It allows air to get under the lap top
and let the fans do their thing.
Yeah, it's really because the fan can't blow it away.
Hmm, I like this other thing though.
That was sent to me.
Emanroke, the chill pack.
It's very, it's an ice pack.
You put underneath your, your power book or your i-box.
I don't know, your i-book or your MacBook, I guess.
Only 20 bucks.
What do you have to lose?
I'll put a link up on the show notes.
Chill pack with a K.
So I made a decision as I was reading all this
and I'm like, I don't, you know,
I'm so tired of beta testing for Apple.
I've been doing this for years.
Since the, since, well, the first Mac to,
that I was given, which was a Mac to X,
which Apple loaned me back when they did that.
That one actually held in for quite a long time,
but I had to give it back to them.
I believe it or not.
You know, way after after,
it was obsolete practically.
You know, I had the power book audio failure.
And I have to say, you know, when did I get this,
it was the last of the mohicans,
the last Motorola based processor,
which is a 167 gigahertz G4 power book.
I was, I hadn't really mentioned it,
but I was already quite disappointed
with a couple of pieces of the hardware itself.
Now, first of all, I already discussed about the sound,
which was fixed with software,
but I presume it was some,
some different hardware that had to be fixed with the software hack.
The keys are popping off, you know,
and the same, I think we had this thing for two and a half months.
So, you know, and already though there's the Mac book,
the Mac book pro, and I'm like, I don't get it.
You know, you buy a new machine,
and there's a new one right,
that's announced the next day, it seems,
and I've just got to start to wonder about the quality of the hardware.
I've had drives fail.
I hear people with optical cable failure.
Now, my keyboard and mouse won't work
at the internal or even through USB.
I'm starting to want to give up.
And so, I did what I usually do in these cases.
Okay, I'm going to migrate to some temporary machine,
so I can at least work.
And you know, I look around,
like I've got one power book with a fried drive
and a fried screen.
You know, I've got one power book with a fried drive,
running off of a fire wire drive,
and I've got the most latest power book,
which won't boot up and is fried as I just described.
And then I had the Toshiba.
So I say, you know what, I'll just use the Toshiba for now.
And I discovered that I didn't really have that much to migrate.
The most important migration is really just making sure
that Firefox is installed because my email runs through Gmail.
I use Google's calendar,
which synchronizes perfectly to the blackberry.
Although I just have it sent SMS, you know, a text alerts.
When it's time for a meeting, I would have you for reminders.
Pictures, all I had to do is install a flicker uploader
because I don't store pictures locally anymore.
I hunted around for some simple audio editing stuff.
You know, multi track audio editing found mixed craft,
which seems like it'll work perfectly, you know,
for if I need to do,
I don't really do a lot of multi track editing,
but if I need to, it's there.
A converter to MP3,
you know, for WAV or AFF to MP3 file conversion,
blaze, media pro or whatever.
You know, just things that will cost me,
you know, if I like them, you know,
wind up paying 29 or 30 bucks for each of these small applications.
But all of my data really lives somewhere else.
And that really made me think about,
you know, what is, what are we really talking about here?
What do I really need?
Now, of course, besides the outlines for,
for the, for my show prep, which arguably,
I'm sure I could store those online as well,
although I do like kind of having the speed of,
of those types of files local,
crap.
Hey, if you're listening to us on a serious stars on 102,
then you want to hear the rest of my fabulous migration story,
you'll have to go to dailysourcecode.com
to download this podcast.
And, well, while you're probably driving,
you've got geese radio coming up,
don and drew Gilmore daily,
DVD weekly.
It's great show, by the way,
DVD weekly, that'll be on at 930 Eastern,
and then a 9 o'clock Eastern, then CC Chapman at 930.
And Mark Yoshimode, an M-Coff,
and the Pacific Coast health players,
are next here on serious,
or there with you on serious,
with Pacific Coast,
Hellway, I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Okay, so if you're still here,
and you're still interested in this migration story,
I really learned some incredible things.
First of all, I, after, you know,
playing around a little bit with,
and this is a small lap.
It's very, so I'd weigh,
I don't know, two pounds,
it's weighs nothing, which is nice,
and has an enormous four,
five-hour battery life,
also quite nice,
depending on what you're doing, of course.
I was surprised at things like the scroll speed,
much faster at scrolling windows.
I also, of course, it's partly the screen,
and this is what Apple really does.
Apple makes really beautiful looking products,
and puts a lot of quality pieces into it,
like their displays,
their track pads,
all of that stuff,
and so they,
it's almost like they,
they finally got the operating system right,
but, you know,
now they're kind of letting the hardware slip a little bit,
and I guess when I'm realizing now that I'm,
I'm using the wind tail combination of windows,
which, I mean, let's face it,
there's not really that much difference.
You know, you just have to kind of get,
even most of the key commands are the same now.
You know, control W to close a window,
there's no control quit,
so you do like all F4 or something.
I can get used to that,
and not have been using it for a day and a half.
I'm kind of, you know,
already, you know,
I love doing this stuff.
It's almost like driving on the left hand side of the road
here in the UK,
and the right hand side of the car,
it's great for your brain,
you know, it's,
it makes new neural connections,
and synapses are firing all over the place.
Yeah, even if you just take a different route to work one day,
that's good,
that's actually food for your brain.
So I did, I thought,
you know,
maybe you don't make me a little bit smarter.
I'll have more to dumb down with this blifig.
I'm liking it.
I guess that's what I, what I want to say.
Now, of course,
doing the show,
I always have,
as I said,
cast blaster running on the laptop,
and then I have all my show information,
on the power book,
which I put on a higher shelf level at the podcast complex.
I'm,
and if you do the show,
you don't even know what that is.
I'll put a link into the picture of the podcast complex.
The station.
So after I dropped Christina off this morning's school,
I went out,
and I bought a,
what is this,
an LG monitor?
So it's a,
19 inch,
flat screen LCD,
no speakers,
no audio.
So it's,
it's a very,
you know,
nicely compact unit.
Only two wires coming out the back,
no audio cables or anything.
It's just,
just it here to provide a beautiful display.
And I bought a,
it was a logic tech,
wireless keyboard,
wireless mouse.
So that,
you know,
I would have a full-size keyboard to use,
because the,
the portage,
keyboard is,
is really quite tiny.
So I hooked it up,
you know,
the extended desktop feature,
which works just like my Mac.
You kind of,
you know,
I had to hunt around for it,
of course to find it.
And that is really the thing is,
you can really do everything you want,
and,
and create the same type of user experience,
that you would find on a,
on a Mac with a Windows,
you know,
generic hardware combination.
It's just how they design it,
you know,
all the,
all the API hooks are there.
It's just,
you know,
all mapped out,
and it's not consistently moved from one machine to the other.
But I think I might be able to customize this to actually create the,
you know,
the experience that I want,
and I might even stick with it.
I don't know.
I'm feeling pretty weird about this.
So I'm going to give it a shot.
Here's what I'll do.
I'm going to give this a shot,
at least until,
I can get the Mac,
and I'll take the,
the Mac back to the store on San Francisco and let them deal with it.
I'm just going to live on Windows for a little while.
And hopefully it won't frustrate me too much,
and you'll be along for the ride.
Hi Adam.
This is Franco from Raka Sitalia,
and from the Land of Great Motivations,
I can give you some cultural contribution to the Charlie.
I really don't know which credit card you want,
but I assure you,
standard credit card dimensions are not in golden rate.
Standard credit cards are off.
Yeah,
and I've got to set this up.
So this was about the conversation I had with the Charles Flasher,
and it was about the Golden Ratio,
about the aspect ratio that is used in art and architecture and design,
and I was pretty sure that credit cards were based on the Golden Ratio,
but apparently, according to Franco, they're not.
It's default by 86 centimeters,
and the ratio is 1.5925 and on and on,
and the Golden Ratio is 1.6180.
They do, maybe it's because I got one of those American Express black cards.
They have a different ratio.
An infinite sequence of numbers.
It's an irrational number, you know.
And it's been considered a very, very strange number,
a Marvelous number,
because it occurs many, many times in mathematics, in nature,
and it's been used in art, in paintings, in architecture too.
If you want the easiest way to get to the Golden Ratio,
you've got to take two measures,
if the ratio between the smallest and the largest,
is the same between the largest and the sum of the two,
you've got two dimensions in golden ratio.
This looks easy,
then you can take the sequence of Fibonacci,
Italian mathematician,
Fibonacci, a lot of time thinking about numbers.
I'll definitely put in a link to Fibonacci,
run semi-link after hearing about the Golden Ratio on an earlier show.
It's fascinating stuff.
You've got to kind of get through all the scary formulas,
but when you're there, it's fascinating.
He made the Fibonacci sequencing,
which every number is the sum of the previous two,
so you start with zero and one,
and then you have one and two and three and five and eight,
13, 21, 34, 55 and on and on.
Each number, the sum of the previous two.
Well, if you take any number of these sequence
and divide it by the previous one,
you've got always the same number.
That's the golden ratio again.
And you've got this in nature too,
you take the nautilus,
which is a creature of the sea,
it's some kind of spiral shell.
You take each arm of the spiral shell,
you divide the width of each spiral arm,
with the previous arm,
you've got the golden ratio.
So it occurs a lot of time,
and it's used a lot in symbology too,
from the mesons with the pentagon,
and you can find a lot of strange, incredible information
about this on any encyclopedia.
You can find it on Wikipedia too,
but you know you are a little allergic to Wikipedia,
so yeah.
Okay, I hope this is useful to sum of our listeners,
and wish you a great weekend.
Bye Adam.
My listeners from Italy.
Ciao, Ciao.
Pronto.
Franco.
Thank you very much.
You know Patricia keeps bugging me man.
She says, dude, when we take it a little bit easier
in a couple of years,
like that's gonna happen.
So I'd love a little apartment in Italy.
Well, I'm gonna have to get my man Franco on the case, baby.
Hey, this is Russell from the Raising Giants Podcast.
I just got done with a purchase of hosting at godaddy.com,
and with my purchase, I received a $1.99 and domain name.
And so, for the next year,
you are the recipient of all traffic heading to
curiecastle.com.
That's right, curiecastle.com was available,
and is now pointing at curie.com.
So hey, thanks for the great show Adam,
and talk to you soon.
Dude, thank you.
What I'll do is I'll set up a page.
That has one of those slurles to the,
so you can open up the castle directly in second life.
How's that sound?
One other thing that there's pretty cool,
although I'm waiting for the most recent entry,
so I can't plan for you today.
And there's a reason for that, too,
because we've got a team of pod show,
San Francisco's in London this week.
Is the EarthLink Ad Challenge,
where, you know, this is the, this is what you hear at the beginning of the podcast.
You think advertising sucks?
Well, we, and that's pod show,
and EarthLink are putting our money,
where our, well, your mouth is,
and we want you to make an endorsement,
or a commercial, or a jingle.
What does it just be creative?
It doesn't really matter.
It's whatever you think will be an interesting way
to advertise EarthLink services.
Go to Ad Challenge ADCH-A-N-G,
something or other.
Double L in there.
I'll put a link in the show notes.
AdChallenge.podshow.com for all the details.
And if, and if you're one of the winners,
then you will actually make real money
by this commercial going into rotation.
So it's an opportunity, all part of our,
quit your day job scheme,
and quite a scheme it is indeed.
Hey Adam, this is Stuart Story, a key Stuart Wolf
in second life.
Just have a couple of comments to say to you.
First one's about the fantastic piece of podcasting software,
called Cast Velastra.
Or to know about Cast Velastra is,
will there be a Cast Velastra light version?
If it is, then I'll gladly test it out for you
before it goes public.
Just engage in it,
and you know what I mean by Cast Velastra light.
I mean like a rundown version of it,
where, right now,
can basically use it for free.
And you don't have to pay for it
like the actual Cast Velastra.
Yeah, but Stuart, dude.
If you download Cast Velastra from Cast Velastra.com,
it does exactly that.
And you can use full function for as long as you like,
only it's time limited,
so you can't create an hour's long podcast,
but go ahead, man, you can test it out
and make as many podcasts you like.
So please, be my guest.
I don't know if you actually check it out or not,
but it's fully functional.
This would help me a bunch,
because I actually do a podcast,
but I am plugged it on your podcast,
but we'll do it at the end of this comment.
It will help a lot,
because we're trying to make the podcast absolutely free for me.
So it's not making any donation,
so we'll ask for a donation of the book.
Okay, alright.
So Stuart, go check it out at CastVastra.com.
And hopefully this afternoon,
I'm going to have a session with CastVastra Mike.
We're going to sit down and do a Skype call and catch up.
I wish I had more time to talk to developers more regularly.
We've got a lot of developers that I love talking to,
and it's a very creative process,
but mainly due to time zone issues and stuff like that,
and just when I'm over here, it's busy too.
And with Mike, I like to spend a couple hours of possible,
and we really should sit together as what we should do.
Because he's got all kinds of features in there.
All kinds of enhanced audio plus,
so you can bake in pictures.
Now, granted, that's only working in his receiver
at the time being called Wind Potter.
But the format is very easy,
and it will work with any MP3 as far as I understand.
So once we're over a couple of humps with our own player,
the dashboard, then we're definitely going to implement that.
And I haven't actually had an opportunity to get into it
to figure out exactly how it works,
but it's a typical CastVastra style doing stuff on the fly.
So I'll keep you up to speed on that.
Now, it's going to be a weird week.
Wednesday, there may not be a show,
because we've got our team in London this week.
As you know, we have a great partnership with British telecom,
and then we're talking about launching stuff really quickly.
So you're going to see Pod Show Plus,
the PDN launching in the United States,
and of course for the rest of the world,
but also specifically a version in the UK,
which will be, you know, we're building a UK directory.
There's no kind of all kinds of stuff that we're doing,
and we're meeting with,
we actually, we now have, I guess we call it a general manager
for Pod Show in UK,
fellow named Dan Winner.
And so I've met him a couple of times over the past few months,
and so it's just, it's going so incredibly fast.
And I know nothing, nothing about setting up business in the UK.
Other than that, I have to get different paperwork,
but that'll be a part of my mission on the next San Francisco trip.
So tomorrow night we're having dinner,
and then, you know, we have meetings,
Wednesday morning, meetings with advertising agencies,
and production people, people for the offices.
It's just, it's nuts.
And what's cool about it is, you know,
this is happening with real revenues.
You know, this is not a,
oh, let's take some investment money and go open up an office
in every European country.
No, this is, you know, like East Coast style that we're doing.
It's like, okay, you know, it makes business sense now.
And we see the revenues, we're going to open up an office.
So it'll be a pretty low key and pretty cheap for a while,
but I'm very excited about it.
So looking forward to that Friday,
I'm also going to go into the office.
So there's a chance that Wednesday will either be,
will not exist at all as a show,
or it may be very late.
So I'll keep you up the speed,
and just keep you up the speed and what's going on,
because this is darn cool.
Come extra.
Hiya, Adam Kerry.
Hiya.
And yes, fuck your blackberry very much because we're in the most mobile can push
he made, but it's almost as hot as Angelina Jolie.
No, no, no, no, no.
Windows Mobile is not as hot as Angelina Jolie.
And let me just say, come extra blogger.
Yeah, it's fine.
Windows is fine.
But usually these Windows things suck as telephones,
or they're too big, and the blackberry really has it.
Combined with Geneva and Eastern.
Anyway, do you know maybe such game called cheeky beggars?
Let's play it.
Adam.
Do you agree with Daddy?
And give me a counted pdf.
Please, it should go on top.
You invented podcasting.
You place the sun in the right position.
You are moving for the fear single-handedly in the right direction.
Without you, Adam Kerry.
Most podcasts would still be feeding pigs in bundoks.
There's the one you should get another prize.
I am sure that Queen of England should name you.
Sir, Adam Kerry.
Of course.
So be good Daddy.
Like go Daddy.com.
And give me please now account at pdf.
Please, please please please.
Yo.
And you're so transparent blogger.
Dude, you know, I don't know.
You want to, we can't surface the pages yet.
We're only talking, it's just moments away.
Okay?
I'll make sure that you're the first one in.
But I don't know, man, to have you as a beta test,
so that seems like a lot of work.
You know what I'm saying?
It could swamp the entire development team.
You know, since, you know,
well, not just since, since thinking about pod show UK,
but even since moving to the UK,
I've, you know, really been trying to listen to as many UK podcasts as possible.
Mainly just to, you know, to soak up culture, if you will.
And, uh, want to congratulate Richard Vobes.
I think today is his 500th show.
He's got me beat.
And he does, I think he does one a seven days a week or something like that.
And, uh, it's, uh, you should check it out.
Richard Vobes.com.
I'll put a link in the show notes.
Uh, I'm subscribed and therefore don't look at the URL anymore.
Um, but, uh, congratulations Richard.
Extremely cool to see, uh, you go in so strongly here in the UK.
And looking forward to maybe hooking up something with pod show.
Hey Adam, Paul Durham from Black Lab again.
You want to test them on you a little about whether or not pod casting works.
How's this?
Let the pod us fear and February with our single see the sun.
Although we did notice immediate spikes in web traffic, pod play and fan mail.
We had no way to gauge the dollars and sense of it all.
But now the numbers are in sales are up 60% on iTunes, 50% on Amazon with no other explanation
other than you guys and the amazing world you're making.
We used to be on Geffen Records.
But, you know, we spend more time talking to lawyers and suits than making music.
Now we're independent.
Spend our time talking to fans, making more money and rocking the daily source code.
Thanks Adam.
Do you?
Dude.
You can't just I can't tell you what that means to hear that.
That is so incredibly cool.
So this is the premiere of their new song, Black Labs.
Ecstasy.
Soon for sale on the pod safe music network.
Let your body you flow.
I do your instinct good and deep as the world just goes down.
Throw my clothes out in the street and be on the wall.
Yeah.
Don't lose I don't know.
Now your sister's on the gun.
One by one.
One, two, three, six.
One is on the gun.
And the sound is the one and the more so.
The feature on your gun.
I guess I should feel like it just stay.
But forgets love and you know what that means.
Yeah.
And someone wants you to sing.
Everybody's lonely.
Don't say anybody's happy.
Or isn't just the alcohol.
I don't know.
Love, love, love, love, love, love, love.
If you feel like starting.
I love, love, love, love, love, love.
I don't know.
Because everyone's ecstasy.
Underneath it all.
And everybody's lonely.
I don't know what that means.
But everybody's happy.
Or isn't just the alcohol.
I don't know.
Wow.
I like it.
Kind of shades of ultra-vox in there.
Yeah, and Windows.
Take care of everybody.
See you tomorrow.
Another pot-show pot-cast.
Stick it in your ear.
Yeah, this pot-cast.
And we're great ones like it on the High Performance Pot-cast delivery network from
Podshow and Line White networks.
I love it.