This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want to hear our content with that ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 3-7-3.
What's that up in this guy?
Play with your crown in the tailwind.
But you're really doing it.
It's no no no.
Look out!
It's the pissed off Adam Curry.
It's the cheese of Adam Curry.
It's the ticked off Adam Curry.
He's pissed off.
A $16 million worth of airplane scrapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Come on everybody now.
It ain't hard to do.
You gotta look somebody.
Come on everybody now.
It ain't hard to do.
You've got some love on it.
Not bad.
Yeah.
Come on everybody now.
It ain't hard to do.
You gotta love somebody.
Come on everybody now.
It ain't hard to do.
You gotta look.
You've got some love on it.
Not bad.
Come on everybody now.
Yeah.
You gotta love somebody.
Not somebody.
Yeah.
Not a love.
No man.
It's a love for you.
It's a normal man.
It's a not for you.
Yeah.
Everybody now.
No one on that.
You're handsin' the air with my like a just don't care.
Get mad at me.
It's fake.
You're gon' dare.
You gotta love somebody.
Get the love.
Oh.
You gotta love.
Yeah.
We never see the love.
Because they never get past her back because they're rolled and broke down.
I won't get over that.
These are a love!
You gotta catch the love!
Yeah.
We never see the love.
Lovely to see the love!
You never see the love!
You never even swim!
Yeah.
I never see the love!
You never see the love!
I look back.
I see the love!
I don't care.
You say where I said right here, right now
Now see
That's another another
That you got to know, wanna know
That's a boy, never see your girl
That you're saying it doesn't end the whole wide world
Take it on the moon, take it on the moon
Give it to the stars, send it to your house
Even if you're gone, give it to the other
Love them with it down, never mind it come on
Get around town and smell the love
Spread it out there, spread the love
Shake it like I don't care
Love them with it
The fabulously talented Jeff Smith
With the love everybody song
Which he made just for me and for
And for magic as well
Wow, before that Derek Kay Miller did the
I'm creepy, pissed off curry
Show opener there
How are you doing everybody?
It's Monday the start of a new week
Daily source code is on coming you from the curry cottage
In the affluence suburb of Gilford and Surrey in the United Kingdom
Wow
Oh man, I'm still not completely decompressed
From 372 from Friday's show
And what an amazing thing has happened here
I still haven't really had the time to completely collect my thoughts about this
So I'll do my best today
Of course, if you haven't already, if you did here
Charlie 372
Please go and listen to Richard Bluesteens
Response on yeast2.com
That's where Richard surfaces versus Madge on yeast radio
You definitely have to listen to that
I think most people who've been a part of the conversation
Have already done that
And right off the top, just let me say that
Richard and I are cool
This is what you can do with people that you respect
And people that you love and people that you
That you trust, you know, you can have this type of conversation
Usually it's not held out in the open in the school yard
Like the way we did it
But we're totally cool just want to put that up front
And in fact, we haven't really had a full-blown conversation
Yet we've only had some email back and forth
And that's mainly due to time differences
And just schedules and all that stuff
But we're okay, totally okay
But boy, I think we've both learned quite a bit
Not just about the topic at hand
But about
About ourselves, perhaps, about heart relationship
And really, I've learned a tremendous about
I've really learned a couple of things about this show
And about podcasting
What was the most beautiful thing for me
Watching on this, there was not one, there's a couple
Let's start off by saying
That having a conversation about bigotry and about words
And actually being able to use the words was the most liberating thing
I've ever done in front of a microphone
Or a camera in my life
And I've been a broadcaster for
More than half my life
I've been a podcaster for over two years
But to actually talk about, you know, gaze and lesbians and fags
And queers and queens and dikes
And blacks and niggers and spicks and Jews
And all this stuff and actually be able to say the words
And not have people freak out about the conversation
Containing the words was a beautiful, beautiful thing
And it's a true testament to what we're doing here in podcasting
And I received so many audio feedbacks and emails
It's just no way I could ever even get to all of it
And I really don't think I should actually
Because I want to put this episode behind us
But move forward the momentum that we've picked up on here
Now, not only was that fantastic
That we had, you know, this conversation
And boy, it was a real conversation
And I have email
Okay, so here's what excites me very much
Is that for the first time in really
I'd have to say since I've been podcasting at all
The listeners came out
The listeners came out and started emailing me
And they typically start off by saying
What a podcaster, I'm just a listener
And here's what I have to say about it
Some of them literally came out
I think at least three or four people who emailed me
Came out and said, you know, I'm gay or lesbian
Or, you know, I'm not completely out
Not everyone knows it and here's my feelings
About the whole conversation
Which was, I mean, gosh, when someone comes out to you
Whether it's in person or an email
That's a huge, huge thing
In fact, let me just read one email that I received
So I removed the name obviously
After listening to your show
Number 372, I felt that I had to write you
And share my opinions. First of all, I'm a lesbian
And I'm not fully out of the closet yet
My friends know, but that's pretty much it
Anyway, when I first started accepting that I was gay
I became very offended when I heard people say things
Like fruitcake, dike, faggot, et cetera
I stopped becoming offended when I realized that
Every person that says faggot or gay
Or what not, it's not a homophobic
It's not trying to be offensive
It's not trying to promote hate towards homosexuals
And most times, they're not even referring to homosexuals
And I don't think it was fair match to say things that you did
I really enjoyed the show because I think it's a wake-up call
To those who are so offended by name calling
And feel it the world owes them something
Arguing over semantics is not going to save
One homosexual from suicide
Creating a more tolerant world
That accepts people for who they are
Will
Thank you very much for this show
Well, thank you very much for that comment
I got a lot of comments like that
But the fact that listeners
We're now coming out of the quote woodwork
And speaking up really hit me
And as I started to evaluate
And I continuously evaluate
The daily source code
I continue
And the feedback that you give me
And of course, everyone has their own opinion
And some people like long shows
Some people like short shows, some people
Rather have five short shows
Some people would have it, rather have three longer shows
Some people want promo
Some people hate promo
But one thing is very sure
It's very certain for me is that
We're still really
Too much of a closed off
Excuse me, Sensei
Close off community
And it's not by design
It's not a fault in any way
But if I think about who's really sending me feedback
And who's participating in the source code
It is overwhelmingly other podcasters
So that to me means that something should change
Because now finally
And you know I love getting feedback
From people who are listeners
By the way, if you send me an email
Or if you get around to making audio comment
And I guess what I really should do
And that's part of the problem here
And we're just not ready yet with podshow
Plus in the pdn
But the minute that's out
It should be a heck of a lot easier for people
For listeners who maybe don't have the the means
The technological understanding etc
To just send feedback
Maybe you just have some widget
You know you just download that
And you click it and as long as you have a microphone
You click once to record and click again
And it sends it off or something like that
That would be probably very smart
And I think of it
I really want to tap into that more
Because that's where we're going to really get some growth
From in this stuff that we're doing
Is involving the listener more
And I really do believe now that the listeners who are out there
Are just listening and and
And maybe some of them will say yeah
You know I'd love to do a podcast in the future
And in fact we'll talk about that later
Yesterday I met a couple of folks who said exactly that
But to actually for the first time
Have listeners who have nothing to do with the
Development of podcasting
Nothing to do with the creative side of creating podcast
Was just very very exciting to me
Mark Yoshimoto Nemkov sent in a comment
Who was of course in a way also involved in
In this conversation
Mark from the Pacific Coast Hellway
And he probably had the best line
That I encountered and all this feedback
He says dude
I love the fact that you defended my name
And all uncut guys and nearly the same breath
Yeah
And you know
And I think I said that on Fridays
That I'm so envious often of
People like Mark who couldn't who can write a rant
And then deliver that
Because I'm pretty much sure he writes all his stuff
He's a fantastic writer and
And to be able to to write something
And deliver the rant and make it sound like
It's you know it's coming out at that moment
Is really
That's you got to have talent to do that
And by the way
Magic has obviously has that talent as well
I'm not very good at it
But what you heard Friday and this is something
That I also have to take into consideration
You heard the non-splift version of the curry
And now you know why Patricia suggested
Like 19 almost 20 years ago
When we were
We'd been together for about six months or so
She said you know you really should try smoking dope once in a while
And that'll stop your brain that'll slow you down a bit
And I hadn't done so
Since Thursday afternoon
All the way through Friday
Because I really wanted to have my head on straight
But what happens is is then all the stuff comes up
The stuff that is of course normally suppressed
By the holy herb
And so there's good news and bad news there
Good news is boy
I'll probably live a hell of a lot longer
If I continue my daily regimen
And a nice and calm and cool and collected on the other hand
The stuff that came out
And the way it came out
And as I was going through this show
Which I had really hadn't done any preparation
Other than just set up the audio stuff that I wanted to play
I could feel it
I felt like wow
I'm in this
The rant is working
It's trucking along
I felt like I was making some sense
But really
It's incredibly emotionally draining
So now what is it that
That caught everyone
And was it just the word that we're using
Was it just the conversation
Yes, I think that's a big part of it
Obviously and this is something we've known
We've been saying for a long time
You know as long as you podcast with passion
Well
I think that may be partially correct
It's not just the passion
It is when someone hears the true emotion
Coming out of another human being
That's when
People get switched on
That is
Part of what is so incredibly different
And I've been thinking about this all week
And even though it's been a very busy week
And then I haven't had a lot of downtime
Crunch and turnily and try and figure this out
But that is it
Now luckily
We don't only have one emotion
Anger of course is one that
I think that maybe we all
Well here's a good one for you
Is everyone's version of the emotion anger the same
I think it probably comes close
And this is
This is why guys like a Rush Limbaugh
I think as an example
It probably goes after the lowest hanging fruit
Of the emotional tree
By poking at people's emotions
And getting them all pissed off and angry
By being emotional and pissed off and angry
That's where you make a connection
As I said I think that's
Sometimes it can be fantastic
Anger can be really good
Anger is in many ways a beautiful emotion
But there's no way that I'll be able to make a show
As the pissed off Adam Curry
There's just no way
And even if I could do it
I'm not going to do it
It's very draining
And if quite frankly it's not all that fun
The release is fantastic
I mean that's like one huge intellectual orgasm
But you know it's
It's only once noile type of
Type of experience as you want to have
So what I want to try and do
It's figure out how to tap into all the emotions
And really make that connect
This is perhaps what I first heard
With Dawn and Drew
Before it became before it really was
The Dawn and Drew show
And this is not a bad thing at all
Because I'm going through the exact same
I'm going down the exact same path
As many many podcasts are doing
What was it that I loved about Dawn and Drew
In the beginning and still do by the way
Is the emotional connection
Two people had who have clearly been together
For a long time and you can hear it
And it's a beautiful thing
It's exactly the same
Oh wow experience
I had the first time I saw
The Osborns
The very first season of the Osborns
Which was a very low budget
Greg Johnson who I worked with for years
Produced that
Because he knew Ozzy or had some connection
There and it was really two cameras
And really just nothing
Thought out ahead of time
And it was really beautiful
Because what happened was everyone said
Oh my gosh
There's a guy who I had a
It was of course a big brain reset
I thought that he was this hardcore rocker
Biting the heads off of bats
And it turns out he's
Like Archie Bunker and he has a dysfunctional family
Like mine and they have arguments
And they have love and it's all very raw
And pure and it's not polished
And of course we've seen that with many
Reality programs
And that doesn't have a change
This thing start to get set up
And written
And I think that that was the
That's really what I'd like to tap into
Now of course we have multiple emotions
And I think
Some of that Donna drew stuff
Or any two people who
Who are in life together
When they have a conversation
It's just nice to hear when Patricia comes in
Everyone loves it
I have never heard anyone say that they don't like it
When Patricia comes on this show
Or when I'm talking to Christina
When we're doing dad daughter stuff
Or I think laughter
Of course is something an emotion that everyone can tap into
That's very very difficult
I'm not good at that at all
It either happens naturally or it doesn't
I'm not very good at setting up jokes and bits and
And fun stuff
And usually just me laughing at myself
Doing something stupid works
And then there's love
That's another
That's part of the
The duo
Host thing
Which you can really hear a
Love emotion
Something else that's played into a lot
Well in fact all the time by news media
Is your fear emotion
Because it's very easy
I mean that's what a
Usment park rides are based on fear
So I hope I'm sounding a little bit coherent here
But I'm really trying to hone in on
Figuring out
How I can tap into that more to make this show better
Because I want to reach more people
For me the success of the daily source code
Is in
More people who are participating
Actively
Whether that's through email or whether it's through
You know a voice mail
Or or just saying hey
I'm listening and you know it
It really makes it all worthwhile
And it really has me excited
Now that said
I got some very important emails
From people
Important because they really struck home
And I've mentioned this particular
Type of email to a couple other people
And the response is always the same
It's oh yeah
And I also must say that I forgot
Momentarily
That both match
But certainly Richard Blustine
Are still in a grieving period
For the loss of one
And boy
You know that can really
Reset your that can mess up your filters and your brain
The only people who can
Forgive someone who is grieving
And says or does certain things
Our friends and family
Because they understand that person
And of course I forgive Richard
Are you crazy? I love it
He's a great guy
And so that's just something I wanted to make sure that everyone just
Thought about for a second because that does put some of this into perspective
But you know it doesn't matter again
I do it all over again if we could because what happened
And the beauty of everyone
Jumping in
And very civilly I must say yeah
There was a little bit of there's always some
Signal to noise in in that type of conversation
But much lower noise than signal
And then I've seen in a long long time
So thank you all for participating
Thank you all for participating
Thank you all for being a part of it
And thank you all for just
Changing something in me
So I'm going to try and continue on it
I'm going to try and figure out what it is
And try to do a lot more of it
Are we are we just only now starting to understand the power of the internet
This oh wow
I think that maybe in five years
We will only just have reached the tipy top of this
Of this iceberg that is underneath the blue ocean of how powerful
I don't know if you can you can't really control it
But I've gotten pretty good identifying flow and seeing
When something catches on
And there's nothing you can once it catches
There's nothing you can do about it
You can only
You can just ride it out
If you happen to be on the wave
You can see it coming
There's not much you can do to turn it left to right
Now the question is how do you get stuff like that started
But I don't want it to be negative
Sometimes it can be negatives
It's clearly always based on people's emotions
And I think that we are
We've got the training wheels on friends
We are just
Just getting started in
Understanding
What this stuff is
And it's big it is so much bigger
And we don't know how to use it at all
That that's what this whole episode show me
We have no clue
You know you just you just lighten matches
And you're you're slamming stones together
And also fire
Look, in fact, maybe that is exactly what this is
We are the cavemen of
Gerati, you know we're just a
Fire, this is wonderful fire
And we haven't learned how to contain it
We're a long way off from nuclear
You know what I'm saying? We've got such a long way to go
So
I looked around for a song
It's going to run over the satellite
We know for those you're listening on
Serious starts 102
You'll get to PCH next and you won't hear the entire song
But I thought it was so appropriate
And I know that module totally understand
And this is really true at the end of the day
I do when I think I always will
Say I love fucking with you
Now that I bow to Chris
Go into dance
No point to blame
Destiny
Holding up to no better
Stand my ground in this degree
For all the difference it never makes
Now you watch me dig-y, my own gray, sailor fucking way
Sailor, sailor, sailor, sailor, sailor
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
11 when you just say it in the song, you know, just use the words and say it really really works for me and throughout all this
I've seen changes in many many people. Most prevalent
Most prevalent is
our friend
Comic strip
Now listen to this one by C.S.B.
Hello, Adam Carey made. We have 21st century nowadays and also we still don't have flying cars and
intelligent robots. We have global cyberspace calls these days the internet
People damage and attack other people in this global cyberspace to a very high extent
That they wouldn't do in person to person contacts
There are three things that are important to me in cyberspace contacts one good wheel to
reciprocate mutual two-sided respect and three open-ness
So one good wheel means that I don't want to harm other people over internet
Two respect means that I don't ridicule and I take seriously other people and their convictions and feelings
Three open-ness means that if somebody tells me that something what I wrote on the internet is a harming
or damaging him or her
Then I'm open and ready to take it down or remove it. I am the first ever paid advertiser in podcasting
I am fan of podcasting
Hi, let me just stop there for one second. C.S.B. and you know very few people know this or remember this
But that is absolutely true
comic strip blogger was
As far as I know the first person to advertise on a podcast
And he did it by buying time on the Donandru show before
For Donandru were a part of the pod show family and
And in the end he did pay you know and he was promoting MS mobiles
MS mobiles.com so I think was MS mobiles.com or or Microsoft mobile in general. I can't recall
But that is absolutely true and
Definitely deserves credit for that. However, I see that podcasting is troubled with the same problems that blocking is
People attack people without willingness to remove lies surrender from the servers
God gave us free wheel for a reason
God in this way washes his hands of responsibility for our evil deeds
But at the same time free wheel gives us ability to achieve great things or to do good deeds
The best kept secret of God is that the hell and heaven are in a reality here and now on earth
Boohoo
You've made my day with it. Boohoo
Boo yeah
CSB getting all intellectual love it. You're right comment your blogger sees it
He sees it we we still have our training wheels on and what we're doing now
In blogging and in podcasting is we're exercising our emotions
We're exercising our feelings we're exercising our free speech and I hope we can get past the training wheel stage pretty soon
Cause man, I'm ready to ride the bike for really, you know, I got to figure it out
I've got to figure out how to how to stay balanced and then this internet thing is going to be extremely powerful
Yes, we can shoot then we can read if we figure out how to use it how to harness
Our emotions and how to project those emotions take emotions from others
Mix them up into into something that everybody can identify with and share with and it not just be anger and it not just be fear
Then we truly can change the world. I'm convinced of it
So I'm going to work on it. I'm going to try and figure it out and that doesn't mean that I'm not going to get it stuff
Because that is you know, anger is a beautiful emotion just not all the time. It can be very tiring and we know how to get it out of me now
Don't we and it's not just a comment. It's it's the lack of spliffage in my case
Okay, so let's look at the week that was Friday
Over the weekend of course, I got up early Saturday morning to go fly and see my mom in
She lives in bullscope which is about so a 25 minute cab ride from the Rotterdam Jet Center
So I'd agreed with Captain Dan who now Captain Dan is also starting to loosen up a little bit
You know the first the flight we made. I was like, you know, anyone who's flown
You're you're you're really dependent upon each other and there's a lot of trust you throw into the cockpit right off the bat
Particularly with a much less experienced pilot as myself. I have to put a lot of my trust
Into someone who has the paperwork, but you really don't know the guy and
But you do start to build up camaraderie very quickly and Saturday
We had our big camaraderie moment which I
Actually debated for a while talking about this, but since I'm still here. I'm very happy to tell you
Everything was great the weather
Just fantastic on the on the UK side of the channel Rotterdam was not so nice at all
It was the ceiling was a thousand feet. They'd predicted 2000 feet, but it was a thousand so
Not the best weather at all to be to be flying in now
What we did is and what I'm doing with with Captain Dan is we do not use the GPS while we're flying
It's all instrument work. So we're really stacking up the radios now
This is for another podcast maybe a whole separate podcast not for the Charlie, but how you fly on instruments is
It's really quite interesting. You're doing it all based upon radio signals and
Directional beacons things called VORs and NDBs and
DMEs a distance measuring equipment, so you so you know how far you are from a certain beacon and you try and
You're late so you can figure out where you are and you do that with a map and
Of course these days we have the luxury of flying with with a GPS where it shows you
Have you don't have to figure out how far away you are from a certain beacon to be able to
Triangulate it to know if you're flying into someone's restricted airspace. No, it's right on the map
You see a little airplane moving towards the circle and you know what you're doing
But if you don't have a GPS or if your GPS malfunctions
Well, then you better know what you're doing in order to get out and also a part of
The night flying and the bad weather flying is all done on these instruments in coordination with air traffic control
But you really have to understand the concept of flying and and you've got to work ahead of the aircraft
You know we're doing 150 knots
Which is fast
Okay, it's really fast
Even though it's not entirely true just you can take a knot for a my it's a nautical miles actually so 150 is fast
And
You've got to work you know, so the between you know in ten miles at 150 miles now
It doesn't take you very long, you know, that's just that's just a matter of minutes and so you really have to have everything dialed up
And you're next next reporting point your next beacon you have to be able to tune into it
So it's really nice to be able to do that with two people particularly someone who's been doing it for a long time
Now we crossed over the channel and and I put that video up on
On the curry dot com so you can take a look at the just fantastic weather over the channel
It was blue skies you could see right down to the to the deck you could see the the ships going by now
If you look closely at that video you'll see
something a very bad habit of mine
Which was broken
Significantly
During this flight is I often
Just because I want less clutter on my lap. You know, I've got a clipboard and as pen and stuff and you know
You've got you there's a lot going on on the cockpit. I often will take my map fold it up and shove it on the on the dashboard
Kind of wedge it between the door frame the dashboard and and a little bit of the window
And this is this was not a good thing
Here's what happened as we're flying along and we were on frequency the Dutch military Dutch mill frequency
Which is what everyone kind of does on the weekend because in in the Netherlands there are very few airfields
There's people don't like people flying in Holland let me tell you
So the airfields that are there are usually military and they're closed on weekends
If you ever want to invade that country by the way the weekend is the time to go because everyone's off everyone's at home
So the airfields are not active and
You talk to Dutch mill and Dutch mill basically talks to the you know
They have radar and they're checking out everybody and and of course sometimes you can get very busy
Wasn't all that busy because of the weather and so we're flying somewhere between
Where are we at between Costa if you're a pilot it's a KO code COA which is a VOR
And HSD which is between Costa and Rotterdam so you know we we've got like another
Like another 20 minutes to run or so and Dutch mill calls me up and says okay
We have an unidentified aircraft flying at your
Altitude we were at that point it was still good weather
So we were about 20 300 feet
It says they're not on frequency
I do not know what their intentions are and they're coming at your 12 o'clock
That means straight on the nose and he was flying apparently to about 2000 feet
So
First thing you say is right I got you
We're on a sharp lookout and believe me you're then on a very sharp lookout and
I actually even said you know what I'm gonna I'm going to descend
What do we I think now he was it we're both at 2300 feet so I'm gonna say the 2000 feet just to give a little bit of margin there
Just just in case and any on there he was all of a sudden we saw him
He wasn't quite at 12 o'clock who is at 11 o'clock but he was coming our way and
He was at that point a little bit higher than we were now we were just under the under the cloud ceiling
Remember I told you it was around 2000 feet
So yeah, actually it was probably two that two and a half thousand feet at that point
But we're going north and so the ceiling is starting to drop
So we call that in we say hey, you know Dutch mill we're visual on him and at that point
The air traffic control marks it off as list. Okay, they can see him. It's done no problem
And remember he's on the on the 11 o'clock side so that's on and I'm left left seat of the airplane so
He was just off to the left
And
We're flying along and we're getting set up for rotted in because we knew the ceiling was gonna be much lower
We had to hit all the reporting points. It's a real airport, you know, it's not something we just kind of fly in join and land
And this is a other aircraft, which
It was a low wing it was a small low wing so I the pipe are probably it went up into the clouds
And while I'm dialing up the other frequency and this is just the matter of maybe 30 seconds
Maybe 45 seconds. Well, I'm dialing up the other frequency. Thank God Dan has eyes open
And he's this is kind of the agreement. You know you never are both looking at the same thing in the cockpit at the same time
Certainly not more than for just a few seconds because you're going so fast and shit happens so fast and all of a sudden
Dan says
Cricky he's turning and what it happened was this guy
Never saw us because there was no way for anyone to tell him that we were in his area and he came
Back down from the clouds. I guess that he got kind of freaked out or whatever you want to get out of the clouds
Also now he's down exactly at our level
He's so close and he's turning left right into us. I could almost read his registration and so you know
Simultaneously we're both like yanking to the right down with the nose and you know
I literally could see this guy's face
As he passed over us
And the reason why I didn't see him was because the map had obscured that part of my peripheral
Vision and that was really really stupid and I'm very happy that Captain Dan was there
But we both literally sat there for like 20 seconds just looking at each other going
Dude
That could have been a real day record
Of course Dan is like oh that could have given us a headache
Yeah, so you make light of it and you make jokes about it but
Between us there was a huge understanding that we had been very fortunate in
You know the past couple of minutes
And it was just a big big learning lesson for me tremendous and and I've broken the the stupid map habit
Let me tell you anyone who's a pilot will know exactly what I'm talking about and you might even do it yourself sometimes
So I'm very thankful
For having Captain Dan a long for the ride and you know once again have realized that
The book of aviation you just don't finish it. It's a it's a book about 15 feet high and every single time you go and fly
You learn something new
So that anyway, so we landed safely and everything was great
It was kind of it was still kind of tricky figuring out exactly where we are and just remember just using the instruments
Trying to find these reporting points and reporting points are usually a spot in the road or a gas station that you can see
But if you're not familiar with it if there's you know traffic in the area if you're doing all kinds of stuff
You're flying at instruments. It's hard to identify stuff
So you really got to stay focused and they're not you know they don't have beacons
You have to figure out okay, this reporting port a point is this far from this beacon
It's on this radio so it means that it's kind of over there and you can really do this quite well and and it worked out
You know it was great and we landed one off to see my mom
It was really cool because my sister was there Tiffany with her son Julius who's almost seven. I haven't seen him in
Boy I haven't seen him in almost half a year and my sister who recently
Separated from her husband recently about a year ago
She has a great new boyfriend who I know
Professionally from his writer and it was cool. Yeah, and Christina and Patricia had bought a wig from my mom and
She was so happy because you know going through all this cancer crash
That's really the bummer. You know it's just you you you you feel shitty on the inside
But all that carries over to the outside and she's lost a lot of weight and and of course
Because of the chemo and radiation. She's lost most of her hair and she was so happy. She was so happy to have
You know just to look her and it went and Patricia is really good at this. You know, she's she really understands
Hair and makeup as we've discussed many times and it was perfect. She was so happy and and you know
It was it was emotional. It really was but it was great and we hung out for for a couple hours and it was just fun
You know we didn't talk about
About cancer and treatments and crap. We just had fun and joked and laughed and my mom was really
Compared to last week. She was ten times as energetic of course a lot of that is due to
The pretneys on that that they're giving her right now because she has to strengthen up a bit in case
They need to do more treatments. She really they couldn't treat her now. They just they she has to have more strength
But she's been eating much more and and she's really really fighting it and I can see it, you know
And that's that's the most important thing and and I think this was probably the first visit
Where we didn't have to talk about all that crap no one felt like talking about it
Just you know talk about fun and going place isn't doing things and she's not giving up man
That's that's what was so beautiful about about the day and then went back
I'll tell you there's nothing cooler
For for for someone who's so nuts about aviation and just the whole concept of a flying car
And you know you're you're talking to all these people along the way and then you have pharaohs and
Sight as we're coming in I call up pharaohs on the radio
You know November 277 Delta Shara is is joining downwind and and then on the radio
Hi Adam welcome home
Wow, you know
No traffic in circuit come on in and park her at your hangar and that was
It was uh, it was nice
Uh
And I got some feedback about my flight as well. I think this is the one home
I Adam it's Mike from the 6620 West kid cast
Hey after listening to Charlie number 370
I also noticed that the air traffic controller sounded just like Roger Smalls
So I took that clip. I did a little audio clean up to it and now if you listen to it
I think it's conclusive here listen to this
Want to call up and yeah get us out
Transformation good morning November 277 Delta Shara request radio check and then taxi to a board for the
Aquarium
Roger
It's how the proper one
We're going for the
Oh and one other thing Adam last year
I sent you an audio comment in a phony Italian accent begging the pod father to let us into pod show
You told me that after the new year you would make me an offer I couldn't refuse
Well
Coupledy to the copy. I hope that offers still stands
I would love to be invited to pod show and just as an observation I think pod show could use more family oriented programming
You know we get lots of feedback from our listeners that thank us for doing a podcast that they can listen to with their kids in the room
We're proud to be a hundred percent clean and we're a hundred percent kid friendly
Our show isn't really intended for kids. It's more for adults who have kids and are looking for a
Kindred spirit to share experiences with if any of your listeners are looking for this type of a podcast
Where the 66-20 West kid cast at
W-w-w dot 66-20 West dot calm. I don't even get it. She's senior. Okay. Yeah, I'll make good on my promise. Don't you worry
I said after the new year, right and and I said after this new year and we're still after the new year
We're getting there very closely. The dev cast is rocking
Now it's gonna be pretty busy for the next couple days since we have Ron and KJ in in London and we're doing meetings
In fact, I got to get out of here ASAP
For our for our after new meetings in London
But yeah, we're getting there dev cast is for the developers who are getting gold and tickets and being brought in
Everyone's gonna get in who signs up for that if you're interested
You know you don't even have to if it's just interested in the development of it sign up at devcast.podshow.com and
Boy, you are so right. You know, I really do have a feeling that that may be Roger Smalls
Is indeed the air traffic controller at fair Oaks that would make a lot of sense wouldn't it
And yesterday
A hold on let me just do one more one more aviation thing because a lot of people had this question
Hey Adam Matthew evil here. I got a question about Wednesdays Charlie, you know the one that you kind of did from the ground and kind of did from midair
You know, I deal with spaceship parts up here on the UTF Revolution. I've got myself a
PMF drive got a bunch of droids spending machines that need repair that kind of stuff
But I don't have any mags up here. I have no idea what mags are you kept talking about
Mags what are mags? Are they something that keeps the plane from I don't know flipping over or
Transforming into a robot and I I don't know
Spark plugs those I understand mags not a clue
So yeah, could you fill me in on that and by the way if you're ever interested in
Flying in something that goes a little bit faster than mock two feel free to join us up here on the revolution
By visiting www dot high orbit podcast dot com will be glad to have you any time
Thanks no Matthew
End of transmission. Thank you. Yeah, a lot of people asked me that and I realized it wasn't too clear
Mags is short for mag needos and they are related to the spark plugs
It's kind of the same as an alternator in your car actually
Although we also have an alternator, but that's for different reasons, but just for the concept, okay
You have your battery and you use your battery really only for when your engine isn't running
But when your engine's running
Something's got to create the spark and the spark plugs and
In the aircraft we use mag needos which are gyroscopic devices
So they are continuously turning at high revolution and they produce the electricity that produces
I'm simplifying it, but they produce the electricity that produces the spark
So if you're mag needos and you have two of them for obvious reasons redundancy, but
Excuse me one is really for the for the left hand side and one is for the right hand side and I have six cylinders
so one of them is responsible for
Actually, I don't know if that's true if they're split up that way we have two of them and if and if one of them isn't working
You don't fly because if the mag needos stops working spark is no longer delivered to the spark plugs and you're going to have an engine
That's going to not run very well in fact. It could run horribly it could not give you enough power
to stay in the air. It could not give you enough power
To get you off the ground and of course the critical part is getting you off the ground because once you're in the air
If the engine quits well, that's a whole different story. You can glide down and find a spot to land
So
So that's what you're always checking for. You're making sure these things are okay before you take off
And so we were getting what we call a mag drop which means you know the the RPMs drop
Significantly when running just on one
Mag needo. Yeah, I guess so then that's split up then
And so that's why we went back and if you have a broken mag, you know, that's a real repair job
But the problem was is the spark plug. So one spark plug was it was getting the juice from the mag
But it wasn't sparking because it was just completely busted and so that's why the engine was running roughly
And it was only basically running on five cylinders instead of six so thanks a Matthew for questioning that and let me clear it up for you
Mag bar
Rare celebrity interview Cindy use it magpah.com
You won't want the engine in connection
Makes you a con. Makes you a con man. Hey, this is Jay Dolly coming up with the next mad pod
You remember Tommy chong from Cheechen chong
Sister Mary elephant coming up mad pod. Hey Tommy. Hello. I is Tommy there. Yeah, it's vegan
Tommy. It's shadow steel. How are you?
Hey, good. How are you? I'm good. So are you ready for our interview?
Yeah, I'm in the car, but yeah. Tommy is impossible to use marijuana too much
Yeah, yeah, yeah, absolutely. You can get too much of anything
You can do too much water, you know, it's called grounding if you use pot. You'll end up like Cheechen chong
Exactly
I mean look at Cheechen
Get media mad pod
mad pod.com
Jay Dolly kicking it again
We missed a chong. Yeah, excellent. You should listen to that. It's it's a great interview very cool to to hear him on on that show
Kind of a hero of mine. I have to say in a way. Remember we all used to go to the theater
Remember the up and smoke album
We've been talking about album covers. That was definitely one of my favorite double albums because you fold it open this double album cover and
Inside of it was a huge rolling paper and
Just about everybody. I knew bought this thing and our new year's Eve
You know, we we all would pool our money and we'd fill this filled this up with herb and smoke it and it was just
It was a Cheechen chong joint is what it was. Remember those days and of course they instructed you to clean out
your seeds while using the double album as well
But man, you know what I'd like to hear from from listeners and yeah podcasts are listeners too, but
What would you rather have would you rather have five
shorter shows during the week or would you be okay with three longer shows or do you want three long shows or we want more short shows
Let me know you know I don't know your habits your listening habits. There's no way from me to understand
just from the data that we have
What you're what you're into you know, do you use it on your commute?
Personally, I think that I mean it wouldn't make much difference in my listenership. I don't think
if I
Probably increase if I did three longer shows, but I may be wrong, you know
So what if the show was an hour and a half is that too long?
For me that's often a barrier when I look at the time
Of course, I don't have a commute, right, but I look at the time
On a podcast before I play and say, well man, it's quite a commitment. I'm gonna spend an hour and a half listening to this
But of course, you don't have to
You can you can turn it off and check in the next time, but give me some feedback on that
I'd really like to know what what you're thinking and at the same time I'd like to welcome
If I hadn't done that again, I thought I had but I'd like to welcome the Alaska Pod Show to the Pod Show family
Adam Curry this is Scott with the Alaska Pod Show. Hey, I want to thank you very much for inviting the Alaska
Pod Show into the Pod Show network and it's great to be part of the family. I'm really excited for the things ahead
And well, you know, I tried to record this earlier and this is how it went
Adam this has got up here in Alaska
I want to thank you for inviting me on the network at the same time. I wanted to share some bearers
And I'm witnessing the just waking up after a long winter's nap
This is really
Adam I gotta go
They've seen me man. I gotta go. Okay, come back
Get on over to the
And on over the website Alaska Pod Show.com
Get away
Is you can see it in turn out like I hope but I want to thank everybody over at Pod Show at the network for making it possible for me to do
What I love to do which is podcasting and sharing Alaska with everybody
Thanks a lot take care of yourself from Anchorage, Alaska. This is Scott Sloan
Okay, Scott very cool dude. Welcome
Was good talking to you on the phone a couple weeks or a go and I'm glad we were able to work everything out
That you now part of the family very proud to have you and I can't wait to get back up to a
To Alaska I've been there once I was there for an overnight
I forget the name of the club. It was
It wasn't it I'm pretty sure it was an anchorage
And it was just you know this was the the old MTV days when I still also had my countdown show the top 30 hit list
Which aired on the radio station on top 40 station there, which I don't recall either
But I do remember one thing beautiful women up there just beautiful women unbelievable
maybe you know
Maybe my brain is just too fuzzy or maybe I'm too old and I think anything this young is beautiful
But I really recall them as being extremely pretty
Now yesterday, yes, we're not even done with the weekend
Patricia and I got all duffied up and we hopped on the train from Gilford around was it around noon and
Bobbed up to London where Ron was staying in Marta and Chris Jacob
He is just coming back from his own vacation, but you know as I said we've got stuff in the city this week
We're gonna see if we can get some business going in the UK and
The first item on the agenda was to go to the draft and darts at the brick layers arms in
W1s that's West London to meet up with a whole bunch of UK podcasters and we've made this purposely very very low key
Whole bunch of people helped out
Neil Dixon Adrian Pegg
I mean, there's too many people to mention who contributed to setting this up and choosing the right place and getting it all in order
And so we got there a little after three o'clock and they're already at least
Man the must have been at least 15 20 people there already we had a nice place the brick layers arms upstairs
Although it was very warm very smokey and the Patricia and Marta came with us and and that was cool because I really wanted to
They had plans that were gonna go shopping and that they were gonna go to herids and Harvey next, you know
By doing all been in New York, baby, and then go back to Harvey next for lunch
Harvey Nichols is the place to go have tea or lunch or whatever
But they stayed for probably a good 30 45 minutes and
And they had a lot of fun meeting people and Patricia said to me
Private later she said you know everyone had heard everything they knew they said oh, I love that when you did this
I love that when you did that and I said you you don't believe me do you that people love hearing you on the show
You make the show fantastically when you come on the show
So thank you very much for telling her that because I think that that will motivate her and make her understand
How important it is to our future
to come on to the show
And
There were tons of t-shirts and there's pictures all over the place and maybe tonight when I I'm staying in the city tonight
So my hotel I'll put some of them up online
There were
People had t-shirts on that said Roger Smalls is the daddy
And I actually I point blank asked a couple people are you Roger Smalls and the answer usually came so
Quickly and honestly that I'm sure that he indeed was not there
But it was so cool to put
Faces to names
To podcasts people had traveled some of them several hundred miles. I'm sorry
I've got a problem with my left ear. I have a headphone ear
Which is not fun. It's like your ear gets really irritated
I've had too many headphones on between flying and doing the show. It's had a readjust for a second gets all itchy
Gosh, I don't even know where to start. Okay. Let's start with the beer
I had a beer in a half and I was like
I think I better stop now. I can't handle it. I can't drink. I'm just I'm I suck at drinking. I'm such a lightweight
And our British colleagues clearly had less less issue with that and it was really fun
It was it was just great
Hearing everyone. Yeah, it's so funny when
If you've ever met someone who you've seen on television or heard on the radio many many years and if you've been to a podcast and meet up
You know exactly what I'm talking about but then you hear someone
And you turn around and you go I know that voice because your brain just starts firing and recognizing and
It was very cool
Very very cool not just from a podcast or a podcast perspective, but to meet up with with Brits who
New about me new somewhat about my life and who I am and could leave all of there
Not not that everyone has that but I think could leave any prejudice or preconceived notions
They may have about Americans kind of you know behind and I was able to ask things about British culture and about
Schools and about that thoughts about what the BBC's doing but also just in general about
Life and newspapers and gossip and and really the culture of
Of the UK and it was very very life enriching for me and the cool thing was of course that after everyone had about three or four drinks
Everyone's microphone came out
It was like a sex party, you know everyone whips it out and and I did the several different chats with some with some folks
You'll be able to listen that if you got a brickcaster dot com, that's where there's a thread and
Some links to photos and you can see some of the cool t-shirts and
And everyone had a you know a nice sticker badge, you know, hi
I'm so and so in the name of the podcast and I made a lot of friends
I really did and I enjoyed it immensely and I appreciate
Everyone's input and thoughts and we had some very good discussions. I had one even outside
We were all standing around and talking about commercial versus non-commercial and it was it was good
It was good. It was good asked conversation. I'm very appreciative of the the UK podcast and community
And I hope that they can also take to heart what I said earlier in this show is let's make sure that we
Welcome the listeners in as well people who don't want a podcast because I still think that we're
In a very close circle. I don't think anyone can really disagree with that
And I want to get them in more and we have to you know, I'll make it my mission to give the audience better tools to
Communicate back to us which is not necessarily writing something is not necessarily
Recording something there are other ways that you can participate in in in in in a program
I'll make that my mission and and let's try and work on that and we have a great opportunity here
Really to lead the way in maybe oh, let's hey, let's call it podcasting two point out
No, we won't because the training wheels are are on here too. We've really got to figure out
How to how to do better with that and I had some awesome conversation
With a number of people about second life now if you have not heard this show before
Then you haven't heard my enthusiasm for this
Well, you can call it a game
It would certainly be and they had they do a very smart thing. I think they segregate everyone under 16
Is in a different area so it's really an an adult game
Not necessarily adult because of sexual content, but just adult because it's adults who are in there doing adult things and
and
People this is crack. This is crack for your brain. I'm so in fact
If I could retire right now and all I would do during the day is
Build my second life and create the world there that I want to create. I would be extremely happy
I would be a very very happy guy and that's how into this I am because this is something about the visualization of
Communication so not just the it's basically it's a chat system, you know, you're chatting with people and you're I aming with people
But you can actually make gestures and give people stuff and invite them places and go places and discover things and learn about other people
And you can tell a lot about a person just looking from the house that he's built there
I got some feedback on it too. Let me
First of all, I was incorrect the other day
When I compared this to
Neil Stephenson's
Metaverse I incorrectly called the book Metaverse. Hey Adam. This is JC Hutchins given you a shout out from South Florida United States. How's it going?
In a recent episode of the daily source code
You were talking about a video game called second life and how I reminded you of a Neil Stephenson novel called
Metaverse
You're absolutely right the video game is a lot like the universe that Stephenson was creating in that book
But the name of this sci-fi classic isn't Metaverse. I'm sorry to say it's snowcrash
The novel is a modern day classic and it's pretty prophetic when you think about online
Communities and how we talk to each other these days
Since you say that you've read snowcrash, I figured hey he might be a science fiction fan
I've written a science fiction podcast novel called seven son book one descent
And since I've got your attention here and God willing the attention of all of your listeners
I'd really appreciate it if you played the new promo for my novel as far as I know
You'll be the first podcast to play it so this will be a world premiere
Thanks, Adam. I really appreciate it keep up the great work keep reading great science fiction novels and check out seven son in your spare time
Okay, I think the I think the promo is coming up right after this. Yeah, it is snowcrash and in fact
I was such a fan of this book and the the lead character in it is a guy called hero
And it's exactly the same as second life except you you jack into the terminal through a
Virtual reality display the phone is ringing somewhere in the house
So you jack into it by putting on goggles and it's not much different. I think
And also virtual reality glob so if you move your arm then it would move within this virtual world
I was so nuts about it. I actually registered a metaverse dot com which I don't own anymore
I think that that was a part of the is there no one picking up this phone?
I think that was actually a part of the sale when we sold our company the metaverse dot com domain name was a part of it
But we 12 years ago Ron and I had set this thing up not actually I set it up with
Chris Jacob and his brother Carl and
Not long after that, you know when we discovered that there was no way we're gonna ever gonna be able to make money with creating content
And there was a lot of cool stuff we had in there was it was heavily entertainment music base
But all independent stuff and you can still find a lot of that on the way back machine look at just look up
Metaverse dot com on the way back machine
which is at archive.org
and
You know the second life thing is
It's just it's just like it. It is exactly exactly the book. Let me continue now with this guys promo because I like this feedback
The President of the United States is dead
He was murdered in the morning sunlight by a four-year old boy
Those are the opening words of 7th son book one dissent the podcast novel written by JC Hutchins and it doesn't let up from there
Join the Legion of 7th son fans who are already following the story of 7 human clones
John father Thomas kill right 2.0 and the others as they hunt down the man behind the president's murder
The man they were cloned from code named John alphas
David Moldauer critic for the dragon page.com hails 7th son as a taught tense sci-fi thriller
Gary P. Dilly Leeland says I definitely recommend it to anybody out there who's a sci-fi lover
Even Scott Sigler author of earth core and infection says
7th son's opening episode is the shock and awe of audio books the first five minutes will have you hooked
Subscribe to the party of book everyone's talking about
Join the dissent find 7th son at jc Hutchins.net and at pottyobooks.com
Right on
It's true the first five minutes does grip you and I'm of I'm becoming a fan of this type of podcast and the
Pottyobooks which I think is a good name too because actually I'm a big fan of audio books people have
listened to the source code for a long time know that I've promoted audio books and I had at one point
I purchased Snowcrash by Neil Stephenson which I think it's it's the unabridged version so it's seven hours
And but mostly it's it's reading and doesn't have the effects in it and stuff and that's what I like about the
Pottyobooks it's taking it one step further somewhere in between the radio drama and the audio book and it's
Exciting and and you could make these productions extremely intricate we're coming out with their own you know
Pottyobooks it's not science fiction, but it's going to well you could deem a science fiction I guess
It's going to be called shadow falls and you should look for that
First or second week of May I believe and and and I think there's we've actually talked about this many times
Yeah, we've forgotten how much we can do with audio we really have
Back the second life because I'm just so jazzed about this, you know, Eric Rice
It's also doing quite a bit and I haven't explored
His area of of second life and haven't
Haven't done any any investigation into it yet, but I know that I guess he bought the the record
There was a record label that had been created there and he bought that and he set up podcast listening stations and he's he's truly and clearly
Into this stuff
So I'm gonna see what he's up to here's here's my plan and by the way, I'm really still learning
Okay, now the good news is or for me at least is and and this stuff costs money
You know this is not free you pay a subscription fee
Particularly if you buy land the larger the land you more the more you got to pay per month
And the business model around this thing is just outrageously smart
But you can also trade amongst each other you can sell things people can give you money
And once you put down your credit card
You know if you want to buy something you don't have enough money is very simple a pops little dialogue box. Oh, you know
You need some more cash you want to buy that and you just go and it automatically you know
You hear the coins drop and then you've got your cash and you can buy something and you can buy anything you want
And not being a designer
I can when I see how something works
I can edit it and figure it out and and all these objects have scripts and I'm not really a computer programmer
But I can figure out just by reading this it's English mostly I can figure out what the script is doing and I know how to modify stuff
When I'm really taking my time building my second life and and something that really surprised me
You know, yeah people
No my my second life name which is Adam Newman and that's N-E-U-M-A-N
Newman
They're able to find me instant message me, but they don't really know where
My place is located is I've kind of chosen to remote area and a and a typical dwelling
I'm building a castle essentially why purchase the castle I purchase the land and what I'm doing now is is
You know figuring out what I want to put in my in my world and all of a sudden a couple days ago
There's like a guy in my castle
Hey, Adam this is Jeff Hines with the Friday night dance party podcast
aka Jeff Cragman your second life stalker. Hey, I was just looking for a prime piece of real estate and
Loan behold I end up on your front door step. What was I supposed to do?
Thanks for the martini, but were you gonna go post it on my ass?
Maybe when I get my castle built you can come on over for Friday night dance party
But until then just listen to the podcast
That's Friday night dance party. Oh, and PS
You're drool when you sleep
I've always wondered about that when I'm logged off and sometimes I guess you're avatar can sometimes hang there or something like that and you don't really go away
Now I figured out how to lock up the castle
That's the good news, but I guess you could still teleport in and you can't I don't know but it doesn't really matter
But here's the plan for me the plan is I want to make this thing completely rocking
I want to set it up so that you know, and I'm gonna have a big ass party at the in and around the castle when I'm ready for you guys
And and hopefully I'll be well enough burst in all of the the cool things that it really will feel like a party
And I know that we can do this if this works this shit really does work. I'm extremely excited
now the conversation I had yesterday with with a number of people including a
Joe twist
Who was a castle's partner and
So she's heavily into podcasting and she's now working for a
I think it's an NGO. It's certainly a non-profit and she's trying to
Really integrate all of these new technologies into well working with a British government actually
And she's doing some I think tremendously important things and you know
She's all over second life as this castle and a lot of people
Either after hearing this show or having heard about it somewhere else have have joined in the fun
Now I have a question for you all because at the end of the day
And I'm gonna be the guy who's gonna say it because I don't care
I say everything apparently on this show at the end of the day
You know you you hook up with someone you talk to him you learn a little bit about second life, but
Isn't it the fact that just about every single person who's on second life at some point or another
Has been hanging out with someone and then you click on the blue ball you jump on it that person clicks on a pinker of blue ball
They jump on it and you have cyber sex
Come on you got to be honest. I'm I've totally totally it look
There are places where you can go by genitalia you can buy actions
You can buy positions you can buy beds that have all these things built into it a
Big part of what is happening in second life is cyber sex, but it's nothing and I've said before that
I've always paid attention to what this sex and the porn industry has been doing because they're always innovators in
Technology
I've never like the whole webcam thing that's you know
I don't want to see anyone having cyber sex and I don't want anyone to see me quite honestly
You know, I think there's better porn out there visually, but this is something wow
You know once again wrote we're reminded or I'm reminded that the brain is the most powerful and most active sexual
Oregon anyone has and and this stuff is nuts
It's it's fascinating fascinating
You can have any kind of sex you want anything you can think of and this real people on the other end and and
It's I'm not quite sure how to categorize it. I will do some more investigation for you
But think about what you can do
You can do an entire
You could do pretty women
There's lots of call girls in second life
You know you might have a fantasy of taking one back to your place and
And going through the whole movie script and
Either with that person's knowledge or without
You know this is fantasy land that is just it's it's making your brain just scream in overdrive
And is that cheating is that dangerous can someone get hooked and fall in love with someone else just based I mean we have lots of examples of the happening through the internet
Lots of examples
Again, this is all part of the training wheels this thing. It's like you know for me doing podcasting
I unfortunately I really don't weblog that much anymore
Although I use the infrastructure a lot for the comments et cetera for this show
but
Hopping into second life man. We're we're barely even walking now and the technology is way ahead of us
and the powerful things we can do so I hope to be able to
Explore a lot of that with you
Especially the folks in Britain because you're on my time zone or currently
Yeah, so it's kind of rough when you log in and everyone's asleep and no one's there because everyone in the states is you know still on one year
But you know, let's experiment I'm getting tired. Can you hear it? Let's experiment together and let's figure out where we can take this place
The cool thing is all the communication
Infrastructure outside of second life if it isn't already integrated into second life
It will be or we can integrate it. You know we can make this this stuff happen we can we can turn it the way we want and I think
That the next time I meet up with a whole bunch of people
I think we'll do it in second life and I'd love to have you over to the castle and I'd love to serve you martinis and
Hope we have some you know some fun things we can do some games and we can listen to stuff together and
Just give me it give me a few weeks to figure all this stuff out and working very diligently and if you've got any
Any tips or anything just you know just look me up you can see if I'm online and
I'm not letting you in the castle yet perhaps because again
I want to make it right now. I want to have my place all set up before I have all my friends over
But looking forward to that. Okay, so what have we done now an hour and 14 and it's holy
Much longer than I had intended
It'll be worth it
Fast with a twist
Only get it while it's hot
Get it a little like that
Yes
Here she comes
She only move but she's not impressed
And that's what she couldn't get less
And a little like that
It's played out as a psychology
It laid out in the gene
I grew up in a lot of little blackheads
She knows it's gonna be
All around
When you call your shape a head to toe
The power comes
From what she shows
It'll be my dream
She tried to drive but she couldn't cry
You knew she couldn't make a face in this
She couldn't be
And a little like that
But a hundred percent success
And a little blackhead
She knows it's gonna be
All around
When you make a touch of rush it got
But you're gonna come again
While it's hot
You know you'll back to
You'll back to
Nice, cush, little black dress from the Bodhisave Music Network.
Let me just look it up for you for a second.
From California and as Bio done with the majors, film and TV, now Indy, I do my own
thing and play guitar, play with Fisher, FisherTheBand.com, new release at the accents coming
soon on download.
Cush Rocks.com, or the Bodhisave Music Network.
Links of course in today's show notes, all right.
Incredibly long show, love to hear what you have to say about it, love to hear what you're
thinking about.
Tomorrow, I probably won't be able to do a source code because I'm going into town now, right
after this is uploaded and put up on the podcast, literally network, I'm staying in the hotel,
tomorrow night because we have, or tonight because we have meetings tomorrow morning, starting
at 8 or 8, 30, something like that.
So I do not want to deal with getting up early and, and I actually have never done the,
the morning rush hour commute train or otherwise.
So I don't know if I'm, and yeah, we have the sidelight windows to hit and all that stuff
and we have meetings all day long.
So probably not going to be a show, although I'll see if I can post some progress to
the web logs.
You can follow along with what's happening.
So if not, then I'll gladly see you back here Wednesday.
We'll continue.
We'll have some more fun.
We'll play some cool tunes and we'll do it all on cast blasts.
For instance, today's show brought to you by EarthLinks.
Stay tuned.
EarthLinks is we're coming out with our one message many voices for EarthLink.
It's going to be very cool.
You can participate in that, particularly if you're artistically inclined and you can win
cash and valuable prizes.
Also partially sponsored by AccuView.
Check out Heather and Janella download.acuView.com.
And what am I missing?
Am I missing one of our fabulous sponsors?
Oh, of course, go daddy.
If you want a 695 deal on the domain name and thank you by the way for the person who registered
Adam Curry's not a bigot.com.
Thank you for sponsoring this show and you can do it for any pod show podcast.
Um, what to get that 695 discount or the discount down to 695 for one domain name.
You should use code DSC1 upon checkout.
I'll see you back here Wednesday.
Thanks everybody.
Bye bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance pod cast delivery
network from pod show and limelight networks.