This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
The show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy.
Delta Sierra Charlie.
4-3-1.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm testing kids that I'm curry.
Got to get myself together.
Got to get myself back straight.
Need to clean my weary head now.
Got to get back in.
Just change yourself.
You'll be driving me crazy.
You'll be thinking you'll do all the time.
Stronger things that happen to me.
I can't tell you why I can't.
It's been like this for a long time.
Got to change yourself.
You'll be driving me crazy.
You'll be thinking you'll do all the time.
Got to do some business.
Got to find a way to change my life.
saying to be In a risk.
Feeling that twice my age.
Cause it's you beingnothing.
You being muacri-
Being me being you all the time.
Time
We'll see you in the mother
I realize that we're late
The way you are the way you treat me
But the guess is just in a life
Is it you, babe?
Just can't believe you
You, babe, this'll be here all the time
I think now that I'm just leaving
Don't think I'm making right
I think that I need to face it
I wanna change less about it tonight
Cause I'm the you, babe
Driving me crazy, you, babe
Driving me insane, you, babe
Never be okay, you, babe
Breaking my heart all the time
I'm just gonna make my own
Taking my brother's love
Oh, man, have I time warped into the 60s
Or have I just visited the potsape using that word once again?
Tones get myself together, kicking off a brand new week of the Daily Source code.
Everybody how you doing?
Han, Han, Han, Han!
Ah, I could yell all I want.
She won't hear me.
Because I'm still in San Francisco.
That's right, coming to you from the Curry condo on the 24th floor of the Metropolitan
and sunny northern California.
Uh-huh.
Why am I still here?
I was supposed to leave on Saturday.
I would have been home Sunday in my baby's arms.
Well, I'll tell you why.
Friday while, uh, while actually while back lab was performing live at Fubar Friday
in our office.
Ron and I sat down and reviewed, uh, not just this week, but, uh, the week before that
we've, as you know, we've really been working on, uh,
yeah, setting our, setting ourselves up for the next phase of our growth.
Of course, we're a media company now that we have, uh,
this big jeloppy called the pod show plus out there floating about.
Um, we, it's, uh, it's, um, there's so much is so right.
Yet so much is so wrong.
There's just so much to do, particularly, uh, on the, uh,
I mean, you know what it is, you build something like this.
There's so many features.
Some, some things turned out better than we expected.
Many things turned out, and not at all the way we expected.
Um, it's very hard to, um, uh, really to spec something out when it's, uh,
when it's still a dream.
And when you start to play with it, that's when, and it's not, you know,
it's not things that we actually could have played with in beta until you,
as I just me or, or anyone else playing.
It's really what, what people are saying, what we're feeling, uh,
the feedback we're getting.
And just some simple logic, and, uh, I said,
they're on it.
And then we, we have, we got work to do.
And I just can't go back.
Uh, I want to, I want to set us up this week.
Uh, you know, just to, to get the last pieces have to all fit in.
So we can get to the next stage, which, of course, includes more development.
So I decided to stay, uh, staying for, uh, well, uh, a couple more days,
but really in, uh, in all, uh, reality that triple be extended now for five days.
So about a three, uh, more than three weeks by the time I get home.
And even though I missed the girls dearly, uh, not quite as much as they missed me.
Oh, man.
That was a call.
I wasn't looking forward to making Saturday morning.
Anyway, of course, Patricia understood.
And, uh, and it's so sad.
The girls that, you know, they had done their hair.
They had, uh, I guess they had even, uh,
uh, that new color in their hair, which, uh, man,
I hope I would have noticed when I got home.
But nothing worse than not realizing it and not saying anything.
You know, and Patricia done all the grocery shopping and had, you know,
because of good stuff to eat.
And, uh, so of course she was a little bit disappointed,
but she understood very well.
And, and the real problem is the house.
The new curry cottage that we're, uh, we're in the throes of trying to buy, um,
because she had set up an appointment with me for today from Monday, 10 a.m.
to go and look at the house.
I have not actually seen the place of seeing the brochure.
I've seen pictures that she's taken.
I've seen pictures in the brochure.
I trust my wife implicitly, of course.
Also a good friend of ours, Mark Egan went along.
Um, and he knows a lot about building and construction in homes.
And, uh, and about this whacked out bidding process.
Actually, uh, you know what they sent to, uh, you know, like this.
Here is the, uh, the, um, the paperwork that has to be filled out for this.
Remember I talked about this like closed bid system.
So final bids have to be in by Wednesday, which is okay because I can just do that from here.
But you should just hear what they, what they want to know.
Uh, they wish I'll require the following information at time of your offer.
Details of your best and final offer subject to contract, because of course it means,
it means nothing, right?
Uh, if, if you are the winning bid, you still will have a contract that still takes three weeks.
Uh, confirmation as to whether you're offered a subject to survey of please, of course it is.
Uh, our client reserves the right to not necessarily accept the highest offer.
And the ability to proceed will be taken into account.
That means if you don't have a house that you have to sell, that'll be taken into account.
That's a plus for us.
Uh, position details of any related sale.
If applicable, please confirm your position.
I don't know 69 in rented.
Oh, this is if you're renting, if you're not renting, if you set it sell, et cetera.
Okay, evidence will be required to demonstrate your position to proceed.
Okay.
Well, then I said, yes, you go call the rental agency.
Finance is your financial position.
I eat cash, percentage of any borrowing, et cetera.
Which I think is interesting.
Um, I don't think that's really anyone's, oh, I guess, I don't know.
I'm sorry, you're right.
Nope.
I think they do need to know this because if you can't get them, if you're buying with a mortgage and you can't get a mortgage,
then that could make it all fall through.
Okay.
I don't know.
Do you not put down 10%, or how does that?
No one's saying anything about that.
Uh, but I have to, um, send along my bank and contact details or clients reserve the right to request a bank reference should it be deemed necessary.
Um, and those are the main things.
So, just to be on the really, really safe side, I figured I'd call our banker.
Uh, fair.
Let her know.
So, I'm going to give your name to these guys if they call you.
Now, she's in, uh, in Holland, uh, because our, um, our real bank, not, not the checking account bank, but our bank, uh, is a, uh, one of these private banking outfits.
So, I've had the same banker for like six years, and she happens to be a single 40 year old bombshell of a woman.
And I hadn't spoken to her.
In fact, uh, she is, uh, Patricia has said to her, you know, hey, if anything happens to me, uh, I want you to take care of Adam,
which, of course, is just fine by me.
So, um, now of course, uh, chat with Herdie for a little while, and, uh, you know, and, uh, she had a lot more to tell than I did.
So, I was like an hour-long phone call.
Uh, and by now it's like one PM on Saturday.
You know, and I've gotten up at six to make sure I call Patricia at a reasonable time during the day.
And, um, and then I call Patricia back, and so anyway, so, you know, but the time I got turned around is like three o'clock.
And, uh, uh, I should tell you, actually, uh, I don't know if it.
I wish Patricia was here because then we talked about the cyber sex that we had, but I'll have to save that until I get back home.
The cyberwank.
So then, uh, I was like, oh, I'm, and I'm gonna take a bath.
So, because I had all these shows, of course, I have a, um, a pod show channel, which I sync up to my iPod for when I'm, uh,
when I'm, you know, I have that, when I'm traveling, when I take that 10 hour flight between San Francisco and London.
And so, you know, instead of, uh, listening to the iPod, I draw a drew bath, a nice bubble bath, which I had not been in since my entire stay here.
And I just listened to some shows.
I listened to, um, oh, I listened to the second episode of Shadow Falls, a rough version, a rough mix.
You know, so I always have a couple of, uh, mainly production things I just want to send back.
Oh, you're gonna love it. It's so good.
And then I listened to one of my favorite shows, uh, which I rarely get to listen to, and it's entirety, because it is a rather long show.
I think it's, I think it's a weekly show, but it's, it's long.
Um, and so I was happy to be able to listen to whispered pearls.
I think episode number 33.
And Michelle, by the way, um, there was a beautiful, um, a beautiful piece for me,
and from my mom that they had done on whispered pearls, uh, a couple of weeks ago.
And I can't even remember if I even thanked him for it or not, everything was such a blur.
And then I'm listening to the show, and this is what I hear, and it was absolutely, just, you know,
you have to imagine, I'm kind of lonely, I'm a little bit bummed out that I'm not going to go home.
And, um, and then I turn on this show, and this is what I hear.
He said at the end of one of his shows recently that if you see a butterfly, the next time you see a butterfly
to think of his mom, and I don't see a whole lot of butterflies usually, where I live,
and, but I, I vowed that, okay, if I do, I'm going to honor that, I'm going to do that.
And so, I was in my house looking out the window a couple of days ago, and outside of my window,
they're past this most beautiful red butterfly, which seems really unusual, they're red butterfly,
but in any case it was a red butterfly, and immediately I thought of Adam's mom,
and set a prayer for her, and wished her well.
And the feeling that I got was the only way I can describe it is just like this huge,
sort of interconnectedness of the earth feeling.
Like, like, I was one of many people who were doing this, and that this butterfly,
if this is even possible, but this butterfly was smiling, and affirming that we are all connected.
You know, that was so beautiful Michelle.
I cried when I heard that, because this is the first time I've heard it on a podcast,
but I've heard so many people say this, who knew my mom or heard the story about her and the butterflies,
and I've seen it, you know, and it's in butterfly season, and the other day,
a butterfly flew into the house into the kitchen where when Patricia was in the kitchen.
And yeah, I'm sure maybe it's because you're paying attention to it, you're thinking about it.
Maybe that's enough, you know, that we overlook these small, beautiful things,
and just for a little period of time we're thinking about it.
Maybe we'll keep thinking about that and think about the butterfly.
And there's one other thing I was really thinking, Michelle,
you should send me some naked pictures.
Hey, this is Max, I'm the host of MusicCrafts.
I play some of my favorite pods and please talk a little about what I was going on the way.
I'm 11 years old, and I'm a little shy, am I?
Michelle is usually less than 20 months old.
But there's a cast that is at the good news, the IK, C-A-S-T-E-G-R-T-R.
You can email me at the MusicCrafts.html.com, go check it out.
It's good to be as good as it is.
Nothing like a young podcaster to get your day going.
Let's see.
Time now for...
Oh yeah, the Troy needs an iPod update.
Man, this is really blown wide open.
I have to say, there's...
Thank you very much for going over to dailysourcecode.com
and posting all of your entries into the comments section.
Keep doing that because this week we're going to give them away.
And I feel kind of bad for Troy.
Not only does he think now that he's not going to receive an iPod
and even though he came up with the idea, he says he's getting hate mail.
This is my theory, you know.
It's like Andy Warhol talks about the 15 minutes of fame.
I'm telling you, at the end of the day, not a lot of people are going to want to have any kind of high visibility anywhere.
Because human nature is just so messed up.
It doesn't matter what you do, doesn't matter.
What the topic of discussion is when you connect people with equal weaponry,
which means you can't actually kill the other guy or anyone with the words.
You can't actually do them any bodily physical harm.
People just seem to do it and we just get all pissed off at each other.
It's amazing.
There's not a single community anywhere that doesn't have a percentage of flaming going on.
Some of it may be healthy, but man, I see so many communities flame out.
And I'm seeing this Troy needs an iPod and I feel really bad for him.
So Troy, no matter what, I'm sending you an iPod dude.
I promise you that.
And then just go to dailysourceco.com and look at all the fantastic entries.
It started with Troy needs an iPod.com.
Suggestion was just go ahead, come up with the best URL registered godaddy.com.
And of course, I'd like you to use check out code DSC3.
So I get some credit for that.
But you can use any other pod show.
Check out code if you want.
Such as it was it's Rob and Taylor from.
Was it all critters?
She said she used her own check out code.
But she'd come up with what did she have?
iPod for podshow.com, stuck in my ear.com, not the most original.
With $16 million worth of airplanes strapped to my ass.com, I like that one a lot.
I go ahead and check it out and put your entry in today before it's too late,
because you can win an iPod and Troy email me your details, man.
So I can send you something.
Voice mail numbers?
No good calls over the weekend.
I was kind of surprised.
Maybe the weather was too nice.
But there were calls, but nothing that I really wanted to put on the air.
The idea here would be to stop whatever you're doing.
Grab your cell phone, punch this number in.
If you know how to do it the plus one, 201, 625, 6357.
Put it in your phone right now.
So the next time you're listening you're on the road, you have no time to write it down.
You can just, anyway, you wake up in the middle of the night.
You got an idea for me.
You call me plus 201, 625, 6357.
Or in London, 0207, 681, 375, 3.
Big day today.
Actually, you know what?
Before I do all the acts, I don't want to mess up the sound light window.
Today also marks a big day for the sound light window.
We've got a little different line up.
Let me tell you about it because we are moving things around.
Right after the show, if you're listening to us on serious stars,
you're going to want to Pacific Coast.
Hellway will drop by.
Follow by Dawn and Drew.
Then the Jersey Todd show on serious.
This Jersey Todd, a lawyer with a sense of humor.
I think you'll like a show very much.
I listened to a show that's going out today.
I think you're going to dig a DVD weekly after that.
Then CC Chapman comes in with, I don't know if he's doing axler and hash tonight on the
sidelight or not.
Then Madge Weinstein with East Radio and Scottsley will rewind it up.
I think he's going to be doing episodes of infection on serious.
You want to get ready for something extremely cool, something totally new if you've never heard this before
and you're on serious.
You're going to hear a book as you've never heard it before.
Also coming up on serious stars, one or two shadow falls will also start airing as well.
So that's the new line up on serious.
Now, PW, the satellite repairman, Uncle Jesse won't get all pissed off at me.
And speaking of that, check out who's checking in.
Hiya, Adam, carry.
Without MTV, you still would be just a local radio presenter in Netherlands, a province of European Union.
CSB shut up without me MTV would still be a dorky satellite channel.
This week MTV is celebrating 25th anniversary.
It's pretty much embarrassing because target audience of MTV are teens who obviously are younger than MTV itself.
The, since you, matey, also match to MTV, maybe you could mention what you think.
What do you think?
Hold on, I just want to set the record straight.
I don't know MTV jacks shit, okay.
Those cocksuckers fired me seven times and kept asking me to come back,
which of course I did all freelance and kept raising the price.
So, no way, I don't owe them jacks shit, please.
Ving is the future of MTV mobile games.
Entering tons, or could it be?
No, put fucking safe music.
Just predict, guess, this was for fuck's sake.
I wish I could convince you to dump black fucking buried by the way and use the jelly you know what, but whatever.
Well, see ya.
Yo.
Three F bombs there.
CSB.
What's wrong?
Are we on a diet today?
Yeah, that's right tomorrow.
August 1st.
So, 81 is when MTV first went on the air.
I was not one of the original VJs, by the way.
I didn't arrive at MTV until 1987.
The reason why many people think that is because with my arrival, MTV had just started to penetrate into the larger cable networks.
And they went from like 8 million households to 40 million households.
So, you know, by all intents and purposes, that was for a lot of people.
The time I was there was the first time people were actually seeing MTV.
So, there's always confusion about that.
That's right.
MTV is 25 years old.
And to answer your question and a conversation blogger, no, they will never be an interactive company with any large degree of success.
They will never be.
They will never break music through pod safe music or any of that because they are a television company.
Their, their mothership is a television organization.
There is to get out of that will be so incredibly difficult.
And honestly, they've been trying.
They've been trying for years to do that to have some huge successes.
Now, of course, they have things that go hand in hand with, you know, they do have an interesting, interesting interactive stuff.
By the way, they silently kind of fired that, I forget who the guy was, but he was going to be the interactive guru.
He was going to make it all happen and guess what?
It didn't all happen.
They tried to consolidate all their efforts and it turned into a big pile of junk.
The one thing people ask me all the time is what happened to the music on MTV?
And I've told the story a couple times.
It's not that long, but I think you should understand exactly what happened to the music on MTV.
First of all, there's music everywhere.
There's music channels on cable, on satellite.
Yeah, you can download videos.
You know, that is the main reason.
I think MTV was actually pretty smart to get away from the music videos from a business standpoint,
because they were losing their stranglehold on the monopoly.
Even in 1988 and 1989, MTV would have to fight with the other channels like BET
for Michael Jackson premiere videos.
And rightly so, by the way.
So, they saw the writing on the wall, but what really did it is when the game show
Remote Control came on.
Remember that?
With Ken Ober, Colin Quinn, Curry, who were Steve Treakas, who was in the band.
When that came on, their ratings almost tripled to a 1.0, which is,
which by any network standards would be seen as a huge failure.
But that's it.
You know, they could sell three times as much advertising, or they could charge as much,
three time, or a significant amount more.
And they just went from there.
Just you look at the history of all the, what they called short form programming that
cropped up.
And that was, that was really the, the deathnell of, of music on MTV.
And they're not celebrating at all, by the way.
There's not a single celebration going on.
I think you're right.
They are kind of embarrassed about being that old.
See where your star's one or two listeners hang in there.
Pacific Coast Hellwise coming right up.
Mark Yoshimoto Namcoff is your guy in just seconds from now.
He's also my guy here on the Charlie.
Hey Adam, it's Mark Yoshimoto Namcoff from Pacific Coast Hellway.
You remember the gin blossoms, right?
You know, hey, jealousy, till I hear from you.
Good stuff.
But whatever happened to those guys, I'll tell you.
The new gin blossoms record, major lodge victory,
is coming out on August 8th.
And the gin's in their record label,
we're kind enough to grant you the world podcast exclusive
to play their just release single, learning the hard way.
Only on PCH.
And I'm spending it Monday, July 31st, and afterwards,
I'll tell you how you can listen to most of the album for free.
Just so you know, I'm working on getting them to agree to release a song
or two pod safe.
But for now, the only place you can hear learning the hard way
by the gin blossoms, legally on a podcast,
is at pacificcoasthellway.com.
So thanks, Adam, for playing this promo.
I really appreciate it.
And if you have any gin blossom stories,
I'd love to hear them.
Unless of course they involve sex,
in which case I know.
Nothing else I'll pass.
But anyway, I'll catch you later.
Bye.
My name is Jim Blasms and my friend,
and Andrew Gole and my friend.
They play on the same.
Get that shit on the pod's head music network.
Yeah, where will you?
And then send me a comment.
Mark Yoshimo to blow off.
Come on, man.
Do something really important for humanity.
He did get Andrew Gole to,
to agree to let me play never let us slip away on the show.
That's kind of cool because that's one of our songs.
But he didn't have the juice to actually get him to recut the,
the first line.
I know it's like, it's a big request.
But how cool would it be if you heard Andrew Gole say,
you heard Andrew Gole singing talk to Patricia on the tail of long distance.
You know why?
Because I always talked to a fucking long distance.
That's why.
Because I'm never home anymore.
It seems.
Yeah.
Also during my,
Yeah, so I play this whole channel that I've set up.
It's a private channel, by the way,
because there's all kinds of stuff in there.
I don't necessarily want people to know that.
I listen to.
So you can't find that I'm pod show plus.
But in that channel, because I have a video I pod,
I also subscribe to rock and roll TV.
I don't know if you've seen rock and roll TV,
it is a kick and ass in numbers,
because we're just seeing how many people are now watching this show.
And they did like,
I was completely blown away.
I really had to,
to really focus on it for,
for a couple minutes before I figured out.
No, no, no, this is definitely set up and produced.
Like spinal tap.
It was like a little,
a little mini documentary documentary,
but it was really,
it was a modern day version of a spinal tap.
It just blew my mind,
but the production that went into that,
you have to check this out.
Of course, I'll put a link to that in the show notes.
Rock and roll TV.
See what share and the guys did.
It's pretty outrageous.
Speaking of show notes,
you'll notice that I'm doing it differently now.
I had a nice long talk with the Mads Weinstein Friday night.
The Mads was in Berlin.
It was a kind of convoluted conversation, regardless.
And I noticed that she hadn't heard,
that probably hadn't listened in a while.
And I know why, because,
you know, I spanked her.
She didn't feel too good about that.
And I said,
well,
you know, sorry,
you know,
it's not, you don't have to listen,
but you know,
I said,
well, you know,
I usually just look at the show notes and then,
and that'll be it.
And I'm like, fuck that.
I hate that shit.
I really, really hate it.
If I, so I'm like,
if I hear one more person say,
well,
I didn't listen to the show because I looked at the show notes.
I didn't think it would be interesting.
I'm like,
that's it.
I'm not doing that anymore.
That's,
you know,
you may want show notes.
Screw you.
You're not getting show notes in nice little chunks.
So you can forward ahead to stuff.
And you either listen to the show.
You don't listen to the show.
Show notes are changing.
I'm just doing headlong.
There aren't many places where one can find information.
News from the strange and the paranormal.
Crypto zoology and more can be difficult to find.
Here at cryptic universe,
we cover a variety of topics from science
to news not covered in the mainstream media.
Every week with a bit of skepticism,
we learn about the secrets and mysteries
this universe may have.
Check out crypticuniverse.com
and subscribe using your favorite podcast directory
or the iTunes music store.
Cryptic universe,
where the strange and the paranormal become reality.
So you probably heard that my space
was down for like 12 hours last weekend.
Not this one,
but the one before it.
Oh, man.
I was supposed to do a sensational thing for somebody.
I've completely forgotten.
I'm sorry.
It's Monday.
You just have to live with me.
No sponsorship today.
For the sensational moment.
I got to set that up again.
Sorry.
So my space was down.
And coming back up,
they had all kinds of troubles where people couldn't log it.
It happens from time to time.
We should have their problems, right?
I don't think I think
they must have had some database issues
and people were their friends.
We're not either not there
or some of their postings were gone
or their comments were gone.
So when I'm on the phone with Patricia,
I said,
did you notice any of that my space was down?
She said, and she took like a beaten.
She went,
so that's what it was.
She said,
I couldn't believe it.
And we compared timing
as to when my space was down.
She said,
well yeah,
Christina was in the kitchen.
She was chatting away.
And she had all kinds of fungal stories
to tell.
And she was helping out with cooking.
And I said,
aha,
that would be right.
So there you go.
Folks,
I think we need for parents.
We probably need a,
like it would be pretty easy to fix up.
I'm sure.
A little like proxy server or something
that you can flip on or off.
So when you want your kid to be with you again,
you just make it look like my space is down.
And then all of a sudden,
they reemerge.
They literally reappear
and come out of the woodwork.
And you know what?
They're actually sociable and really nice.
Hayadam,
Franco, you're from Rokastitalia.
Hayad,
you're wife,
both some volume bills from the farmers.
Wait a minute.
Just just to make sure they're Franco.
She thought about it.
I caught her just in time.
She but the point was there is that she saw the spam
and thought,
oh well, that might be kind of cheap and easy.
Maybe I should purchase.
Of course,
I made sure she didn't.
And so she didn't actually buy anything.
But your point is well made.
And you know,
I work as a medical doctor and I can give you a little advice.
If somebody can find questionable
to buy something from spammers,
ingesting bills,
made in some clandestine,
you cry and lab is absolutely a no-no.
You know,
these bills are made using
complicated procedures that can have
a lot of toxic by products.
And the refinement of those
is very, very important.
So please just give Patricia this advice.
Don't eat those pills.
Okay.
It's over now.
And the doctor is a folder.
Other doctors are a folder.
Of course you are because you know it's good for you.
You know what's next, don't you?
Franco says,
don't eat the pills.
Don't eat the pills you buy from the spammers.
It's where I love about pot-safe music, man.
You look at her, look right here.
Be pretty topical if they want to, you know?
Check out what the genders have to say
the rock and roll.
No junkies in Geneva.
But if you're ever up on my side of the whole green line,
I'll take you down to the sea.
Down here, the folks are scared of death.
Then we're super,
you watch it now for the fire.
One of the buckles in the ideal.
I watch it now for the mama.
Then grab all the bad boys in this pile with crazy.
Well, they've been rocking in a pile with baby.
All right.
Sitting in a pile with baby.
That's it.
That a girl of the nameless.
Don't see much and hurty days.
Because that must be about 19 roadblocks between her and Brown.
So they say,
I said,
out here, the folks are dark in peace.
Then we're super, you watch it now for the fire.
One of the buckles in this pile with crazy.
I watch it now for the mama.
I see what I can now see.
Then I say,
all right.
Well, they've been rocking in a pile with baby.
All right.
You're comfortable.
And a horse of better have round.
No junkies in to be in.
But if you're ever up on my side of a old green line,
I'll take you down to the sea.
That's I'm seen.
I hear the folks are dark in peace.
Then we're super, you watch it now for the fire.
One of the buckles in a secret police.
I watch it now for the mama.
Got round and all, then mammals in this pile with crazy.
I see.
Well, they've been rocking in a pile with baby.
All right.
I watch it now for the mama.
Just imagine for a second, the genders were signed with a big major record label.
And have to record the song a year ahead of time to even get on the schedule.
It's like, hey, you know, we got this great song called Rock and Romala.
But can you kind of coordinate that with the war so we can get it out at the same time?
No.
With the pod save music.
Just with what's happening in general.
Doesn't even have to do with pod save music.
Within dependent music and the distribution we have built right in.
The song you put it out there when you want.
It can be up and being played on hundreds or thousands of podcasts the next day.
This is truly something big.
Okay, everybody.
So it's clear what I'm going to do.
I'm going to pod show HQ will have heads down.
We're going to be working really hard with the teams today tomorrow and Wednesday.
And I'll still get you a show Wednesday morning.
And then Wednesday afternoon.
I take off going back home to Blighty.
So I'll be back at the cottage Thursday.
I might even do a show Thursday morning with Patricia.
That would be that would be possible to get it to you on time.
And then Friday and then the weekend.
And this weekend I'm doing something else.
I don't care.
I'm going to be doing something else.
Thank you very much for listening today.
It's the start of a great new week.
I'm sure of it.
Hope it's going to be a good week for you.
If you got anything to say drop me an email.
Adam Curry dot com.
And he comments go over to daily source code dot com.
You can put it right in next to the episode.
And I'll see you tomorrow right here.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance podcast.
Delivery network from podshow and line-white networks.
I love it.