This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code, get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy!
Desents the perfect intro to the Charlie.
You don't have to wait 200 episodes.
Go's front will intimidate the Swedish version right now.
Close your eyes and imagine who you hear.
Do this night to let the audience shine cool down,
off stick to the 166.
That's right, Swedish girls say first to the 166.
Imagine the DSC, 466.
It's fun to hear the curry's both having some kicks with Adam and the Lady Patricia in the mix.
So happy together.
One kill!
Yes, Adam and Patricia, Adam and the Lady Patricia.
I got blue right away.
That's all you got to say.
I'm thinking about thinking about some things I thought I'd never be thinking.
Too many drugs dropped into my mouth.
Looking for something new, but I end up drinking.
He'd know the warnings on the show.
I'll take my chance and be into danger.
I want to taste life more and more, but you need a little risk full of this picture.
This is just action under the control.
Hard casting for you to let go.
Can I feel it?
I got blue right away.
That's all I got to say.
She's just a flame and a bomb.
Now, how do you explore unstable?
A big suit with a briefcase.
I'm holding contracts state and higher label.
All in all, do a phone on hold on.
Do a way for the next operator.
I want to taste life uncontrolled.
Oh no, give a go.
I hope to see you later.
This is just action under the control.
Hard casting for you to let go.
Can I feel it?
I can feel it?
I've casted for you to play soul
This is a station of the nature
You have given up your love you're not in good show
This is a station of the mode control
Like a sporadized hero
You have given up your love you're not in good show
All the rest in there are the lies
All the cast in the same world
It's the seed
Everything that has the lies
All the cast in the same world
No control
Gee, I wonder why they call themselves pepper
Do you think it sounds a little bit like the Red Hot Chili peppers?
Just a little bit
That was good though
You can find out the podcast music network
And of course in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
Doesn't get any more real than this
I was normally I would ask you what you thought of the song
And you would have listened to the whole thing
But you were on the phone
Exactly
The moment the song stopped
The minute the song kicked in
Yeah
And I was like, what the hell do I?
Why is the whole playing in the background on this song?
Because my generation is your room town
You wouldn't reach me
I don't know
Bruce, what we didn't hear
Because we were listening to all the opening sequence
That's it
That was Bruce, the realtor
Yes, it was Bruce the realtor
Everyone already knows we're looking at 10,000 homes
How many times?
At the same time
And there was another house
But the lady is not moving
Quick enough
Quick enough for us
Speak into the microphone
So let's look further
Because she never know what you find
That's what we said
Correct and we know
We know now that you don't have to be decent
And just wait
Just do anything you want to do
Yeah
What does that mean?
Well that means that we were always very polite
Because that's the way we thought
That's how we've been raised in my dear
Exactly
We are polite
In other countries
You'd just say yes
And that's it
You've got a house
You've got a house right
And you say yes
And you
Don't me shit
Doesn't mean you
So now we got it
We finally got it
We got it
But no that's what I mean
We understand
We know the game now
Yeah we got it
So we just go on
We say to people
Okay
If you don't want our offer
We're move on
Yeah
And then they get scared
So
So yes
This is for the Curry Colosseum
Uh-huh
They said yes
Really?
Yes
And how soon can they get the fuck out?
He wants to talk about that
Yeah
Because she's ready to move
Because she already has her
Old people
Apartments somewhere
Wow
That's exciting
And it's only one street away from where we are now
No
This is an exciting move
So far away
Wow
That's great
Yeah
Now we just have to figure out how to legally do it
People fucking hate me here
I have no cloud
Adam who
No
It's
And then you know the Americans with their beautiful stories
And you know
Sometimes you know
Because I always like
Smooth
Talker
Yes exactly
That's what I always do
And then I look at them and they laugh
And I can see they're generally
They generally are humored
Exactly
But there's something behind there
That maybe says
You fucking yank
Yank
Don't you think there's something just hiding
I'm not falling for it
Yeah
You fucked us 250 years ago man
You don't want to trust you
We still don't trust you
But you guys save everybody in the war
So you know
We've got of course
We love you
Why
We love the Americans
Yeah
World War Two
Was definitely
They saved us
They came with the Jew and government
Chocolate and
Haptus
Your mom remembers that right
Yeah
When the liberators drove through
Her parents had a hotel
Oh, I bet she had to
A good time with the GIs
No, they're all third
Uh huh
She was a decent girl
Please
And she always said no
No
Oh please
And she really regrets it now
When those Americans
When they came through after
After kicking everybody's ass
When they came in
They were getting laid
Left and right
Yeah, with her
Chocolate and
Gums and great bodies
The circumcised teenises
Yeah
Oh my gosh
This isn't you
I just actually read in the paper
That
They know now that
It doesn't matter if you have sex
Or not
If you feel you don't want to have sex
Did you know that
Doesn't matter for what
That's healthy
Well, they thought that it's
Very unhealthy
When you don't have sex
You know like when you say to people
Who have no
Relationship
Oh, that's very unhealthy
You should find a boyfriend
It's not good for your body
Well, you have to have sex
No
Of course you do
If you don't have sex
And you're doing
You're occupying your mind
With something else
And you're very busy
And you actually don't think about it
Yeah
That's okay
Yeah, but you have to have sex
Once in a while
Nothing
Because we were talking about
Sex
And I was just reading that
And I thought it was interesting
Because sometimes
You're not thinking about it
You're doing other stuff
So kidding
You know and I say it doesn't matter
If the body doesn't ask for it
It's okay
I think my body is asking for it
Right now
My body is saying
Oh, it's asking
Do you hear it?
Just talking about it
For men
He's already like quick
Pointing
Sometimes
That's it
Hey, dude
So we have a house
We have a house
Oh man
My dog
Now we're stuck
It's a curry colisean
Is that we're going to call it?
Uh
Yeah, it's sort of an empire
Roman
Kind of a Roman look
And I have to say
This time
Although we are in England
We thought we got them
By the most English kind of
In looking house that we can find
Turns out
A lot of the English houses are
Fugly
So shitty
Yeah, especially inside
Yeah
You know
Like Dutch people for example
Think it's very important to do stuff
To your house and make it beautiful
Because it's your home
It's your past
Americans do that well
Very proud of it
Yeah
And here
It's just a place
Yeah, we already talked about it, I guess
Yeah
People like to do other stuff
You know
For as long as everything
You're working in house
Yeah
It's okay
And they're sitting
In houses
There's still 70s
But I think it's also
It's just so expensive to buy a house
Very
Because you have to pay tax
It's a varying scale
If you buy a house over 500,000 pounds
It's 4% tax
And I think
Between
4 and 5 is 3%
And it goes down to 1%
But you still have to pay a percentage
In just tax
And there's no
No, there's no
The ductible
No interest deduction
From your income taxes
Yes
So I think they're happy to get a house
And then they probably all have good intentions
Oh, I'm going to fix this up
I'll change this
We'll do this
We have a little bit of money
We'll do that
And then never happens, of course
Because it never does
It's a lot of money
And we have to do some stuff here too
Before we move in
If it all passes
And we just moved here
And we're not here for such a long time
We had to do a lot of adjustment
And that's not being
That doesn't go over very well
That we have only temporary residency
And not permanent residency
Yeah, yeah
For you
Yeah, absolutely
Absolutely
I'm accepted
Everywhere
Yes, you already
The lady price
And the lady
Yes, that helps
But anyway
This house looks very American
It certainly does
Very American
Yeah, but it's nice though
Isn't it?
I think it looks beautiful
Yeah
We're going to make it even cooler
Yeah, because in London
You see a lot of that empire style
You know, with the little pillars
And this is not too big
Because you know, there's a lot of work
If you have a big house
I know that now
Who wants a big house
Just have a house
That everybody has his
You know, his big house
It's also very easy to buy
There's a lot of them you can buy
Yeah
But it's very interesting
When it comes to selling
Yeah
It's a lot harder
I already explained the chamber
He didn't get it
This is sort of radio show
Sort of
Oh, I'm so terribly sorry
It's very...
Do you want to sauce it?
I thought it
Yeah
You expect to ask you that
Any minute now
But would you like to have a sauce it?
Last night
It was kind of scary last night
All of a sudden Patricia is upright in bed
And she says
The lady Patricia says my chest hurts
Well, there was an elephant standing on her chest
Suddenly in the middle of my sleep
And I know what I was dreaming of
I don't think it was something exciting
Or everything
I think all this stuff is giving you stress
Even though it doesn't feel like stress
Just not knowing stuff
I have this
I know I have the feeling in my stomach
It's like, am I excited?
No, yes
Yes, yes
Exactly
You don't want to be excited
You're almost in the phone rings
I'm like looking at the phone numbers
Like this is the agent
Is this, yes
Somebody wants money
It's not
Crikey, it's a bill collector
Yeah, maybe that's it
Because in my head
I just...
This is funny
I have had those times
I know
I know that
But
Yeah, that could be
In my head
I'm having fun with it
But it's also very irritating
So do you think that that's what the chess pain was
Because it was quite concerning
And I tried to stay asleep
To make sure you weren't dying on me
In fact
You tried to stay asleep
A wake-a-me
Oh
Right now, obviously
But then I actually woke up
Like an hour later
And then I was
And you were really, really still
And I was like, oh man
Yeah
And I was like, what?
Touch my nose and you were warm
What to do with it either
Because when I go to the doctor
But you just went to the doctor for this
Yes
And he said it was the house stream
No
She
And she said
I was probably stressed by it
Without knowing it
Now you know I am a inside stressor
Yes
You wouldn't see anything on the outside
Because I'm so used to being in control
Because everybody's watching
Control
Yeah
Everybody's watching
People are watching on TV
And I'm in control
It's not true
But it's not true
No, of course not
But that's the entertainer lifestyle
That's why
I think so
While entertainer is dying
Almost dying
Yeah
And you're so nervous
But nobody will notice
So maybe I was stressing
And I don't know
I don't know
And
It's still hurt today
It hurts a little bit
Like somebody was running over me a little bit
Yeah
Very strange
But
Don't talk about it
I don't talk about it
I don't want it
No, I understand
And when I wake up
And from this
I was like, oh, leave me alone
Don't do this
I don't want this
You sure you don't want to have that checked?
Well, it's going to be time anyway
In a couple of weeks
And then I have to come and go to the
You sure you don't want it
You don't want to go earlier
No
Maybe maybe no
We have to check
Maybe no
No
Okay
We have a house
We'll have a house
We'll just find out
How long it'll take to get the house
I think we could move pretty fast
Yeah, but
It's not the house that we want
You know, on the inside
We have to do some
No, but we can start the work pretty quickly
And it's only inside work
Mainly so it wouldn't involve outside work
So that could be done even in the winter
Yeah
So
Could be okay
Yeah
Don't you worry, baby
I got it all in the control
I'll take care of it
I saved a couple of voice mail messages
This one
It's a real bummer message
But I figured if anyone could help
It would be the lady Patricia
Adam
Well, it's someone from the world
Calling your show
And I have a real mind
Fuck up in my head at a moment
I was wondering if you plan my comment on your show
And then
So what do you stick about is time to meet?
That's what
Anyway
Here's my problem
I had a sister-in-law
And my sister-in-law is involved
You know, very very heavy
Relationship
It looks like violence
Lots of alcohol
And a lot of
Over and forth
Driving each other with
I don't know what
Issue is just one step up
But
Whatever she goes back to get her stuff
Something's happening
And she's going back to it
I don't get it at all
I'm totally frustrated about this
Nothing I can do or say to make this change
I was wondering if there are people on your show
That have similar things
Or experience similar things
I don't know why
I don't know why she goes back to get her stuff
Every time she goes back to get her stuff
Something's happening
Or experience similar situation
I wonder
Why do I know the people go back
One of my thoughts
Is that could be
And that's why it's actually my big questions
You could be that you get addicted to the bashing
That you go back for
Why don't go for more movies
Stupid
That you go back to someone
Because you're addicted to the violence
I don't get it
Maybe someone in your show
And you can answer that
Well for me
Well of course
There's always someone here who can answer your question
Because no matter what your question is
When it comes to love relationships
And everything of human interaction
The lady Patricia has advice for you
Well I think
I think that
She wants this relationship to work
Probably
But it doesn't
Right
And she wants it actually to work so bad
But it doesn't
Right
So every time she goes back
He probably says
You know I'm going to do
I'm going to be better
I promise baby
Look at my eyes
I will do better
And I'm not going to do that
I'm such an idiot
I'm such an
An asshole
You know they say
Everything to make themselves
Yes I know
I am this
And I'm not going to do it anymore
And you want to believe it
You want to believe it
Because actually there's something in that person
That you really love
Only that other part
You get with it
Well I think the alcohol won't help
That's definitely
And of course the alcohol
They drink both right
Sounds like
Yeah
That of course too
That has to stop
Because otherwise
Because you're not yourself
You know with alcohol
Everybody knows that
You're saying things
And you do things that you usually don't do
Yeah
So that's not good
But so I think there's a part
So what she loves
She loves him
So what can can you do anything to
Break this cycle
No I think she has to do it
She just has to live for a while
And say you have to stop drinking
I don't know what she's drinking
Well he has to stop drinking
And prove that he can do it without alcohol
And then sometimes
You have dinner maybe to get
And see if it works out
But you know
And then start slowly all over again
But dude
I think this is wrong
I think that's so wrong
She cannot go back to it
And if she did not work
And if they stopped seeing each other
For now
Maybe she gets over him
But they need to separate for a while
I think it won't work
I think she needs to make a break
So the brother-in-law is right
And what is the brother-in-law
So that means it's exactly
Exactly
It means it's his brother
If it's his sister-in-law
Oh yeah
Then it's his brother
Who is the abusive one
So maybe he should have a talk with his brother
Okay
And say you know bro
Lay off the booze or something like that
Yeah it's his sister-in-law
Yeah right
But anyway
Yeah they have to separate for a while
Or anything
But they have to just
Stop seeing each other for a while
That's my idea
And maybe we'll never work
I don't know how long they know each other
It won't work
She needs to stop
Don't go back
Yeah
This is bad
You know that I like that
Once I say
I know that's why I'm disagreeing with your advice
I mean you're exactly like
Well you know
But that was younger
I don't know how old she is
I thought differently
You know you still believe that
But when I got older
I thought
I'm not going to waste my time
Exactly
That's the pictures I wanted to tell you
I don't want to waste my time
It's life is beautiful
There's so many nice men
So many nice people
You know go and have a look somewhere else
Markio Shimoda Nemcoff
From Pacifico's Hellway
Potio L.A.
Just Shadow Falls as well
Yeah
He did a thing yesterday
Like his guaranteed method
Do you hear the rain outside?
Yeah
Listen to it
It's rain
It's like a cloud break
Yeah
There's so many women that say
You know I can't I can't find a guy
And he said the sure the sure way
To absolutely get a guy
Is to lower your expectations
Yeah
And I think you know really
Well that isn't it
What we always said to my sister
I'm glad you brought her up
I wasn't going to
She's still things that
She's listening to this show
Yeah sort of James Bond
Will stop in front of a door
Hey
Open up
And then he comes out of his beautiful
Where?
And says is he supposed to?
Asked an asking Martin
Or anything?
I was looking for you
You know
Yeah
It's not going to happen
The thing is any guy will do anything for sex
It probably
No
They'll get married for sex
Absolutely
You just have to lower your expectations
You know what?
And some of these not so good looking guys
They're probably great lovers
And really great guys
Yeah
Probably
True
They are looking me
I mean I'm just smoking mirrors
Yeah
You know that?
It's always happened somewhere
Where you don't expect it
You know
You never know
It comes in
Maybe just walking the store
Now you've got to lower your expectations
And you know what?
My sister doesn't even look anymore
She stopped
She said I'm happy
I'm happy the way
Really?
Because we can look her up
I'm sure that we can find some daily source code guys
Just so much energy
I don't know
She's working
She's very busy
She doesn't have a problem
She says she doesn't feel lonely
So
You know
Alright
She's wonderful
For I think she would make a beautiful
And wonderful
Yeah, I agree
I agree
You know
Okay
I want to talk about Richard Hammond
In a minute
But first we got to play a song
Okay
Because there's Friday
You know people sending shit in
And they expect to play
Okay
Why is this?
You're out there
I'd like to make a motion
To rock this mother out
You're on her
Please don't bang that gavel
You can try this cowbell out
Let's all give a nod
To the hardest work in law here
He's charging time
Yeah
Oh yeah
You're on her
What do you say?
He might even live with this case
He's charging time
Yeah
Oh
He's charging time
Showing now
Yeah
He's charging time
What's up ACs?
The official musical
Just of the Chacha
So
Whoa
The stuff I sensed last week
Didn't hit you
Dude
Dude, this ain't some marketing guy
You're talking to this ain't
Bend over bitch
No man, this is Jersey Todd
But alright, I'll give it to you
I'll give you last week
It was a little flat
I got to send you something new
I got to send you something fresh
I got to reboot
The Jersey Todd portion of the Chacha
And I got something for you
You're not going to find it on the
Potsay music network
But they're coming
We're working on it real hard
I'm sending a billion emails
These people
They've given me an exclusive to play this song
And they told me I can play it on any
Other podcasts that I can find
And I'm playing it today on the daily source code
Yeah, this is something different than you've heard from Jersey Todd
This is the wild bunch
With yeah, yes, stop the bleachers
You're going to like this
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop,
Left to down the ring yet
Sump, Sump, Sump.
The blushers here then make me scared
A brand new sound getting all happened to ear
Anna
Yeah
War
Weear
This is just somethin' different
Make it a blindfold
I wear what an issue makes
racism and body
From this
Somet move the watch
And snake
Everybody in the house, everybody in the park, everybody in the same old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old
old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old older old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old older old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old watch old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old old
Oh, I love that.
Jersey Todd back with the vengeance.
Oh, eat your heart out, black out, Pete.
This is yeah really, that was awesome.
I wish we had a better recording.
That of course was an MP3,
Yeah.
Oh, I love that.
Jersey Todd, back with the vengeance.
Oh, eat your heart out, black out, Pete.
This is yeah, really.
That was awesome.
I wish that we had a better recording.
That was of course, was an MP3.
Yeah.
I've been MP3.
I'm sure, but I bet that sounds awesome on speakers.
That was good, wasn't it?
That was good.
Wild bunch.
It was a good for you.
It was fucking great, baby.
Oh.
Get him on the podcast and music network.
Cheers, Todd.
Yes.
ASAP, dude.
Definitely.
Big, big, huge.
I agree.
I think that could be.
Shh.
It's got everything.
Big.
It does, doesn't it?
Oh, and you know, you're dancing right away.
Even me.
Yeah.
I'm dancing.
I'm the honkyest white guy.
You'll ever see it.
And did you see me dancing?
Yeah.
Booga.
Wow.
It's raining even harder now.
Yeah.
People would think we're in the shower.
Just listen.
Listen.
This is for a second.
It's nice sound, isn't it?
Oh, you can turn your mic.
Professional here.
Yeah.
Thank you for your sound.
Sound Boogie.
Yeah.
Blow up.
I put the mic down a little bit.
Wasn't blow up that movie?
Blow out.
That was it.
Oh, I love them.
Put your mic down just a little bit.
Why?
That's not why my mouth is.
No.
But what you do is you talk on the you look down and then it goes down past the mic.
Oh, okay.
It's now at your nose.
Yeah.
That was not.
So you were.
Saw John Travolta kissing a guy.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
You showed me the picture.
And I said, oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
Yeah.
On the steps.
I bet he'd be really good.
He's one of my favorite actors.
He's really good.
I love him.
Doesn't matter.
I don't care if he wants rough sex with me.
That doesn't matter.
His own business.
I'll have rough sex with John Travolta.
Hey, I have a different sound now.
Yeah.
Because you're talking out of your nose.
No, I'm not.
Yeah.
What did you do?
I don't know what I did.
No, I just moved it later.
It's better now.
Yeah.
Told you.
If you talk into it, it's better.
We wanted to talk about.
Richard Hammond.
Right.
So yes, they already talked about what happened to him.
And everyone knows who he is.
He's one of the, actually they call him hamster here.
He's one of the co-presenters of the BBC's top kids.
He's sort of a Dudley Moore kind of a,
Yeah, Dudley Moore.
That's right.
It vertically challenged.
Yeah.
But this is good.
Hamster is a good description.
Yeah.
Handsome.
And also handsome.
So we crashed in this jet powered car while doing,
I think about 280 miles an hour.
Test drive.
For the TV show.
Yeah.
And so now what they're saying.
More money.
More money from you man.
It's a charity.
I'll call her back.
Okay.
Where was I?
Test drive.
You're right.
So this, you have to imagine dragster.
It flipped upside down.
And you know, your head is basically in a roll bar cage.
Okay.
But that dragged through the grass upside down.
So he got, you know, his face was basically being impacted by dirt and anything else
that was being, you know, shoved into his face.
God.
So they say has a serious brain injury?
Yes.
And they, and they don't know whether he'll recover fully from that.
Yeah.
You know, you never know with brains.
That's what it said in the paper.
It's horrible because it's such a blow.
I heard that it actually happened to Lady die.
It's such a blow that your brains are shaking in your skull.
Of course.
You know.
And so the brain gets a blow, too.
And he's in a different position.
I'm sorry.
I see that I bought the name.
And I'm speaking Dutch to his banker.
Very important right now, of course, for the, for the house.
Yeah.
He's really building something for him.
See?
Oh.
Isn't it amazing?
It just keeps on raining.
It's about them bringing me money.
Yeah, that's good.
That's good.
Bring the money.
So yeah.
So probably his, his brain, you know, had a huge blow.
Yeah.
Well, as I said yesterday, it's not speed that kills.
It's lack of speed that kills.
Yeah.
And you need to be a pilot, actually.
Well, they call it a pilot.
Yeah.
It doesn't mean you have, I mean the, yeah.
Because you have to actually, because it wants to go up.
Of course.
It's 280 miles an hour.
You can fly.
Go so fast.
I mean, we fly at 60 miles an hour.
That's when we take off.
Yeah.
So you have to keep the car down.
Oh, yeah.
No, how to do that.
And he had was no experience.
Well, so the conversation I had, or what I talked about yesterday is.
I've done a lot of really life-threatening things for television.
Yes.
And, you know, a lot of people would say immediately, well, you know, you just
want to do these dangerous things just to be famous or a star or whatever.
But that's really, it's really not what it is.
What happens is you get some kind of almost invincible feeling.
Yeah.
You know, like, I mean, you've done things, too, that, that have, for, for
television or in show business.
And I'm sure have not been the safest.
Terrified.
Yeah.
I've repelled down from the, a hoi, you know, huge stadium in, in Rotterdam.
I've, I've, I've done tons and tons of helicopter trips with.
Of course.
And as a senior, sometimes you have to stand somewhere up very high.
Yeah.
So start over there.
Understand.
Yeah.
Down to stairs.
You know, there are builds just in a couple of hours.
So they're not the good stairs.
And I, and you think, you know, while you're seeing a look in the camera.
Yeah.
So, so.
Very dangerous.
Why do we do that?
Why do we do this?
Why do you think you have to do that?
But you don't actually.
But what is it?
What, I mean, because it just, it builds up and it builds up.
And it, remember Kevin Celius through sporting fool, the same thing.
Yeah.
The craziest, the craziest things.
Well, once you did a couple of things, you think that nothing will, will happen.
You're okay.
You know what you're doing.
I mean, all those, um, celebrity races I've participated in.
Yeah.
That was some serious stuff.
And he's not racing guy.
He's not, you know.
Of course not.
But I mean, all you have to do is.
He's a TV presenter.
Why does he think he can do that?
Well, that's when I'm asking you.
What is it?
I don't know.
Well, no fear.
Interesting.
And then I see those little too lovely two kids that he has.
Two years old and I say, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Yeah.
Be beautiful.
And I think don't you think about it?
So have you ever been worried when I went off to do stuff?
Of course.
Really?
Yeah, of course.
Do you remember anytime you were actually.
Every time you fly.
Well, besides the flying.
But I mean, other stuff.
I've been there.
And think my husband is hanging there somewhere in the air.
Really?
Yeah.
Sometimes I sit behind you and I think, what the hell am I doing?
Really?
Why?
I'm sitting here in a little tiny chair.
I'm hanging somewhere in the air.
You know, you think there's actually nothing there on the need.
You don't want to think about it.
You know?
Okay.
But I mean, besides that, I mean.
People do that.
You know.
And once you do these things.
You hang on anything.
I've seen you in the air.
And you take your camera with you.
You know, you just do it.
You're not afraid.
No.
But you know, something like this happens.
I'm like, wow, man.
There's a lot of things.
Like going to Iraq.
That was another thing.
I didn't have to do it.
There was no reason to do it.
Other than I wanted to do it.
That also could have obviously had been potentially dangerous.
We worried when we were in Iraq.
Yeah.
I know.
Where are you?
What?
Anything can happen.
Anything.
Why would it happen to somebody else and not you?
And then.
And then only one time something really happened.
That was the motorcycle.
And you know that.
Yeah.
And you know when you do that's what I want to say.
And you know when you do all these things.
That will be one day.
Did something will happen.
And thank for and be very thankful that.
Yeah.
I think I got lucky.
You got lucky.
Yeah.
I remember we came back because we had flown the helicopter there.
And then we came back.
I couldn't actually even fly the helicopter.
And you still feel you back.
Oh yeah.
Absolutely.
Oh definitely.
Yeah.
It's been two years ago.
Oh you back.
Three years ago almost.
People.
Human beings are so fragile.
Yeah.
Just worthless pieces.
Skin and bone shit.
Nicks.
Nucks.
All right.
Let's do some happy for a second.
Yeah.
Hi Adam.
This is Tom from the Parkview podcast.
And I thought I'd relate something to you that happened a while back.
You had mentioned before about butterflies in your mom.
And I always associate your mom.
Now when I see butterflies.
Well, it's not running about a week back.
And I was doing one of my long runs.
Kind of about a mile into my run.
I was listening to the Daily Source Code.
You and Patricia were on talking.
And I know the sister fly started.
She's running with me.
She's tagging along.
And this one was kind of odd because it actually stayed with me as I was running.
And it probably stayed with me for about a mile and a half.
And just kind of fluttering around.
And almost like it was, he's dropping on the conversation.
Or at least keeping me company.
And then after about a mile and a half, it decided to take off.
But it did remind me of your mom.
And I thought I was kind of spitting that I was listening to.
You have Drish Talk.
Yeah.
And I don't know what the subject was about.
But it was almost like the butterfly was there.
And kind of listening in and giving it a lot of approval.
And then taking off.
Isn't it nice?
That's so nice.
Yeah.
I think those things.
I've got 25 of these people sending that in saying that they've had similar butterfly experiences.
Yeah.
Suddenly you, you know, sometimes they just lend on you.
And they sit on you and I think, wow.
And then you think about your mom.
Well, yeah.
That's what my mom always said.
So if you chase a butterfly, you can never catch it.
But if you just sit down.
It'll sit down in your shoulder.
Yeah.
It's just sit with you.
True.
So that's nice because you always remember your mom.
Yeah.
So actually once a year, at least when the butterfly's around.
And when the butterfly's around.
And now we are.
Sometimes you see butterflies in magazines everywhere.
True.
It doesn't stop.
It's almost like a Jamaican tropical rain.
That rain is actually stronger and better than our shower.
I wish it was this strong.
This is a power shower.
Once you go outside and take a shower.
Yeah.
Let me film it for my video show.
Come on.
That'd be awesome, dude.
Are you going to think else?
Are you going to give anything else?
Well, I'll play one more song.
Okay.
And then we'll go back.
Yeah.
This is kind of interesting.
I can't remember who recommended this.
But I heard it and it kind of goes with the weather.
Don't be late for the rest of your life.
I'm not a butterfly.
You have a chicken up.
But every day I'm learning.
The dreams were met for fools.
It's all in some disco.
No one ever wants to serve it.
We're here.
So don't beg for the rest of your life.
This train leaves the tent.
So you have to do this side.
You're still telling what time I'm all right.
So don't beg for the rest of your life.
You're alive.
Of course you was a child.
But that crooked smile.
She kept everyone waiting.
Until there was no one.
But that needed some.
And he was always overstated.
So don't beg for the rest of your life.
Because more than it comes quickly.
In the blink of an eye.
This pretend my day will die.
So don't beg for the rest of your life.
For your expectation.
I've thrown them away.
You need for compassion.
With this nothing.
So don't beg for the rest of your life.
It's a goal to make all the rest of the rest of the rest of your life.
How American is that?
From Omaha, Nebraska, anonymous American, don't be late for the rest of your life.
It's been Wayne's World podcast.
You like it?
Yeah, it was nice, wasn't it?
That was very nice.
I'd read a little bit.
It's almost done.
I'm sure you looked like you had something to say there.
Well, there was something that just keeps on popping into my mind.
Okay, here it comes.
Um, should you let your teenager have a sleepover with her boyfriend?
I know.
Well, I don't think we're going to get the answer in time.
Because it's, uh, is it tonight?
See, they're going to, if they want to do it, they're going to do it anyway.
That's what I always have.
Let's just back up for a second.
This is, you or me, that's you.
So this is, uh, Liam, who now has an apartment.
No, not a apartment.
We call an apartment.
Well, no, he has a room, his own place.
He's going to Gilford University, which, of course, is good.
I encourage that.
And he's in studying political sciences.
That's good.
He's for reasons why have to say.
Yeah, he's still 21.
He is.
But for an English bloke, the drinking seems to be under control.
No, he's not drinking anymore.
He stopped for Christina.
He stopped completely.
Well, he, she said, you can have two drinks a day.
That's it.
Because we don't like it.
We curse.
Really?
He said that.
You didn't tell me this.
I didn't get it.
He just told me.
Really?
Yeah, she said, don't like it.
Although, you know, he's not drunk or anything.
But she doesn't like it.
But he is responsible.
He, he does look after her and do appreciate that.
Yes.
And, uh, and he, actually, we found out that he, so far, we think that he's a very nice guy.
Yeah, he is.
He's still fucking 21, you know?
He's like that really bothers me.
He's very sweet.
Yeah, but it's still bothers me.
Yeah.
He's a young 21 year old.
But, you know, you know, so Christina said,
are I going to stay at Liam's house Friday night?
Yep, I'm going to go out and then maybe stays.
Is it going to go out too?
Well, no, I think the idea of a romantic dinner at home is, is okay with me.
But we're going to go out and then, and then we're going to go out.
No, they're going to go to coffee shop.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Or maybe a movie, I don't know.
Or maybe they're going to watch a movie?
So anyway, so first of all, she's legal.
So she can do it, you know, she can do whatever she wants in this country, at least she's legal.
And not legal for me.
Yeah, and I think you're right, you know.
They're going to do it anyway.
And every time we said, okay, so that's, you know, uh,
I just, you say your boyfriend, you know, okay, and then was over.
Yeah, I guess what I'm worried about is I just don't want to become a habit.
I just don't want it to be staying over there more and more and more and more.
No, I said he's uh, uh, he's welcoming our house.
And he did, because I, you know, I've been sleeping in the, in the guest bedroom.
That's it, but um, yeah, you know.
So how do you feel then?
Actually, I, um, not bad, you know, it's different times.
And, um, as I said, if they want to do it, they do it anyway.
And, you know, better in a very relaxed, at a normal.
Well, make sure she knows that if she, at any point, at any time wants me to come pick her up, I will.
Yeah, we have to sell it.
Even if it's the middle of the night.
She wants to come home.
Yeah, not a problem.
We're there.
No questions asked.
No.
Okay.
I think I'm going to go slip my wrist now.
Hang yourself.
I think so.
I think it's time.
I got a question as very mature.
I'm very intelligent, you know, I believe, I believe in her.
I got to go call Bruce.
Yeah.
Okay, baby.
Thank you.
Well, you're welcome.
Football Friday.
Yeah.
Football to you.
Okay.
You know, football to you too.
Yeah.
Football me.
Okay, honey.
Uh, we have a date tonight.
Oh, yeah, we can go out.
You make a reservation?
Yes, I will.
So that is, that is kind of an upside-down.
Well, I said, let's wait.
What's going to, what's going to happen with the house?
Yeah.
Well, that sounds like a plus.
I think we can celebrate.
We can celebrate.
Okay.
Exactly.
Sushi.
And would she like to be the elephant tonight?
And stand all my friends.
Standing your chest?
Might, might trunk mine.
You're in the face.
All right.
Yes, you got a date.
Okay.
I love you, baby.
Love you, too.
Get this podcast and more great ones like you.
On the high performance podcast delivery network from Pod Show and Limelight Networks.
I love it.