This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want to hear content with badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta's Yeracharly 372.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
You gotta get angry.
You gotta get me.
That's the only way you can play.
I guess I'm not really an angry person.
You're an angry now.
And you as per sit in my ear.
Those amazing works I never thought I had.
And she said,
Just close your eyes.
Lay our hands out.
And let your friends see us stay.
All of them now, because I can take you over this down tonight.
On my magic cup, it's all on time.
I'll take you away from the rising light.
The places you've never ever been before.
As we passed in your bonestar,
But she said,
You remember to sew,
Stroke back with feels.
That I'll sweat all the dreams.
And I'm dead in the ceiling like red
Who we played, I didn't see.
And she said,
Just close your eyes.
Lay our hands out.
And let your friends see us stay.
All of them now, because I can take you over this down tonight.
On my magic cup, it's all on time.
I'll take you away from the rising light.
The places you've never ever been before.
And I'm dead in the ceiling like red.
Just close your eyes.
Lay our hands out.
Let your friends see us stay.
All of them now, and I'll take you over this down tonight.
On my magic cup, it's all on time.
I'll take you over the rising light.
I'll take you over now,
I'll take you over this down tonight.
On my magic cup, it's all on time.
I'll take you away from the rising light.
The places you've never ever been before.
And I'm dead in the ceiling like red.
Just close your eyes.
I was on television in the Netherlands and people project their baggage on to me with great
frequency and certainly in the last two years with podcasting, words are scrutinized, things
are, are looked at over and over again and people always love to post and start flame wars
and I rarely ever get into them because well with the written word, I really can't win.
I'm no good at it, but when you get into my realm into the realm of audio entertainment,
you get into podcasting, and particularly when you accuse me of bigotry, then I'm going
to respond to it and I've been thinking about, in fact, I didn't even sleep well last night
because of what I heard yesterday on Madge Weinstein's yeast radio episode number 366.
I actually tried to, excuse me, I actually tried to hook up with Madge for a Skype call
to discuss this, but I guess Madge was somewhere in hotel and was checking out and was traveling
so it didn't work, but maybe that's actually better because now I've had some time to collect
my thoughts, there's an eight-minute rant at the beginning of this yeast radio episode which
really hurt me and it's so incredibly stupid in my mind that I almost, for a couple of
minutes, I've actually thought, wow, maybe this is just the publicity stunt, I mean it's
so lame and so off-target, particularly for me, my background as you know is I grew up in Amsterdam,
which is the Netherlands, one of the most tolerant societies in the world of multicultural,
multicultural, multilingual society and everyone just lets everybody else kind of live and
do what they do and I've always been that way and I've never, and by the way a country that
is dealt with horrible, horrible, bigotry and prejudice in the past 50 years think of the
second world war and how many Dutch Jews were annihilated, shipped off to concentration camps.
So I grew up with very clear values, not just instilled by my parents but instilled by the culture
of the country. So for someone to call me a bigot, now you really, you really get my blood boiling.
So that said, I have to preface what you're about to hear and the rest of the show with the fact
that it is a total exercise in freedom of speech and you will hear some very profound things
and some very profane things and I think those two often go hand in hand which is probably
why I get them mixed up all the time and I've done my homework and done a little bit of research
and let's see if we can get to the bottom of this and then hopefully move on after that because
I'll accept a lot of things but I will not accept the label of a bigot or someone who discriminates
based upon anyone's features, beliefs, heritage, etc. Okay so this is and actually I was very unaware
that this was a huge issue but apparently it is a huge issue until I do listen to you know
you know I listened to as many podcasts as possible and I listened to yeast radio yesterday
which started off like this. Imagine seeing a hair coming to you from the car, a Chevy Cavalier,
with a license plate in the front that says freedom. Never forget 9 11 with an American
plant flag and a lesbian. My name is Bad Weinstein this is serious. I was one or two and he's
radio dot com and I'm very angry today. I'm angry because my boss Ampery allows
they get into homophobics ridiculous statements on his show. Okay I'm going to stop right here
because I do want to set the stage properly because I'm going to be as I always am completely open
and honest and to start off Mad Weinstein you're not honest your name is Richard Bluestein you are a
white male and from what you've told me you're a homosexual white male and you are not a woman
you are not a lesbian in fact when I first heard Mad Weinstein and this is some big confusion as well
when I first heard Mad Weinstein in January of 2005 I was elated. I was so happy because here was
I was listening to someone in those early shows which I think were the best that has ever been
produced for East Radio. I truly believed here was a transgendered man from Chicago or a trans
sexual or transvestite but anyway very clearly someone who has a recognizable type of
self image who was just angry and pissed off and I really really enjoyed listening to that and I was
completely dismayed when I found that was where some confusion came in the register of all places
was so stupid to think that I didn't understand that Mad wasn't really a woman no I thought that
this was truly a transvestite a transgendered person who was just angry at the world and venting
on a podcast okay but when I found out that it's all an act because Richard Bluestein is a very
nice, very calm almost introverted person when you meet him face to face so just so you know that
this is a lie to start off with that Mad Weinstein is not a lesbian is not a woman
and I found out from Mrs. Slokum because he heard the show before me she whatever her it
that Adam's curry played this promo for some idiots that that referred to exam as a bunch of
faggots okay so before we go any further let's go back to daily source code episode 3-6-9
and listen to this is the second time I've played the promo actually this promo was first played
a couple months ago and I didn't catch it then and nothing really nothing really offended me then
although the second time I heard it and you'll actually hear this because I'm not just going to
play the promo I'm going to play a clip from the actual the hell was that stop it I'm angry over here
I'm going to play you a I'm going to so I'm going to play you this clip that
well you'll actually hear what I respond to because I cracked the microphone when I heard something
about fucking the guy at the ass or whatever it was and was like whoa you know that I hadn't actually
caught that one before and I heard nothing at all wrong with what was being said let's listen to it
and you listen in and then we'll talk about that in a second and we'll continue with Mad just
see you there
it's a me on the baby countdown I'm out now top one two with three I'm going to take that spot now
where you can drive down the jigsaw radio to be specific and I'll add to nature if you want to
come get it you're the best how you say yeah I'm serious when my fucking bag is that next
little I think you'll be in some line so there you go fuck this the faggot's at xm
now I believe that what the guys from hood hype who are not idiots by the way I think they do
a fantastic show and it's very difficult for a R&B in hip-hop to get played on the radio
outside of all the bubblegum crap that is being plugged day in day out but this was not
derogatory towards homosexuals this is a use of a word in the same way Mad Weinstein
the Richard Bluestein that you use the word Kant and I would never ever use the word Kant
directed towards a woman or a group of women and nor would you or should you so I think it's
there if all of xm was one group of homosexuals then I would have said well wait a minute that's
a problem but now it's being now there's a term being used which by the way I had no idea and
that's unfortunate that this is how we have to have this conversation I had no idea that that was deemed
a very offensive word I can understand if I said to someone who's gay I said hey you fag
but this is I think there's a distinct difference and of course as we get into this I'd really
like to know what is okay and what is not okay are we allowed to say queer are we allowed to say
queen or we allowed to say light-footed you know what what are we allowed to say if we are talking
about homosexuals should we say homosexuals should we say gay you really got to educate me on this
topic okay so I didn't respond to that because this is clearly the guys at Hood Hype saying
serious rocks xm sucks and this is just the way they happen to say it and I didn't pick up on it in
fact I did pick up on something I did find it maybe a little bit offensive for someone to listen
you'll hear me respond to that here okay and by the way as hip-hop lyrics go I have heard a lot
worse now when you use the word republican I think that is derogatory and in fact I think the
continuous use of that word match wine scene creates an even wider divide that we in the united
states then we have already between democrats republicans red states blue states that's actually
calling someone a name based upon what they are and xm is obviously not a satellite station full of homosexuals
okay so to take this to the extreme extreme and saying that I'm allowing bigots to a promo
and idiots I'm among idiots by the way you're calling them idiots to promo something that is
bigotry on my show is just wrong okay it's just wrong now I do understand your point if it's offensive okay
and when people say hey I was offended by that I always respond in the same manner we'll get to that in a
second let's continue now and then so I thought well that's terrible and then I'm turning on
listening to Howard Stern Howard Stern every other word is fact fact fact and Howard talks about how
gay people should get married all the time he clearly clearly knows supports supports gay people
in terms of his I think his intention is actions but you know when you just use it
fact to uh to uh insult you know anyone like the all your derogatory word kind of like I use
kind right that refers to my hatred of women right okay so you actually are coming out and saying
you hate women and you don't really Richard it's your act okay this is the magic act that you hate
women and that's why you call them cons and because it's an act which by the way I don't always find
funny it seems to be okay all right and by the way the fact that you bring Howard Stern and
to this really started to convince me that you actually were doing this just to get some kind of
publicity going or some kind of controversy uh hopefully and I know that you're a Howard wannabe
I've seen you do a time and time again unsuccessfully I've seen you even bring in a black woman
to be your co-host trying to get a Robin Quiver's type of vibe so that's the only thing I could think
there now um you compliment Howard on his actions and uh you don't do that with me I'm not looking
for any compliments I'm not looking for uh for any uh any pets on the shoulder but please please don't
tell me that my actions haven't proven that I'm anything but a bigot that I'm anything but prejudice
and then I don't care about anyone what they say what they do who they have sex with how they
have sex in their private lives I don't care I have consistently given the gay community the same
access to everything that pod show has to offer everything that I personally have to offer okay
you don't mention that but I do sign your check and I actually don't sign your check and that's another
point I really despise the lie that I am your boss I am not your boss you know damn well what our
relationship is this is the same with every single podcast and every producer of a podcast every podcast
that we have a deal with I am not your boss I cannot tell you what to do I cannot kick you off the
network so to position me as I'm your boss and ooh boy aren't you the really big man now because
you're going against the man you're going I'm not your boss okay and you know it so that's bullshit
but that doesn't work because I am a woman and I am a lesbian you see how that works
how it turns out is it white male Adam Curry white male Richard bluestine white male okay
you don't know if I'm gay you don't know if I'm bisexual you don't know if I like being fucked
up the ass you don't know that I just mind I'm 41 years old I think have been around the block I
think I know what life has to offer I think I've explored the limits of my sexuality I don't need
to exploit that for a laugh like you do so yeah and they excuse that you don't listen to your
own show sorry that doesn't hold water anymore you used that one before but the cancer shit
excuse me this is two very different things I never said I don't listen to my own show I said I
hadn't previewed the cancer the promo where a joke was made about cancer I could have easily
not aired that show we went through that before this is something completely different and I
stand behind the promo from hood hype I stand behind it because it is something completely different
now let me just see if he talks about Mr. Slokham here so you know what and you wonder why you
now okay so I did get exactly one email about this from I guess Jeffrey Taylor is Mrs. Slokham
and it's not a long email it's one paragraph I'm gonna read it to you right now Jeffrey Taylor says
and it sent to me and copied to bloated lesbian at gmail.com mages email address
disappointing that you let the fuck the faggots at xm comment from hood hype promo flot pormo flies
as pormo atom the context of the epitets usage promotes anti-gay hate speech and perpetuates the
notion that faggot is an okay pejorative the national mental health association estimates that high
school students in the US here degrading words like faggots 26 times a day and contributing to
the culture of having faggot be the ultimate insult in US youth and urban culture also contributes
to the thousands of suicides by marginalized kids each year I request that you address what may have
been a careless mistake saying shit like that is not okay at all so I responded sorry
didn't even hear that part sorry I didn't hear anything derogatory and to say I mean what pedestal are
you putting yourself on here look at the world around you there are kids who are killing themselves
by throwing up every day because of magazines that project an image of what they should be
young girls are starving themselves to death we have hundreds of thousands of kids who are
fucking homeless who have no parents do you have one did you adopt a kid today to save them
oh no we're going to go on a little faggot rant against the pod father the boss
that really really tick me off and it's bullshit because it wasn't used in a derogatory fashion
in a derogatory way towards homeless sexual's it's a fucking word okay it's a word
that's gonna eat this that show why don't gay people listen to uh Richard you don't know
of gay people listen to my show you don't know that and I don't care who listens to my show
and if the bothers you don't listen and I do not wonder why I didn't I never said on eat this
hot show which was a stupid interview which was insulting to me because all that could come out
of the mouths of the three-part people who were interviewing me on the show was do I take it up the
ass who would I fuck who would I kill who would I marry why haven't keeping the girl been
signed a pod show really intellectual guys too I had him carries part whatever that thing is
silly source code well maybe it's because they don't want to be called a fucking faggot like they
did when they were in fucking eighth grade asshole okay who's the asshole here have you
listened to your own show do you wonder why you're not making a dent politically which you'd love
to do because you keep calling republicans republicans the language that comes out of your mouth
is atrocious and it's directed specifically at the people who you're trying to put down unlike
what I did here you know and I'm just sick of it not listening to how it I'm listening everything
and I like how it but it's like why does every other word have to be faggot faggot you know
I don't give a shit how famous you are whatever there's that's just shallow eight per behavior
so I have a question for Adam per ever quest for our certain which is what is the difference
between calling somebody a faggot and calling somebody a nigger or a chink or a cike
or calling someone a cunt what's the difference explain it to me why is it okay
to call somebody a fag or a faggot but it's not okay to call a black person a nigger or a
Chinese person a chink I'll tell you why I'll tell you what the difference is okay
because there is no difference if you're black it's okay to say nigger have you not noticed that
if you're gay it's okay to say faggot and you do it all the time
Kanye West she's a gold digger the the biggest in your face example
of this this crazy ass position we've gotten ourselves into of political correctness
about what you can and what you can't say crap I miss the fucking satellite window sorry pdob you'll
have to edit that somehow so we had a sanitized version she ain't nothing but a gold digger
she ain't she ain't going with it broke broke broke no the actual lyric was broke nigger and it was
played in cars all over the fucking place played in clubs but no on the radio then all of a sudden
you have to we have to be politically correct sorry did uh actually I found another comment
from zilla fag okay there's a podcast out there who was I believe a member of Q Potter
called zilla fag zilla fag okay what are you trying to tell me here
here's the comment Adam it was not at all cool playing the piece from the SL hood hype dot com
the f-c-k the f-a-o-t-s from part of that clip was not only insulting it plain pissed me off
I hope the big wigs that you wanted to hear that are not at all impressed as I am just angry from zilla fag
who sent me an email on November 15th 2005 from zilla fag subject pod save music from a
faggot it's such a cool band and show oh man I would not send you this if it didn't kick ass love
the pod save band and of course my shit okay so I'm drunk glad to land and save and love you
and baby ooh what is the wife's name zilla fag again the subject message of this email
pod save music from a faggot it's such a cool band and show so I pulled the show up listen to this show
okay this fucking zilla fag zilla cast is all a good be music motherfuckers yeah I know yeah
I'm doing a music cast god dammit I never thought I'd do this shit but fuck it and it's pod save
motherfuckers so fuck you and you goddamn record company bastard motherfuckers trying to tell us what
the fuck we can listen oh this is really good this is really intelligent okay you're not going to call
everyone in the music industry a motherfucker it's in two because we have to pay you shit all kinds of
fucking money and you're all a bunch yeah hold on let me go shit yeah the fucker is yeah check this out
crap here we go okay motherfuckers that's the end of the show it's kind of like a point 22
blow job thing going on because motherfuckers putting out some good fucking shit it's very original
very fucking diverse very fucking excellent shit motherfuckers need to be put out into the world and
that's what the fuck I'm doing I'm promoting the shit all these bitches and I'd suck their dicks as long
as they are cut you know I'm sorry I don't like uncut caught all right so you know now you're
insulting people who have a forcekin you know and if and if you truly want to be taken seriously
clean up your own fucking act first will ya I'd like to know the answer to that and why you're
ready you can ask so why is it okay for homosexuals to call each other clean queer fag why is that okay
why is it not okay for me to say that even if I'm not directing it towards homosexuals what is your
fucking problem mark talk of already lempo of very funny now we're going to make fun of somebody's name
and it's one thing to do it as a joke but this is not a laughing matter Richard and you can ask
made a very let's say an artistic skits about to chopping men's dicks off when they're in the glory hole
that's hands in addition to getting it as furry as by calling that a period big herd fag now that
is so incredibly unfair of you to say that mark you're motor nemcalf quote got to where he is
by calling me a big herd fag which by the way we've been going on with this joke for quite a while
never heard a peep from anyone because you don't think I'm gay you don't think I'm homosexual you don't
think I'm bisexual you don't think that I might have any kind of kinky things going on it might be
offended by the word fag you know what I'm not you can call me anything you will sticks and
stones will break my bones and I've been called a la hell of a lot worse in print on
dignation with wiki pedia people have said the most hurtful things I have to give you some credit
there magic you did come to my defense but not for all the nasty things that people said and mark
Yoshimoto Namco is a very very talented writer very talented performer and I happen to think he's
very funny and has nothing to do with his big-haired fag comment getting him to where he is it's
because we came up with a business relationship a business deal just like you and I know different
whatsoever you know there is a difference he actually makes me laugh yeah I'm just thinking
here in that word fucking everywhere you know what I mean it's a fucking word and if you're going to
do it then I want to hear you say nigger I want to hear you say spick I want to hear you insult
every single race now why do you have to push that on me why do you have to push your
thinking on to everybody else you've done this before and privately we've had this conversation
Richard we had this conversation where you said I want to have Steve Webb from life spring on my podcast
but I'm going to make a deal with him the deal is he has to he has to say I'm sorry I shouldn't do the
voice he has to say that gay people can get married under the eyes of God and I said to you I said why
you do that why do you want to force your lifestyle on somebody else he's not forcing his lifestyle
on you in fact Steve Webb who sent in a very civil comment to me about using Jesus Christ
in in what he felt were inappropriate matters we had a real conversation about it you know
not just all this hatred that you're spewing all of a sudden and I'm so pissed off we had a civil
conversation but he didn't try to force his religion on me he only said hey you know this is what I feel
about it and guess what we didn't have Muslims sending in comments saying well this is fucked up
shit oh you're doing his promoting Christianity didn't have any Jewish people sending comments in
saying well that's fucked up no it seems to come from the same place time and time again like you're
so fucking underprivileged will you're not you're a white male living in America you should be happy
and proud and color preference and all that shit because I or explain to me why it's okay
to say Fag and Fag at every five seconds I don't say it every five seconds you're trying to get
on the Howard Stern show is what you're trying to do and it's pathetic which results in that kind of hate
I disagree I totally disagree by the way Richard you're overweight you're fat I think that
people being called fat as a kid is a hell of a lot worse and causes a lot more damage than being
called a Fag in the eighth grade when you might not even know what the fucking word means and there are
kids who kill themselves all the time mainly because their parents are assholes results in thousands
of kids that kill themselves every year not to mention the fact that in some countries other people
kill take care of that for you oh okay right so now what are going to do we're going to
equate our society to other countries where they kill homosexuals and it's not just homosexuals
by the way they kill Christians they kill Jews you're not alone in this you don't have like some
kind of special little everyone hates me club except for the one that exists in your mind get over
it like our occupied or act like a ran where people get hung literally for being gay yeah I'm
fucking sick of it now we're taking it just too far I don't give a shit who you are if you're my fucking
boss so see now there you go again trying to be the big man I'm not your boss don't lie tell the truth
tell everyone what our arrangement is I can't tell you what to do in your show I can't stop you
from putting anything in your show I can't stop you from publishing anything in your show I am not your boss
it's a lie it's a fucking lie and it really that really pisses me off you're full of shit whatever it's
bullshit it is total fucking bullshit why am I saying this on my show because I want to get it played that's
yeah you know what there you go there's another clue
nudge Weinstein is sent in several audio comments that I thought were so unfunny just not fucking funny
that I didn't plan so I think that you're upset and worried that I wouldn't address the issue
and that's why you put it on yeast radio and lie about things about me being your boss you're not a big
a big you are big get big imploded but you're not all of a sudden fucking super here on ooo look at how
dangerous this is look at this look at the high stakes on playing uh uh not true no I don't like it
because they're usually not funny what I like is the pissed off match this is actually a very good
example I really do like it when you're pissed off and I really do like it when you go off in the
rant and you're one trick pony that's what you do best give up all the rest okay give up the
Florence night and gale bit give up trying to be Howard Stern give up trying to be funny and video
because you're not your one trick and your one trick is good and stick to it uh now again I have
controversy on my show but it's probably why don't I I am not at all about controversy on my show okay
that's the way you think and you're trying to put your baggage onto me because that is exactly what's
happening here you want the controversy because you want to have the attention which is so
typical for you okay well I played it for a second he didn't even hear that comment give me a
fucking break I did not hear a bigot comment I did not hear bigotry I heard people just talking
okay not directed towards homosexuals if Hood Hype had said those faggot's a cue potter
I never would have played it never you know you just insulted people do you realize that oh
but it's okay I guess right if you're gay then you're allowed to insult other people
you I mean you started using the word nigger you started using the word chink what happened to
you you forgot that one kike spick what happened to all that oh because you're in some kind of
quote minority which I don't believe I think there's a hell of a lot more gay people who are afraid
afraid to come out because of this because they don't want to be represented by assholes like you
somebody's been calling them a faggot fuck that bullshit all you had to do was say you know I'm not
really comfortable with that word would you take that into consideration instead you call me a bigot
which I'm not and you know it and fuck words my actions speak for themselves and you should address those
you know and then you apologize for saying Jesus Christ as your friend radios I've been
oh no I'm not afraid I'm going to offend Steve Webb and you clearly have some bug up
your ass about that because someone else believes that same sex partner shouldn't get married
under the eyes of God and you have a problem with it you can't seem to handle it that's what that's
about I don't care if I offend Steve Webb I care if people say to me hey you know I have an issue
with that and I'm a listener of the show I'm working up a sweat here you know I thought to
ask you know that is such fucking bullshit so you wonder why people don't listen to deli so
no I don't wonder why people don't listen to daily source code and it's a lie the numbers continue to
increase okay and clearly you're listening clearly Zilla Fag is listening clearly Mrs. Slokham is
listening they're not tuning out they're tuning in so I've never said I wonder why no I said
why don't queue potters send me promos that's what I wondered okay nothing more nothing
let's go back and listen to the show I've never wondered about any group based upon
background heritage race religion or sexual preference if they listen to my show or not I mean
that's what podcasting is about I'll say what I want I say and I say it from the heart
all the time I never hold back certainly not in this case no they said me promos they suck
most of the promos are so stupid and so full of stupid language that I don't want to
offend the rest of the world with the idiocy that I get sent as promos once in a while they're okay
but here's an example magic you send me a nice little bit and talk about the golden tick and
then all of a sudden oh no I have a golden shower for you ha ha ha ha ha ha I don't need anyone
to kiss my ass unless I request it and I've had my ass kissed in a sexual fashion I really didn't
joy it I'll have you know our faces or our ears I don't know it doesn't work that
fucking way does it so you know just be equal if you're gonna say fact good fine say fact
but I want to hear nigger I want to hear a chink I want to hear a spit and I want to hear
some way to insult white people this is so stupid this is so incredibly stupid do you hear
yourself do you hear yourself and I want to hear that I want to hear it all yeah well you use
that all the time particularly directed towards women who you just said you hate you hate you hate
now do I really believe you hate women now probably not but you're so frustrated so
first and I know where this is coming from you are frustrated because you don't have the success
you feel you deserve and I've heard this before there was a big conversation a big thread
in the Q-Potter community why don't gay actors get to play the role of gay people in movies
because they're talented as nothing to do with whether they're gay or not it's because they're
talented capital T okay all of it's every and so or not at all or you can just explain to me
why saying faggot is okay it may be it's not derogatory but let's hear your argument maybe you
have one okay what I want to hear from you as first of all I'm going to restate it again
in this case this was not derogatory towards homosexuals you tell me what words are okay match
is it okay to use faggot if I'm talking amongst faggot's who are friends
like zilifag said potsay music from a faggot is it okay to say queer is it okay to say queen
is it okay to say gay tell me what can I say what will not offend you have a decent normal
conversation with me will ya but I think it's fucking bullshit you know and I think this gay people
we need to stand up for ourselves every fucking time people try to marginalize us no I did not
marginalize you my action speak exactly to the contrary I've done everything but try to marginalize
quite the opposite I've given you the exact same access the exact same resources the exact same
respect that anyone else gets from me anywhere in private life or in business life
because it's not fair yeah you can we can entertain you with our queer eye for the fucking
I don't watch queer eye for the fucking straight guy I'm not interested in that show
it doesn't entertain me at all I don't watch gay themed entertainment because it's funny because
it's gay I don't do that your problem is with Hollywood baby it's fucking Hollywood it's
get over it already and make a difference stop bitching and make a difference and do something
funny and entertaining for a change okay that'll help no I did not see broke back mountain
then have absolutely no desire to see it that's a movie that is only interesting for the American
audience who have been so suppressed that you can't even talk about homosexuality anywhere
except in a gay club we're in a gay community that's where you should be working on
I don't get entertained by that I don't have to see men hug by the way it's beautiful one
men hug it's beautiful one women hug and kiss and cuddle and make love and have sex
anyone can have sex with anyone I don't give a shit and I say as I do when I do as I say
you're only in the free cage that lives in your mind okay it lives in your mind and you've got
to break free from that you need serious help you really do because there's no physical cage
it's in your head the only restrictions that are placed are you are the ones that you place on your
self and you know what with the language that is used in your show the language that is used
in as an example of another cue potter show the Zilla Zilla Fag show excuse me that's what turns
people off because it's so easy to say mother fucker Kant bitch it's so easy to do that why don't
you try and get some new vocabulary okay like watching some fucking these DL even the
they fuck you all you know and why are cute potters in so you have the nerve to say what do you
insular because this is exactly what you're doing you're bitching and moaning about things that are
not true you're lying about it propagating lies that I'm your boss I don't even know if you listen
to the fucking show in fact everything that I'm hearing tells me you didn't you just read the email
from Jeffrey and when oh fuck that shit did you actually listen to the hood high problem
did you actually consider that this was not directed towards gaze did you consider that at all
oh sorry can I say gay can I say gays can I say homosexuals please tell me what words I can use
or insular because we treat each other like equals and I don't treat you like equals that
what you're telling me I want you to tell me that when I have not treated you with the exact
same respect as anyone else that I encounter in my life personal business business wise tell me
and tell me the same about fucking pod show the company that run and I've built from the ground up
tell me the company that you are a part of you're insulting me you're insulting the company
and it's based on lies because the rest of the world evidently thinks we're just a work to
call somebody you know that is so lame the rest of the world oh look at poor me the rest of
if I took on that attitude every single time I got yelled at flamed and called the most ugly
things that you can imagine hurtful names not necessarily based on my homosexuality but I've
had I've been called a fag a lot more than you imagine a hell of a lot more my entire professional
career I've been called a fag a pansy boy doesn't bother me because I switch it off in my brain
I think ah well whatever they're ignorant they're just putting their own baggage onto me
their own fucking baggage like you're doing my very existence just family so fucking important
because the Bible this the Bible that you're acting on all that shit I am acting on normal human
conversation and not on rants and and foul language from a group of people who feel marginalized
who feel that they've been put into a cage which is absolutely not true the world is open to you
everything that I have to offer is open to you as there is to anyone else that I'm working with
you're afraid afraid of what afraid of my sexuality I think not my friend I think not
I'm not afraid of my sexuality I don't feel a need to share it all the time like you do
just don't feel that need you want to do that fine I don't give a shit that's fine
but don't be surprised if your audience is not what you want it to be because of that
because you're talking to yourself you're talking to your own community which I think is a very
poor representation of the gay bisexual, trisexual, transgendered community a very poor representation
you're afraid that we're going to take over the world because we have a fucking talent
oh yeah oh yeah I'm afraid you're going to take over the world that's why
so what am I doing I've done nothing but try and help you take over the world I want you
you Richard Bluestein to take over the world with that talent that you think is so fucking great
but if you keep getting stuck in this stupid bullshit you'll never get anywhere
and you're marginalizing yourself no no more insults and q potters q wear gay lesbian podcast
we got to stick up for yourself and thanks for missus local for sticking up for yourself
and for emailing out of curry who responded to the xm think the comments are repeated again
was that the xm somebody I don't remember this the site that's at the promo said
xm's a bunch of facts no you didn't listen to it okay you didn't listen to it
and it's still is very different if if the promo would said the q potter or a bunch of
facts it never would have made it on the air never you know and
and this is like a road out of curry a long email one paragraph not a long email one
paragraph basically why this isn't right the fact that it does cause you know people to kill
themselves this kind of hate speech and your kind of hate speech doesn't right I'll tell you
if I was gay and I'm definitely somewhat gay not but not not even 50% but as I said
I've explored all the limits of my sexuality I know where I stand I'm very comfortable with where
I stand not afraid to talk about it but if I was gay and I'm thinking wow that's the community
I got to grow up in without asshole I'd shut up about it you better believe it if you're not gay
oh oh I'm sorry I'm sorry now I'll sudden you know all about me you know what I've been through
you know my life you know what I've had to go through is a kid you know what what trials and tribulations
I had to go through all of a sudden you're fucking special no way mother fucker you're not special
you know more special than a black kid growing up in the projects you know special
then growing up in Israel and having bombs thrown at you from the Palestinians or
growing up in Palestine and having the Israelis shoot you from the sky you know more fucking
special than that mother fucker in fact I think you're a lot less special because you're not at any
physical harm or danger right now you didn't drop homeless you out of your mind
get some perspective and you can't fucking imagine what it's like to grow up as a gay or lesbian
like an outcast like your life doesn't even make fucking sense oh and that's all that's the same all
over the world right that's the same everywhere Richard you you were an Amsterdam for a couple
years you know it's not true you know where I grew up you know that that's very different in other
parts of the world some parts are worse some parts are better some parts are hmm kind of uh
that's the way it goes but don't tell me what I know and don't know you don't fucking know me you don't
know what I've had to deal with you've no fucking clue particularly when it comes to my sexuality you
don't know so don't judge me and I don't judge you never have never will to think you're
except on your no talent the fucking only person in the world who doesn't like whatever sexer
supposed to like it doesn't like the sports you're supposed to like I feel like a fucking free
and then I have to deal with this bullshit when you grow up except fucking testosterone and
this really like radio which is more to go for it to pop gas to camp oh okay so now we're going to
marginalize radio by saying it's 10 testosterone induced switch on the bit fucking radio
Richard's turn it on listen scan around the dial that's not true it's absolutely not true
god my handle there are a few isn't satisfied with their own sexuality so they have to
there you go there you go again presuming that because people aren't satisfied with their own sexuality
meaning that boy I guess we haven't explored I guess we're really dissatisfied because
well gee you know what sexuality has nothing to do with it this is a beer's a wake-up call
folks wake-up call from Madge Weinstein wake-up call for the cute potters and Richard Bluestein okay
sexuality has nothing to do with being gay okay if you like anal sex if you like oral sex from
the same partner as a man if you like having sex with women it has nothing to do
with homosexuality if you're attracted if you are physically a not sex if you are physically
attracted and can fall in love and I think you know what that means no I'm sure you know what that
means if you can fall in love with someone of the same sex that is homosexuality not just the act
or the so-called act of homosexuality it's not in fact on eat this hot show I was very open
very honest and no one picked up on it within your so-called marginalized caged community I said
you know yeah I kind of like being a bottom I like the idea of penis but I don't like the
idea of being attached to a man I was open about that what do I get I get laughed at
laughed at by you pod father goes pod bottom and then when I said that Reagan Fox immediately went
into all kinds of gory details about oh well this Patricia put vibrator in your ass and I was honest
I answered all your questions honestly and you know what you didn't make me feel very welcome at all
go back and listen to the show fucker there's to marginalized make themselves feel better
temporarily or at least think they do to be wild you know that really the more I think about the more
angry I get about that I was so open I was so honest and you laughed at me and you you did not
at all welcome me into your community in that particular show go back and listen to eat this hot show
where I was on listen to what I said and I was ridiculed ridiculed for saying honest things
about my personal sexual behavior which has nothing to do with my feelings towards the opposite
sex if I could fall in love with a man which I can't because I just don't have it in me that's not
me that's you that's fine I don't give a crap but you sir you are the one that is marginalizing
and not being fair and actually putting me down I realize you can't take any of it fucking with you
fuck this I am so fucking pissed off you know and you know Adam curry likes to take it and
you'll take anything that will save him from having to write you know to actually have to
talk during his show okay so now we're gonna go and slam my show right that's what you want to do now
can't can't win can't lose can't win either way if I don't play the promos then I'm then I hate the
queue potters I hate the queers I hate the gaze hate the faggots because I don't play the
promos but I shouldn't play promos I should be talking make up your mind sorry you got to listen to it
why don't you talk it's more interesting it's fucking promos anyway Jesus Christ
except when it's one of yours right which is so important to you that's when they're good right
I shouldn't be talking when you send me an audio comment and you play this fucking promos
from that psych psychopathic comics what right do you have to call anyone a psychopath what right do
you have what right do you have you have no right to call someone a psychopath or a stalker you
have no right whatsoever to do that certainly not in the position you're in the position that you've
taken good stalker who is not funny who is not you know clever like writer small
maybe it's not intended to be funny maybe and I have to say if you would listen
and if you would participate in the conversation comic strip blogger is actually quite intelligent
quite successful in business has his own podcast is a very talented artist and has some very
interesting things to say about what's happening right now in the European Union and he does it
in a very similar fashion to what you do using explodives pissing people off sound familiar
I think you just jealous who's just basically a psychotic person who was used as a child and
as acting out on his weird end right so if your gay is a child then it's not okay to call someone
gay or fag or whatever but if someone was abused as a child it's okay to laugh at them and to
ridicule them is that what you're saying as I just said he's accomplished plenty on his own
that's clever now you have to draw the line on content maybe you need somebody to produce
or show for you now I think you need somebody to produce your show for you because that'll
get you back to the Mad wine scene that I started working with in January of 2005 that I fell in
love with someone needs to put your head back on straight stop trying to be Howard Stern stop trying
to be things you're not and stop please stop trying to make me feel that you're that I'm putting
you in a box and marginalizing you stop that because some of this shit just doesn't belong in it
you're saying to piss off the people who you know are you're part of yourself part of your
no you're starting to piss me off that's what's going on here
you know I'm not gonna hide what I think so because I know you're not gonna hide what you think
that was the agreement we made you liar and I think it's clear how pissed I am the fact that
this isn't even a comment I'm barely so scared this is going on my show only right I can expect
myself express myself the way I want to so I'm sure that Adam Perry and his show today it's
blamed how he didn't listen to his show and he should any apologizes but oh fuck that no okay so
that's where you're wrong all right I'm sorry I didn't rush ahead and listen to your show
and that I didn't get all my email to find out about it so I could have done it yesterday sorry
it took me a day later sorry about that oh shit you know this shit's all over the place it's
not even just everywhere yeah Keith and the girl it's perfectly fine to say fact but nobody
it's perfectly fine to say fact except when you don't think it's fine to say fact is that it
they're saying nigger because they're afraid they're gonna beat up but who's gonna you know
but assisting nobody's gonna hurt you if you're assisting well let me tell you
let me tell you so what you've done that you just you just completely
marginalized yourself what you just said is that people are afraid to say nigger
because they think some big black guy is gonna show up your front door and knife you to death
yet the same time people aren't afraid to say faggot because they're scissi boys
dude I watch porn there's a lot there's a lot of gay men out there who could fuck me up really bad
who could kill me with and snap my neck like a twig that's bullshit stupid argument next
yeah I guess again all right so that's it very very disappointing
very disappointing all right I'm done with this I've nothing left to say I've done about it what shit
I've done over an hour of this and I think I've made my point very clear if you want to have a civil
conversation if you want to tell me what the ground rules are for you would make you feel
comfortable and uncomfortable we can do that because it seems that other people who contribute to the
daily source code to my show can do that in a civil manner unlike you which really I did not expect at all
when I first met you thought you were pretty cool so when I liked to hang around
so I introduced you to all my friends pretty soon I was no doubt you were ahead of it with everyone
several on the scene then I started to get some subtle signs and didn't know exactly what they're
like the people that you'll know before corroborate your stories and the details of your shady
past and seems so gory and the things you said you're done and the places you have bad
I didn't meet up from Berlin without the stairs between you had a stink at you I saw a crack of a
little like someone on the case get out of my face I get out of my way stop hanging around my
friend I'm still after them just get out of my way I don't need you around I'd be happy when
the fun will wait here I'm not a place and another town I guess you're pretty lucky
that I'm no one I was found out but eventually they all will see a decision I'm no doubt
because when you build out house I can't I'll tell you what you'll get if your strong wind's gone
I'll come along you'll get the end of the day you better think about this get not you I'll
come along you'll get the end of the day you better think about this get out of my face
I get out of my way stop hanging around my friend I'm still after them just get out of my way
I don't need you around I'd be happy when you're fun will wait here I'm not a place
I don't need you around I'm still after them just get out of my way stop hanging around
I'm still after them just get out of my way stop hanging around I'm still after them just get out of my way
I don't need you around
I'm still after them just get out of my way stop hanging around
I told you not to bring anything this morning and you're worried about that
I can't imagine because I could hear your answers and your reactions
I hate that I hate lying and I am a homophobic because I play this promo just made me so angry
I can do anything but you know the things that you boss is asking so that's not true
because you are the real boss I am the boss the homo thing now being married to me is almost being married to homo because of the homo
I don't want to get angry with you
sometimes she had to defend herself because she was so nice about explaining the friend in our house
my mom's friend now he lives with a guy and they stay in our house
and she has a little girl she thought that was just the most normal thing
so it's so funny to hear this whole thing and it's stupid thing going on
for anyone to say that I am not comfortable with my sexuality
thank you
I think you said enough for that exactly what I'd be married to you
that is very funny
but really made me laughable
but it's stupid
it's just stupid I think that match just wants a lot of attention
I think so too and I'm still not sure if this was done to get controversy going to be talked about
he talked so much about Howard Stern and this as well
Howard Stern
I think we're exactly the same he doesn't give a shit
he's fine but he says Fag instead of gay instead of queer instead of queen
which one I just just give me the list please just give me the list
what word can I use if I actually am talking about homosexuals
not about a competitor to serious satellite radio
it's stupid
I'm coming from somebody who's dressed up and doesn't know who he is
thank you
all right we're that will leave it big thank you
it felt really good though to give it off my chest
yeah I heard you
downstairs
you cross the street
and by the way I was going to say
when those are open you know
it's so unfortunate that little Britain
isn't on in the United States
if people were to see that show
and how the United Kingdom how Britain
is so open
but not just that
but it's just funny
it's funny it's like laughing in yourself
and then yeah all that that's great Britain
or the Brits are very good at that
laughing at themselves
yes very good at it and then you have
always been hello it's Linda
so this is one scene between the university
and there's this woman which is of course actually played by a guy
and her name is Linda
and so students come in and request things like
you know I need my courses changed or I need my
I need to take the test over
and then she'll always have to call someone
to say you know I have this person here
here's the request they have and so
and it's a comedian who actually is a man
and he's a woman
what match really could be if she were funny
so it's Linda and then so incomes
you know this really boochy looking girl
and then so yeah I have to change my coursework
and so oh one moment I'll call you and she'll call and say
hello it's Linda yes
I have here I have Carol here
yes the butchee one yes you know the big fat
diek you know and so just keep on doing
and it's like hey let's Linda
yes you know I wasn't
but Lumpa here
yeah there's like a midget and call it Lumpa Lumpa Lumpa
the Chinese guy yes the Qingchan China man
and it's just funny you know get
over your fucking silly
and that wasn't okay
maybe only in America
maybe that's it
the country by the way and we did look
didn't we move because of the old
that was definitely one of the reasons
not actually because you are an American
and you're very proud of it
but I was very annoyed with certain things
you know that was a pity
we actually decided to move
when uh what's your name
Lidles mom
uh um
I forgot actually
Ronnie and
Ida Ida Ida
Ida came to our back door
and she said
Patricia
I'm the one that has to tell you
we had a conversation all the moms at school
we have a complaint
you have to wear a less tight clothes
when you come to pick up Christina
because all the boys are looking
yeah I know you're showing
of your figure too much
yeah meanwhile they
do not have the same figure that you have
so it's like projecting there
their own frustrations
if I could wear a beggy t-shirt
so you don't see my figure
you're showing off too much excuse me
yeah she's showing off
I have to go to school to show off
so
and that was actually the last thing
and then there was the magazine
that we had in a house
you know like playboy
oh big problem
I used to take showers with Christina
yeah I'd actually hold her in my arms
and when she was little
and up until she was probably about
five maybe or it was a chair bath
you're going to bed
we actually you and I decided
you have conversation still in the bathroom
while you were taking shower
morning when my daughter was in there
yeah I hear you too have a conversation
she doesn't even see it
but we actually actually
I stopped doing that
because we were afraid that she might mention that
and we could actually get into real trouble
later yeah but now it's another problem
no well you're not going in the bath
in the bathtub
but you're taking a shower
sometimes I have to say hello
do you know your naked
crap crap crap crap
can't we all just get along everybody
who gives a shit
and we all die naked
no don't die naked
I hope I die naked
I hope I die on top of you
maybe you're on top of me
I want to do it
okay everybody that's it for the show
thank you very much for your contribution
okay thanks a lot
okay
let's just laugh
let's laugh
and that's it for the show for today
have yourselves a wonderful weekend
and i'll see you back here on Monday
bye bye
another pod show pod cast
stick it in your ear
get this pod cast and we're great ones like it
on the high performance pod cast
delivery network from pod show
and limelight networks
I love