This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
The show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy.
Delta Sierra Charlie 424.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky ingredients in it.
I like to think I'm flying into this church.
Fantastic.
It's Adam Curry.
Ladies and gentlemen, the godfather of soul.
Game brown.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
I like to think I'm flying into this church.
Oh, fantastic.
It's Adam Curry.
Ladies and gentlemen, the godfather of soul.
Game brown.
Got a brand new thing.
Ain't no thing, you know.
But it's a body girl.
Huh?
You can't hold it.
Blood guard.
But your body can't hold it.
Hey, hey, hey.
I like to think I'm flying into this church.
Oh, yes, sir.
Oh, good, man in pure brains.
You got troubles, please.
jay.
Keidhan.
Dude, no.
hot beans in it.
Oh, you.
It got to be kids, I mean, es,
There's a whole way
Seven, up, you're down
Ow!
Say again, hey, hey, hey
Good time
You do
Good time, hey, y'all
That brand new thing
It's no big dealer
But it's a bad dealer
You can't hold it, but it's bad to move it
Come on
Hey, hey
I love you
You're up to this step
And burn it
That you're going to steal
And hear it
Look
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey
Come on, skid
It'll be
I'll make a challenge
I got nuggets
Fuck!
Fuck! I got nuggets
I got nuggets
And I got nuggets
Oh yeah!
You don't deserve it.
You got it.
You got me as pleased.
Somebody please.
Take that.
Good.
No hard feeling.
Oh man.
Yes, they're morning.
All of a sudden you showed up on the Podsafe music network.
James Brown and gut bucket.
Even if that song is sucked major as I still would have played it.
Do you believe the endorsement that this is for the Podsafe music network?
What the heck is going on?
Are we doing okay here?
Yeah.
For the Podsafe music movement in general.
James Brown put this track up on the Podsafe music network.
And that was yesterday morning.
We're preparing for the Board of Directors meeting.
And all of a sudden Chris Rockwell starts typing everybody.
Wow, that is indeed.
And I was like, dude, are you sure?
Yep.
We checked it.
It's been verified.
And this is actually a move by the godfather of sold himself.
I mean, how can you, how can you argue with that?
It's great.
Link in the show notes, of course, too.
Got bucket.
James Brown on the Podsafe music network.
That's crazy.
Everybody how you doing.
It's early morning.
Today is of course.
What are we Thursday?
Is it July 20th already coming to you from Northern California from the Curry condo?
Just a little bit past 7 a.m.
For me, of course, I feel once again like we're so behind the rest of the world.
Here on the west coast of the United States, everyone is already pretty much had their day.
And it's going to be beautiful.
I can see it's going to be another warm day today.
It's going to be clear skies.
Got some little bit of haze up there in the mountains.
They seem to be filled with more.
It looks like oil tankers and maybe is there a container ship out there?
No, oil tankers are more.
It just seems like there's a lot of ships today.
I don't know.
I'm sure it's not related to anything with the weather, but just noticing.
So I'm tired.
The jet lag is already catching up to me.
Of course, it's been kind of whirlwind if you think about it where I arrived.
It was at Tuesday, dropped my stuff off at the condo, went straight into the office to prepare
to help prepare at least our presentation for the board, which is really it's presentations
of the wrong word.
It's really we sit there and we evaluate for ourselves.
What the hell do we just do in the past a couple months?
And we write it all down and we say, hey, okay.
And here's some stuff we can do better.
And here's some stuff that we learned.
And then we share that with the room full of smart people, which we did yesterday.
So after all, this may have been excitement about James Brown being on the pod save music network.
We went off this time.
It was turned our turn to go over to San Hill Road, which is where many venture capitalists
sit, but ours in particular.
And it was as I predicted, it was a lot of fun.
We got some great insights, some great ideas.
I think they were blown away by some of the things that they saw.
And here's, so I've talked about Ray Lane before.
He's on our board.
Ray ran Oracle.
He's run big companies and he's very, very involved in not just in pod show,
but in what's happening in general in media, in pod casting, all forms of media.
And so he comes up to me.
First thing he says, scruncher.
I'm like, yes.
Hey, what do you think about the godfather of soul?
It's he a folder or scruncher.
Hi.
Hmm.
Need to know more.
So after all that scruncher business, and then Ray said something interesting.
He said, you know, there's this thing going on in Los Angeles tonight.
He might be interested in.
It's the official, oh my blackberry is too close to everything.
It's the official launch of this new car from the Tesla Motor Corporation.
And it's a car that runs on batteries.
And, you know, it's, you know, me with Trinity and alternative stuff.
I'm always interested in cars in general.
You know, but normally when you think about something, there'll be,
environmentally friendly.
I don't even know how environmentally friendly these cars are.
You know, it takes something to charge these batteries.
And the battery in this, it's like this is actually like a driving battery.
But normally, these cars look like batteries.
You know, they're, look at the Prius.
It's a very popular car, but it's not really a sexy car.
So what, what this Tesla Motor Corporation has done is they went to load us.
And that you know that load us alone.
I think it's at least or they're alone.
I don't know which one.
But you know, load us.
They went to load us and had them design the car.
And then they put the engine and the battery and the battery.
I think weighs 900 pounds.
It's almost half the weight of the car.
It's a two-seater.
But this thing has an incredible performance.
It goes from zero to sixty and four seconds.
I mean, it's like, and it has, I guess it's two speed automatic or something.
And I'm not quite sure what the top speed is, but basically they were demonstrating the car.
And they had it set up pretty cool at a, at a hanger.
And it was at Long Beach.
That's the airport we went to because Ray said, hey, why don't you guys come along?
And we'll fly down.
Now, whatever you get an invitation to fly in a golf stream for, you pretty much are going
to grab that.
Particularly if there's 30 year old Scotch on board.
And you know, to fly to L.A. and to look at some incredibly futuristic car that, basically,
is a laptop with a, a laptop with a 250 mile battery radius that actually drives.
Because that's what it feels like.
It's like a driving laptop.
But it was very cool.
And here's the, here's the best part of that whole trip.
Now you know why I'm so fuzzy because it's like flying.
And, you know, maybe I don't drink.
So just before landing in L.A. or Long Beach,
I walk up to the front because I want to sit on the jump seat and watch the landing.
And this is like, how many people can fit on a golf stream?
And 16 people is a big plane.
It's just, it's me, Ron, Marta, of course, and, and Ray.
And that's it.
And so we're flying.
And we go sit at the front and watch.
And so it was pretty cool.
You know, there was some haze or fog.
And so we kind of dropped down about just about the 1000 foot levels.
Or we saw the runway straight now.
Got under the runway position, glide pad.
And I was looking a line.
And everything is the same.
You know, it doesn't matter if you're flying a golf stream where you're flying
the Delta Sierra.
The whole concept is the same.
And the radio works the same.
So I'm enjoying this.
Dude, did they fuck up the landing?
It's like, if I hadn't been wearing my seatbelt on the jump seat,
I would have been through the window.
And Ray, of course, wasn't wearing a seatbelt.
And he landed up by Marta's feet somewhere.
And not quite sure what happened.
I think they came in a little bit high.
And well, the speed was probably good.
But I think they came in a bit high.
And just something dropped.
I think they just hold the power.
It seemed like just a, hey, you know,
it's one of those landings that you just fucked it up.
I'm sorry.
I've been through that.
But to do it with a $30 million airplane was pretty funny to see.
And the excuses that came out were even funny.
But I could totally appreciate it.
And I felt pretty bad for the guys.
So that was, how about that man?
How about that for a life?
Crying.
I get around.
So, you know, was back at midnight in bed by 1230.
Up this morning, it's six to, you know, get everything.
And I'm also kind of like auto awakening at six o'clock.
I'm getting too old for this shit.
Let me see.
What do we have here?
Adam, John, from here of Cook,
Moynihan, I had just listened to,
set a source code 422.
It's laughed my ass off when you're the landing story there.
It's like Cherokee 180.
I had a couple of landings like that myself.
I know what it feels like.
I don't know.
If anyone other than pilots could get the humor in it like we could.
And it's always amazing how when we do something stupid like that.
The first thing we think about is how many people up in the tower are laughing at us.
I just thought I dropped your line.
Let you know still listening.
I'm still working out in the garage.
Build my airplane hopefully.
She'll be in the air.
Just winter.
Things go right.
I'll try to do a podcast.
The first podcast from the first flight.
Keep trucking.
Love the show.
Tell when's my man.
Yo, buddy.
Tell when's.
Yep.
That's exactly it.
The only thing we're not worried about safety.
We're not worried about safety.
We're worried about who's laughing at us when we do that ship.
But it was just really nice to see that.
Not just me.
Low at low hour pilot.
But a very experienced guy is messing up once in a while too.
If you got anything to call into the show.
Love to hear from you.
And I'm getting but phone numbers now.
But but phone calls.
Which, you know, someone's basically programmed the number into their mobile phone.
Sat down on their phone or whatever.
And then it dials and it's probably Adam Curry daily source code.
So I'm always at the top of the list on people's phone book.
So it's working.
You are putting my numbers in there.
If you want to pre program it right now.
It's plus 201 plus one for the US 201.
65, 65, 65, 7.
And in the UK plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3.
I have something here in my show notes.
And I don't want to forget.
The 28th of July is officially CIS admin day.
That's it.
CIS admin.com.
You know what?
Let me just go take a look at that side for a second.
And I've recognized this in the past.
I think I've even recognized it before.
It was podcasting.
Let's see.
July 28th, 2006.
The 7th annual system administrator appreciation day.
There you go.
Don't forget your CIS admin.
And we'll talk about that more as we get closer to the actual day.
I've got an email here from who is this from.
From Brent from Pod Show Radio.
He's got some great news.
He says he's got the first full podcast interview with Rick Nielson of cheap trick.
And they'll be available starting tomorrow Friday.
And I'm just going to kind of paraphrase from Brent's email here.
He says he digs podcasting dude.
Cheap trick has a link to my show on the front page of their website.
How jealous is Michael Butler going to be when he hears all this?
I mean, Michael, Michael Butler.
The largest cheap trick fan in the world.
I mean, he missed out on this opportunity.
Oh, my goodness.
He's going to be so green with it.
I add them.
This is Derek the band of from Johannesburg in South Africa.
And I hope you are well.
Just wanted to pop into it.
You know that I've started a brand new show on Pod Show.
And thank you so much for the platform to be able to do it.
You'll find a www dot Derek the bandit.
And Derek is spelled DEREK.
Nice and short dot pod show dot com.
It is my anthem of the week where I feature one electronic dance music anthem that is found
its way into my record box.
And their pod say Adam, I just have to say a big thank you and congratulations to you
and the whole team at Pod Show.
You guys have done an absolutely incredible job.
I'm still trying to find my feet around some of the certain parts in Pod Show.
But I'm sure in time I'll get there.
Adam have a fantastic weekend in San Francisco.
And from the bottom of Africa, you take care.
Cheers, cheers.
I love it when he says that when you think about it from the bottom of Africa,
up to the northern part of California.
But the heck is going on?
These increments are really doing cool stuff for us.
So of course, Derek is very pleased with Pod Show plus.
I have to say that yesterday, even though I wasn't able to check out the system the whole
time, I think we're doing two major releases per day with fixes, features, stuff happening.
So you definitely want to check back often because things are coming together and things
actually are working.
Now of course with all of that positive noise, we got to put some negative in.
Common strip.
Of course not safe for family listening.
I don't carry.
For facts, fake.
Your podcast is becoming boring.
You are boring me.
You need more action.
More controversy.
More something and not just playing voice feedback from your eskises and horse.
I can't help you in the controversy department because I have found peace and
throws with judges, smalls.
And we are not at any conflict anymore.
Well, that's a bummer.
Gee, I was so enjoying all those comments on curry.com.
No, I think the piece is better CSB.
And that, you know, when it comes to that, I'd rather you be a little boring.
However, I would love to help out in other areas.
For example, why the fuck you keep promoting only youngs and spirits
stick if everybody knows that Americans of British origins in USA are in minority
and most Americans in USA are of other non-British origins.
Mostly German, Italian and Irish.
For facts, fake.
You need to leave American British ghetto and be more global.
For example, Adam, maybe.
Tell us, what side are you taking in current military conflict in Middle East?
Personally, I don't take any side.
I don't want to take any side.
I just want fucking peace everywhere.
They are worth and in the blogger's field too.
And by the way, bringing that uncle of yours, who is Korea expert as soon as possible,
it looks like World War III is cooking faster than I thought.
Stay healthy.
Bye.
Oh, he didn't give me his typical yo.
Okay, Commissioner Blogger, I actually started to make a little bit of sense there with this question.
The Middle East conflict, I think the number one thing that we should do
is which is stop sugar coating this shit.
It's not a conflict.
It's fucking war.
It's real war.
And I don't think I haven't seen a lot of television while I've been over here.
But, you know, you just look at CNN and they got the graphics out and everything.
And I guess, are they now calling it war?
I think we should just call this a war, okay?
It disturbs me greatly.
Are you kidding me?
It really disturbs me.
Everything that's going on there.
This is a huge issue.
And then to see that conversation that Bush and Blair had.
If the answer and everyone's here in the States, it seems like certainly the White House and everyone is concentrating on the fact that the president said shit.
Oh, boy.
Expertise.
Shit.
But I think what was far more outrageous.
What he said is that, and look,
I'm just going to take our president's word for it.
If he says that all that has to happen is that,
and I couldn't understand it.
I don't know if it was she or they or if that means coffee,
a non or whoever has to say it,
but someone apparently has to call Syria and Syria has to call Hezbollah
and then they have to stop that shit.
If it's that fucking simple, why don't we find out who's supposed to make the fucking call?
Call fucking Syria already.
Will ya?
And then to have Syria call fucking Asbollah?
And then the shit will be over.
Is that all it takes?
We have the answer apparently.
Make it happen, please.
Now a word from our spine here.
It's the Yanks versus the Brits.
We'll drive each other crazy,
but everybody knows that it's apparent to see.
Let just like you and me, it's the Yanks.
And the Brits, the Yanks versus the Brits.
Mind the gap.
Not exactly Yanks versus the Brits,
although in this case the Yanks will get slammed
as it pertains to the Tour de France.
I don't need to matter.
I'm currently at the Tour de France,
I'm in the Alps.
I'm trying to leave a message for you.
This is strange thing that the American seems to be doing here.
And it might be a few of your Yanks versus Brits section.
They think the bus they got for two hours climb to the top of the
some of the legendary climbs of the Tour de France,
such as the Col de Glendon, Galibier, Alps,
and then I hear the top of the climbs.
Herb. Herb.
The shuttle button is the right to take it down.
Now if you're going to do that for two hours,
ride a commanding.
Surely you want to actually enjoy the experience of
hammering down the other side at 70 kilometers an hour.
It's just very odd.
Everybody looks at them.
It's a strange thing.
They look at the condition coach at the top of the mountain.
That was all really.
The French of A police today because the American
favourite Floyd Lannis died of death on the final mountain climb
today.
So I'm sure the lead keeps.
The French Davis boys and youth people will be loving
that one tomorrow.
So I'm going to sign off with you.
Good afternoon.
Bye.
Okay.
So am I to understand that the US riders in the Tour de France
and please, let's not call it Tour de France.
It's Tour de France.
They do the mountain hill climb thing.
And then when they're done,
they instead of, you know,
coasting down on your bike,
which is I have to say pretty much an American past time.
They jump into their air condition bus
to drive them back down the mountain
to base camp or whatever they stay
for their, for that particular part of the tour.
Yeah.
I have to admit that is very much the American way.
Absolutely.
Excuse me.
Send sail.
This sent sail a moment brought to you by
cold aren't brought to you by
just admin day July 28, 2006.
Um,
In fact,
it would be even better if we had
a McDonald's up at the top of the mountain.
That would now, that would really make it happen.
I'm, in fact, I'm amazed.
They don't have the McDonald's.
In Iraq, when I went to,
to Iraq in 2004,
and we were in Camp Smitty,
but we went down to Bosra,
which is actually is heating up down there.
A couple of people have been killed recently.
English soldiers have been killed in Bosra.
That's where the Dutch,
Marine helicopter base was.
And it's a huge base.
I think there,
there must have been seven or eight thousand
troops on this base.
And, and of course,
the Americans were there.
The Italians were on that base
and the Brits,
I believe, at the time.
And, of course,
not only was there,
um,
a Burger King,
but there was also a Pizza Hut.
And that,
if you want to talk about bizarre,
stand in the middle of the desert,
and then go to the Pizza Hut.
That is truly bizarre.
Remember that movie Patricia and I were talking about
little man?
Well,
you've heard about it.
It was number two at the box office.
Excuse me.
Did I call it or what?
Without ever having seen the movie,
without just only seeing the trailer,
I was able to predict it had,
you know,
the blackbuster written all over it.
And, um,
so the movie company is so happy.
They've actually contracted us to talk about it some more.
And so this is what I promise you I'm going to do.
This weekend,
either tomorrow night or over the weekend.
I'm going to go see little man.
And I'll report on it next week.
To exactly what I thought about it.
But, just the feedback I've been getting from people.
It's, yeah,
we love this,
particularly Americans.
We love this kind of movie.
I think isn't it coming out in,
I thought it was also out in the UK.
I thought I saw it,
promo is for it.
Anyway,
you can check out the little man podcast at littlemanpodcast.com.
There's interviews on it.
Actually,
I think you'll like the podcast.
It's,
it's pretty darn good.
I wish they would make a promo for it.
So you can also see the trailer over at littlemanpodcast.com
and check out the movie.
Because it's the cool thing to do.
That's what we do.
We do cool things in America.
Like when it's really hot outside,
we want to be cool.
So we go into the movie.
It's cool.
And then what do we watch?
Yes.
Exactly.
We watch stuff like Little Man.
Is this a great country or what?
Good morning, Adam.
John here from Geofus.
And just don't have my work at the A3 this morning.
And just about the lesson to DSC423.
I think it says that it was delivered through to my icon
to buy a playlist that I can send you via.
For sure plus.
Hold on one second, John,
because I got a sick about the serious satellite folks.
You should go to podshow.com.
So you two can download this show easily.
And I'll talk to you tomorrow.
For the thank God it's Friday edition of the Daily Source God.
We were having the discussions on the comments on your phone.
We were having the issues where I was adding stuff and nothing was getting saved.
And then I'd be getting in and my iTunes will be thinking,
but they wouldn't be any.
I have shows in the speaker that play a playlist.
But now I'm having to say it's been available for two days.
I'll take this.
And stuff didn't ask those.
Cheat us to the guy who you're in to getting that little fixed.
And they're finding the digital mining non-podshow plus fees
into my iPod NASA.
I've no fully running of a podshow plus.
That's great.
And hey man, you're missing a hot one over here.
I mean, yesterday it hit 37 degrees.
So a little bit warmer for a minute.
So here are the good work.
So again.
Bye bye.
Cheers, John.
From Gilford.
Check it in from back home.
37 degrees.
That's like 96 degrees Fahrenheit.
Something's outrageous.
It's in the mid 90s.
And as you know, we have no air conditioning.
That's actually that's pretty bad for Patricia's health condition.
So she's been staying indoors as cool as possible.
You know, fans everywhere because of the lack of air conditioning.
But John, cool.
I'm glad that it worked out.
I told you that we get that fixed.
And believe me was top of the list because I've been.
Listening to podcast and watching video podcasts exclusively through through podshow
Plus all throughout the day to period.
And I got, I got used to it.
You know, I no longer am using iTunes only.
I have one playlist that I sync up my news playlist.
And if you go to atom.podshow.com, you can see my channels right there.
And you'll see what shows are in there.
And that's the one that syncs up to my iPod.
And if I want to change anything, I want to add it from my travel.
Then I just do it right from my podshow plus account.
Also, so I told you that, you know, we're releasing twice a day.
We're putting new updates up there, new updates, fixes, features,
etc.
And so the channels are now, there's a couple other things we still have to
Fix on the channels, like the name of the channel.
And I think the show notes are being truncated.
There's all kinds of stuff that we're still looking at.
It's just, it's amazing how much we didn't catch in beta,
even with hundreds, hundreds of beta testers of which several
hundred were developers.
And there's still a whole bunch of stuff that we just didn't catch.
So we're fixing all that.
But you can also now, if you go to your to my,
go to your collection and under your channels,
you can import an external RSS feed.
So if there's something that you can't find through search,
you could, of course, just copy the link and place it in there.
Also, we import OPML.
So if you want your subscriptions to carry over and you want all your podcasts
to be manageable through our interface, you can import them with, again,
under the advanced button there on the channel.
You can import, it's right there up at the top under your shows.
You can import an OPML file.
So what you could technically do if you're using iTunes.
And we should, which has the screencast do to actually do a screencast
of this because it is cool.
You can take everything you have in iTunes.
You can export all your subscriptions as they call it.
Into Gets on Pod Show Plus.
You can export that as an OPML file and then you go into my collection
and you can import that OPML file.
And then you can start to split it up and make all kinds of different channels.
So we're getting some shit done that isn't gentlemen
and liking it very much.
And keep the comments coming for Shadow Falls, man.
People are loving this.
Shadow Falls.podshow.com.
I think part of the appeal has got to be the music.
Munk has really outclassed himself this time into a whole new level.
And so I'm kick so much ass.
It's Molly Steen.
I am from DMN.
I just became.
I was dead for her.
For us to be.
Bets wins both ways.
Never asked my name.
I am here.
I am here while you're sleeping.
I am late.
I am late for a crazy.
I am here.
I am here for godийs my way to my home.
I am here, I am there where you're sleeping
I am alive, I am alive, I am there for a free sleep
I am, I am
I am here
I am alive
To forget all of his life.
On how else do you love me?
That's our autograph.
Ok, let's go take a look at that!
Amazing.
I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here
I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, and I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here,
that again. Link in the show notes, of course, taking to the Pods have music networks
who mugs page. I am Molly's theme. It's from Shadow Falls, check it out at Shadow Falls.podshow.com.
This is something completely new. I'm the kid that used to lay in bed when I was five or six
years old. Had a little blue record player where you opened up the lid and then in the lid was
the speaker and I think I had a couple albums. One or two that I stole for like, I don't know,
for some reason I took like Jesus Christ to restore something that my parents had downstairs.
See? I've got to think of Mom for a second. But I also had a vinyl of Peter in the Wolf and it
was with classical instruments and you'd hear this like, well, well, of course, we all know Peter in the
Wolf. And then here comes the wolf and you hear the cello you go. So this whole theater of the
mind thing appeared. You know, and I could really visualize the story as the narrator told me
what was happening and the instruments were playing. So now when you listen to Shadow Falls,
immediately it's like, it's like reading a book but without reading.
Immediately you've got this. You can see it. You can see I have a picture of what the actors
look like at the scenes. I can see it all. It's really, really nice to have this experience.
Now you really, and I recommend you be completely alone and not the stir because you don't want
to have to stop. And then it's only like 25 minutes, but you don't want to have to stop made way.
So find a quiet place to listen to this to this show. I guarantee it's an experience you probably
haven't had ever. And if not that, then in a long, long time. Okay, Doki. So I'll tell you what,
I'm going to head off to a pod show HQ. Today we start moving forward. Oh, you know about Shadow
Falls. I wanted to say, I actually have the entire backstory. And I have, and there's like outtakes
and stuff. And I'm thinking maybe I should let you hear some of that. Or maybe I can post some of
the backstory somewhere because you'll love it when it comes to the, you know, who's going to win
the wolf? It'll be the coyote. Or it'll be some other farm, man. Hopefully the show notes should be
a little bit organized today. I cast Blaster My Cook knee up and told me that I needed to start
a bulleted list in the show notes because now just by clicking and playing a sound that automatically
makes an entry with a time code into the show notes. And if you actually fill out your ID3
information, it will put that in there, which a lot of people still are doing. All right, send me
your music for tomorrow. Well, yeah, it's going to be the thank god as Friday edition of the Charlie
when we're Northern California. We got to rock it out. So send it into me. And that's yes, I'm looking
at you, Jersey Todd, the official music colleges of the Charlie. Get it in early, get it in the
as soon as you can. I'll be back here tomorrow on the source code. Thanks for listening. Bye. Bye.
You still got to hit the right button no matter what. Another pod show podcast. Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance pod cast delivery network
from pod show and limelight networks. I love it.