For the first time ever, the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr. in one action-packed DVD collection,
own all 27 episodes, the cult hit, including all new interviews with Carlton Koo.
First thing that Brisco did that impressed us was, we're not only to come in and really read the dialogue well as an actor,
but he also did a standing flip in our office.
You flipped too for Brisco County!
If you like the kind of TV you can't get on TV, get your copy of the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr.
Available now on DVD!
You'll just do show 475 and you'll come back at 500 and give me what's in your pipe.
A $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm casting his family curry.
Kids today don't pay no attention.
They're bouncing right off the walls.
They're supposed to be still, they're supposed to have fear, that's supposed to be all.
And all the children can't seem to focus.
They're acting out of their minds.
They've been running up a tape and stirring it up, they've been crossing the mind.
We found this thing that comes and comes and we've got enough to go away.
We've got enough to go away.
We've got to do it now.
Let's put them all on the riddle.
The children need discipline now.
Before we land this awful condition, they call it being a child.
I guess they couldn't tell that the kids weren't well.
They let them run wild.
The kids won't mind taking their schools.
They've got it all in their lives.
If they start feeling blue, they get stuff to let you.
It's worth it, we've got enough to go away.
We found the thing that comes and we've got enough to go away.
We've got enough to go away.
Let's put them all on the riddle.
The children need discipline now.
We've got enough to go away.
You've got to feel free to sing along if you're there.
phonics, riddle in, different Tennessee.
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
Welcome to the Daily Source Code episode number
four, seven, five.
Once again in the Curricondo in lovely Northern California.
San Francisco to be exact.
Hey, it is really dark outside at the moment.
I'd forgotten that even in Autumn and Winter,
it even gets a little dark in San Francisco,
at least it doesn't get light as early.
Just past six AM hour and we are rocking to go
in other two weeks here in partially in San Francisco,
at HQ and I think we're going to go to Los Angeles
and New York for sure and sometime next week.
And all right, I might as well come out and say it.
I mean, we were talking about,
yeah, the so we played the song, Riddle in there.
I think that we may have up the dosage,
a little bit too much for some of the Pachio kids at HQ.
I woke up this morning and guess what?
It appears that somebody did not reregister podshow.com.
I might as well just cop to it right now
because I know what's going to happen for the next week.
It's going to be nothing but headlines.
I'll write the headline for you, okay?
Bloggers, you ready?
Whoa, unbelievable, a company that raises almost $25 million.
Can't even register their own domain name.
Go ahead, go ahead and do it.
I'm just going to presume that's exactly what happened.
And however stupid it is, it did happen.
Luckily, we've got a really good relationship with GoDaddy.
So I'm sure we'll be able to get, hopefully,
by the time you're listening to this has been fixed,
but it's just unbelievable.
A stupid can we get?
Ah, this is not the way to wake up.
I really, really hate, if you're listening to serious stars
102, you're thinking the fuck as he talking about.
And didn't this happen with Yahoo at one point?
Or I think it happened with Microsoft,
but it's so unnecessary and so stupid.
And then all of a sudden your domain name gets parked.
And then all your email doesn't arrive.
And people can't get a podshow.com as,
oh, it's so incredibly lame.
I just feel so dumb.
I'll take full responsibility for it.
So yesterday afternoon arrived in SFO,
and I had made a very conscious decision upon leaving.
I had said, I even said to Patricia, I said,
look, I'm so tired of carrying around this studio.
And I don't mind taking the microphone and stuff,
but just unplugging everything.
There's every piece of equipment has its own power cord,
which, of course, needs a U.S. power cord,
or it needs an adapter, and then the adapters
and strong enough, we've been through that before.
And it's just a whole bunch of wires,
and it weighs a frickin' ton.
So I decided to force myself
into finally setting up a full blown studio here
at the condo, by not taking anything.
The only thing I took, of course, was the high LPR 40,
and as we got in around, was I set the condo yesterday
around two in the afternoon.
And like, okay, I'm gonna set out,
and I'm gonna go get some stuff.
Now, I went down to the garage,
and I was gonna fire up Trinity,
which she fires up fine, but there's a flat left rear tire.
Yeah, it just goes from bad to worse here.
So the rear tire was flat,
so I couldn't go to guitar world.
So I figured out what the F,
I'm gonna walk around, see if I can find anything.
Now you have to know where the condo is situated,
which is south of market, but it's very much,
it's right near the Bay Bridge.
It's kind of in the twilight zone.
There's three or four blocks of nothing whatsoever.
But I figured this is San Francisco,
this is a music town, I should be able to find something.
So I set off, and finally,
it was a third, and
dot Harrison, a little bit further down,
but on third, actually the address is 493, 3rd Street.
I see this really funky small store,
called Black Market Music,
and it's owned by Rock and Rick.
And so I walk in and the proprietor,
Rock and Rick immediately says,
hey, Adam, how you doing, man?
I'm like, okay, I'm feeling good.
And this store is literally,
it's where old music gear, and I'm talking instruments,
but also PA systems,
a rack-mounted system.
This is where that shit goes to die, I guess.
It's kind of like that the airfields out there
and what is it?
In the desert in Arizona, where airplanes go to die,
and so I explain the situation, and he's like,
oh man, okay, let's see what we can do.
He's like, I just sold a Mackey board,
which is a well-known brand of mixer.
I just sold out the other day.
He didn't really have any, in fact,
he didn't have any mixers at all.
He had all kinds of outboard gear,
all kinds of rack-mounted stuff, compressors,
limiters, oral, like, ciders,
and we need more oral, like, ciders in our lives, don't we?
All this stuff, and so he basically loads me up
with a whole bunch of cables and stuff,
and so I come back to the condo,
I'm trying to piece everything together,
and I literally found one piece of kit,
which I'm using now, which is just unbelievable.
We've actually been talking about this device
in just in the past week or two,
when we're talking about the Apple,
trademarking endeavors for the word pod,
an iPod, and podcasting, et cetera.
This is, so what I'm doing is I'm running the microphone
through the pod.
That's right.
This is, if you've never seen one of these things,
what do I call it?
It's the ultimate guitar direct box.
So I just plugged the higher into it,
I selected two preamp, I selected compression,
and a low and behold, it kind of works.
I got a little noise gate on there,
and I'm plugging that directly into cast blaster,
so doing all the mixing on cast blaster itself,
because I couldn't just couldn't get all these other things,
all the work together, they were humming and whatever,
but it was so cool that rock and Rick was able to help me.
He didn't even, he said, go ahead,
come back to Monday or Tuesday or whatever,
and you can pay me then for whatever you use.
It was so awesome, it really was a very nice,
and it's just funny to be using this thing,
this red pod device, pod, you hear that pod, pod, pod, yeah.
I'm calling it a pod, everybody.
A little bit of hiss, but it's working.
So we'll have to use that for for today,
and I guess sometime this afternoon,
I'll see if I can find a board,
maybe Michael Butler has a board that I can borrow,
but I'm kind of vibing on this pod,
they's not bad at all.
We got new members of the pod show family,
who have just announced this,
and some people who've been talking to over a long time,
I think probably three quarters of a year,
trying to get, have you heard me talk about Chef Mark,
and trying to get him into the pod show,
podcast network?
Well, he and some friends are there.
Hi Adam, it's Jennifer from Food Philosophy.
Now that we're officially in bed together,
I'd like for you to step into my kitchen,
where I can evoke your senses with supple textures
and titillating flavors.
I'll try to make sure we're always alone,
but sometimes you might hear from Chef Mark
and the kitchen elves.
Damn it, I'm trying to record over here.
And found!
Sorry, Jennifer, it's these kitchen elves,
they just keep getting into everything.
I'm sorry, Master.
We love the trafals.
As I was saying, Adam,
you can find me at Food Philosophy.podshow.com.
Bring your apron, and we can cook up a little something.
I can't believe you did that,
we know that I'm very powerful.
You know, it's for nothing but trouble.
The hell is going on there?
Food philosophy.
That's right, I'll part of the Guild of the Fork.
And I think we're gonna hook up with them in New York
if we're lucky.
I'm doing some things,
advertiser, like huge advertising agency,
what we call it, conference, I guess.
It's a full day.
And I'm on a panel with the guys from my space
and the guys, I think the guys from YouTube as well,
so that should be pretty interesting.
If they haven't been bought by Google by then,
although somehow I don't really believe that rumor,
everyone's talking about it.
I think that YouTube must be talking to a lot of different people
and someone let out the Google thing.
But the genies out of the box,
which actually, if they weren't really in deep conversations
and ongoing negotiations with Google, YouTube, that is,
they could probably get a hard time finding anyone else
now at this number of $1.6 billion
has been put out there.
It'd be very interesting to see.
Now the guy that we've been working on
to get into the network,
haven't worked out all the details just yet,
but he's been a fan of his for a long time
and I've talked to him several times.
We've had a lot of back and forth
between his show, I love the company,
and the chacha, the charlie here.
His name is David Epilito,
that guitar man from Central Park,
and he put out a song.
I think he put it out over the weekend.
You've just got to hear this.
This is what I love about music today.
Is it can be topical?
You can have a song out within seconds,
put it up on the podcast, music, network,
have people all around the globe enjoying it,
playing it on podcasts and just sharing it.
Mama, please, don't let your boys grow up to be pages.
They'll something from thatkatarman.com.
Kids go to DC to learn how the government works.
They'll soon find out that it's all run by sleazebags and jerks.
They'll run countless errors,
stay late, nuts, and weekends work hard,
and then hardly get paid.
By fat sanctimonious self-rack just phony's,
but often just won't get laid.
Mama, don't wreck your babies grow up to be pages.
Or head down to Congress where they'll be in touch
with hypocrites, hasty white perverse and such.
Mama, don't let your babies grow up to be pages.
The belt weighs a black hole that don't have no soul.
Better just let them stay home.
Congress has always been good at protecting their asses.
Especially so close to elections that need to be won.
They're out of memory, they shrug and sweep it under the rug.
Say the good old boys, just having fun.
Some well-written spin can't erase any sin.
Just wink, have a drink, and it's done.
Mama, don't let your babies grow up to be pages.
The sex is the least of the dangers they'll know.
They'll soon learn to push it and lie like a pro.
Mama, don't let your babies grow up to be pages.
Yeah, that belt weighs a black hole that don't have no soul.
Better just let them stay home.
I'll see y'all on the Wednesday wake-up call.
That's David and Polito.
Mama, don't let your boys grow up to be pages.
I've got a topical soul.
So cute because Christina did another pod save the queen.
If you weren't already subscribed, you didn't get the show already.
It's pod save the queen dot com.
She really rocked out this time around.
Now I heard from Patricia.
Christina preps her show.
She takes all kinds of notes and she gets the song.
She's going to play the Christina my daughter,
which is so I love that.
Following in the family footsteps of show business.
And she said, hey, mom, she had some questions about the whole folly thing.
And she said, but this is so wrong, right?
It's okay if someone's gay, but not with teenage boys.
And then she did this whole spiel in her podcast,
which you really should hear because it was just cute.
It was so cute to hear how kids perceive these stories,
how they talk about them, how they process them, basically.
Pod save the queen dot pod shot dot com or pod save the queen dot com.
Hey, I just got an email in.
It looks like the planning permission that we've put in on the house that we've been looking at for.
Oh, shoot, I don't know.
What is it now?
Three, four weeks.
The one that had the covenant on the garage.
The garage.
It looks like we got all the permission we need.
So we can go ahead.
Of course, don't you figure that always happens.
The minute I'm in a different time zone.
I'm eight hours away.
So now I'm going to have to be doing stuff in the morning and late at night.
And getting all this stuff squared away.
Because there's just a tremendous amount of paperwork that has to be done in the UK.
And of course, nothing's final until you've completely gone to contract, etc.
So now we have to take the planning permission approval.
We have to take that to the insurance company.
Because if you do any kind of modification, you want to have some form of insurance.
And so we've got a little rigger moral there that we have to do.
It's going to be, it's going to be quite interesting, my friends.
Hi.
This is your invitation to join me Ed Ovet on a podcast that's out of this world.
With a new episode weekly, you'll hear independent artists from all music genres.
Some comedy?
They know your podcast, there's voice contest with prizes.
And sometimes even a software tip.
So why listen to four different podcasts when you can get them all rolled into one on the Ed's Mix Bad Podcast.
You can find me in the iTunes directory.
Or subscribe via my RSS feed found at my website.
Ed's Mix Bad.com.
So I'll be looking for you on the next episode of Ed's Mix Bad.
Just point your browser.
Where else?
Two Ed's Mix Bad.com.
Alright, so this is where not having a Mixer really breaks down when you have no more volume
left than what people are saying.
Oh, I gotta get that squared away today.
Okay, so...
Cricky, what am I going to tell you?
I'm still a little bit fuzzy just from the jet lag and from the trip.
Although jet, I don't really have jet lag last night, man.
I still had to do some stuff for serious that I was going to record.
I promised PW fenton that I would have all that done by Monday AM.
So this morning, early, so I had to do it last night.
I couldn't stay away.
I literally passed out on the couch with my glasses on.
You know, glasses completely bent out of shape.
Work up at around 11 last night.
And you know, where you wake up and you've got that completely staggering drunk.
You just fallen over yourself.
So I had some orange juice, had some tea.
You know, really had to psych myself.
It wasn't a lot of work.
It's like five minutes worth of work, but I was just so completely trashed.
So we're going to do this week at Pod Show HQ.
We've got a lot of stuff that we've been working on.
And one of the things is video and have some specific ideas that will be coming out with very soon.
Actually, over the weekend, some of you may have seen some testing that I was doing at curry.com.
Accidentally kind of flopped out onto the homepage of my weblog.
And then I shoved it over to another place just so I could test it.
If you found it, and you can actually email me because our domain name works again.
What do you think?
Just messing around trying some stuff out.
Also brand new.
This is the season finale, which is the six and final episode of the season of Shadow Falls.
It is out now if you've not heard Shadow Falls immediately go to Shadow Falls.
PodShow.com.
Do not wait to hear the rest of this show.
Unless, of course, you're mobile and you can't help yourself.
You can always find the address on the show.
It's a daily source code dot com.
Add Shadow Falls dot pod show dot com.
Audio drama and it's best.
And you want cliffhangers?
We got cliffhangers.
Hi, this is Kappa Victoria Wood.
Hi, Holly Jenkins.
Hello, this urban.
And Tracy Crouch.
We're the babes from the cast of Shadow Falls at Shadow Falls dot pod show dot com.
And you're listening to Adam Curry's daily source code.
See, we got to get Shadow Falls back for our second season.
Because now all of a sudden, the ladies from the show are waking up.
Now I've got the hot babes calling me.
Hmm.
And I speak in of which no phone calls today because I can't play external sound effects.
It's a whole long story, but it's all a part of the not having a mixer.
So I hope you'll just bear with me and be able to get through it.
Oh, man.
I'm so totally spacing.
It's so weird.
You know, you get used to a certain sound when you're doing this stuff.
And my studio at home at the cottage is so precisely just everything like that.
You really become conscious of listening to listening to everything.
Yeah, let me just, I'll play on, I'll mess with this pod for a second.
First of me take the noise gate off.
So now you hear the noise in the background, right?
Isn't that interesting?
This works really, really well.
Now I'm going to put the noise gate back on.
There we go.
Now I could actually change any of the settings on this thing.
Because this is meant for guitars, right?
So.
Oops.
Hello.
Wait a minute.
I can't get it through.
Screw it.
I didn't work very well.
It's going to give you a little example of how that work.
We got a brand new sponsor, which I'm going to tell you about.
I'm very excited about because it's a product that I actually use.
Haven't used it in the UK yet.
But hold on.
I'll give you that in a second.
Where is the, what I'm looking for actually is the,
Oh, man, I can't believe I can't find this.
Here we go.
See what I was looking for.
Right on.
Okay.
So please do call me.
Let me know if you were finally able to get through and listen to the show.
And I'll have a mixture and all that stuff ready to roll by tomorrow.
And we'll, uh, and we'll continue with yet another Charlie.
Okay.
New sponsor.
I don't know if you ever heard of this stuff.
It's called Splenda.
And it's, uh,
Yeah.
Well, it's a sugar substitute.
Um, if you go to destinationflavor.com.
Uh, that's the website that explains all the new products.
Basically this, uh, the sugar,
do they even call it a sugar substitute?
Let me see if they have a name for it.
Uh, uh, um.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh...
Product background.
Here we go.
I've got the whole background around it.
So let's figure this out together.
Splenda.
Flavor blends for coffee.
It's a delicious new product from the makers of Splenda.
It's a no calorie sweetener, uh, each flavor blends for coffee,
packet contains a combination of Splenda, no calorie sweetener.
And one of three delicious flavors.
So you can sweeten and flavor your cup of coffee at the same time.
time. So they're available in vanilla, French vanilla, mocha and hazelnut flavors. So what
I thought we'd do is have you tell me what your flavor is? I'll be experimenting this
week. As you know, I'm a big proponent of the Senseo. So I don't have a Senseo machine here
at the condo. It's actually better. I have a cappuccino maker, espresso maker. So
now we have all these different flavors at the office. I think we've had them for a while. They've
been hanged. At least ten, ten weeks, maybe even three months. Since the last time I was here,
I know that they were laying around near the Beverage Center at Potio HQ. And I'm going to
be testing a different flavor every single day and giving feedback to you. And I'd like you to
try it out as well. In fact, there's a special number that is set up for you to call in and tell
us about which flavor you like. You ready? You might want to write this down. It's a 206-604-145-206-604-155.
Of course, I'll put the number in the show notes. But give it a try. Let me know what you think.
Do we have any goodies or anything at the Send-Anybody? I want to send people this stuff so they
can try it out. Hmm. Okay. I really should have read this whole. This is an incredibly long briefing
that I've got here. Oh, they have even, they have a Q&A. What is Splendid No Calorie Sweetener? Answer?
Splendid No Calorie Sweetener is especially formulated brand of sweetener. There's made from sugar,
so it tastes like sugar. It's available in distinctive yellow packets. Ah, that's the trick. The yellow
packets. Right. Convenient for sweetening drinks and sprinkling on cereal. Oh, man. What else could
you sprinkle it on? Use another question. Is Splendid No Calorie Sweetener suitable for the
entire family? Yes. Splendid No Calorie Sweetener suitable for everyone, including children and
people with diabetes. Hmm. Is it considered a natural product? No. The sweetener used in Splendid
Sweetener products is sucralose. Sucralose? Those sucralose is made from sugar and has sugar like
taste. Sucralose itself is not natural. I like it though. I have to be honest. I have tried the
French vanilla. I'm not tried the other. I don't know about hazelnut. I don't know a big hazelnut
guy. If you've seen these or if you've tried them out, or if you want to, let me know. I think
I should be able to send out packets of this. Again, call us at 206-600-4415. One more sign to get
out of here. This is from those wonderfuls. They all call it a wonderfuls. This is the Hillbilly
song. Unsign band from the UK, now on the bot save music network. This should get you rolling.
Hey, what's up, Naver?
I'll leave him all alone and I'll do that one nobody else.
I got what you want, Naver. I got what you need, Naver. I got what you want, Naver. I'll save it for myself.
I'll leave, I'm a silverat. I just don't want nobody else.
I'll leave, I'm a silverat. I do not want nobody else.
Get out of the city waiting, I'll try and look with you. I want to give you some new baby you
would be too. I want to give you some damn. I want to give you team back. I'm going to give you some
better. No you've never had. I got what you want, Naver. I got what you need, Naver. I got what you want,
but I'll save that for myself. I got what you want, Naver. I got what you need, Naver. I got what you want,
Naver. I'll save that for myself.
I got what you want, Naver. I got what you need, Naver. I got what you want, but I'll save it for myself.
I got what you need, Naver.
I've got what you all were asking it for myself.
Saturday 21st of October, you can see him live in action if you're in the UK, a channel 4.
It'll be the Digital Music Awards 2006 where they performed after winning the
unsigned band category at the et cetera awards. It is the wonderfuls with the
Hillbilly song. Okay, that's it everybody. I'm sick and tired of this morning.
Already, I've got to go work on our domain name. I've got to work on a
buying a house and oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, this stuff I was here for. I like work
to do here in San Francisco. Oh, hey, hey, okay. I'll be back tomorrow everybody.
Thank you so much for listening, barring with my begrudging for today. Have
yourself a fantastic week. Another pot show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.