Already a hit state side now you can check out the following podcast and good old
blighty btpotjo.com single-handedly making a men's for the Boston Tea Party one show at a time
You're listening to Delphus Yehera Charlie the daily source code with the one and only pot
on their adamant curry brace yourself for the show that's got it all
potsafe music the lady Patricia and of course your host and curry Delta Seara Charlie 5
0 9er
Sometimes the add-ups on a loan he meets his love right there on the microphone so here she is
yes the lady Patricia the say to have some better than one and with this angel from above
there's nothing that they both can't do make you wildest dreams come true
So grab your ear buds and jam a man and let the fabulous show begin
It's adamant Patricia yes adamant Patricia
adamant the lady Patricia okay I don't know who this is but stop fucking calling
my
Now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now
now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now
He did wasn't mixing
Some very sexy punks up
He's been, some was, he's been, he's been, he's been
I've all, all, all, all in my food range
I'm with each and every touch
Oh, touch
Poke
Puzzo
But, but, I want to speed up, but, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but
I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to and speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to speed up, but I want to.
I want to squeeze your butt, your sexy sexy butt, what do you think I've been doing
my exercise?
I noticed.
Now you do that.
She didn't notice it at all.
Melody Diva is from Australia.
Yeah, I love it.
It's good, isn't it?
It's wonderful.
I want your butt.
And you can actually buy that through the Pod Save Music Network.
It's good.
I like it.
Let's see how it ends.
Come on.
Go butt, something like that.
It's a coincidence, because I actually wanted to tell you about the guy that I'm
dancing with right now.
Oh, yes.
A butt like that.
You're jumping the gun, my dear.
I haven't even properly introduced you.
I know what it's like.
You were thinking about it.
Oh, no, huh.
That is 20 years of captivity is what that is.
Hey, everybody.
Welcome to the Daily Source Code episode.
Five.
Would I say 50 or nine or I think it's 508?
Really?
Oh, fuck me.
Yeah, I said 509.
It's 508.
OK.
You were ahead of time again.
I had of the times and on top of the news.
I know.
Ladies and gentlemen, back by popular demand.
Finally, in the Curry Cottage studios, the Lady, the Diva, star of silver screen
and microphone, the Lady Patricia.
Hello, darling.
Hello, my dear.
Did I miss you?
Are you kidding me?
You know, there are hundreds of thousands of people around the world who
want to know one thing right now.
Yeah.
Did the house was it up to standards when you came home?
Was everything in the right place?
Was the checklist completed?
I was, say, I was blown away.
Yeah.
Everything was right?
You know, I expected everything, I thought, no, you know, I know how they
clean up for, probably in the closets for those of you who missed the discussion of
the checklist.
You know, like I was telling the audience that when you go flying, you have a checklist.
And you have to do every single bit of the checklist.
Otherwise, you know, you could have a real bad day.
So I created a checklist for when you come home and all the things have to do every
single day.
Yeah.
And I did the checklist and it worked.
I saved my life.
I'm amazed.
I'm amazed, really.
And you know, I hated when I come home and it's a mess and, you know, you're tired.
But no, everything looked fine.
Although this morning, I had a little peek in Christina's closet.
I wasn't responsible for that.
And it was one big pile.
I was not responsible.
She threw all her shit in there.
The door.
And jammed it.
She was sticking there.
So it wouldn't pop open.
Jammed the door.
And closed it.
Okay.
Well, I did have a big advantage of today.
So being here on Friday.
I have to admit, that's a big advantage.
Yeah.
That really made it a lot easier because we picked up on Saturday.
So, you know, we basically walked around on our socks on tiptoe from Saturday until I
picked you up from Friday after Teresa left.
And you kept it.
Just don't touch anything.
No.
Every plate we use.
We washed immediately and just put it right back into the cupboard.
True.
Well, no.
It's so good to have you back, huh?
And of course.
Later than we actually, uh, yeah, now I have to say I was a perfect general in and not
tell anyone what was going on because you're only supposed to be going for three days.
Yeah.
And it wound up being five on the six to extra day two and a half extra days.
Six, if you include Saturday, so you were there practicing for dancing with the stars,
which everyone is well aware of.
Now, I just want everyone to know that, uh, while Patricia is doing this,
the entire Dutch pret, let's call them the press core, but of course, it's a paparazzi
and it's trying to get it all over me.
Idiots trying to fill the TV shows are trying to get a hold of you in order to, you
know, do an interview.
And of course, of course, your people are saying no, but she's not interested.
She's dancing.
I'm here for dancing and for for this TV show.
And they all wanted to also want me to just be quiet and, you know, leave everything
to them.
So actually, you're not allowed to say anything.
Well, it's not like they haven't even tried to get to get some interview.
Well, they asked me every time they say, is it are we allowed to tell them this and that?
And then most of the time I say no.
So, of course, uh, necessary.
You being part of the show, uh, we have an exclusive here.
All the news about, uh, your most recent adventure.
What was going on?
Okay.
Let me tell you.
Um, now I have to say this is a very special one because normally,
you're, um, it's longer.
Can I just say I love your lips?
That's a, that's a very pretty color red.
Oh, thank you.
I thought it's almost Christmas.
Yeah.
Very nice.
Looks very Christmas lips here.
Yeah.
Um, normally you train a little bit longer.
You have to come back every time.
You know, it takes a while.
The whole show.
But this one is a special one.
And that's why I said, yes.
Yeah, this isn't like the two.
Because I have no time to go back.
This is not the two month extravaganza where you have to do like 10 different dances.
You're only doing two different dances, correct?
Right.
Okay.
It's a special super super celebrity dancing with the stars.
Yes.
Of course it is.
Yeah.
The very happy are good calls for good calls.
Well, um, no.
No.
I don't really know.
That's what it calls.
Well, it's for my calls.
That's good.
Very good calls indeed.
My dear.
Very good calls.
Because when they called me, I said, you know what?
I haven't done, um, something in a while.
My mom was standing next to me.
Yeah.
And yeah, she was happy.
And, you know, it was getting dark outside.
I'm not, I wasn't really training.
You are not a winter person.
I'm not a winter person.
No.
So normally I would do my walks on the downs, you know, and with the dog or anything.
But now it was not, it's not the way to go outside.
And I have every time I have my excuse, I don't know.
I'm going outside.
It's cold.
Right.
So, um, I thought, you know what?
I have something that I can look forwards to and say, I have to train.
I have to do it.
Because it's for, you know, for this, for the show.
Because if I do, if I say yes, you have to look forwards.
You have to do it.
You've got to kick some ass.
And not just that.
You have to, you're representing the family.
Exactly.
Represent.
That's the most important.
You're representing, you cannot suck.
No.
You don't have to win, but you can't suck.
You cannot suck.
So my mom's standing next to me, jumping up and down.
You have to do this.
You have to, this is you.
And say, mom, let me think for.
So I said, what did I say?
I said, well,
if you really want to do it for yourself, okay.
But realize that everything is going to come back again.
The press will come and everything's going to happen.
I said, do you handle it?
I said, you said.
Can you handle this?
So I thought about it.
I called the girl and I said, you know, why not?
Because I think if somebody has, like me, a heart problem.
I mean, the people in inspiration, my dear.
That's what I thought.
Exactly.
If I can do this, it's a great boost for myself.
Maybe it's my wings.
I will be an example for other people.
Have a problem, but maybe bigger than I have.
Maybe smaller that we can do, you know, these things.
And the only thing is combination of the strengths and the high set
at the dancing.
And you know, because you need a lot of breath for that.
And the combination with being excited and it's a little bit,
let me extrapolate.
Let me extrapolate that.
So with your current heart condition, actually exercise, of course,
is very good.
Dancing, as we know, is a great cardiovascular exercise.
However, your particular issues with your heart,
come upon with stress or form of emotional reaction.
And you have to, yes.
And you have to, you really have to pay attention to your breathing.
So you're, I'm just just playing this on the sidelines here.
So your worry is because of the excitement because it's a show
it's live, it's a contest, all this stuff that you may actually
have a fence.
Hyperventilate in that could force through you into a complete
vomiting spiral.
On live television.
I don't want to make you nervous or anything.
But that's great for the show.
We're not familiar.
No.
It would definitely be good television.
So yeah, so I want to know that.
And it gives me more strength after that.
And maybe I won't worry that much anymore.
Who knows?
You know, I thought about all those things.
So first of all, it's for me.
So how far, so how far is it?
How is it feeling so far?
I mean, great.
Okay.
I noticed that I'm in great shape.
Oh yeah.
But you know that.
Yes.
And by the way, may I comment on your ass and it's tightness.
It's quite.
I mean, this dancing should not.
Can I hire this Remco guy to come once a week?
Just dance with you.
That's very good.
Okay.
So I'm in great shape.
That's no problem at all.
And I can still move my hips.
I get compliments for that.
It's going very well.
I have to say it's more difficult than I thought.
It's very difficult.
Yeah.
Because I've never did that before.
I'm not a dancer.
Especially not with a partner.
I know my routine and you know.
Right.
Now you're doing the walls and you're doing the.
Samba.
Okay.
Yeah.
And so that's the most difficult one.
How do you actually learn that?
I mean, I don't understand.
I don't know where you start.
But in the beginning, you can even say,
I don't get it.
You just remembering all the different steps.
You have to remember it.
And I was just, you know, hitting my knees against him.
Because I was doing something.
But I have to listen and follow him.
Wait.
Someone else told you you have to listen.
No.
You can't really.
I can't concentrate.
No.
Oh, you're kidding me.
My god.
These are revelations.
This is fantastic.
I can't concentrate.
I'm so bad.
If things happen around me.
Come on.
So, you know, these are very interesting.
So, I'm laughing.
I'm laughing.
I'm giggling.
I mean, it's fun.
Until now, it is a lot of fun.
Because I cannot do it.
But he's teaching me.
Now, when you say you can't do it, I don't believe it.
I'm sure you're very helpful.
I have to.
Yeah.
But I am.
I have no idea.
You're basically bullshitting your way through the steps.
I've never.
You know, we always been on the stage and looking at people.
Dancing with each other.
Right.
I was never there.
Not well.
Not this type of dancing.
No.
So, that's different.
That's different.
And the thing is, I, you know, I'm a person that need to be in control.
I think, you know, all of that.
Oh, let me think of, ever noticed that hat.
I said, it's very hard to let somebody else be in control.
So, that's my biggest problem.
Listeners, do you hear now what, now you hear it from someone else?
What kind of for 20 years have been locked into this?
Well, thank God.
I'm in control here.
Well, that's true.
Yes.
You're so out of control.
Oh, boom.
All right.
So, so you've been doing this for several weeks now.
And you had to do this in another training session.
Yeah.
And you were supposed to actually be back today and do another training session.
For me, it's a little bit more difficult because I live in England.
Yes.
And you're not going to stay there.
You husband can't always fly you back for.
You're in in America.
So, I have to be here with my child and my dog and my cats and my house.
So, you know, I cannot just leave it just like that.
So, what we do is Remco is his name.
He is a world.
Now, he's not a national champion dancer.
So, that's good.
Yeah, yeah.
He comes to England and we did a couple of rehearsals and went to Holland and everything.
But what happened?
So, we're a little bit behind of the other contestants because he got a good poisoning.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
That was like a three-day ordeal.
You know how that that takes a while, especially for your.
What is it?
Your physique and I think.
So, an energy.
There's no energy left.
So, that was that.
That was first.
Then a couple of days ago.
I'm falling off of a chair.
It was like that.
Hold on a second.
You fell off a chair.
I fell off a chair.
Just like that.
I was laughing.
You know how.
Where was this?
The rehearsal.
You were sitting on a chair and you fell off.
How did that happen?
You can't have just fell off of the chair.
Well, if the legs just went to the back and.
Were you tipping on your chair?
Well, I was.
You were tipping on your chair.
And just slide it away.
And I ended up on my bum.
Really, really hard.
So that hurt.
But in the right side of my body.
Fell on another chair.
But that was okay.
Because you know, I'm a talk girl.
And I do crazy things in the house.
And I'm falling and sliding.
You're always slamming your bum on something.
I know.
I'm hitting a lot here in the house.
So no problem.
So I stood up and started dancing.
But every time he grabbed me in my waist, I thought,
Oh, my God.
It's like a crack to rip or anything.
You know, but didn't pay any attention.
And two days later, I still had money.
Excuse me.
And I'm not pouring you or anything.
No.
I had a burr.
Okay.
Well, yes.
I've heard the story.
You know, yeah.
Okay.
And then I got this horrible pain when I came home.
Because I'm staying at your father's house.
And my sister's house.
In the middle of the night, a wake-up.
Sweating like crazy.
No.
I mean, I was crawling in the bed.
I was so in pain.
I've never...
I thought, I had, you know, I got a baby or anything.
It was this your heart?
It was delivering a baby.
I don't know.
Didn't feel like your heart was there something wrong with your heart?
No, not at all.
It was all down there on the right hand side of your...
So I wanted to get out of the bed.
And then I don't know it anymore.
It was one big bang.
I was on the floor.
And the phone came up.
And I probably passed out.
Oh, no.
It was one.
And then when I came, it was one.
That was it.
And I said, you've only, you know, I have to go back to bed.
And I take a couple of aspirins.
And I probably...
You do such a trooper.
You know, I don't want to be.
You know how?
I don't want to believe it.
This is not true.
I'm going to go back really.
You don't say.
So I'm going back to bed.
And it started again.
And it got even worse.
And I was...
Was this like a shark?
What?
If you want to throw up?
So the pain was so bad that it made you actually vomit?
Yeah.
Oh, no.
So bad.
That's really bad.
No, no.
No, we are a non-puking household.
We don't.
We just don't do it.
Literally not.
So we can help.
I passed out again.
And he falls.
That's it.
I'm going to call an ambulance.
Hold on a second.
You didn't tell the story exactly right.
You come on man.
You were like Elvis.
Come on.
Come on man.
I want the most part.
What is a person doing when you don't feel well, especially in your...
I'll tell you.
I know.
If I could only take a good shit, it would all be over.
I'll be this.
Okay.
Maybe I'll...
If I go to the bathroom.
To the bathroom.
You know.
Take a shit.
Maybe there's a trap.
Oh.
So.
And then you...
And you fainted on the door.
I'm afraid.
Eating a big Mac.
Let the ketchup.
I'm afraid.
You said the next thing.
Did you do an Elvis?
Ha ha ha ha.
Right.
So you've...
You've on...
There's a middle of the night.
So you've on called the hospital.
Yeah.
If you call the ambulance, because the hospital is very nearby.
So what they do is they sent a doctor first.
You know?
Because ambulance is very busy.
They have this national health care, by the way.
You can tell that they actually sent someone out.
How long did it take before they came?
Oh.
It was in about 10 minutes.
Dr.
And a nurse.
Fantastic.
So when they walked into the go like, oh my god, it's Patricia Pi.
Or were you not paying attention?
Oh, she noticed.
Yeah.
She noticed right away.
And was the nurse a woman?
Yes.
Yeah.
She was a men nurse and a doctor.
And what they looked like was a woman.
She looks pretty good in that.
Even without the makeup.
Yeah.
Are they weren't doing that?
No.
I don't even know.
Of course you know they weren't.
No.
I wasn't even thinking about that.
Okay.
So what did they say?
Well, and then she gave me injection in my thigh.
And she said, this is a sort of a bomb.
A bomb?
Yeah.
Bomb.
And so you will not be impaying for the next hour.
So that was nice.
That was nice.
And but the pain just kept on going.
But she said, you have to go to the hospital the next day and check out.
So they didn't know what it was at that point.
Well, she said, I think looking at your urine and everything.
There's blood in it.
It's your blood in your urine.
Yeah.
So it was my kidney.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was my kidney.
So there was the first doctor.
And the next day, I had other doctors in the hospital saying,
It was a kidney stone.
Oh, wait a minute.
How did it go?
So what I understood is that this could.
And I know, because we had 700 employees at our last company.
And I have actually seen this happen.
Young people as well.
Yeah.
Who all of a sudden, it's not really necessarily kidney stone.
But it's like, you know, little bits and pieces.
And they can dislodge.
And I've seen people lying in the pool.
Well, you've seen people lying in the pool.
Wait a minute.
Let me say it.
I've seen people laying in a pile of people.
I know.
You know, passed out in the bathroom because of the pain.
I mean, it's really, really bad.
Yeah.
So it's not like you have kidney stones.
There's like some dust or something that got dislodged or something.
It can be so small.
And you know, lots of people.
They say one out of three people have this.
They actually, everybody has a little bit of that in your kidneys.
Because that's what the kidneys do.
Yeah.
But sometimes because of a blow or an accident, you know, something that happens.
They get dislodged.
Or for instance, if they start to travel a little bit.
Or for instance, in like four weeks, if you were moving, moving house.
Yeah.
Could have happened.
Should have happened then.
Okay.
So it could, it would have happened anyway.
That's what they all said.
So because I thought, oh, I'm good now.
I'm dancing.
And so what do they do for that?
What are they?
Oh, they gave me a little bit of a medicine and a painkiller.
And they asked me to keep five days of rest.
And then see how I feel.
If it's stay is still there.
You have to go back to the hospital.
And maybe they can help you destroy the distance.
But it's going very well.
Since you're on the show, I presume that it's going very well.
It's going very well.
It's still a little bit.
That's lingering on the pain.
But.
So of course you couldn't travel.
I mean, you had commercial airline tickets booked now.
You had to cancel.
But you couldn't even actually.
No.
I mean, there was no way we're going to let the diva walk alone and in pain through
a through course.
There was an awful lot.
Wonderful.
Yeah.
You picked me up.
Captain Dan and I came.
And it was not the best of weather Saturday.
I'll have you know.
I didn't even care.
No.
I know you didn't.
I wanted to be airlifted and go.
Well, that's exactly what we did.
But then it was.
That was a fun trip for us.
It was.
Yeah.
It was not easy.
But you picked me up.
We ran some shit weather over the channel.
That's for sure.
I just wanted to be in my own bed.
My own house.
But it's going very well.
And and Remko and my dance partner is calling me every time.
Because he's afraid that you're going to cancel.
Yeah.
So, you know, how is everything going?
But everything's going well.
So, now you are behind.
I'm behind.
Absolutely.
Can you catch up, you think?
Never.
But it doesn't matter.
The pro.
I'm a pro.
You'll figure something out.
Show, we'll go on.
Show, musko on.
And Remko will be here next week.
And this week.
I mean, and well, we'll dance a little bit.
Because, of course, I'm going tomorrow.
Unless you don't feel good enough.
Then I'll stay.
But if you feel okay.
But the good part is.
Roxie, Christina's.
Of course, you know, my sister's daughter.
She was, she wanted to come with me every time.
And I thought, why?
Hold on one second.
Those of you who are listening to us on serious stars.
One, two, if you want to hear why Roxie wanted to come along.
You got to go to www.damesourcego.com.
And she's over 20.
And she's seen the show.
So she knows how the dancer looks.
My dancer.
And she is with mouth open.
She's going to look staring at his behind.
Because this guy has the good.
And that's why he was so funny.
You were playing this song.
Oh, okay.
Because this guy has the greatest.
He's got a good ass.
Tied.
Beautiful.
When do I get to meet as well?
I want to eat Mr. Ass.
You've ever.
I mean, he's not gay.
So it's lovely.
Should I be worried?
Or is everything okay?
Should you be where?
Look at your body.
Oh, yes.
Do you see what I have?
I'm sorry.
I mean, why go for hamburgers when you have this steak at home, right?
Yeah.
We can't even better that.
Filming your baby.
That's it.
Wow.
What a story.
That is quite a story.
Now, of course, I didn't say anything on the show because I, you know, the last thing
we wanted is, you know, like, tabloids picking up a, you know, like, a hope of
Trisha.
Yeah.
It doesn't sound right.
That didn't keep me.
Oh, it sounds so old.
You know, women don't want that.
No, of course, women don't want that.
No, men, you know, that cancel concerts and everybody needs to know.
We don't like that.
No.
But this morning, I got the call that they're looking for me.
And they're the magazines already, right?
Well, because someone saw you in the hospital, probably.
Exactly.
And it's not that cool.
Amazing.
How people will then call a gossip magazine.
And you don't.
You know, I'm seeing you in a hospital.
Yeah.
I know.
So that's why here it is.
This is the story.
Wow.
Yeah.
Okay.
Wow.
I'm blown away by this.
Damn.
You know, myself.
Cook.
Yeah.
I know you are, baby.
Wait a minute.
You want it.
Hey.
You have some some voice mail feedback from one of your biggest fans.
And do that here.
You've been a bad boy.
What are you talking about?
With this girl.
Oh, Jesus.
I got a, I want to talk about that in a second.
Being a bad boy.
Yeah.
First this.
Hold on.
Okay.
Why didn't that work?
Come in.
Okay.
Pay attention.
For you.
Yeah.
I'm carry.
I have a message to your wife.
Patricia Pai.
So Patricia.
Just listen to me.
Of course.
I wish you getting well soon.
And good health.
hereby to do some things because I see the two squander your life or what is left of it.
Patricia, to save your soul, yourself, please do the funneling. Point number one, forget about
stupid Netherlands and the dancing competitions and others stupid Dutch things. Just pretend
that these Dutch idiots don't exist. Point number two, Patricia, please resume your singing career.
But this time, focus holy on UK and USA. Create new songs. I repeat clearly, new new new
music. Look at it, new new and create them yourself, all in cooperation with Braids and Americans.
But no Dutch allowed. Have you read these songs on the internet, passionately on iTunes and
passionately on post-set music network of your husband. Point three, point number three, never stop
singing. Sing to your last breath. I'm singing. Sing till your last breath. I thought that was
so funny. I don't see now that I don't know. This is why I love them on the show because
I mean, he's opinionated and a little rougher on the edges, but he's smart. So you love that,
don't you? I thought that we had done this on the show, but apparently I just, I don't
talk about it. That I'd played you the Jeff Smith new Christmas song. And I hadn't told you
who it was. And I said, who do who is this? And you said, oh, that's Jeff Smith. And I said, yeah, you're right.
And you said, I'd love to do a song like that with Jeff Smith. I wouldn't mind doing the
duet and we could, you know, record you part here. So I talked about that. That's what, of course,
where comics were blogger tapped into it. But Jeff actually, of course, he immediately created a song.
And yes, yeah, no, you're hooked now, baby. So I thought it would be a fun idea. And I
cleared it with Jeff as long as I really disclamed it. I haven't played this for you. I haven't
played the track yet. I've had it for a couple days. I want to play it for you now. Now, this is a demo,
a capital DMO. Okay. So Jeff is actually, you know, the track isn't there. The horns aren't there.
You know, none of that is completely done. I don't know anything about songwriting. I have my
own opinion. Oh, yeah. I mean, I know you. My famous song, if you know how they started and how they
sounded in the beginning is very different, right? So I thought it would be really fun to take the
creative process online and do this now in the show. Okay. Have you listened to the track?
Now, Jeff is also singing your part. So, you know, you're not allowed to laugh. But it's just
for the idea. Well, listen to the song. And then, you know, you could pull it apart and give
your opinion. Okay. It's called you better thing twice. And it is a demo
by the fabulous Jeff Smith.
I can feel it's just a matter of time before you chatting me up with the usual.
Well, if you think you get my love and after the drop of the hat, your better thing twice.
Your better thing twice. If you're thinking wrong, that's just simple as that. Your better thing twice.
Your better thing twice. You could add it up through the map however you like. But one and one together,
but it's still ain't right. I appreciate the awful book now. He'd my advice. You better think twice with me.
There's something we could go in on in your mind. I could see you on it, but I'm not that blind.
Playing a cool white side, you're a blaze. Yeah, I say it on with that hopeless gaze.
Don't try to hide us all the way in your eye. Yes, I know you're waiting for your drink to arrive.
Well, maybe if you're thirsty let me put it this way. I don't play that game.
That's so cliche. Well, if you think you get my love and after the drop of the hat,
your better thing twice. Your better thing twice. If you think you're thinking wrong, that's just simple as that.
Well, you better think twice. You ain't no roll of the dice. You could add it up through the map however you like.
But one and one together, it's still ain't right. I appreciate the awful book now. He'd my advice.
Your better thing twice with me. But then the band started pumping. The whole room was jumping,
and at a moment we were on on the floor. A condoled fate over the weather,
but we ended up together. The trumpet's hide is bagged for more. Yeah.
Hey, what was your name? You don't move so bad. I like the way you swing.
Hey, how about that? You look calm and crazy. I think I was wrong.
It's probably better this way on second thought. Hey, what if you think you get my love and after the drop of the hat?
Your better thing twice. Your better thing twice. If you think you're wrong, that's just simple as that.
Well, your better thing twice. Don't be cool as dice. We're in the stars and I'm on all the moon. It's just bad.
My big better than you thought. Oh, it might be so nice. Sega time around might just be all right.
So your better thing twice. Oh, better thing twice. Yeah, your better thing twice with me.
I want to give it another go.
In comparable Jeff Smith with the demo of you better thing twice. Okay. So what did you think?
Yeah, it's it's yeah. I like it. You got to be honest because otherwise it won't work, right?
And not Jeff is amazing. I'm crazy about the course. Not special enough because the beginning
you expect a little bit more and you think here it is. It's really going to open up.
It's really going to be open up and wow. What a great melody. But then the melody of the chorus is not as strong as the
first. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, okay. Let me just let me see you going to find out.
Yeah, here's the chorus. Yeah. You better think twice. You better think twice. Yeah.
There's a little bit of a line. But one and one together, but it's still in right. I have three
she's your normal. It's a normal. It's a bit too much of a, it's too much of a mess there. A little bit
messy in the chorus. Yeah. Okay. But I kind of like you can do and then do the math and then and then I kind of
like that. That that's all right. I mean, I'm not a musician. I'm just a disco jockey. It's not as promising as
you think it's promising. It's promising something, but it's not, you know? So the chorus needs to
need to be more promising. Now this by the way is the way records are made, right? I mean that you,
you'll hear a song and you'll talk it over with the producer and with your, the other musicians.
That's seeing this, this process. I mean, it has a lot to, it needs to open up a little bit more
and something special need to start there. Okay. And but the whole idea, but the song, I love it. Yeah.
I like that. I think your voices will sound nice together, too. Don't you think? Yeah, I think so too.
You can be really good. Yeah. You'll kill on the right key and what key do you need?
Garage key, dorky. They're all these key. R key. Whatever key you want, baby. I'm here to facilitate.
I know, figure it out. Sometimes, you know, depends on what kind of work you have, what is
what feels good. You sometimes, it's, it's one song is different than the other, so. Of course. Of course.
Okay. And be it old and now. Okay. So Jeff needs to work work on it now with those comments.
I'm sure he'll have something back to you in like a day and a half. He's so fast. But of course,
I'm going to be in San Francisco so we won't be able to do anything for like a week and a half.
Does matter. But I can't wait to do this. But does it need to be, is that a Christmas song? No, no, it's
nice. It's just a jazzy. It's on me. It's a very jazzy vibe. Very naughty jazzy song.
Let's be kind of naughty. Okay. I don't know who this is, but stop fucking calling to Sally at home.
What did you do now? I told you about all that. I told you that that girl kept calling up in the
she came to San Francisco. Yeah. Luckily, I didn't run into her or that guy who called. Yeah.
So she's back. I think she's out of the picture. That was pretty scary. Yeah. Scary, man.
I mean, not scary, but it's like, I kept saying, don't come to San Francisco and she came to San Francisco.
Yeah, be careful. But everyone started jumping on the stop fucking calling jazell thing.
And I just got to play a couple of different ones for you. I got a lot of really good ones. Here's
Angie B of the chill cast. Hey, I don't know who jazell is, but stop fucking calling Adam Curry.
Wow. Well, Angie loves me, man. Yeah. Angie's my-
As I can hear. And she's my girlfriend. She's got a great voice. So while I was holding the very
tight ass, you were doing this. Uh-huh. Oh, and it even gets better. And I was worried about-
Oh, what you were worried about? I was so worried about you. What are you doing?
No, I didn't- I know. I was- see that. I'm afraid now that I'm falling off the stool.
Just sit tight and listen to this. I don't know who this is, but stop fucking
using sugar and start using splendor. Here's one that'll totally blow your way.
But stay spent with the outlating and the Alfred- Doots' on-trends, in the data that Lechandani's
Randeo, we're going to go in for a week. Yeah, okay. So this is my old radio show in Holland
From my 1980-33. Oh, ma'am, it's still quite long, actually. It's probably still long.
Oh, beeno. Crocadilles.
The get- hear and rom black crocodile match.
Roda, oh yes!
I don't know who this is, but stop fucking taking the piss out of that crocodile's asshole.
I'm telling you, man.
You know that I didn't even recognize your voice.
Well, it was also 25 years ago, my dad.
And in Dutch, you've sound so different in Dutch.
Yeah, I do.
There's, uh, there's one more you got.
So mature now and so rising.
Hey Adam, it's Paul Durham from Black Lab.
Thanks to you guys for the Podsake Music Network.
And all the podcasters who have been playing our stuff this year.
You guys are real.
You are leading the independent digital revolution and we are psyched to be a part of it.
Today I am happy to announce the first of a few goodies that we have in store for the podsphere.
Few months back I went down to Houston to shoot the first Black Lab video since major label days.
The video is for the song Lonely Boy.
Our latest single from our album See The Sun.
Since podcasting has been so integral to our distribution this year,
since both radio and MTV are, like, dead.
I figured the first place people should see the video is on podshow.com.
So check it out there and then come visit us at blacklabworld.com.
Adam, do me a favor.
Stop calling, Jiselle, asshole.
I get away with money.
You know I've paid for it and somewhere I can't believe it.
Do you feel something when you back in the sea?
Something you want to see again.
I could be the one.
I could make it out to you.
Take me back.
I'm lonely boy.
I love you.
You say,
My broken heart becomes real I say,
I tell it she'd tell you you say,
I still rap all the lies I've told you,
10 dollar bills and smoke and money doesn't burn so clean.
Do you feel something when you back in the sea?
Something you want to see again.
I could be the one.
I could make it out to you.
Take me back.
I'm lonely boy.
I love you.
You say,
My broken heart becomes real I say,
I'm lonely boy.
You say,
My broken heart becomes real I say,
I tell it she'd tell you you say,
I still rap all the lies I've told you,
I still don't want to see again.
I could make it out to you.
Take me back.
I'm lonely boy.
You say,
My broken heart becomes real I say,
I'm lonely boy.
Let's see.
Black Lab.
Lonely Boy.
I think the video premieres tomorrow on podshow.com.
No worlds.
It's a planetary premiere.
We used to say it.
I'm TV.
Radio and MTV are so dead.
These guys get it, you know?
They really...
They are so like dead.
Even Christina is now out telling bands to go on the podshow music network.
You guys aren't rocking if you're on the podshow music network.
Because you get your shit played.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So, you know, I always think I would love to do a show like this with you.
Just this be the show.
It would be so nice.
But first of all, I think it's too hard to coordinate to do it every day.
You know what the real problem is with a daily source code.
I get a format going and then I've got a whole bunch of stuff to talk about and stuff to do.
And you guys can pay me.
That's a big problem.
Come here.
I'll give you my big schmons, baby.
Then you'll own me.
You'll own me.
She wants.
What are all these pictures from Britney Spears?
I cannot believe it.
No.
You know, I can't believe it.
They're not hers.
What do you mean?
That's not her part of her version.
Her version.
Of course it is.
What do you know what they can do with pictures?
Yeah.
And if it was like that.
No.
Really, you know, her vagina.
Yes.
Because pictures of her, you know, part of her body.
If I were her, I would say, you know, sorry, but this is not, these are not my lips.
I showed you pictures.
She can say.
I showed Patricia the pictures yesterday.
And you were shocked, I think.
You were absolutely shocked.
I would be so shocked and so embarrassing.
But you know, it's.
I think it's.
I don't really know what it is.
First of all, I really don't care.
I mean, it doesn't turn me on.
It doesn't do anything for me.
Of course I took a look.
I can't, I can't help but look.
But I like it.
So whatever.
It's for her.
You know, it's Britney Spears is very famous.
She has to go on with her.
So the female body is a beautiful thing.
No matter what part of her.
I know.
But this is, it's all your lady.
You don't do that.
Yeah, but she's, I don't think she's showing that.
But she's not showing it on purpose.
She's stupid.
No, she's stupid.
She's out there thinking, you know, she's out partying with Paris,
Hild, and in Los Angeles.
And they're just not wearing panties.
It's the thing of the day.
Well, you know, I, I did that a couple of times.
But then underneath a long dress, you know, that you couldn't wear any underwear.
So they never saw your beef.
So you have your, your panty hose or thing under it.
And you cannot wear anything like a g string or anything.
Right.
But long long long long long.
Long long long.
But long.
But this, this doesn't make any sense.
Long dresses are not in fashion and it's because they're getting out of the car.
That's the problem whenever they get out of the car.
But she knows she has to get out of the car.
She does now.
Maybe she likes to win blue.
The wind blowing there.
I don't know.
I don't get it.
I don't see the.
Now.
Well, maybe.
I hope not when your fame is not when you're stepping out of the car.
Not when you know there's just not.
It's just not.
It's like the Geneva convention.
You want to go on with your career?
I don't know.
You think this is going to hurt a career?
I don't think it's going to hurt a career.
One thing she can do is say, listen, you may, you might think this is my my vagina.
Oh, but it's not.
This is not a part of my body.
No, I listen.
I'm going to tell you.
It's different.
She has to compensate for the lack of fucking talent.
She's got no talent.
So she's going to do something.
People with talent don't do these things.
Yeah.
People with talent.
Exactly.
Don't need to do these things.
Don't even go need to go out and party.
No.
Like it's 1999.
Yeah.
It's just not necessary.
Paul Paparazzi don't call the press.
It's not necessary.
She has no talent.
And that's what she does.
And you know, and of course we're all obsessed with it.
And it's more important than any other news going on in the world.
Which all with his bothers me tremendously.
Where's this going to?
I think God.
You know, years and years ago, you, you know, they had respect for these sort of things.
You didn't see any Sofia Lauren, you know, in a baby suit where her butt hangs out.
Nobody would ever do that.
You know, you just didn't do that.
Right.
So times change.
We used to have steam engines, you know.
Things change.
It doesn't bother me.
I am.
I think we need to get over it already.
Okay.
So it wasn't, you know what?
I'm embarrassed when I see that.
And let me tell you.
Let me tell you.
Should you be embarrassed?
Because it wasn't really pretty.
That's what no.
That's what she should be embarrassed about.
Yeah.
Wasn't her young girl?
It doesn't look very appetizing.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
They're entire days that I think.
Okay.
Wow.
So anyway, getting back to it.
It's out of my system now.
Would you do a show like me with me like this on a regular show like you, like me?
Wait,.
Adding.
I'm interviewing.
Frigina.
How long?
What?
David Gist, swears his housekeeper's name as legitimate.
How are you getting?
Virginia Casimba.
I was funny.
Yeah, I was funny.
It was pretty good.
How about this?
How about if when I'm here, we do like three shows a week?
Yeah.
We could do that Monday, Wednesday, Friday.
Well, you know, I promise that if I'm in the house,
I'm not doing anything special, just call me.
And is it Patricia?
Yeah, but we have to do something.
What we have to do, I mean, we'd have to do.
I mean, I don't know.
I mean, sometimes I think it's important that people have
something every single day and sometimes I think maybe it's better
if we did a little, like, today's show is definitely longer.
We did a little longer show.
It's a little longer show.
But I promise I'll be in the show a little bit more.
But that's very important.
I can't believe people want to hear that.
I mean, either.
But, you know, it's like I'm stuck with this.
So what am I going to do?
It's not like that.
Thank you.
Thanks for a wonderful show.
It was fun, honey.
I'm going to go back to downloading and bring you pictures.
Yeah.
I love you too.
Okay.
Take care, everybody.
I will know show tomorrow because I'm traveling to San Francisco.
I'll be back Wednesday.
Wait.
I'm going to do my sign off.
Nice example.
Yeah.
Another pod show pod guest, stick it in your ear.
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT Pod Show Media Network.
Howard by Pod Show and Limelight Network.
Control your part in the show at btpotshow.com.