The thy father knows, the thy father knows
Walking down the street on a foggy night, wearing sunglasses, me and my partner show my hair
On hunt the suit of a guy called, the thy father
The thy father knows, the thy father knows
Keep your eye on podshow.com, because pretty soon we're going to help people all that
I think once we get our podcasters up and rolling, and there's a shitload of them
We're going to be bandwidthing, y'all kinds of support, and that work support if you will
Then we're going to go after you, we're coming to get you 100 million listeners
Sixty million dollars worth of air playing strap to my ass
Than the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying you to the future
It's time once again for the Charlie Daily source code is on for Wednesday
How are you doing today?
They met in Paris in 94, oh was it 95?
She was there studying abroad, he was on tour, playing in another dime
They partied hard in the pocketweights, a little north of the sand
He dreamed about her in so many ways
She dreamed about her in French
Well she knows what to do with my coat
She knows how to make it feel
He knew that he's the one, he's the mother's son, not like anyone
Just needs time to heal
They met in New York a few months later
He was still living alone
Hugging the ball and masturbating
Never answered his phone
Their first date was a movie together
Outside of Brian Park
And the spirit of St. Louis
Just went on for a meal until they drank wine
Until they saw us cause
Oh she knows what to do with my coat
She knows how to make it feel
He knew that he's the one, he's the mother's son, not like anyone
Just needs time to heal
They finally hooked up
For the first time
The night before the Fourth of July
He fell so awkward saying goodbye
Into the girl who just changed his life
Now my friend, they are in separate bars
She even gets that boy to go to the gym
Now if you don't think that's love
You must be standing calm
Oh make it man, you're just dreaming in friends
Yeah, because she knows what to do with my coat
She knows how to make it feel
He's the mother's son, not like anyone
Just needs time to heal
Well she knows what to do with my coat
He knows how to make it feel
He's the mother's son, not like anyone
And she just needs time to heal
Yeah, he's the one, he's the mother's son
Not like anyone
And just need a time to heal
Well that's right, he just need a time to heal
By requests, candy butchers, what to do with Michael?
Mike Viola at his best
Nick Zitler requested that one from the pod safe music
Now where he calls it a pod safe classic
Oh my goodness, I don't know about that
But it's definitely a good song
You can find that at music.podshow.com
And of course, links to all of that stuff
In the show notes at dailysourceco.com
And usually about a day later
When you get all the info in the wiki base show notes
At show notes.ingfo
Well hey everybody, how you doing?
Welcome to the daily source code
The Charlie is on from the cottage
In the affluent suburb of Guilford in Surrey
In the United Kingdom
And this morning after dropping Christina off at school
I jetted back to the cottage
So come home
It's like nine o'clock
And then I almost automatically
Gravitated towards a big guy, porn
You know, is this a homosexuality thing
I didn't actually realize that until I just pulled up the
Cartoon of the profit Muhammad
You know, Americans are freaked out by that
What is it with it with you know
Is this a metro sexual moment
And you know
I don't think I have to tell you how pissed off I am right now
Oh man
I really, you know, I have a whole bunch of mixed feelings
About some European countries
Everyone here is just trying to smoke a lot
Drink a lot and drive as fast as they can
And that did not appeal to me
Why?
Because I'll never see any of that money
Because homophobia
I think we want to stay away from doing
And hopefully it will work itself out
In the course of the next couple of days
I may not be your cup of tea
But I encourage you to listen to this song
The shapes
Hey, who are you guys?
How'd you get in here?
Stepping away from the microphone
Are those guns?
You're going to floor now, Gwingo!
Pig!
Time up!
Go on!
Don't hurt me
I'm fragile
We are the podcast liberation front
We have taken Adam Kreeh Hostage
And if I check the daily source code
We will have Lucia
Don't you not even shoot in your gun man
You're just going to shoot, shoot, shoot
And put your fingers in the air
Well, really silent man
I don't want to shoot
But I got two strikes already man
And I'm not going to go on in the car
Then go get it man
Oh, okay, but I need some quarters for the meter
Dude, you're a real shitty revolutionary
If you aren't married to my sister
I never want to let you in the podcast liberation front
Anyway, I thought we were the podcast liberation army man
I couldn't get the domain name
Always army, why can't we be the podcast liberation navy?
Because we don't have any votes
Don't mess
I just shouldn't dump your ass
Dude, dude quit fighting
Don't you understand
We have Mr. Adam Kreeh
We can have whatever we want
He's right
Let's not fight man
All the manices
We have Mr. Adam Kreeh
Right Mr. Adam Kreeh
Oh, bro
We need a Mr. Adam Kreeh
What should we do with him?
I need time to think
Really commercial or something
I don't know how to work this thing man
Don't you get a button man
What's the matter, Karen?
I have a terrible sore throat
Do you have any throat lasenges?
Well, I have my balls
My balls?
What's that?
It's a throat lasenges shaped like a lollipop
Nothing will sue the or throat faster than my balls
Wow, they sound great
Do they last a long time?
Absolutely
In fact, you can leave my balls in your mouth for hours at a time
And that's smooth soothing feeling never goes away
Wow, I can't wait to try them
Here you go
Now tell me
Don't my balls feel great on the back of your throat
My balls throat lasenges
The next time your throat hurts
Lick or suck on my balls
Now a new limited T-bag flavor
We are the Pakistan Steestars
We have high depth of daily source code
Feel her evolution
My favorite book is Fealtz
Your free day of winery, man
Free day of winery, man
I don't know, man
I think one of them is a badge wine scene
The chick is more Canadian
Uh, dude
You know, badge is a dude
He's better at not knowing
Hey, we still have a figure
Now what to do with the Ita Curry
Let's say we pass them around
Dude you're gay. You're gay. No you're gay. No you're gay. Dude. Dude. Dude. Look over there at Paco.
He's got Mr. Adam Curry. Oh my boy boy. Oh my boy. Oh Paco's gay, man. He's gay.
Dude. Go around the cottage and see if you can find Adam Curry Statue of Leopard Concord.
Hey, capitalist pun father pig. What's in the closet here, man? Oh Mr. Adam Curry doesn't seem to want us to look in there.
Open it up, man. Holy shit, man. Oh damn.
But those video tapes, man. What's on them? It says here, introducing everyone's head that's torn by poison.
May 1989. Next one says, introducing girl, knowledge true by Millie Vanilli, June 1989.
I think these are all a Mr. Adam Curry's MTV shows. All of them? See, there must be 10,000 tapes in here.
It is not healthy to obsess about your past Mr. Adam Curry.
Maybe we should put on some MTV for Mr. Adam Curry to watch. I think he likes MTV.
There you go Mr. Adam Curry. Hey, who the hell is that? It looks like the crib keeper. He says it's current loader.
No way. He is dead, man. He died in 1997 at a Spice Girls Press John Kid.
That's his desiccated quarks and amied with wires and shit. That's creepy, man.
Look, you can see the strings if you look close enough.
Shhh, turn that off. I think someone's here.
Meet, play a podcast promo. They don't board them away.
Hey Adam and all the daily source code listeners.
This here is random acclaim from North Platinum Braske, inviting everyone to come check out my show,
the Nebraska Duce cast. The only podcast that's all about Duce in in Nebraska.
Every week, we'll tell you where you can find the best Duce's who's got the best prices,
and we'll have our world famous side by side Duce off.
We'll pick the week's best Duce's against each other and see which ones the best.
We'll tell you which Duce's have the best bouquet, which ones are the most vinegary,
and which ones are just two damn water in a drink.
Now that's just some fine taste and juice right there, boy.
Which one? Well, you'll just have to listen to the show to find out.
So come on by the Nebraska Duce cast and Nebraska Duce cast.com.
Duce cast, dude! What kind of people listen to this daily cold sore?
A daily source code, man. I don't know, man.
But I'm starting to think they don't get out of the house too much.
Just buckle, man. I think he's still with Adam Curry.
buckle, you'll get in there, man.
Boy, boy, boy.
Boy, boy.
Hey, wait! This gives me an idea.
I think I know why we can make a lot of money, man.
Pacific Coast tell way presents a special offer for men, women, and lovers across the world.
If you're looking to spice up your love life, look no further than the Adam Curry sex toy.
It's not some cheap piece of latex.
It's not some battery operated plastic gadget. No.
The Adam Curry sex toy is in fact, Adam Curry.
The Adam Curry sex toy will service your every need and enhance your love life like nothing ever has.
With over 35 points of flexible articulation, the Adam Curry sex toy comes ready to perform.
Whether you're a woman, a man, a married couple, a gay man, a gay married couple,
a group of gay men ready for a party, or just looking for that special something to add to the atmosphere at your bath house.
The Adam Curry sex toy is just what you've been looking for, but never dared to dream possible.
The Adam Curry sex toy comes prepared to perform or receive a wide variety of love making activities, including missionary doggy style.
Reverse cowgirl, donkey punch, fish eye, hot launch, and the filthy Sanchez.
And thanks to the miracle of podcasting, the Adam Curry sex toy now comes with hot vibrating lip-flaping action.
And it was awesome.
It doesn't podcast.
Morning, hot lip-flaping action cannot be turned off.
So if you're looking to bring your love life to the next level, try out Pacific Coast Hellways Adam Curry sex toy.
Available exclusively at PacificOcellway.com.
It puts the ass in podcast.
Man, this hijack is going nowhere.
Hey, any of you ever done this before?
See?
I wasn't involved in a failed assassination attempt on Kennedy.
With the humans back in the 60s?
No, dude.
With Martha Quinn in 1992.
She wanted that ugly four-eye skin, Kennedy on MTV, Rob Downman.
Dude, turn off your phone, man.
We're in the middle of a hijackie.
Sorry, sorry.
Hello?
Michi Cabron.
Mama.
Busy.
I can't talk right now.
Okay, Mama.
I gotta go.
I gotta go, Mama.
Oh, sorry.
What did you do, man?
I knocked over this statue here, man.
What is that?
A really Martin figurine?
I don't know.
It's just a bunch of hair, man.
I think it's him.
Mr. Adam Curry has a hairy little statue of himself.
I think it was an award or something, man.
Look, there's an inscription.
Do our favorite big-haired fang.
Love Pacific Coast Hillway.
Oh, that's really sweet, man.
Those guys are the best.
Oh, yeah.
I hear they give a lot of money to the poor and stuff.
And this is the poor social causes.
And they all have really big penises, man.
Dude, how would you know that?
Pacific Coast Hillway.com, man.
They got pictures and everything.
Okay, first of all, that's not even true.
Second, why would you look if it was true?
It could be curious, man.
Dude, the cops, we gotta get out of here.
Michael, you gotta get off Mr. Adam Curry, man.
We gotta run.
I'm stuck.
I need you to help me.
I'll do it.
What do you mean, man?
He glanced off, man.
Back to hurry.
Yeah.
I'm starting Mr. Curry.
This is good.
I heard you are.
Then it hurts me.
Run!
Oh, just put some ice on him, man.
He'll move back.
Oh, we got it.
Oh, now!
Leave a look at it with me.
Oh, yeah, sir.
And we're gonna do something different today.
It's been quite a, quite a crazy morning, actually.
The bottom line is, right now, I'm gonna get it in the can.
I believe it could be the other way around.
I don't know what the proper name is.
What was going to happen is I was going to be picked up by Roy,
and I think Nick was going to come along.
We're getting screwed.
I was cool.
Of course, I'm tethered.
And then I'm going to have some lunch.
Oh, man.
Meanwhile, on the podcast, music thing is seen,
things are going very well.
We have a major, major artist sign up
and has dropped three songs onto the PMN.
And one of those is titled Ever Since.
I'm gonna play it right now.
This is Leslie Gore.
I dreamt you.
I drew you long before I thought that I might never find you.
I chased you.
I traced you and held your picture up into the light.
All the way to the night,
some day is too long to just cry.
All the parties I've been through,
you were missed.
I waited ever since.
I met you.
I tried to forget you.
You know I felt somehow,
someone had sent you to me.
And as if you knew me,
we picked up where we left off
in another life.
The times I tried to settle out
for so much less than this song.
I waited ever since.
All the way to night,
some day is too long to just cry.
All the parties I've been through,
you were missed.
I waited ever since.
I met you.
Oh my gosh.
Matt's from Bristol says,
Adam, I waited a hospital last week
for small operation, nothing too serious.
Thank goodness.
I think that that I was prepared for that
and that I almost automatically
gravitated towards explaining
but I have the long-haired lover from Liverpool.
Man, what a genius, genius talent.
The funny thing was that in his email
he said, hey dude,
love it if you stick it up at turbine.
Anyway,
the,
to,
and so I fired off an email.
I said,
you know,
right now,
and then I'm going to,
anyway.
We got to go.
We got to get out of here.
Those of you listening to a serious channel 102.
This is the daily source code part of the pod show line up.
Up next,
we will have Pacific Coast Highway,
followed by yeast radio and Dawn and Drew.
We'll take you up until 10 o'clock eastern time,
7 Pacifica.
And if anything,
it'll be fun to figure it out
if we can stir up some shit.
Dig it.
All right.
One more song.
Cool water's banned.
Don't forget where you came from.
I'm a little confused.
About all this enemy fire,
about drug laws and holy walls,
and people freaking out,
over what they want to freak about.
Oh,
so tired.
There's nothing on my radio.
Some little girl who laughs and sleep,
reloads and tries to sing,
how she wants to dance.
And all of me,
I sometimes wonder what they gave to me there.
And don't forget where you came from.
No, I won't.
Don't forget where you came from.
And don't forget about all the people.
You'll laugh into your head.
And don't forget where you came from.
And don't forget about all the people.
You'll laugh into your head.
When I think my girl got a call to share her time, go by, got a little too husk.
You're blaming all I'm talking about, yeah, I'm just easier, a little easier.
Slow down, so we're going to find a down, with a graph screen, you were so obscene.
Maybe your sign didn't look like mine, but I'm fine.
Yeah, I don't want it.
So I'll be where you came from, no, I won't.
You'll be where you came from, no, I won't.
You can't even change from no matter what you're gonna be when you're making it.
It's over here now that I'll be following you and I'll be into your path, into your head.
Go Waters Band, don't forget what you came from, from the rose pedal to the metal CD.
You can find it all on the Podsafe Music Network at Podsafe MusicNetwork.com or
if you prefer music.podshow.com.
That's it for me and I'll see you back here tomorrow.
Bye-bye.