Potcho is pleased to bring you the following killer content direct from the all new feature rich potcho dot com get it play it dig it
And now a word from the toots tell me shows up in what you said is you wearing an opposite
And I ran just picked up but with pink sunglasses. No, it's raining outside for the little gray
Let's take the boy out of MTV, but you can't take the end of the boy. That's all I can
Did you have to kiss this rain when he comes when you come to him? I've kissed it. Well
You kiss
Exactly
Not with the you joke
Kiss my ring. I've got a big jump
Oh, interesting. Well, he's got what? He's a smart guy
I've got $20 right here for you. And a US cash on the ticket
If you want to be out to it. He's come on. Bye. Delta, Sierra Charlie 501
$16 million worth of airplane strapped my ass
Then the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into the shirt
I
Question everything
Everything is wrong by definition
Answer key in repetition
You don't know anything
It pauses me in hindsight
Frammonition my static heart is fish
I bitter harmony
I know that it sounds very dumb before
I guess I've just expected more
The bigger ball with one
Now stillness all is done
But make him plan some real time
But we're on the burn economy
When I close my eyes
You always disappear
It's not like me to shave and say I'm sorry
Where's my finish line
It's never been down here and I feel waiting for a back lift story
The world will wait for me
So I thought when I was feeling upset
But I was so many young and stupid
There has happened
Others will be placed
I know what I was
But that points to nothing
When I close my eyes
I always disappear
It's not like me to shave and say I'm sorry
Where's my finish line
It's never been down here
And I've been waiting for a back lift story
When I close my eyes
You always disappear
It's not like me to shave and say I'm sorry
There's no way
So when I close my eyes
Just disappear
You always disappear
It's not like me to shave and say I'm sorry
There's no way
So when I close my eyes
Just disappear
You always disappear
It's not like me to shave and say I'm sorry
There's no way
So when I close my eyes
Just disappear
It's not like me to shave and say I'm sorry
There's no way
So when I close my eyes
Just disappear
It's not like me to shave and say I'm sorry
It's
Nurse reverse engineering kick-in-off episode
Number five zero one of the daily source code coming to you from San Francisco, California from the Curry Conno
Good morning
Good afternoon, good evening or house tomorrow down there in Australia
I love it when these guys write some stuff on the pod tape music
Now work about themselves
Indie rock band from Toronto
Please visit our MySpace page
Here it goes
We're all proud of our country and city without being overly political
We have a sense of humor we hate rock stars we just love to write and play
Hope you enjoy let us know if you do well of course just by reporting the song you automatically be notified
Hey, it's a bright and early here on the west coast
Of course I'm here this week um out at Pod Show HQ
In San Francisco thanksgiving week so
Getting the hang out with a lot of people
There's a couple of uh I got definitely to get together's planned
Near the end of the week looking forward to that a little bit of bonding with the
With my amigos and amigos out here
Hey big news that I have just not seen anyone report on I really really really don't understand why I'm not seeing more
More about this certainly online
Clear channel has agreed to be acquired
The buyout is going to be completed
18.7 billion dollars let me just go to the
I'll crap I hate it when I do that I have all my notes in google note pad and if you click on a link there
It doesn't pop open a new tab or a new window
Sox anyway
Here we go clear channel communications the owner of so this is from
New York business.com
The owner of seven local radio stations said Thursday it is agreed to be acquired for about
$18.7 billion by group of investors led by Thomas H. Lee partners and bane capital partners now remember
Whenever an industry is on its last legs there's only one thing it can do it's
Consolidate so that's what clear channel was it it consolidated thousands of radio stations
But also outdoor venues and all kinds of
Related businesses and then there's only one thing way to go after that that's exactly what this is the company will be taken private
It's a management buyout
You know this is very similar to barbarians at the gate. You know KKR did with RGR in the bisco
That usually fucks companies up
I hate to say it for all the folks who are working at tier clear channel related companies
But that means that certainly for the next year there's gonna be a lot of turmoil in radio people are gonna be
Looking for well looking out for themselves of course
I don't know what they had like 40,000 employees in total
So when a new company comes in a management buyout like that what they do typically is they
Trim everything down get rid of the quote excess fat which is usually comes in the form of people
And then they they start you know chopping it up into bits
So I think this is the time we really need to strike my friends
It's strike hard. There's so many podcasts out there
Some are good in some are
This custodian. Oh, they're not that bad. Oh, not take the one called dancing with elephants for example. It's family safe
I told you join Greg Tanya Nikolai and Caleb. Wow find them at dancing with elephants.com and join the fun
Okay, we'll see you later. Bye. Bye
Yesterday got a kind of a weird phone call on the voicemail
Apparently from someone who knows jazell jazell. It was been calling me up and
chatting me up to say the least
Let me just play that again. So so we can remind each other of this
I don't know who this is but stop fucking calling jazell ant hole
I got a lot of people saying hey, what's going on with that? Okay. I got an email
From jazell honey. I heard your show today
Want to say I'm so sorry for so lots of those sorry for that message in your comment line
I am so embarrassed that was Nick who's a complete jerk and isn't anything I really want to talk about but he doesn't control my life
A friend of mine says I said there is a train that goes from San Diego to San Francisco if that's true
I'm gonna come up there on Wednesday because I don't want you to be all alone for Thanksgiving
And then she says here's something to think of me by and she sent me a picture
Excuse me the old man and me can barely handle this is like a
Very nice belly button picture
Love jazell PS I would tell you to call me, but I don't think it's safe for me to use my phone for a couple of days until I get a new one
PPS I looked it up fun. Oh god. I looked it up on the internet. I know where the pod show offices, so I'll just meet you there
jazell. I don't know this is such a good idea
Oh, sorry, it's way too early for me. You know
Maybe we should get to know each other a little bit before you actually come on over here
Yeah, I'm just over current you tell us near just responding to a comment made by the guy from spine grayio.com
I think that's at 496 I'm a little bit behind at the moment
You sort of that was zoom
And he was saying that's
Well, you know if you could set a windows media play just monitor a directory and if you download your podcast as an app
Then it will upload them and that's all well and good and that's better than the iPod does because you need
I actually want to get your podcast and it's a point that windows media play can do that
But unfortunately windows media play is not supported on the zoom the only software that the zoom supports the stuff that comes with the player
Most of our so confident in their previous
MP3 products that they're not supporting
Those previous products including the thing that's bundled in every copy windows on the using
So there's only pretty much a podcast free zone at the moment
Just so I see that back to you. Thanks a lot, bye
Yeah, I appreciate it lots of people and I haven't really talked about the zoom that that much
Obviously because out of the box it doesn't really understand what to do with podcast and unless you
There is a way of course to drag an MP3 file into it somehow. I haven't seen one of these
I have my hands kind of have been itching to check on out
But most of what I've heard is oh, you know, they don't support podcasting
And of course already the hacks are appearing on the scene. This came in this morning
Yeah, and I'm this is a shoes calling from Chicago
You were talking about
All of a sudden you were talking to soon and that's how you need software
or
And that having software to play
podcast or to get podcasts while I found out there's a program called our website that's called feed your soon
All-one word that call of course, feed your soon that come off is a program that accompanies the soon player
And let's you download
Podcast to the zoom so you can play them and it seems to have some next features and hey, maybe there's a solution that you guys might want to be aware of
You know, it's interesting. So I'm looking at this feed your zoom dot com look at looking at the page and
It's just like iTunes
Which of course, you know, on the one hand it's good because it looks like it can actually
Subscribe you to podcasts and automatically download audio and video onto your zoom device
Of course, this is yet another piece of software you need to manage
To use to manage content to get it onto the device
You know, I think that there's a really a hugely missed opportunity here
You know, what's happening with these hardware manufacturers is they they market these MP3 players and video players and they market it with you know
Essentially the only thing the consumer
Cares about or at least I do as a consumer. You know, well, what content can I get with it?
It's just like VHS and beta max, you know, who was buying beta maxes
Well people who didn't want any content
You know video stores sprung up and then of course everyone went to VHS because
VHS had all the actually the porn I guess in the early days and
All of these devices all these portable media devices are all being marketed as music machines
I really believe that if you put a cheap machine out there in the marketplace
But marketed it
As a podcast receiver a pod catcher or
Something along those lines I
You know, or just said hey you want some great fucking alternative content to your radio. It's on this device
Excuse me since I was blind on folders and all that stuff
So I think that the first you know, there's got to be someone out there who can put a
$99 device in the marketplace. Maybe we do it without audio first just to do it without video just do it with audio
And and you know market it with look at all these these great shows you can get on this device
I think that you know, I think that that would work
And of course the zoom will support pod casting absolutely you know that it's it's gonna be in the next step from where revision or whatever
So I think that's the missed opportunity here
And it's very very hard to compete with something as massive as as iTunes in the iPod
Anyway, keep an eye on it. So yesterday I told you that I was receiving lots of emails and audio feedbacks about
Being discussed on this week in tech episode
What is it?
207-7-H whatever that means. That's the identifier here on the file and and I listen to it
I was pretty amazed first of all about
the misinformation
being the disseminated through the show
But also the invitation was quite interesting. Please listen in with me to this week in tech
Leola port
Jonsi de Vorak, well I'm a big fan of and I've known for a long or I met a long long time ago
And I'm a big fan of what he does and then
Forget the guys name he interviewed me at podcast con uk on Saturday and London and essentially he interviewed me and then
Went right on to to he is a I guess a semi regular on Twitter
And he had the following to say about me
So I was anyway at the grocery store, you know, and he leaves you know after you know
You should hold on a second. That's somehow it jumped back in in cast blaster
Let me see
He's Jonsi de Vorak talking about
Famous people and that of course is the impetus here to start talking about me
Ah, that's Leo talking some crap come on get to the
Somehow I had it set up exact the exact point set up in cast blaster and then it like jump back
I don't know if that has to do with the file size
This is that's how the real world feels about podcast usually a logging web 2.0 web 3.0
They don't care the whole world's going yeah, whatever
Yep, that's very depressing
All right, it's true you're right. What is the the other father of podcasting adzam curry yesterday?
What oh my god, this is amazing. Where did the man? Where'd you meet him?
Uh, podcast con uk. Oh really they had a podcast uk version of the portable media expert right in it with emphasis on the word con
All right, all right, that's a funny line
That was the in joke. Yes, so tell me about what happened to podcast? Well, he tensed up the apparently he's moved to England
Yeah, that's right. He was apparently how about I've been there for two years, dude
Belgium or somewhere and now he's back
Yeah, he's actually he tends up because is it hot show?
Yes, this guy is now pretending like he doesn't know who I am or or who pod show is he was all over me in podcast
I got to find out what this guy's name is because now he's like, oh, I'm going to talk shit about Adam
I think this company has his company has now got a sort of uk version, which is
BT pod show British telecom pod show who sort of bulls with concept. He is a man. He is a mad deal maker that man
I can't believe we turned up. He's got you know how much you just seen how much much venture funding he got for pod show
Half million oh it's over 15
Really no actually it's a over 23 15 million wiki pd says eight and a half minutes
Oh, it's behind the time. I got no, no, please whatever you do believe wiki pd
Okay, that shit's always right behind the times
I wanted to go in and edit that and put in the correct number and I got deleted because people said I was over inflating shit
But both numbers are ridiculous. Where is the show me the money?
Yeah, so what is so tell me he shows up in what you said he is he wearing an outfit
And I rate just pink jumper with pink sunglasses no this raining outside and we're the middle of grey London right now
Yeah hold on a second hold on a second dude first of all
These aren't pink sunglasses
He was sitting no more than 20 centimeters away from me
Their glasses and their rose colored glasses
I love watching in the world through rose colored glasses
You're totally misrepresenting that I was wearing sunglasses inside now
They were not sunglasses did completely wrong and then the jumpa as you call it is a sweater
Of course, it was pink and matched the glasses before I leave the house. I have two very stylish women
Who evaluate what I have on and then dress me up
I'm so sorry. I didn't know that you or the rest of the podcast community were the
Fashion icons. I thought you were no got the pink sunglasses take the boy out of MTV
But you can't take the TV out of the boy. That's all I can say right and he was really interesting even though he's like
What he's like 63 now oh fuck you Leo dude
You know so many people
I got really I could start it very early. I was on television when I was 19. I'm only 42
Please don't make me feel any worse than I already do about that Leo. This took at the long blonde hair in the pink jumper
And he's out in the corner. It's basically just chatting to people who are coming up and looks like grandpa on one stir
He Leo. I know you're kidding about this, right?
He never happened to graceful aging gracefully. That's all I ask
I'm throwing some quick say what was it what he's what he was kind of like the bad boy in the corner. Is that what he was doing?
No, man
That was just feeling up the females yeah people were just like saying hello and he was throwing it
I think well the did you have to kiss his ring when he comes when you come up to him or man?
He has got quite a big ring. He does. I've kissed it. Well
Kissing you kissed not exactly kissing when anyone was here somewhere
Yeah, no punch line. He was just throwing crotes out like you know how thick was it was never going to be worth
Anything that it was just like a policy. You know what you want to know the sad thing and that dig stuff
You know that is so you are such a dickweed
You know, I thought you were a journalist. You know that is not what I said
You're taking my my words completely out of context
Who is this guy but when he get brain damage
No, because he has eight and a half million he knows
Well, yeah
digs never going to be worth anything
Kiss my ring. I've got a pink jumper
You show you don't like Adam I take it. No, I'm just teasing him. I don't know. He said he listed he said right
This is the best quote from him all day. I said I slice me at him. I actually do a podcast
I'm on the as by a friend of my Lea La Poe. I do this week in tech. He said oh, yes
I know this week in tech. Oh, yeah. I know he said generally I all like do is I check the website to see if the
I'm not that late. Oh, interesting. Well, he's got what's up? He's a smart guy
Adam carries your biggest fan job
I'm not as big as fan, but you know, I met Devorac in the very early 90s
Maybe it was even maybe it was 80 maybe it was 1990
This outfit in California and at the time I had it, you know, I was just working at MTV for a couple of years
I had an agent in Los Angeles Marion Rosenberg very famous agent who
I think what I had gotten some kind of gig on a totally hidden video
Which was a Fox TV show and the executive producer of that a guy named Kevin Wendell
Who would I think actually help set up the Fox network of television stations
formerly known as the
Code hanger network
The wire code hanger network
He was brought into Cnet early on because it was a television project
It was going to be a television channel and it was going to be a tech oriented channel
On cable and
So I think it it came through Kevin Wendell and he had of course teamed up with the founders of Cnet
Shelby Bonnie and
Halsey minor
I'm sure there were other investors and they basically
Said you know, you know, they contracted me to come out and do a pilot and the pilot consisted of a number of different shows
There were basically creating a I think like a 12 hour block of Cnet programming and based upon that
They would go out and get get more venture funding and it was one of the most amazing trips of my life that that I've ever made because it was actually was it was life changing
Because I remember I'd never really been to San Francisco. I remember arriving at SFO and you know
Seeing like I'd never seen so many laptop bags in my life remember this is a 1990 or 91 very very early
And you know, there was a guy sitting over in the corner with his C++
Developers kit
Yeah, you know the the actual shrink wrap box under his arm. I'm like wow that this is and I was geek, you know, so I thought yeah
This could be kind of a place for me
You know what the real bummer is
God, this is a bummer. If you're listening to this on serious satellite stars 102
You got it down low the rest of the show with daily source code dot com to hear the rest of the story
Because there's some good as history in here when it comes to Silicon Valley so anyway you guys love to do that and I also have a shakes live recording
To anyway
They they didn't even have a website in fact
During that I think it was like a weekend where I
Where this was taking place it was a really cool set
You know lots of television professionals. So it was pretty fun to work with them
There was a co-host on the channel at the time Dr. Mae Gemison
astronaut
And she was extremely nice and there was a
And then there was kind of like a roundtable
program
For get what it was called but it was very much like the McGlockling group and John C. Devorex sat there with a number of other
um
Well, I guess you would call them pundits these days
In fact very much like what the Gilmore gang is only it was a video version and I was fantastic you know there was
John Perry Barlow I
Met him there and hung out with him
That's where I met Mark Cantor for the first time and I'll never forget you know three o'clock in the morning
Mark Cantor holding court and all these kids and myself included basically sitting around and
Spoken dope listening to stories of early Macintoshes and early
Just really the early Silicon Valley days of personal computing and it was it was just so enthralling
I'm like wow this is like a like hippie stuff out here for geeks and I have to admit I felt very very comfortable and very very much at home
I really don't think so no
Adam's a great guy and really what there would be no part you know he used to be a scene at in the early days and they got rid of him
For some oh
I hope that is not what Shelby and Halsey told you John C
Here's what here's what happened so I did the pilot which they paid me for and
You know before I did that we actually signed and agreement you know that said well, you know if everything gets picked up then we'll take you on for this amount of money
And it's like two million options or something like that options in C net
And as I said a minute ago, they they didn't have a website so actually while I was there that week and a registered
C net dot com for them and
I set up a email forwarding to their AOL
addresses because they had all they had was AOL
America online and American online didn't even have remember this was pre American online
Giving their users access to the internet remember those days when you could only use the AOL browser and
And they would only let you go to certain sites and it cashed everything for hours and all man how the good old days
And so you know I actually ran there their
Their email and their domain name registration for almost a year so after that weekend
You know a couple things happened. Oh, also I had to move to San Francisco to do it and you know that was one thing the
Petrition I definitely weren't really it wasn't the right moment for us to move to San Francisco
But also I felt that they had no vision, you know, I was I and I remember telling them there
Said you know, do you do please you know the future of what you're doing here is great the whole idea of a content
Network around technology is fantastic
But you've got to look further than a cable channel. You've got to look at what you can do with this stuff online
It's all gonna come it's happening and of course these guys just didn't have the vision because they couldn't even see the internet because they were on AOL
And so I I wasn't too sure. I was gonna take the gig to start with but then they did something really
I think it was really stupid
Oh, it certainly wasn't a nice thing to do. They got investment in based upon
I guess partially based upon the pilot and then they had to do like a reverse split and
What's the word I'm looking for right I never have to deal with this word
Oh
I'm spacing
I know the Dutch word
for Valtara
crap anyway
I had two million shares and then all of a sudden all that had to change and there was all this paperwork and
Delusion. Oh, thank you. I told you it never have to deal with that
And and everyone was deluding
So instead of you know taking this out of their own option pool or however else they were dealing with the money coming in and the shares being split up
They took it away from people they had you know promised a part two before that. It was just it was like fuck you
You know you guys got no vision and you clearly aren't entirely nice
So I'll just pass you know thank you very much
I had a good time but I'm not gonna take you up on the opportunity so they didn't get rid of me John C. Devorek
I did not get rid of me
God
But I'd like to know if that's what they told you in another way. He was quite the visionary
I mean when he was at MTV
He left and and started an ISP
I mean, I know here's a piece of sharp eye. I did not start an ISP
Leo God this how this is you got you know this is what happens whenever you listen to or listen to a
Show or read something that's about yourself you hear all these
Incredible inconsistencies untruths and mistakes and you've got to question
The next thing you're listening to or reading which you don't know that much about you've got a question if it's ever's a writer not
No, I did not start an ISP
I started a company called on-ramp
Now there was an ISP called on-ramp in Texas at the time but it was definitely two different types of companies
I started a really what was it turned out to be an interactive advertising agency. We were building websites. You know first client was
What do we have? We built planet reboc.com but wiser dot com tampax dot com the website
You'll visit more than once a month
We built continental airlines flightcontinental dot com
You know that's what I was doing and yes, I did leave MTV. I quit on the air and said
I think the internet's the place to be we should go find that piece of video someone has it somewhere
It was right after the number one of the top 20 countdown. I remember it was loser by back
Which I thought was just so interesting but I'm surprised you know I think I remember I was in Europe
In the late 90s before the dot com bus and I was reading one of these I think it was a Dutch paper
Talking about him how he's worth a hundred million
Devorac can read Dutch
Dollars and he's very good at promoting himself and
I couldn't figure out what yeah, I think and wow, you know because he owned all this stuff and then didn't I don't know what happened
And then next thing you know he's been doing a bunch of other stuff and so I I think he's he's
Become a mysterious person and so far as what is what he's worth what money is
I got you know what we want to keep it that way John C. Devorac
I want you to be always thinking what's courty up to what's he doing behind my back?
What I've got $20 right here for you Adam U.S. cash on the table if you want to be on Twitter just come on by
$20 waiting for you
I bet he's heard of Skype
Yeah, he'd be fun to talk so was podcast content fun of concast UK con anyway, so any goes on and on now I'll put a link in the show notes to the show
So I emailed Leo. I said dude 20 bucks
Stick you know shut that up your ass. Of course. I'll come on only to do with ass
You've never asked me to be on the show, but I'll only do it if John C. Devorac is on
So he wants me to do it Sunday, but I'm I think I'm flying back Saturday and one and you know
I want to arrive until Sunday late and warning and
I'll be jet lag and I want to be really fresh when I talk to these guys and get that English guy on too
That's the so-called journalist will you please?
Hey Adam Mike here from the fishball at fishballacoustic.podshow.com
Just wanted to let you know that the recordings that we did of the shakes at the podcast conference turned out really well and a couple of
their songs I'm reliably informed have now been uploaded to the pod save music network
So if any of you listeners want to check out some great live music from the podcast conference on Saturday
then head over to the PMN where you'll find two or three tracks from the shakes and maybe you'll
obliged by playing one of those on your show you never know anyway congratulations on the big 500
Adam nice one mate. Talk to you soon cheers. It's another first the first kick we've ever played
We've had name badges
You guys has been a bit rock and roll rebel. It's not wearing his
Look at him raging against the system
It's next on the chinkled daylight
Hello
What can you do with your man who won't be able to change?
I swear, but I swear, but now they're blue.
All the trippin' payin' for me, use cock and disappear.
And all I seem to think about is you, thickening it in daylight.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Stop me flaking out, yeah.
Uhh, uhh, uhh, uhh, uhh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
I can't talk to him because he's dumb.
Singin' to you the most handsome I'm strong
Take it easy and take it on
Yeah, yeah
Stuff me flyin' out again
The shakes from podcast con UK
I think I need a little bit of daylight
Yeah, those guys are great
Fantastic links in the show notes, of course
DailySourceCode.com
There was one more thing that I didn't get to play yesterday
That was just so funny because it's since we've been talking about history here
And the more I think about that guy who passed himself off as a journalist
And then, you know, clearly trying to, you know,
Bake entertainment out of our encounter
Behind my back with, you know, just fuck you
Get that guy on, okay?
When I come on the show
I gotta talk to him too
All right, this is something I didn't get around to yesterday
But I really liked because it is a piece of history
That's, that's pretty funny
Anyway, I just thought I'd send a little gift to you
This is a little something I stumbled across
I'm getting ready to head home for Thanksgiving
And I just wanted to take a few things to listen to
On the way, you know, just in case I get bored with the family
But anyway, I was stumbling, I stumbled across this on a website called
MP3airtracks.com
That's Mike Papa, numero3airtracks.com
It's from KQLZ in Los Angeles
And the morning guy, Michael's got Shannon
I, you might know, you might not, I don't know
But just take a listen as we go back to 1980
And a good morning to Adam Curry
Just getting up as one of him at his lovely wife
For sure, she was in town for the TJ Martell
Celebrity softball game
He's telling me a funny story that happened Saturday
Tommy Lee and the Molly crew is kind of like
Running his mouth, Jacket is yours
Up there with his softball bed
Now that first time up
Strikes out, you know, hard as a strike out in softball
Second time up Tommy Lee strikes out again
The third time he pops it up into foul territory
And one of the L.A. kings, I don't know which one
It wasn't grassky, one of the L.A. kings runs over
And catches Tommy Lee's hit
Behind his back
Any free
It threw his bat down, he started
I'm gonna read
KQLZ Los Angeles
Pirate radio
All right, that wasn't Tommy Lee
It was Vince Neale
He was one of the crew, it was Vince Neale
Popped out in softball time
Sorry Tommy
The light grew anyway
Nice travel back in time
Is it just weird we need a little more played echo
And radio these days
That'll solve the problem
Not breaking up clear channel
He's played echo
It's all about the echo
But anyway again, congratulations
Five hundred Charlie's
You keep making them
Keep commenting on them, okay?
All right, yeah, thank you
Yes, when he says played echo
He's talking about about this effect
Michael Scott Shannon, never bother
Oh man
Yeah, that was Pirate radio
Actually, that was another gig
I had just been an MTV for like two years
And I was asked to come out to work with the Scott Shannon on Pirate radio
Was a KQLD
Something like that
KQX, I don't know whatever, Pirate radio
103.5 FM in Los Angeles
I'm glad I didn't do it
Because the station didn't last very long
It's you know Scott Shannon who has built some very successful radio stations
That was not one of them
Yeah
But it's not it didn't just sound like a podcast, man
With all the play echo
Oh
Yeah, that was a good day, man
That was the time we were out there
It was indeed not Tommy Lee was Vince Neil
But it was the same softball
We had these annual softball games
And Sam Kinniston was still alive, man
That was pretty wild
He drives what up under the diamond
And his white rolls Royce with all kinds of chicks
It was like falling out
I
Yeah
What was I going to say?
I was something really important
People are escaping me already
I got to go
Oh yeah, I did want to mention that we've got a new in the attic coming up
That's the Pete Townsend Rachel Fuller Show
That we have on podshow
Now, BTpodshow.com
I think they're linked from the homepage
So let me just see if I can find this
Hold on a second
Let me just Skype Ron
Doing DSC
Five minutes
Okay
I don't understand that
So there's a new one
I don't think it's been put up yet
But I just want you to listen to this
Pete Townsend man
He's he's awesome
He just listened to the intro for a second here
You're right
So I'm Rachel Fuller
That's Rachel, man
You're watching podshow
Fucking brilliant
Wait, I want to let me get into the
The thing where Pete stars hold on
I'd love that song by the way
That's their opening
Yeah, let's get to
You got to hear what Pete has to say
What
He's so cool man
I now have email with Pete Townsend
About the show
This is the legit podshow
I just...
Problem
What?
It's the wrong colour
Let me pray
I should be blind
Do you like my breast?
Do you like my buns?
Do you like my feet?
I do like my butter
I do like my waist
Do you like my arms?
I ain't talking about a control man
All right, portions of this show
I brought to you by GoDaddy
Get a really good deal on a domain name
For a whole year
$6.95
When you check out use code dsc3
When else we go to earthlink.com
And of course the fine folks
It's Splenda
And there's all kinds of links in the show
Notes there
And they'd also like to hear from you
So check that out
All right, I really got to get going
Meetings are starting, shits happening
Now it's time for the show
So I gotta go
I'll talk to you guys tomorrow
Bye-bye
Another pod show pod guest
Stick it in your ear
Get this pod cast
And more great ones like you
On the high performance pod cast
Delivery network from pod show
And limelight networks
I love it