D.S.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A
N.K.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.K.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.Y.D.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.C.A.A.C.A.C.A.C
Y'all around, round wide a green
Even rushes from all the space
Have a ride to grow and live
So don't you tell me
Everything's right
It's the real, have a ride
Every massive world
Everyone is warm
No, there's garbage in this world
But the news makes sure it to deliver at home
Violence, disrespect, and sex
No, there's it's all the same
You laugh, you cry
Most of my dislikes out
If you've got the green, you're safe
Because this system will cut your break
So don't you tell me
Everything's right
It's the real, have a ride
Every massive world
It's the real, have everyone is warm
We'll think of others
It's the real, have a ride
You can't sing so high in this world, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't
We don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights, we don't have our rights,
You know, when you get an email on Tuesday from the official music colleges of the Charlie
Jersey Todd, saying you got to check this out.
You got to check it out and spot on, J.T. Of course, he's from Jersey, Dan Annable.
That was, uh, affliction, influences according to his page and the pod safe music network,
Bach, Beethoven, Chopin, Glenn Gold, Billy Joel, the Beatles.
Yeah, what do you expect? Dude, love that song. Fantastic. Everybody how you doing
depending on where you is, uh, where you is at. It's either Tuesday or Wednesday.
Perhaps it's even Thursday if you're not down on it. This is the daily source code
episode 488 coming to you from the Curry Cottage in the affluent suburb of Surrey
known as Guilford. Um, it's been crazy. It's just been crazy, but I, I really wanted to get
to show out today, uh, particularly because, um, tomorrow's show will be late as well. So I wanted
to make sure that you had something, something to, to listen to. And then we try and keep the
daily in daily source code. Um, so, um, today, women. So yesterday, after the show, I rushed out
the doors. I told you, um, went to the office. We were finishing up a shoot for a show called,
Who's on it, which is, um, hosted by OJ, uh, done in the pod show London crash pad, which is
not really what it's officially been dubbed. So that show will be launching, uh, I think, uh, November
9th is when we start launching that show, BT Pod Show.com. Of course you'll be able to, uh,
watch the show and, uh, and get it as usual through, uh, Pod Show.com as well. No worries there.
Um, and then, um, basically Ron and I spent the rest of the evening and night working on
our presentation for this morning, which was a scheduled for 9 a.m. with, uh, uh, the BT folks,
British Telecom, or partners here in the UK. Um, and it was pretty intricate. You know, Ron and I
really like to put on a show. We've been doing this for, I don't know, 12 years. So we have huge 65-inch
plasmus. Was it yet? No, was it 65-inch or centimeters? Nothing was 64-inch plasma screens. Uh,
yeah, great sound, uh, system, uh, laptop hooked in, you know, nice plexiglass, electrons. It's
very, very swank. We've got this, uh, crew here, uh, audiovisual crew, um, in London who just
know exactly the way we want it. And it's very cool. It is literally like a performance. It's a
little show as we call it. So the BT folks rolled in, uh, exactly on time, of course, you know,
you, you got it. You can count on those English, man. They are always there on time. Um, so this
was an update, uh, we're getting ready for the launch of BTpodshow.com, uh, it was an update where we
are, uh, and then we really, um, had an entire proposal attached to it. Um, uh, uh, how we were going
to, uh, spend, uh, some of those, uh, BT sterlings, shillings, uh, on, uh, on really, really rolling out
pod casting in the UK and, and really taking hold of it in one fell swoop. Remember BT spends a
lot of money on advertising. All telephone companies do a lot of it. So what better than to put that
to use for for the, this new movement. And I'm very proud of, uh, of the presentation we gave. And I think
it really caught storm. I think that they, they, they, they did get their own fires. We got meetings tomorrow,
another 10 a.m. meeting. So, um, it's, um, I only had like, I think I landed like three or four hour
now I had probably four hours of sleep, Ron probably got three. We were working two separate rooms,
which actually by happenstants were next to each other. Um, and I was working on a, um, a demo
for the IPTV, which is basically, um, well, they, they call it, you know, television over internet
protocol. And I just look at it as another great distribution vehicle for video and audio podcasts.
And more actually, you know, pictures, you know, uh, your, uh, your digs. Imagine that,
dig in undiggin, uh, managing your entourage with a remote control. So I was working on that piece of
demo. And, uh, so tired. It was really, really rough. You know, to do that in a hotel room makes
even suck here in the band with us always kind of iffy. Um, it's nice though one of my favorite, uh,
video producers, um, Skype to me and we chatted for a couple minutes. Uh, if you've never seen
cats cast, uh, you got to check it out, cats cast with kz.podshow.com. Uh, Kacha who actually, um, uh,
did the Adam's family reality show with me is now doing a video podcast. It's fucking awesome.
You got to check it out. I mean, this is, this is what happens when you let a pro loose on stuff.
Again, it's really whack. It's great. So that was nice. Um, it kind of, uh, distracted for a little while
there. And then, uh, uh, did that with a boss? We were really tired after the meeting.
I had, uh, full English, which I'm totally into that. This full English breakfast. Man,
does that shit fill you up? Hopped on the train almost, uh, fell, uh, luckily I woke up at
woken when I was dead tired, fell asleep. You know, I probably would have gone all the way down
to ports. I hadn't woken up because of the one stop at woken, uh, came back, you know, hung out.
Oh, Christina has a new, uh, boyfriend, by the way. I told you that Liam was out of the picture.
New kid, cute, nice kid tall, tall, nice teeth, hooves all seem to be in order.
I can't wait to talk about him with Patricia. We have a lot of stuff to discuss. We've actually
started a couple conversations in the past a few days since I've been back and we keep saying,
I don't know, let's just wait. Let's keep that for the show. Don't talk about it. I don't want,
I don't want too much good stuff to get out. And she's now saying that too, by the way.
And she has a pretty cool, uh, announcement to make. I don't know if she can do it this week or
next week, but I'll definitely get her on. Once I get all the pod show San Francisco,
people back to San Francisco and I get some peace and quiet around here, you know.
Then only then can we get to the really cool stuff?
Uncrawling casting with Adam. Oh yeah. Adam, who are you ready to be stumps? Bring it on.
That's he is. Then he will cast a cast with young format.
Ah, the rematch. Hey Adam, this is hit test number 70 on the daily source code.
And according to all the emails and other responses on last week's hit test one time return
off the hit test in the daily source code. It's still very popular, so hopefully this can occur
more often. And of course, that all depends on the possible licensing agreement. So
I'll tell you more about that. In meantime, there is a hit test. Three intros. Let's do answers.
And this is intro number one.
Of course, it's the second time I've heard it. This is uh, Donna summer. I've got my thing. I love
is in control. Donna summer. Number two.
That's uh, Crab or Crab.
Jimmy Summerville. And today's final intros number three.
Oh, I know that one. Oh, one of my favorites. That will be remember the promise you made by
Crab and John. This is fun again, buddy. And times up and these are the answers.
I'm sure number one. Here we go.
Yeah, song from 1982 by disco diva Donna summer. This is love is in control.
Oh, this is time like with some cowbell.
Inside my life.
Just hold on to me.
Hey, Quincy Jones production that sounds much like the Jackson's.
Donna Summer. Sorry, cute. Finger on the trigger. Love is in control. As answer number one.
And this is answering number two from 1984. Small town boy. This is Bronsky Beats.
Oh, I got the Jimmy Summerville part right and the lyric right.
Yeah, Jimmy Summerville and small town boy is answering number two.
And this is answering number three in today's contest.
From 1986, Gark Robin. Yes, Gark Robin. This is the promise you made. I got that one right.
Not nice at it, y'all.
Now with a great song.
Answer number three in the second return of the hit test in the daily source code.
Cac Robin and the promise you made. Two stars for the curry cottage.
Okay, well, that's it. All 80s music in this hit test. Hopefully there will be another hit test or more hit tests.
But of course, it all depends on whether you have good news and licensing and how that's all going to be
taking care of if possible at all. Well, thank you for playing at him.
Maybe until next time. So until then, take care and bye bye.
Well, thank you, Gark Robin. And I'm sure Yon will be posting links to those songs and iTunes.
You know, Yon, I don't think we have to worry about any licensing dude because the way she had those songs.
Cac Robin was not the way I remember it. Remember the edits you made.
Hey Adam, it's Carmen Tyler. Oh, hey Carmen. I wanted to say hello and to tell you, well, first off,
it's pretty early in the morning for me. It's like nine o'clock and I usually don't like it till 12.
Oh, the life of a fave a beauty queen. I usually don't wake up until 12.
But I woke up this morning and for some reason, I had you on my mind.
Okay, see, this is what you get when you, when you don't do a show for a day and all of a sudden
Carmen wakes up thinking of me. What do you think that means, Carmen?
What do you think, former Miss Louie Ziana was doing thinking about me early in the morning?
So early in the morning and so strong were these thoughts that she felt compelled to talk to me at nine a.m.
Three hours earlier than her.
Three hours during her beauty sleep period. Which is a little crazy. So, um, I wanted to let you know
that you guys all of you pod gasters out. Hold on a second. I was just
That's going to make sure I'm in the right mood for your Carmen. I have really inspired me and I am actually podcasting now.
I have my own podcast. Yeah, yeah. I've only done three episodes. So, um, I'm a baby. I'm a neophyte.
Oh, what? A neophyte?
Oh, man. Hold on.
Should I can't even spell dictionary.com? How'd that K get in there? Hold on.
Dictionary.com. I use this all the time. I love that. I don't know why I haven't bookmarked it yet. Okay.
Neophyte.
Big word for the pod father. Oh, neophyte with a y. Okay. Did you mean neophyte? Yes.
The neophyte. Okay.
Where are we here? A recent convert to a belief
a pressolite or a beginner, a novice, a neophyte at politics or three a Roman Catholic church, a newly
ordained priest. Hm, she is definitely part of the cult or be a novice of a religious order
or congregation. Oh, and check this out. Yeah, we have a little uh, uh, thought that there was a little
speaker icon. Oh, what happens here? If I click this, would it work? Oh, premium login.
Yeah, I think not. Okay, Carmen. You've joined the dark side. Hey, this is Carmen.
Ah, shit. I'm sorry. But I'm having fun doing this and I completely respect you guys because this
is like hard work and I don't have like a lot of major equipment. So Carmen, even though you've never
sent me the naked pictures, I assure you you have the proper equipment. I can imagine with all
this stuff that you guys put into it and everything and I'm sending my promo, but I'm not sure
if you can actually play it because it's um anything. We're going to have political calamity by
extreme, which is one of your favorite songs and albums I love that album. Okay, anything. But um,
I'm going to send it to you anyway, but people, if they want to listen to it, they can go to
www.carmincast.net. Of course, it's k-r-m-y-n-k-s-t.net. You can listen to my second show to find out
why it's .net and not .com that was irritating. Okay. But um, I'm really having lots of fun and it's
really just a silly show and I talk about crazy things that come to my head. No, I like you show
very much, Carmen, of course I've listened to it and I'm going to play your promo in a second too.
I like it. I love it. I particularly love what you're saying today.
Okay, I said in my promo, no one wants to be inside my head, honestly.
No, no, I'm going to leave that one alone.
That I just wanted to pass this information along and just tell you again how much I thank you for
your support for me as musician and um, you guys are awesome. Oh, and maybe I guess maybe you could play
the um, we had the hit test the other day. So, or yesterday, or listen to the one yesterday.
So, maybe you can't play this promo. I'm not sure, but you use your discretion and everything,
but I just wanted to let you know about it and then I'm having a really great time and enjoy it.
Okay, Carmen. I really appreciate what you said there. And by the way, there's I got a little
bone to pick with the podish beer. So, you know, this is something that's been ongoing for several
weeks. If not several months and I didn't say anything about it and people email me at least three
times a day about this and it's really heated up. Um, a couple of months ago on, you know,
Ricky Jervais, Ricky Jervais podcast, the only podcast in the Guinness Book of World Records.
The only people desperate enough to actually actually call up the Guinness Book of World Records to
prove something. Um, started, um, a promotional campaign on audible, which is they had a deal with
audible, which I guess wasn't too successful because they shut it down. I heard Ricky Jervais
on the BBC London talking about a total of 180,000 purchase tracks or podcasts in that case,
which by the way, you know, at a pound of pop, not bad at all. Nothing to sneeze at,
but it wasn't the millions and millions that that he perhaps expected. Maybe it's a little more
worth any expected. That's kind of the way he sounded on BBC London when he was talking about it.
They started his promotion and position Ricky Jervais as the pod father. And at
insult to injury, they actually used the the the pod father poster graphic, which,
man, we've been using that for, you know, what, uh, over a year, maybe a year and a half now.
So, you know, the exact same setup. And I just want to reiterate that, uh, I'm not the self-proclaimed
pod father, Andrew Grummit, uh, who developed a co-developed iPod or lemon, uh, gave me that moniker.
And, of course, it's stuck and, and I, and I've been wearing it with pride, obviously. I think it's awesome.
I think it's funny. Um, and I figured that there was just a little bit of bad blood, you know,
they're over at audible, um, because you remember when, uh, had all those meeting was Don Kats,
the CEO of audible, and then they were going to come out with this really stupid offering that we
thought was pretty stupid, which in hindsight, I don't think it's gotten a lot of uptake.
Was it word, word cast? I think it's called, um, just those not the direction we wanted to go,
but yeah, it was a little slippery and kind of tried to slide us into that deal and we pulled out
at the very first portable media expo, actually. Uh, so I thought, uh, okay, so that's probably
audible, kick-and-shin, you know, whatever, uh, just move on. But now Ricky Gervais is, uh,
is back to him some pod cast. And, um, he's being paid to do three pod cast by the Guardian,
the Guardian newspaper in general, a respectable, uh, a newspaper. Um, although lots of people
have very strong opinions about the Guardian, and today on the back page, and of course I've been
seeing, you know, the emails that started heat up again, but now I really sought for the first time.
There it is. Three pod cast to be done, uh, released in conjunction with the Guardian, uh,
by the pod father, and they use the same graphic and, you know, the same positioning.
And I, I don't mind if Ricky Gervais wants to, uh, take the title, uh, but this cannot be a
serious publication that, that basically plagiarizes. This is 100% plagiarism, and everybody knows it.
Everybody who's been in pod casting for more than a day knows that is plagiarism.
And, uh, no one's calling him on it. The other, you're emailing me, but gosh, you know,
it would be nice for someone to say, fuck you guys. And what kind of newspaper are you?
You know, what else do you plagiarize? You know, the Guardian's going to pretend they don't know
about this, they'll please, please. All right. Yeah, what do we have? That time for Carmen still.
Hey, this is Carmen Tyler, and I have no idea what I am doing. So I'm trying to do pod cast.
Just go to Carmencast.putshow.com.
Bring on the Velcro.
I don't have a DB. I just get bored releasing, and my brain goes in million just different
directions at one time, which is just absolutely crazy. No one was being inside my head.
Oh my, guys, that is so crazy. I can't believe you just said that. That's K-A-R-M-Y-N-K-A-S-T dot
putshow.com. Yeah, it was, uh, yep. Just inside the satellite window too, Carmen. There you go.
So for those of you on serious satellite stars 102, I'll be back tomorrow with more from the
Curry Cottage in the affluent suburb of Surrey, the United Kingdom.
Since there was Blender. Hey, I got some misinformation about Guy Fox Day. They're so nice to
hear all the Brits calling in, help them me out. And boy, I'm actually learned quite a bit about this.
Let's see, uh, let's hit and check this first one out.
Um, I think a little problem can be worn up by Guy Fox. Uh, I have to have them telling the
links fee, but there's absolutely brilliant program, uh, done by Richard. How many of you
know about Blender isn't the, uh, so you're not my own ever crush on, um, in the rocket
powered off the top here. Yeah, it's probably myth busters to show your talk. No, wait,
mate, Richard Hammond's not on that. Um, Brainiac, maybe that's the one. Get a brilliant
program on Blender. How was it, Paul? The seat was possible on us, um, anywhere, panic
and so I'll send you our link. This is, I've got to put a thought like, you know, while it was on
me mind and, uh, you're always saying, you know, in the phone calls, so just a bit, bye. Okay, so that was
uh, just part of, um, the fact that this is, it was not last, uh, or over the weekend, uh, was
it, uh, Brittle of, uh, Saturday. It was, um, it's November 5th, so it's still coming up. And you know,
how you remember it, uh, apparently there's a little rhyme that has been around since 1700's
or something or other, uh, that helps people remember when Guy Fox Day is. When I move,
remember the sister, no, then the jump had a trace and it's lost. I see no reason why I
got a trace and it should never be forgot. How cool is that, man? Some dude came up with like,
you know, so this happened in 1700's made up this, this silly rhyme. And it's carried fourth
for hundreds of years. Remember, remember, remember the fifth of November, every school child can
remember that. I got to come up with one of those. I really got to have one for me, so that
in a couple hundred years, someone will still be saying, remember, remember, the days of flavored
splendor. Hi, Adam, this takes me to tag in. Do you play on the city that are really
an awesome old dream or how about you on? Yeah, this is turning out to be a really interesting
show, isn't it? Yeah, you know, this, I don't remember what Jeff said. Anyway,
this stuff you're talking about, one for a night, and it is a celebration of birth,
or it's turning out to have the parliament and stuff, but it's some specific November. And there's
like, parents and nurse urans and stuff about it, right? Remember, remember, the sister's November,
the dump had a trace and plot. I know of my reason why dump had a trace and she'd never be
forgot, or she'd ever be forgot or whatever it is. Anyway, and sorry, let's go for the time
from just before Halloween until the middle of November, so that's all the banging and stuff
that you're hearing. So, if you can't find the sister, you're not missing it. So, still up the show,
still harder. Bye. I shall speak to Captain Dan, if that is possible, the fifth of November,
what's the date on that? Oh, me, yeah. Oh, we have a message incoming, just as I'm grabbing the
blackberry. What's the message here? That's from Ron. Hold on, he's still up. Poor guy. I'm old. He's
really old. I don't know how he does it. Okay, what's I looking for? The date November fifth is a Sunday.
Okay, so I know Dan would be available, but I have no idea. So, the plan would be to see if we can
fly at night during Guy Fox Day and film it, of course. If I've seen no reason why we couldn't,
I don't know what the rules are if there are no tabs, notice to airman about flying over certain
areas on a night like Guy Fox night, but if someone knows the rules, Captain Dan will know the
rules. Something else have been getting a lot of email about. Let me just see if I have an example of
one of these. Hold on. Oh, boy, do I love Gmail? So easy. Just do a search for Splenda. And here we go.
Oh, this, I think this was it. Now that I actually had to talk to the, the original sales
weasel, Greg Man, it's his account. Now, we had expected people to shoot. I get, did I delete that?
What the hell was I thinking? We had expected people to, you know, to question Splenda because
there are some questions about its ingredients, about health and safety of, of using the product.
And it wouldn't be fair, you know, to do a promotion like this, which is already incredibly
successful because people actually really like the product. You know, it would not be fair to ignore
that. So even though I expected to talk about a little bit later on in the campaign,
there is concern about Splenda and your health using this product. And it's stuff that
resonates throughout the internet. And so we talked to the Splenda fall and said, you know,
so what do you want to say? You know, what's going on? And they said, look, point everybody to
SplendaTruth.com. Now, of course, it's not going to resolve anything for those of you who do who
believes different and want to believe that, you know, different, I can't convince you.
But, you know, there's a lot, this is, Splenda is a member of the Johnson and Johnson family of
products, a family-owned company, mind you. So this is, you know, this is a true American institution.
They are not going to put their customers at risk. And then, and so at SplendaTruth.com,
there's, I basically went straight to the FAQs. They've got Splenda and safe to safety testing sites of interest,
about Splenda FAQs. And so, you know, their questions like a Splenda brand,
Swedener made from sugar, which yes, super low, or Splenda brand, Swedener's made from sucrose
through a patented multi-step process, blah, blah, blah, it's Splenda Natural Answer No,
sucrose, the highly intensive, sweetener, using Splenda Products is not natural.
It's a no calorie sweetener. Then it has all these questions about, let's see, what's something
interesting. It's Splenda Absorb by the body, I kind of like that one. The vast majority of
sucrose is not absorbed and passes through the body unchanged. I don't like talking about this about
any kind of food to be honest, but, okay, it says the guy smoke on a fatty. Some sucrose is
passively absorbed, but is not broken down for energy and rapidly excluded from the body. The
small amount that is absorbed passes very quickly through the body and is excreted in the urine.
There's no accumulation of sucrose in the body. So you can go check that out if you so wish.
My question was not in the FAQs, which is, you know, does the French vanilla actually affect
the taste of your.
That's the voice, Mel number. It's a phone in anything you want. Hey, in the city,
Podshow is sponsoring in the city, this huge independent music event, which is going on
going on for years up in Manchester. And of course, Ron and I couldn't go with the real
bummer because dude, I had the plane lined up and you know, ready to go, but we had this big
meeting today. So we really could not go up. Jill Mills is up there, along with our buddy from
Green Dragon podcast, and they're checking in. Hi, Adam, it's Gil from my cafe in the 50th.
Adam is really a day from Gini's by size bonus.
Basically, we've been paired up, but she know, and we've been going around seeing loads of
them. And in my role, they know full book for the network. I've got been picked for you if you want
to look at me. No, I'm not given true. Okay. All right. Well, basically, I've been going around
I've been caught with all the A&L people who are here looking to sign the book on label.
This is Jill Mills. She's something Mel's man. I got to tell you. She knows everybody in the music
business. It's like, you know, it's like, you know, Bonna walks in the room. Yeah, I was like,
Jill. She's like, I'm believable. Everybody knows Jill. And she's, you know, and now she's going to tell
us who, you know, who's been signed. I mean, this is she is so deeply embedded into the into the
scene. And you have it on the hospital, see that these bands will be getting signed. We'll be
hearing a lot more of them in the future. Okay. So get your pen from parts ready and move some
turn. Terry Naomi, the answering machine found. Brick a large, friendly fires. You get all this down.
I'm just a twang. Number one phone. Clark, you can't. And the strange death of liberal
England. I have it on good authority that most of the fans will be getting signed as they
will. I've been most of the fans, but we both have been going home. We have been running our shows
rugged on behalf of each of you. You guys have been, yeah, you stop with the B.T. Pot show. You
guys, you didn't get enamored. Hammered. Hammered on our dime. You're up there smoking crack.
Getting drunk. Screwed around with the bands. All in the name of progress of music.
Yeah, I've been working really hard. I'll tell you. These 12-year-olds are killing that.
Nice. And that's just doing it part-time. The highlight of the week for me so far is seeing a band
called Bokey. Oh yeah. I'm just amazing trio. I have some Japan. Not a girl band. They were absolutely
fantastic. I know I've got a list came from the me of bands that I've fallen in joy. I'm not going
to be negative about talking about the crap band at what the point. But I'm with you. I mean,
did you say crackbuff? Yeah, it was one of the first gigs we saw. Wasn't that Bokey?
And what I have to say to you, the thing that's not me is, you know, when bass players, basically
they play their instruments, like they're as close. Which is what they're there. You might have
had a scene like so wide before bass guitar. Most of the ensemble was on about four and a half
or so. Unfortunately, we did try and interview them afterwards. But they speak about three words of
English between them, so it became actually interesting. Well, if it was the best word they knew
was yes. Yeah. Which please me no one will have questions I was asking. You'll fail. No.
I think we should keep the rest of history. Yeah. So people can find us on folks like reason that
works. There we go. Okay. So there you go, Adam. Yeah. That's me, GD. Um, I'm Mateo Mills.
We're fortunate for in the city. Oh, we good. You guys rock. But you know what really pisses me off.
So, you know, here we are sponsoring this event. We've got to chill up there. We've got a whole crew
up there. We're preaching the gospel about the pod safe music movement. And then, you know,
our two stars, it sounds like they're talking through a fucking, you know, my first microphone.
My first podcast recorded. It sounded like absolute crap. What was that? Can we, can we get these
people some decent recording equipment? All right. We're officially looking at November and December.
So I think I'm within the boundaries of the law to play Christmas song.
I know that famous Christmas tree. Yeah. People are shopping for them loved ones.
I'm making plans for a Christmas freeze. Learning all goes by and the length of night.
And then we have to wait another year. What event? We did Christmas. What a wonderful one.
This one we did. We never feel blue. We make all our dreams come true. We're Christmas.
We're everything. It was time to bring out the good people. I just look around now and you'll see here.
Everybody's a nice and full of life. And they give to those who aren't me.
Yeah, we're everything. Christmas. What a wonderful one. This one we did.
We never feel blue. We make all our dreams come true. We're Christmas. We're everything.
So I'm going for the summer to the spring. I'm taking a nice year until then.
It's Christmas again. What is everything? Christmas. What a wonderful one.
This one we did. We were never feel blue. We make all our dreams come true.
Christmas. What a wonderful one. This one we did.
We never feel blue. We make all our dreams come true.
We made all our dreams come true.
Christmas. What a wonderful one.
This one we did. We made all our dreams come true.
We're everything. It was time to bring out the good people.
Christmas. What a wonderful one.
This one we did. We made all our dreams come true.
Christmas. What a wonderful one. This one we did.
Yeah, Lady Patricia just stuck her head around the door saying, come on to bed and I said,
hey, it's you.
It's you.
I'm a pod say for peace.
If every day we're Christmas, just within legal boundaries of playing a Christmas
tune, myself and post legal boundaries that is November.
It's okay.
And of course, you can buy that song in the pod tape music network 99 cents.
All proceeds go to UNICEF, it was a very successful last year.
I'm sure we can do it again all over again this year and your support is welcomed.
I love that song.
You know, you Christmas songs, this is, I think this is a real keeper because you burn out
on that shit, right?
You just were like, oh man, I don't want to hear it anymore, but just playing it again
is like, yeah, you know, it works, it just, it still does, it's still got it.
All right, buddy, I got a couple things to wrap up here, then I'm going to hit the, hit
the, hey, get some z's and off to London early tomorrow.
So we'll talk again very soon, daily source code.com for all of the show notes, go
data.com and use checkout code, DSC3, that'll give you a domain name for entire year
for $6.95 and add them at podshow.com for more of those sexy stories, ladies.
I love it.
Get this podcast, stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast, delivery
network from podshow and line-white networks.
I love it.