For the first time ever, the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr. in one action-packed DVD collection,
own all 27 episodes, the cult hit, including all new interviews with Carlton Koo.
First thing that Brisco did that impressed us was, we're not only to come in and really read the dialogue well as an actor,
but he also did a standing flip in our office.
You flipped too for Brisco County!
If you like the kind of TV you can't get on TV, get your copy of the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr.
Available now on DVD.
Delta Sierra Charlie 472, a guy semis and more custom intros will y'all mjones in here.
We're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV
we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we're going to get on TV, we need one button for my phone to get on TV,
hopefully it makes me enjoy so my hours, we're going to get on a TV, we're going to have two
I'll take it again and I'll never need the trace
If I don't do, I'm gonna know about it when it's right
Can't wait in the way I play
I never dreamed when they parted with me
Look at mama, my name is a racer, I'm the fuck
Can't wait to tell the time for the racer
I'll take it again, I'll take it again
I'll take it again and I'll never need the trace
If I don't do, I'm gonna know about it when it's right
Can't wait to tell the time for the racer
I don't do anything, nobody will ever do
I can't run in a Westway
I'm near the green wind, I'm telling you
You can't mama, my name is the way
So I'm the perfect man
I'm the perfect man
The genders are back
With the remix
I have to form tunneling with some fulation
My name is Horatio
And did I hear some cowbell?
They're all of a sudden
I love this song
Of course I've played it before
On the source code
But I saw that they actually someone sent me an email
That they'd updated it
Added some cowbell
Did a new mix and that's perfect
That's the perfect way to do stuff
On the pod save music network
Get your shit up
Release early release often
There's no different from software
It's just ones and zeros that you put in out there
Daily source code
472 coming to you from curry
Cottage
It is Tuesday
I'm really excited today
Because we're doing something
So new to us
Certainly
That is turning out to be such an interesting experiment
And really fun to experience and witness
You know that tonight is the digital music awards
In London
It was at Roundhouse
Which is a pretty famous venue
And this is a show
That will be broadcast on television on Channel 4
But not until the 21st of October
Which is obviously kind of a bummer
When you're talking about an award show
But what we saw was an opportunity to really create some content
At this event
Because there'll be all kinds of artists there
Many unsigned
Some just starting out
Some who have independent record deals
There'll be some sea liberties
And deliberities
And so you know of course as a part of our partnership with British telecom
Who are sponsoring the digital music awards
We said let's go make some content
So we had a couple of different ideas
And obviously just shooting stuff
And creating our own atmosphere
Our own party on the night off
And as I was missing in all that visual communicator software
That I do perversion for profit with
I said why don't we just stream some stuff live
It could turn out pretty interesting
Maybe someone will watch it
And we'll just do something
We'll figure out
And as
Things progressed
And we're also recording a show
That we're doing for BTpodshow.com
Which is
What does it have you got it?
Which is it kind of taking the idea of
American Idol or X-Factor
Any of that taking it
Two steps further into the independently produced realm
And really showing you what
What a production like that is
So actually we're streaming it live now
We have hundreds of people who are coming into un-dition
And we said look
We have distribution
We can bring you into homes
On to mobile players
Web browsers around the world
Have you got it?
If you got it then come on down
Let's see it
We've got people singing, dancing, acting
Which is very interesting
And we're really doing it as a show
Multi cameras
And we bought a little switcher
And we lit the set
And we turned the audio for a second
And obviously we brought in the same
Caliber of talent
You should see the host
Over here
She's really pulling this together
We had a good feeling about her
And we really reached out to
The non-podcast community
Specifically
Because there's just such a
This is really podshow
Going to try and involve the audience
An audience that is not necessarily involved
In podcasting
But maybe as heard a show somewhere
Maybe has something on YouTube
Let's bring them in and show them the tools
Every single person that comes through
We also give them a podshow
Plus profile
With the recording of what they just did
It's a very interesting experiment
And as I'm sitting here watching
Because the stream has been up all night
And we're actually doing the auditions
As we speak
You get hooked
You just sit there and go like
Oh my god
Because you're not just seeing a set with a host
When there's a little lull in the recording of it
You're seeing the crew and you're seeing outside
And you're really part of the entire event
And it's really blown my mind
There is something about the live aspect
That I'm just really getting excited about again
This is the only thing
If there's anything that I'm missing from podcasting
It is the somehow there's some magic
To knowing that what you're watching
Or what you're creating is being seen
At the same time that it's taking place
And by, well in this case
Thousands of people are now jacked into the stream
And a little disclaimer
We are not streaming experts
We brought in a few different partners
And it was all kind of last minute
So everyone's just trying to get shit working
And we really wanted to go for the lowest
Common denominator of it just works
And so we're trying flash streaming
Which I'm not too nuts about the frame rate
That doesn't seem to be fantastic
The sound is great, the picture quality is great
I just like the scene more frames per second
Particularly if you got people moving around
And the streaming stuff there is an R2
So we're going to have to figure that out
So please don't call me and say
There was shitty
Because of the quality
Because I'm telling you it is
It could be much better
It wouldn't really matter
Because the content is just really
I'm really liking it
Let's just tune in for a second
Who's this guy?
I press play on the remote
Oh man
I'm late, I'm moving y'all
Ah, it's too bad
There was a guy who could speak dyslexic
On command
That was rather interesting
There were a couple of good singers
My son Olivia is not trying to get rid of him
So you can check that out yourself at
BTpodshow.com
Hey, let's just listen to a little bit of Olivia
Our host interacting with the talents for the audition
Do you want to wrap as well?
Yes
Okay
Right, perfect
We're going to see the full gamut of talent here
What a range
Can you act as well?
Use your mic, dude
Yeah
Okay
Oh, wait, he's actually
Oh no, he's going to say
BTpodshow.com
It's going to be up for at least another 12 hours
So by the time you hear this show, it's still the same day
So it's killing
Oh crap
All right
Let's listen to something else
Let's reach out to a trucker
Shall we?
Hey, Adam, you saw a 30 man
If I was walking out there, something for you
Let's truck for two times
All of us won't let you know that
I've been listening to you
And wonders if you were listening to me
My podcast is at trucker
Two times dot dot show dot dot dot dot
Thank you
See you later
Trucker two times
So, you know, I listened to this comment
I thought, well, that's an action
It does little promo
And he's a trucker, right?
And truckers
I guess they get really lonely
Because he just didn't stop
Dude
Truckers, the backbone of any country
You got to love him
And of course, there's trucker Tom as well
Who was part of the pod show family
Let's see what's going on with the audition
Oh, that guy's still singing
It's really something different
So take a look at it
Let me know what you think
I hope you're listening to it today
Let's see, there was
I guess I'm going to manage like five different audio sources
You'll only turn off the audition
There we go
I'm still getting feedback
Of course, because folks are listening
You know, on a delayed time
Time line
I'm still getting feedback
About asparagus making your urine smell
Skunky
Yeah, and this is Chris and Philadelphia
You wait for X.com
I haven't been calling in for a while
Because I haven't put in
We want to on my laptop
And think of the iPod working
Find the iPod catcher
Love the light, you don't care
I'm calling in about the asparagus
Just like a month ago
My girlfriend made asparagus
And it was really awesome
And you know, right after dinner
You know what?
What the hell is that stink?
You know, we both have that gene
I guess that breaks down the enzyme
Into the nasty smell
And to us it is nasty smelly
So that's it
And they already know on the folder
Or a phone folder
It's gone off that goes into the genetics
But in my parents taught me
I guess I just kind of figured out the scrunch
And now I know better way
But I do have that
One in a
50% gene
So there we go
Talk to you later
Bye
So that's kind of interesting
We can actually use asparagus p
As a matchmaking service
Asparagusp.com
Because it may be it works
Maybe if
Maybe there's something to it
Maybe both have to have that gene
And you're compatible match
Patricia and I certainly
Both have the gene
So
Hmm scruncher folder
Skunker
Yeah
Could be
By the way, if you're trying to get into the stream
It's busy
And if it's as access denied
Or connecting
Just it refresh
You will eventually get in
But it's a new experience
For pod show
We've always been on the delayed timescale
But this is something totally different
All together
And then there's my girls
The list of these bitis
Always doing something good
If you've never heard their music
I should play one of their tracks
Again
Oh, what was that?
On the door just slam shut
On the DSC
They really helped me
Really conceive the pod save music network
When I played one of their songs
With their permission
I emailed
I think it was Lee Ann
As I kind of played your song on my show
I didn't even think we had word podcast back then
And she said sure
And then other people who are doing shows
Start playing it
After requesting permission
And then Lee Ann came back and said
Hey, we're like selling some CDs here
And that's why I said wait a minute
If we can just make that permission part
Really easy
Then we could have something that would really work
And low and behold it is
And the girls are making you aware
That if you want to change the course of your country
Oh, it's almost second
That's San Francisco
Operations working on the streaming stuff
Send me stuff through Skype
So if you want to change something in your country
They're really
Fucking Skype
There really is only one thing that you can do
And then you know what that is
So you see your parties not to blame
Elephants and donkeys are not the same
You better cast that ballad
Cast that ballad
And pick your favorite name
Thanks lips lay off
Unemployment given me the blues
As you vis or hybrid
I don't know the time to choose
Better care the end or aim
So much to think about it
Every day you better cast that ballad
Cast that ballad
You better cast that ballad
And chase your fears away
Right wing, left wing
Everybody's wing
Everyone's wing
I believe you don't, you'll just be sad.
Some folks say the market's gonna take it maybe true.
Losing all our social security,
It could happen to me, to you, if you're right,
Wing Hawk, who's for the war?
He's loving him, he's feeling so,
You better cast that ballad,
cast that ballad,
and give your business a chance.
I told you once, I told you twice.
Being patriotic is awesome, nice.
You better cast that ballad,
it's the only true American way.
The Syvia's pretty sense,
so you gotta do it, cast that ballad.
To amongst all this excitement and great stuff,
there's some shitty news.
Patricia, knew she had an appointment yesterday at the dentist,
really the oral surgeon,
I should say, you know, she's been working on her teeth,
which you know, of course, if you followed along with the show,
and you've heard her talking about it.
Yesterday, it turned out to be much more of a slash
and drill session than she'd expected,
and it's real, it's dental surgery,
so she had a horrible night,
you know, her cheeks all puffed up,
and just definitely not in an award type of mood,
so she's not gonna go with us,
which is a real bummer because I really wanted to show her
off to everybody and she just doesn't want to go,
and I tell her she looks great, she does look great,
but she is definitely not feeling up to it.
So I'm gonna go with the kids,
with Christina, with Liam,
and with another friend of theirs, Roxy.
So it's gonna be interesting.
Yesterday,
I was, yesterday, I played a clip,
and I told you that this, you know, this one person
has been trying to get me in touch with a childhood friend
who has something in some news for me,
but, you know, tell me at least who the childhood friend is,
because I don't really have good experience with that kind of thing,
you know, with childhood friends,
and which childhood, you know,
I've lived in a couple different countries,
and I just really want to know who's looking for me before I reach out
and touch someone, and I'm not really getting very far with that.
So people are calling in, who apparently are childhood friends of mine.
Hey, dude, I'm Mrs. Keith from a childhood friend, man.
You remember me? Keith's second grade, remember me?
Dude, remember that library book. He's called, man.
Guess what dude?
My brain never returned it, man.
It got my number to $5,000.
Then, in late feet, that bro.
You know, we, I own the money.
You got to send me some money, man.
But, I need $5,000.
I'm in jail, that's why I couldn't call you, because the library book from childhood friend.
And, stock man, bro, I really need help.
You said you did my friend forever to keep second grade.
You remember me, man? Come on, pay up, dude.
I know you got money, everything.
The money doesn't end, man.
Pay up is $5,000, I'll leave you alone.
And nobody, I get out of jail.
I stock you, dude.
The creativity never, never ceases to amaze me. That's for sure.
Let's check in with the roundhouse for a second here.
There we go.
There's a lot of hip hop and crank and, uh, high fee, lots of high fee.
What's this guy doing?
He's a lawyer.
A judge's wig on?
He got a check this shit out.
I think we're putting it on podshow.com as well.
I thought it'd get as many people watching this as fossils.
This is great. I know we're going to find some superstars amongst this bun.
So, even Olivia is happy.
You have a thing for 90 days, don't you?
That's fantastic.
I've written the theme about 90 days.
I've written the theme about, can I hand it folks?
Yeah, I've written the theme.
I'm sorry, I'm a little bit discombobulated today.
There's a million things going on.
I got Skype windows popping up.
Trying to pull this off, but I wanted to let you know what was going on.
What's happening?
And that we're definitely going to have a good time tonight.
So East Coast and West Coast by the time, was it lunchtime?
By the time you get home, they'll be planning to see we're going to have the party going.
There will be celebrities and celebrities.
And I'm sure I'll be rolling in some of that some of this audition footage.
It is just incredible.
Alright, this is one of the bands that is actually nominated for tonight's award ceremony.
Don't get tricked into thinking that you know what this is or how it's going to turn out.
It's ironed sure Westernizers available now on the Pod Safe Music Network,
performing tonight live with the Digital Music Awards.
For the Western buyers and families standing over their empire, we think of that thing.
We think of a thing.
We shunned some power.
How it got to it's gotten zanned.
Just lying back all up.
We fly, we fly.
Time is in short.
I'll let it to hot for the last night.
We fly, we fly, we fly.
We fly, we fly.
Holy scrap paper, what is that?
It's an automated, it's not bad, it's got another song too, check out kind of the same genre.
Western Miserers.
Looks like we've got the streams working now, let's check and see.
They're doing interviews now with some of the unditioned candidates.
It's addictive, that's what it is, just addictive to look at.
Everybody somehow get a show out to you tomorrow as well.
Let's see, oh, I should probably do this for you before I leave home.
This is a celebrity endorsement from someone that you don't know.
Don't switch off yet, I'll be back.
The New York Times once called me the most famous person in New York that nobody knows.
That's true, go ahead, search it.
But you know, to several hundred thousand people, I am known as that guitar man from Central Park,
and I'm here to tell you that earth link is just about the best thing you can get on the internet these days.
I mean, if you're anything like me and you hate junk mail, earth link spam blocker alone is where the high speed connection
it starts at 1295 a month, it comes with free anti-virus software, a firewall and spyware blocker.
Look, take the word of somebody that you don't know, and you have no reason to trust.
Get our link.
Right on, okay, so now I got phones ring and I really got to get out of here, let me just turn that up.
Oh, we have a, I do magic.
Oh, I'm magician. He looks like a Reverend.
Oh, this is great.
Have you got it? Is the name of the show? And you can watch the unditions lie.
This is great. I'm really enjoying this.
Alright, everybody, daily source code.com for all the links to podshow.com if you want to see the streaming video.
It's also on the homepage there as well as BTpodshow.com and Adam and podshow.com for poetry and, you know, beautiful things.
Take care, everybody. I'll hopefully talk to you tomorrow. Bye-bye.
I'm podshow and limelight networks.
I love it.