This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
What killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Dildesiro Charlie 4.5 Niner
No, no, no, you think it is.
If the Dildesiro Charlie 4.5 Niner.
Yeah, no.
With the very nice Adam Curry.
Don't like him.
And sometimes the lovely Patricia Pi.
Nice Terts.
Dildesiro Charlie 4.5 Niner.
But forget that number.
This is the first Charlie of the rest of your life.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Hey, everybody.
It is the Daily Source Code.
That's a surprise.
Wait a minute.
No Pod Safe Song to start off the show.
That's right.
Because we're going to do something different today.
While the entire world I'm sure is talking about September the 11th.
We're going to talk about stupid stuff on Skype from Portland.
Portland.
It's my friend Ken Clark.
Kenster J.
Who I haven't spoken to in what can a year.
Do I?
Am I on?
It's working.
You're on, baby.
You're fine.
He had to teach me how to use the new version of Skype.
It had been a while.
It's been so long.
I don't have the latest version of Skype months.
Six months, maybe.
Yeah.
Well, of course, we've had some email contact.
Actually, I tried calling yourself phone last night.
Because I thought that yesterday was Sunday.
Silly me.
I was going to bust you up.
And I don't know what number I have.
But I got like some answering machine that was in Spanish.
That would not have been mine.
Well, no, but the person who I called was nice enough to call back.
I guess I got my number from caller ID.
And I'm like, hello.
Hello.
No, no, no, no, no.
What's your name?
Come on.
Go ahead.
Tell me.
You can't pretend.
No, Ken Clark.
A little background on Ken.
For those of you who joined the daily source code in the past six months, I guess.
Like Ken and I go way back to when I first started MTV in 1987.
87.
Yes.
Ken was the director of on air talent.
Well, is it was that the title, Ken?
Or was it at that point?
I think I was like the VGA coordinator.
Right.
The director ship probably came later.
Yeah.
It's like, give me my coffee.
Ken bitch.
Now.
But Ken had already been there for what five or six years before.
I even got there.
Ken.
I started in New Year's Eve, 1984 and 1984.
Okay.
So three years.
Three years.
Good.
Yeah.
And over the past two years on the daily source code from time to time,
Ken and I will catch up for something called the MTV Chronicles.
And we'll just, you know, talk about some crap about old times.
And I think sometimes it has something to do with MTV, sometimes it doesn't.
That's true.
Well, in this case.
Right.
In this case, there are actually two reasons for us to do another MTV Chronicles.
Although it will also be just kind of an update in general.
The first one was the 25th anniversary of MTV, which of course passed by very silently from the MTV side.
And Ken is much more ingrained in the MTV alumni community.
I've, I've no one ever emailed me.
I'm completely shunned.
The alumni, the alumni mailing list.
There was a five year cut off.
If you were with MTV within the first five years, you made the list.
Oh, really?
Oh, I didn't know that.
Okay.
And I, I was in there.
I started out in a three and a half, four years in.
So I, you were just on the other side of the cut off for the alumni list.
You know, it's so often that I'll read in the, in a newspaper or in an,
in any kind of mainstream publication, you know, Adam Curry,
one of the first VJs.
I'm like, man, you know, first of all, obviously they're not doing research,
but it must really bug like the original guys that, you know,
I don't know if any of them care anymore.
Yeah, of course they do.
Of course they do.
They're pretty laid back about it.
Yeah, but I mean, you just like fuck, you know, it's just irritating.
They could say early MTV VJ.
And that would be relatively true.
Yeah, but it's funny to think that, but if you look at 25 years,
you were there from like five to 10 or 11 or 12 years into MTV's life.
Yeah, you would have been an early MTV.
Well, what happened was, just as I came into MTV,
they were going to 40 million households.
Remember, we still had to do a lot of sucking up to cable companies.
We had to go blow them and go do like they were coming.
They were going to send their grandchildren and their advertisers.
Kids down to the studio to meet Adam Curry.
Like there was some no redstone themselves.
You know, they've got some some cable company in Botfuck.
And like, you know, and at that point, they really were just like,
cable, you know, trench diggers.
Didn't we call them trench diggers, too, at the time?
We got some more trench diggers coming through with a grand kid.
Remember that?
No, frankly.
Oh, well, I remember that was the distribution at the time.
I mean, I was like really important for MTV to get on basic cable.
Remember that?
It was.
Because it was.
A lot of cable companies said, now we're going to push you up into the premium packages.
And I think it was for that very reason that MTV was so censored really.
I mean, how careful did we have to be with anything?
You couldn't offend anyone in the music industry,
and he sponsored and certainly got someone in BF.
Because then we might get thrown off of this.
They did work.
Very hard.
And employed a whole bunch of people to ensure that MTV offended no one.
Affiliate relations was always.
Wasn't that it?
Who were always calling down?
Yeah, but there was also that the head censor Michelle von Thos.
Oh, there's a forgotten about her.
Yeah.
The hammer.
She would go through the lyrics, right?
The lyrics of every single lyrics.
The videos.
She basically had the final say as to what the hammer.
Is that what she was called the hammer?
Michelle von Thos.
The hammer.
She's living out here at this point in the lovely Pacific Northwest.
Is she no longer with MTV networks?
Oh, no.
No.
She's not.
She probably had a breakdown from that crap.
I withhold all come in.
Oh, really?
Wait a minute.
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Oh, I know.
I've got to rest a May one time at an advertising agency from someone named Michelle
von Thos who had just relocated from New York.
And obviously, she was no longer with the channel.
She's no longer with the channel.
Tom Fresher.
No, there is Tom Fresher right.
Yeah.
So that was another reason for us to get on the honkers because well,
we have lots of stories that we've actually withheld about Tom Fresher in the past.
And of course,
I'm not going to hold back any more now.
Well, we'll talk about that in a second.
I know the one you're thinking about.
Yeah.
We'll see if we get there.
That's not a funny light story.
And that's pretty heavy.
No, it's not a light story.
But I do have a funny time-pressed-in story.
All right, hit me with the Tom Freston story first.
Well, it's just, we were all, you know, let's just, let's just position this for a second
because people may not even know what the hell is going on.
Tom Freston was CEO of MTV Networks, which was MTV VH1 and Nickelodeon, from trying
to think, wasn't John Reardon there before him?
I don't know.
I'll say there was the President of MTV and then he became the right, that's right.
Now, he's the right.
The network.
Right, right.
I don't remember where Reardon fell in there, but Reardon was a big mockery muck in the
day as well.
I don't know what happened.
It's, um, and then my graph was graph.
A graph.
Yeah.
So every time Freston moved up, my graph would be right.
Now, Freston went to become a more respect for Judy McGrath than I did for Tom
Freston.
Well, exactly.
So my point was going to be after a whole bunch of rap and with you as the Tom Freston,
I was never impressed by him.
I never thought he did anything intelligent for the channel.
I thought he was just an accountant that sat up there and just like, you know, smoked
dope with people.
Didn't actually seem like he contributed to anything within the channel.
Do you ever see him in any meeting of any significance ever, um, no, go ahead.
On the rare occasion that I did, though he never knew who I was.
I was with the channel for 10 years.
That's right.
Who's that guy?
I know it was worse than that.
And I was a director of honor director of honor talented at that point.
And he would, why, we, we all, everybody just verified this to it.
The MTV alumni reunion in New York that I had.
And she's going to tell us about, yeah, we got, there's nothing scandalous, but yeah,
I'll tell you about it.
We just all got hammered.
Uh-huh.
And everybody was laughing because they remembered, Freston would walk into a room and he, he would
say, well, hi, Adam, how are you?
Hi, Bob, hi, hi, Dave.
Hi, nice to see you.
Hi.
And he'd look at me and he'd say, and who the hell are you?
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Every time.
And that, and they'd say, well, this is Ken Clark.
He's the director of honor talent.
Oh, yeah, right.
He's a hundred grand a year, Mr. Freston.
Surely you know that.
I know.
He's just a human flash-wasting money.
So then, you know, two weeks later, I bill hi, Dave, who said hello to you.
I mean, and that went on for 10 years.
Well, so anyway, so I remember how it went.
I think Freston moved up as Frank Beyondy moved up to corporate.
And I forgot about.
Yeah.
Oh, you know, I, I met his daughter the other day, beyondy's, beyondy's daughter is working
at zero.
Barbie, barbie, barbie, barbie, beyondy.
She doesn't show now with Martha Stewart's daughter.
It's pretty funny.
Anyway, so he moved up and then, and the graph, oh, no, then they brought in Reardon.
I remember it was really weird because John Reardon, no, wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
We had Lee Masters.
Oh, I like Lee Masters was the shit.
He's the guy that hired me.
He hired me.
He was MTV Networks president.
That's how it worked.
He was in writing network.
MTV president.
Freston went to MTV Networks, then Reardon came in, and when Reardon came in, Lee went
out.
He started E Entertainment, which was the movie channel, what was it, what was it called?
What was it called?
It was called, it was called something else.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
It was like a movie kind of a gossipy.
No, it was some kind of movie channel.
It was dumb.
Yes.
Yes, naturally V. I'm such a fan of Lee and snatched TV.
But then Reardon was living in Tom Freston's house.
You remember that?
And then Tom Freston fired up much, obviously, he had access to a much higher level
of executive.
It was really weird because he was in Freston's house and then Freston fired him and
never to be heard from again.
Where was Freston, why weren't Freston in Freston's wife in Freston's house?
They were, they were living with the Frestons.
It was really weird.
It really was.
And he didn't, Reardon didn't last for like half a year.
Well, did the guy move out immediately?
I think so.
Yeah.
It was like a really weird situation.
I don't know.
Maybe he was known to come with Freston's wife.
Didn't they split up?
You got a divorce, didn't he?
Freston?
No, I didn't have.
Yeah, I think so.
So anyway, so Tom Freston just last week was very publicly fired.
By the way, what?
He claimed he resigned.
No, come on, please.
Can't, I mean, it's in the business press.
Everyone's saying he was fired and the reasons were.
So I'm going to redstone, who owns a Viacom.
Viacom.
It was like 83 and humble, this guy was unbelievable.
You don't fuck you, don't fuck you, don't fuck you, don't fuck.
Tom, Tom, Tom, no shit.
So Freston apparently had missed out on the MySpace acquisition, which is what Fox
got.
Rupert Murdoch, of course, arch enemy of Sumner Redstone and say, excuse me, overall
ratings.
No, the overall strategy was unclear and you know, they haven't really gotten anything
together.
So that really felt, and I agree, it did kind of feel like MTV's lagging around.
And then the most recent video musical words ratings were down 30 percent.
I think that was like, you know, the straw that broke the camel's back.
Oh, I had that on my list.
Did you watch it?
Oh, you know, I sat here with Christina.
I didn't.
So I can't.
Oh, well, Christina's 16, she's perfect MTV age, she sits down and she loves all kinds
of music.
But after 15 minutes, she says, I can't stand it, it's just too much hip hop.
It's too much fucking hip.
I don't mind a little bit of hip hop, but it's all hip hop.
She could, she literally walked away.
I actually, I had to t-boat it and I too find myself fast forwarding through at least
three acts.
I'm just like, okay.
It's just too much.
I saw like a wrap up on, you know, entertainment tonight or something.
And I realized that I really, really am now completely out of touch.
We're old, officially.
I thought I knew what was going on.
No, but I know, but I obviously not.
And Jack Black was just horrible.
And I think he's a very funny guy.
Great actor.
I can't really like him.
Yeah.
This was definitely no.
Oh, it was, it was just not happening.
It was like everything was supposed to go wrong.
And it wasn't funny the way they were, it's just wasn't funny.
It wasn't funny.
So anyway, so Tom Fresen's out.
So that means that MTV is in flux.
And who is this guy?
They brought back this, with a D.
Daughter, what's his name?
I think he was name.
Yeah, it was a guy who'd done something before.
Anyway, what I'm looking for that,
what a lot of people commented on on this year's video
musical awards, particularly the pre-game show,
is John Norris and Kurt Loder.
I still alive.
I actually, several people either called or emailed me
about John Norris's hair color, about John Norris
in general.
I just think, you know, I feel really bad saying that
because I got along with John, you know,
but that was, I never did.
I never got along with him and he hated me.
I did okay with John, I really did.
I have nothing personal against him.
It's just that that was like 15 years ago.
And we've all grown up and I turn the thing on
and he's still sitting there.
Like Frankenstein talking to these people
and there is something hermetically preserved
looking about him.
I just, for Maldahide does wonders.
I question how stimulating that job can still be.
He always wanted to be, you know,
this is where exactly where you wanted to be.
And, you know, the MTV News Department,
bless him because they did,
I have to say, transform the channel
with a lot of their long-form programming
and a lot of it really, really top-notch stuff.
And they totally drove that and Dave Ceronek certainly.
And he was great.
And I heard Kurt was very important to the channel
because he was a really credible,
he was a journalist at the time he joined the channel.
The problem is whenever he goes to interview someone,
he has the personality of a fucking dish rag.
Well, that's true.
I mean, he just, that's the downside.
He's a great writer, great journalist,
but I never thought he was a huge TV personality.
No, he's very, and I'm quite certain
that he would probably agree.
He's very, very, very.
Certainly after 10 Martinez.
I really, he could knock him down my boy, Kurt.
He could slow him down like, you know,
he'd been pushed out there and he would endure it.
Oh, right, right, right, right, right, right.
He would endure them in a long, you know,
MTV news snippet, but as soon as it was over,
I was like, for Christ, they'd give me a cigarette.
You know, the cigarette was always right out of the...
Like mine.
Mine was always under the table too.
I know, which we're always smoking.
We were always smoking in the studio.
Part of the fun thing about going back to New York
that week of the MTV reunion.
Yeah.
And seeing a lot of people, some of which I,
some of whom were gone well before you even got there.
I saw the lady that first picked up the phone
when I was a college kid in Ohio,
and I kept calling MTV trying to get somebody on the phone,
they gave me the time of day.
In this lady named Claire Joseph picked up the phone
and finally, and talked to me,
and helped me get in touch with Brian Godchew.
Was Brian there?
Was Brian Godchew?
Yeah, yeah.
Excellent.
As was Claire Joseph, and she left before,
you know, I guess she went to VH one or something,
but I had not seen Claire Joseph in like 20 years.
And so like I, I just went right over to her,
and I said, Claire, you know, how the fuck are you?
You may not remember me, but, and I like,
like, I don't know, like, almost made her cry.
Really?
I mean, in a good way,
because I said really, if you hadn't taken the time
to be a nice lady, I hadn't know what they all would have happened.
I like, I would end it up like all my other friends
school, you know, like working in a gas station in Toledo
with a deeper capital L loser.
All right, so, so, so, so, so, so, first of all,
it was Philip Domin, that name doesn't ring a bell
and Thomas dolly, that, that does ring a bell.
Dolly rings a very distant bell, hang down.
Yeah, time, dolly, it does.
And that said, well, was he, was that a song?
Was he?
Oh, the, the new team, down, yeah, Domin and Dolly
is the same one that led Viacom from 96 to 2000
after Redstone and fired an earlier,
oh, after he had fired an earlier CEO, Frank beyondy.
There you go.
There he is.
So, when beyondy went out,
fresh then moved up, and those guys moved into,
into Viacom, into running Viacom.
They sound like an afternoon showed.
Everybody, it's Domin and Dolly,
we're the, yeah, here, we're on the MTV
and she's not always everybody, yeah,
we got some really good, interactive stuff,
we're your social networking stuff.
All right, so who was there?
Who was at the, at the 25th reunion?
And by the way, it would have been nice to have been invited.
It was this only, this is a five year thing, too.
Well, no, actually, that was probably open to everybody.
T, and I, I see, I see.
Take more blame than anybody else,
but it was, it was kind of assembled
by really, really early people.
I was in America, I was in San Francisco,
but I would have come to New York.
Well, they, they didn't, there was an LA
that you could have gone down to LA
and joined Martha Quinn and Nina Blackwood.
Okay, well, I'm glad you didn't tell me that.
And Ken's size, Lure.
Ken's size, well, there was, there was a simultaneous gig
held on both coasts.
Oh, was it a satellite link up?
Well, they tried, but nobody could make anything go, I don't think.
It was, there was a video cast done of it
and it was, it is available online somewhere.
Excellent.
All right, so who was in New York?
Who did you, who did you see?
You know, there was a huge list of people
that wouldn't mean anything to anybody.
Right, skip them.
The, was Julian Goldberg, still at MTV,
when you were there?
Jillian Goldberg?
Jillian.
Jillian?
Yeah.
He was a tall bald guy who was very instrumental
in the early MTV days.
There had been like Ken's size, Lure,
and Jillian Goldberg.
Were these in the honor promo department, guys?
No, they were probably heads of production.
I don't think so.
I don't know.
Size little rings are gone, but Jillian Goldberg
was the original executive producer of MTV.
Well, I, one of the things I found for the reunion party,
I, you know, because I have the vaults of stuff,
is I put together these little packets
and had them all copied and bound to pass out to people.
Oh, that's nice.
Funny things like, you know, the Michael Jackson Memo,
the infamous Hammer Memo, and I had the original
five press releases from MTV, a subsidiary of Warner Amix.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
And now I'm seeing the hiring of Mark Allen, J.J. Nina.
Oh, that's cool.
And so, Jillian was there.
Did you hand out any of the, any of the blooper
really have?
No, I didn't take any video.
Dude, we've got to put that online.
We've got to put that online.
Oh, you know, I had a great conversation with,
I ended up having a couple of gin and tonics at the bar
with Rick Krim.
Oh, I like Rick Krim, who's all right.
I always liked Rick Krim, the minute I saw him,
I was like, Rick, dude, Rick is a VP at VH1.
I think, still in talent, artist relations.
So he's with the network, no longer with the channel.
And I kind of like VH1, you know, VH1 sometimes.
Well, VH1, no, plays Metallica.
So, I ended up talking to Rick for a long time,
but we were talking about the fact that I've got a lot
of really cool shit on tape and that, you know, over time,
it's degrading and rotting.
Yeah, it is.
And that someday, all this shit needs to be burned to DVD.
I mean, there's a, there's a vault of it.
A truckload, a veritable truckload.
Can, can, listen to me.
I will have it all pay for it to be professionally transferred
every single last tape.
How much the idea have like, that's really worth saving?
Well, I'd have just, I've got about 15 boxes of great quarter-inch
reals.
I'm going to, you know, you need to, you mad, you mad,
you mad, you mad, you mad, you mad machine to spot them.
Well, yeah, but a lot of them are labeled in stuff.
I mean, the looper, the looper, yeah, much that.
Let's just get the blooper real.
Let's just transfer that.
Let's put it out.
There's a few blooper reals, but yeah, I could probably, you know,
siphon off the looper.
I'll find a place in Portland that'll do it.
And you just bring the tapes there.
And then they'll do it professionally.
And then we'll put them up online.
I'll take the risk.
Don't worry about it.
Well, have your people, call my people this week.
Oh, I should have started that.
Shell.
That'll be so cool.
There's some awesome stuff there.
I mean, the best stuff, really.
So actually, the week of the, the week of the MTV thing,
MTV did everything they possibly could
to thwart any press.
Yeah, they didn't want to see mold, right?
Well, yeah, that was the story.
Was it they wanted to see meong in fresh and relevant
and dwelling on the fact that they were a quarter of a century
old made them feel old.
And I, I think that's probably horseshit.
They received such, you know, unanimous bad response
to their celebration of their 20th, which
was the biggest piece of shit that's ever come down by.
That they were probably afraid to go anywhere near the 25th.
Freshness, but was puckering.
Well, they, they refused to release any, any old video
or footage of MTV, any press or media outlet.
I heard through the grapevine that even Kurt Loder was told
that he was absolutely forbidden from doing any press regarding
the typical, that's so typical.
That's so typical.
MTV, Martha and Nina and everybody were told that, you know,
they weren't allowed to use any photos or any footage of them
to any media outlet from the MTV era.
Really?
No, another infamous MTV memo, like if they were,
well, I don't have access to any of this.
This is here, say, a new hobby, knowing the network,
as well as it sounds like it.
I'm pretty certain that, you know, the powers that
be decided that they really didn't want to celebrate the 25th anniversary.
However, you know, the founding staff, including some really high
ups, it, freshness was actually there at one of the two parties.
So, I mean, you know, in New York, in New York, yeah.
I heard that when he left, the one I didn't go to.
When he left the building, everyone crowded the hallways and the plot
of it as he left.
A plot of that he was leaving or a plot of him, applauding him, I believe.
Oh, okay.
I didn't know what you were, you meant.
I would have been like, goodbye!
No, no, no, no, no, no, he would have looked at me and said,
who the hell are you?
Thanks, thanks Bob, thanks Adam, whoever you are, thanks.
Great work and we're the, I really love your work.
No, I'm sure he did.
So, no, it's kind of odd.
No celebs showed up.
Big celebrities, no, because it wasn't that kind of party.
You know, MTV, like VJ-wise in New York, we had Alan Hunter and Mark Goodman.
We're both in New York.
What are they doing now?
So, I know that they're, all the original VJs are on serious, yes, that I'm aware of.
Are you a revival channel?
Mark was doing terrestrial radio in Los Angeles, and of course, he pointed that out.
I'm also doing a terrestrial radio.
No, actually, he didn't.
Mark Mark was very cool.
I have no idea what he's doing now because he recently relocated to back to the New York area.
Oh, really?
Yes, he's living in, he's living in the suburbs of New Jersey in a place that you know,
not real well, it's, it's not, we're living lived.
It's not Montclair or Verona, we're lived.
Where is it?
It's a place where a lot of your money went.
A lot of my money at Lannick City?
No, no, yeah, like you have a pressure used to know gambling.
Come on, honey, it's only three hour drive.
Come on, let's go.
Whenever, yeah, whenever all man, whenever all man, all power would fly over you guys
would hit at Lannick City.
A lot of my money went.
Where the hell did my money go?
That's a good question, Ken.
Where did it go?
Short, short hills.
Oh, short, short hill.
Of course, short hills, mall.
I wasn't the short hills, mall.
It was the mall at short hill.
The mall, I'm sorry, yes, the mall at short hills.
Yeah, a lot of money did go that way, didn't it?
Yeah, I said, where are you living now, Mark?
And he said, out in short hills, I was like, in short hills,
only shit.
Yeah, that's expensive there.
Well, I would presume most places in short hills, pretty upscale.
I would think he's worth it.
No, I don't know, I don't use it anywhere in New Jersey
is probably expensive.
Yeah, that's true.
OK, so here we go.
And Alan, Alan Hunter, still does house, right?
Is still in Alabama, had his lovely girlfriend with him
and his daughter who is his daughter and goodman's daughter,
both our teenagers now, and we're like knockouts.
It's kind of alarming that everybody's daughters
and the talk to be these gorgeous young women,
everybody in the restaurant was, you know,
ogling at them, nobody had any idea.
They were underage.
They look at me in the 20s.
I'm sure you know how that goes.
Oh, Christina showed me her fake ID yesterday.
Oh, great.
She's like, you're like, yeah, look at this.
Oh, you said you're 19 here.
Yeah, it works.
She says in her nice little British accent, it works.
That's funny.
She's nuts.
So the week I was in New York, though,
it was like 100 degrees, and there was like 98% humidity
and like 31 people died from the heat.
OK, so do you remember how bad
New York used to get when I remember spending
one summer in New York and vowing to myself never, ever again.
Yeah, and then you bought the house out in New York.
That's right.
With the pool.
This is no way to live.
Yeah.
Allen, anyway, no.
Allen Hunter is still down in Birmingham, Alabama.
He's still doing his video production stuff.
Has a film production company actually has his
film artist, you know, a lot of independent films
is involved with Sundance this year.
And also owns a big facility that's recording studios
and a club and whatnot, really, Birmingham.
So yeah.
Right on.
I didn't know about it.
Yeah, and he's holding the studio on the ground.
Yeah, that's cool.
Sounds like it.
That's great.
No downtown Julie Brown, I presume.
No downtown Julie Brown.
That was it in terms of VJs.
And then there were just a lot of cool people like Brian
and Helene Gross, who I have been seen in towns.
And I, you know, like I said, I had a great conversation
with Rick Kram and, and, you know, I'm trying to think
if there's anybody else who'd have been particularly interested
in.
No, not really.
Not at the party.
I had a wild weekend Manhattan.
Now did everybody sit around and mope about how
in TV doesn't play videos anymore?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
This was a group of people who really, really enjoyed working
together, getting together, many of whom
hadn't seen each other in 10, 15 years.
Nobody was, what MTV was doing now was pretty much
irrelevant conversation.
It was, it was how are you?
What are you doing now?
You know, it was a lot of, do you remember this and that?
I mean, seeing each other and, you know, triggered all sorts
of funny memories of shit that happened back then.
OK, so I'll forgotten.
Give me a story that they recalled that was good, can?
Well, I had found a couple of memos that I had
or letters that I had, that MTV memos brought a few laughs.
Yeah, things that were in the vault.
I found a great, before you remember Communicar, right?
Our boy of it, car service.
Let me just, yeah, let me just explain Communicar in New York.
It was really one of the first mass scale radio cars.
So it's like, it's like a cab that you can call no difference.
Except the cars wall, this ugly burgundy, kind of,
they were burgundy, burgundy town cars and you had vouchers.
And so, you know, the car would cost, you know, whatever car costs.
I mean, if you left it for now, it cost 25 bucks or something like that.
We didn't ever find out really directly what it costs.
It was all went to corporate.
The corporate would give me vouchers vouchers vouchers.
Yeah, that was like gold boy.
Can sky would give each VJ, you know, two vouchers per recording session
want to get two one to get from.
That was the big limit.
That was early.
That was the big limit that we were all riding in was fucking Communicar.
And the limits were only for when people would see you like, you know, bullshit can.
They never never gave us limos.
I always got my own limos.
Yeah, no.
Who got the limo the night you were in that limo with downtown Julie Brown and it backed over
the old lady.
That was my limo.
I paid for that limo when we back over her.
It was downtown Julie Brown doing in there.
I don't remember.
I really don't remember.
I do.
I don't remember her being in the limo.
I don't remember backing up over the old one of the old ladies.
That was pretty funny.
Yeah, oops.
Sorry, lady.
I think that was for the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame awards or something like that.
I think that's what we're going to do.
I just have another funny story, too, that came up.
Before that, the Communicar story, before there was Communicar, they had a different
car service.
And this was before my day at the channel, frankly, I think I started right around the
time they went with Communicar.
And they're probably still with Communicar, frankly, I don't know, but Mark Goodman
was getting picked up at his house one morning to go to the studio for his taping.
And they got like partway there and he realized, like, having forbid, he didn't have
a voucher.
And so you got voucher, well, you got voucher, you got voucher, you got voucher, exactly.
This solution Mark proposed was drive me to the studio, I'll go in and get one, you
know?
I mean, I'm comfortable.
Yeah.
He's like, no, the guy's insisting, he's going to take him home immediately.
Didn't they call JJ Jackson the franchise, he's not what they call them at Communicar?
Yeah, probably.
Just JJ.
And Dr. Dre had a lover also.
Those guys left the car out all the time, it's like just for 10 hours.
And he's in front of the club.
10, 12 hours.
It's like he was sitting there.
All right.
So, Judy McGrath and everybody would have a stroke, sitting up and out for like a $400
Communicar bill.
So, this argument ensues in the town car and it finally got to the point that escalated
the car driver, brandishing a screwdriver and trying to like poke Mark Goodman over the
seat.
Excellent.
And like Mark finally dove out of the moving car and like was almost killed in
traffic.
All right.
And he had written this really, really funny memo to like the president or the vice president
of MTV and also copying the head of the car service about that whole, and you have
that memo sitting.
I do.
And it was a very, very funny memo.
Oh, you're going to read it.
You're going to have to share it.
Oh, it's very, very lengthy.
Oh, okay.
I don't want to read that.
It's, it's three pages of, of recanting this story.
I mean, I guess the important part is that he,
tried to stab him with a screwdriver and I believe it was the next week that they switched
to community.
That was the end of that.
But it did remind me and this, I wasn't so much an MTV story as an Adam Curry story.
Oh, boy.
There was a time after I had left the channel and was working for me, right?
Yes.
That you were in Los Angeles doing something.
It was something, perhaps it was this, I think it was the circus of the circus.
Oh, dude.
Circus of the stars were the rocket car of death with, what was her name?
What was the host of the show?
Oh, fuck.
Dear, dear, dear hall was not known.
Was that her name?
Dear, dear.
Dear, dear hall.
What's her name?
Come on.
That was dear, dear hall.
It was dear, dear hall, right?
I don't.
I remember Cameron Diaz.
Cameron Diaz was on that show with me and she was doing a trap.
He's number.
And she was 13.
She was a little fat Puggie kid through 13.
And anyway, I should have gotten her then, and nailed her.
You had to, you had to nip up to San Francisco for some sort of radio station promo.
Really?
And you were supposed to take just like a shuttle flight up to San Francisco and do this
radio station gig.
And then fly back down to LA for the next day's taping of circus of the circus of
the stars.
No, it could not be circus of the stars in LA because I was really sick then.
I remember.
Well, it's when you abandon your car, you abandon your car.
I remember this.
Wait a minute.
Let me back up.
Budget rent a car in Los Angeles.
I don't know if they still do it.
They had this great service.
And we were always allowed to rent a car through budget.
Now I always paid extra money for the car that I think didn't I can?
Did I always put on extra cash?
Yeah, like a Mercedes 500 SL or something nice convertible.
Oh, Lexus.
Yeah.
Nice cars.
Nice car.
And what was cool about the service is you'd arrive at LAX and the guy would be waiting
for you at baggage claim and you'd walk over to the car, which you'd already driven
there.
You know, he'd take your luggage.
It was like, you've got really good.
It's like, you know, okay, I'm on the lowest wrong of the show business ladder here.
But I got a guy picking me up.
I got some hot wheels.
You know, I got a nice, nice ride here waiting for me.
And sometimes when you take the guy back and drop them off, because I always stayed at
the water stay, same James Club hotel.
The same James.
Yeah, fuck, I forgot about that.
Yeah.
And so, yeah, so I don't think it was a trip to San Francisco, but I do remember at one
point.
I think it was a, maybe it was a BMW I'm thinking, because I always tried to rent
a different car each time.
So I wanted to drive cool cars.
I think it was a BMW that had everything integrated.
Whatever it was, I basically drove up to departures at LAX and I was late for the flight.
I just, this is not how you were supposed to do this.
I should point out.
No, you're supposed to, how did it?
It was a valet return lot, like a block or two from the airport.
Right.
You're supposed to go to the valet return.
Yeah.
And then take the fucking bus.
I had no time for that, can.
So I drive the beamer up.
I get my stuff.
I jump out.
I lock the car and I get on my flight and I call a can from the plane and say, what
I say, hey, Ken, I don't think you locked the car.
I think you left the keys in.
Well, if the key in the car, that's right with the doors open.
Hey, Ken.
I wasn't even sure if it was in the curb lane to be honest, you were in a triopic jam.
I just got out and took away.
I think you just got out and then called me from the airport and as you were running
to the gate and said that you had just bailed the car.
And so then I had to get on the phone with budget or whoever the hell it was.
There was budget.
Before a budget, it was luxury line.
You remember the luxury line?
Luxury line.
Beverly Hills.
Yeah.
So they, they were not, I had the call them and tell them.
I'll never forget the guy in the phone cracked me up because I had to tell them what
you'd done.
And I told them what you'd done and the guy says to me, bit serer, he can't do that.
You seem to misunderstand the point of my call.
It's been done.
And then when you came back, they didn't want you to have a car.
No, they didn't want to.
The car.
I wonder why.
Gee.
That's kind of amazing.
I don't know why we got talking about that.
We did a lot of cool shit and Los Angeles back in the day man.
We went there all the time to do fun stuff.
Yeah.
We really did.
Everybody was always jetting off.
And I'm telling you, every time we went to LA, it was just a barcherous.
Everyone was always messed up.
Everybody behaved pretty well in New York.
I mean, we've said before while doing the MTV Chronicles,
that that place ran like a well-oiled machine.
And we had a lot of fun.
And we got along well.
But it wasn't the sort of sex drugs and rock and roll sort of hijinks that people might imagine.
No.
The minute you gave us those commune car vouchers, we were off.
You know.
Yeah.
We're loose now.
But for some reason, LA was always free rain to.
Free rain to partay.
Yeah.
It was cool.
Everybody.
I used to do all the skiing stuff.
I went to all those ski resorts and we used to.
But that wasn't Colorado.
We'd like send you off to Aspen.
Aspen Vale, Brecken Ridge, Whistler.
The special brewer.
Yeah.
The special camera men that can ski backwards while holding that camera.
No.
We had a guy one time.
I think it was in Brecken Ridge.
And turnout he couldn't actually really ski.
It was really, really sad.
It was so sad.
He was strong.
Like a million times.
His camera was completely messed up.
Well, couldn't he just stand in a stationary location?
Have you come flying past?
Yeah.
We did a lot of that.
He was actually at the top of the mountain.
Afraid to go down.
Yeah.
Made a little bit harder.
He's like, I don't think I can go down.
Any other stuff in the packet that you want to share with us?
No off the top of my head.
I can't think of anything in the packet.
The party I should have gone to.
You know, there were two parties in New York.
One the night of the first.
Because that was the actual anniversary of MTV.
But that was Tuesday night.
And I was actually flying in.
I was I was landing at Newark at about the time.
The party was going on.
And I opted not to go straight to the party with my luggage.
So miss that one.
But at that party, we had my graph and fresh and.
And you got to tell me about these things.
Can the entire upper.
At.
At whatever.
It's a show.
Thank you.
Sorry.
The upper echelon.
It's still morning here in Portland, you know.
Yeah.
And I'm not sure I can say that we're in any way.
But they were all there.
And I missed that one.
Yeah.
Sounds like that was fun.
Well, would you please.
When it's 50th, would you please send me an email?
So we can.
Well, I don't know how many people will be left.
I mean, the one thing that I do notice is in.
Carloader John John Norris probably won't be.
Most people look pretty good.
But, you know, especially the early early folks, you know, I started there.
When I was 21 or 22 years old, and they were already in their 30th or 40th.
That's right.
And so now they're really old.
Because that was like 20 years ago.
And then.
I don't know.
It's actually not really funny.
Well, we're getting old.
Everybody's doing well, though.
I hear Beth McCarthy might be leaving Saturday night live.
I don't know if that's true.
Really?
Well, how is.
How's Saturday night live doing?
I catch it once in a while when I'm in.
You know, I haven't.
I haven't watched network television at all in years.
Although I did check out the the the debut of Katie Curric this week.
Oh, yeah.
How was she?
She was all right.
Yeah.
That's another something a redstone move right there.
He personally made sure that they got her with the moon vest.
Who is the golden child now?
It didn't so much strike me as news.
It's just like a half hour of of feature packages in some promotion.
Exactly.
That's what people want.
No, you don't know.
Yeah.
That's what it's because I like the news.
So while I was in New York.
The big news.
I was, you know, as a.
It was so hot out during the day.
It didn't even go out until after dark.
You would just sit there in near hotel room and.
Wack on wait for the sun to go down.
In the air conditioning.
So you spent a lot of time watching the television.
It was one afternoon.
It was all over the news.
Our old friend boy George.
Oh, he had to clean the streets, right?
That was while I was in New York.
It was like to go down.
No.
I actually thought about going down in my camera.
And I had a lovely dinner with our old friend.
Jill Stemple who's actually very well.
Jill.
The diva.
The diva Stemple is the bureau chief of the.
She opened in his heading the New York bureau of the world entertainment news.
Network.
Went.
The guys.
The guys we used to buy our news from Lloyd Bany and.
Oh, he's still around.
That's Jill's boss, man.
That's pretty funny.
And she's the bureau chief of the New York bureau.
They're doing well.
So she's laughingly.
It said where you, you edit it.
Why didn't she go down there with their camera and take some.
Really?
Celebrity.
I was like, because it was a hundred.
Fucking degrees out.
Then I didn't want to have a hate stroke.
Did I do like an in store appearance at a hardware store with boy George once?
You did something funny with boy George in a store once.
You guys knew each other.
He's a really nice guy.
He's a sweetheart when he's not a hero.
He just keeps having trouble.
Yeah.
I met him a couple of times.
The first time he was on heroin.
And then remember that.
I remember that.
Yeah.
I wasn't there.
But I remember you telling me about that.
Right.
And that was in Holland.
And they said, whatever you do, don't talk to him.
I said, okay.
And then I started went to announce him and I said, hey, don't talk to him.
Why do you mean?
Because he was on heroin.
He was like completely fucked up.
And he was just going to lip sync to the song on stage with all
bunch of kids in front of it.
And that was going to be it.
And so I go up to announce him.
And instead of doing, and here's boy George.
I said, hey, man, they say you're on heroin.
Oh, no.
Did you believe?
Yeah.
He was really.
He didn't know what was happened.
But the woman from virgin was beside herself.
But then, he didn't hear that did that.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I heard it.
Yeah.
That's like one of those things.
But then the later we met at the, it was like a, a mis, a hard
Where's the mis Channel or something?
I don't know.
It was mis Home Depot.
Somewhere in New Jersey.
It was for Z100.
And he was in the, he was in Georgia.
I didn't remember that.
Yeah.
He was a photo of you guys.
The judging thing.
That's exactly what we were doing.
It was during his really puggie days.
Uh-huh.
He had a lot of makeup on, and it started to slide off.
I think you're right.
Now, that was big news over here, actually.
The garbage cleaning.
Yeah, I always go to New York for the big news events.
And you know, there were a couple other people.
I got really, really stink and drunk one night with Leslie Pinkney.
Well, I goodness.
These are all people who used to work with us at thinking of ideas.
And well, and it's, it's quasi relevant because Leslie is now vice president of music
development for tempo, which is the Latin and Caribbean music channel owned by MTV Network.
Okay.
Interesting.
So these people all kind of landed on their feet?
Yeah.
That's nice.
Leslie's doing well.
She looked great, and she can buy a mean shot or ten of patron silver.
And the other person that I got really stink and drunk with.
It was a theme.
Separate occasion.
Oh, yeah.
Every night I was in New York was our old friend and former makeup artist to the stars.
Keon Stava.
Keon.
Oh, man.
How was she doing?
Keon's done really well.
She's doing makeup.
Whatever happened to Jimmy.
Jimmy had a falling out with MTV Networks.
And then he went to the west coast.
And he was, I don't know what he got swallowed up.
He got swallowed up.
She knows.
What he's doing.
But I forgot.
We were really drunk.
I'm sure she told me.
That's funny.
Oh, wow.
So yeah.
She sends her love to you as well.
Keon was always very cool.
And I'm hot on the chair.
I had a brief chat with JB and our friend JB Miller.
JB Miller.
You used to work at MTV with us with Steve Leads.
He's can't remember where Steve wins.
Oh, no.
I talked to Leads all the time.
Where is Steve now?
He's not serious.
Yeah.
He's a satellite.
He does talent, create coordination.
So you know, all the Steve Leads.
Yes, Steve Leads.
Everyone who comes on to any show.
It's not to be confused with this brother Harvey Lee.
No, no, no.
I saw Harvey a while back, too.
But yeah, no, Steve is a, hey, baby.
I'm on with Ken.
You want to say hi to Keon.
Hey, baby.
Hold on.
Patricia.
I put your earphones on, huh?
Where are my earphones?
There are the hang in there.
The white ones.
This may not be this may have to be a multiple installment show,
because trouble is about to start.
Oh, okay.
You got it on.
You can hear me.
Yeah.
Say how to Ken.
Oh, my God.
It's like you're in the room here.
I said, I wish you were.
I want to.
I said it.
It felt like Adam was almost inside me when we used to,
and I put it in the phone.
Excuse me.
It's been a while since we've talked.
Yeah.
And we've each other.
So he was in stereo.
She's me.
Oh.
I want to give you a hug.
How are you, Patricia?
I'm fine.
I'm doing good.
Very good.
Very happy.
Tell me about the house.
Tell me about the house and then we'll hang up.
You want to tell me about the house?
No.
Did you lower the,
wait, new house?
Yeah.
Yeah, we finally found something.
I think we found something.
I'll send you a link.
You know, can't see real estate.
I know.
He knows all about this.
Oh, yeah.
Dude, you would clean up here.
It's fucking mess.
Eating well.
Fucking mess.
When are you coming over, dude?
I think, well, I'm looking at my schedule now.
And um, have all like a week from Friday.
No, okay.
I don't know.
No, but you have.
When am I going to just nip over to,
to Portland, I would be easier for everyone
to get together and stand for in Cisco.
Wouldn't it, for you, yeah?
Yeah.
He's really saying that.
He's like, we're going to be in the meantime.
The bottoms.
They're all the time.
And don't you go visit?
No.
Not a lot of them.
No, not a lot.
But she's been twice, dude.
Well, that's what I'm saying in it.
At that point, you're an hour and ten minutes away from me.
So, you know, I should just nip down.
Yeah.
But that's saying.
But that's your country.
You have to see another.
I would rather go to.
I would rather go to London.
Yeah.
Well, there you go.
I have to go.
I have been in London and see everything this so much.
You would love it.
We'll go visit boy George together.
It is.
Well, it is my mother country.
You know, I mean, my last.
I know.
Didn't I say that to you when I met you the first time?
Are you English?
Yes.
Actually, I am.
Can you tell by his accent?
I know.
Yes.
Oh, we don't want to pass.
There was a pass.
A pass.
A pass in the mix.
Yes.
And so Patricia came up here to get me down for dinner.
It's been like 50 minutes.
So we should stop anyway.
All right.
I guess that's enough for now.
And it's going to send you everybody.
Can wait for next year.
But the 20.
So it's to do our next in storm.
Yeah.
Now, listen, can't will you really come to San Francisco next time on there?
It's entirely possible.
It's a lot easier for me to nip down to San Francisco that it is a schedule time to go to English.
You should come and you'd like it.
You'd like it.
It's a good vibe.
Well, cool.
We'll talk about that actually.
Okay.
Well, thanks for taking time out of your your morning can.
Well, and thank you for having me.
And so much fun.
How do you want to say anything?
Take a bite?
I would just want to say goodbye.
And I just want to see you can.
I know.
I love you.
I want to see you too.
But you know, I think of you.
It's so frequently.
You're with me almost as much on a daily basis as you were when I was working in
Your home.
Oh, really.
Well, actually, it's the same that we do because sometimes we talk about you.
I don't know.
You know, sometimes it doesn't come up.
Yeah.
And I said, okay.
I'm still there.
You're still in there lurking in the corner.
Yeah.
You would not believe Christina though.
You would not believe her.
Well, the pictures every time I see a picture.
I just my jaw falls.
And I say, like, holy shit.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
My little shark in.
I still have photos here.
There's a photo in my office.
From her, like, oh, I don't know.
I remember being at her second birthday.
But I think this photo is from like her fourth or fifth birthday.
And it was that you had a pool party in your backyard.
Um, so no.
I look at pictures ever now.
And I just, I feel like an old fuck.
Yeah.
And remember always naked.
Always naked.
She was always naked.
The moment she came home, she would take off her clothes.
She actually still does.
Yeah.
She does that.
And I've left numerous times about her obsession over the pantyhose.
Yeah.
What was that?
The pantyhose obsession.
She wanted a pantyhose.
Always.
I just, she always nutrition.
Telling her to stop with the pantyhose.
I'll put them all in the fireplace.
I got you.
Really?
Good one.
She meant it.
Mommy meant it.
Yes.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
You have to see her.
I know.
Beautiful.
So you got any stories on before we go?
Interview stories.
Oh, I'm TV stories.
We're just doing MTV stories.
No.
Remember we were discussing the fact that I had been in New York for the, for the 25th anniversary
of MTV.
Oh, you did.
When I was talking about the,
remember you used to go with us to Los Angeles.
And we, we did a lot of fun stuff in Los Angeles.
The only thing I just, I saw him again.
John, uh,
Norris.
No.
Yeah.
You're coming in the neck.
John Norris.
And I remember he was sort of a go for them.
You know.
Yeah.
Oh, he was here.
He was a writer in the news department.
I'm sorry.
I thought he was a go for it.
I drew in your,
I drew in your V.J.
I could really clearly Patricia treated him as a go for it.
Hey.
Hey, boy.
We'll get my call.
It was my latte.
And he was in the back care of the car.
I remember that.
And we were in Los Angeles.
In Los Angeles.
And we had to go to somewhere on the mountain where you had an interview with somebody.
Can he log in?
Was that problem?
I don't know.
But he was in the back of the car.
He was a very,
uh,
uptight,
very nervous.
Oh, yeah.
And you know,
his eyes were very big and he was so.
I thought you were going to say emaciated.
Now maybe.
But he was,
he wanted to be at him.
I just knew it.
Really?
Yeah.
He was constantly looking into.
And you,
you could tell that he thought I won't be there.
Oh.
I'm in the wrong spot.
Yeah.
He got there.
I mean,
Oh, yeah.
He got there.
You got there.
Huh.
Aren't you glad we don't still do that by the way?
Yeah, but it was always it was really really fun then, but thank God we don't still do that
No, but then it was the MTV that you know MTV should have been you know
Oh, hey, hey, that's not fair. MTV evolved. They had to do what they had to do. That's fine
I know but it was it was it was the time when it was fun. Do you still do you think they still have fun?
Yeah, I think they have fun. They probably have fun. I mean because they weren't there then
So they don't have the perspective on it and there's always new people coming in and then there's no
An exciting and no trends in do you know. I mean to us we we got old and jaded and it wasn't funny
No, that's right. I started the suck the only thing I remember there was people got fired all the time
Well, yeah, I mean revolving door bring it there. They were there and then we're gone. You mean VJs or you
VJs everything well VJs and everyone else at the channel base
I mean makeup is kind of a revolver, but I think that's the nature of the business and of television
Yeah, I think so. I think so. I think so. Yeah, it was a bit of a springboard, but you know they brought people like Andrew
Daddo from Australia
Well, they was a nice guy. Yeah, he was all right, but
There was that Richard Wilkins guy that you liked actually you got along with Richard. He was all right.
He talked about that funny guy. He's still an actor an actor
The funny guy. Yeah, the funny guy. He was so Kevin Steven Steven. No, I he's in Seattle and I think he went back to whatever his degree
had been was like an engineering. Yeah, he was too into it. He was way too intelligent for that. He was
saying well, I think he got through it all just by doing a lot of mushrooms. Yeah, screw probably was. Yeah,
yeah, he was fucked up all the time all the time. Yeah, that's my money that in his infamous addition
where he shaved while he was in this audition tape. Yeah, doing the thing and then started doing
this bizarre way was it was it a special impersonation or something. He put on that shirt and tie and yeah,
I see it. He was in fact tripping
and he got hired those were the days man. We could get hired for you in some shrooms. That's it.
All right, I can't I'm going to go have I'm going to go have dinner and all right. I'll talk to you real soon. Okay. All right. See you guys
I'm going to shoot. We miss you, can. I miss you too. Okay. Love you. Bye. Bye.
Another pod show podcast. Stick it in your ear.