Think Advertising sucks.
Think you can do better?
Pod Show and EarthLink are willing to put our money where your mouth is.
Listen to this podcast or go to adchelens.podshow.com to see how you can win big
in the EarthLink make advertising better challenge.
Diltess Yara Charley.
Three.
Nineer.
Four.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
They pack the bags and off they go.
Though they might be quite far from home.
The world is their oyster and she is his pearl for sure.
It's Patricia and Adam set out for another world tour.
New Yorker's San Fran without her just wouldn't be right.
Yes, she's the real reason for Adam to come home tonight.
But when they're away and they both want to play at the flick of the wrist or up on the split
they can find their way around.
Paint the whole town for sure.
It's Patricia and Adam set out for another fabulous wonderful
filled extravagant happy ever after world tour.
And coming to you from northern California Monterey.
Pebble Beach to be exact.
It is the daily source code for Friday.
Good morning.
It says still very early on this Friday morning out here.
She can tell from the nasal sound.
This is not going to be a typical Friday show.
We've been here at the Cliner Perkins CEO Summit for the past two days.
And there's plenty to talk about, which I think we'll probably do a nice Memorial Day weekend show
with the two of us at the condo and really get you ramped up on many of the amazing things
that we've witnessed once again.
But a lot of all the people who are here, one person really stood out on the first evening
so that was when we get here, huh?
I don't know.
Wednesday, Wednesday evening after a very long flight from New York and an equally interesting
and long car trip from San Francisco Airport down to Monterey.
There was a dinner and so the dinner features all of the CEOs.
That's who was invited here, all the CEOs that Cliner Perkins has invested in companies
and the spouses if they choose to bring them.
But there was a special guest, which was announced who would be our entertainment for the evening.
And this special guest did probably about an hour and a half of what at first brush may have looked like
stand up, but it really was something completely different.
His name is Charles Flycher and if that name doesn't mean anything to you right off the bat,
if you, and I'll put a picture of him up in the show notes on dailysourcecode.com and curry.com.
He also was, he's an actor, he's a scientist and most of you will probably know him as the voice of
a many other characters, Roger Rabbit and who framed Roger Rabbit.
And I was just mesmerized by what this guy was doing and what he was actually doing with the audience and how incredibly intelligent he had to be
to be able to make all of these different observations and make it all very funny.
So we hooked up actually not long after his performance and I said, I really want to get you on the daily sourcecode
because I think you were 100% podcast material and not just audio video and over the course of the past two days
we've actually come to some agreements, this would be a very good thing to try.
And for today's Friday edition, which you can just chill out and listen to over Saturday or Sunday,
it's about 40 minutes.
I talk with Charles Flycher around midnight last night in the ballroom I think of the hotel.
We tried to find a relatively quiet place.
And I'm going to let you listen to that now and I'll be back at the end of the interview.
I think you'll see that this guy is definitely interesting, certainly entertaining and without a doubt wacky.
So when I came in late last night and you were already performing.
How long...
You were now when I started?
No, no, no, because we came in late and then Ron sent me in it.
First of all, I didn't know that you were here.
I was like, join us for some great entertainment and for our guests and I'm like, God, it's Robin Williams.
Let's see here too.
No, no, but they do a lot.
He invests with the client of Perkins.
Really?
Yeah.
And they keep saying, you know, it's like they got Bono and they got Oprah.
And so they have this Hollywood side scene.
So it's a tie-in.
Exactly.
So it was like, you know, a special guest.
And I'm like, because I knew that Charlie Rose originally...
Right.
Well, I guess he does this all the time.
But he had some heart sugars.
That's what he said.
But what was amazing is that...
So I came in late and I'm sitting at the table.
I don't know most of the people here.
I know Ray and John and the people at our table.
And I think a lot of people would say, well, that was a great stand-up comedian.
Wasn't he funny?
But I'm like, this dude is something else.
You were doing shit on stage and I'd never seen before.
Of course, I've been deprived maybe of a lot of light on entertainment.
But you've done research and you were just doing shit on the fly that was amazing.
Totally blew me away.
Oh, well, that's my goal is to create new synapses.
And many people realized stuff that they didn't realize they realized.
When did you hear about doing this particular gig?
Well, they first told me about it a couple of months ago.
I was booked.
So you did have a while to prep for?
Oh, no.
I didn't get the book with everybody's name in it until just yesterday.
I did it for yesterday.
I got it.
I looked through the book before I did the show and just kind of,
because in my act, I usually work the crowd.
What do you do?
And then I worked that all into bits that are cohesive and leads to songs at the end.
But everybody here, you know what they do?
So I focused more on the idea of the names of the corporations they have.
So you were planning on doing that before the year?
Well, I have figured to be something about that because some of the names just seem really cool.
Like a spatial photonics.
A little spatial photonics.
That was cool.
And someone just seemed really kind of lame and good technology.
Even though it is good and you know, know now.
Yeah, I hadn't heard of it.
I hadn't heard of it.
One true media and I'd heard of it.
Yeah, I heard that this is pretty cool.
It's kind of like a random.
Yeah, they got some kind of app that does stuff and matches a video.
Yeah, it's totally, it's basically like a real time editing thing.
They just, you know, so it takes the first picture in it.
Well, from a group of different random possibilities, it will zoom into the left.
And then the second picture will flash cut.
Oh, really? Okay.
And I haven't seen it.
That's just what I...
It really incubates in terms of rating about it.
He uses it for something.
And apparently, you know, it will change that.
Just like on, there's certain, I use Mac, I would guess.
But they still have screen servers.
And you can have it going around and where it picks from this one in that one.
And you get the Ken Burns effect.
The Ken Burns effect.
Is that it? The Ken Burns effect?
Well, that's the silver.
I think it's more like, you know, Ken Burns himself.
It's more the George Burns effect.
Ken Burns ripped me off with his Gracie Shadow Grace.
You know, so I sat down and like, I know this guy.
Of course, everyone has that with you.
Yeah, I know this guy.
I'm very mad about it.
I don't think you want everybody.
Because everybody likes you.
You're probably doing something wrong.
You want some people to be offended and some people not to get it.
It's good to be.
I don't think anyone is completely like.
I mean, you know, nobody likes Elvis or nobody like the Beatles.
Yeah, even Jesus, not as an icon.
You know, it's impossible not even like selections.
So a lot of people know you from who frame Roger Rabbit,
which I just realized that movie, although it seemed so incredibly fresh.
And memory was 18 years ago when I came out in 1988.
Yeah.
It's 18 years ago.
Man.
Isn't it 18 or 15?
It's 17.
I just know it was longer than it was in high school.
Yeah.
It doesn't seem, I don't calculate.
So like, to me, I kind of just consider it's always now.
Right.
Yeah.
That was Roger.
So did you two other voices in that?
Three.
Okay.
Good call.
Twenty seconds.
Cool.
There was a question on jeopardy ones, I think.
Like regarding that.
I was Benny the cab.
Right.
And two of the wizards.
It's like on greasy.
greasy.
Right.
Did you see?
I want to kill him.
I'm kidding.
Yeah.
Do you consider yourself actor, comedian, observer of people?
I consider myself to be many different things.
And all related to my central self.
And all of my career people have advised me that I needed to just pick one to which I responded.
You know, I have to limit the things I love to do because you have a small brain.
You've been going slim.
An agent, obviously.
I'm not even.
Sometimes they were just, you know, presidents.
You know, so I looked at just before I came out of the room.
I looked at, I think it was Wikipedia or something incredibly authoritative source.
It's an amazing amount of shit that you've done.
Lots of TV.
Yeah.
And then off that basis, you know, I've been doing this for a while.
So if you make living for a while, you're going to get some kind of credit score.
Mm-hmm.
And the irony, I guess, is that I feel now that I'm in a position now.
I'm really bad to like start doing things on another level.
And then all of a sudden you bump into the podcast guys.
Podcast guys, which is interesting in many ways because maybe three days ago,
there was a big article about you guys in the LA paper.
Yeah, the LA Times.
Yeah, the Times.
Yeah, which I had read.
And I sometimes pretty interesting.
Again, I just, I was reading that I was thinking, like somewhere in Martha Quinn is going,
Whoa.
What's that?
How did you do that?
Wow.
I got the new Trajina here.
She's sitting there going.
Can I have a cafe, coffee, coffee, and going back to France and around?
All those people.
Well, this is actually, this is our second company.
We took a company public in 1996.
Yeah, I would have some like large coin above.
Yeah.
They just made it.
I think having money, or even with a calm business, the fuck you money,
which is not necessarily means that you can say fuck you,
but it's certainly possibilities.
And which is like, do this?
No.
Because if you have no money, I'm saying fuck you.
You're saying, I really rather not.
What's that an instruction?
It's an instruction or proposition based on predestination.
Yeah, that's, I think that's really, I think it's cool.
Especially when you do it on your own ideology in terms.
On terms, and you still have your dignity in.
It's not like, you know, you did Chinese gay porn.
There was a fluffer for pandas.
Which pays really good.
Just a taste of pandas.
It's like it's actually a day.
If we're sitting there running, I go like, this is a podcast.
He's a podcast.
And we've been doing this now.
I've been doing podcasts for almost two years.
And for the first year, I kept on saying, where are the, where are the comedians?
Where are the, the wordsmiths?
You know, this is so perfect for them.
And you're the first one that actually bumped into,
switched on and understands and is interested in it.
Yeah.
It seems like that's, that's, everyone who can do that.
You know, the stuff that you do.
Just really fast, very well thought out.
Brilliant.
It's not all comedy, but it's just, it makes you sit there and think for a couple seconds.
I don't know where they are, but then I do, and they're not, they're not thinking about that.
A lot of times they have an adversity to the technological ability,
which prevents the sensitivity from manifesting proclivity.
And because I am, as you said, indeed the word wise,
but I also love bits and bytes and technology.
And I think it's having that understanding of essentially an evolution of medium,
which leads to large, which makes the small one.
It makes the one all depending on the position point of view
and how many pandas have recently allocated.
Are you not a point in, in your career, your life,
where you're ready to do something more experimental,
or less, let's call it less mainstream?
I've always been there.
I mean, I always consider everything.
I don't really consider that modality as affecting me.
I mean, if I get a job going to movie, I'm doing that,
but I just, as the role kind of said,
listen to the beat of a different drummer,
I've always just kind of followed my own instincts.
And if it sticks fine, if not, I'll just, you know,
put it on the shelf and just keep making stuff.
But I definitely, when I read about it,
and then talking to you, realize that this, you know,
it's like meeting a girl that, you know,
you really like just realize that this works.
I get this, or reading a book that you really like,
or the first time I saw Salvador Dali,
his paintings, personally, or the first time I heard Hendrix.
It's just a connection where there's a resonation
and your soul and just kind of go,
yeah, or someone, you know, gets you,
and there's just like,
have you heard the raccoon tours?
I know that new album, I think, Jack White.
Really great.
I think it's, and I like plugging other people
who are especially when they don't need it.
Because they're doing really well.
But when you hear something that's new,
and you just immediately go, yeah.
And it's the same kind of thing about this whole dynamic,
podcast thing.
It's also a vibe of the people too.
You know, you know, you wouldn't even partner
or you think it's just, there's a,
like a raccoon tours, there's a rock and roll,
kind of sensibility.
It's just, it's an ideology of dealing with things.
It's different than other business modes.
What we notice, what we discovered is that,
the easiest thing is to compare it to,
particularly the audio is to compare it to radio,
which isn't a very fair comparison.
But when people hear podcasts,
they, they all of a sudden,
and they realize how deprived they've been
of quality audio entertainment,
particularly from the radio.
Yeah, everything is, you know,
it's a formatted package sliced down totally solos.
To be like the last thing that was successful,
you know, a bunch of guys in the morning.
Yeah.
Good morning.
It's a wacky morning zoo.
What do you think is old?
Oh, the new.
It's really pretty predictable.
Yeah.
And it's, you know, it's television without the lights.
And the real radio, the old stuff was really cool
because it, really the imagination,
take over, you know,
you know, we're in a room,
because the room we're in right now is,
like, about three inches of grip jelly on the floor
and at least large,
I don't know, they look like bugs.
They're just kind of bouncing around the background
and these chairs are floating,
they're just weird chandeliers.
They're kind of like breasts,
but then again,
more like,
just candles that are flared outwards.
And that's the room.
No, everybody,
here's that,
we'll get a different variation of it.
And someone's going to go,
I know that room, man.
They,
Tina, they're in the jelly room.
I told you, it's real.
Oh, Frank, you're tripping.
No, baby.
It's the jelly room.
These dudes are in a prank you're tripping.
No, baby.
So we've talked about,
about some ideas and some stuff that you might do
with podcasting.
How would you want to utilize this?
I want to do a show
that incorporates my,
my loves,
essentially,
which are the arts and science,
including everything from music
to literature to painting,
to the ability of humans to figure out
how the universe works.
If we were talking about that,
the golden ratio,
golden ratio is one of my major inspirations.
Can you explain that?
Yeah.
Well, if anybody is listening at this time
in their lights are on,
if you look at your thumb,
the distance between
the knuckle to the middle of your thumb,
and that to the end of your thumb,
is the golden ratio.
It's dividing a line into two parts,
where the division is not half.
It would have to be 0.5.
It would be at 0.618.
And it sets up a mathematical harmonic
where the smaller is to the larger.
So the first little part is to the second part
as the second part is to the entire thumb.
It just keeps going.
If you look at your next finger,
it's the first part of the knuckle
to the second part, to the third part.
Yeah.
If anybody, if you draw a 5.8 star,
and where the lines intersect,
that is also the golden ratio,
a point of social goal,
golden section, golden mean proportion,
lists the Fibonacci series,
several diales at all the time,
a lot of artists MC Escher,
it's part of everything.
Is this a,
a mathematical or,
or physics equation that is,
there are several ways that you can derive it.
You could first talk about it.
One way to get it is the square root of 5,
plus 1 divided by 2.
And that gives you 1.618,
or the square root of 5 minus 1 divided by 2,
which is the 0.618.
As far as the Fibonacci,
which is a mathematical series
where the next number in the sequences
derived by adding the 2 before,
so 1, 2, 3, 5, 8.
When you then get to 89,
over 55,
that gives you 1.618.
So there's several ways to get it,
a self-server to his fee,
and it's,
it's a bizarre,
amazing magical thing.
Another indication of its magical powers,
I would say,
0.618,
if you divide 1 by 0.618,
you get 1.618,
which is the same thing.
If you add 0.618 to 1,
which is 1.8 to 1.
So this number,
which is 1.8,
you can divide it into 1
or add it to 1,
and get the same answer.
That's the kind of indication.
Wow, that's crazy,
man.
That's the thing.
If I give you this,
you give it back to me,
you know,
it will be the last distance again.
That's crazy.
You give it a bud,
and in my mother gets high.
And in nobody coughs,
that's crazy.
The bubbles is flipping.
Oh, so funny.
You were explaining that to someone last night
to get a performance.
And I think you actually thought you were still telling a joke.
When I started scuiving into my mathematics stuff,
which is,
I referred to as moleeds.
And I actually did the moleeds on the tenetra years ago.
And I said,
moleeds,
that's the name of the,
what I consider the primary particle of the universe,
where everything is based on.
And we're working on for 28 years.
I went out to dinner last week with this great French artist,
named Jill Bruvelle.
Once again, I plug for other people.
Bruvelle, B.R.U.V.
Sounds like he needs it.
Bruvelle, like,
oh, this guy, he's, he's a genius.
He's like a cross between,
if I had to cross it Salvador Dali
and served to Soleil.
Okay.
Just amazing artist.
He's French.
And the waiter comes up and he goes,
moleeds.
We were talking about moleeds.
Because he knew about moleeds.
He used to do a bit about, I did it.
We were talking about the bit.
Because for those of us who were too young.
Well, I think they would be moleeds.
Everyone but me and Grandpa Shnove.
Well, it's based on a relationship with the numbers 27 and 37.
And the bit that I did was just,
you know, making some comedy out of the real math stuff.
But in the last two years,
I've made significant breakthroughs on it.
I'm trying to compile it on house so that I can present it to people in the scientific community.
So it can be proven in a way that will,
you know, bring me some, you know, some, some coin.
Some equine respect, you know,
well, they don't give the Nobel Prize in mathematics.
Really?
Yeah.
And there's one theory that states,
Nobel, who,
and then that nine of my, and started the prize.
How does that work together?
The dynamite thing in the past.
He just has money.
And his girlfriend was basically
swept away and taken by a mathematician.
So, you know, it's like, what about math?
No, we're not using math.
Why not?
Just Frank stole Becky.
But the other people say,
well, he considered math a part of everything.
And there is another prize for mathematics,
but you have to be under 30 or something.
But, you know, I am about the prizes about
you know, about the bitches.
And it's about the changing science.
That's, that's cool to me.
To me, the real rock stars are scientists.
Not that, you know, you too, and those guys are all,
but, and some of those guys,
and 200 years, people still be playing there.
There's stuff, you know, probably Abba,
and the other groups.
Abba in the movie.
Exactly.
A new group.
Although, Abba is a palindrome.
It is.
Absolutely.
Which is important, kind of mathematical property.
My favorite palindrome, or palindrome,
if you actually listen to the words,
is Satan oscillate my metallic sonatas.
Same back as in forwards.
And palindromes are important, I think,
because they are back as in forwards.
And there's a sequence in male DNA.
That is in the male, you know,
in the X-Wad.
That comes on that's palindromic,
which is kind of like backup.
So does that mean that
palindromes work better on males?
No, it just means that, like,
because it's really the male that decides
whether it's going to be a boy or a girl.
Okay.
So it, like, just to make sure the things are a
messed up, like, you know, we got some
messed-up sperm over here.
Read it backwards.
Oh, yeah, thank you, dude.
So, like, you know, if you whack backwards,
it'll still come out.
That's why you know, when you whack, you can go
up or down.
He's like, it's a palindromic activity.
Yeah, so my palindromes and back to numbers.
And it's all, everything's related, essentially.
And that's kind of part of the essence of the pod show,
which I believe at this point,
will be referred to as flashes universe.
I think that.
I like it.
And it'll be video.
I think it'll be video or radio.
Pictures.
Yeah, it'll be work or just loud pictures.
Turn off the picture.
Turn off the sound.
Yeah, I think videos.
Good.
Because a lot of the things that I want to communicate
are better communicated with visuals.
Mm-hmm.
And most of the work that I do as far as experimenting
and studying, I create pictures and then
study patterns.
And that's how I kind of went to play the guitar.
I made my own little chart so that I could
they'd be more visual.
And I would make different colors.
So I'd memorize the frigion mode and blue red and green.
Just thinking that my brain would like maybe
be more partial to one color.
Be easier to remember.
Yeah, you know, that some people, like it's easy to
remember that one color.
Just I just like experimenting with visuals.
I'm definitely very visually oriented as far as
processing information.
For some reason, I don't know what it's spatial or
facial or just I like looking at stuff.
Have you decided what you want to be when you grow up?
I decided that when I grow up, I want to be king of the universe.
Well, but I'm not going to grow up for wild,
but I think the universe needs a king.
And this is not to be confused with the duty.
Not to be confused with call.
This is just king of the universe.
It's just it's a social position.
And there's responsibility because the galaxy is
and moving all apart.
And there's a lot of dark matter out there.
And, you know, I think it's a good, it's a good goal.
You believe in extraterrestrial life?
It's not even belief.
It's, you know, I know.
I mean, we are extraterrestrial.
In some sense, just because, you know,
this is extra.
But, you know, the day it just
think that life is just here in 13 and
have been in years or so of this universe is just
really silly.
Yeah.
Of course.
As to whether they've been here recently or when
who knows, and I think glad UFOs are just that
they're identified flying objects.
But there's definitely lots of realms that we don't know about.
And this whole system that we're having fun with
is a lot more magical than people think.
Not all people like the magic people.
And many people know, there are many levels.
Then, you know, chakra five,
calling chakra four.
Your dinty parts are ready for my
flopping web one.
Yeah.
It's definitely this.
Things are magical.
I've learned anything from being here
these past two days.
That's a really good question.
I learned that the coffee is better at night.
Seems wrong.
Yeah.
I learned that the guys working in the other room are very
friendly.
Yes.
I learned that I won't be a podcaster.
And I think sometimes you learn something but don't know you've learned it
until later.
And I've often heard people say that wisdom is being able to
know right after something happens how you would react
to suppose like a week later thinking, you know when I should have
sent a lawyer and I should have said, no man,
you put up the curtains.
You fucking moron.
That's what I should have said to him.
He called me a loser trick trap.
And I'm too isolated.
But by the way, you're a loser trick.
Yeah, you put up the fucking curtains.
Yeah.
That's wisdom.
Okay.
So you didn't really learn that much from me.
I don't know.
You know, I know that I learned that there's a lot of really wealthy
people here.
And there's some...
Why did what I learned that you can really misjudge people
in the very first moment.
And when I was doing my thing the other night,
we didn't when I was talking to the lawyer.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Well, I spoke to him later and he's like a really good human.
But very socially conscious and has kind of a spiritual center
and is really into doing more than just, you know, taking the coin.
Oh, please.
He has your fooled.
Is that what it was?
Yeah.
That when it was good because you were so...
I mean, maybe it's not fair to a lot of these people in the audience.
Well, that's in the audience.
Yeah.
That little moment.
You came just by that.
But then I knew it was okay, but after talking to him,
I was surprised at the level of his social dedication
and his wanting to contribute.
Yeah, that's pretty much the culture of planet Perkins, though I have to say.
Well, that's another theory.
That, I don't know.
Another thing that amazed me that what you would think is basically greed
and monetary gain could somehow partner up with some kind of social responsibility.
I suppose that is what I have learned.
I've learned that even rich people.
Lots of money in the ability to help people that are even rich,
and people who come at you can still have a quality.
Like, you can raise corn and still have a movie theater.
You can eat pop tarts and still have a pop gun.
You can cheat yourself in the foot and still have a metaphor that makes no sense.
Tomorrow morning, there's a special viewing of Al Gore's movie.
You're going to get up on one side.
You're going to get to the world.
Because there's also Q&A with Al Gore after that.
Yeah, but it's a satellite, but what an opportunity.
Well, he was a Ted.
Oh, you bet him?
Yeah.
He, like, my, I presented there.
And he said kind of things to me.
Really?
He was actually hilarious as both of the fictitiously.
He was doing stand-up.
The first presentation was he was doing, you know,
basically the movie idea, which is important stuff.
But then he was doing stand-up.
Yeah, he was talking about no longer being by his president and driving a tourist.
Right, so he's got a whole wrap going for that.
Yeah, he was really going to man if you lose the election.
You got to have something going whenever someone meets you.
So he'd be like, you know, and either way, there's that losing thing.
Maybe it was actually taking.
Either way.
Could be.
It doesn't matter what he is.
But he was very funny.
And I offered to red jokes from the fiat we needed.
And as he accepted, yeah.
Well, I haven't heard from the director.
Okay.
From some people that claimed to be out of work.
So did it.
Ted, did you do something similar?
Ted is a technology entertainment design.
It's once a year in Monterey.
It's an exclusive invite only.
It's a invite only.
It's about five grand for three days.
And it's like kind of a Star Trek college campus.
And they have amazing presenters there.
And I, for three years ago, they asked me to be there.
Because Thomas Dolby is the musical director.
And his wife and Thomas used to see me in LA at the improv years ago.
And they asked, and the theme of that one was happiness and Chris Anderson, who produced
it when a comedian.
And I did that one and then they asked me back.
And then back again.
And there are some really dynamic speakers.
Two years ago, the last girl was speak.
18 year old girl talking about a cure for cancer.
How the heart is the only part of the body that didn't be cancer.
I mean, this girl was extraordinary.
And, you know, you hear things there that you read about in the paper five,
ten days later, you know, breakthroughs.
For real.
Yeah, it's an amazing event.
It's really, it's really cool.
So it's as a stand-up comedy always been kind of your platform,
your place for honing your skills.
Well, one of them, that's one of the ways that I express myself
and do some kind of communication reciprocation.
And I started that.
I was pretty little, but I also had this need to express myself visually
as far as, you know, drawing or painting.
And I called you.
I mean, obviously, we only just met.
So I haven't, you know, normally we've done research.
No, but I think it's better that way.
Yeah, I think it's better.
I just met a woman who knew nothing about anything that I've done.
And that's better in a lot of ways.
Because sometimes, you know, you just track people that are interested in you
because you've achieved something somewhere that is appealing to them
and that kind of attraction is usually based on some kind of
superficial attribute.
So it's good because that way your questions are genuine
and not handed by, oh, when there's a question here,
it says, so tell me about the Franco Smokmark.
They tell you about it.
You know about it.
We discussed it yesterday.
And a green in the green.
In the green.
That one on our flute.
Yeah.
I mean, that's really what television and all.
And all mainstream media has really become that.
It's, it's one of the, I guess the eventual downfalls of anything that has structure.
I mean, even films, you know, the three-act structure.
You know, you can kind of get around it, Quentin Tarantino.
You know, put the beginning at the end.
And there's different ways to tweak it.
But essentially movies have three acts.
And you know, it's a little different because it's all based on time.
And when you only have a channel and 24 hours in a day for that channel, then it has to,
you have to have regulation and structure.
Sure.
You know, the show.
It's something to me.
The first segment is this.
And yeah, there's the guest.
Yeah.
There's the pre-interview.
And you got your five questions.
And you know, I asked him three.
And then they looked on the little card.
And so tell me about this.
And it's not as it's just so and graceful.
That's where Johnny Carson was really.
He was very different.
He was different.
Yeah.
And to me, Letterman is more accepting of that.
And I found that he's become since he said a kid.
I can sense in him change of growth.
And he just seems to love more.
Hmm.
You know, and I think a kid can do that too.
Very easily, probably.
Yeah.
And he was a great admirer of Johnny.
And Carson used to write for him after he retired.
He would send jokes to Letterman.
Yeah.
And Letterman was really in strong acknowledgement of that.
And the whole Letterman Leno thing.
And Leno got the show.
And there was this thing.
Leno didn't really pay tribute right.
And Jay.
Yeah.
That's all Hollywood stuff.
I can't get so that.
But you know, I'm just happy people come make money telling jokes.
It's selling so.
Yeah.
That's for sure.
Very much what it is.
Well, you know, if you really do get into.
Into podcasting is the thing that I think you'll be brilliant at.
Is helping us change advertising.
Hmm.
Because that's the real challenge.
Well, advertising is is back to what is advertising sold on.
Seconds.
Twenty seconds, thirty seconds.
Get the message out.
Um, and the easiest way of courses.
If you use this product, you'll get laid.
If you don't use this product, your hair will fall out.
I mean, that's two basic ways to get laid by someone.
So does it.
Is it more of the product placement pattern as we're talking?
You know, when I walked over here, I, I watched my hands with this.
Um, Agua soap.
And if my.
No, no, no.
It's, that's the beauty.
It's, it's not about placing it.
You know, we're sneaking it in.
Um, it's advertising is content.
Um, people.
People.
So this show is brought to you by podcast.
Actually, it's universe brought to you by.
Well, no, uh, it could be, um, let me see, uh, an, an active example.
It could be brought to you by acupue contact lenses.
But, uh, maybe the whole show is one big commercial.
Yeah.
People want.
Content.
It's just content.
No matter what the subject will respond to your show.
Or you have many.
Many.
Yeah.
Many different ones.
So it's earthling.
Um, is one.
Um,
We have, uh, as we have a couple of, uh,
internet related ones like go daddy.
Um, I've secured them in.
I'm going to go daddy.
So, so by the asking away, but wait, if you use, uh, uh,
promotional code DSC three upon checkout, your domain name would have only cost you
$6.95.
Yeah.
Well, if you know where daddy goes.
Because for 32.
Yeah.
Really.
No daddy.
That's, uh, I love the names of new.
Technology companies shifting.
And I think it started, uh,
I guess Yahoo.
And then Red Hat.
And, uh, that's not it.
Oh, Google.
Google.
Blue tooth.
You know, as a technology, just where it's become more poetic.
Blue tooth has a history that name, though.
It was, um, Blue tooth was, I think it was a Viking.
And yeah, his name was Blue tooth.
Blue tooth.
Yeah.
No, no.
It's a blue tooth.
I can look it up.
Yeah.
It was Blue tooth.
And he somehow, um, brought other Vikings together.
And they weren't fighting with each other.
And that's the whole idea.
That's Blue tooth.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Come on.
64.
I think.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
And Blue tooth connects multiple devices.
Yeah.
That's really.
Some of these names are actually based on.
Sure.
They weren't messing with you here.
On nicotine.
The same day after this guy in the Cote.
Really?
Something to do with tobacco.
But, uh, the, uh, I blew too.
I thought it was just like some guy, you know.
I'm like an upper split one.
Blue tooth.
Green tree.
Elemental wise trick.
White out.
Here we go.
The blue tooth name in history.
Hold on a second.
I'm not kidding you man.
He's not kidding.
For this we've bossing us.
He is actually going to some sort of digital device.
Which is probably not a sponsor.
But could be at the speed, but he is using it.
Could be a blue bear.
Black there.
A raspberry.
Raspberry.
Eric Carmen.
Was that raspberry?
Yeah.
And then it was in a group of color raspberries.
Uh, out of, uh, Cleveland, maybe?
That's the raspberries.
No.
No?
Eric Carmen.
Yes.
He was.
Eric Carmen in the raspberries.
Here we go.
Harold Bluetooth.
I was close.
Oh, Carl Luther.
Yeah, Viking.
Not a Viking to call a Harold.
It's from Denmark.
He was king of Denmark.
Can you second it?
In the late, in the late 900's.
That's, that's like hundreds.
The same Harold?
Harold.
Oh, yeah.
That's a big difference.
Wow.
He managed to unite Denmark in part of Norway into a single kingdom, then introduced
Christianity into Denmark.
He left a large monument.
The jelly room stone.
In memory of parents.
He was killed in 986 during the battle with the sun.
Schwedd forkbeard.
I'm not making the shit out.
You're not.
Put the guy who wrote it.
No.
I'm not saying.
Forkbeard and Bluetooth.
And the giant gel stone.
Here.
I'm not saying.
Is this a Wikipedia?
No.
But this is, well, no.
You can find this in many, many places on the internet.
This name for the standard indicates how important companies from the Baltic region.
Nations, including Denmark, Sweden, Norway, and Finland are to the communications industry.
Even if it says little about the way the technology works.
I've heard a different version of that.
Well, you know.
But it's something that there wasn't Harold Bluetooth.
It does bring up an interesting point.
It is how much of history it really happened.
I mean, really, I know what, you know, I can see.
And before Photoshop, what videos you've seen.
And there's a lot, you know.
They don't teach the Armenian genocide in American schools because we have military bases in Turkey.
So things are obscured and hidden.
That's for all my Armenian friends.
I don't know if you're young, young, and any.
Or Tom Palayanian.
So, you know, something you think may have happened.
But you know that the agenda of the white man, and I use that metaphorically, is, is
one who will like twist stuff up to make his plate fuller.
Well, well, either purposely or not.
Because, you know, somebody's reading the document.
And then he took cloth pro to the river.
I don't think he meant river.
I think he really meant stream.
Because, like, 12 gigabytes, and all of a sudden,
Plopra had a system that was 19 gigahertz.
And that gigaavis.
And some things, you think, are real.
But Bluetooth and fork-paired.
I'm just, I'm skeptical.
It just sounds a little too funny to me.
The Harold Bluetooth.
Harold Bluetooth.
I didn't think Harold was a common name.
Harold.
Oh, Harold.
Harold Bluetooth.
Mr. Forkbeard.
Your Bluetooth is ready.
Mr. Yellow S.
Mr. White calling.
Mr. Green fork.
That's just the eye of that.
But I had to see.
And what about Red Hat?
Is that Thomas Red Hat of?
I don't know what the genesis is behind Red Hat.
I think it's just weed behind most of these things.
Well, it certainly helps me to understand all the names better.
Well, and not just you, you know, everybody that, you know, has a bluetooth
or Red Hat or a Sun Microsystem.
Yeah.
Growing up in Amsterdam, it was pretty much the way the way you go through life.
You were supposed to be alone.
Delta 9.
And, you know, in this country, alcohol was legal.
Yeah.
Beginning of last week in some places, if you're 12.
And I don't think it's changed quickly.
Yeah.
But I'm still amazed at Harold Bluetooth.
I think it's the Fort Bay.
I don't know why they didn't go with Fort Bay or just the name.
I didn't even go with Fort Bay or technology.
Fort Bay or the BirdFork.
I wonder what, what, what.
Yeah.
It's.
Oh, Harold Blatton.
There you go.
That was, it's a bluetooth.
This is, of course.
Oh, but a song.
Is, of course, a translation of the Blatton.
Well, a mastodon means milk tooth.
Okay.
You know, the woolly mammoth, the mastodon.
Oh, yeah.
Milk tooth.
It's the big tusks.
There were calling milk tooth.
So Bluetooth could have been milk tooth.
It was like, if it had like a larger trunk.
It may be more bandwidth.
It smelled like, you know, I could earn this ass.
Blatton.
Harold Blatton.
Yes.
But this year, mother, I have Blatton.
No.
My flat student doesn't have a blue ass.
And green hurl.
Blue teeth.
Well, the thing about this just goes to shade.
You could be entertained.
And you may find out something that's educational or a lie or a combination.
I think five-sight theater had a record.
Just go everything you know is wrong.
Which kind of speaks that whole premise.
And I was looking at about just writing a bunch of just new history.
You're a Steve Gilmore?
Steve Gilmore?
Steve Gilmore.
He produced a lot of fires at theater.
I remember Proctor and Bergman.
He was really the producer.
Or at least so.
He claims.
He's in Wikipedia for a few years.
And Blatton.
He also does a couple of podcasts.
For all bozos on this bus.
Fashioned theater.
I remember back in the...
It was kind of podcasts.
But that was part of the day.
It was surreal.
It was definitely out there.
And that was when FM radio could still put on.
You know, you could put stuff on.
No one would give a shit.
And I guess that's not true anymore, is it?
No, but FM radio at the time is.
Okay, now I'm going to play Zeppelin the key of G.
Now it's all play this and it's all corporate and blackmail.
Which is why this is really the new way.
And no concept of limited resources of frequency or spectrum.
Ordination.
I mean, that's the big one.
Direction.
Incredible.
Yeah.
Because like how long is this show?
How long can you go?
Yeah.
How many days a left before the end of the world?
What happens is your audience starts to tell you what is right for them.
And it will be different for every show.
And of course, it's different for lots of people.
But I usually make 40 minutes.
And 40 minutes seems to be right for most of the people who listen to my...
To my program.
There is a duration time.
I sometimes want to go on a club at the comedy store.
And if the show starts at nine and you're 11 people have been there for so many hours,
there's a point where how long can you laugh?
I mean, how long can you eat and how long can you have sex?
It's just like a point where you say, like, you know, I've really been laughing.
One of the time I want to check out laughing.
And my cheekbones are...
And the computers, the memory, you know, that's limited.
But I think with the human mind, I don't think pass you.
You could like, fill it all up and then you say, oh, yeah, and bring some salt.
You can put a disk as full.
You can't see anything.
No, I can't see anything.
I've always kept it.
I got to let you remember.
Oh, bring some salt.
That's not a problem.
I got it.
I got that extra gigabyte.
That's not what it is with Haral Bluton.
The big untap resource.
All right, man.
Listen, it's almost midnight.
So...
Well, this went for the test.
That was how long was this podcast?
This is 43 minutes.
Wow.
See?
I didn't even...
I didn't even look at the time.
Well, a 40 is often associated with waiting.
The word quarantine, which comes from the Rippler 40,
waiting for days, Moses, the desert 40 years ago.
No, not 40 days and 40 nights.
Right.
It begins at 40.
See, this is what I like about you.
The most is you have this incredible amount of historical knowledge.
You know, it's like a huge skewer data.
But I can bring it up at the right time.
It's like I got that with song lyrics.
Yeah.
It's like, you know, a snoop, but with a collar.
But that's cool.
You know, that's a very good point though, 40, 40 being another magical number.
There are magical.
But it's numbers are associated off and with, with constructs or events.
And, you know, prime numbers.
But prime numbers.
That's another podcast.
Yes.
And, um, I look forward to, uh, to casting my own pod upon this room.
Well, um, we're going to hook you up.
Um, I'm glad.
And I, uh, I thank you for this opportunity.
And I just like to say to all the creatures in the jelly room.
You can leave now.
The jelly people went away.
I think that means you should turn off the machine.
And we can return the jelly monkeys to the slippery dreams.
Fantastic.
Well, there you go.
That's, uh, Charles Flasher, uh, recorded, um, at the, uh, at the, uh, the heck is the name of this place that we're at?
Where are we at?
On?
Yeah.
What's the name of the hotel?
Can you ask me?
Yeah.
Look, quick.
I got, like, 45 more seconds.
What's the name of the hotel?
It's a, it's, uh, thank you.
The, in that Spanish bay, Pebble Beach.
I should have known.
So, um, that's it.
We're, uh, we have a couple more sessions this morning.
Hope you enjoyed this, by the way, Charles Flasher.
Um, as you can tell, he's a guy who I think will be, uh, great to bring in the podcasting.
So, uh, tremendous success for Pod Show here.
And, um, uh, and over the, more of a day we can Patricia and I will, uh, of course, do some more world tour segments, right, huh?
Absolutely.
Okay. And now we're off to breakfast.
So, thank you all very much.
If you're listening to serious stars 102, uh, Pacific Coast.
Hellway is next.
And, as I said, uh, even though it's, uh, it's a holiday Monday.
We'll have a show for you.
So, take care.
Have a great weekend.
Drive safe.
And if you're driving, remember to, uh, take the keys.
Bye-bye.
Get this podcast and more great ones like it.
On the high performance podcast delivery network from Pod Show and Lime Light Networks.
I love it.