Delta Sierra Charlie 3-4-9er
Hey Adam, this is Richard Hull. Don't forget to turn off that black pre-before-start recording today. Bye for now.
She sat, she sat, she sat, she sat, she sat, she sat, my girl got it so long.
There's never been simple air, there's never been short content.
Won't help me see bad night, no, no, no, no.
She sat, she sat, she sat, she sat, she sat, she sat, she sat, she sat, my girl got it so long.
The neighbor's been, I've seen her watching you, I've seen those bolder fingers twitching in that net.
There's never been no, no, no, no.
Ain't you still yet?
Oh, huh.
He used to days, he sideways.
He threatened me of all gone.
I'm not disding, he was so low.
Now who is it gonna come in?
He sat, she sat, and she sat, she sat.
She sat, she sat, I don't get what she said.
There's never been a wrong way
There are no easy answers
I don't make my own mistakes
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
He used to take things away
He said, you tricked me of alcohol
I've decided so well
Now prison from here
He used to take things away
He said, you tricked me of alcohol
I've decided so well
Now prison from here
He said, you tricked me of alcohol
It's too late, it's all the way, it's late
It's with me, I'm alone, I'm a city, I saw the world
It's now a reason for everything, I'm a real just for it
I'm a real just for it, I'm a real just for it
Hey!
Oh, a gravity, risen from the Podship Music Network
Everybody how you doing welcome to the
Early source code coming to you once again from the
Curry Cottage in the Fabulous UK
You know, I've noticed a lot of commenters lately have been from the UK
This, um, hey gravity is also from the UK
What are they?
A two-girl three-boy dynamic UK-based guitar band
Fronted by Electric Shomtoos singer Justin Barry
Very cool, check it out at music.podshow.com
What is it?
I don't know
I've all kinds of sound issues here today
Sometimes I just wonder if it's my head if it's my brain or my ears or whatever it is
Not a nice day today
It's raining
Yeah, just, you know, nasties, pouring down rain, dark outside
Not really good other than to sit inside and record a podcast
And man, I've been so busy doing things
Oh, um, also a video music cast coming up
I think I'll put one together today
I've been receiving material from all around the world
Looking for great music videos
Podsafe, of course
I've received play that aren't podsafe
And also some fun things I'm going to stick in there
So be on the lookout for that to show up in your aggregator and your pod catcher and your iTunes
Or whatever you may be using
Go to dailysourceco.com
And click on the link for, you know, it says direct link to show
Just click on it starts playing, so it's a beautiful thing
Uh, let me see
Let's start off with
This is the first complaint I've actually heard
About the use of the word the Charlie for the source code
Of course the genesis of this is the daily source code
Uh, I started tagging my podcast, which makes it much much easier for people listening on iPods
And especially not even iPods
Um, on devices that don't even have a display or a proper display or if you're driving
And you just, you know, hit the play button
And you can hear exactly what show it is
And you kind of remember which show you listened to last
And that became a bit tiresome
So I changed it to DSC and then I changed it to Delta Sierra Charlie
And um, I didn't come up with this Charlie thing
And someone actually called it Cha Cha the other day, which is quite frightening
Uh, Mr. Carcran has other thoughts about that
Hi Adam Chris Carcran here from the car cast
Just wanted to send you a little piece of feedback
And ask you a question
And I've never asked you to change anything about your show
I would not even pretend to know as much about programming a podcast as you do
But I gotta make this request
Lately, you and your listeners have started calling the daily source code the Charlie
Just wanted to maybe we could stop using the phrase the Charlie
And the reason is as I'm a 32 year old man
I've been in broadcasting for 10 years
Now I'm doing podcasting exclusively
And uh, I'm
No pansy
But
As a child
My mom used the word Charlie for something other than someone's name
In fact
That's a nickname my mom gave a male penis
If a time I was a little kid until probably about the fourth grade
All I knew I never knew the word penis
Hold on, did you say male penis?
As opposed to female
Female penis?
We just called it a Charlie
So you can imagine the way that I feel and the
Repulsion I feel every time I hear someone say
Talk to you on the Charlie
Or
I heard on the Charlie
Catch you on the Charlie
I just I can't do it anymore
So just wondering is a suggestion
And if you say no I'll understand of course I'll keep listening
But I'm sorry to go that out to you
Thanks for doing what you do and of course if you're listeners want to check us out
They can't at thecarcast.com
Or they can search out an iTunes
Just search for the carcast
Thanks Adam and talk to you soon
Yo dude
So that's kind of weird
I'm older than you are
Almost ten years older than you are
And I grew up my parents are really specific you know
It's a penis. It's a vagina
And this is what it's called you know like an arm or a leg or whatever
This is oh this pure I presume you're from the US
Very pure a technical
I oh I despise that so much
You know not calling things by the proper name
Your PP your thing your wing
It's just a penis and by the way
I'm very proud of my penis
I like my penis
How can you be freaked out when someone talks about penis?
Come on man, it's been there for a number of years
And I've kind of figured out how to use it
And I'm getting pretty good at that actually
So so Patricia tells me I'm improving
But no no no please parents
Just call it by its proper name
My gosh, you know they'll learn how to what other names are easier and sound better later on in life
But come on tell them what it's for tell them what it does tell them what it's called
And I appreciate the feedback
But that's just not enough to change the change
Using the phrase to Charlie
The pod show podcast network is really coming together
We have a whole bunch of beta tester podcasters
Who are actually using the system in two parts
They're using the the upload functionality
And our de-gap dynamically generated audio placement system
For their uploads most of them are using their own wordpress web logs or wordpress web logs that we've set up
Which of course will not be the final solution we have a whole show site that is automatically created
And adapted with every single upload
It's become very very easy and had a brief email exchange with cast blaster mic this morning
Looks like we're down to the wire here on integrating cast blaster
Which is the program I'm using
You can find that at castblaster.com
It's really really really simple
And when it integrates with the PDN, yesterday by the way
You might have seen a really strange URL for the
For the Charlie
On 348
That was because I tested the de-gap and PDN system myself yesterday for the first time
And it held together
I did get some one piece of feedback about something in the ID three tags being wrong
I'm not quite sure what that was about but I'm getting screenshots
And we'll have more feedback on ID three tags later on in today's source code
But what's really cool is we have a number of people
Predominantly I'd have to say Richard Brue were hey
Who really does all of the he manages all the relationships with the podcasters
And you know and delegate stuff for escalate stuff
Whatever has to be done
But he's really the main point of contact
He's doing it such a great job and you can see how
And they have wiki set up and mailing list and god
I don't know all kinds of stuff
And people start to communicate and figuring out how to get stuff across the network
We're learning how to schedule things and Jay Donnelly is one of these guys
Who really gets it and he's doing some incredible stuff
Since he joined the net actually's been doing lots of incredible stuff
But since he joined the network he's coming up with more and more
Including some very interesting
Super celebrity interviews
And that was a cue to start
There we go
Hey this is Jay Donnelly from madpod.com
And on this week show we have an exclusive interview with Thomas Dolby
Shadow has an exclusive interview with the man blinded by science
And he talks about the future is podcasting
Thomas what's your take on top 40 radio these days
Compared with 20 years ago
I don't listen to top 40 radio these days
So I'm really not qualified to answer that
But it doesn't really appeal to me
You know I don't listen to very much of it
Occasionally I hear a hit that I like
Occasionally I'll focus on just one piece of a song
You know like I don't know
Personally that's not where I look for inspiration
I look for inspiration on the satellite radio now
Which I think is much more varied
On internet radio stations and podcasting
What it becomes a collective program from Santa Monica
I'll podcast that and take it to the gym with me
So you know I tend to reach a little bit further in
than standard top 40 radio
20 years ago I wouldn't say you know radio had a white night
I'd say that already radio was in a state where
You know computer generated playlists were starting to dominate
You know it was all about keeping up with the front runners
It was all about the the ads and the rotation and so on
DJs were not really choosing their own songs
You didn't get a sense of you know a single guiding intelligence behind the playlists
It felt like big corporations were already involved
I know a lot of people complain about how it's become consolidated
You know by a few big companies now
And that's certainly I don't think it's a good thing for radio
You're global audio internet connection
J. A. Domali and Shadows to you
Mad
Don't get mad
Get media
Mad
Coming up this weekend on madpot.com
Yo excellente
It was something else that was going to happen today
What the hell was it?
I was um as I was playing that
J. Domali clip I was thinking
I've been sleeping really really deeply
Maybe that's it
Maybe I'm not awake yet. It'll come to me. I'm sure
Um more pod save music on the way in today's show
And quite an interesting conversation about ID three tags that we started
Just the other day
Predominantly as it pertains to the pod save music network
And I just want to reiterate the pod save music network is a network
It's not a store. It's not necessarily a website
It's a network where people come together
Where they contribute where they you know contribute karma
They take away karma. They report back karma
Um and you know and this is really intended because it doesn't make sense to have
A real central resource because we have that
You know it's called iTunes and and and all that stuff
You know you get what you want
Um and they have tons of people working on that
Well tons I mean I think the iTunes team of course by you know
Relatively speaking is small but still you have to have four or five people
Working on stuff and making sure everything you know works perfectly
And that would either mean tremendous scale to be able to afford it
Um or price fixing which is another thing that is being talked about quite a bit
lately
Um
Well let's see what this particular piece of feedback is about because it does pertain to all of us
Whether you're a listener, a podcaster or an independent artist who wants to contribute to the network
Hey Adam Dave Jacobs from the rock and roll Jew show, rock and roll, Jew.com
I want to disagree with you on the ID3 tags and the pod save music network deal
Uh as a music podcaster I also have had frustrations in downloading tracks
Not just from pod save music network but all kinds of other places on the net
And they sometimes will come down with no MP3 tags or really messed up MP3 tags
It really does make things a lot more difficult for the podcaster
And I can imagine for the music producer as well
Who's even less forgiving than a podcaster
Now you can say hey you know this is the store
It's up to the bands and if it's all messed up
People just won't buy from those bands anymore
Unfortunately I think if you really step back and look at it from a customer perspective
That's just not what they're going to think
The customer really doesn't know nor do they care that it's up to the bands do this
And is not pod shows responsibility
They don't know nor do they care that you're not trying to run a store
All they know is hey there's cool music on this thing and I want to buy it
And when I buy it I want to get it and when I get it I want it to be right
Period and if it's not right again
They don't know who's in charge
They're just going to come straight back to you
And that's going to be a real problem for pod show
When people download music and something's not right with it
They're going to come straight back to you
They're not going to go to the band and say hey I download one of your tracks
And it's all messed up
No they're going to come straight back to the pod and say
Music network owner because you are you know the face of the whole thing
So I think you really have to think about it from that perspective
And realize that you might end up with a big customer service problem
Whether you like it or not because in the mind of the consumer
That's just the way they're going to approach this
Even though you might like it to be somewhat different
So I don't know what the solution is
I'm sure there's some sort of a technology thing that can be worked to make it better
And I will as a podcaster and music consumer put the shout out to all bands
Hey guys
Really be careful with your MP3 tags
Take the time to do it right and make sure that it's good
Because when people download this stuff you want it to be right
It just makes for a better experience for everybody
And that's it
Talk to you later
Bye bye
Well I'm going to respectfully disagree with you
They are first of all you're talking about customers
These are not pod shows customers
These are customers of the bands
Okay
So you know if we're going to provide customer service
Well then we have to stand for some form of service
The show was really trying to be a resource in this by providing the resources to pull it all together
And have a central place where commerce can take place
But also people should be able to get in contact with the bands
That's all coming it as we revamp the pod state music network
It's all part of the grand master plan
Oh I remember today when's that?
Yes, I do remember
I believe today Rob Wall should podcast 411
Has an interview with myself Ron Bloom and Bill Reinhard from
Limelight networks we're talking about the pdn
So make sure you check that out
I haven't seen it show up yet
But I believe it's today it's being released
So back to this
And also I don't believe that people by the way
If people do all of a sudden just start showing up
At the pod save music network and saying
Unlistening and you know cruising through songs
And listening to them and saying here something cool all by it
I would be surprised
And if we get to that point where people come in
Drows will then we will have to rethink the strategy perhaps
Or work with the other partners which are podcasters
And are independent artists
On coming up with better solutions
But for my money
I see every single independent artist or band
As their own mini corporation
And they don't need a record company for promotion
Or for support
Because you know it's pretty
Cost effective these days to record your own music
And the only people really involved are the the listen of the podcaster
And the artists but they are working together
What's been happening so far is
People here are song on a podcast
They go to show notes or they go directly to the pod save music network
Sometimes directly to the artist's site
It's all good to me
And that's where they should be able to find out more information
Now as a corporation
It is the responsibility of the person
Actually pod show is not selling anything
The artists are selling this
We're just making it all possible
And by keeping the overhead as low as possible
Right now as you know as we enter into our beta period
And a couple of songs are available on the network
We're not taking any cut
It's a nine cents that goes to our partner
For doing the transaction
And the rest goes directly to the artist
And in the future we want to split that up
As the unlabel concept starts to expand
And snap together
Once we have those freaking emails worked out
So we can actually sign people up properly
We're getting very close
Once we have that done
Then
I lost my train of thought
Screw it
My point is it is up to the band
Or the artist
They are responsible for that
Now there are some things we couldn't put
We can put in place that I thought of
While listening to your comment before I start to do the show today
One is of course
When you upload something
And I don't have an artist account
So I actually have to check into this
The first thing that we can have is all kinds of flags
And warnings that say please enter your ID
Three information is important
Then we could have a version of
I guess we could have some kind of checker
That once a file is uploaded it checks for ID
Three tags
But maybe the best way to do this
Is something like the CD database
I've always loved that concept
And I'm sure it still exists
And maybe we can tie into it
Or let's just create our own for pod safe music
And if you've ever seen how that works
If you go to burn a CD
Or use to work this way
Or not burn if you want to rip a CD
Is it just rip?
Yeah, then you'd insert the CD
Your program would go out to the CD database
See if there's already an entry for it
Because they're all marked specifically
If there's not an entry for it
Then you're asked to enter the tracks
And information yourself
And then I think it looks at
Three or four different entries before
It makes a final entry and it locks it down
And that's it
So we could do something like that
Which would then reverse
Engineer the ID three tags back into it
I still think it comes down to the artists
Having to do that if they're serious about their art
And selling it or distributing it
Then they're going to have to
You know, they're going to have to do some extra work
And it's not all that much work
It's just, you know, people don't realize
And it's so awareness is the main thing that we can take care of
But again, not a store, not into customer service
And we already have plenty of customer service
And we're dealing with
With the staff that we have available
Jonathan Quirk
Sent an interesting email
Understand the radio station consoles
Often have a cough button that mutes the microphone
For as long as it's pressed
Yeah, that's pretty traditional
Given your frequent gastious emissions that you blame on the coffee
Perhaps casplaster might could add a
Senseo button to casplaster
This would spare our ears from what is becoming
Tiresome with repetition
Rather than dead air resulting from its use
Maybe it would pause the recording momentarily
Or it could mute the mic and insert the words
And say when you're best speaking voice
Well, saving us from another bell
Well, a casplaster actually has that
It's called pause and it's called talk
You couldn't click either button off if you want
But I think you what you want is you want it on the listener side
You want some kind of warning when it's coming up
So that you don't have to listen to it
No, that is not one of the features planned on the
The final release candidate of casplaster
Which is coming up
We're just about to release one point out
We'll just about casplaster mic and I
And I'm not talking about it
It's what do you up to beta 61 and beta 61 which isn't out yet
Mike has done something incredible
He really went the extra mile and I appreciate it
And I'm sure the droves of
Other people are going to appreciate it
Because he he started to work on the accessibility
And we've talked about this many times before
But blind the blind community
Has problems with lots of websites
That there's screen readers can't follow
We have plenty of issues with that
And you know and I have committed to working on that
As soon as we get some of the basic stuff out
And rolling we're going to be doing some work in that area
And proof of that is Mike who is made casplaster
Accessible
Now I believe that it's already accessible
You know the all the play buttons and everything
We'll respond in the was it jaws or whatever other screen reader
A blind person can use
But the problem has always been the levels, the meter
So I have a visual feedback here
Which is basically like two LED meters
That are yellow and then they go into green
And then they go into red if you're over modulating
And he sent me a little clip yesterday
Which I don't know if he'd want me to play that
In fact most of it's in Dutch
But it's really cool you can set it up
So that if you start to hit the peak limit the peak volume
You get a little
Audio feedback in your headphones
Which will only be in your headphones
So it isn't actually recorded on the show
So then you know you have to pull back your volume
A little bit which is just fantastic
And I think that we could have all kinds of audio cues
Going on to be very, very cool
So look forward to that
I believe that's coming out in version 61
Hey Adam it's Heather from Ruby Food Radio
Where it's all girls all the time
And I've been listening to everybody
Gush about Laura Clap over the course of the past couple of episodes of the DSC
And I'm really glad she's finally getting some attention
Because she's an amazing talent and she really deserves all the accolades that she's getting
And women don't seem to be getting much attention in the podcasting world
But hopefully that's going to change soon
I for one I'm trying to do my part
So if you want to hear other great female artists like Laura check out my show
Ruby Food Radio at RubyFruitRadio.com
I am subscribed more chicks in podcasting
Love it
If you're checking out this podcast on serious stars
The pod show podcast line up coming up
We have Pacific Coast Hellway
Then a full hour of yeast radio
Don and Drew go more daily after that
Then Brian know with the Frank Truth
And we wind it up with the Michael Butler within half hour of the best in pod safe music
And I'll be back here tomorrow for the Thursday edition
The satellite window is closing
Wave goodbye to our friends at Sirius
And it's just us here back together
This is great emails
Dave
I won't tell you where Dave is from you'll find out
Well I guess I can he's from the poop report
Hey Adam with Chris Rockwell obviously suffering the world's worst case of constipation
That means he hasn't done a daily download in months
I turn to you
poop for peace day is coming on April 14th
Without Chris you are my conduit to the podcasting world
And thus humanities greatest hope
The message of poop for peace day is simple
Republican or Democrat
I really need some some music for this
Well I'll just give it a little echo
The message of poop for peace day is simple
Republican or Democrat black or white
Man or woman Christian
We all suffer equally under the tyranny of the bowel
pooping is the only point of commonality
All human beings face and as such
It can be the basis for world peace
So if you want to know more
Go to poop report dot com slash piece to get information sign up for an email reminder
And download banners and posters
You know strange things have happened
Some have changed the world by sitting in the back of the bus
And some could change to
Oh man
And some can change the world just by sitting on the throne
Comics trip
Oh man it just gets better
I don't know if he's going to send in a comment every day he keeps threatening not to
But then he keeps sending in fantastic audio comments ladies and gentlemen
It is not mad wine scene
This is a real person a real
I'd have to say fan of the show
There's no other reason why it'd be so
Intricately involved
Yesterday asked our friend comic strip blogger
What his talents are what he can do
You know what are his skills
And maybe we can work with him in that regard
You know I always see the positive in people and
Comics are bloggers been
He wants me to use the word candid
But I would say in some ways abusive
Certainly of the English language
In the comments at curry.com
Which regard the daily source code
And I asked him to let me know
You know what he does he certainly seems to have a lot of time on his hands
And here's his response
I don't carry my skills
I don't want that to know
Frisky you are
Well no point in elaborating on that I see
Because I am not your whole
I repeat
I am not your whole
So unless you seriously
Want to hire me at Potshore Inc
Stop being so curious for a fact's sake
Generally
I have impression that you are one of those gazes
Who like to play
Unsuriously with people
Like cats play with mice
Show me wrong
And agree on granting me in person
And interview mainly about mobile phones
And then I will tell you my skillset
The other shit
Why?
I should give you information
If you don't want to give me an interview
Cut the crap alright
You have your head stuck up your ass
Adam curry
So let's change topic
For me to poop on
Take a cue there
From...
Was it the insult comic dog?
No no no comic street blogger
I'm sorry
It works the other way around
You want the interview
You got to do something for me first
So tell us a little bit about you
And you know
You can send in your questions
I'll answer them
I love mobile phones
That's all I have to say about the topic
But we still love to know more about what you're about
And what makes you taken
What you can do
And how we could put you to good use
Comic street blogger
That's really what we want
Hi there
I'm Doug Rhapson
The host of geek acres
It's a weekly podcast
About
Well
Geek stuff
The internet science fiction
And other good stuff
Hmm
That's not a particularly good description
Maybe I could get someone to help explain it
Oh
There's my friend Kelly
Hey
Kelly Lewis
How would you explain my podcast
Geek acres
It's about three generations of women
And their lives
And it's very very witty
And the characters talk very very fast
Um
Okay
Yeah
Thanks
Maybe we need to dive into this
Um
Oh
There's Steve Ealy
He knows about podcasts
Steve
How would you say that Geek acres has changed the potosphere
I believe that we live in an era
Where anything that can be expressed as bits will be
I believe that bits exist to be copied
That's
Deep
Are you getting a sense of the show yet?
It's video games
A generation of women
And some bits
Anything we've missed even
Speaks on a mobile
Play
Yeah
That too
Look, he'll just have to check it out
Geek acres
The weekly podcast
Available at geekakers.com
Or via iTunes
Hey Adam
It's Adam here
Where are doing the course on podcasts
I'm podcasting.au
We're just listening to the childy episode
Three, four, two
About people ripping off your flicker images
Oh man
That was such a real bummer
What he did extremely bad
Good luck with the core case
And I hope it's got news
If you want to see our flicker images
Go to the tax schoolworks
All on word
Or go to podcasting.au
All right, fun to visit
I'm before I say in Patrick's day trying
Podcasting.au
And if you're coming
Bring me something for this
Yeah
Influencing children all over the world
Very proud of the job I'm doing
That's podcasting.au
By the way
A bunch of kids who are doing some podcasting
It's great
Check them out podcasting.au
Let's get back into that
Multi-teared internet thing
Because a lot of confusion about
The two issues at hand
One is email
ISPs
Where you get an email address
Filtering out all kinds of email
Which actually you want to receive
And basically
Charging for email
That you may not want to receive
And then of course
There's the AT&T
Controversy
I love seeing that word
The AT&T Controversy
They're saying that they want to charge
Services like Google
Like Yahoo
I'm sure eventually
Potcho too
And if you start a business
They'll charge you too
Just like they're
You know they're
Calling our email spam now
The same will happen
And people I just get tons of email
The people are saying
Oh, now I finally get it
You know I wasn't getting
Registration emails through
So here's where it gets a bit
Confusing
Myo Yard Enough
So to add them
Listening to Charlie 248
I think 348
Not so easy to get around
Large ISPs like AT&T
Bill South or even AOL
See you may reject them as your ISPs
So that you vote with your money
Which is what I said yesterday
As you know if you have if you're
With an ISP that is charging money
To receive email
Then you may want to consider
Taking your money elsewhere
However that's not so easy
You see AT&T and others own large
Backbones that are throughout the whole
Continent and that smaller
Broadband ISPs rely on
You may be choosing your own smaller
Small ISPs but because they rely on
Large ISPs to serve their customers
Voting with your money becomes irrelevant
As AT&T will be taxing your small ISPs
Instead of you, AT&T doesn't care who they tax
And the small ISPs will increase their prices
To cope with so that you get hit
Anyway
Just some food for thought
Agree something has to be done about it
Tearing the network is ridiculous
Enjoy Myo
Okay, so a couple things here
First of all, service is like Google
And also the Pod Show PDM
Doesn't work
It's not like we got out
We went out and bought three gigabits worth of bandwidth
That is the model that I believe will not scale
For the type of media that we're looking at
In fact, I've been sitting here watching
A show download from Potomatic.com
I have no idea if it's their bandwidth
Or what it is but it's just been grinding away
For an hour trying to download one podcast
They're whole site of slow
This is because
This is huge data
This is just unbelievable
If you take all these podcasts, the size of the files
And the number of people that are downloading
Companies like Google and Pot Show as well
We have either directly or indirectly
If peering agreements
So we sit actually at a different place
Where we connect to backbones like AT&T
And there's no money changing hands and no taxation
It's really okay, you're going to give me this bandwidth
I'm going to pass off this much to you
It's kind of equal so we call it a peering agreement
Because we're peers
So no money actually changes hands at that point
This is down at the consumer end
Which is a lot more interesting
Because you have basically paid for your eight megabits per second
And they're going to tax that
A little bit further up the pipeline
You know as to what comes in
So it could indeed affect your ISP
But I think most ISPs
Have similar type of arrangements
Peering agreements the larger ones
Not everyone has to participate in this multi-tiered system
As it pertains to email
I don't think that
Any backbone provider will filter the email
This is the ISPs services themselves
Who are of course performing a great service
By filtering out all the spam that you don't want
But I believe we're performing a true disservice
If they charge companies for sending email for guaranteed delivery
That was not the intent of email
Not the way it was supposed to be set up
And it's just a bad idea
Hi Adam, it's Barry Reiketer at thickandblock.com
Catching a couple of DSC's lately
Sorry the Charlie
Notice one of my co-workers Matt Snaggress
Posted audio feedback
Well it turns out
I RIT department should be writing you a check
Because I only found out that I was missing out on some pod show emails
Because they were getting trapped in our spam filter
So went back and looked and sure enough there was some emails from you
Which brings us to another subject
I know this has been a big subject on the Charlie for the last couple episodes
I managed to catch an episode of this week in tech
And they were talking about it too
But the idea about this couple of things on spam
And certified emails and AOL charging
This whole issue can be really resolved with something that you
You mentioned a few episodes ago
Which is you know RSS
I mean it's a solution
Why you know I know you mentioned
Not wanting to talk about technology on the show
But it's just so brain dead easy to have an RSS reader
And subscribe to feeds of things
Instead of jamming up people's email boxes
It'll be guaranteed you'll get more data probably
That people are looking at it
Because you can go back to web server logs
Or a advertiser or a content publisher
Corporations should use it internally
You could have the HR channel
You could have the facilities, the parking lot channel
You could even have that there's leftover pizza in the kitchen channel
So I mean RSS seems like the solution
I wonder why more corporations and publishers and marketers aren't adopting it
Because that seems to be the way to go
Anyway Adam, that's my rant
Thanks for listening and keep up the great work
Love the new long format shows
Hope you keep those up too
Thanks a lot
I really appreciate the feedback that these two guys are giving me
Because they're actually in a way
They're customers of pod show
But they're very, very on the ball
These guys from the advertising and marketing community
And they are really all over this stuff
And so first of all I appreciate that
Second of all you have course RSS is going to be great
You know, I think we still need better aggregators, better news readers
Anxiously awaiting the arrival of Windows Vista
Which will have an RSS engine built inside
That all kinds of new applications will be able to be built on
And of course that's where we can start to integrate
RSS delivery
That you can integrate right into
I guess right into an email client if you will
It could look like email except you could actually have a little button
I don't receive email from this person anymore
Actually, I just had an interesting idea
So what if we had some kind of interim gateway
Let's just say it's on your computer right?
And email comes in
And let's just say it's completely
Oh man that's going to be so tough
Hmm
Maybe you can set up a channel so that if I sent you an email
It would be from Atomacrui.com
And that would you say okay turn this into a channel
Which means guaranteed delivery to you
And it would show up just like regular email
And of course on the other side
I mean this is all under the hood stuff
So no one would ever have to see this
I think the only additional thing is
A button in your email client that says
And forget how we do it under the hood RSS
I think is probably perfect
But let's just forget that
Let's just say you had one extra piece of functionality
That showed up in all email clients
And that was
No longer receive email from
Let's not call it spam
Let's just say no longer receive email from
This person or this entity
Or definitely you know always receive email from this person or entity
Maybe maybe that would work
But the real problem comes down to the registration emails
When you're making that first initial contact
So I have Joan Kelly who writes in
Hey Adam I'm a lady listener from Australia
Ah
It's the Sheila
We call you Sheila's down under
Firstly thanks so much for the Charlie
The Charlie
I love your show
You are such a pal from me to listen to
During my driving time or other times when my ears are free
You are an inspiration with lots of creative energy
Good great communication
Believe you said a good example
Okay, that's all I thank you very much
A refreshing change from the pathetic siege
Mentality of big business and it's death throws
This crazy stuff of emails not getting through
When people try to reach their customers
Is legitimate transactions
Just makes me so cross
I did experience that problem when registering
On the positive music network to make a test purchase
Finally I realized lots of mail went a stray from various podcasts
Or when I tried to register or obtain logins or something
Including even the Don and Drew Show and many many others
They probably thought their listeners were either
Giving bogus email addresses or letting their replies
Or letting their replies get lost in a junk mail folders
See this is not just pod show
It's all kinds of emails and registration
Things that are going back and forth
These really big these really
But really these idiot big email companies
Are vandalizing the email process
It was well known that hotmail block Gmail invitations
I didn't actually know that how lame is that
Oh
But I presume they were just
Singling them out to hurt email competition
I think that's really wrong by the way
I have used my noxious little hotmail account for situations
Where I may be allowing my address to get into the wild
But now I realize that all
A hotmail account is good for is for collecting spam
The legitimate mail often can't even get through the junk folder
Spam starts before you even open your hotmail account
Of course since every possible address seems to be already on
The spam or list
Getting to the point at last
I realize I must be kinder to genuine organizations
Or sites that I communicate with
Especially if an automated reply or applying bulk may be involved
And give them the address from my own mail server
So they can reach me without some poor guy having to manually
Resend a password to log in thinking to me
Interesting that's such individual manually operated
Generated messages from PMN do arrive but not the automated ones
Okay, so first of all
Yeah, that's true
Both Chris Rockwell and Chris McIntyre
Rockwell for pod sake music network and McIntyre for pod cast
Ali actually do I think combine the probably about 100 emails a day
They were approving manually and sending out
I guess from different email accounts or something that does work and does get through
And that's a huge burden
I mean may seem pretty easy but it's not
You know this stuff is supposed to be automatic
It's supposed to get there automatic
So but I just had another idea about this because of course
The ultimate solution is to run your own email service
Now this is where it gets kind of kind of funky
But wouldn't it be great
God do you remember the cube
Which I who made the cube
It was bought by Sun Microsystems at one point but the cube was a beautiful box
It was this actually very aesthetically pleasing in a kind of 80s kind of way to look at server
And you literally just you could hook it up to your cable mode or your ADSL
And it had everything built in
It had your own little internet, a place free to store files
You could mount folders and just it was basically a server
But it also had an email server built in
And a couple other
You know a couple other really nice features
And I don't know if they discontinued
Work on that or not but of course these days it would be a box that would have Wi-Fi built in
Let's say we could really
We could really get that down to something quite cost effective
And it probably shouldn't even have Wi-Fi
Just stick it into your cable mode
And it'll basically just appear
I think we have enough open source
And it ran on Linux of course
I think we have enough open source technology to make that a pretty seamless operation
So what if we just instead of calling it an email service or just called it
You know the ultimate
Well we'll have to work on the messaging and the marketing
But the whole point is you would have control over what is spam and what is not spam
And even if something got caught in spam you could still go back
Into your own
Server and you could fix that now
Doesn't sound like something that consumers would want to get into
What if it was just seamless what if
By the way Gmail a Google thought for you guys Jesus
I would buy this in a heartbeat
So I could have unlimited storage all my stuff would be secure where I wanted
It would be accessible all over the internet
Presumably of course because if your home connection goes down
But that's gotten so much better over the years
I think that'll probably survive
And you could have all the functionality you wanted
You could have webmail
It could be completely secure
You couldn't let anything through that you want
You could of course could have set up your own RSS versions of email
That may be a way to go that would be a really nice consumer device
Just a small thing plugs in call the ultimate email manager or spam
Whatever you want to call it just so that people understand what it does
And we could solve a lot of those problems just a thought just a thought
Let's see a couple more things before I go today
And I have another pod state music song especially for the Wednesday
I had him this is CQ I just thought I could give you some quick audio feedback on Charles 346
Charles
Roger Smalls left you a note about going to the park and not being able to chase
Follow women or pick flowers because it's a public park
You know as you well know there are many
Public schools in the UK
Those are privately educating children
And therefore that is parents are paying for that education
So it's another use of the word public meaning private in fact
And therefore having to be paid for independently
Just thought I was an interesting thing
The other thing you might want to check out is my website which is www.goct.com
For slash I hate Adam Curry
Don't have a chance
I wasted my time going to that URL
Now you know what that's interesting you should have told me this before the before I went to court
Because it is true in the UK a public school is what we in the US would call a private school
Once again
Someone sent me in the correction this one nation divided by a common language
You say tomato I say tomato tomorrow
Tomorrow by the way is the judgment
I'm nervous I gotta tell you I'm really nervous about what's going to come out of all this stuff
I really well
I'm quite sure the judge is going to rule in favor of violating the creative comments copyright
Again it all boils down to what kind of message is the judge going to send
You know the Netherlands seems to be very interesting country these days
There seems to be quite a lack of regard for individual copyright and intellectual property
Looking at their ASCAP VMI over there the Buma Stemera
And the Taiscopi Reicht and all these guys who are just hoarding money
Investing it
Investing other people's money losing that money
And then just polishing that away on the final year end results balance sheet
Not good so I think a message has to be sent about the value of intellectual property
Because it does work both ways if I steal a 99 cent song
I can get a hundred and fifty thousand dollars lawsuit slapped against me
If I what if I just post it some pictures from playboy magazine
Yeah, I've been through all that crap before so tomorrow we'll hear about it
Some other great news
I've got a fantastic lead on a safety pilot Captain Dan
Who actually flies out of echo golf tango fox trot fair oaks airfield
Which is where Delta Shiro will be parked starting the end of this month
And so we've had some email back and forth and really really hoping that that we can get that together
Be so cool to have a local person doing that
But still if you have any any ideas about someone who could fly as safety pilot with me
You know most then weekend sometimes in overnight
It's a paid gig of course and the more experience the better obviously
I just you know yes, I talked briefly about the Academy Awards
I was so proud I forgot to tell you this the movie Capote
Was directed by a guy named Bennett Miller and I know Bennett not very well
I know his brother extremely well JB Miller
Who used to work at MTV in the town department in fact he was the guy that the first person I saw in Patricia
And I walked off the airplane at JFK when we came to the states and I came to work for MTV and we started our new life
He was there to pick us up JB Miller just an incredibly smart guy
He now has a company called Empire Entertainment and he produces huge shows for corporations with major major stars
And I remember it was a couple years ago
And that I was at JB's apartment and his brother was actually I don't know if he was living there at the time
But he had an avid editing suite set up in the apartment and he was running around
And then it's very very creative they're both these guys both you know
They're on the edge of brilliant and loony and it was it was so incredibly intense
And he was doing a movie at the time called
Was it not rush
Oh stupid of me it was about a tour on one of those London double deckers and downtown Manhattan
And they were editing it and you know Drew Barrymore was in and out of the apartment
It was just an incredibly weird scene
But you know a very creative and artistic scene
I just wanted to say I'm so incredibly proud of the work that Bennett has done
And how far he's come in such a short amount of time and I haven't seen the movie yet
But I do intend on seeing it it looks absolutely fantastic
And so props to him I mean out of the gate
So it's his second feature the first one that was a real full blown
Why the distributed feature to be nominated for best director is is just fantastic
I still don't have to see all that shit on television because I really don't care anymore about the award ceremonies
But I got to say men props to you for sure
So more props going out to the palm cast member pum pum pum
The French podcaster who quit his day job to podcast full time
Well congratulations to him and his wife
There baby girl arrived her name is night night eely
There you go night eely
And so we have another podcast listener on the scene
Now only what is it?
99,999,999 to go and then we're at 100 million mark
All right, winding it up for today
This is a song that I've actually played before on a Wednesdays
Kind of fitting for your Wednesday morning vibe as we roll the Charlie outs for another episode
Free judgment day
I stepped out of my doorstep
We in stem on in look real fun
Took a glance at my wrist wall
Getting in my rhythm time
Let my little girl sitting pretty in the bed
It's just my arms I touched the sky
Time to clear my weary fear
In stem on in
Take my blues away
It means they're morning
It's gonna be a part of day
It's come so many times before
I used to cry when I put my life
But I'm not going too many times
With a miss Johnson
It's our school boys skipping by
Took a dome to my head
What a thing
What a high
Let my hands kick to my feet
Dance around the y'all so sweet
A listen to the bird is seen
The music was a treat
When it's dead body
Take my blues away
It's gonna be a part of day
It's come so many times before
I used to cry when I put my life
But I'm not going too many times before
I'm not going too many times
I used to cry when I put my life
I used to cry when I used to cry when I put my life
Just call so many times before,
And use the crowd of all my life,
But I might go to,
And I'm going to evolve,
Now I evolve,
So I evolve,
Now my life,
Now I evolve,
So hopefully tomorrow I'll have some information for you about the judgment of the theft
of my pictures for publication in a commercial magazine, as well as the endangerment of my
child.
You'd hope that at least we'd get something somehow, don't you know what I mean?
Adamaccurry.com for all your feedback and dailysourceco.com if you're looking for a place
to find the latest shows.
Remember I'll have a Victor Mike Charlie a video cast, a video music cast coming up
today, sometime later, so your results may vary due to your time zone, and, well,
oh, there's a message from PW Fenton saying, where's the damn show?
If I cast Lester, cast Lester, see you guys tomorrow, another pod show podcast, stick it
in your ear.