This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 421.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Thank God it's...
There's a lot of entertainment grabber in the person.
Snap out of it.
What a hot odor.
Will it meet your filler cans?
Subcrime like a little girl.
It was a crime like a little girl.
Once you try to get jacked off under the table in front of the whole damn family.
And have some real problems.
Jack ass.
With how I wish you was wrong.
But try to get along.
Oh, yes he's right.
I should kiss him.
I just can't be beaten.
Yes he's right.
How I wish you was wrong.
But try to get along.
Yes he's right.
I just can't be beaten.
But now I wish you was wrong.
Sunny combs and kitty cat rodeo.
Yes she's right.
And with a song like that, you know that she's here.
And she's right.
And it's right.
And they, yep, huh?
I've already started.
I've played a whole song already.
Yeah, that's where you said five minutes ago.
Sunny comes and kitty cat radio, of course.
So you can find that on the podcast and music network.
I'll just play a, I'll just do this thing before Patricia gets in here.
Okay, Adam, you totally called us out.
Yes, we were totally putting all this on.
The episode of Bone is already recorded.
And we already know the results, but we will never tell.
You'll have to listen for yourself.
I will tell you that it was the most fun I had in a long time.
I love C.C. and he loves me.
We were honored to be the first contestants on this show.
And personally, I can't wait for it to start playing.
It was so much fun.
And thank you, which you taught, Rutherford, for helping us out with this little promotion.
I believe it will premiere next week.
So go to bone.podshow.com and pre-registered.
So you don't miss it.
Actually, I participated in one of the very first pilot episodes, which never, of course, was posted.
But just to see how the game worked and how the questions were.
And I had a lot of fun too, I have to say.
Bone.podshow.com, the brand new game show from Podshow.
How do you only receive one thing?
Did you just not hear my wife said she would be right here?
Aaron Warm is posted on the webloggedcurry.com.
Adam, I don't exactly go for the you don't hear things I say.
This is referring to a conversation Patricia and I had where she said that just like Ron,
I don't hear a lot of things that my wife is telling me.
Aaron says, it's a catch 22 for poor men.
The proof that we don't hear stuff is that we didn't hear something.
How could we be sure that it was ever said if we didn't hear it?
Try turning the tables and trying to convince your wife that she didn't hear something that you said.
See if she goes forward or questions whether you've ever said it.
Hello, dear. How are you?
I was in a little bad.
I'm just feeling time until you get here.
I'm going to turn off the fan.
That's nice.
Well, it's loud.
Well, thank you for joining.
What were you doing?
You said you would be right there and then took another like 10 minutes.
I played songs. I played promos.
When no cleaner was here and then when he cleans the window and he's done,
he wants to check.
What the headphones on?
Wait with your story.
Yeah.
Have you taken glasses on?
You know, any of I want to sit here?
Yeah.
I'm disturbed.
You know, I have to take care of business first.
Yeah.
You know.
Okay. Well, why didn't you say, yeah.
I'm going to take care of business first.
I said that.
But I said I was starting the show.
Yeah, now.
So.
Your show.
Oh, now it's my show.
And your phone.
Oh, okay.
Oh, just wanted to make sure.
Did you hear that?
It is still my show.
Of course.
Yeah.
Would you please stop moving the microphone up?
I just moved it down.
Oh.
Yeah.
Because otherwise, you're talking on.
But I'm taller than you think.
No, you're not.
That's the more.
Why?
Because then you're projecting into the microphones, which better.
Okay.
Do you want me to, can I help you with something?
You seem to be swiveling an out of control on the bar stool.
Oh, I'm fine.
Don't worry.
Hey, baby.
How you doing?
It's Friday.
Yeah.
It is.
I was so tired.
The whole week.
Yeah.
Well, we went to bed every night at one thirty.
What's the matter with your curse?
You don't want to go to bed.
You don't seem to understand.
You never hear me complain about being tired.
Even though I'm tired.
You're young.
You're still young.
Well, thank you.
When I was your age, I wasn't tired.
I know.
But why don't you just go to bed?
You don't have to wait up.
Just go to bed over.
No, I have to.
Because I'm afraid that you guys leave the candles burning.
No, honey.
I have an entire condo in San Francisco, which is still as far as I know.
I was not burned down yet.
Yeah.
And I've got candles.
I do lock the doors.
Excuse me.
This is.
It's that the reason why you stay up because you're afraid that we're going to leave the candles.
I leave the candles burning.
Leave the doors.
I do not.
I do not leave the door.
The refrigerator open.
I don't.
That's your daughter.
Stop it.
Oh, you really get me riled up when you do this shit.
Don't.
Don't be blaming me for like the fridge door of that crappy ass.
How can you even call it a fridge?
That's true.
Yeah.
It's not even a fridge.
It's like a cupboard.
But.
Okay.
So, did you hear me laugh?
Start laughing when you get angry.
I'm sorry.
You know.
Honey.
Girlfriend.
You have not seen me angry.
You have not seen the devil come out of me because the devil in me is wearing
Prada.
Okay.
So, I've already established.
I don't leave the refrigerator door open.
Okay.
So, I leave the.
So, the refrigerator door.
I'm not really open.
But you have to close.
Close it.
Okay.
Look, give me a checklist.
I'm good at checklist.
I have to do this before I go flying.
Give me a checklist.
And then then you'll know.
And then I'll even check it off on the piece of paper.
So, and in the morning you can get up and you can see that I did the checklist.
Okay.
So, it's the refrigerator door.
No candles.
Lock all doors.
That's the garden door.
Three things.
Three.
I want you to have the rest you need as an older woman.
So, okay.
What else?
Now you know.
That's it.
Exactly.
And just to know that you guys are still walking around through the house.
And, you know, you need somebody to just say, okay, guys.
Okay.
All right.
So, it is something totally different.
Yeah.
And I can't sleep when I know other people are still awake.
But the other people are your husband and daughter.
You know, we're fine.
The other people's in that we're fine.
It's so unfair for you to blame us that you are tired.
You can go to bed whenever you want.
I don't think it's that it's just getting up.
Did you bring your tea?
No.
Where's my tea?
I've made it for you downstairs.
Put it on the counter.
No, we're safe today.
What's the matter with you?
Because you were late.
And you're pretending like, oh, whatever, do you show?
And I made tea for you.
Okay.
Of all the things we discussed Wednesday on the show, I already told you this.
What was the number one thing everyone caught onto and called in about?
Oh, the folder in there.
Folder or scruncher.
Sure.
You will not believe the things people are interested in.
Yeah.
And think it's important.
Check it out.
Hi Adam.
This is Jan from bucket at bucketpodcast.com.
I was just listening to Charlie and listening to your conversation about punching
versus folding.
And I have to say, I always thought the burning question about toilet paper was whether you put
the roll on so that it feeds from over or from under.
There's an argument in my house at least.
I don't know which is a different between men and women over and under.
Or maybe a fat regional whatever.
I'm totally over by the way.
And I'm a scruncher.
Hi.
Yeah, I'd need to see.
I'm a scruncher.
Yeah.
I need to be over.
You know.
I totally agree.
It has to be over the roll on the under.
Yeah.
And otherwise it could.
It's own.
Through gravity.
It's own weight could unroll the entire roll.
Yeah.
I agree.
And hotels always do it like that.
So there must be a rule for it.
I like it over with little point in it.
And I think that ladies are more folders because of the scruncher.
Yes.
But most of them are, I think, folders because we're more sensitive there.
Dude.
I'm a folder.
But you're sensitive.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you know.
You're so sensitive.
Yeah.
You know, there's something else that, you know, that always seems to be a point of discussion
is men don't put the toilet seat down.
Yeah.
And I think I'm a very simple solution to this controversy.
Why don't, why doesn't everybody agree that when you're done with the toilet, you put
the lid down.
Yeah.
I think women should also put the lid down.
I think there's nothing more to do.
I always do.
And the, and the real.
The lid.
That's what I mean.
So that way everybody does some work.
So it's not like women don't have to do anything.
But I see lots of women who complain about not men not putting the seat back down.
I hate that gaping.
I hate it too.
It's just like a big look.
Like, you're here.
Did you hear that?
Ready for you.
Did you read about, there's a McDonald's that opened up in Holland.
And of course, McDonald's is a franchise with the American company comes and checks it out.
And he had two of those urinals, the ones that,
the modern art urinals that looked like a big, big mouth with big red lips.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And the Americans said, you can't have that.
You have to take it out.
Well, I mean, it is kind of like putting your dick in a mouth.
I mean, let's be careful.
Even that.
That's the joke.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, but that's no human.
No, there's no humor in the McDonald's corporation when it comes to that.
But does the only thing they have on their mind in America?
Correct.
How come they didn't like it?
Maybe.
See?
So we have scrunchers and we have folders.
And we have another category.
Oh, yes.
Oh.
Hey, Adam.
This is something that starts all the podcast.
And I, uh, we're just going to like to weigh in on the scrunching versus folding.
And I'm a roller.
Uh, try to figure that one out.
A roller?
But they have?
I think.
Well, listen to this next one.
Um, this is a roller.
A roller.
This next person, Dr. Oh, we know.
Friend of the show.
Oh, you've rolled it up.
No, no, no, no, no.
I think it's, it's roll around your finger.
Listen to this side.
Hello, Adam.
It's, uh, Dr. Oh, here.
You see, uh, noisy traffic sounds.
Oh, I'm over.
Pretty good.
I run out as well before.
And it just message.
I just want to say yeah, along with everyone else.
Um, condolences about your mum.
Um, I want to, to send a message before today.
How much are you talking about your mum?
Um, made me go up and see mine.
Uh-huh.
Because I thought.
I've been thinking about what you've been saying about mum's.
And unfortunately, I don't know everything else.
You know, then you realise that I should make more of an effort to get on a train
and travel three hours to see her.
Uh-huh.
Ah.
I think people go visit their mum.
Yeah, you should.
Yeah.
Three hours by train.
That what a pain in the house, that is.
That is, yeah.
Um.
Break it through my mum.
And the, uh, folding or punching, uh, debate.
My mum used to tell me, and me to use two sheets of toilet paper.
See, it's got this.
Um, and I used to really get annoyed when toilet paper was not folded until I became angry.
Uh, and then sometimes I would just punch up just because.
But I also do the, um, to wrapping down the two fingers thing.
So, you know, and you're quite cool.
And it's quite cool.
And it's pretty cool.
It's hard.
I'm going to put it on.
Uh, so I shall leave it there.
Um, and the Elena?
Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you.
Dr.
She talks like she has still a piece of paper in there.
I know her.
I don't say that.
She's front of the show.
Uh, she's walking.
Yeah, I know.
But what is that rapid around your finger thing that's kind of, I don't like that at all.
That sounds like it.
Because you could rip right through and then, you know, then, of course.
You get the drink.
No.
Neal touch.
Oh yeah, that's not good.
And what if you nail by it?
Oh.
Which, of course.
Do you notice when you look at Big Brother, you know?
Big Brother is on how many people buy nails?
Well, that one girl is us.
Yeah, it's outrageous.
What's her name?
Many people.
Well, I haven't seen many in Big Brother.
Really, they all buy their nails.
Oh, everybody is doing it once.
It's just, I've never, ever, ever did it in my life.
But then again, my nails are really hard to do.
Yes, right.
The Korean ladies make them into rock.
No, but it's just disgusting.
There's so much dirt underneath your nails.
Don't stick it in your mouth.
Don't do that.
And you, and you know, and the look of, you know, those nails are just so.
They look so nervous those hands.
Yeah.
Very nervous people.
Chew it off.
Yeah.
Well, anyway, so Patricia and I really have one official Charlie mission for you.
Doesn't matter whether you fold or scrunch.
Yeah.
You need to use, excuse me, Sensei.
Oh, this Sensei moment.
Hold on, I had to email about that.
Brought to you by podshowradio.com.
Sorry.
How long can we just go on about the toilet paper?
Oh, forever.
Oh, man.
I could talk about pooping forever.
Fantastic.
That's a man thing.
It is totally a man thing.
Yeah, we women don't.
Anyway, you need to use wipes.
Okay, baby wipes or whatever the hell you call it.
Now, very talking about, you know, very, very important.
Everybody, that is the thing.
Just buy those baby things.
Don't flush them.
Always look at the package.
And you can read if it's flushable.
Why the flushables don't get the non flushable.
No, no.
It would be very careful.
You know, but these are also toddlers and baby things.
It says flushable.
I know they're Patricia hygiene moments.
Yes.
It is so lost.
I must say you're so, always in all sorts.
Everybody will have a very clean, beautiful, but non-sour.
No.
Non-sour.
Except after.
I was always so disgusted because when I was young,
I used to trim.
You know, we have the trims just like in San Francisco.
Like the lady in the trim.
In Rotterdam.
And I had to take the trim to go to gym or to go to ballet classes.
You know.
And when the trim was full and you already set down,
you were lucky to sit down.
People would come and shove their asses.
And, you know, got because it was very crowded with everything.
And the butts will just, you know.
Just kind of waft weight.
Waft? Yeah.
Past your nose.
Your nose.
And I always thought, what is the matter with these people?
Why do they smell?
Wow.
And I think that the solution is.
Proper hygiene is wipes.
We know there's, we've had all that wonderful product that we got.
I even wiped the dogs in it, but you know.
Okay.
You think that's a joke.
It's absolutely true.
And they have doggy wipes.
Yeah.
Yeah, but the doggy wipes.
The dog uses the, the people wipes.
No, no, no, doggy wipes.
You don't use doggy wipes.
Yes, I do.
I have it in the basket downstairs.
Really?
Yeah.
Those are doggy wipes.
Doggy wipes.
Oh, can I?
Are they substitutable in case the human wipes are?
I don't know.
Just a, just a two dogs.
Yes, that I, we'll get to your thing in the second.
Yes.
I talked about this movie, The Little Man, which is The Wayne Brothers.
And they want me to talk about it on the show.
And I said send me a copy of the movie because it opens today, actually, in America.
Send me a copy of the movie so I can take a look at it.
And I can tell people, it's one of these typical summer blockbuster really idiotic kind of kind of movies.
It really is American movie.
Yeah, you know the Wayne's Brothers.
The Wayne's Brothers.
From an living color.
Oh, those Wayne's brothers.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's sure.
It's kind of like, remember the movie white chicks where they were.
Oh, okay.
So it's that, in fact.
Incredible.
Exactly.
But it's going to be a big blockbuster.
You know it is.
Because I'm always funny.
You know, seeing on the couch and, you know, it's nice, but not going to a theatre.
So they said, sorry.
We can't ship the movie to Adam.
This is coming from the guy over at, was at the media planner, Universal McCann.
Oh, yeah.
That was the name Bill.
No Robert.
Not Robert.
The biggest reason is that they've shipped DVDs of past movie pre-releases.
And they've been burned by employees forwarding the movie and then putting them online.
Oh.
So they don't want to send them out of any works that are afraid that I would rip the movie and put it online.
Yeah.
I wouldn't do that.
No.
So there are a couple things I can mention.
Because that's this podcast about the movie Little Men podcast.com.
With interviews from the Red Carpet Premier with Sean and Marlon Wayne.
Very, very funny.
Those guys are funny.
Great actors.
The plot is silly.
It's silly.
It's like quite chicks.
Okay.
Here's the synopsis.
They're little.
Check it out.
In the hilarious comedy Little Men, Sean Wains plays a man so anxious to become a father.
That he mistakes a short stature baby faced criminal on the run.
Played by Marlon Wayne's for his newly adopted son.
Oh, no.
Uh-huh.
Exactly.
Oh.
Our daughter played hokey to go see the movies.
We found out.
Yeah.
Boy.
That was disappointing.
Yeah.
Horrible.
And she's no good at hiding that shit because she actually left the rest of the movie.
No, she looked me in the eyes and I said, you're lying.
You're lying.
Because I found the receipt for that.
Yeah.
I found the cinema.
It said Monday 11 a.m.
And I'm looking at the killing.
That's a school day.
Uh-huh.
And you know what?
She's so stupid.
She leaves it in her bag.
You know, while I always clean it out, get the stuff, you know, from lunch out of her bag.
So.
I don't think she'll be doing that again, though.
I think so.
No.
Because she saw that I was very disappointed.
Because I say.
I see.
Intelligent people don't do that.
Yeah.
No.
Don't do that.
So she's coming home with Dan today.
Dan, who, of course, was a accomplice in this.
You're going to give them shit.
Yeah.
You don't have to tell anything to him.
It's, I'm, I'm, you know, as my response to me.
No, I think you should give Dan some, a little bit of shit.
Just a little bit of shit.
Shied.
Come on.
Get some shit.
Just a little bit of shit.
Stupid little brat.
Beat his beard to a pulp of food.
Really?
Why did she do my job today?
I don't know.
Is your ass out of balance?
Cheers.
Oh, hon, oh, hon, hon.
I paid her.
I'd have to present her with me.
Once to know if you're scrunch or a folder.
It's Patricia.
Patricia Pive from the daily source code featuring Adam Curry.
Oh, you know, Patricia.
Radiant smile like a baby with wind.
Really big, full-bodied hair.
Yeah.
Little big, you know.
Put a makeup on with a spade.
Femesing of the nose of the herd off.
Very short.
It's a bottom on the curb when she crosses the road.
That's right.
Miss Piggy.
Okay.
I'll tell her.
Pid ups head he uses a scrunched go for lovely to see Patricia.
Closer door on the way out.
It's time to play the music.
It's time to light the lights.
It's time to meet Patricia on the map.
But show tonight.
The talking about short.
Well, before we get to that, just, okay, go ahead.
Talking about short.
You know what I'm writing a paper?
What's that?
A new study by the
Medics at Bristol University.
Yeah.
Show that people with short legs have better sex lives.
No.
They have heart problems.
Really?
More heart problems than people with long legs.
You can't even know that.
You can't even.
It's got to do with the sort of a vein that goes through your body.
So.
It's.
It's the.
What does it said?
It means there's less chance of a clot halting blood flow and causing a heart attack when
You have long.
Longer legs.
Sounds like it sounds like they need to fill some of that page to me.
The arts.
Watch your weight and have regular.
No, you know what?
Like sure the man, especially sure the man.
Yeah.
You know.
They have more heart problems.
Isn't it stupid?
Well, who did this?
I have actually I don't have very long legs.
No, on your legs are beautiful.
They're nice and lengthy.
Well, they belong to my body.
Thank God.
He imagined them on me.
That would look pretty weird.
They look good with my body with my legs.
But.
Isn't that strange?
No.
It makes sense, I guess.
And you know that.
People with big heads.
Our often on American television.
Hold on one second, hun.
If you're listening to us and stars one or two on the serious
satellites, you can download the rest of the show at daily source code.com
and then we'll be back Monday with a full four hour block of the pod show on stars one
or two.
The bigger your head, the less chance you have of getting dementia in old age.
Really?
I'm lucky.
You're not.
I have a small head.
Of course, it's easy.
I need the small head to stick it up my ass once in a while.
It's very important.
Oh, God.
You know what's nice?
You know, well, go ahead.
I was going to say something else.
Kylie is back.
Hold on a second about Kylie.
No, just that.
I want to stay on the blood clot stuff.
We got an offer.
Oh.
Yeah, this morning on email from a Dutch company that makes a certain type of,
I'm not going to say the name of a certain type of healthy,
the margin like products.
Yeah.
And so the agency, it's gray advertising because the relationship,
send me an email and said, would we be interested in appearing in a commercial
for this?
Yeah.
However, we would both have to have high cholesterol.
And I said, well, they did that with Lulu here.
Well, I replied and I said, well, you know,
they pay well.
Well, I says it will have high cholesterol.
If you have high budget.
If you have high budget, we can have whatever cholesterol you want.
We adjust.
Oh, gosh.
I need some margin.
Now, it's probably a approach.
I think other people too.
Maybe.
No, it's not.
It's seen pretty individualistic because we fit into the age group.
Fuck.
What are you talking about?
I'm an old man, baby.
I'm going to be 42.
I remember when my dad was 40.
I was like, God, guys old 40 is old 42.
Well, the 40 is you have to, you know, have the regular checkups too.
For those of you who missed yesterday or Wednesday when we talked about the new drama series,
scripted drama, which means well written, well acted, well produced,
fucking brilliant shadow falls.
And you can pre-register.
It's going to happen this month.
Only a couple more weeks.
Shadowfalls.podshow.com.
Here's a clip from the first episode.
Here and gotten her car.
Hoping to find her friend from the college newspaper at home.
Hey, Ramsey, you in there?
I don't believe he is scared of it.
Jesus, you frightened me.
I'm sorry about that, darling.
Oh, I know that voice.
Who you know?
My name's Brian.
Brian Gend.
Say,
you look just like your father.
He, he, you know, my dad didn't you sort of.
I'm the one that killed him.
That's not good.
Yeah, that sounds good.
It's going to be great.
This is going to be perfect for all those trips I make.
Lovely.
On, uh, between here and San Francisco.
Yeah.
I love listening to drawn radio dramas.
An audio books and all kinds of stuff.
Yeah.
I love it.
I can really get into that.
It's a crazy reader.
So it would be very nice for me too.
I like to listen.
You devour the sun in the mirror every day.
I fall asleep.
I don't know what it is.
Really?
Yeah.
Now have for you.
Oh, my eye.
You even fall asleep when I read.
No, but I love to listen when I was young.
My mom always read all sorts of books for us.
Mm-hmm.
It's a lost art.
This is the telling stories and audio.
We have a couple of podcasts that I do it very well.
We love it.
But really, when it comes down to a whole piece of fiction, there's brand new.
I think it's fantastic.
I love it.
Sensei.
Excuse me.
God.
Kylie's back.
Is that what you wanted to say?
Well, no.
There was a big picture in the paper this morning.
I thought, oh, you know, I'm happy.
I'm happy for her.
Man, she went through it.
I think she went through it.
Yeah.
She's going to tell us now.
So there's a couple of interviews.
She's going to be on the TV.
She did already.
She's got to do.
Letterman, Leno, and Parkie.
Yeah.
That's what she has to do.
I think so.
And she's going to tell us how she felt.
And, you know.
Don't have to tell me, man.
She thought, like, shit.
Well, she was very scared.
No kidding.
Yeah.
And the thing is, you know, when you're famous, you have to hide.
What do you mean you have to hide?
Well, you know, you have to hide inside because they're always,
paparazzi.
Paparazzi, looking for you.
See how bad you look.
Oh, man.
Did you see about those pictures in the Italian magazine of Lady Dye?
No.
I didn't see the pictures.
Well, they didn't publish them.
No.
But in Italian.
Yeah.
I had a publish it.
I would be to that.
Well, there's only one reason, of course.
To sell them.
To sell magazines, of course.
That is just without any reason.
That's true.
That's yeah.
That's without respect.
That's not necessary.
Horrible.
I've got a message from Callie.
Hey, Adam.
It's Callie from Geek.
Brief TV.
It's been way too long.
Hasn't it?
Here I go today.
I heard my very first daily source code.
It was the second podcast I listened to.
The first one was Dawn and Drew just a few days earlier.
Within six months, you convinced us to buy our first Mac.
And then we bought another one.
And another one.
When Dawn and Drew quit their day job, we started an audio podcast.
Then Apple released the iPod with video.
We saw Tiki Bar and had the idea for Geek Brief.
It's a year later.
We have a worldwide audience.
And now, Pod Show Plus is making it easy for anyone to do the same thing.
It's amazing.
I just wanted to say thanks.
I also want to tell you about a new artist in the Pod Save Music network.
His name is Doc Bates.
And when we told him about the PMN, he loved it so much that he uploaded several of his songs
and moved his fan site to Pod Show Plus.
My favorite is my old pickup truck never lets me down.
Would you play it for me?
How can you refuse?
You're just this piece and make it really fast?
No, that's just the way Callie talks.
Really?
Yeah, that's what you're talking about.
You know, from a Geek Brief TV.
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe she just gets excited when she's talking about it.
Thanks, sir.
I bought some country, baby.
Don't you like the country?
Have the black top looking for a gravel road.
Yeah, my old pickup truck never lets me down.
She's got a mowing drive all the walls there.
Yes, she got a CVN, a CDN, a no-late track.
She's my old pickup truck.
And a lack of old pickup truck never lets me down.
Yeah, my old pickup truck never lets me down.
Oh my god.
Well, she takes me hunting in a fishy anywhere that I want to do.
We ain't never been stuck in a footnut street or snow.
He's got a tiger ball tower to keep a soul track.
Got a cooler in the run and a bed in the back.
Got my hunky turkey rope rocking over you.
Yeah, my own pick-up truck.
Never let's be down.
She's got a four-wheel drive, a one-to-one stereo sound.
Yeah, she got a TV and a CD and an old eight track.
She's my own pick-up truck.
Never let's be down.
Yeah, she got a CD and a CD and an old eight track.
She's my own pick-up truck.
Never let's be down.
Doc Bates, Missouri.
Missouri.
I'll pick-up truck.
Never let's be down.
I'm K-country.
How you doing, everybody?
Sorry.
I could do that.
I could totally live in some shit-kicking town and just do that.
You don't have a job.
Yeah.
Can you just imagine that?
How does that sound?
I feel like.
Big sound, a K-country.
How you doing, everybody?
It's Adam Curry, bringing you the country and western sound and the blues
that you love the tears to us.
We got it.
Missouri, buy it.
For some violence.
Some get-fiddled.
Okay, maybe.
Yeah.
We could always move.
Could always move.
I don't think so.
Well, I could do it.
I could do it.
I'm not a country girl.
You don't like country music.
I love country music.
I really do.
Yeah, yeah.
I like it.
Some songs.
Of course, there's no country girl in me.
Do you know when we used to play records backwards?
Like the Beatles records.
Yeah, yeah.
And also the Osborne Black Sabbath.
You could hear satanic messages.
Uh-huh.
You know what happens if you spin that country record backwards?
You know what happens?
Uh-huh.
You get your wife back.
You get your dog back.
You get your car back.
You get it all by.
Uh-huh.
Adam C.
Death Zero from the Area 51 group.
Amen.
Let's hear a short show.
Sorry, 20, man.
And you're talking about not getting enough audio comment.
Criticism of odd show, odd show plus.
You probably not going to want to play this something here.
I've got one dippy thing that actually really is kind of making the sight look bad.
Honestly.
It's a bit of a sign of the teachers.
The first thing I notice is, join now it's pretty and it is missing an apostrophe.
And it looks unprofessional.
It looks like some happens.
It makes the sight kind of look half-assed.
Like someone didn't know their grammar.
Did not approach or eat.
It is.
Has an apostrophe.
Looks unprofessional.
It's all I can tell you.
And I know it's from the last thing you guys are worried about.
You're worried about things breaking.
Otherwise, uh, as a soccerer got myself, I understand that.
Yeah, somebody just needs to get in a photo shop and turn a apostrophe in there.
It'll be happy.
It'll probably take you guys a little bit better.
I'm not sure.
Now to me.
Yeah.
What?
Well, on pod show plus, we have on the homepage.
We have, it says, join now it's free.
Okay.
And it's, we spelled ITS.
Yeah.
And it should be IT apostrophe.
Oh.
Oh, no.
That is important.
I can never figure that out.
I thought that.
The apostrophe was, uh,
No, because when you leave away,
No, you leave away.
You know, you leave a letter.
It's, it's instead of the letter.
Yeah.
I don't know.
But that's what you're saying.
It was just such a hard language.
There's so many exceptions to so many rules.
You're quite good at it, actually.
I must say.
Yeah, you're very good at it.
Have these things?
At English?
Oh, no, I'm not.
This you are.
No, I'm, I'm avoiding a lot of words.
Listen, from a girl who, when she was a little girl,
you used to take the tram and smell sour but in, in water,
Damn.
Although, and you've done quite well for yourself.
You can give the way from Rotterdam.
Oh, the way from Rotterdam.
Yes.
So we're planning a couple of trips for the next few weeks.
Of course Tuesday, I'm going to San Francisco for the lower week.
Because we have a board meeting.
I'm looking forward to that.
Because it's the first meeting in a long time.
Are you ready?
Oh, I do.
Oh, yeah.
Very much look forward to it.
Don't you?
I love it very much.
I love the company, the people in the company.
Yeah, you do.
How are you kidding me?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
It's totally makes sense.
I know you're tired now and then, but you always say, yeah.
But it's fun.
I really love what I'm doing.
I do.
So there's no bed stress.
I don't know.
There's no stress at all.
Really?
To be honest.
So when I come back, then we're going to Euro Disney.
Yeah.
That'll be cool.
Kristina wants to go for her birthday and invite some friends.
Well, she's inviting friends.
I thought it was just one friend.
I think it's a bad idea to have two friends.
Because three is a crowd.
It never works out.
It's not a good idea.
Yeah.
Not a good idea.
And we're getting the big ass goofy sweet.
You and me, baby.
Yep.
We'll take the train, the fast train.
It's three hours from Waterloo Station to the heart of the magic king.
And then we can listen to, it's going to start yet.
Shadow Falls.
Yep.
We can listen to it.
That'll be cool.
Yeah.
Together.
And then we have this Sunday.
I'm going to take you to a visit Lou.
Yeah.
So we're going to fly up to south.
And that'll be a fun trip.
Yeah.
I'm so glad you're taking advantage of your personal, your private pilot.
It's very good.
And we want to go to the water that plays Captain Dan.
Said he went to in front of France.
But they have a beach, like 20 minutes from the air.
We see that too.
Yeah.
Can't wait.
But no big big picture.
Don't make people jealous.
What do you mean?
Are you kidding me?
I think all those lovely trips.
No.
I think that the listeners are very happy.
Yeah.
I'm going to take that off.
They're very happy for me.
Because we stay home a lot.
Yeah.
We work a lot.
That's true.
All right, babe.
What else we got going on?
Today we want to go out for dinner because Christina's going to go first.
Go first.
Yeah.
So she'll be doing a podcast.
I guess over the other day.
Okay.
Let's go and have a nice one.
Can you have you booked anything?
No.
Because it's Friday night.
You know, Gilford is quite popular.
True.
Yes.
But maybe everybody used to go for dinner.
At the Gilfest.
It's a Gilfest.
So yeah.
I'll do that.
What do you want to go?
We're dressed for it.
We're not going to say because then people are going to look at us.
Yeah.
All right.
I was bothered by the way.
I haven't heard him in a long time.
They were not with Roger.
Maybe somebody's talking to him?
Marcus Mowler from pot you HQ sent me an email.
How's that?
What's that?
I don't have that.
Maybe there else some mama the half.
What?
I said awesome mama.
Yeah.
That's the province where camps committee.
Um, was turned over to Iraqi forces today.
Uh, what the hell is going on?
What is that?
What time is it?
Is it maybe...
Oh, Barbara.
Barbara.
Can you just close the door for a second then, huh?
Um, sorry.
Oh, it's not Barbara.
I know that.
What is it?
Oh, it's somebody outside.
Oh, okay.
Uh, anyway, Camp Smitty is the, uh,
the camp that I stayed at for about 10 days
and did a live broadcast when the Dutch marines were there.
Um, the, uh, the Japanese were just just arriving as we were leaving.
Um, uh, the bridge weren't there yet.
Um, so now they've, uh, they've left, uh, the province.
It's secure and it's in hands of, uh, the Iraqi security forces.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's pretty cool.
That's very good.
Well, some of the work was actually real.
Some of the stuff that was going on there.
No, they did a good job.
Absolutely.
I still, I'm still waiting for my invitation to go to Afghanistan.
Totally would go.
Don't give me that face.
Please don't give me that face.
Don't give me that face, baby.
All right.
Anything else for the peeps before we, uh,
check out into the weekend?
Let me think, is there anything else?
No.
Yes, absolutely nothing going on in your life.
Look, the sun is out now.
It's because it was a little bit windy, but it's very nice.
Mm-hmm.
And I need a very nice relaxing weekend.
Okay.
That's what I want.
Well, I'm going to be gone Saturday.
I'll be gone Saturday, so you can have a nice relaxing Saturday.
Of course.
I will wake you up when I get up in the morning.
You know, because Williams arriving 930, so I'll probably leave the house around 915.
I'm sorry.
You know, this is why I want separate bedrooms.
I keep saying this is a good idea.
We have our date, and then we can, you know, we can have dinner and then come back.
And of course, we're seeing there won't be here tonight.
And then we can do all kinds of dirty things.
And then you can go to bed on time.
And I can sit up and then...
Hang on.
It's chandelier.
Yes.
And then I can play around until whenever I feel I want to go to bed.
Well, we have to find the right house.
Oh.
Here you can have your bedroom.
Hey, baby.
Oh.
And you can sign the first day.
No.
Really?
You're not saying that?
Maybe it's worth it.
Oh, yeah.
First day.
I let Trissoty.
When you walk in, you set my circuit tree.
Back it up.
We've got to do it.
When people swear it out, you always play cool.
I think I know you feel.
I'm going a bit.
And you lock through what you're.
And don't get it.
Get your quit fix.
In my car.
You got a sweet truth and I'm your chocolate bar.
Oh, no, no, no.
Ah, no, nothing.
Hey.
Oh, you kiss provocers.
Cause I do.
New ya'll down.
Yeah, I'm the catwalk, I like to play it to squid
You don't really want to show, spray paint you
Touching you
And cruise yourself, don't be wrong
So take a chance, give me a shot
You think I'm bluffing, I think I'm not
Get on your high heels, give me a heart attack
I got a question for your sweet ass
No, no, no, no, no, no
In that sense, do you kiss all the first hue?
Do you kiss all the first hue?
Cause I do, do you do what I do, and with you
If you do, what you do, what I do
I'm good at you
We're a little baby, you look so hot tonight
Can I hold your hand?
I'm thinking
Now this is what we're going to do in our day today
We're going to do all the things all the couples like to do
We're going to go more movie
We're going to have some dinner, take a walk
Look at the moonlight, anything you want but baby
I got a question
Because I do, because I do, because I do, because I do, because I do, because I do
Because I do, because I do, because I do
Dango Jones, I like that
Do you kiss on the first date?
Yeah, right in the bus he was in a proper way
Did I kiss on the first date?
Then, shack on the first date
Don't, shack on the first date
No, no, no, no
All right
I take a look at that
That's a good song
You've heard it before
Yeah, I could sing it
Yeah, yeah
Gee, it's just like
Just like real hits, not amazing.
Do you chag on the first date?
Don't chag on the first date.
Uh, I'd take it you haven't checked out
Podgeo Plus yet.
No.
I haven't as a time, huh?
Okay. All right.
Well, anyone else listening to the show?
The winners, I'll make dinner for you.
Go ahead, register at PodgeoPlus.
Go to atom.podshow.com and dig me.
Dig me on the plus baby.
Ha ha ha.
Why do you laugh at my life's work?
My dream.
Mm-hmm.
I enjoy your life the way you are here in the house.
The other day Patricia said to me,
I'm just living your life.
Yeah.
But not, you know, in a bad way.
It's pretty exciting.
No, in my life.
It's very exciting.
No.
What?
All right, baby.
So, uh, we have a date tonight?
Yes, we do.
Oh, I'm going to rip you apart.
Oh, God.
Okay.
Hey, everybody else.
We'll talk to you on Monday.
I love you, baby.
Love you, too.
Bye.
Another PodgeoPodcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this Podcast and more great ones like it.
On the high performance Podcast delivery network
from Podgeo and limelight networks.
I love it.