Already a hit state side. Now you can check out the following podcast and good old
blightybtpodshot.com. Single-handedly making a mens for giving you Madonna.
One show at a time.
This is Paul Durham from the Band Black Lab. You may not think that plugging your iPod into your computer
and listening to podcast is a revolutionary act. However, you have to realize every time you do it,
you are taking one step closer towards the destruction of commercial radio as we know it
and I say, God bless you. Delta Sierra Charlie 5-0-7.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
You're listening to Delta Sierra Charlie. The daily source code with the one and only
Adam Curry. Brace yourself for the show that's got it all.
Hot-safe music, the lady Patricia, and of course, your host, Adam Curry.
It's where I fell out of love and I laughed with a hundred bucks and my heart was now
whatever right. I checked out to be your brave spirit.
Mingo for it's days where they're due from cocaine and sugar's out of my baby.
I had it my baby, but baby, so I checked out, baby, so go round my heart up.
What did you see? It's all I want out of here, guys. I was gonna say it's a lie away.
I get it all I swear I can walk on water. There's so many voices and my smile must be in motion.
It's never gonna be peaceful and it's better and safer. I was looking at the neighborhood
who is having a baby, having a baby, with a baby.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Just what the doctor ordered, the sweetest sea by this love machine, it is Fubar Friday.
Hey everybody, how you doing it is, the first of December.
So what do you say, bunny bunny rabbit rabbit something like that?
Very good to have you all along for the ride just before the weekend.
Just before the weekend, crap here in the UK.
It's going to be rainy today and Sunday.
We have a true gale force winds coming our way.
And I missed all this.
Somewhere there's going to be a slot in the middle known as Saturday amongst the population.
And that's when I'm going to have to go brave the elements to go pick up the the ailing lady Patricia.
Yeah, she was supposed to come home last night from her rehearsals for dancing with the stars.
And she's been in Rotterdam staying with the sister.
And she took ill Wednesday night.
And she's really hurting all over and she absolutely cannot get on a commercial flight.
And let's someone literally carried her bag and hurts the carry of bag even.
So Captain Dan and I are gearing up to brave the elements to see what we can make the crossing on Saturday.
We should be able to just kind of work it in between two stored front.
So it's Mr. Mom all over again.
Today though we had the big clean up day today.
So I came by and she helped me out.
Christina has actually been doing a pretty good job.
And I know that we've been doing a good job because the real estate agent came by.
She wanted to show the house to somebody.
Of course, you know, we're leaving in just four weeks from now.
We're actually leaving this cottage to for another one.
And then I said, you know, I'm sorry, my wife's been gone for four days.
And neither she nor client could believe.
How incredibly good the place looks.
She said, well, if my husband had been alone for four days,
it would be a real big style.
Jim's from there.
You get it.
That's not to listen to.
You said, he said, I said, you conversation put that just to put.
Yeah.
Chris Moiles friend.
Don't leave.
He can play it back if you want.
Not going to be put from but I don't believe I said.
Chris Moiles was against podcast.
And I said he was an asshole, which is a totally different thing.
And it looks up in the office of me.
Oh man.
I love it when you guys are high, drunk, stone, and calling is fantastic.
Please continue to do that, particularly you folks here in the UK.
You seem to be more prone to that.
I'm going to be rolling along really fast today.
I got lots of music for you.
I mean an incredible amount of music.
I'm going to go way overboard today.
I can guarantee you that right now because I know one song is particularly long,
but I think you will really, really enjoy it.
And I just want to blow through it all.
And I do have something, well, in the final thought of the week is where we'll really slow down
and talk for a second.
But first, let's just scan the globe and take a look at what's coming to.
Brian knows news aggregator with the world news mashup.
Potio is pleased to bring you the fuck me with a chainsaw.
God dammit.
Little news mashup.
The news doesn't get any better now from our aggregator.
Thank you.
Today's story.
The number of British troops at Iraq will be significantly reduced by the high intelligence
of dolphins for less than an hour before a profoundly shameful episode among the bright sparks
of the deep after 18 years on death row according to a report released Monday.
Israeli troops pulled out of German Chancellor Angela Merkel in a stiff monotone podcast
performance from cool toys with a high-hack ability potion to endless electronic projects
splashing the sex positive optimism that usually permeates personal FM transmitters through the
high-tech etiquette.
Cities like London and Dubai will be scraping more music owned by record labels behind a new
military recruitment video game in the Balkan state as its people prepared to welcome world
leaders.
Speculation is rife in Lebanon over who killed the worst movie director ever from a Pakistan jail
after the Middle East risked three civil wars to enter India's retail markets.
King Abdullah of Jordan challenges his web critics to a boxing match as the genocide trial of
Saddam Hussein resumes.
His lawyer walks out and protests over a rebel advance as troops deploy outside the ashes series
after beating England by 277 runs in the first test at Brisbane.
The trial of Italy's X-prime minister Silvio Burlisconi on fraud charges is postponed
after he spends the night in Colorado with my family.
For last night we put aside grudges and gave a festive sendoff to opt out of Afghanistan
combat.
Germany, France, Spain, and Italy will come a depressure this week to surrender the traditional
popular looking increasingly precarious last night as domestic factions were to take over
the world's richest energy giant quite literally in the shadow of the news.
And finally today I had almost make me want to grab a tumblr of Jack and a lucky strike
loud and unbalanced world news mashup.
The news doesn't get any better.
Brian, no, with a world news mashup, with your world the entire week in one podcast
and you can find that at world news mashup.podshow.com.
Hey Adam, this is Terry from Little Ruts Writing Hood.
You might remember me, you might not.
If you do, great.
If not, guess what.
I don't have a boyfriend that's going to come after you for calling me.
So anytime you want to pick up the phone go for it.
I do have a gift for you.
This is my Christmas gift to you.
A little bit early, but I figured since you're doing Christmas stuff already so
mine.
As the pod father you keep us informed with your opinions so non-conformed to turn off
the DSC we simply cannot foresee, entertained each and every mourn
perceivably.
Addicted to the Charlie ourselves we find.
However, missing Patricia is no longer a state of mind.
As of now another day rolls around and the Chacha 507 is where we're found.
Keep up the great shows and the pod show stuff.
And by the way, even show 999 will never be enough.
Enjoy Adam.
It's a great season.
You have a great thing going on and I'm glad to be a part of it.
Bye.
Thank you.
That's so sweet.
By the way, I apologize for what I said earlier.
I really tried to limit myself on swearing.
So apologies if that offended you.
Now in the other hand, fuck me with the chainsaw.
I'm okay with as long as it's gentle.
I'm okay.
I don't know who this is but stop fucking calling Disneyland's home.
Hey Adam, it's Jack from GetJack.
GetJack.
Podcast.com.
And I thought I'd have to horn in on Jersey Todd's territory.
So it's just a song.
It's on the Pods Life Music Network.
These guys have been there for a while.
But they just posted some new stuff.
It's my little radio.
This one's called Leave the Light on for a food bar Friday.
There's something in front of me doing.
It's so.
Since this is this song, it's been hit on the institutional C sharp.
If you like of design, let the lights turn golden right off.
If it makes the last sound, it's really good.
If I have something to talk about, let's kwel.
Sure.
Makes the sound make the sound best.
It's just my concern.
Both of them dance.
If you make it pronounce, intersection.
I'm ready, do you want to go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, out, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. go, no, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
You're going to go again, you can't leave me for all night
Sing no one can find out that's what we've been here
Just tell me, I'll have said it, say what I want to hear
Just pull me in closer like no one ever did
In my hands, if you shake it, I won't let it on again
Will you leave the world alone for me?
Will you make sure I can fall asleep?
Do you want to go again?
You can leave me for all night
Will you leave the world alone for me?
Will you make sure I can fall asleep?
Are you feeling now?
Are you nice and fubard?
Oh, Todd, Sergio Zita, don't worry.
Of course I'll get to you, please don't worry about it, buddy.
Please chill out there, take a seat.
About 15 minutes.
What do you get when you put two guys in an orange room?
Add a pair of mics?
A mixer?
A compressor?
A couple of sets of headphones?
PC?
Some software?
John, you're killing me.
What do you get?
Well, little thing I like to call bloodthirsty vegetarians.
And what my friend is that?
It's a podcast.
Oh, so it's one of those new internet radio things?
Yeah.
What do you do?
You talk about politics, media, culture, and philosophy?
Yeah.
And you play music?
That's right.
But why is it called bloodthirsty vegetarians?
Well, because we are vegetarians.
But one of the show to be about more.
So it is.
Groovy.
I'm hip.
Let's do it.
What we already do, man?
Not dig this.
You can find us and subscribe at www.buddybedge.com.
Solid.
That's bloodthirsty vegetarians.
Solid is a rock, rock, rock.
Oh, yes.
Of course, if you want an easy way to find any podcasts that you hear about anywhere.
Just go to podshow.com, go to the search box.
And you'll see how easy we've made that.
And of course, you can collect all of your favorite shows.
Even your favorite episodes.
Put them into channels.
Have those show up on your iPod.
Damn.
We've got some exciting stuff.
Oh, yes.
Speaking of which, sexy fruit talk.
Hello, Mr. Yannahau.
Hey, Adam.
Jennifer here.
It's time for another finger-looking Friday.
And guess what?
Why?
We're all alone today.
Yeah.
But never mind the kitchen.
Let's step over to the wet bar for a cocktail.
Oh, yes.
Please.
That's beautiful.
Today's recipe is a little bit girly.
So it's actually perfect for you.
Hey.
It's a leechy martini from our Gilded Fork mixologist, Damian Sim.
Oh, okay.
And it adds the perfect touch to holiday festivities, especially if you're serving an Asian
menu.
Now, for this drink, we recommend canned leechy fruit because you'll need the syrup for
the cocktail.
And you can usually find those in the Asian section of your grocery store or in Asian markets.
Ready?
Make sure you have a three-piece cocktail shaker and a clean martini glass.
Oh.
I know how your boys are.
You're going to take an ounce of leechy lecure.
Two-thirds of an ounce of vanilla flavored vodka, a dash of clontro.
Two ounces of leechy syrup from the canned fruit and the remaining leechy foods for garnish.
The trick here is to chill all of your ingredients, including the garnishes and the glassware
and the shaker.
So just stick them in their refrigerator until everything is well chilled.
Then fill your cocktail shaker about three quarters full with large ice cubes.
You want the most surface area possible.
Then you're going to add in the leechy lecure, the vodka, the quontro, and the leechy syrup.
Shake and chill the cocktail shaker with firm and vigorous strokes, I think you know what I mean.
Until your hands can't take the cold and then a little bit longer.
After all the ingredients are blended, place a leechy fruit on a cocktail pick, put it in the glassware,
and strain the ingredients into the martini glass.
If you've shaken well, your reward will be a wonderful textural experience filled with
tiny little ice chips floating on the surface of the cocktail.
Now, Chef Mark will be here next week to talk about some nibbles for the holidays.
And in the meantime, I'll be featuring different kinds of holiday entertaining ideas
and a special show in December on the art of the cocktail.
At foodphilosophy.podshow.com.
Have a great weekend, Adam.
Jennifer, are you sexy?
Minks you.
Love it.
The double entendre is the sexy talker.
Normally I'd say Bon Appetit, but I guess now it's, uh,
score, roast to your health.
This is Paul Marshall, and this is a promo for the podcast novel 7th son.
Oh, my God.
7th son, book two, is about halfway through, and it has been fantastic.
But it's just gone supernova.
It has just hit record levels.
If you are not listening to 7th son, then get over to JC Hutchins.net now.
That's JC Hutchins.net.
You can find it in iTunes.
You can find it anywhere else in any other podcast in directory.
But JC Hutchins.net.
Go there.
Download it.
Listen to it.
Now.
But what is still available?
You can go back.
You can download book one.
We're about halfway through book two, and all my God, it is so good.
You must download it.
If you don't do anything else today, go to JC Hutchins.net.
You know, I, I played this promo for a number of reasons.
Uh, the primary one being that I love it.
I just, oh, sorry.
I absolutely love it when listeners send in their promos.
And it doesn't have to be elaborately produced.
And this was clearly, uh, this sound like a phone call, even.
What this was recorded on a phone or a really crappy device.
But did you hear that kind?
Did you hear how into this he is?
Now, I can see Mark Yosimat.
Yark Motion.
No shame.
No shame, Odey, the memc of.
I can see him steaming right now.
I think he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he he, he, he he, he he, he he.
You know what?
It's because I believe in this type of content.
This is a category of content that is absolutely going to explode.
We're already seeing that with, with Shadow Falls, of course, Scott Sigler.
is a fantastic job, it's, you know,
it's third audio novel by now.
And the seventh song I have listened to it,
I like it very much.
I think that this, it takes a while, you know,
it takes a while for something like this to catch on,
it takes a lot of effort, but the community
around these types of stories,
and this form of audio storytelling
is really, really big.
And I give them shit,
but Mark Yoshimura Namcoff actually
is doing some fantastic work in this area.
Outside of Shadow Falls,
I has a, where's my fucking latte?
And number one with a bullet,
please listen to this show.
And I stress this upon you,
not just because I play a cameo in it, of course.
I had him, it's you, it's her, it's who,
it's a so-fi Friday morning,
and not surprised, you're not here.
Very overcast,
there's some activity, but not much,
see, got to see her sitting in the hanger here.
Just to say that I have a feeling you said
on the podcast, we're going to be in San Francisco quite soon,
but if you're around next week,
journey next week,
know, the week after,
we're commencing about what will be,
about the tenths thereabouts,
we can have our helicopter here, our twin squirrel,
with our million and a half dollars worth
of train modeling laser scanner on it,
we'll be working out of here,
most of the week, serving some railway line
to our London.
And it's pretty cool equipment,
real casting edge technology stuff,
genuinely rocket science stuff.
And if you happen to be around,
come and have a look and we'll show you how it works,
and show you some of the things that it does,
but if you're in San Francisco,
it'll be warmer than here,
than I did say a bit dry anyway.
And look after stuff,
see you at the very front of these days, bye.
Yeah, you, thank you very much.
And I always appreciate you looking out for the Delta share,
the old girl, you know,
she needs a retention,
if you just give it a little pad once and again on there,
on the, on the, on the calling or something,
you know, just make her feel good.
I'd really appreciate that.
Unfortunately, I will be in San Francisco
when you have your twin squirrel,
which is a Eurocopter for those of you thinking,
what the hell is you gonna fly now?
And actually, you know, if, if you let me fly,
I do have a license, you know, for rotary aircraft.
If you let me give me some stick time,
I would even, I'd consider changing my plans.
What day is it today?
It's Friday.
But they Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday,
food about Friday and it's final fun to phone the week.
Now, my timing is all off today,
because I still have Jersey taught on the way.
And then I had a song that I really wanted to share with you guys today,
which I'm gonna play next.
That timing's off because the folks on serious sidelight,
channel 102, the star's channel,
will not be able to hear all of that.
In fact, you're pretty much gonna be kicked off of the show,
in about a minute from now.
So the timing's all off, but here's what I was trying to,
trying to work out for the final thought of the week.
And it's a very touchy subject, very difficult to discuss.
And I don't think I can really find the right words,
but I think the song will say a lot about my feelings about the topic.
You know, this, this Michael Richards video tape
that, of course, was captured by TMZ.com,
which is an America online company.
And as far as I know, it was played all over the U.S.
with the dreaded N word.
And I've said before that I'm really a little unclear
on how it happened that words and certain gestures became,
well, basically illegal and you just can't,
you can't do them, you can't talk them, you can't speak them.
You know what, I'm just gonna talk some shit
for like 13 more seconds while I raise my right hand
above my head, spread my fingers, and wave goodbye.
To all our friends on serious satellite radio,
I'll see you guys after the weekend.
Unfortunately, they're not gonna hear all the cool shit
and I'm glad you're hanging around.
So yesterday, we were having a conversation.
And by the way, I found it highly interesting
that although no one ever dares utter the N word,
anywhere.
This piece of video got aired on mainstream media
in many cases without bleeps over the N word.
And of course this, and I don't know if the controversy
around Michael Richard's video was that big outside of the U.S.
Of course it received mentions, but really,
don't think it was that much a topic of conversation.
Certainly not here in the U.K.,
but I know from talking with Patricia
that it hasn't been in the Netherlands either.
So that's kind of the just gives you an idea
that it's just not such a big deal.
Well, they don't care that much about what happened
in other countries.
See, I told you it's gonna be very hard
to get all this out right.
So anyway, so yesterday I'm having a conversation
and I realized that even in this private,
one-on-one conversation with someone
who I've known for, you know,
I've got, I don't know, 20 years
that we were talking about this video
and neither of us use the word.
And even in a descriptive form, just to say,
oh, you know, when Michael Richard said,
fill in the blank.
And I'm trying to, last night, I was trying to figure it out,
you know, is it because, you know,
if you use that word, even though this friend of mine knows
that I'm not racist, I grew up in the Netherlands,
you know, when the Netherlands wasn't racist,
I think they've changed a little bit over the years.
I went to school when I at West Virginia to university
and my roommate, I was an African-American kid
from Trenton, New Jersey.
And having grown up in the Netherlands,
this is about 50% white 50% black,
the Salem College, Salem, West Virginia.
And nothing really dawned on me.
I just kind of, you know, this was Thai, Thai Hamilton.
And what was kind of fun is me coming from Amsterdam
and him coming from Trenton and his own community.
When we both put out our boom boxes with cassette tapes back
in the day, we turned them on,
we basically had the same music,
which was very cool.
And we had an immediate bond.
And I hung out with a lot of his friends,
where my friends actually at school
because he had more people that had come along
with him from, or that he knew from the Trenton area.
And I, of course, coming from Amsterdam
had almost no one there that I knew or understood
where I was coming from at all.
And, you know, so totally oblivious to any color.
And then I thought that was it,
last week in San Francisco, I was watching something
on the biography channel, I think it was.
Or it was A&E biography, that's what it is.
And it was about Bill Cosby and about the Cosby family.
And there was a very interesting comment
about, you know, the setting of the Cosby show, of course,
which was, you know, how could this actually have happened
on television that we had the incredibly unlikely scenario
of a rich African-American upper class family,
a, was it a doctor husband, a lawyer wife?
But what they said in the, in this biography piece
was the American audience was completely colorblind.
They just love the Cosby's.
It was the family they wanted to be.
And when you think about that, it's absolutely true.
You know, and I cannot remember ever having a thought
crossing my mind about color.
You know, the Cosby's were fun.
You know, you love them.
You love the way they sat around and sang songs.
The colorblindness, yeah, I think there was absolutely true.
So what is it with this word that we don't even utter?
We just won't speak the word.
And therefore it's so incredibly evil
as Michael Richards has found out.
And I think the, you know, I think it comes from embarrassment
and whereas, as far as I know, the concept of,
give the slaves or the descendants of the slaves,
I'm just paraphrasing.
I don't even know if this is fucking true or not.
They deserve 40 acres in a mule.
Spike Lee always talks about that type of soon.
There's some grain of truth in it.
Well, I don't think that actually happened.
But crap, I talked all the way through the final thought
of the day music.
Well, let me just continue.
That, that of course didn't happen.
But instead, I think that we've given, you know,
we've decided that there's this word
that we will not utter ever in our lives
because it is the, it reminds us of the injustice,
the racism of, and this is only 40 years ago,
the racism was, you know, there was a lot of segregation
still in the United States.
And of course, all the way back to slavery
and that this is like our punishment
that we don't get to use a word.
And of course, it's completely inadequate.
It's completely inadequate as a solution
because that seems to be the only thing
when it comes to race these days.
All I hear about is this word you can't use.
And by the way, the word gets taunted
in the white man's face all the time.
Now Kanye West, number one hit record.
You know, African American culture in general uses this word.
But we're not allowed to use the word.
And I'm not, I don't give a shit
because I don't care about it.
I don't need to use this word.
But to me, why are we talking about it?
And why are we so worried about a fucking word
when the real problem is truly racism?
That's really what the issues are about.
And it just, yeah, I don't know, man.
It just really bugs me.
It seems like all the attention, all the focus,
that the media puts on racial issues
surrounds the use of language.
And that is just totally wrong.
Does this make any sense?
Because I feel like I'm a little bit lost.
But anyway, I'm going completely non-pod-safe
to express the point.
I'll even go to jail for this one
because it is the legend's TV wonder.
Listen to the words.
Let him burn into your mind.
That man got out of a ship on the first column of the strip.
He was a frontman.
Who will most of the trains keep on tracking that first thing
by the hell man.
We take to meet you all a lot.
To the magic colors, we have blue and white.
We are must be given, but see that we're different.
But with justice, not for all men.
This could be a repeat of it's time for us.
This promise made for all men.
Hot surgery.
The first one's success for me.
It's time for us to be given, but see that we're different.
We're must be given, but see that we're different.
With better nature, all are not.
To magic colors, we have blue and white.
We're must be given, but see that we're different.
But justice, not for all men.
This could be a repeat of it's time for us to be given.
This promise made for all men.
We're must be given, but see that we're different.
We're must be given, but let's see that we're different.
We must be given, but see that we're different.
What's the power of the show?
It's not the power of the singers.
It's not the power of the singer.
It's just physics the way I view it.
Okay.
Well, come on in, buddy.
Please, of course.
You think I was going to forget you?
You're on a black magic motion to rock this mother out.
You're on a piece.
Don't bend that girl to try to kill Belle out.
And let's all give up now.
To the heart is walking low.
You're just in time.
Yeah.
Just in time.
What's up, Adam?
It's Jersey Todd.
The official musicologist of the Cha Cha.
And I know where my segment usually is on the Daily Source Code.
Generally less than five minutes from now.
You're going to do that.
Click, click, click of your lighter.
And well, the song I have for you today may give you some pause.
Today, I've got a song about the E.V.s of drug used called the Pot song from Dan
Costello out of New York.
It's got a really, really great message.
But frankly, I can't get past the really green and leafy chorus that just makes you want
to come back for more.
I mean, I've heard this song a thousand times and it really sticks to your lungs.
I mean to your head.
Oh, whatever.
This is Dan Costello on the Daily Source Code.
Geez.
I wonder where I can get some splinter around here.
No, no, no, no.
Not for my coffee.
I just want to snort and see what happens.
I forget it.
Here's the song.
Dan Costello, the Pot song.
This is the last time I spoke about this whole cue.
Not sure how much the stuff is all I don't want up on the line.
And do it enough.
This is the last time I've screened my boat without a control.
I'm here and home on this waste my soul.
Yeah, we cover each other.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, oh not no, no no, no, take this morning and bring it to as high as I may sitting as long as I'm comfortable,
You have done it again, my friend. Thank you so much and thank you everybody for listening to my crap all week long
I'll be back next week
I leave for San Francisco Tuesday if all goes according to plan so Monday another show from the cottage
And I do really sincerely hope I can get the lady Patricia to join us
Hopefully well, of course, I hope she feels better, but if she still immobilize that you can't run it around and be doing other things
And then we can basically we can nail her down to the chair here in the studio
So have yourself a great weekend. I'll see you on Monday. Bye bye.
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT Pod Show Media Network
Control your part in the show