Find this podcast and others like it at the number one new media network,
patreon.com, better, faster, strong, stronger, and now with new mini-fresh sent.
This is Delta Sierra Charlie 502.
With the real potfathers stand up,
Ricky J. Ves, Adam Kerry, to potfathers, what the fuck?
You know, I think you have to fist fight to solve this problem. Ricky, where are you writing?
Is it too much for you to hand the Ricky?
Stand back and watch me shine, stand back and watch me shine, stand back and watch me shine,
stand back and watch me shine.
Don't worry, I've made a way and got my life inside.
We're changing for the moment when it will look longer high.
Steve, inside me is a spark and when I feel it's time,
I will release it from the hot stand back and watch me shine, stand back and watch me shine,
stand back and watch me shine, don't stand back and watch me shine,
I am everything, and I am nothing, I am yours, and you are mine,
I'm primitive, I have the power for it is don't you as I can shine,
so watch me shine, I will possess a second of your time, will be mine just for a while,
so stand back and watch me shine, stand back and watch me shine, stand back and watch me shine,
stand back and watch me shine.
Steve, inside me is a spark and when I feel it's time,
I will release it from the hot stand back and watch me shine,
stand back and watch me shine, stand back and watch me shine,
stand back and watch me shine.
stand back and watch me shine,
I'm so wish I could say it was pot safe, but we're not quite there yet.
This is a song that's been stuck in my head for the past couple of weeks, because it's
the theme tune to In the Attic.
That's the show we have going on now with the P-Tounsend, his better half Rachel Fuller,
Pete's Brother, Simon Townsend.
If you find it at In the Attic.com, of course, Pete and Rachel and Simon also have profiles
on Potch-O-Plus, BT Potch-O.com to be exact, but you can get to it from Potch-O.com or
from BT Potch-O, Rachel Fuller. Potch-O.com, Pete Townsend.potch-O.com, and that song is just,
it's been haunting me, and I sent an email to Rachel and I said, I really want to play
that on my show, knowing, by the way, that Michael Butler is hot on her trail to get some
first stuff up on the P-M-N, as well as, of course, he's going to go after some of the
who stuff.
But if you want some classic, unleashed, unhinged, who tracks acoustic, Pete Townsend with
the other celebrity musicians, you definitely want to check out in the Attic.potch-O.com.
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
Coming to you from, yeah, again, a very misty Northern California from the Curricando
and San Francisco.
I've got a lot of stuff we're going to talk about today, but before we do anything,
big news, and I'm trying to get a date on this.
This is from the AFP, I don't know what the AFP is.
It's a different type of news organization.
Anyway, the Hague, in-suit, no, that's not the word, in-so-scient, I've never seen this word
before my life, INS-O-U-C-I-A-N-T, in-so, despite police warnings, a Dutch group
was reportedly set to roll the world's biggest joint, sending the previous record for a
marijuana cigarette up in smoke.
I love it how those news guys write.
The world's largest joint will be a 500 gram, that's 17 ounces, meter long, 3.3 feet long,
monstrosity, rolled with cigarette paper and easily dwarfing the previous 100 gram winner.
The ANP news agency said, I guess, the AFP copies from the ANP, to beat the record, it must
be made entirely of marijuana, with no tobacco mix.
Afterwards, we'll light it up, predict the event organizer, Tice for Hay, who is hoping
his feet will land in the Guinness Book of Records.
Well, dude, Ricky Javez can get in there, I'm sure this can get in there.
The Dutch police are not amused, however, warning they will intervene if the joint surpasses
the five grams of marijuana allowed for consumption and selling the Netherlands.
I'll get arrested with you guys.
Let me know, please tell me.
Tell me one and where this is going to take place.
I need to be a part of it, and let me know on time because I'm going to be needing to
hotel room.
It's Bernie from Bernie's world.
Congrats on making it to 500 and beyond.
It's got to be hard being away from your family on Thanksgiving, but as the jersey dude
with a bunch of Europeans for family, Thanksgiving in the UK must be strangely unceremonial.
Well, you know that there is no Thanksgiving outside of the United States.
The Thanksgiving was done here because the people who left the UK, I think that there
may be some version of Thanksgiving in the UK, probably a good riddance.
Hope while you're here, you get together with some good friends for the day.
I have to tell you, hearing you, Leo and John and Conflict to sent my podcasting world
into a tailspin.
I mean, if the rumor girls were to jump in, well, that would make great video, but seriously,
this is about you.
Go on to it and set those dudes straight.
I love them, but sometimes they're just talking out their asses.
One more thing.
I don't know who this is, but stop fucking call in Giselle and it's all a happy Thanksgiving.
It wasn't you.
No, I didn't sound like you.
Hi, I do have a shoot, where is it?
I got another email from Giselle, I think.
Let me see.
Here it is.
Honey, this is from Giselle.
I haven't been able to listen to your show since Monday and I'm so bummed.
I missed the sound of your voice in my ears.
As promised, I'm going to get on a train tomorrow.
I come up there, but since I have to take a seven hour bus ride from Santa Barbara,
I probably won't get in until very late.
I'll call you when I get there if you're up who knows.
Just have my number.
Thank God.
But if not, I'll hang out and call you back in the morning.
I've never seen Frisco before, so maybe you can show me around.
Maybe you could be Frisco.
Yeah, I know I'm corny, but I'm also horny.
Love Giselle.
P.S.
I hope it's warm because I'm bringing it short skirt.
No, no, it's where long pants.
P.P.S.
Hope you like surprises because I have another one for you.
You know, now I'm really just curious.
At this point, I just really, I really want to meet this woman.
No girl.
I don't even know how old she is.
I do not repeat, do not want to meet the guy who called up and said,
stop fucking calling to Zell.
That I'm not into.
I do have plans for Thanksgiving, though.
I've been invited to hang out with some of Podgeo folks who are all getting together.
A lot of people from out of town out of state gathering has going to be a lot of fun.
I'm thinking I'll make my famous stuffing.
That's one thing I do.
I do know how to make stuffing.
Of course, I have to take it over there and actually stuff it into the turkey.
I guess we're having turkey.
I've got to find out more about that today.
So yeah, this twit thing.
It's pretty interesting.
Lots of people sending in comments.
Hey Adam, this is Chris from Naperville, Illinois.
And I was just listening to this week in tech number 77.
Thought you might be interested in checking it out around the 50 minute mark or so.
Well, Leo offered up 20 bucks if you would come on their show after hearing that.
You always download the episodes with the Vorac and I'm, but, of course, this was after he said you look like grandpa monster and were 63.
Although, I do think you're actually younger than Leo.
So I think it might be interesting if you just kind of shoot him an email and pop on the show.
Tell us.
Oh, you mean, oh, tell us dude.
Don't even act shortly.
I'm definitely younger than Leo Leport.
Yeah.
Well, we get to work it out.
I'll go on.
But I want to make sure to Vorac is on.
And I'm sure we're going to have a great time.
And I, but I definitely want to talk to that.
That's so called journalist who, uh, who was just kind of making fun of me after I was kind.
Then I have to speak with him.
Didn't I give him an interview?
Didn't we have a nice chat?
Uh, you know, it's very hard for Americans to understand if you've never been over to Europe.
If you've never been to the UK, it's very hard to understand what the media landscape is like.
Now, you have to understand that for many, many years, the only television you really could get was BBC 1, BBC 2.
Uh, and I guess ITV came along later.
But really, there's a very small amount of television stations out there is sad light now and there is some cable.
But a lot of people still get their signal straight off of the rabbit ears, although that is changing over the course of the next couple years.
But still, like you have relatively few commercial stations and nothing quite as localized that is commercial the way it is in the US.
We have, um, like, what is, uh, what does NBC over here in San Francisco?
I think it's channel 2 or 5.
I don't know.
I was in New York.
You have WNBC, it's channel 4.
You know, they're both commercial entities and they, in some form belong to the NBC network, but they also carry local programming.
You know, how many radio stations are there in the United States?
Several thousand radio stations in the UK.
Very similar situation.
For many, many years, it was basically the BBC.
I think they had one, two, three, and four.
I'm not even sure if they had that many for that long.
But that's all non-commercial.
It's a government, uh, which, of course, means a government owned owned by the people.
But there's, it's a non-commercial system.
And of course, very few people can actually be on the radio in the UK.
Now, um, lots more commercial stations have cropped up.
But, you know, they've, they've kind of run into the problem that all broadcasts, all traditional broadcast media are seeing is that people are.
Basically, um, leaving, um, you know, the program at Fermi version of what the BBC might do.
And they're filling up their iPods.
And of course, that's where podcasting sprouted from is that, uh, look, you know, we can make shows.
And you don't need a huge BBC tower in studios to, to create that.
You can just do it, uh, oh, cast blaster.
Oh, remind me to talk about that later on.
Cast blaster is a program that was made specifically.
So that, just about anybody could put together a show.
Just like the famous Chris Moiles in the United Kingdom.
Chris Moiles does the morning show.
I don't know how long he's been doing it.
Uh, and I know a couple of the, the previous morning guys.
And this is like the prestigious spot on radio in the UK is to do the, uh, the BBC breakfast show.
Is that what they still call it?
Um, we'll do the morning show on radio one.
And, uh, Christine, then I listen to it sometimes on our way in.
And, uh, I do not know Chris personally.
Um, but a lot of people sent me a link to his show this morning.
Now, uh, the BBC, um, they have a kind of like a, what are they call it?
Uh, it's the listen after the show service or whatever, or I missed it service.
And you can listen to, it's really funny because I, I was able to listen to the entire show from the
morning that aired, uh, on Wednesday and in the BBC on the BBC in the UK.
Uh, and, and you can do it through a kind of like their own streaming player.
And it's really interesting.
It must be because of the music rights.
And they do play the full, uh, music tracks.
It's, it's literally a, a rebroadcast of the show.
You can't rewind and you can jump ahead like by 15 minute increments or five minute increments.
So it's kind of kind of hard to, to cue this up.
But I just wanted you to hear.
Folks in the UK is really what I'm talking about.
I want you to hear.
Uh, the level of understanding of what podcasting is doing and what podcasting is amongst the mainstream media in the UK.
And I think a lot of people who are creating their own shows,
whether they're audio or video are really going to be smiling when they hear that.
Really are competition because I guess if, you know, we're competing for ears is what we're doing.
We're competing for ears.
Some are competing for eyeballs.
Uh, the competition is fairly fucking clueless.
Let's just listen to this bit.
This is the Chris Moile show from this morning.
I mean, you've only moved around the court.
I mean, we've got two streets one.
No.
But 10 minutes, right?
And that's is, I guess, this morning crew or whatever.
And then I'm just coming back in.
There's about a minute left to play on the Justin Timberlake track.
And I walked past Michelle the cleaner.
He went out to take a dump during the Justin Timberlake track.
And he came back and he walks past the cleaner who apparently is a foreigner.
Because he makes it a bit of a joke about that as well.
Is he not finished yet?
No.
He's very thorough.
Right, thorough.
In all fairness, you know, I've seen I swear.
And I saw this for the day.
I saw a cleaner upstairs by one of the desks with a duster, right?
Kind of waving it over a desk like that.
Just kind of like, I can't fast forward through this piece.
Unfortunately.
That desto next one.
They didn't actually clean it.
They just kind of, the breeze from the loft of the Justin.
Come on.
Get to your story, Chris.
Some papers, but that's about it.
Yeah.
Well, as Michelle's very thorough.
And he also has to do a smoking rate, which is at his grace when we get in the morning.
I don't know what Colin Murray doesn't there at night time.
But there's tab ends.
I think they fighting there.
I think he has a wrestling match with his pretty.
Ah, I see.
They got to talk about the night guy in your typical morning show radio banter.
The 10 minutes before you guys on the air just to get him all fired up.
Apparently he's right.
Fight me.
What?
He's moved apparently.
Yes, he has.
He's now on a 10 o'clock at night.
Yeah, he's moved to week day evenings.
Come on.
That's right.
So anyway, Michelle the cleaner says to me, I'm just walking past the mic.
You're right.
I've got to get back into the studio because my record ends.
But he wants to ask me just a very quick question.
She has a very quick answer.
Chris.
I'm just a Chris podcast.
He doesn't ask you questions.
He just says words.
And then you have to work out what he's on.
Well, podcast.
Nice wanker.
Don't make fun of me the way people talk, man.
Especially people that clean your ship because they're also the people that will piss
in your coffee, okay?
Yeah, and I'm there halfway through the door.
You know when you walk in, so when you go, what about it?
You stay down under the podcast.
Yeah?
What about it?
What what's that?
What?
What is it?
What does that mean?
Oh, it's like an internet.
I want you to listen really carefully.
So I think when by the time I get to the end of this story, which he's drawing out,
you'll realize that the person who is cleaning for Chris Moiles understands extremely well
what a podcast is.
And it's probably listening to, it's probably listening to Pacific Coast Hellway
on his, on his iPod.
He's probably trying to tell Chris Moiles that he's listening to something more entertaining than what he's doing.
You download it.
What is it?
Jingle.
No, it's, oh, I don't know.
It's a show.
Anyway, okay.
That was it.
So Dave, you know, when you try and get your head round what podcast style had to download,
it's similar to this.
It's something you'd out.
It's a show you download.
Okay?
Brilliant.
I understand what a podcast is.
And I know that it goes onto your pod machine and stuff.
Put me in this.
You're pod machine.
It's because they can't say commercial brand names.
They can't say iPod.
Same category.
I understand.
Well, yeah.
He understood it straight away.
Yeah, so do I.
How many podcasts have you downloaded ever?
Ever?
Yeah.
None.
There you go.
Dumb.
Are you a podcast to listen to on the computer screen?
Right.
At work.
By clicking on download the podcast.
That guy switched on.
Don't listen again, though.
That's good.
Listen again.
I used to.
I used to download Adam Curry's podcast.
Did you?
Yeah.
He's the pod father.
Easy.
Yeah.
He's pretty.
They they reckon that he's the man who invented podcasts.
Really.
Yeah.
Which is kind of like.
Well, I don't know how you can invent it because it kind of just happens.
Yeah.
But now he's kind of creditors as I was the first one.
And he's to do this.
I don't know if he still does it probably still does.
Like a review of really bizarre podcasts around the world.
And one of the first ones I've heard was extracts from a podcast which a pilot does.
He's an airline pilot.
And they he recorded, basically, the conversations that airline pilots have.
Because you know, when you're.
As you know, because we're all trying to find a source.
Well, yes.
Some of us actually are Chris.
If you're a pilot and you're flying to New York, one show up in the air.
All right.
Anyway.
So that was really interesting to me because I know exactly what show that was.
And that was pod finder.
And that was the I think the very first pod finder that included come fly with me with Joe
Deon.
And I truly believe the Chris Moiles listened to.
You know, one or two podcasts when you heard about it and he's not interesting.
King because I have the transmitters.
And he hasn't listened since it sounds like some of his crew there.
Listen, listen more regularly to podcast podcasts.
I should say Chris, I just want you to know one thing.
And I know that this will get to you and I know that.
I know you'll hear it.
Uh, about.
Um, was it just before we launched with the BT pod show.com.
So that your boss, um, called us begging and literally begging to have BBC radio
one content included on BT pod show.com.
And it was pretty interesting because at that time we were literally
considering, uh, do we want to put any mainstream stuff on BT pod show.com?
Do we want to put anything that's mainstream?
Any mainstream podcast in the UK onto BT pod show.com.
And, uh, and honestly, we had already decided to do it.
Uh, because we feel that, you know, why would we want anyone to not be able to get to something
if you're making it available?
But, uh, you may not understand Chris.
Well, your bosses do man.
And maybe just maybe you should take a look at your ratings.
Hi, my name's Bob Bulls.
And I wonder if I could talk to you.
I'm, uh, producing some content on a commercial basis.
And I wonder if there's something that I could speak to.
Would you be so kind of to call me on O7?
So here's the guy who, uh, uh, yeah, yeah, yeah, I don't want you to hear the phone number.
Okay.
Hold on, listen to this.
Um, and the content is evolving a very high profile comedian.
Um, I'll tell you more of you call me thanks very much.
Chris, that's what's happening.
Okay.
That's what's happening in your backyard son.
Hi, Steve Web here.
Merry Christmas.
James Cooper and I are having a lot of fun putting the life spring admin calendar together for you.
And this very short podcast is to ask you to participate.
Yes, you can be a part of the show.
I know that people from all around the world will be hearing this and that of all those people.
Many of you speak languages other than English.
And many of you know how to say Merry Christmas in other languages.
It would be just fantastic if you would record yourself saying Merry Christmas in a language other than English.
Record an MP3 for me and send it to Steve.livesprayingatgmail.com or phone my listener comment line at
plus one two zero six three five zero call.
You can identify yourself where you're from and what language your Merry Christmas is in.
Come on, represent your country.
And thanks for joining in.
I'm Steve Web, the host of the life spring family podcasts and co-host with James Cooper of the life spring admin calendar.
And we'll be talking to you on December 1st.
Alright, Steve.
Good deal, man.
I'm sure people will send that in.
I seem to remember that the host of this show speaks Dutch.
Yeah, for all the cast faced in a colloquial new year.
Some really stupid happened.
You really know you're growing when this happens.
So, you know, how long have I been working on cast blaster?
How long have I been using cast blaster?
How long have we been talking about it?
Cast blaster, of course, a piece of software that enables you to create podcasts really professional podcasts
because you've got the same stuff as any...
You've got the same stuff as Chris Moiles, basically.
You're body weight may vary.
And you can find it at castblaster.com.
And we've made this thing very slick.
It integrates completely with the podcast delivery network.
When you sign up to do a show at Pod Show, you can use cast blaster just one program.
And it'll record your show.
You're information, your show notes.
Any other types of data you want to...
You want to have up there.
And you just hit, you know, publish.
And it sends it all up to Pod Show.
And it puts it right into your feed and does everything automatically.
So, we've actually been working on that for over a year.
Mike, for state, is the only developer on cast blaster is now working on a video version.
And yeah, actually, you can see that at testing123.podshow.com.
And he's doing some cool shit.
He's got, you can plug in multiple USB cameras.
Yes, it's here, it was blended up.
And you can switch back and forth and you can start to clip.
So, it's going to be fantastic.
I've not used an alpha version of it yet myself.
But something really messed up happened.
I want to apologize to Mike and set the record straight.
And also, you know, that's why I do a lot of the stuff in the daily source code is because people
the company listened to it and they learned about it as well.
So, yesterday we had a problem.
I noticed it early as I was, you probably saw that the show was up later than normal.
Because every time I tried to upload with cast blaster, it would throw an error message.
And it would say, you know, whoops.
Not working.
So, of course, I immediately called...
I'm just looking for the email here.
I immediately called the Andrew and said, oh, dude.
Now, we got to fix this.
And, of course, if it happened to me, then it happened to other people as well.
Oh, no.
And I can't find the email.
I thought I'd copy the right email, but I didn't do it.
So, Mike sent me a note this morning.
You know, if there's a problem with podshow plus,
at the bottom of every single page, there's a link.
One is for listener support.
If you're having issues getting shows,
listening to shows, understanding however it works.
And then there's one for podcaster support.
And it goes right into a real tracking system.
So, you get a ticket number as a sign.
So, we can track it and make sure the problem was resolved.
So, apparently, a ticket went in for this very problem.
Because people are using the cast blaster.
And, you know, when it doesn't work for me,
he's not going to work for lots of people.
And the answer that came back from podshow podcaster support
was, and I quote,
as cast blasters, a third party application.
And it appears that something is wrong with this set up
of this third party application.
You will need to contact the folks at cast blaster directly.
Fortunately, they are a great group of folks.
I'm very helpful.
We apologize that we were unable to assess what does this
with troubleshooting third party applications.
We appreciate your understanding.
And, of course, Mike is like,
what the hell is that?
First of all, the nice folks is one guy.
Well, there's people on the forums like Barry,
and there's people who help moderate the forums.
But it's, you know, we go on the product.
So, anyway, it's working now.
And this is also, you know,
and it's so cool to be able to be in San Francisco,
even if it's, you know, like a weird vacation short week.
There's a whole bunch of small things.
You just, you know, this is why I'm not a big fan of working
over long distance.
Because there's so many small nuance.
There's so many little things.
You just miss, you know.
Yeah, everyone knows exactly what they're doing.
And, and, you know,
and it's a process that's been done for 30 years.
Yeah, maybe it'll work very well at long distance.
But now I can, now I can feel all of the sounds like,
oh, now I know why I'm not seeing a lot of cast blaster promotion
in places where I'd expect it like garage.podshow.com
is because they probably think it's a third party application
and it has a very low priority,
which, by the way, also isn't right
because if people are making shit that works with our shit,
which smell on that shit.
So anyway, apologies to Mike and everyone
who's been working so hard on cast blaster.
And, as I said, it is working again,
so that, of course, is the good news.
Love to hear from you.
Little low on the phone calls now in the US.
Plus 4.4.
Duo 7.
6.8.
1.
3.7.
5.3.
Plus 4.4.
Duo 7.
6.8.
1.3.
7.5.
3.
And, for those of you in the United States of America,
I just want one, two, one, six, two, five,
six, three, five, seven,
last one, two, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven.
Andrew Grommer can't stop singing that one.
Hey, Adam, it's Mark Yoshimoto, Namcov,
and I just want to tell you,
and the Daily Source Code listeners,
that the Shadow Falls experience in second life
is now open.
Remember, a few months ago,
when you said, wouldn't it be cool
to build the town of Shadow Falls in second life?
Well, guess what?
The sexy second life siren Brittany Mason,
put together a cracker jack team of builders,
and they did just that.
They built the whole town.
I mean, it's really cool.
It's like the houses,
and all these buildings,
like the library,
and the police station,
and the diner,
and these woods,
like this really thick forest
that surrounds the whole town on Pacho Island.
It's really creepy.
It's really super cool.
I mean, you got to see it.
It's amazing.
So, first off,
really great idea on your part.
But I wanted everybody to know
that the Shadow Falls experience
is not just this sim,
where you can just walk around
and look around and just hang out.
No, it's more than that.
It's a game.
Tell you what,
I'm going to pitch it to you right now
as if I were at some Hollywood studio.
As if I had like a meeting on the Foxlot,
and I was pitching this to a big movie producer.
Okay, okay.
Hold on a second.
Let me get in my big movie producer role then.
Okay.
Yeah.
Mark, yeah.
You shouldn't mind an echo.
What's up, buddy?
I'd be like,
Adam, okay.
Picture this.
Imagine,
missed meets the Da Vinci code.
Get the fuck out of my office.
That's how it would go, Mark.
You go into this game,
and they're these clues.
They're like riddles.
And when you solve these riddles,
they give you little pieces of the puzzle.
And keys that open like secret doors
and combination codes that open up secret boxes.
Let me think.
This idea is getting interesting.
Maybe you should lay down on it on my couch here.
Mark and put on a wig.
Yeah.
Could you just put that dress on that I have over there?
And inside some of these boxes,
some of these treasure chests.
Our head in little pieces of the tragic history of what happened
in Shadow Falls 300 some years ago.
And the only way you could piece together this prequel
is if you solve all the riddles and get all the pieces of the puzzle.
And you do this while you're searching all over Shadow Falls
in second life.
Pretty damn cool, huh?
We'll check out how podcasting ties into it.
Some of the clues come in the form of little audio bits
that I'm going to drop as little mini episodes into the Shadow Falls feed.
And of course, it's like the answers to most of these riddles
will be easier to solve if you know your season one of Shadow Falls.
For instance, I'm going to give you audio clue number one.
Here you go, you ready?
Yeah.
It begins in the woods where Jacob was done by the big sign.
Karen's friend gives you clue number one.
Let me repeat that.
It begins in the woods where Jacob was done by the big sign.
Karen's friend gives you clue number one.
Let me think.
I know who Karen's friend was, but what was on the big sign?
Chris Moiles is a wanker.
Game on Adam, can you figure out the riddle of Shadow Falls?
Well, you can.
If you go to the Shadow Falls experience.
Only it's second life at secondlife.com.
And of course, you know, I want everybody to know everybody you can hear this.
The second life is free.
You don't need any money to get a, you know, an account and the log on and to go to pod show island
and experience Shadow Falls like you never have before.
And while I have your undivided attention, just want to let you know that my new podcast novel number one
with a bullet is on the front page of iTunes.
Well, at least it was today while I was recording this.
And thank you, CC Chapman, for pointing that out to me.
And I'm kind of hoping you do me a solid and play the trailer for it right now.
Thanks.
Adam, I appreciate it.
And I'll see you in second life where I'm hoping your avatar doesn't try to grab my ass.
Okay.
I'll catch you later.
Yeah.
I'm so happy that worked out that project.
Brittany Mason has done an incredible job.
I wanted to get on.
Yes.
I'm.
I'm at consmen locked out.
And I have to call the Linden Labs and then whenever I call, you know, I'm like,
Okay, today I'm going to call.
I'm going to get my account on locks.
I can go in and look at shit.
And then you know, it's like some worm has been unleashed and you can't get in pain in the ass.
So I guess everything's up now.
But I know Brittany Mason did a phenomenal job on that.
And it's really interesting when you do an episodic series like this.
So what do we do six episodes of Shadow Falls for the season one?
So we want to do season two, which, of course, is all in the plan in the works.
But a lot of people have already heard the six episodes.
And you know, what we're doing now is we're really working on this fantastic,
you know, piece of work for new people who come into the network.
And there are new people who are learning about podcasting every day.
Just imagine if Chris Moiles could actually hear this.
If we actually got through to him through his thick skull.
You know, so that's what all these things are for.
Now there is also quite a community around the back story and Mark has been doing these
very interesting projects to follow.
I love the fact that it's branching out now into into second life.
So that's I think that's a very interesting way of tying people in.
Because as you know, in second life, you can't do it on volume.
He really can't.
All right.
So this other show Mark's talking about number one with a bullet,
which is, was it a pod novel?
God, this sounds really good.
He already has like a writer's prologue.
I guess there's what it's called up on the feed for number one with a bullet.
And then he sends me this promo.
This teaser to play for you.
And it is the guy who reads this and I'm not mistaken is he is the guy that does all those movie trailers.
You know, the in a world where women wear comfortable shoes.
I'm really insanely jealous of it.
Have a listen.
Top 10 Hitman face off.
You know, last man's standing winner take all contest being bet on by some of the world's richest men.
The only rule is to stay alive.
And for Johnny Dane, it means finding out that getting out of the business doesn't mean getting out of the game.
From the mind of Mark Yoshimoto Namcoff, the creator of Shadow Falls comes number one with a bullet.
The free serialized audio book guaranteed to put your adrenaline in the crosshairs.
Get on target at number one bullet dot pod show dot com.
Oh, man.
I love that guy's voice.
Because when he says something, you're like, damn, I got to go listen to that show.
There's just no two ways about it.
The guy with the heavy voice told me to do it.
And to do some to me, Mark, please.
I want to get a couple of those for myself.
Some pod save music to wind it up for today.
My friend Jimmy Golding, who's true character from London.
It's the rocket to the moon.
We're in making a lost food drama.
We share the midnight feast.
Look the space machine has landed.
We shot it and we screamed.
We want to rock it.
To the light of the moon.
We share the midnight feast.
We want to rock it.
We've made astronauts with so much and steps on the bed.
We said I love so funny.
With the gulfing gold on my head.
And we stayed at night to watch the moon.
Making history.
We're in making history.
There's a guy I got to hang out with more.
Jimmy Golding.
He's just exactly what you think of a really hit British artist.
He's a great star.
I was like six years old, five or six years old watching Neil Armstrong on the moon.
I just want to clear up because I think there was some misinterpretation.
I'm not going to say anything about the national health care service in the UK.
Listen to this comment.
I'm not going to play the whole thing, but this guy told me it's understood what I was saying.
I'm going to get picked up on this book.
You really need a big careful of what you say.
I don't mean that as a threat.
I just mean get you fuck script before you start having a go at an organisation that is the pride of the country.
I don't even know what I'm going to say.
That's what I just want to get rid of.
I thought I was clear.
This is what we were talking about in the United States for years and never been able to get together.
I love that fact.
It's a very difficult thing to put into place as we've already seen.
I found out that it would take three weeks of agonizing pain for my daughter to be walking around with her.
Perhaps cartilage floating around her knee before she could even get an MRI to see if there was cartilage in her knee.
Let alone before she can get the operation.
Those are the drawbacks of a healthcare system because despite the fact that there are MRI machines standing empty.
And it's just a matter of money, which of course is what it always comes down to.
But I don't know, please don't let us misunderstand me.
I love the fact that people under 16 or over 16 if you're still in school, they get free healthcare.
Are you kidding me? This is fucking phenomenal.
All I'm saying is there's always a lot of complaints because people die.
And then it makes great headlines.
Oh, the guy had to wait three weeks and he died.
So it sucks, but no, please don't get me wrong.
I love the fact that there's a national healthcare system.
And I wish I was smart enough to figure out how something like that could work better in the UK and just work it all anywhere else.
No, no, don't get me wrong.
So he has not like three minutes of comment, but I just want to say, no, I totally appreciate the NHS.
I think it's a fascinating system.
Something that we should look at here in the US for a number of reasons for its success as well as for its failures.
I was just saying that people bitch and moan about this stuff.
I mean, you can't win. If you look at the newspapers in the US or look at the newspapers in the UK,
whenever it comes to healthcare in the US, you read people are dying because we have no healthcare.
And the UK, you read people are dying because we have shitty healthcare.
And of course, it's not true. Any healthcare is better than no healthcare.
Do you guys all, is it, is dental also included in the NHS?
I bet it is. I'll bet it is.
You can't even, you know, that I can't even ensure Patricia privately for, for dental.
I mean, once you're, I can't do it for myself anymore. Once you're over 40, forget about it.
You know, because that's when shit just keeps falling out of your head.
It's also a myth, by the way, that English people's teeth are bad.
That may have been two generations ago, but you should look at Christina's new boyfriend's teeth.
Oh, man. What a pretty boy that is.
Hey, everybody. So tomorrow, thanksgiving.
I'll be celebrating here with a couple of folks from Podshow.
You may be on your way. You may be on the plane listening to this as you're going to go see family.
Whatever you're doing, be safe, be happy, enjoy the time with your loved ones.
I'll probably be doing a show. I don't know if I'll do one tomorrow, but Friday for sure.
Maybe not the same time since I don't have to hit any satellite windows.
And I'd have to say that I'm thankful, obviously, for the health of my family.
And for everyone being strong through an interesting year.
And I really want to thank everybody who was participating in this thing we call podcasting.
If it'll be called that forever I doubt, but there's something really special going on.
And it's for people who are making people who are bacon and people who are just listening to them, people who are enjoying them.
And thank you all for sending me stuff and helping me out and keeping me going.
Oh, yeah.
Please, I'm thankful for people who make pig ass joints that are going to try and set world records.
I'll talk to you later guys. Bye-bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this pod cast and we're great ones like it on the high performance pod cast delivery network from Pod Show and line-white networks.
I love it.