This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
The show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy.
Delta Sierra Charlie 3-9 or 7.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Uh-huh.
Was all we ever cared about?
We had it, we had it all.
Oh, I'm talking about the good time times.
Drinkin' all day.
Drinkin' all night.
Dance by the firelight.
Come on.
Drinkin' all night.
I'm talking about the simple times.
Thinkin' everything Ryan.
Drinkin' all night.
Drinkin' every day,
Thinkin' all night.
Drinkin' all night.
Come on, we're ready.
Show me your numbers with theining
All that tell me
What you know you know
You know that tell me
All about how
You know that
I'll be thinking about you night
Oh
Thank you
Darling
my
I'll be thinking about you night
Dang
I love you
Now, even though these headphones cause such a grin on
Daily source code 395. I love the trishes new headphones
Everybody how you doing welcome to the Daily Source code coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey
known as Gilford. This is the Daily Source code from curry cottage and
Very very busy today
Yeah, first of all
We're still a bit messed up when it comes to timing just because of the eight-hour time difference between San Francisco and here and the flight back, et cetera
yesterday
You know, I did the show and it really it did wipe me out
I have to say because you know, it's not like you just I make it sound
Pretty simple. I hope at least that's how I want it to come across
But preparing any show takes at least an hour of going through whatever there is and of course
You know, I had a big backlog of email and voice mail and feedback and audio attachments, et cetera
So living kind of within Gmail for an hour and a half then doing the show then making sure it's uploaded and then I'm like
Okay, I'll sit down and I'll all up fire up the dashboard
Which is how man when you guys see this you're gonna love it. It's our
Well, what you would call a player, but it doesn't really suffice to say it's a player as a part of pod show plus it really all of your
Your channels you can create your own channels that will roll out one after another
So you know, I listened to my news channel and which includes video from rocket boom and includes geek brief TV and it includes
the latest it's a half-hour show from the BBC
The New York Times front page Zifrank of course, and so you know
I'm sitting in the big green thing which is this reclining chair would I've had for ages ever since so oh
Man, we've had this thing since think new ideas in New York. I just realized we've had it for 10 years and it's pretty beat up
But oh man, I know many many a server admin who was slept in this chair
During a late night in New York
So I'm lying there and with a laptop on my lap and listening to the podcast and kind of browsing through you know some other
Backtated emails and and then I wake up like two hours later
You know with my my lap completely on fire because these power books get so incredibly hot
But I was so still I late so still
It didn't slide off or anything. It just stayed there stuck right on my lap and
Then there was another hour so that I dosed off during watching TV with the folks downstairs
So I was pretty messed up and decided to stay up a little bit actually
reawoke
Around I don't know 1231
Stayed up for another hour and then finally went to bed got up this morning around nine
So we're trying to you know, or I'm trying to manage myself back into the right time schedule
now the in laws have been here for
Almost two weeks now and of course they took care of the house and the animals are most importantly Christina
While Patricia and I were on our world tour
So as and you know Patricia's dad is a very accomplished
musician arranger
band leader and he and he Patricia both have a tremendous love for a big band sound combos
You know the the old jazz
Old school music which I love of myself as well of course
So I surprised them and we have tickets tonight to see Sinatra
Which is the show that we've the the musical that we've discussed on the on the Charlie several times
And so everyone's really excited
But of course it starts at 730. It's a London's West End so we got to leave the house at five
You know, which is right around the time San Francisco wakes up and we've got all these initiatives underway and then the team is coming in next week for
You know to get Pod Show UK rolling in the so it's just so much happening
So I'm gonna let the comments lead a little bit today and and I played brother love
Which you heard at the start of the show
Not without reason, of course, bro low being still one of the most played artists on the Podsaic music network of all times
But he also just had a concert in New York City and
Unfortunately we had just left the city couldn't be there to witness the show
But leave it up to the Charlie listeners to send in a report
Hey Adam this is Jeff Hines with a Friday night dance party podcast just got back from the
Brother love New York City show here and it was fantastic the place was rock and it was packed
It was out of sight. Yeah, it was above a strip club, but you know what?
Just because there was stripers downstairs doesn't mean that wasn't loving going on upstairs
With brother love and the people were crazy
It was great to see all the podcasters and all the
Podcas listeners and really really rocked the house. It was a great show and
Brother love put on a great show
So I give a shout out to brother love and all the podcasters and all the listeners because you know what it's working
What you're doing is working out there and people are loving it. They're digging it. They're coming together. It's a great community
And it was fabulous when brother love played summertime
Everyone was singing the whole song man. It was great the place was rocking
So you know, it's really working and the power of podcasting the power of the pod sitting
Isn't that work and the power of brother love so keep it coming and this is Jeff Hines
I'm the Friday night dance party with a report on brother love show here in New York City
Keep on podcast and peace out. Bye
All right, yeah, thanks, but he also called back later and said that
Believe it or not ladies
We're actually throwing their panties on the stage towards brother love. I believe it hands down
I believe it. Yeah, it really is working. It really is and
If if you haven't been over there yet go to music.podshow.com
Which is the pod safe music network and you can buy many of the tracks that are up there
We have like 30,000 or something that are already within the I think it's 30,000 within the network and
Everything that gets played on the daily source code as we ramp up towards our public data release is is made available for purchase
Through the PMN and
It's 99 cents per track nine cents goes for the actual transaction and the rest of the money goes to the artist
So you're supporting them big time when you purchase through there and of course
You can always re-log into your account
Download the song again. There's no DRM. It's an MP3. You can give it away. You can put it on all your devices
And if you do give it away as the person if they like it to go ahead and purchase their own copy
That's kind of the system that we're trying to cobble together here, but it seems to be working sales are actually happening. Love it
every single day I log into
our
Podshow plus beta site, which is still closed beta although I think we have
I'm just gonna guess. I'll say we have close to between four and five hundred people probably on it now
So this thing is really alive and it's it's populated even though the page is don't surface publicly yet, which you know
We only know what's gonna happen when when everything goes public
But we're getting very very close to the release and I'm kind of happy that there were letting people in
Lots of people into participating in the beta
Particularly you know, do we chose to get a lot of developers in so there's a lot of
excellent feedback but also a number of the or I think all of the
Podshow podcast network podcasters are in they're using the system if not just to upload through the podcast delivery network
but also and to really enjoy
The well, there's so many different facets to it. So every day I log in it seems like there's a new feature
There's something new happening and it's it's getting really really cool
Hey Adam, this is Joe from a guy girl in a bottle just wanted to give you a quick call
Say welcome back to Sonic California. Hope you have a good time down there. Oh, dude. This is how this is how behind
Hey my email and feedback. Sorry about that. Bonneray. Hey. I just finished using task blaster for the first time to post up a show to the
PDN get the whole integration and
Wow that stuff totally rocks save me a ton of time. I really like the way it does the show notes and everything and pretty jazz about that
So pass along to the developers not sure if you want to put that out on the deathcast
But that is really great. And I can't wait to see the response from the other podcasters
We'll take it their hands on some of these tools on another note if you in percussion would like to go do some wine tasting or
Partition while you're hard at work
Let us know would be more happy to
Send you a couple of recommendations in the area a couple of quick drives not too far from San Francisco
Talk to you soon have a great time
Cursus curses
See now I'm only hearing this now. We could have got
curses I say curses I tell you
Man I hate it when I'm behind I've had to go you know I've been deleting Gmail's again because my mailbox is full
I just you know
I got a lot of listeners and I really love all the feedback. I just don't know how to handle it all
I mean, well creating more time like like Joe just
Like he just mentioned you know I literally save 45 minutes in my normal production process now
uploading to the podcast delivery network all the show notes go up automatically everything flows through and it does make a tremendous amount of difference
You know longer you know doing your ID three tags and all that stuff separately
So yeah, I can't wait until everybody gets their hands on that
That's for sure also I'm trying to kind of build a bridge over to the dev cast. I want the dev cast to be much a geeky here
I want to stuff to be talked about in there this way beyond my comprehension which I think will make a good mix where you know I can just
You know kind of go along for the ride for the flow and and interject some of my questions which coming as a user of technology will probably be helpful
um
But so I'm still gonna you know
You know put specific feedback about a lot of this beta stuff on the on the Charlie because it will pertain to all of us in the future
I am this is a Joel Bench from the thinking and driving podcast the thinking and driving calm
I've got a comments for the dead cat
Recently had my golden ticket and I've had a moment to
To poke around on the pdn data
It's great. I love the community seal. It's very cool
I do not have a question though
It seems that I had my podcast and I can then only
Add new episodes through the pdn now. I do understand that the the owner that have a unified platform for producing and and consuming
But I still want my podcast home to be my my personal blog which is on a
Wordpress blog and I'm using podcast
My
Right, and this is I remember this now so the whole thing starts to crap out because of a cell phone connection
Which is real bummer, but I did want to just respond to this briefly
This is a very good question
And it and it's really
Hmm
I don't know what category to put this under, but I think that there is a disconnect between
Podcasts and web logs and and there's also a connect between the two because
Really the way to create the easiest way to create an RSS feed or a podcast feed
Is by making a weblog and so that was kind of the default and has been the default for quite a while
Listen, you know, so here's how you set up a podcast you get a weblog that I put an RSS feed and then you know
You put your show notes into the blog post and then out the back end poop say
Show notes
Version of show notes with the attachment in the enclosure for the file so it can automatically get download and put on your iPod
Where else you designated to go?
But there I really feel that you know the weblog part of it is such a small part of what I really want on my my podcast home as as you describe it
And that's why we've brought in so many developers
To start working on different modules that are appropriate to what we're doing with media
I'm not just audio of course, but also video
And how that all fits into a social media network
So, you know my space is a social network
Facebook is a social network, but those are really for pictures and text and
How do you really connect
When it comes to sharing media and not just links to different blog posts or different pages
Excuse me since sale this since sale moment brought to you by geese radio
Since I'm not getting paid for them, I know as well do something with that moment, right?
Now, I also use a WordPress weblog for
For curry dot com and I often cross post the show notes of each individual show to curry dot com so
I've put out a challenge which is not a very big one. I don't think but you know we intend to be completely open
With with with with with with the PDN we've got all kinds of API so uploading your show doesn't have to work through cast blaster
It can work through a web interface. We have a flash interface and you'll be able to if you're if you have an audio program
It will be very simple for the developer of that audio program to
You know just add a little button that says upload to the PDN and it'll do that from there as well
So there's all different ways that you'll be able to get stuff in
But I like the idea of having a little widget or what we call a module
That will actually take the show notes of an individual episode and post them onto a weblog because I wouldn't mind just like
Flickard does you know you have a flicker picture and you want it on your weblog and you can say
Post this to my weblog so I think that'll be a cool feature to have so that's something that we are working on
But I have a feeling that when you really see the full power of the PDN and the fact that you can map your own
Domain name to it
So yeah, you can so I have a daily source code is now on the podcast delivery network
You can't see it because it's still a close data
But I fully intend to map daily source code.com to that individual page which is of course
The real way to control all of your content
By the way, does anyone know how if you want to be a registrar if you want to be you know like like network solutions or like go daddy
Is that a tough process?
I've been thinking about doing that for a while
I'm just not sure if they have all those positions been dulled out
I mean, I just really don't have the energy to dive back into I can or whatever the
Organization is called
the figure out who can become a registrar how that works if anyone can send me a pointer it would be
Well, it would be highly appreciated. Hi Adam. I have to disagree with the caller yesterday who suggested that you
Shouldn't have even mentioned the closest problem you are having with the audio on Monday for two reasons first
I laughed quite a bit
While I really felt your pain
I couldn't help laughing at how mad Patricia was getting you by laughing just as much as me
Once again, podcasting's best reality show
Second if you didn't mention it. I along with a few hundred otherwise asses would have been yelling at you via email
Hey dude, what the hell you're doing ever here of a windscreen?
The sad part is that you probably didn't hear the incredible job I did
of fixing your missing of the closing of the satellite window
I skillfully edited in an old announcement of what was coming up next on serious
serious listeners never knew that you ranted right on through the end of the serious window
I am forever your not so humble servant p-dub the satellite repair
Well, that deserves a shout out P-dub
Everybody sing along with P-dub's favorite song the satellite repair man coming after you
What's he going to do he'll picture missed in sessions and answer questions too
There's nothing in the universe and you can't do for you a satellite repair man
Woo
That's right
I wish a satellite repair man of your own for everybody listening to the show. There's nothing like having a great satellite repair man
Who can fix everything in the mix?
By the way, yeah, I got so I know the people listen on the delayed basis. I know people are weeks behind on the show
And by the way, I I really appreciate it when people want to catch up
Man, you can also just decide to drop a whole bunch of stuff. You know, just catch up
That's very interesting. I mean, is that because you don't want to don't want to miss
the continuing threads and continuing themes? I mean, do you do the same with traditional radio? Do you know what?
Of course, you I guess you can't really
I thought that was a non-sensical question, but in my mind, you know, I miss episodes of all my favorite podcasts all the time and I really go back
To catch up. What I do is just listen to the most recent one and see where we're at and that of course is an issue with my time
But anyway
Pdub said something really interesting there. He said, you know, this is a what a very nice compliment podcasting's best reality show
What happened on episode 395? I just want you to know that I'm not
Cognizant of what's going on. I do know what's happening and I think that show was really me pushing myself to the limits
And this was not because of just the sound it was because it was hampering the way I could communicate
I couldn't actually talk into the microphone the way I want to I had to think about other things
while talking and and I just won't do that anymore. I refuse
I've done this for years with mainstream media
You know the sound is shit on the station today because you know there's some other jock decided to to tweak the processing, you know
Yeah, so what you do is you you bear down you grin it bear down bear grin bear down on it
Whatever it is, you know you just shut up and move right
I hate it that I've always hated that and the same with television is oh my god
Patricia I had this long conversation about doing a video version of
Adam and Patricia, you know no longer the daily source code it's being completely captured from underneath me
And and you know and I say you know you have to understand that there's so much you were so
dependent upon other people and and their creativity and a lot of technical things can go wrong with television
And you know television only really works and you've got the right crew and it does take a crew it does take other people
You can't just throw a camera in front of someone and say okay now it's a video podcast
You know, now it's entertaining serialized video. I just don't believe that it takes so much more
You know the reaction shots when a director and the video switcher in the right vibe and the camera man is offering the right shot at the right time
That's a very creative process you can't just solve that with technology
So it so it really bothers me when I have to adapt to technological problems or other things that just hand for me
That are beyond my control
But at the same time while this was going on and while Patricia was laughing and she's no dummy
She she she understands that we're doing something new here and something creative and something fresh and by the way
We do have some experience having done our reality show
The Adam's family which we also did all the production of
You know that we're we're trying to find new ground and one thing is for sure
This show elicited a lot of response and
While I was getting pissed off I was cognizant of the fact that people have responded very positively in the past when I get pissed off
It's like yeah, we like it when you're pissed off an emotional so I think that
No matter what the emotion is it's a good thing
It's a good thing if you hear someone getting angry
Just as good as someone who's getting very sad or someone who's
Madly in love you any kind of emotion. I think if you can actually portray that
Which is what media does this is what songs do this is what
Television and radio try to do all the time except
Mainstream media has resorted to the lowest common denominator of
Giving you raw emotion and that is fear
That is fear that's why every single commercial not everyone but let's say just about every single commercial or news report or any
program other than some of really well written series and films
Are trying to reach out to hate your fear buttons because everyone kind of has the same thing with fear and it's pretty easy to predict what's going to work
One of the things I fear is the closing of the satellite window which is about to happen for you serious satellite listeners on serious 102
We got PCH Pacifico Selwai coming up next followed by yeast radio Don Andrew Gilmour gang and a new digital flaunts him tonight
And right after that Michael Butler and I'll talk to you guys tomorrow for the Friday festivities on the cha cha cha
Adam this is Doug and Boulder Colorado and I just got done listening to DSC 395
And I got to say I've been listening to hundreds of your shows
But I never laughed so hard is when you are screaming your equipment and your microphone and here your microphone
I got a time man
I was laughing at you
I was laughing with Patricia that was hysterical good job
420 from Boulder killings and
73s talk to you
That's awesome wait a minute. We had 420 tailwinds and 73s
So we had listen to this language man. We got a code all our own
Yeah, great. Thank you. Thank you very much
I was laughing too believe me. I really well as
You know it so this is the the conversation Patricia and I had she said you know people are emailing us calling us from all over the world saying
You know this is better than reges and Kelly now that of course can be taken in many different
ways as a insult or as a compliment, but you can't deny that there's a lot of people watching that particular television show
Which is a a US morning talk show for those of you not in the know or not in the country. I should say
And indeed what is that show? It's a it's a grouchy guy gets pissed off a lot and and a beautiful
Sidekick woman or I was it's not a sidekick actually
It's presented as a sidekick
But of course when it was Kathy Lee and and now Kelly, you know, it's a beautiful woman who was pushing back and it's that
It's that very dynamic which is which I think you're hearing work when Patricia comes on the show
Now of course, let me say right off the bat if if this was the Adam and Patricia show five days a week
You know we'd have to quit a whole bunch of other jobs. We have it takes a lot of it takes a lot out of you
And it and it can't always be fantastic and you know you run into ruts and routines and that's another thing that
That I'm experimenting with you know you'll you'll see me go off and do something completely different interview or
And not even interview or talk with Charles Fleischer
And then I'll go flying and then we'll do a breakfast show just trying to mix it up a little bit and not everybody likes it
But at least that you don't fall into some monotonous tone which is bad for I think listeners
But also bad for creators because it just becomes a
Format that you kind of crank out and and you can get very very lazy very easily
And there is there is kind of a
What is the thing we're talking with Charles about the the golden ratio?
You know there's there's in in art and drawing and architecture and physics
There's certain patterns and sizes that are feel comfortable to the human well to the human spirit
Really just to look at them the size of a credit card actually is based upon the golden ratio
Same thing holds true for podcasting somehow
There's a golden ratio that you can hit and it doesn't always come in the same form every single time
But it is out there and
Together we shall explore it
Hi, Adam Steven Shlanker here from the coolness round-up part of the pod show family
I just couple of quick comments about listening to your later show the first is dreaming of second life
I've tried second life, but it really kind of slowed down my computer
So I really haven't been back in since but I do play world of warcraft
Which is a massive multiplayer online RPG game which also immerses the viewer or the player in a 3D environment
Where they can go on adventures gaming and do things with other online players now
I've noticed that after a particularly long time at play on a particularly intensive quest that I too
End up dreaming about the online world at night
I'm not an expert on dreams, but one school of thoughts says that our dreams are our brains way of
Unwinding from the days event, so if you spend too much time in second life or in world of warcraft
It would make sense that our brains are playing things back
Of course for it also set a cigar is sometimes just a cigar
And regards to your bad audio show and the listener who called in to say that your yelling was very in professional
I just got to say I loved it now. I too go on a yelling rant when pieces of technology just aren't working right
And you being yourself just shows that you're just an ordinary guy like the rest of us
Anyway, just wanted to chime in on how much I enjoy the show and how much our podcast the coolness round-up the tech show for everyone
It's happy to be part of the pod show network
We've got a lot of great shows coming up including our one-year anniversary show in a few weeks
listeners can find us at podcast alley iTunes or coolmasroundup.com. Thanks Adam have a great day
Hey Adam hey DSC listeners
This is Scott from American cliché, and I am proud to announce that I've joined the pod show family
That's right while doing my little show about politics and bizarre news
Featuring my silly observations about life
I somehow managed to suck her pod show into signing me
I can't wait to drive Trinity around San Francisco hang out at the curry condo and get my sweet corner office at pod show headquarters
It's gonna be
Oh, Adam doesn't let people drive Trinity around. Oh, okay. Well, I mean, I probably will need a car from hanging out over at the condo
Oh, okay. I can't go to the condo either and no office
Okay, you know what that that's fine. That's fine. I'm still really excited to join pod show
Hey, you guys if you want come on over to my site
American cliché dot net and see what my show's all about
You can also do a search and iTunes for American cliché and Adam and the rest of the gang of pod show
I have no idea where you were smoking when you decided to include me in the network
But you know what? I don't care. I'm just excited to be a part of it
All right
That's all that takes man. We're smoking excitement here. You know what I'm saying?
It's time once again
Little cowbell first
Trinity
It's all good
The fabulous Jeff Smith with the full version of the Trinity theme couple items for Trinity today no audio feedback
But a couple things I want to point out you don't have to go to the show notes to get the full load out on
This new fuel based on water of course. It's a kind of a hydrogen is a YouTube video
Which you just you've got to see this because this guy has developed something
That a fuel that comes out of water
And returns back to water so it sounds very much like a hydrogen process
But I'm not quite sure it's of course. It's a fox news report. So not only is it illegally on YouTube
So I hope it stays up there for a while
But also it's very shallow in in the reporting fair and balance perhaps but shallow for sure
But this guy also has a he has a government contract now to create hummers hybrid hummers
God that sounds like something from second life doesn't it a hybrid hummer
That runs on this water this water stuff and a hybrid of course with the with gasoline or maybe it's maybe it's a hummer diesel
I'm not too sure
So you've got to check that one out and a lot of people sent me that link and I appreciate it
Let's see here we hand another link which again go back to the show notes daily source code dot com
That biodiesel
This is from Portland, Oregon
Is now cheaper for the first time is cheaper than diesel
biodiesel company says as fuel is cheaper than regular diesel in Oregon for the first time
Sequential bio fuels is the leading biodiesel producer in Oregon the Portland based company says it's sold biodiesel for less than standard diesel last week
biodiesel has been selling about 20 to 30 cents per gallon more than standard diesel as of late March
But the blend known as b99 which means 99% biodiesel
1% standard fuel was selling for only two of was selling for two cents a gallon cheaper than standard diesel
on Monday when this
When this
Report was put out which I think is old actually I'm looking for a date here
That's pretty amazing
A new source without a date on it. Okay. Well, it doesn't matter
So but that is extremely good news, of course, and then just a thanks as you know go daddy has this
Number of promotions across a whole bunch of podcasts in the pod show podcast network and if you
One a domain name for $6.95 a pawn check out use the promo code DSC3
That's what Ian Stanley did and you said listening to your go daddy piece on
Was it delta share a try 359
You're talking about gifting domain names next thing. I know I find myself as browsing go daddy sites slow
During a slow lunch hour in a moment of triviality. I remembered your comment on gifting so he gave me
A gift
Trinity biodiesel.com currently redirects to the main daily source code site
This is so fantastic. It's a great idea by the way. It really is you know people get a whole kick out of
Receiving a domain name as a gift
So yeah, that's that's a bit of our Trinity segment for today
Time for some pod safe music. I'll read email about this one after the song Spanish artists from the pod safe music network
Reality
How's that for pronunciation
How
You
So I'm not to show with the Spanish pronunciation of Irene would be but her name is Irene
She's from Buckle on a Spain who's introduced the world of music at the tender age of six as I read here from the pod safe music network
She was raised on this into soul music. She stole from collections from her older cousins and this is her first demo a demo
Mutalia dots my rein you can find on the pod safe music network and if we can get through to her then we'll make it available for purchase today as well
And thank you very much coach food for sending in that suggestion if you have anything you find on the pod safe music network
You think it would be
Excuse me airball you think it would be appropriate for the Charlie please let me know
I just love playing that stuff really do
Hi, this is Phil and this is Tony from the soccer shout podcast
Subshad is the daily podcast that delivers a round up the best of British and European football
It's one part bar room discussion one part audio letters page
We're trying something a little bit different for the world cup and Germany this summer
We want to incorporate a ton of different voices and points of view into our show
We're appealing to bloggers and podcasts to get involved and contribute to the show and the ramp to the world cup and during the tournament itself
We're gonna put all of this together bring some really amazing coverage hopefully something a little bit unique in something
You won't find anywhere else during the summer's world cup in the process
We're gonna be showcasing some of the wonderfully talented bloggers and podcasts is out there
Explosant them to a wider audience of soccer fans
We're working hard on publicity have coverage on BBC radio and the UK Sunday times already lined up
If you have a blog a podcast on a website and you want to contribute to our world cup shows drop us a line
Subshad at gmail.com
Check out the website
www.subshad.com for all the details
I'm no BBC of course, but I hope I can contribute to getting you some listeners great idea and I did subscribe to the show
I'm not a sports fan. I'm you know
I listen to the skinny on sports of course because I love just a 10 minute here's what you need to know about sports
So I can be up on the most important stories of the day
Skinny on sports.com, but you know the soccer thing. I do get into that
I mean soccer is a pretty easy game to understand first of all and
There's a lot of ancillary politics and stuff that I don't get into but I
Can really get into it. Yeah, and I'm usually eroding for the the Dutch guys
You know the Dutch football soccer football players soccer players are
World renowned
Except when they play for the Dutch team and they all seem to suck. I'm not quite sure what's up with that
this year however
You know, I have just a real funny feeling that the United States has a shot and I most people expect them to be
Shut out in the semi finals or maybe even the quarter finals, but I just have this feeling, you know
It's it's been building for 20 25 years in the states and actually
Women's soccer is really catching fire, which I think is great as like hockey
And I love women's hockey field hockey too
Uh, it's not about the outfits and the aggression that really gets to me, but
I think the US has has a shot and I'm maybe playing uh, paying a lot of attention to it
This is definitely not a US event, you know, but this is our Super Bowl over here
And end the playoffs. Maybe it's like the NBA playoffs of course
I'm fortunate that the NBA playoffs are you know almost upon us so it kind of competes but if you can find it and I'm sure
These matches will be available
You know, grab a beer sit down take a look at a match. I'll let you know which one I think is going to be exciting
And then we'll find out what channels they're on the states and let's see if we can promote this a bit because
Even from a guy who just doesn't like sports and doesn't isn't interested in watching sports
You can really get into this and you know you've probably traveled to some country in Europe that you can
Or around the world outside of the US that you can root for if the US gets
Eliminated but watch him they got a strong team
Hey Adam, this is Jerry from anapolis. I was just listening to DFC
I think 394
The one with the interesting guy that you met at the conference you're the day
The climate perk as whatever was called yeah, I'm glad sure and you mentioned the bell and I I get you might even mention it
Briefly here in the minimum on your show. I just had to stop it and
Funniden real quick the deal about no bell is that
You didn't that dynamite is rich guy and
Oh, okay, right, so this was the conversation we're talking about why the Nobel Peace Prize is named after
Nobel
What was his first name Nick Nick Nobel
Who invented dynamite and so here is an answer?
Today is a bituary prematurely made it to the newspaper and when he read it
It basically talked about how he was the inventor of this killer product dynamite and he decided
He did not want to be known
That we solely for that so he came up with the idea of
philanthropically
Supporting a peace prize
And that's the short history behind the Nobel Peace Prize
All right, well you show keep it up. All right, man later. Thank you very much. I'm I'm running so long on today show
I still have a couple things. I just have to play for you. They're like this from the past
Member Rob Caselo
If you're a long time Charlie this new you will
Says music here
It's got a message for you
Hey Adam hey Patricia this is Rob Caselo. I just wanted to thank you guys for your support
and keep doing what you're doing and I really appreciate
You taking the time and effort to support positive music and
Independent artists it's working and I don't even know my family now. I've fans all over the place
I'm getting constant emails especially from Europe all over Europe and being bombarded
With requests for sheep music so I finally did something about that and I put together sheep music for I do
That's available on my website now and
And
Want to think all my fans please keep writing and I'll write you back as I can
Not sure I'm gonna get out in the road and maybe soon maybe a couple of years
Who knows but I'm gonna keep making music and that's that's my main focus so I can reach all of you
Through podcasts and through the internet
Thanks again Adam and Patricia keep keeping up. Thanks
So if you never heard Rob Caselo's music I urge you to go to the pod safe music network at
Potset Music Network dot com or music dot pod show dot com check out what this guy does man
This was uh, but a year and a half ago when when he showed up on the scene in his music
It's just unbelievable instrumental beautiful piano pieces and now apparently also
Available in sheet music form which I think is
Probably the best way to share
Music if you're just talking outside of all media, you know, so that people can pick up this sheet of paper or
Retrieve it on the computer and and play it in their own version
I just do something about that and you're by the way it's still illegal to copy
lyrics and sheet music according to the publishers which just is a little bit beyond me. All right
I got one more song lined up and one more piece of feedback
Which pertains to something exciting happening this coming Saturday
Hey Adam, you love from what house radio aka what house radio on second life
Hey, sorry I missed you at the pajama party. I was there early, but I guess you uh
out there after I left I had to running take care of real life, but I wanted to share with you
I was listening to deathcast number five and willing to be whole what are you exciting thing is I got my golden ticket
And then later in the show heard you talking about possible components to the interface of second life
So I don't know between podcasting and second life and now the option of
Helping out with the development I need to find a way to quit my day job
Real life which is getting in the way so very excited about that and hope to just hear something
Then work on some stuff and great opportunity, but anyway, hope to see you in second life soon
Our new Patricia's with you, so you probably won't get there as much as you want to but
Been working hard developing stuff in there, so I want to show off a few things how to heal later
Bye bye. All right. So I've I've toned down my my
Presence on second life a lot
For number of reasons one is I'm a little tired of talking about it myself
Honestly, but you know as a reference as to people I meet there. It's fantastic because it still is it's just a meeting place for me
You know, it's a meeting place. It's a very powerful
Astmojo interface that you can do stuff with in PD love has really helped out a lot with our new meeting place
The pod show palace which will open up on Saturday and I will be there now I'm planning on going to visit my mom
Saturday and Sunday. So cleverly I'm staying overnight in a hotel with good broadband access
So I'll be able to be a part of this as well, but there's a whole bunch of people in second life who are
actually staffing this this event and
So opening times not quite sure something will be posted somewhere. I mean, this is this you have to spend so much time
So basically this thing is just gonna open up and there's gonna be DJs and and pots eight music artists and performances and lots of gambling
And PD love has actually helped out quite a bit with creating these fantastic
Fantastic what do you call them one arm bandits slot machines with all kinds of daily source code stuff on the spinning wheels
It's really it's it's amazingly cool. So I really appreciate that now
Some people don't really like the second life talk now. There's people don't like the airplane talk
There's people who don't like the Trinity talk. There's people who don't like the metro sexual moment talk
There's people who don't like me talking this people don't like Patricia talking this Pete there's always someone who doesn't like something on this show
And I've gotten pretty good about criticism
Particularly if the criticism is followed by
Something that builds up or suggestion etc and yeah, I get a lot of criticism
From listeners predominantly and I really appreciate that because the fact that you actually took the time to send me a message about something is great
Now that being said you can't please all of the people all of the time of course
But when the criticism comes from really close from someone
Maybe I respect even even more than others because I know the person
But when the criticism is is just about one particular topic and
Saying you I hate this it just
Unconstructive feedback
It is a little bit of twang there, you know, it's like oh that kind of hurts a little bit
And so if you listen to other podcasts and you send off
Feedback or criticism just reread the note twice
Or maybe three times before you send it off because it does make a difference whether it's from a listener or someone closer to home
It can it can hurt just a little bit
Particularly if it's just the I hate this, you know, or I don't like this or what
Folks who do podcasts, you know, it takes a long time. Yeah, it takes preparation. It's it's an art. It's not a science
You know, there's some science to it, but it's an art
It's it's trying to find the perfect mix trying to hit all the points that work for the audience
Taking that feedback and doing something with it, but you know, it sends something constructive not just
You know, I don't like this, you know, I hate this or stupid. We shouldn't do that or you know stuff like that doesn't help at all
And
Serendipity would have it that I received a suggestion for the song which would be the last one for today's show
We put the email here
It's just from
Long email actually
Simon Simon little hails and he turned me on to this artist
Kelly Mueller
Who's now on the pod safe music network and he convinced her
Number of months ago I presume
To actually add her music to the pod safe music network and of course, you know, I'm always like, oh, this is a great find, you know
No one will will have played this yet, and then I go I'm actually doing this as we speak going into the pod safe music network
And I see well, it's been played on the bald guy show night tiger the chill cast the manly geek show financial aid podcast random thoughts the F1
The one podcast journey inside my mind
Ticato urban podcast the world's li pod and cult pavilion, so I'm certainly not
one of the first people to play this
But it isn't artists from the UK
Her name is as I said Kelly Mueller. She's one of a very select group of singers
I'm reading from the bio now today. They use the piano and songwriting as a musical weapon of choice
It has an added bonus that Kelly's crevacious figure alluring looks a natural blonde curls are
Pleasing to the eye and she's blessed with a four and a half octave soulful voice
Four and a half I mean couldn't we go to five it would have made so much sense
But when I listen to the song
I said I don't give a shit about the four and a half octave range the words of what hit me
Your words
You're toxic words I like rain to me and
Our eyes above them like a thirsty flower
Drinking your words forcing me taller with every sin
Using each stroke to grow eyes
But I won't retaliate
I don't believe in hate
I would sooner drown the rain on you
But that doesn't stop you raining on me
Trip, drop, trip, drop, trip, drop, raining on me
Now you're intentional silence forms a cloud of a rain
Darkening my thoughts and forcing my mind to run wild
Your message is brutal
In your delivery is unkind
But I'll soak it up just to save your pride
Oh, but I won't retaliate
I don't believe in hate
I would sooner drown the rain on you
But that doesn't stop you raining on me
Evereword, you spill is a new tent
Am I trusting you?
Oh, you know I'm not waterproof
You keep testing, testing, testing, testing
Just to see if I drown
Trip, drop, trip, drop, trip, drop, trip, drop, trip, drop, trip, drop
I need you, me
Trip, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop!
I won't retaliate
I don't believe in hate
I would sooner drown the rain on you
I won't die
I don't believe in hate
I would sooner drown the rain on you
But that doesn't stop you raining
Rain on me
Telling me you're from the pot-save music network
Your words keep raining on me
You can't stop, you won't stop
Rain on me
And you can find her song and more songs
From Kelly at music.podshow.com
And that'll be it for today
I'll be back tomorrow
Friday festivities, send in your pot-save music suggestions
Have a great Thursday everybody
Bye-bye
Another pot-show podcast
Stick it in your ear
Yet this podcast and more great ones like it
On the hyperformance podcast to live re-network from Podjo
And line-white networks
I love it