This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
GoDaddy.
Delta Sierra Charlie 417.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Well, hey everybody, how you doing?
It is Saturday.
Welcome to Curry Cottage with a little update on the podcast.
We're going to take a nice and easy today.
Today is Saturday.
It's the 8th of July, 2006.
We're a couple days post launch and post send off.
And I really wanted to give you guys an update of what's going on.
Where everybody's at, what's been happening, how I'm doing, how you doing.
So, I found some instrumental music actually that I figured.
I'll play some pod save tunes later on with vocals.
Let me just tell you who this is before I forget.
This is a dark horse summer dreaming from the Podsick Music Network.
So let me rewind you if you don't mind.
By the way, I've got my sensei here and I've got everything else that I like having
to be in a nice chill mood.
Stake you back to Wednesday.
There you go.
Wednesday was back at the cottage, flew back with easy jet actually.
Since the aircraft was back in at Ferrox.
I'd sent a foolishly sent Captain Dan back.
Of course, he did have to do something else.
Some other stuff.
When I arrived on Sunday.
So anyway, so I went back Wednesday.
I was way too tired to do a show.
It was so much going on because of course the plan was to launch pod show
plus on July 4th for your full-blown media independence.
And this was all coinciding at the same time with
Mom's passing the private ceremony for the family.
And of course, by her request the 50s rock and roll party that I was that I'd organized for her.
And so I was just I was waxed man.
Wednesday evening the wind commander who really, he pulled a whole bunch of strings.
He actually had someone drop them off in their own plane at Ferrox.
Because I really, you know, first of all, I like having a safety pilot.
Certainly when my mind is on a whole bunch of things.
And definitely if I've got my family with me.
So he was really, really nice.
And he hopped out, jumped in with me, and we took off for Rotterdam.
Which was actually nice flight.
Christina's still a little bit nervous about flying.
Although she's getting much, much better.
And we're paying a lot of attention to it.
You know, making sure that the ride is as smooth as possible.
Requesting different altitudes if it gets too bumpy.
You know, she watches so much.
So many different horror movies.
Her idea of, you know, airplane disaster is, you know,
Oh, it's, it's a, it's a thunderstorm.
We're being struck by lightning.
You know, the stuff that rarely ever happens.
If at all, it's always some other reason.
Um, so he stated to the brand new Western hotel in Rotterdam,
which is nice.
We had two rooms.
And it was, uh, it was just nice to kind of relax.
We watched the game, uh, which of course was, um,
a France against Portugal.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hello.
Is someone coming in?
Yeah.
I thought Patricia was coming in.
It's just the door.
Don't go away.
Let me go close.
Come on.
All right.
There you go.
Um.
So we watched the game, which, you know, kind of had half my eye on.
Ron, by this time, had arrived in London because we were a big meeting on Monday.
Um, for Pod Show UK.
And of course, at the same time, uh, we're desperately trying to unleash Pod Show
Plus and the podcast delivery network.
And man, it wasn't an incredible time.
I was up until three, uh, that evening or Thursday morning, um, on the phone with San Francisco
and Ron was in London and I was in Rotterdam.
And what a pleasure to work with this team that we have at Pod Show.
You know, we, we obviously, the, the launch was delayed due to, um, that was due to one
bug.
One significant bug that was so significant, of course, was as small as an Ampherson.
And what, what really happens is, you know, when you have all these moving pieces coming together,
and if you look at the new Pod Show.com and you see what we've built, I think you'll understand
that there are a lot of moving pieces.
And one little anomaly in, uh, in fact, in the data can actually make a huge difference.
And yeah, can, uh, can screw up a lot of stuff.
Um, and so we just, because, you know, particularly with the data we use, which is, you know,
people's people's data, making stuff, changing stuff.
Uh, we had hundreds of data testers in there, but you make a new episode, your feed changes.
And then, you know, it's, if you can't replicate a problem consistently, then it becomes much harder
to track down.
And at a certain point, everyone's tired and then you just have to kind of like regroup and sit down
and, and we beat it all the way down and then we said, okay, then we'll launch tomorrow then.
And of course, that was Thursday.
Uh, at this time it already was Thursday, but it would be several hours later, San Francisco
time.
So, I decided to, uh, not think I turned off the phone, just completely shut off everything
and concentrated on the day itself, which was fantastic.
We had a very private ceremony, uh, from my mom.
It's just, uh, my sister Tiffany Willow, Bob.
It was a keto and, uh, it's my sister's friend.
Um, she'll hate it if I say boy friend.
A little bit more than that.
Uh, and out of San Dro, uh, Willow's husband came over from Italy and Patricia myself and Christina.
And it was, it was beautiful.
Um, you know, exactly the way my mom wanted it.
You know, not a whole bunch of people just us sitting around, um, listening to Vivaldi
and then the last song that was played.
Ah, so typical Elvis Presley's are you alone some tonight, but then in the version where it
cracks up laughing and starts singing the wrong lyrics.
So, it's really a fantastic choice because you can laugh and cry at the same time.
It really, it worked very well.
Uh, then we all went back to freshen up and get ready for the 50s rock and roll party,
which was held at this place called Catties Diner, um, above Amsterdam, actually, or
just on the outskirts of Amsterdam.
And, you know, my mom was so right.
What a fantastic idea.
You know, no uncomfortable speeches, you know, really fun music, a great atmosphere, food,
drink and, you know, everyone kind of loosens up and then, you know, instead of people standing
up and giving speeches, we all could have personal share personal stories about, uh, about my mom
and how she, uh, affected us or touched our lives or, you know, just talked about how she was a person.
And it really was a very, I mean, I would recommend, it doesn't have to be the 50s theme,
but I would really recommend that as a, depending on your faith, of course, and your beliefs as a
great way of healing and kind of transitioning into what is the unavoidable, you know,
void that, that opens up.
You know, even during the party, the party for my mom and thinking, I should ask my mom,
she'd know that and I'm like, oh, no, wait a minute.
I'll twist this as that.
As by the way, it's for, uh, EL84 from the Pod Sabin music network with forever my love.
Man, without instrumental categories, outrageous, big.
So after all that was done and everyone had said goodbye, um, and I will be posting pictures, um,
at curry.com, and I'll probably put something somewhere in the show notes from the comments section,
maybe even the blog section of dailysourcecode.com, which is still the same address,
but you'll see it's now points to the dailysourcecode.com page on the Pod Sabin music,
on the, the Pod show plot, so it's my own page.
So, um, you know, why, why we play a full song with vocals, and then we're
talking about the release.
I played these guys before, where they're Wednesday's song, it's a slack stream.
Sun again, we'll shine.
And they can't be music, right?
It makes you want to smile.
In fact, I am smiling.
We're slowly lost in weight, and you'll ignore talking straight.
Don't you know where Sun's going to shine again?
When you look is running out, and your mind is full of doubt.
Don't you know where everything will work out, just fine.
We're slowly getting shine.
But for who I'm showing up, my baby, the shine.
And all those distinctions, all closer that they seem, all my baby.
The shine.
When the world is just a stage, and we're all players in the play.
When you are to be honest, they may be waiting.
And I promise we all met about living life, but haven't found.
When the world's been rushing me, oh, about this time.
We're slowly getting shine.
I swear to you in the time, oh, my baby, the shine.
And all those distinctions, all closer that they seem, all my baby.
The shine.
When the world's been rushing me, oh, about this time.
And all those distinctions, all closer that they seem, all my baby.
The shine.
When the world's been rushing me, oh, about this time.
We're slowly getting shine.
And all those distinctions, all closer that they seem, all my baby.
The shine.
When the world's been rushing me, oh, about this time.
The slack street.
It's on again, well, shine.
And you know it.
Shine it again today.
And the affluent suburb of Surrey.
Known as Kielfitt.
Okay.
So you can hear the fan in the background, by the way.
It's not as hot as it was.
We're kind of past the heat wave, but it's still up there.
And of course, my room with all the equipment captures all the heat and just kind of holds it all day long.
So Friday morning, we woke up on time, kind of in a days, obviously, and got dressed,
checked out the hotel, went off to the airport.
The wing commander was, well, now, I need another 50 hour inspection.
Which show, wing commander William does for me and Antwerp.
So that was pretty convenient, because he just fly over and then he'd fly the aircraft back.
He'd get it fixed.
And then sometime next weekend, whenever he'll come, they'll come over.
He'll bring it back and then I'll bring it back and then I'll fly back home and then it's done.
It's a little bit of logistics, but at the end of the day, lots of good flying when we go through these exercises.
And it's maintained by someone I trust implicitly, which is probably the most important part,
and who trained me how to fly.
The helicopter, as well as fixed wing.
So he was going to show up at 11.
We were going to do wheels up at 11, which between William and I mean,
see at 5, 2, 11, and I'll have the aircraft pre-flighted checked ready to go, loaded, etc.
I kind of love this aircraft so much, the Delta Sierra.
I haven't done the thing I've talked about it in a while, but it's a Session 182,
which is really, if you just look at it, I'd say, oh, it's one of those kind of look,
this sporty airplanes, but people who know, it's much bigger than a 172,
and really can take a full set of luggage, even with two women in the family here.
We were able to get all the luggage in, no problem, it's nice and comfortable,
a full-auto pilot, an IFR, you can fly in any conditions, and it's very fast for a
certainly for a single-engine aircraft.
So I went out, unlocked the plane, it was at the Rotterdam Jet Center, I got all the luggage in.
And there's something you do, by the way, that is really 100% drilled into me for safety.
Whenever you have the keys to an aircraft near the aircraft, you always put them up on the dashboard,
so that particularly with the piston engine aircraft, or really only with the piston engine aircraft, I guess,
because even though the master switch isn't on, if the key is in the ignition, it's just like a car.
If the key is in the ignition, or even a short without the key being in the ignition quite honestly,
but it will happen with the key in there, if it's even clicked one little notch to the right,
if someone were to touch the prop and turn it, or maybe pushing back the aircraft, it could actually fire up and start,
and that could have disastrous results.
So it's really amongst engineers, predominantly, that this has been drilled into me,
so that, of course, is from William, is whenever you got the keys, put them on the dashboard,
so everyone around that aircraft knows, it can't just fire up by accident.
It's a safety thing, so it's drilled into me.
So I pre-flighted everything, actually added two courts of oil.
This was the last time around the mineral oil, it's now getting its whole new lubrication system, whatever that's for another day.
And William showed up, and so we all hop into the aircraft, and this is, you know, it's the Rotterdam Jet Center,
which is really where all huge private jets come in, so we're kind of small compared to all the other guys,
but it is, you know, it's, they've got the luxury lounge and everything, and you pay for it,
but it, it does make you feel pretty good and important, you know, you walk right out to the airplane,
and people accompany you and carry your bags and help you win, and do anything you need.
They remove your chocks and, you know, the stuff that the two blocks of wood that,
keep your aircraft from rolling, it's a full service outfit.
And I reach for the keys, and they're not there, and I say to William,
it's okay, very funny, you know, he'll do this, he'll do all kinds of stuff like this.
That's a part of the ongoing education, you know, in, like in the middle of the flight, he'll
secretly turn off the autopilot and then see how I respond, and it's all basically responding to situations, etc.
So it's a very funny William give me the keys, you know, usually don't last more than 30 seconds,
these practical jokes, because I don't have him, and I knew he didn't have him.
Well, let me tell you, in short, the keys that I know where I always put them,
we're gone, and, and we search for an hour and a half, including unloading the entire aircraft,
we went through trash cans, put hands and toilet bowls.
I mean, everything we could do to find these keys, and they were unfindable.
And let me tell you, when you've got that whole legs, luxury set up and everything,
it's like standing at the side of the road with your Ferrari, because you ran out of gas.
I mean, it's really stupid and embarrassing.
And well, luckily, William knew how to get a spare key up to the airport,
so we finally got back, and then when I got back, I was like, okay,
I'm going to have a cup of tea and jump right into it.
I know Ron was already doing stuff, and he was online.
And San Francisco was up and about as if some of them had not even slept, I believe.
The site was live at this point, and of course,
has all kinds of stuff being worked out, all kinds of little things,
and some medium things, and a couple of big things, one of which is that,
you know, I popped up in my browser only to see that I was evil.
And that I was a hijacker, and stealing feeds, and being a bad dude.
And there's a couple of ways I could have gone at that point,
but I definitely looked towards the heavens and said, okay, mom,
give me some fucking strength now, because now we're in for a ride.
And you know what, I think, well, actually what I want to do is,
and I desperately want to do a dev cast with a couple,
like a Skype with a couple of folks from Pod Show HQ,
who've been working so hard just to, even while they continue to fix stuff,
just to talk to him, but everyone was so, so slammed,
but that's what we'll get into all the real nitty gritty stuff.
But for now, I do want to explain to you just a little bit about what happened,
what the perception was, and what the reality was.
And for 10 foils, 10 foils had moments, 10 foils, 10 foils, 10 foils, 10 foils had moments.
And now it's time for the 10 foils have moment.
The Jeff Smith, everybody.
Thank you very much, buddy.
Jeff Smith, the Jeff Smith.com G-E-O-F-F for the Jeff.
It's a 10 foils have moment, that's right.
So, let me just explain what the word out there on the internet was,
and then what really happened, and how we addressed it, and what the real issues were.
So, as you know, Pod Castile is a part of the Pod Show family,
and IndiePotter.org, and so these are huge directories.
And we obviously depopulate the Pod Show plus experience,
so people can find stuff where we have, I think, a very good search,
which we're still working on.
It's not quite there yet, but it's getting very close.
All kinds of ways to integrate within the system.
We pull all of the information in basically from the original RSS feed,
the podcast feed, if you will.
And just like any other, anyone else who wants to do anything with that information,
you basically have to have a local copy because the reliability of external feeds
is just not that high.
And so when we have the information, we want to hold on to that.
For at least 15 minutes or until it's requested again,
so that we can do all kinds of stuff like it, like give you simple ways to add it to channels,
to share it with people, to feed back information,
so there has to be some kind of consistency.
So we basically cash that, no different from what iTunes does.
Now, what we actually went a couple of steps,
well, let me see, let me back up a second.
No, no, I have to go all the way through.
So if you were to look for any show,
and it doesn't necessarily have to be a Pod Show podcast,
remember, this site is built for audience members and for listeners.
You go searching for the show,
and then you'll find a couple different ways to play the show.
You can click play it, which will fire up our,
our dashboard, our player.
I'm more about that later on,
which basically gives you a way to play an episode,
but also look at everything else in the feed,
or if it's a part of a channel,
you can look at what's coming up next,
and you can jump ahead to stuff.
So there's lots of things going on in there,
but something that I actually like very much
is we're also transcoding the feed,
excuse me, since say this, and say a moment,
brought you all about Apple.podshow.com,
a new site I saw pop up.
We give you a way to play it in Windows Media Player,
which actually works very well.
I'm amazed, also a real player or Winamp,
and then we have an XML button,
which means, hey, here's the raw data,
you can put this into any kind of aggregator or player
that you want to.
So those four buttons, if you will,
or five, actually I think iTunes is there as well.
So those five buttons are all lined up next to each other,
and then underneath it there's a play button
for to play it in our dashboard.
And all of those, of course,
work on this internal copy that we have
the most recent copy of the show,
which is the only way we can reliably produce
a good experience for someone who just wants to listen to the show.
It's that simple.
And what of course should have happened
is the link underneath the orange on white XML button,
which by me is still the standard RSS button.
I know we have this kind of like that Firefox logo
thingy that now it means RSS,
but I'm still kind of old school when it comes to that.
And so that of course should be directly linked to the original,
which contains all the original information,
no added bits from us, the original copyrights, et cetera.
But because we have these internal feeds,
and this is completely a mistake on our part.
It's not a bug.
This is funny because people were saying,
oh, well, it can't be a bug.
Well, no, wasn't a bug.
It was a dumb mistake, you know, just,
it slipped through.
So instead of linking to the external feed,
it linked to the internal feed.
But what was interesting is that a number of people
who are in the podcast community immediately jumped
on this and said, you know, your thieves, your stealing,
you're taking our feed and, and stripping out copyright.
Well, no, I mean, we're not stripping out copyright.
It was just an internal feed.
That's why it's at NA.
It's just like a zero under the copyright link
in our internal feed.
It has different information.
It's not your original feed, which, yeah, I mean,
if we're going to republish that as your feed,
that would be completely wrong.
And by the way, we've also gone back
and fixed the Windows media, the real player,
and the iTunes as well as the, the Winamp feed.
So they reflect all the original information.
It was just, as I said, on my web blog,
it was just a mistake, you know,
it, it, QA said, hey, it all works.
Well, of course, but, you know, you had to check
down a couple bits lower.
And again, with all the moving pieces, it slipped through.
Now, no, and now, there are only a few people.
It was nice to see you said, hey, you know,
maybe this is just an honest mistake.
And that's really where, you know,
you see what people are really made of
when they come out and say,
you know, this is not unintentional.
You know, curries way too smart for this.
You know, this is clearly, since they couldn't steal
our content with contracts, now they're doing it
through our feeds.
And just all these horrible, horrible things that were being said,
when all that it took was, well,
it actually was even more work than I expected it to be.
Because this code hits five different places.
And you've got to be careful when you're changing things
and alive and, well, we have, of course,
we have a development and data environments.
But when you push something through,
you just got to make sure it all works properly.
And so it was a relatively simple change
to just link back to the original feed.
And with that, it all kind of went away.
But boy, did I learn something about a few people?
Even people who I know have professionally released web services.
You know, this is not just a product that we put in a box.
You know, and there's a whole different level of testing
that goes on with a product that gets put in a box
and shipped out or downloaded and run.
I mean, this is something that is continuously morphing.
The data is the data that the users and, in this case,
audience members and podcasters have flowing
through the veins of the system.
So there's a lot of variables that you can hit.
A lot of people do some incredibly interesting things,
which guess what?
They don't always conform to what technologists and engineers expect.
And so we're learning to come closer together.
And that's working quite well.
But for these people who know how, if you really look at it,
you can see, oh wait a minute, yeah, I see what happened.
These guys put all these internal feeds into these other player options.
And then they just put the external feed underneath the XML button,
which if anyone had just said, hey, you should just link to our,
to the original feed, and it would have been okay.
You know, but all the screaming and yelling,
which actually worked quite in our favor,
because, and some people even,
weren't even accusing me of this being the plan,
like trying cause controversy immediately.
So we were like, number two on Technoradi,
which is amazing.
And of course, because of all that, this unleash,
although I certainly was talking it up on the Charlie,
you know, there was no press release that went out.
This was just to go live and get it going,
but there were so many people in the system at this time,
several hundred that it became a much bigger deal.
And, you know, we're our data center as all modularly built.
So, you know, you find out pretty quickly how many simultaneous users
you can handle on one box.
And so, man, we brought on six extra boxes.
So that was really good.
And now that things have stabilized, you know,
some things have been temporarily shut off or don't work,
but in general, everything is there.
And I'm using it and loving it,
because we built this as audience members.
You know, this is how Andrew Grumman and I worked
in the early days when he was doing lemon.
And with many, many different teams, you know,
really from an audience perspective, and hey, you know,
yeah, let's look at the image instead of the text links.
And why don't we look at things horizontally instead of vertically.
And I'm using it, and I'm really, really enjoying it.
And I'm liking all the, I'm not a my space guy
or a real social network person.
Yeah, and a couple of porn sites, but, you know.
But I'm seeing a lot of value in it.
I really am.
And I encourage you to go to dailysourcecode.com.
And leave a comment.
You know, you can dig the show.
You can create a channel.
You can interact with other listeners to the Charlie.
And sign up and let's have some fun.
And come up with ideas.
Will you please?
Because this is just the beginning.
This is just the baseline barrier to entry.
There's so many incredible things.
Just even playing around with the system.
Come up with great ideas.
You know.
Uh, this is just a shit load.
A lot of stuff.
Um, so, uh, let's see.
Yeah, that went until about two o'clock this morning.
And, uh, then I went to bed.
And this morning I got up.
And I could really see that everything was stable.
And, uh, and now we can really start moving forward.
Uh, creating, uh, and, you know, just an example.
The, the player that you're seeing.
Now we call it the bubble player.
Uh, it is not what we intended to release with.
Or unleash with.
It's, uh, it's really just, uh, almost an engineering technical design.
You know.
So there's, there's a new player, which will be coming in the next couple of days.
Um, you already see some of the functionality in there.
You know, if you're listening to a show that you just find somewhere within the network,
you can add it to your channels really easily right from the player.
You can, uh, fire up entire channels from the player.
It really, it becomes, uh, an interface you can use with just the,
the, the, the play out, uh, bits, uh, that you, uh, that you, uh, that you would want.
But you can also get the functionality without going to the larger site itself,
or going into your account.
Uh, good.
So there you have it.
Uh, we're cruising along.
Lots of stuff to, lots of stuff to deal with and lots of stuff to work on.
And I, once again, I want to thank everybody at, uh, at Pod Show for just a bang-up job.
And for working so hard through your holiday weekend, uh, you know,
and people jump in to help out.
And of course, so congratulations to Richard Brueher,
and, uh, and his lovely wife, Ali, um, who on the 4th of July, um,
just near the very end there on the day of our, the official day of our unleashed,
uh, unhead, uh, an unleashed of their cell, their own.
Uh, Addison Brueher, hey, is now welcome, uh, to the family, a beautiful baby girl,
six pounds, two ounces, I think, uh,
guess everyone's back home already, and, uh,
oh, what's this?
I got, is that an email for Patricia?
My wife is emailing me. It's driving me nuts.
From downstairs. She's probably emailing me houses.
Um, yeah, everybody thanks, and particularly thank you for being so patient.
I know we had a lot of hiccups with, uh, with registration emails and, and all kinds of stuff.
Um, in general, everyone was just really irritated,
but extremely nice about it and understanding, and, uh,
and I think that we're paying it off now that you're able to get in.
Okay, let's play another song, and, uh,
then we'll close down this up there.
Do you believe me when I say I'm sorry?
The lives are out this way, it's not the way that I wanted it to be.
Do you believe me when I say it might be when you turn away?
Maybe you mean everything to me, everything to me.
Open your mind and your heart.
To be able to give you a brand new start.
We can grow all the pain away.
We can love without being afraid.
Yeah.
Do you believe me when I say I'm sorry?
The lives are out this way, it's not the way that I wanted it to be.
Do you believe me when I say it might be when you turn away?
Maybe you mean everything to me, everything to me, everything to me.
Go ahead and get free, because I don't sometimes do you will believe?
Do you believe me when I say I'm sorry?
The lives are out this way, it's not the way that I wanted it to be.
Do you believe me when I say it might be when you turn away?
Maybe you mean everything to me, everything to me.
Do you believe me when I say I'm sorry?
The lives are out this way, it's not the way that I wanted it to be.
Do you believe me when I say it might be when you turn away?
Maybe you mean everything to me, everything to me, everything to me.
Broken Jair from Kansas and listed on the Podsame Music Network.
You'll find links and show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
You probably noticed depending on how you're listening to the show that I still have the American flag butterfly in my podcast picture.
I'm going to leave that up for a couple more days.
You know by now that my mom was nuts about butterflies.
Of course, everybody, as I told you, took a butterfly out of her box and wore it during the party,
also during the cremation, of course.
My mom was nuts about butterflies and it's almost like magical.
You see her pass away in the time where butterflies are just coming to life.
They only live for a week or two weeks and they're all over the place.
Whenever I see a butterfly, it's really easy and nice and comforting for me to think about my mom.
And for those of you who knew her and those of you who know her or knew her,
by Cariously through the source code, I'd like you to think about that as well.
Next time you see a butterfly, think about my mom.
Okay, everybody.
There might be an update tomorrow.
Lots of stuff happening in London this week.
So I hope to bring you up to speed on that.
As I said, Ron's here.
So certainly busy Monday and Tuesday and we'll be preparing for stuff tomorrow in London.
And also, I hope you had time to stop and think about to 777,
which was the 7th of July.
The one year anniversary of the bombings in London,
a hard spot to those people as well.
Hey, everybody.
I'll see you on podshow.com on the plus side.
Bye-bye.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast
delivery network from Podshow and line-white networks.
I love it.