This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want to more content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
What is this?
It's a daily source code rewind.
6 million dollars with their pledge rights by us.
With the next generation free of cost, anybody here's.
I like to think I'm trying to keep you ready.
You're fantastic.
You built a CRT.
BBC.
I'm sure they're bummed out about all this noise about the Minister of Parliament
and they're trying to now really push the pedal to the metal.
They get their money from public funds.
Well, I mean, from public funds, the public literally pays for a television and radio license.
It's a hundred and twenty-one pounds a year.
Ten pounds a month and you can watch and enjoy all the BBC programs.
If you don't buy the way and even if you buy a television set, they'll track you down.
And the fine can be up to a thousand pounds.
But it's good.
I enjoy what the BBC delivers.
And now they want to raise the amount of money they want, above standard inflation rate.
So they're asking for, I think, 2.3 percent more.
I'm not too sure on the figures, but it's a hell of a lot of hundred millions more.
Which means that we, the inhabitants would have to pay more.
And so now they're going through this whole review process.
And they're trying to prove that it's going to be worth it.
One of the things is very interesting.
They said it's that they're dealing with extraordinary inflation, which boils down to the fact,
they say that because of the media landscape today, it's very hard to get good qualified people.
So they need more money to attract these, these high flyers who are already been snapped up by
other broadcast corporations and other production companies.
And I was like, please, would you open up your ears for a second and listen to the talent that's all around you?
No, no.
They've put that in a separate little box and they're saying, we're going to make the BBC.com website,
or BBC.co.uk website.
We're going to make it the place for user generp when a minute.
For user generated content content content content content.
So they're trying to be hipsters.
And they're also saying it's going to be, this is interesting that they want to be the place
for independent music.
Okay.
That's, we'll see what they do with that.
I still find that there's a huge disconnect within the BBC between BBC digital who responsible for all that stuff.
And the program makers, the people who are making radio and television programming,
they really don't cooperate together from my personal observations.
So it was just, you know, so they're trying to make it show that they're worth all this extra money.
And I think they're going to be, it's going to be declined, I think.
And justly so.
Yeah, and so now they're also publishing the salaries of the top TV hosts and then radio presenters.
And it's just, it's, and the newspapers are really going at this.
You know, you have Rupert Murdoch who owns Sky, who has used really a competition for the BBC in the marketplace,
even though it's competition for eyeballs, not for advertising money,
because the BBC doesn't have any advertisers.
And so the sun newspaper, which he owns, of course, is slamming the BBC off the time.
So it's just fun to watch.
Over the weekend, I did show Patricia a second life.
And I was a little wary to be quite honest because, you know, she's a smart.
She's like, um, online game.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, okay. What's it about fucking?
I said, well, there's that.
And she said, well, just don't let anyone see you.
Okay.
This is why I love my wife. She's so incredibly smart and with it.
But she was actually fascinated. And she's been asking a lot of questions.
And she has some pretty good insights that we've been talking about business opportunities for second life.
And I think we can really be productive.
There's a lot of things.
In fact, I wouldn't mind sitting in my office and having representations of other podshow people at HQ,
sitting in my office, sitting in the office or in the same proximity.
And we can, you know, pass stuff to each other, which would be notes or, you know,
the way we do in real life.
Only, I think that this is a much richer interface.
And you really do get sucked in, whereas if I'm on Skype or on IM or, you know,
or emailing with people, then, you know, it's still seem somewhat removed.
And the reverse is also kind of true that, and I've said this before,
second life is doing something to me in real life.
In fact, I actually went out shopping with Patricia on Sunday and had a good time.
And as she's walking along, I'm looking at her saying to myself,
how she would really look good and, you know, dress like this sort of.
And it's because I've been looking at all these avatars and having these exact same thoughts.
And it's really giving me some kind of extra appreciation for, um, for real life.
It's hard, it's hard to explain it.
It really, really is.
But emotion and communication melted into one with the visual aspect.
It does something to you.
Again, I am the guy who gladly point you towards the drugs that won't kill you.
In five years, we will be using this type of architecture, I believe,
for a lot of our day-to-day communication.
And what's happening is there's this just fantastic world where you have everything that you can
imagine, you can make, you can dream up, but there's infrastructure of money flow
and land and ownership and rights and stuff like that.
And I see so much opportunity.
And I don't necessarily see it as, oh, let's go all sitting a circle and listen to a podcast.
But once again, what happened last night, where I think we had at one point almost 50 different avatars, people,
on the rooftop of Curry Castle.
Partying, um, I really got to figure out how to, how to play Podsake music.
I got this box of free tunes and what's cool about it is,
when I start playing it, everybody in proximity hears it.
And if you walk away from it, it actually gets softer and it's a stereo vibe.
So if you are to the right of me, you'll hear it in your left ear and vice versa on the left side.
It's, it's outrageously cool.
You know, you can dance, you can chat, but then all of a sudden, all of a sudden, ladies and gentlemen,
who should crash the party?
But Madge Weinstein beautifully, beautifully animated as the bloated lesbian.
And, you know, so that was very funny, of course.
But what, what I really, really liked is, um,
Kachia was there. You know, Kachia, she just done all this great video work for us.
And does my headers on Curry.com. She gives such great head there.
And Madge says, hey, is that Kachia, the video chick from Holland?
They paired off and they went off into a separate corner and had a conversation.
I mean, that doesn't happen on just regular instant message systems.
This was something extraordinarily cool.
In fact, I know that at least five people who were at the party got laid last night in second life.
And yes, that's an uneven number, but hey, it is second life.
Now, just as in first life, real life, you have to respect other people in second life.
And no, none of my neighbors, and all of a sudden, I have sprouted quite a few,
including my good friend comic strip blogger with his lighthouse to the right,
who has not once dropped by the castle because, as he says in the comments on Curry.com,
he, uh, he didn't receive an invite.
So I did make sure to invite him, because I think that people would really get a kick out of meeting him at a party.
But I have neighbors, people.
So could you please do me favor and not be flying through other people's castles and houses and messing about with their stuff and sitting in their chairs and stuff?
Otherwise, everyone has to lock their shit up and it's just not, it's not cool.
So a little bit of respect for the neighbors if you don't mind because they actually did come and complain.
They were cool about it, but, you know, it is a neighborhood and it is kind of looking pretty gaudy.
So if you wouldn't mind taking your crap with you, you know, your cages, your sex machines,
there were some awesome stuff there this morning.
I left the, the rotating pod show, um, headphone head ball about the castle.
So it's a little more of a beacon and you should be able to find it.
A curry castle just to go to the search command in a second life.
Since, yeah, totally messes with your head.
Totally sets you up differently than you'd expect.
It's not really a game.
It is interaction with other people.
It is very much like real life.
Now I've been on, you know, for a lot like 12, 13 days now.
Some people observations and some things that I really, um, that really I don't like about the system.
If you, uh, form a friendship with someone, which if essentially is like becoming, you know,
you're both on each other's body list, you can at that point be tracked by your friend.
And you can teleport to your friend no matter where they are in second life.
Now that really takes a whole lot of respect because I have business meetings.
I'm, I'm right now doing some interesting business stuff development in second life.
Uh, we're not buying an island, but you better believe we're buying something.
You better believe we need much bigger infrastructure for what I expect we can actually do with this.
I mean, cheese. Think about, you know, the pod save music artist performing live and then being able to meet and greet them later.
You'll find the experiences almost as good as the real thing almost as good.
Certainly a heck of a lot more convenient.
So, you know, I've, I've been in meetings, I've been other places when all of a sudden someone who's on my friends list drops right in, you know, and it's rude.
And you really have to treat that with respect. So what I've done is I've cleaned up my friends list.
Everyone who added me as a friend, I've pretty much removed every single one of you.
Not because I don't want to be your buddy and hang out, but before I give away friendship, um,
I have to know that I can get that respect because it's, uh, the interruptions are not fun.
And I, what I don't think is anywhere or something, you know, I like to be in second life.
I'd like to be able to listen to podcasts in there, do my email in there, watch some video podcasts, maybe invite someone in if I see something cool.
It's a great way to share media, by the way, particularly that song stuff, man.
Just I click on the CD that I have on my hand and everyone can hear it, you know, that's a very, very cool way to share audio.
And the same can be done with video because people have demonstrated that to me.
But I'd like to have like a cone of silence, you know, so I can just pull something down where no one can see me, no one can hear me, whatever I'm doing.
And this is not about sex, by the way.
But of course, that would be an integrated part of the experience.
But, you know, because I can't have sex now, you know, anyone can, can just teleport down on me and take a picture, you know, I'd be the laughing stock.
I could just be spin Martin posting that everywhere. No, no, no, no, we're not going to, I'm completely,
celibate.
Second life, celibate, SLC, Sierra Lima, Charlie.
Because of that.
You know, so it would be cool if there was some way of pulling down a cone of silence.
So if you're not on my friends list, you obviously can't track me.
And then the I am's cranky, oh, man.
Just, and I don't, there's no way to shut them off.
You either shut off every all communications or you shut nothing off, and that's a real bummer.
So, you know, I just have I am's coming in all the time.
It's okay. I'm learning to ignore them or respond when it's appropriate.
But, you know, if I don't respond, it's because I'm probably doing something else.
And I am very, very excited to tell you that what we're doing, and it'll be under the pod show banner.
It's going to fit perfectly with what we're doing.
And I hope we get lots more listeners coming in.
Podcasters, of course, very welcome, because you guys are enthusiastic and you bring such an incredible network of people and,
and music and entertainment and fun.
I want to be able to encapsulate that, as it were, into something that anybody can really enjoy and experience.
And also, we'll help you learn.
Okay?
So I'll keep you up the speed. I say within about 30 days, we should have something up and running.
I'm just not going to tell you where or what or how, but very, very excellent and exciting opportunity.
Do you take it in the air?
Yeah.
Lady Patricia, let's drop by.
Hello.
This is not just because we love each other very much and we like doing stuff together.
But it's all about ratings.
Oh, isn't it so sharp?
I don't like that.
What?
Well, that's not honest.
Of course.
What do you mean?
It's the most honest thing I can say.
People love it when you're on the show.
Okay.
But I just do it because sometimes I like to talk to you.
Is it okay?
No, it's okay.
I can hear you.
Yeah, Patricia was complaining about the sound in the studio.
It's right.
I gave, I lent Christina my headphones.
Uh-huh.
Yep.
So that's how they got busted.
Yeah.
I like it.
So anyway, due to popular demand, I'm trying to get Patricia.
I'm trying to wear it on.
This is not, it is nice.
Adam is in his underwear.
No, I'm not in my underwear.
Adam is on the way.
Not in my underwear.
Oh, yeah.
I have my black, uh, for say, slacks on.
Are these my first six?
Yes.
Yep.
And my rustling, brumly, crumly shoes.
And this is, this is, this you gave me.
This is my Italian wife beater.
Yeah.
Oh, is it?
My other ones are really wife beater.
This is a little more stylish.
I said, are you going to beg the bread?
Yes.
I'm making a pasta for you, baby.
Come here.
I'll make your pasta rise.
So we're doing something fun tonight.
I think it's seven o'clock.
Hopefully it's fun.
We don't know that.
Uh, we were watching Joan Collins on Jonathan Ross.
Two, three weeks ago.
Yeah.
And you like Joan Collins?
You're, uh, like her.
She's, she's a feisty lady.
Yeah.
And how old is she now?
She's got to be pushed in seven days.
Wow.
She's got to be very close.
She's already seven.
Really?
She looks amazing.
And, you know, you can say anything about her.
She's well preserved.
Now she's well preserved.
She looks good.
And she's.
But that's gone.
I think even on there's something very sexy about her.
Yes.
I really, really, really just, I'm curious.
What the rest of her looks like?
Why?
Because I just want to know.
I mean, would it be like a, would her head stick out like a sore thumb?
About the rest?
Yeah.
I think no, no, no.
I think she takes care of herself.
For skin is not bad.
She knows.
She's still with that guy.
Didn't she have some younger guy?
Yeah, she has a younger guy.
Those guys will keep you moving.
Yeah.
She said that she's very happy with him.
She tried a couple of times.
I mean, with her.
She's been interested.
She's been married.
Some interesting guys.
Yeah.
But didn't work out.
Who was she?
She's a strong woman.
Who was she married to?
I don't know.
Yeah, come on.
There was some famous guy.
She was married to.
It wasn't her?
No.
I thought so.
And some whack-out guy that didn't work out at all.
Peter or something.
Yeah.
He turned out to be some kind of, of course.
Of course.
So she's doing a tour.
A small theater to a.
Yeah.
An evening with Joan.
And I can't.
Yeah.
And so we're lying on that.
And now we're looking at each other.
We're saying, what is she going to do?
Yeah.
And I grab a blackberry.
I'm like, yeah.
Let's order some tickets.
Yeah.
So we were very curious.
What an evening with Joan Collins.
Yeah.
It's about 35 miles away.
It's not in London.
She's not in London at all.
It's a nice, nice trip.
I hope so.
Yeah.
So it's to the south of here.
So it's about.
Why are you doing that?
Why?
Well, we don't have to go.
If you don't want to go, we don't have to go.
Oh, why not?
But because.
You know how to do a lesson.
Yeah.
I thought it'd be interesting.
How my future will be.
Oh, please.
I mean, this is your future.
Right here on this show.
This is your future.
When Jonathan asked her.
You know, why she did this.
She said, why?
I need the money.
That's what I always say.
I mean, work.
I need the money.
That's what I always say.
People think that.
I don't always use more money.
People always equate celebrity status to wealth.
Don't have to do anything anymore.
Yeah.
It's so not true.
Look it up.
Yeah.
Don't have to do anything.
You want to live like a star.
If you want.
Once you are a star like she is.
People expect her to live in a beautiful house.
She cannot just live in a little college.
It's like we do.
Of course she could.
You know, people expected to live in a mansion.
And she lives.
She has a beautiful man.
I've got to tell you.
I am so beyond that.
For myself.
Oh yeah.
Then why are you building castles in second life?
Well, to accommodate.
Why a castle.
Well, why just because I like what a castle looks like.
Why not a bunker.
For exactly the way you just said a bunker.
And besides, curry bunker does not have the same caché as curry castle.
So what I mean is everybody would like to have their own castle.
Let me just say, well, we've had a castle.
And I miss it.
Still very much.
Yeah.
That's part of it.
Because the castle I'm building in second life is a great place for entertaining.
Oh.
Okay.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
Okay.
You want to get into second life now.
You want to talk about that?
Well, you know.
I see that it's.
Very, very interesting.
And it's brilliant.
And I see it as a game.
But I don't see that.
You don't see the purpose of it?
No.
I mean, people can hardly deal with the first life.
And now they're escaped to.
They want to escape to a second life.
Well, let.
Let.
And then and then probably somebody that they're not.
And then probably be a girl a chick with big boobs and a very extremely high heels.
Have you seen me in second life?
Are you the girl with a boobs?
No.
So everybody's of course somebody that they actually are not.
Well, you, you can.
Is that the, the fantasy?
Well, did you, well, first of all, let's just step back.
See, I am the girl with the big boobs and the extremely high heels.
Yes, exactly.
And, and all the girls in all the girls in second life who look anything like you.
I immediately have a crush on.
The only thing is they're about six feet tall.
Uh huh.
That's the only difference.
And if you were in second life.
Yeah.
But if you were in second life.
The, the only thing you change about yourself is you make yourself taller.
Right.
True or not.
Yeah.
Okay.
Now, let me just step back for a sec because I said this to you last night.
You said, who has, in fact, you, you did want a real Patricia.
Who was time for this?
You're really.
And I said, this is.
People have hard time for each other.
No, boy.
No.
Yeah.
Before you get into that, let me just step back.
It's replacing television time.
It's replacing all that other time that is spent on other entertainment.
I don't think that it's in addition.
You know, so we spend.
Time to find the TV.
If we watch television together, you know, that we always,
uh, you know, or argue about it.
Or usually about.
Can't you make comments during the commercials?
Have you, you know, or, you know, a discussion.
Or you talk about it.
Or you enjoy it together.
And you know, with me, you do something together.
Together.
Right.
But that's what second life.
To get lots of people do second life together.
Couso and Joe.
So I need to sit there with my laptop and play with you together in second time.
Oh, you don't have to.
Well, first of all, I'm allowed to have some personal time to do whatever the hell I want to do.
Right.
And you know, like you don't do that.
Oh, I take advantage of that privilege.
And this actually is, if anything, this is cutting into my flying time.
I might have, I might have decided to fly instead of, uh,
sit on second life for two hours.
So, but it's a, it's a choice.
And that's what I think is so interesting.
Why are people choosing this?
Don't give me that, that's smart.
You think I'm talking out of it?
I'm not.
I'm serious about it.
I'm serious.
Okay, dear.
Um, so, uh, Mark Yosimoto Nemkov.
Hold on, you know, from Pacific Coast, Hellway.
So we interviewed Blake Morgan, who, uh, is the owner of the record company.
And also of a couple other, uh, pod save artists that we've played.
Listen to what he says.
Undeniably, every single time, um, any of our music has been played on, on your show or on Adam's show.
I'm, and Adam playing, uh, ever since, um, from Leslie's record.
We, we saw a gigantic hit instantly.
Like we saw a huge spike instantly.
And it's not like a coincidence or anything.
It's, it's absolutely clear.
You can see it on iTunes.
We know it happening off of our site.
There's no doubt about it.
Podcasting works.
It's the new radio.
Yeah.
Well, I wouldn't go so far.
Say it's the new radio.
But for those guys.
I always say it for the music.
Well, but for the, you know, people from traditional music business.
Yeah, it is, it is the new radio.
It's the new promotional vehicle.
And they're selling on iTunes.
So wait until we finally get everything open up.
And the MP3's will be available on the podcast music network.
I think we can actually break some of the shit that's going on.
It's going to be phenomenal.
Yeah.
The following is an actual pod star conversation.
May 1st 2006.
Pod star emergency.
This is Adam.
Yeah.
I'm stuck in a stop wait.
And the guy we're coming next to me is listening to corporate radio.
So loud.
I can't hear my favorite podcast.
Okay, sir.
Try not to panic.
I've just called in an air strike from the pod father.
That things happen to people who listen to bad radio.
Is everything all right now, sir?
Yes.
Thank you.
Oh, bless you.
Odd star.
Tell us where bad radio lives.
And we'll make sure it's gone.
So the pod show palace coming along quite nicely.
Quite nicely.
In fact, I'm looking for
Scriptures and animators.
Who, so this is real life stuff.
Okay.
I'm looking for Scriptures and animators who can help out with this project that I'm working on,
which I think will fit seamlessly into what we're doing in real life and podcast.
And we'll just give us an extra dimension.
You know, not trying to hook you on crack or anything, but it could happen.
So if you're, you know, think, what is it?
Machinima?
Is that what they call it?
You know, where you create videos from second life.
Think that.
Think about, you know, great animation.
Think about, you know, the Scriptures who, and I've looked at the scripting language for second life.
It seems.
It doesn't actually seem all that rich.
You know, there's some, there's some good stuff in there.
But could do with a lot more.
But if you're interested, fire off an email to pod show palace at gmail.com.
So, Scriptures and animators experience in second life, please only,
and send them off to podshowpalis at gmail.com.
Again, neighbor.
Open up your parcel to me, neighbor, so I can drop by unexpectedly when you're having sex.
What is that?
That's the recycle bin dudes.
They're late today.
I was bank holiday, of course.
That's why.
Uh, yeah, here.
This is a sound seeing tour of the cottage recycle pickup.
Recycle it.
Don't waste it.
Call the recycling hotline.
143, 445, 084.
There's a bunch of guys with no t-shirts on outside my house.
Okay.
So, well, that's going out in the background.
It's, it's not all irritating.
Uh, make so little say.
This is what pod casting is all about.
We don't.
What soundproof studios?
We ain't got no stinking soundproof studios.
When it comes to the, to the world stage,
it's all about turf.
It's all about money.
It's all about who's, who's the boss of who is coming.
Yes, coming strip.
Comic strip.
Can't start a weekend without a note from CSB.
Hello, what I'm carry.
How are you?
So, I am just a listener of your show.
I would like to suggest you something is a listener.
Namely.
One of my favorite radio presenters.
He's a number of correspondence who are regular listeners.
Appointed by him to report on subjects such as video games,
London Underground,
urban, music, urban music, etc.
The opportunity to become a correspondent is a very, very,
one and much valued by listeners of this radio presenter.
I, I hereby suggest Adam carried you two,
we'll appoint some correspondence on various topics
and let them pluck the topics of podcasts
and you would play the short audio reports on a regular basis.
Once a month for example.
I want to hear for being a correspondent on European Union
but I reckon that several people would want to hear
as correspondence on various topics and areas of interest.
Just ask your listeners.
So, have a nice weekend mate.
And move your skinny ass out of this fucking gulfot
to admire the rest of beautiful UK too.
Ciao.
Dude, I admire it plenty.
I saw Portsmouth just the other night.
And tomorrow I'll be flying over Dover
and all kinds of other wonderful places.
It's beautiful.
And as a pilot, you have such a different perspective on
the land that you live on.
So, I enjoy it.
You know, comic strip.
I think that's exactly not the way to go.
Everybody, every listener of this show
as far as I'm concerned is a correspondent.
Whatever's going on in your piece of the world,
or in your piece of your life.
Let me know about it.
If you think why does Adam suck so bad on the cowbell,
I just want you to know that I don't really have
the proper equipment yet because I've been using a pencil.
And the pencil just doesn't have the right,
the earth or length or weight to really get into the rhythm.
All right.
So, I want you to know that there are obstacles
in my cowbell playing, and I'm really trying on.
Okay.
I told you about the pod safe music.
Some are stuff that we're working on.
Now, I haven't really discussed this with the sales
and marketing team, but just think parks.
Think big parks.
Think all around America.
Think wouldn't it be great if you could go see
a pod safe music showcase in a really professional environment?
Wouldn't that be cool?
Okay.
Now, there's only a couple of them.
So, and trust me, it's not the mouse house.
Okay.
So, there you go.
Second life.
I got a sign off here.
I can't see tailwinds.
I'm not a pilot.
I can't do the wider flick.
I don't even do that stuff anymore, unfortunately.
But I did think of one thing that I could sign off with
to be to wish you many blow jobs.
So, BJ's at them.
And I'm hoping this catches on because I really want
to hear comic strip bloggers say,
the low jobs and then charity,
or how about, you know, rather small doing it.
They've a good job to be with you at them.
So, there you go, buddy.
We'll be getting many, and we'll be getting many blow jobs
in the next week.
Thank you, later.
Oh, man.
At first, I'm like, no, not another second life comment.
But then you really pulled it out, man.
I appreciate that.
Yeah, many BJ's to you, man.
May you receive or shall you give this weekend.
Either one is fine.
Let's have more of those this weekend.
Okay?
Get your ass out of second life.
And let's concentrate on blow jobs.
Much better idea.
portions of the show brought you by earth link.
The pod show challenge on the way soon brought you by earth link.
You're going to love it.
You're going to be able to participate in wind valuable cash prizes.
And change advertising at the same time.
I know it sounds really hokey, but you can love it.
It's different.
I have a lot of fun just prepping for it.
Also, of course, I'll keep you download with her
and journal download.accu.com.
And if you're looking for a great deal on domain name,
go to godaddy.com and upon checkout,
use the special promotional code dsc3, dsc number three,
and you'll get your domain name for only $6.95.
And that's it.
A little bit longer than intended.
We'll be back to 40 minutes on Monday.
Another full week coming up.
Have yourselves a great weekend.
BJ's everybody.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this pod cast and more great ones like it.
On the high performance pod cast delivery network
from pod show and limelight networks.
I love it.