Think the show can't get any better. Think again.
In just days, podshow.com unleashes the new podshow plus network.
All new features and functionality designed from feedback provided directly by you, the audience.
podshow.com, changing the world, helping you win valuable prizes.
Not necessarily in that order.
Oh, snappin' eye are debating which is best, scrunching or folding.
Scrunching, folding, scrunching, folding!
Uh, don't you think that's a little weird considering both of you wipe your butts on the ground?
You are go for you know. Oh yeah, why don't you boys just introduce the show?
Ready happy? Ready snappin'?
Delta series, Charlie, four, nine, two.
With 15 bags of splinters stuck in our hands, sugar!
And 15 bags of toilet paper hanging from our cracks.
We don't need no sticking sugar!
I'd like to think I'm right.
For the future, I hope, for the future, for the future.
They're heavenly liberty Jones, works in the shop that she owns, listens to music like swing.
When there's no customers in,
just because she don't like to drive.
Take the sea as stood five.
And tease her thoughts out of sight to the river at night.
If this is your selfie, why don't you come for me?
Take me away from my friends.
If this is your fault, why don't you worry?
We keep your mind back to my face.
If this is your selfie, why don't you come for me?
Take me away from your memories.
If this is your fault, why don't you come for me?
She's got a dream that I'd like
Because her name would imply
If things are only designed
Is it you, Sophie? Why don't you go?
Perfect, take me away
You can ride those
Is it you, Sophie?
I wish it to be what but
We could go by but to my face
Is it you, Sophie? Why don't you go for me?
Take me away
You can ride those
Is it you, Sophie?
I wish it to be what but to my face
Why don't you go to my face
Is it you, Sophie?
I wish it to be like this
I wish it to be something
ning at the podcast con Uk?
Hey, we can't after next, and I hope to introduce them if I'm in the country on the island.
The known as the United Kingdom.
Liberty Jones, could find them on the podcast music network.
Gosh, I love that.
What a great song, really, really good.
Everybody, how you doing?
It is Wednesday coming to you from the Curry Cottage in the affluent suburb of Suri
The Alberta is the daily source code episode 491.
Thanks to the govers for opening up the show.
I'm sorry, 492.
Yeah, you're listening to one tired mofo today.
It really started yesterday morning after only three or four hours of sleep.
Ron and I had a big meeting presentation over to BT at 730.
I love it.
And you know, as I've said before, with these bridgemen, particularly the BT guys, 730 is 730.
There's no two ways about it.
So, of course, we stayed up late preparing and there was stuff going on at the office at the evening before.
So yesterday was kind of, after we were done Ron and the lovely diva Marta jumped on on the plane back to San Francisco,
where Ron, I think, went straight to the office because of our unleashed.
Now, now we had some fun yesterday.
I don't know if you caught it, but we knew we're going to have significant downtime.
We're switching over to pod show plus 2.0.
Or as I say, it's 1.9.
That was right.
It is 1.9.
It's almost 2.0.
We've still got a very, very tired team working hard on stomping some bugs.
I think we're going to probably send him to bed and just forget about it.
We'll fix everything else tomorrow.
There are time tomorrow, which will be our time today here in the UK.
That's what it is, man.
It's like there's no good time to do this stuff.
It's always going to be late, lots of late hours involved.
But what was cool is we did our first dry run of the plus, which is our 24-7 video station.
Amy Mac hosting talking to folks at Pod Show, there were interviews around,
quarter to two here.
I just had to stop.
I couldn't watch any more.
I was too late and you had to get up early.
And we had kind of a restless night because one of our cats, Cindy,
we have two and we're very, very fond of all of our animals as you know,
didn't come home.
Now this is not abnormal for the cat not to come home during the night,
but it is getting a little bit cold.
So that really bothered Patricia.
So she slept kind of restlessly.
I know she went out of bed even after I went to bed to go and see if the cat was at the door.
And he wasn't funny thing, though, this morning, the neighbor came by had Cindy, had the cat in a cage.
The neighbors have a cat.
And this and every single cat in the neighborhood hates this cat.
In fact, when we moved here are the neighbor across the street,
and Mary and said, oh, you know, this cat over there,
the terrorizes the entire neighborhood.
And we were like, I know whatever, because our cat definitely doesn't take any shit.
And they have been fighting for two years,
often on the, our cat and the ferocious tabby cat have been fighting.
Now there's been trips to the vet, you know,
holes in his head and stuff.
And so the neighbor has Cindy in the cage.
He says, well, once again, he was in our house,
and he got locked in the closet,
but I just want you to know that he sprayed the entire house.
I say, Mark went up for the good guys.
Way to go, Cindy.
Patricia is off to the dentist, otherwise she would have given us a blow by blow,
because I was actually upstairs doing stuff for the serious programming today.
And she actually answered the door.
So, hopefully, you know, we are actually still married,
and we do live in the same house,
and we have a life together.
She's just, you know, coming onto the show just hasn't worked out.
Anyway, so everyone worked really, really, really hard.
And we've got the new pod show plus up and running.
Some pieces aren't working, some things are buggy.
What's being worked on right now is your channel feeds.
If you make a channel, that feed seems to be broken right now.
So, that's being fixed.
The video uploader is also not working.
We'll help him wait until you try that shit, man.
You're going to love it.
It's really cool.
So, now we have four networks under one network.
We've got music from the pod set music network.
We've got people.
Of course, we have a huge network of people who are on pod show,
plus we've got shows, which includes everything from traditional podcast,
audio, video to, well, to some full-blown productions.
Like port city PD, which we'll talk about later on today in the show.
And there's video.
And we're doing something, I think it's really cool.
It was great to see sod was indeed, he's responsible for search,
and also a video.podshow.com.
And he was talking about, oh yeah, no.
We just got and steal all the stuff from YouTube and Google.
We bring in the top things.
If you want to see the top videos across the internet,
just a kind of pod.
Ah, very funny.
Very, very funny.
New tools for producers, lots of new things for, for users,
audience members to interact with their shows.
When we get a work again, you'll see that you can create
collection channels, so feeds essentially, of any element,
not just of shows, anywhere on the site we see a picture,
or a single episode, or a video, you can just drop it in,
as well as with a show and create a custom dynamic feed.
I mean, there's a lot going on.
I haven't even found all the things myself yet.
So, yeah, so that's the warning.
We're all kind of tired, and we know that things still are kind of broken,
that there's a stuff that has to be fixed.
But I'm sure in the next 24 to 36 hours,
that's all going to shake out.
And then within that time period,
BT.pot show.com is also going to launch.
So, busy, busy, busy.
There's like 50 people who are just hanging on by their fingernails,
but so cool to hear, particularly the British audience,
being very excited about this unleashed.
And was it talking about that two days ago
that I really had noticed the British audience has really,
you know, picked up on the DSC?
Well, here's the theory.
I had on this shelf, not just on my way,
work, but on a program of folks.
Yeah, thanks for playing out fucking Christmas tune.
It had suddenly got colder.
So, it's the morning of the seventh,
I get to congratulations in order.
Your BT podcast, Ian, it's happening.
And do you, if I wanted to say,
you still seem to be, you seem to be surprised.
A lot of the British are phoning up.
We seem to have remembered the number.
Well, one, you told us to put the bloody thing in our night in our phone books.
But also, I think the popular audio,
amongst the British, can be attributed somewhat to the fact that you're here.
And you're talking about areas that we know,
places that we go to, places that we know of,
and I'll familiar with.
But when you're talking about the state,
they haven't the damn clue what you're talking about.
I really, I really don't know.
I know of the largest city, but there's some pieces.
Only.
So, it just feels a little, a lot more local.
If you were in the state, and you were talking exclusively about the state,
I wouldn't tune in anyway, it's game at night here.
So, yeah, congratulations.
Please see, bye.
Yeah, that makes a lot of sense, dude.
Blok, I mean.
So, a question for you.
When I'm in San Francisco, and I'm there for two weeks.
Do you listen less?
Because I'm talking about things more local there.
You know, just a thought.
Great to show on television last night, by the way.
Was it, I think it was ITV.
British heroes.
I think I said, was that totally true British heroes or something?
Ah, what a tiered jerker.
I'd tier streaming down my face.
See, now that's what I call a piece of local conversation.
Because people in the states are going, huh?
I don't care.
The hell is going on, I wonder.
And now we're from our spine tier.
It's the yanks versus the brits.
We'll drive each other crazy, but everybody knows that it's a parent to see.
Let's just like you and me, it's the yanks.
And the brits, the yanks versus the brits.
Mind the gap.
So, one of the things that I'm learning here is how
the traffic violation system works.
When I told you that our car was snapped on camera, speeding twice,
doing about 40 and 30 zone and gone through this whole rigour
morale and they asked me to send my driver's license, which of course I didn't do,
because I have a Dutch driver's license.
It is international or internationally accepted,
but so apparently they'd want to take points off.
And people are sending me a lot of information about driving.
It seems that this is one pretty big scam though,
but this morning, as I was listening to the voice mails,
and that number again.
Here's what came in this morning.
Disconcerning to say the least.
Hello Adam, this is Paul calling from Battersea.
Notice he doesn't give me a last name.
Adam, I thought I'd called to talk to you about your recent experience with the speed cameras.
And to just give you a quick warning,
you've been squeaky clean so far on music like this thing,
but I think you've dropped the car in terms of the seriousness.
Yeah, luckily I haven't violated any controlled substances laws either.
This is of what you've just inadvertently walked into.
You probably don't know, but failure to give information
as to the identity of a driver can be an offence in his country.
So then go on and deliberately supply false information,
amounts of drops in the police,
or attempts into the vertical suggestives.
And the bad news is that this can lead to a conviction
and a prison sentence.
So what's a face out of you seems to be quite a simple matter of a speeding offence.
You've now gone on the air on a podcast and admitted that you're now providing false information to the police.
Okay, I didn't go back and listen to the episode,
but I think what I said is that the mail was sent to Brian Curry first of all.
So I corrected them on that.
And I presumed pretty much, and so does Patricia, by the way, that she was the one that was speeding,
but we don't know for sure.
We don't know. I speed all the time.
Oops.
Just did it again.
You could probably add to that as well,
that you're now also liable for three penalty points,
and what's called an NS90.
So both Patricia and yourself and now both eligible for penalty points.
You know, it sounds like you know a lot about this.
You've been down to the form numbers NS90.
My advice would be to quickly write back to the police,
and just say to them that you misunderstood and inadvertently gave wrong information
and split them with the correct information.
That way, at least they won't come back to you as any of your listeners,
healthy, provide the police with your podcast.
Oh, now do you hear that?
You hear that, my friends?
Which one of you would go and help the police without information?
Maybe only James from Battersea?
Not very good news, but that's the way it works.
And by publicly telling people you're getting false information,
you might be asking for someone to knock on your door quite soon.
So good luck and the structure.
Right.
Of course you're a scruncher.
Man, I do not like the tone of that message.
It was really pretty frightening.
Oh, I just remembered.
Of course it was me.
Yeah, yeah, I remember.
It must have been me speeding.
That was when I was testing out the cruise control,
when I said it to 40 instead of 30.
Yeah, that's right.
Dude, from Battersea, you're more frightening in this guy.
Yeah.
My original stocker is back.
Hello, I've been Roger Hayer.
I've got a question for you to ask,
Blender, the sugar paper.
Once you know why, don't go and make tea bags with sugar inside.
I hope you're not working too hard.
I've just finished my exams today.
And I'm going to be free a little more.
If you'd like to go out for a drink later.
You know, my number.
So bye for now.
Oh, you don't hear from the guy for months.
And then all of a sudden he comes back with that.
Interesting.
Roger, I think that's a pretty good idea, actually.
I think we should go and propose it to the splendor folks.
I think we should talk to them about that.
That's not so stupid.
And, you know, same for Jennifer, you're not low.
You're not low from food philosophy.
You know, why wouldn't we have folders with the, with the splendor flavoring put right in?
And the tea is a good idea.
Is it possible?
Can you, I guess you can put tea in sugar or sugar substitute or sucralose or whatever it is.
Splenda, as all I know.
I'm not one for flavor teas, but I, you know, flavor teas is a huge market.
In fact, in the Netherlands, which is a big, big tea drink in country as well.
You can hardly get a regular good old cup of rosy.
You know, rosy Lee would be a cup of tea.
He did it again, integrating into the UK.
Roger, are you going to be at podcasts on UK?
I think there's a lot of people who would finally like to meet you, my friend.
I really do, including myself.
And now that I know that you're inventor as well, that's very, very, very compelling.
So we got this new show on the network, which I'm very excited about.
It's called Port City PD.
And what's, what I like so much about this show.
Since here, I was Splenda.
Is, that it's done by, it's done by people part time.
It's, I'd have to say, amateurs, although they've gotten sponsorship in the form of products.
For the show, so they kind of are professional.
But, you know, it's like 20 people work on this to create an episode, a cop show,
which, for me, doesn't, is, is on par if not above anything Steven Batchko can do.
It's really good, the writing, the actors, the cinematography, the sound effects.
It's fantastic.
Oh, you're running a promo, just before the unleash, a promo for it on the homepage of Pod Show.
Maybe you saw it.
I can play some of the audio for you here.
The soul of the city is plagued with corruption.
I used to believe in justice.
Now, I'm on the air.
I'm going to tell you how I really feel.
I hate that.
Wow.
I just want to say,
Okay, let me just tell you how I really feel.
I hate that.
Okay, Adam, we just want to let you know how we feel about this.
We're just, you know, we just want to be someone who we are.
Well, this is Robin.
I'm sorry, Adam, and this is Suzanne.
We're from InsideWorks.
And the divicast.
And we just want to start a dialogue about this.
Yeah, this is an, oh, my gosh.
How can this be on the first page of Pod Show?
You know, I feel like we're members of the Pod Show family.
And this is in congruent with who we are as InsideWorks and the divicast.
And for that matter, right underneath this advertisement, the very first thing.
And I know it's random.
Hold on, hold on, hold on a second.
First of all, advertisement is the wrong word.
It's a promo for the show for another network family member,
Poor City PD, who, you know, get treated with equal respect and equal vigor throughout the network.
You know, we, we try and promote everybody equally across the board.
Very interesting, you guys take offense to this, particularly because you should know that at Pod Show we don't judge content by
Hmm, what is the word I'm looking for?
By its content, essentially.
You know, are you offended by yeast radio?
Are some people actually could be offended by, that's where you're going to talk about.
The bedtime stories, my kids love the gofers.
There's political shows, left and right wing.
We don't judge.
We don't take a stance on any of that.
Care, don't care to because then it wouldn't, it would be my network.
It's not my network.
It's our network.
Let's find out why they don't like this.
You know, it pops up, but it was bedtime stories, my kids love.
That was the very next thing in the director right underneath this advertisement.
So does that mean, I mean, bedtime stories, my kids love.
Does that mean that you can't enjoy a hard-hitting cop show?
If you want to listen to bedtime stories, if you want to play bedtime stories for your kids.
And what was so bad?
Did you see actual, you saw a lot of guns firing and cars peeling out?
What did anyone get killed?
I don't think so.
It's just such a contrast.
Yeah, it's an uncomfortable contrast.
For you, for you, it's uncomfortable.
For you, it's uncomfortable.
I wouldn't, it's not uncomfortable for me.
And you are the only people who have, um, who've complained about this.
Doesn't mean that other people aren't uncomfortable with it.
But let's listen to this because this really interesting stuff.
Just, I don't like it.
I just don't like it.
That's not a really interesting story.
That's what I want to do is give you some feedback.
Let you know what we think about it.
And we give it two thumbs down.
So I want to start a dialogue about this.
And also Robin, I just want it before you know what, before we close,
I just want to say, what it taps into for us.
And I'm sure we're not the only one.
But what it taps into up for us is Robin's mother was murdered.
And she was shot in the head.
There was blood spilled everywhere on the carpet.
It was absolutely horrific.
And so.
Whoa.
Okay.
I can understand.
Now I can understand why for you guys this might not sit well.
Although I don't think that, again, there was no blood splatter.
There's no shooting of people through the head.
It's just a promo.
It's a promo for something fictional.
You know, you just.
Ship, man.
The satellite window is closing.
Are you folks on serious stars one or two?
If you want to contribute to this conversation,
you have to go to dailysourcecode.com.
Download the show or click on play it and listen to it.
So you can hear everything else that was said about it.
Okay.
Understood.
Oh.
Hi, honey.
What's up?
Yeah.
I'm recording as do you see face microphone microphone face.
Yes.
Mouth open words.
Um.
How to go.
You have.
Okay.
I'll talk to you in a second.
I'm just in the middle of something really heavy.
As typical.
For us to have to just see all the.
It's not that we don't like some violent movies.
I mean, you and I go see some different stuff.
It's not that we're all a crunchy totally.
Okay.
Well, then what's the problem in this is.
But this is to the extreme.
Well, and it's.
I was it to the extreme.
Why?
What was the extreme part about it?
All I've heard so far is I didn't like it.
And it's a surprise when you.
It's in your face.
When you go to pod show and we told in our listeners in the past go to pod show.
But you know, when you have.
The match-weinstein.
A Richard blues thing, talking about americans on East Radio.
Also, that's been on the homepage when you've.
Kalilvo has who definitely exploits her.
herself.
Her beautiful, sexy self.
You don't take offense to that.
Wow, this is it's a personal thing.
And I don't think we're going to have a discussion about it because.
Well, it'll never end, it will never end.
You know, now we're going to, we have to have a rating system.
exactly what we wanted to rebel against. Now, I'm not saying that it would be boring to
me to have this type of promo on the homepage all the time or even more than a couple
day, even more than a day. I want stuff rotating all the time. But, you know, to say that this
shouldn't be on the homepage, that's just wrong. I'm up for a new account. Yeah, we really
promote Potcho and haven't seen this now. I'm like, wow, I can't do that right now.
Yeah, I feel uncomfortable with that. Why? I want to look, I will listen to one more comment from
you guys. Why? What are you still uncomfortable about? What is so incredibly wrong with that promo?
Not a single drop of blood, not a single body falls. It's just a whole bunch of noise.
Violent noise. Violent noise. I'm not comfortable with sending people to Potcho to sign up
with that being on the first page. So, Adam, I guess what I hope is that.
Okay, so we'll put a whole bunch of govers on the front page and bedtime story shows and
diva cast and inside works. Come on, guys. You're so intelligent. You're so much smarter than this.
This is a personal thing and it bothers you personally, but you have to recognize that we can't
be in the business of censoring out what the members of our network are making and I'm proud of
whatever one makes. Really proud of it, particularly port city PD because they do it on a almost
zero budget. These are volunteers. They were volunteers. Now, you can finally give them a little bit
of a production budget to get something going, but they've been doing this just because they wanted
to do it. So, we can't make that kind of art anymore because then you don't feel comfortable
sending your friends, but don't send, don't send anybody. Robin and Suzanne, you're here
by forbidden to send your friends to Potcho. No longer. Um, number one that you kind of hear us when
we say this to you. In number two, that you just respectfully contemplate what we're saying and
that you don't just discard it because you don't like the message because I know it first,
you might be thinking, oh, well forget those guys and blah, blah, blah. But we really, I love the
DSE, love Patricia, love Christina. Yeah. And I guess, um, Robin, we just want to leave
with two things of what we would like to see potentially happen. One is either to modify
you want to censor promo or to just to move it. So, I'm not saying to censor, but just to move it
either to a different place. So, it's not on the front page. It's not the first thing people see
or to modify it. So it's not so graphic and violent. All right. Love you, man.
There wins. Okay, Adam, and thank you for hearing us and bye for now. You know, you guys sent
me the first time we met, you guys sent me a comment when I was getting a lot of heat from people,
just about Potcho and just in general. And, you know, not that that's really stopped.
But you guys said something really smart, which, and I wish I'd gone back and found that episode,
but too lazy, frankly. You said, don't accept other people's baggage. You're doing exactly the same
thing. You're trying to put your baggage onto me. It's unfortunate that your baggage is really
fucked up because I can only imagine what it's like. You know, but is it, is it any worse,
you know, to see your mom die over the course of two years from lung cancer until she's just
nothing more than a bag of, a bag of bones lying there, gasping for air? Is that any worse?
Is that any less graphic? Is that any less disturbing? I talk about that all the time.
Is that any, you know, I just don't think it's any worse than then having your mom murdered.
Dead is dead, but don't try and push your baggage onto me. It's clear that this is a part of
popular culture. Shit, man, do you watch music videos ever? So, I'm not, I'm not, as you say,
Suzanne, I'm not saying forget those guys because of the message. I'm saying it because you clearly
state that this is a personal issue and will all your friends that you are no longer allowed to
send to podshow.com until you clean up your act. I love that. Are they going to have the same
baggage? No, probably not. They may not be that offended. You just might find out and go look at it again.
And by the way, I would really appreciate it if you would look at the show.
Look at the show and give me an honest critique of the show for it's for the artistic value and the
work that would into it. Please, and by the way, this is all very much a representation of what's going
on in the world around us. This is really happening. The stuff you see in music videos is a representation
of the world around the makers of those videos. The stuff is really happening. You can't hide it
on another page and move it off the homepage. You don't have to. I need a chill. What happens when
two of podshow's sexiest podcasters get together? The booty needs to be shaken sometimes,
you know? It's just an important part of life to shake the booty. I was like,
disgusting, important things. I know. I was trying not to be a sex object. You recognize that
it's happened. It's happened whether I want to do it in my own. Not to treat you like a sex object
though. It's really difficult. I don't feel like a sex object can't find a baby really made a connection.
So you guys didn't hear it because it was happening during the song, but Angie was actually typing
me a little love messages on Skype and they're very, very, they're very, very secrets the things
that I will never share with anyone. Okay, so maybe I've embraced the sex object thing.
I think some babies have been created listening to a free and easy.
I got to tell you, I was looking at the plus last night as the engineers and the whole team was
working on bringing a podshow plus 2.0 and we rolled out the chill cast. It was real and I was sitting
here. You kind of got to imagine the scene. I was sitting in my in the studio office second bedroom.
And I had the stream full screen. I figured out if you if you right click on the for Windows users,
if you right click on the on the video and you can zoom to full screen. So boom, you know, I'm sitting
there and Angie B pops out and I'm kicking back in the big ugly green chair and I'm smoking away
and I'm drinking some tea and it was just it was she was sexy man. It was great. It was I even
I emailed her. I mean, this is Angie. Angie, it's so sexy, baby. So she teams up with Julian Smith
for a dual cast. I think it's did actually go out on you know, over your head. I think so.
You know, over your head, dud net. Still very happy with the Nokia E61. Not being paid for that.
Should be battery life, not bad. You know, this is what happens when you get a new new device
particularly with Wi-Fi and it's got, you know, all kinds of Bluetooth is consistently honest.
It's got all kinds of real battery slurping applications. Went through a whole day, you know,
problem, including all the extravagant work I've been doing. It was so cool. I'm on the train.
And I've got the I've got a scallop was a scallop 500 Bluetooth earpiece. It's only one
unfortunately only one year, but it kind of worked out because I'm on the train coming back
from the office and shortage, which is in London. And I threw the Wi-Fi at the office. I downloaded
a couple of shows, you know, just through the podcasting application, which Nokia, they actually didn't
come bundled with the phone, but of course you could download it and install it. No problem.
And so I'm listening away. I'm checking my email and then the phone rings. The podcast stops playing.
I answer. It's Patricia. We talk. I hang up. The podcast starts playing again. It's fucking cool.
All on one headset. Really, really cool. And then I got a message.
Yesterday, what do you got a message from? I might as well mention since I'm using Gmail.
There you go. Robert. There we go. And he turned me on to this thing, Goosink.com, golf,
Oscar Oscar Sierra Yankee November Charlie.com Goosink. And apparently you can then sink your
your Nokia or Nokia with your Gmail calendar. So I'm like, yeah, yeah, I'm sewing to that.
And so you sign up and then you're supposed to receive a text message. I guess with the link to the
application and an installation instruction, the text message never came. So now I'm registered.
I've been on to their forum. I've seen three other people have the same problem and no response.
So I remember upon sign up, it said, you know, oh, if you have a Nokia, then it'll just send
your text message or you can install it manually. And of course, I clicked on that, you know,
to go past the install it manually part. And that you can't go back to that page. So now I can't
figure out how to install it manually. It's really, really sucks because I, you know, that's like
to talk about the missing link. It's going to be so cool. I have to say Google really is changing a
lot in the world.
Hoody friends, just don't know where's he here. You know, when I was a kid, we didn't have no
delivisions, no DVDs, no interweb become pewter thingies. Nope, we had the wireless radio in our
imaginations to entertain us. Join me as I wander down memory lane with my friend Robert,
as we listen to the podcast from yesterday. Available at history here dot pot show dot com.
Yeah, it's cool. Excellent show. So the rest of the day will be spent working on pot show plus
2.0, BTpot show dot com. Shoot, I hope the show even gets up normally. It looks like all other
feeds are working well. So that shouldn't be a problem. I haven't actually tried cast blaster. So
we'll find out soon enough if that works. But the overall vision is pretty clear. You know,
you'll be able to manage your media, your friends, your music, your shows, and put them anywhere.
So forthcoming from pod show, a mobile application, you think it's an accident that I have this
Nokia, which really kicks ass. A, of course, IPTV. So it'll work on on your set top box
across the world. I think I saw some messages about Tvo. I mean, this is we're really getting
the distribution. It's really, really kicking in the high gear. And I got to tell you, I'm
chaffed my friends. Suggested sent to you by Tino Felon. Adam, you'd like this one.
Bit like the Peshitamo, Durand, Durand, and others from that time. And of course,
on the pod save music network. Okay, Tino.
My turn, moving up the line with something warm, my mother told me I said I'm gonna keep
in your line. All good things can't diverge in me.
My turn was here.
For a miracle, always come in late. Everybody holds and everybody waits for something
energy out of me. Everybody holds and everybody waits for something energy out of me.
Yosa, sorry, a little distracted there. A stereo movers. And waiting, thank you very much for
the suggestion. Of course, you can find a link to that, which is on the pod save music network
from daily source code.com. Folks from Canada. And just getting some news in here. Let me see,
okay, the collection feeds are now working. Oh man, let's see, front page, player. Oh, looks
like, looks like people are gonna go to bed pretty soon. They really should. I deserve a
metal region every single one of them. We're doing the earthly clues. That's right, baby. Earth
Link, bombastic broadband. Delicious dad. That's Earth Link. Earth Link comes home to you and brings
it home to mama. That's right, sister. That's what I'm talking about. In Earth Link would help you out
with all your internet needs. It's just good. Earth Link.com. Let them know that public kitchen. Yeah,
that's your favorite. Actually, I'm talking about it. Yeah. And of course, we're a great deal on
a domain name. Visit godaddy.com. Use check out code DSC3 for the deals at 695 for an entire year
for any domain name. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay. So I'm trying to get the team off the sleep.
Now Andrew Grummit is still on what times it for him? Crap. It's a, if I calculate backwards,
six, wait, I'm going the wrong way. Am I, oh, Jesus Christ? It's like 530, 435, 30 poor guys.
Okay, so most, I guess most of it's working. So stay tuned. Updates will follow. And of course,
tomorrow have a complete update for you on everything that's transpired. And more than likely,
VT Potcho.com will be up as well. So have yourselves a great day, everybody. Thanks for
hanging in there, hanging with us. Thank you very much to everybody at Potcho for all the hard work
they've put in on getting the new site up and take care of yourselves. Bye.
Take it on the high performance podcast delivery network from Potcho and line-white networks.