Delta Sierra Charlie 3-2
$16 million worth of airplane strapped my ass
in the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into this journey
I'm just kidding
It's so curry
Coming to you from the sunny suburbs of Surrey
It is the daily source code from the Curry County
I can't think of nothing worse
When it's almost back all the time
I love the scriptboard
I love it
Too long too fine too fine
You can't come party with him
Friends around someone else
That's your way
It's someone living here
Everywhere you look Allah keeps me
When you're back
You've been wasting all your time
Yea that's the day
And I'm sure one of the girls don't want
One leg and one leg and one leg
You're the very star of the body
It's a baby to the sunset
And I'm sure one leg and one leg
You're the very star of the body
It's a baby to the sunset
And I'm sure one leg and one leg
You're the very star of the body
You're the very star of the soul
And I'm sure one leg and one leg
There you are, you are the Ferris of the Mall.
It's criminal from San Francisco, kicking off Thursdays
edition of the Daily Source Code.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
Everything here is good.
Sad news.
Yesterday that reached me after I'd already done the show
about to the passing of Chris Penn.
And it really sucks when someone from your own generation
goes, first of all, it makes you more aware of your own mortality
and all that typical crap.
What is this hissing sound of here?
What is that?
Whatever.
I know all three Penn Brothers, I've met them all on the same occasion.
Michael Penn, I met at MTV when he first came out with his,
I guess it was his first album.
And both Sean and Chris, I met on the funny,
we were on an airplane together.
They used to be the service between New York and Los Angeles
called, oh man, shoot.
Now I forget the name of it.
It was like the golden something.
God, now I can't remember.
Anyway, it was an exclusive airline.
And it cost like, you know, 50% more than regular first class ticket.
Or maybe not that much more, but I did cost a little bit more.
I wish I could remember the name of it.
And basically they had, I think it was 737s.
And they could only take 25 passengers,
or some ridiculous amount like that.
Maybe it was 35 passengers.
And they had a bar and it was really chic, you know,
I'd had, you know, it had state rooms.
We could sit two and two across from each other with a table
that would come up from the floor.
And you could, you know, you would have your meals served there very
much like the Oriental Express.
I remember actually going to the bathroom the first time.
And I thought I'd walked into a wrong room.
It was so huge, just unbelievable.
And so one time I was traveling to Los Angeles.
And this is MTV days.
And across from me, and next to me were Chris Penn, Sean Penn,
and their mom, I think her name is, I want to say,
I lean, I think.
And so there you are, you know, you're going to sit there for six hours.
And we all knew kind of who we were.
And so obviously conversation did start.
But not after Chris had taken off his T-shirt
and he was basically drinking beer from a can with no shirt
on it.
I think he had shoes on.
But they were delightful, both of those guys.
And this was actually not long after Sean Penn,
had, I don't know if they were just separated
or the divorce from Madonna.
And, you know, of course, during a six hour flight,
there's a lot to talk about.
And, you know, I said, you know, we'll do.
So I hope everything's okay with the personal situation.
How uh, how that going, he said, dude,
hell, half no fury with that bitch.
And, uh, so it was nice.
It was nice meeting those guys.
And it's sad that Chris has passed.
I think it might be alcohol-related,
maybe just overused his body a bit,
but nonetheless sad, it's like fucking my age.
Um, very exciting this morning.
Um, I uh, I was able to import my entire podcast subscription list
from my iTunes right into my pod show,
which is, I've told you about this yesterday.
This is this whole, you know, listening interface
where you can become, you know, a registered listener
of a podcast, uh, it handles all of your,
um, all of your subscriptions, you know,
neatly manages it, um, you can share stuff with each other.
And what's nice about this is so basically, you know,
from iTunes, you just say, you know, okay,
it's export my entire subscription list.
Uh, you, you, uh, you know,
click that into my pod show.
And all of your subscriptions then appear there.
Do you hear that?
That's the, oh, it's the window cleaner.
How you doing?
Uh, it's not listening.
All right.
Um, so you import all of those, um,
and they, they show up in a playlist.
Now what's nice about it is you can then choose
windows media player, real of this.
Of course, an XML icon or you just click on,
and here's the, this is the cool thing.
You just click on the iTunes logo.
And then it subscribes you, but only to one feed.
So all your podcasts show up in one feed.
And what's great about this is anything you change.
You, you can subscribe to this feed, you know,
through any podcasting device, basically.
Uh, so you could have, you know,
subscribe that home.
You could have a version subscribed, uh,
you could have it subscribed at the office.
And you change everything just from, uh,
in any web browser.
That's where you can add and delete subscriptions,
or, you know, as we say, get a show or I already got a show.
It's much simpler language.
Um, and when you change it on the website,
which you can do from anywhere,
it changes across all of the machines that,
that are subscribed to that one single feed.
And you can have multiple feeds, you know,
by basically creating a new playlist.
So you might want to have a different set of shows that download at work.
Um, as to, as opposed to what you have at home.
It's really cool.
Uh, I'm totally digging this.
You can rearrange, uh, the order, uh,
you can create new playlists and sub playlists.
Just shit, just keeps on going.
It's really, really cool.
I think that this is the first time I've seen something focused
on the listener and really the listening side of the equation that is,
that's gotten me excited.
And that this, of course, is me and, uh, in listener mode.
Yo, Adam, trucker Tom here with an epiphany.
I had regarding the pod save music network.
Why not set it up so that everyone participating on the network
could leave identifying tags for pieces of music,
similar to the way you can leave tags on flinger photos.
And then make the tag searchable.
Then I could search for terms such as kicks ass or mellow
to find the songs other PMN users had left.
It would add yet another great way for everyone to find the music that we're looking for.
You can find links to everything I'm involved in at truckerfoto.com.
See ya.
Right on, trucker Tom.
Uh-huh.
We rough on my ass there, TT.
Um, you know, absolutely.
That is, um, and I know, no Georgia scientist is listening and he's probably smiling.
Of course, it makes so much sense where you can tag content.
Wouldn't that be awesome if it would be, you know, if you're able to tag a song from the
pod save music network or, um, tag, uh, geez, I don't know, a picture or whatever.
And then those tags would carry through.
So if there was an enhanced podcast file, the tags would still be intact.
Of the pictures used in it and the music used in it.
Mm-hmm.
I don't think there's technological barriers.
I think that what we're doing is the right thing, man.
We're just sitting here dreaming about this shit, totally digging it.
Um, for the past, what is it now?
Almost two weeks we've been announcing a new podcast members who were joining the podcast, uh,
the pod show podcast family and today is no exception.
I don't want any coffee.
Quit your day job stuff is really cool, but you know what?
I really don't have a day job to quit.
Just remember, I'm Jade Ollie.
I'm not shadow steel and we do crap in kudos, celebrity interviews, pod save music,
and we do stuff like, uh, like this.
I remember your time.
Oh, man, I'm nice cup of sense out.
Crap, wrong promo.
This, you know, when I was a young boy, they told me not to quit my day job,
because my shit ain't shut.
Well, you know what?
I'm a podcaster now, and because you've had a curry and pod casting,
I can quit my day job.
You can quit your day job.
I can quit my job.
You, why did you?
This is TV, slip, shit, you know what?
Oh, quit your day job, mother.
In celebration of being a new family member to Pot Show,
I thought I'd write a new music jingle, so, um, uh, here it is.
The Bad Fathers, the Bad Fathers,
walking down the street on a foggy night, wearing sunglasses,
being my partner, Joe Monday, on hunt pursuit of a guy called,
The pod father, the pod father,
keep your eye on PotShow.com because pretty soon,
gonna help you to all that, and I think, uh,
once we get to our podcasters up and rolling,
and there's a shitloader that will be bandwidth,
and y'all kinds of support, and that works support,
if you will, uh, then we're gonna go after you.
We're coming to get you 100 million listeners.
Yeah.
I'm Jade Donley, madpod.com.
Thank you for inviting me.
I had no brother love.
Yo, JD, thanks, man. I love it.
Hopefully you'll send me that as a separate file,
so I can use that on the show once in a while.
And you know what, you too soon, we'll be able to talk about
Acqueview and the sponsorship of Heather and Janelle.
Download.acqueview.com.
So that was the window washer.
I thought it was the, um, I thought it was the, uh,
the radiators that just need some of the air needs to be let out.
And I turned around, there was a guy staring right back at me.
It's kind of weird.
And he was listening to me because the windows open is head was right by the window.
I don't know what he was thinking.
Well, maybe it's just thinking him out.
You know, I'm just cleaning the pod father's windows and it was so.
So, um, yeah, I met JD and in person, um, when I was in San Francisco last time.
Very smart.
Lots of the cool production ideas and always walking around with a recorder.
Nice to see the dig.com is picked up on the ample ignoring or,
at least not being very communicative about the, uh, sound issue on the new
power books, which is affected my show severely, um, and is affecting apparently lots of
people who are professional, um, users of sound applications.
Let's, let's just put it that way.
And, uh, I'm sure that it'll get fixed and it'll get resolved.
Somehow I have a very nasty feeling that it's a hardware issue and that it's going to have to be fixed
at the hardware level, which means, you know, everyone taking their, their machines back to the
shop, not an option I'm looking forward to.
But that's kind of what it feels like to me, um, you know, so maybe there's something that can be
done with a firmware, but it couldn't, you know, these are new machines.
This is new hardware.
So that's where I'd look for the bugs first because it didn't have this on the previous power book.
A power book defect dot info is where you can sign up if you're having the same
problems everybody else is having.
We just want a little bit of attention, I guess.
It makes no sense to me that Apple just doesn't say it's one simple paragraph, you know,
hey, dudes and dudeettes, we hear you.
We're working on the problem, looking into it.
That would shut everybody and everything will be quiet.
You know, we'd wait.
Oh, wait, no problem.
Just let me know.
I know it's not in the DNA of the company, but it's so like
1980s to do it that way.
Here, here's how a technology company operates in 2006.
Email from Ed Truji, oh, now I'm buttering this.
Let me see Ed Trujilo, I'll go with Trujilo.
Ed, hey, my, my name is Ed Trujilo.
I'm the president and author of the programs at www.contactplus.com.
One of your loyal listeners suggested that we send you a free copy of the Countdown
Clock and I agree, please enjoy.
And how cool is that?
Only yesterday, the day before I was talking about this, this wonderful
piece of software called Countdown Clock, which does exactly what I want it to do.
Nothing more, nothing less.
You can set the time to start.
It counts down 10 seconds before it hits zero.
It starts flashing out.
You get your attention and then you can, you can self-select a sound
that it will make when, you know, like an egg timer.
And it comes with this default, which I'm kind of grooving on recently,
which in some countries is used on television shows, apparently.
And it's great.
And there's a 30-day evaluation period.
And I was going to buy the program anyway.
And so now I got a free license.
And I hope that other people who are looking for Countdown timers,
it should you need one in your podcast.
We'll take a look at Countdown Clock at contactplus.com.
See, that is how the technology company of today operates.
Let me see.
What else do we have here?
Oh, this was like we got some good feedback and questions and comments on the
pod-sick music network.
And splits and fees and payments and royalties and all kinds of stuff like that.
Here's one dear to my heart about the tax man.
Adam Jason from San Diego.
And listen to your shows and your sounds that you're ready to roll out your
pod-sick music network, music cell and machine.
And I just wanted to touch base with you on something.
See, if you actually look into the tax implementations that you might have
in giving checks to these artists who are giving you music
and you're selling it on there, we have.
There's just something that if you have a look into,
I'm sure you've worked all out.
But if not, I would just recommend having your lawyers be with other lawyers
and lawyer talk and make sure that you're open it out in the
clear and you're not sending yourself up for a huge tax liability.
Anywho, love what you do, keep doing it, rock on.
Go dude, thank you, appreciate it.
Yes, we actually have quite a bit of experience with this.
Brian Longus, who is our director, I'm sorry, senior VP of operations.
I didn't want to demote him like Michael Butler always does.
Has a lot of experience with affiliate networks and with global payments.
The hardest thing actually is, if you're a member of Amazon as an example,
they'll send you a check, they'll send you a US-based check which in most countries
around the world cost three times as much to process through your local bank
as the actual amount on the check itself, which really sucks.
So the most obvious thing to solve is, how do we get money to people as efficiently as possible?
The taxation issues were very rare when I appreciate you saying that.
Yes, I filled the sense say we're up a little bit too much with milk today, so it's getting cold
on our second. I love making it with milk. I love it with milk.
What else was I going to say regarding that? I think we hit that one.
So melts I wanted to talk about, I'll suck on me, just move this down here. I'm doing
stuff from my outliner here so that I can keep track of everything. What do we have on the
satellite window? Another six minutes good. So the news now about Google, Google providing a
sanitized version of their search results to the people's Republic of China.
And so what I'm hearing and reading and seeing everywhere is, oh, you know, now they're
they're only doing half evil, they are evil, you have all kinds of complaining and whining and
moaning. And well, I'm thinking, well, what is the big deal? First of all, if we truly believe
in freedom of speech, we should be helping our brothers and sisters in the people's Republic of China
and enabling them to get access to information that is being held back by their government
and by complacent corporations. Now, by the way, I'm not against Google stands and they're saying,
hey, at least we're getting something to them and we'll keep working on it. Okay, that's fine.
You know, I have, I have no other opinion about that. But from what I've seen,
there's some form of filtering going on based upon words, words like freedom, like sex, like
anal intrusion, you know, whatever. And the results actually show up and it says,
underneath the results, it'll say, some of the results for this query have been filtered for your
protection or whatever. Well, how simple is this shit? I mean, if we really want to help, our
brothers and sisters, all we have to do is come up with some simple schemes that just translate
the words into something else and then back to the original words on the other end. You know,
we can keep out running this as fast as we want. It's like the, you know, it's simple
cipher stuff. You know, and, of course, Google then have to work on replacing the code and
working out the ciphers. I mean, it's substitution cipher. You know, like my daughter, she's on on MSN
and very often when she wants to have a private conversation, PAW parents are watching.
She switches to a font, which like the Zing Daps, Zip Vits font, whatever, that just shows
symbol. So you can't read it. I mean, stuff like that is really simple. Shouldn't we all, if we
really truly believe that we want to help our brothers and sisters in China? And I do believe that,
shouldn't we be, you know, not be bitching, shouldn't we be immediately creating,
maybe a whole separate set of documents? You know, I'd like a plugin for my weblog software that
when I click it, it also produces a document which at first glance will look like a lot of
gibberish because the words freedom will be spelled as, you know, FR33D0M or something like that.
I mean, it seems simple enough to circumvent the filters. And I think if we can organize
where we would all have these, oh, I'm just starting to get into this. Now, where we all have these,
you know, little publishing widgets that are built into our systems, you publish and it produces
the page in English and it also produces a version that sits on your server and gets indexed,
but, you know, all of the offensive quote words that get filtered out are shaped like,
instead of saying porn, we say, prawn, you know, PR-0N. Come on, how hard is this? So let's,
you know, stop beating Google and Yahoo and Microsoft over the head. And although important to
make note of what they're doing, I don't want to, you know, I don't want that fact to be buried at all,
but come on, technologists, let's get this going. You know, this is how about the WordPress
development organization, you know, this is a great idea for a plugin. And what are they doing with
digital media files? Are they going to scan every single one for the words freedom or they're just going to
block all MP3 files and all podcasts? I don't know. Hey, if you're in the People's Republic of China,
send me an email, add them at curie.com. Let me know if you can hear the sound of my voice.
This is good stuff, you know, we can, we can really make a difference here. Let's not focus,
and let's not give up just because, you know, there's a, there's some form of firewall in place.
My God, we can hack into Paris, Hilton's phone. We can certainly circumvent this.
This will call me down.
Do you believe anything is possible? We do. We are a flank. We believe in an internet that's
safe from virus, hidden scammers. We're a Earthlink. We believe your personal information
should be just that, personal. And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe.
We're a flank. Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts
can do for you. Earthlink, we revolve around you. Hey, everybody. Hey, Adam, it's the car simulator.
Wanted to leave you an audio comment just driving here in my car, fart at the i River. I was
listening to DSC322 and you asked for some artist feedback on this split business
with selling music over the PMM. Anyways, wanted to say, long time listener, a long time
fan of what you're doing, love podcasting, got into it cash, like 2004 and 2004, something
like that, loved it, loved it, loved it, then loving and listening to the DSC for a long time.
Got my own podcast, by the way, carcinator.com, go check it out.
As an artist, about this split business,
under the old system, riders and publishers and whatever would get mere pennies. Each time
their works were played on radio or their works were sold on a CD or out or whatever.
I'm talking pennies. I don't know exactly what it is. I'm as a cap, but the PMM pays pretty much the same
here in the States. It's not 10 cents. It's not very much money per player. It's been on the radio.
You know, you're sitting in your car listening to your serious satellite radio. The stars
103 think, and hey, this guy's in his car. He's talking some interesting stuff about
making money in the independent music business. But you can't listen to it all because
the windows closing. The specific coast, hell, way is next and you can always join in the
festivities tomorrow and the thank God it's Friday edition of the source code.
And for y'all who were hanging out on the podcast, we continue. So with podcasting, what
sounds really cool is not podcasting specifically, but through a podcast, somebody purchased
as your music eventually through PMM. I mean, the idea that you could get 25, 30 cents or 40 cents
on the dollar or per sale is just stupid money for a writer, publisher, artist, whatever you are
in the old system. So with how we should go forward and kind of what you ask for,
you know, some feedback and it's yet. Why not we, why don't we look at it like this?
Potchos taking nothing up front, which by the way, hey, that's so fucking cool. And I love
that you're doing it. And I think it's going to really pay off for you in the long run so
good call on that. It's just, you know, way to go. But anyways,
whatever you take, which is, you know, nothing at first, whatever's left of that
should be split down the middle between the podcast that's sent you there or the artist. And
if no podcast, you know, if there's no referring podcast or whatever, there's no other
marty then, you know, the artist could take take all of it. All of what's left after, you know,
PMM processes it. That's nothing for now, whatever it is later. You know, those are my thoughts.
So whatever the, the sense work out to be, let's say at first, I'm getting 50 cents on one of my
songs that I sell on the PMM, then that's pretty amazing. I mean, you're talking 50 cents.
That's, that's stupid money, the old way. I mean, stupid money for the writer and the artist or
whatever. So, you know, then that leaves 50 cents if say, if I'm the artist, but I'm not the writer
and I'm not the publisher and I don't know how that would work out. Or let's just say it works out
that way. There's multiple parties involved on my side. I've got 50 cents to split up on, you know,
each unit sold. Now, I know we're going to be dealing in a lot smaller numbers, but hey, I mean,
I think it's a good place to start, you know, and if this grows into something huge,
you've got, you know, independence making some pretty good money, you know, as it were,
only far more money than I'd ever make, you know, getting my songs sold through iTunes.
You know, even though it's delivered to the internet, it's just, it's still paid using the old way.
So, you know, it's made a few people rich and it's, you know, made a lot of people
enslaved. So, whatever, you know, anyways, I'm weird. Hey, carcinator.com, if you want to check out my
website and what I do, and I admit thanks for the time, thanks for the great show, I'll be listening,
and talk to you all later. Thanks Adam. Yeah, all right, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool. Thank you.
I appreciate it. The first artist, musician slash writer, songwriter, who was actually provided me
feedback on this issue. That's fantastic. I'm so happy to hear that, you know, that you already
know that you're going to be able to make a lot more money per sale than you would through iTunes.
Now, I just want to reiterate here, you know, we're not building a store, because a store means
everything's for sale. Remember, this is the pod save music network we're talking about. So, if you
don't want to make your, as an artist, you don't want to make your songs available for purchase
and DRM-free MP3 download. You don't have to, you know, that's fine. You could still only make
it available for podcasters. That's fantastic. Conversely, if you help in the purchasing process,
if you're there, the transaction, you send someone over who buys something. You can always donate
your money to the artist, your portion. That's no problem. And yesterday there was an idea for,
you know, like credits so that you could then offer a credit to someone else to, you know,
for them to get a free song, the money would still go to the artist, you know, it's good stuff
there. And I think it would just make it, like he had a dog, man. Ever since Jesse died, he's,
he feels like he's, like he's really protecting the, the entire place. And he's no bigger than a
football, you know. Schwabar, it's okay. Damn. Okay, brief update on the court situation with a Dutch
rag mag. We're going to court. They, they tried, excuse me. He offered me,
both at 1,500 bucks or euros. Sorry. Some caught my throat there. They offered me a hairball,
probably. Oh, no, I know what it is. Oh, god, late last night. Anyway, I'm sure Professor Lauren's
lesson will be happy to hear about the hairball. Because he got in touch with me through,
listener of the source code, who is apparently in one of his courses or classes or what you would call
that and Lawrence jump right in and he's working with my attorneys and we're taking these guys all the way.
There are two, two sets of procedures in the Netherlands. One is the Court of the Ding,
which is kind of like an express process. And in that, you know, we're going to have the judge,
the judge has to base and remember, no jury here, only a judge. The judge has to say,
yes, violation of law, yes, endangerment of a child, yes, invasion of privacy.
And then, from there, we go into something called the Bowdoin Procedutor, which is a much
longer process. It could take two or three years, actually, where we actually get into,
you know, how much money they made, how endangered the child was, you know, all this stuff.
But first, we get a year or an a and then we go into the, to the second process. I'm really
doing, I'm taking this all the way because I'm just pissed, you know, when you have women and
children being sued for for allegedly or even if they are, you know, sharing some MP3 files
to the tune of, you know, $50,000 dollars as a fine and the, you know, the RIA settlement agency
calls you trying to finagle you into a settlement. Hey, man, screw it, you know, it works the
other way around too, particularly with creative comments. It's important that we prove that this
does hold up in court. So this shit just can't happen. The arrogance just blows me away.
Real arrogance from these guys. So the, the expedited procedure may even serve next week,
as soon as next week or early next week. So I'll let you know, keep you up the speed on that.
Hey, Adam, it's Brian from Jester on the Pod Safe Music Network here. I had some thoughts
regarding the recent discussion about introducing new people to podcasts and the usual response
of, I don't have an iPod. Now I like to burn CDs of my favourite podcasts for my friends,
and I thought it would be a really good idea to have a short five minute what is a podcast intro
that anybody can download and burn onto a CD that they're giving out to their friends. Of course,
the podfather himself would be the obvious choice of hosts for this. So how about making
a special introduction and saying something like, Hi, this is Adam Curry. The person that gave
this CD would like to introduce you to the wonderful world of podcasting. You could then go on to
explain how to get podcasts, why people should use the subscription features, and why they don't
need a freaking iPod. I think this might be a really valuable resource to get lots of new listeners.
You know, I like that idea very much. Hold on, let's do it right now. Stick this on fun of
whatever you're going to burn onto a CD for a friend. And let's try this on for size. Hold on a second.
So I do it a little bit of echo, make it kind of like an attention getter. Oh no, let me see,
what I do it here. Hello, hello, okay. Now that's too late. I can't do that.
Oh, the delta in a dime. Hi, this is Adam Curry. Now the person that gave you this CD did so
to introduce you to the wonderful world of podcasting. As you can hear, you don't need an iPod
to enjoy the wealth of information and passion that podcasting has to offer. Ask your friend
about their favorite site to learn more about podcasting and enjoy this podcast.
There. See, that way you could wherever you learned about podcasting, whatever work for you,
you can send them off there. So there you go. It's a good idea. And if we want to do more
produced stuff, we can. Let's just see how this one works. Now let me get onto your comment
because you had something else pretty cool I wanted to share. On a different topic and under
the alternative advertising category, I've just added a new song to the pod safe news it
network, which is dedicated to my favorite daily source code inspired Christmas present.
Yes, that one. Check it out on the PMN under the artist's name,
Justa, that's J-E-S-T-A. Thanks, Adam. Bye.
Justa? Well, so let me tell you, the timing of this could not be better. We've got KJ in
New York, Atlanta, Chicago, preparing for the next trip that Ron and I are going to take to New York
Atlanta, Chicago. Because, you know, we're going back to Madison Avenue. It's time for round two.
We want to have stuff baked into budgets for next year. And, you know, we've got a lot of interest,
particularly around what's happening with some of the advertising and some of the reactions we've
seen from our listeners in podcasting. So, how cool is it when someone threw an advertising
that was made by a listener? Riddlekakes made that, made the the initial ad. And we talked about
the eye dog a lot. You know, we had ongoing conversations about it and feedback from you guys,
which we continued to loop through everything. It was fun to talk about. You bought one.
And then you liked it so much. You made a song about it, which you've now made available on the
podcasting music network. This blows me away and check out the song.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I
love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love me, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you , I love you,I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love me, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you,
You would take for four and right
And the thing that I need
Cause from inside and not never go
It's all I need is me
My music and my eyes out
I don't care about anything
I don't need a sweet
My music and my eyes out
I don't care about anything else
Now now
All I need is me
Cause I'm music and my eyes out
I don't care about anything, there's all I need as need
From music and my eyes out
I don't care about anything, there's all I need
I don't care, there's all I need
I don't care about anything
I don't care about anything, there's all I need
Do you realize what's happening here?
There's a fricking revolution, this is fantastic
Can you imagine this happening in traditional media?
No way!
No way in hell!
hell and it certainly wouldn't make it onto the air. No way. Now, here's what I could predict
the next step would be. If someone out there has video editing skills, you know, make a video
for this. Make a commercial. I can only imagine how quick, you know, it's the typical,
poppy, dribble thing, friends like sounding, thing that would get your attention and make
you feel good about the eye dog. Come on, you can feel it. You know, and then everyone could
get paid for contributing in that process. He's.
I think I'll hold the PMN back just a little bit.
Something I didn't know, but was pointed out to me. I've been talking about this auto-delete
function that is in iTunes. If you don't listen to more than five episodes or five episodes
of a podcast that stops downloading new episodes for you and it kind of messes you up on high
frequency output feeds. Well, it turns out, according to Dorky Dude, Dorky Dude,
he says, I recently downloaded iTunes 6.0.2.2 3 and they fixed the podcast problem.
Right click on a podcast and click, do not auto-delete. Hope this helps you in the listeners.
Thank you. Indeed. I didn't know that. So I've already, and it's still not a default,
but this is better than nothing. So that is appreciated. But I think it should still be default.
Otherwise, you know, people can definitely get confused. And I think at this point, it's about
the experience for the listeners. Wouldn't you agree? Hey, everybody. This is Bob from the podcast reviewer.
I want you to check out my show at the podcast reviewer.com. I'm not a regular review show.
I actually care about what the podcasters think of what I'd say in the reviews. And I even try to
help them. If you're a podcaster, send me your podcast to the podcast reviewer at gmail.com.
And if you're a pod guest listener, well, come listen to my podcast. I listen to all the crap.
So you don't have to. If I say it's good, it's going to be a good podcast. And if I say it sucks,
well, you can download it. You can listen to one episode and find out that I'm right. So
check me out at www.the podcaseryviewer.com or shoot me an email at the podcast reviewer at gmail.com.
So I think this is good. I think we need more podcas like this, you know. And, you know,
create your own directory, strap that onto indiepotted.org. You know, I definitely feel that we need
more pathfinders who can show the way for different communities. You know, and it would be great if you
can make a podcast, which is really a jumping off point. I try to do that obviously a lot with the
daily source code. All right. That's it for me for today. Patricia's going away to
visit her sister for a couple of days tomorrow. So Nick and Roy are going to pick her up. Now the
the 182 RG is a momentarily entirely dismantled. It's getting a black edition engine put in
new interior and oh yes, that one empty spot on the dashboard, Patricia wants me to put a clock
in it so she can see what time it is. Back seat. That's so wrong. So she's they're taking
their picking up in her mooney, which is kind of like the Porsche. I would say a single engine
four seaters. It's very fast. And then I'm taking Christina and her new boyfriend, Owen. Oh yes.
Taking them to a gig in London Friday evening and that is panic at the disco and two other
bands that forget their names. And since Owen lives an hour and a half train ride from Gilford,
he'll be staying over. Oh yes, separate bedrooms, of course. It was so cute. I overheard Christina
talking to Patricia yesterday and they were talking about Owen. And she said, isn't he's an acute mom?
Look, he's like really tall and lanky and gauky, just like daddy. That's like home.
Of course, I don't have the four lip piercings and the nipple rings. But otherwise,
he's a sweet kid. Hey, I'll talk to you guys tomorrow. Thanks for staying subscribed.
Thanks for listening, daily source code dot com for new shows and subscription and Adam and
create our com for feedback to care. Another pot show pot cast. Stick it in your ear.