From New York, Delta Sierra Charley, three, three, five.
We're 16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Such me so slowly, it is.
Yeah, I think I know where I am now.
I like it and better, you're looking out, you make it so hard.
You're telling me not all of them.
You're having to go, yeah.
You're pushing my hands down in my lips.
I'm getting cold, yeah.
You're so afraid.
I'm afraid I'm playing you.
I'm not that jerk who's always messing with your heads and now.
Who's?
Let me stay, you wanna play, you wanna play with you.
Let your baby.
Bear with us.
Don't walk away, you'll never stay, let me be with you.
No, don't let it in this way.
I have a body root for the girl.
The wheel they walk away.
Play, play, yeah.
What about the band of girls?
I love to be just like that way.
I used to go.
Right now I'm young, yeah.
We get so sexy when we make it dancing slower.
I'm gonna stay, you wanna not play with you.
You're just not used to guys, don't mess it with your heads and now.
Who's?
Let me stay, you wanna play, you wanna play with you.
Let your baby.
Don't let it in this way.
I think you wish I was a different person all together.
I do believe I am the right one to run down.
If you don't know what I put up with with your crazy head,
you're gonna regret that day.
You let me get away.
Just wait and say you wanna play, you wanna play with you.
Let me hear about you, yeah.
Yeah, I'm close.
Hey, Larry.
Brother love on the Charlie.
Hey, everybody.
How are you doing?
Coming to you from New York.
This is the Daily Source Code in my hotel room.
It is Valentine's Day, Tuesday.
It's early, early, Tuesday.
How you doing, everybody.
Sorry about Monday.
If you missed the podcast yesterday, boy, I had an interesting trip.
Of course, you probably know that New York had the most snowfall on record
or some ridiculous statistics like that.
Something all the news channels could talk about.
And I left on Virgin Upper Class Sunday to fly to Newark Liberty International Airport.
I've learned it's actually called Liberty International Airport.
You should be just a Newark.
I always fly to Newark if I can.
I'm really happy that Virgin flies there.
That of course is because they're deal with the continental.
But I like Newark as an airport.
It's really nice.
Undervalued, I think, of the three New York metro area airports.
But actually, so we left while Newark was closed due to the snow.
I guess that they had been told the airport was expected to open and we landed.
Maybe only 10 minutes past schedule.
I think we're supposed to land at 10 minutes to seven and we landed around 705.
And then we sat on the ramp for, oh, gee, I don't know, two hours and 45 minutes.
It was nuts.
The reason being, there was an LL747 that was blocking the way.
And we just could not get to our jetway because it was stuck in the snow.
And now imagine, you know, it's not like you put some wooden planks underneath the wheels.
Or throw some sand down.
This takes a little bit of a little bit of work.
And then I finally gave us a different jetway to go to.
And of course, the jetway was frozen.
And we couldn't get that up to the plane.
So that was pretty gnarly.
Of course, that delayed everything significantly.
PW Fenton was also coming into Newark.
And we left at the same time.
We were actually texting each other.
I left at, see, my flight left at 4 p.m. on Sunday.
Of course, I'm flying back in time.
And he, his flight left around the same time.
So that was what four is like 10 a.m. or something like that.
Florida time.
He only had a two hour trip.
I had a seven hour flight.
And we both were on the tarmac at the same time.
He got the same, you know, he got such mega delays.
And we actually passed each other.
I played past his jet blue plane.
And we're texting back and forth.
He even got to the hotel later and I did.
I tried jumping like an SUV with four other British businessmen.
And we had a kind of interesting ride into Manhattan.
Lovely.
That was beautiful.
We're downtown in Tribeca at a hotel.
I've never stayed up before.
It's just beautiful.
And it's so New York.
You know, this is, if you imagine New York in the snow.
And the kind of the warehouse like buildings.
Yeah.
Gosh, man.
It is picture picture perfect.
And the snow is piled up high on the sides of the streets.
And people are slipping and sliding.
And it's beautiful.
But still, the city is functioning.
People are getting around.
And cars are able to move.
And we were able to conduct business, which was really.
What was.
What the strip was all about.
And see, who do you have?
Let me just tell you.
We've got to run us here with his wife.
His lovely wife, Marta.
I'm here.
So, though.
And before I continue, of course, it being Valentine's Day.
She probably won't listen to the show.
But you all know how much I love my wife.
And I sent her such a beautiful bouquet of flowers.
And actually, she, you know what?
She, let's do this.
She gave me a card and envelope.
Let me just, let me just grab.
Oh, actually, I have something for this.
Oh, I'm so prepared.
You're going to love this.
I brought the superset up.
And I can actually mix in.
There we go.
So I can mix in the, the wireless microphone.
Let me walk over to my bag.
Okay.
See, of course, you know, whenever they asked me at the airport,
did you pack your bags yourself?
I always have to lie because of course I didn't.
My wife pack my bag.
Well, I don't know.
I'm not going to tell them that.
Now, I'm back onto the, to the Heil microphone.
There we go.
Now, cool.
Was that she, let me just, let's share the card.
Let's see what she said.
To my Valentine Adam.
She loves card.
She doesn't do it like that.
Do electronic stuff.
This is beautiful.
It's so pretty.
Okay.
So it's a beautiful card with, you see, kind of an ardeco coffee table with two
copper chinos on it.
Pair.
I can see the iPhone tower in the background.
And then you kind of see the tables at eye height.
And you see clearly a male in a female hand holding hands on the table.
And it says, happy Valentine's to the one I love.
I stole a touch and he opened up the card.
It says, you stole my heart.
And then it's a personal note here.
It's in dot.
So I'll read the Dutch part.
And if you speak Dutch, you'll like it.
The Benjamin Crow to leave the informal states.
The Kribbles in my bag.
I'll say, now you can't.
Forever my Valentine, your Patricia.
Wow.
20 years.
And still.
Just like yesterday.
He was like the first time.
Any foreigner song.
You can think of applies.
Okay.
So I'm here solo.
And we're both happy to sacrifice.
Not being together on Valentine's day for the greater good of podcasting.
She's assured me.
Let's see.
KJ finally got here.
He was stuck in Dallas.
He came in from San Francisco.
Chris Jacob.
Our SVP of business development.
And he was in Dallas for like 48 hours.
And she had like that.
We have Greg Mann, who was also from our sales and business department.
The pod show he's here.
And let me see.
Pete, I'll be a fenton.
He's here as you know.
His dad was here this evening.
And Paul Vogelsang, or Folgelsang, as we would say.
Of the mommy castors was up here today.
It's just been fantastic.
And of course, no parties complete without brother love, who I gave him a call.
And he popped right on over.
And we just had a good time.
He meets a pizza downstairs in the lobby and other assorted finger food and drinking a little
bit and talent tall tales.
It's really cool.
And tomorrow, it'll be back to work, back to the grind.
But we're having a lot of fun on Madison Avenue.
Oh, by the way.
Check this out.
I picked one up for myself.
We're not going to have a metro section moment in today's show.
But check this out.
Do you know what that is?
Yes.
Indeed.
Those in the know.
It is the Gillette Fusion.
The five-bladed job with the precision blade tomorrow.
I'll be testing it out.
Because I already shaved for today.
And I will bring a full report in the metro sexual moment.
Of course.
See what else we're going to talk about.
Oh, gosh.
This was the funniest thing.
So we've had several meetings.
And, you know, we're here talking to advertisers, talking to agencies.
This is basically taking orders as well.
And doing some education where education is needed.
Very interesting.
The questions that are out there.
And some of the challenges we've been given.
But one thing really, really freaked me out.
We're in a meeting today, this morning.
And, you know, as we're talking about stuff, and I'm talking about user-generated advertising.
We're talking just about, you know, where this whole mash-up of media is going that we,
you know, the podcasting is a part of.
And one of the guys in the meeting holds up his phone.
And he says, and I could already kind of tell the, you know, that they had listened
at least once or twice, certainly to the source code.
And these guys were, were glued in.
And the holds up his phone.
He says, you know, listen to this.
So, of course, unfortunately, I don't have anything to play from Roger,
because I haven't heard from him in a kind of, about a week or so now.
But Roger, you're famous.
You are big and new, but you're, maybe, you're happening.
How you doing, everybody?
This is Marcus Couch from the scenes scene and pod show music rewind.
And I just want to let everyone know that the newest episode of pod show music rewind
is out.
That's episode number 20.
And it features the usual suspects, the rock and roll geek indie cast,
in over your head, accident hash and the scenes scene.
But as you know, last week, we put out the call for new guest pod casters to join the
play.
And this week, I'm proud to present mad pod hosted by J. A. Donnelly, the Jersey Todd Show,
which is hosted by Todd from New Jersey, the Miami Valley Music cast hosted by Rich Palmer
and zero gravity radio hosted by Mark Rees.
And these are some great music pod cast that you guys should check out.
And they feature music from the pod safe music network.
And I'm happy to have them on board.
So check out the show pod show music rewind.com.
And if you'd like to submit a clip for your music pod cast, you can edit together
about a five minute clip.
Make sure it's got songs from the pod safe music network and email that to podshowmusic
rewind at gmail.com.
Thanks again, everybody.
This is Marcus Couch.
Take care.
Marcus kicking some ass there, dude.
So yeah, we're definitely looking to expand the pod show music rewind.
It's a great show if you've never, if you haven't heard it before, there's also an enhanced pod cast version of it.
And so there's a chance to be in this show to contribute.
By the way, I forget who sent me the Curry Sauce DSC jingle at the start of the show,
but I love it.
Thank you very, very much.
I'm just a little discombobulated.
I've got the jet lags and stuff like that.
I need some new openers, man.
But that was just great.
As an email that I received, I just wanted to share with you,
because it just shows what pod casting can do and what people will do to get pod casting.
Dan Gray sent me this email.
He says, Adam, I've been listening to pod cast for a year or so now,
and wanted to share with you an insight into how pod casting helped one guy out over the holidays.
I recently returned to the UK after two months in Iraq.
Hey, I know you visited, and can report that pod cast helped to keep me sane.
Now, I presume that he's in the service has to be almost judging from the email.
Let me tell you, having been in Iraq for a week, I can imagine how a full tour of duty could drive you really insane.
It's a real treasure of pod casting.
Something that no one else has, the ability to listen to anything you want to in some very strange places.
I had to jump through hoops to download pod cast out there and check this out.
I wrote a CGI script that would download a pod cast,
reencode the MP3 file to a very low bit rate, split it into floppy, dissized chunks,
and placed it on my web server for download.
Many thanks by the way to the guys at t35.net.
For a long way to abuse their paid hosting service a little.
For a half hour show, this process took about three minutes.
So basically, that was, I guess, happening at home on as one of his machines in the UK.
Then waiting for me would be three to eight, one point four megabyte files that I could place on to floppy disks.
Of course, no USB thumb drives allowed in the service, I guess.
And take to my laptop to join and listen to, using piles, floppies,
felt like a step back to the stone age.
Using this process, I was able to listen to a podcast every two to three days.
Obviously, I couldn't listen to everything I wanted, but geek counterpoint,
the daily source code, coffee geek, and rockin' old geek show,
and the BBC all helped keep my spirits up and what can be a lonely and tedious place
and a time of year when it's hard to be away from family and friends.
Obviously, I could do this only for myself because I'm a technical guy,
but it's an interesting proof of concept and maybe an application that podcasting should look at, multiple bit rate feeds.
Good point there.
My thanks go out to the Lauren, to the Lauren, Michael, Mark, and yourself for keeping a fellow pilot happy.
Well done to the BBC as well for taking a lead amongst commercial broadcasters,
nice to see him thinking ahead.
And this really just blew me away.
First of all, the inventiveness of it all.
And really taking some of that into consideration, some of these multiple bit rates.
And that is something that we should probably think about on the podcast delivery
network as well, which I think today the press release goes out about
our partnership with limelight networks.
I hope it's today because I'm about to make some ten announcements.
Not like those of you listening to show didn't know about that,
but for I would have to say probably six months.
We worked on understanding bandwidth, understanding building it versus purchasing it,
understanding pricing, understanding players, understanding and when I mean players,
I mean who would a play is, who to play is be understanding content delivery networks
that work with streaming versus large media objects.
And we hired all kinds of people to come in and help us.
And we really, really spent a long time.
And when we finally met Bill and his team over at limelight networks,
well, instinctively, I already knew that these are going to be the guys for us because
they're renegades.
They're sitting in there in Arizona flying under the radar,
but kicking some major ass.
And they've got just such an incredibly strong technical team.
They're the architecture of their network.
And I know a little bit about peering and really being on the back bones.
The back bones, baby.
That's from my data, my data barn days in the Netherlands.
And so happy that we were able to work this out.
And these are the guys that have really worked with us and are working to support independent podcasting.
So that we can give you all these fantastic services for free if you're interested in joining the podcast network.
And of course, details of that are coming soon.
But the whole point here is to really level the playing field and give the independent podcast or
just as much opportunity as the mainstream.
And then some, we feel.
So I hope that that press release goes out today because I really already told you a lot about what it's about.
And this isn't the corporate message.
This is just me saying how incredibly happy I am.
I've been using limelight for a couple of months now.
The daily source code has been rolling on the limelight network.
And you know, here and there we've bumped into a couple of interesting little things.
We've worked with the team and this thing is now tuned.
And the pod show podcast delivery network completely.
After burning nitro flame throwing network, which supports it, which is limelight.
Okay, that was a rant in a half.
Let's see.
We've got to talk more about Madison Avenue and advertising.
That's what's going on this week here in New York.
So first time to pay some bills in the body.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
Where are a flank?
We believe in an internet that's safe from virus hissing scammers.
We're earthlink.
We believe your personal information should be just that personal.
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe.
We're earthlink.
Make this smart choice visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
Say, what is the sound remind you of?
Well, here I am again.
And I want to tell the world.
And then what do you think of when you hear this theme music?
I'll give you another hint.
Sometimes you might hear this.
And now it's time for this week.
It's 3-8-7.
And then other times, you might hear something like this.
And now it's time for Ed's software, too.
Did I mention that we play pod safe music?
And we even hear from the musicians.
Todd Learner here.
You are listening to Ed's mix music.
Take this podcast for free.
And oh, yeah.
Don't let me forget of the podcast that's like to talk about us as well.
Hi.
This is Mike Tuddle from the Sky Pieces Radio podcast.
It's Sky Pieces Radio.com.
And you're listening to all the mix.
Hey, Adam Bob from the Bob show at www.bobshow.net.
Where there still is no Bob show to be heard.
My career seems to be yet.
So many audio feedback to your show.
But that's okay.
The reason that I'm submitting this today is,
Well, a couple of three comments that I'd like to throw at.
You're regarding Friday's show.
First of all, it was very refreshing to have your wife Patricia on the show.
She's a charming lady.
And opinionated.
And actually, I like that.
And especially when the audience are well formed and well presented.
The other thing that I like is the fact is the interaction,
I guess, between you and your wife.
And the interaction between you and your daughter.
It's really neat when you have other people on the show.
I think it provides a new dynamic.
You don't want to tell you how to do your business.
But those shows where people visit you are always the high point of the DSE stream,
if you will.
I have become a DSE consumer.
I've bought an iPod and I dog.
An MM50, a San Seo came with a burp, apparently.
And my most recent purchases would be this,
a high LPR50 microphone, peer 40, sorry.
I like this microphone.
Makes me sound better than I do in person.
I've been actively promoted, but when you got it at the,
at the portable music expo and started using it,
I noticed the distinct change in your sound that I really liked.
So another sale for Adam Curry.
Also went out and got some software.
Gas blaster.
To help me, that's one of the card buttons.
In the apparently, the podfather version that just came out.
So that's all good.
Thank you for all of that.
I think you've given me a lot of inspiration and a lot of direction.
But now to the point of my comments.
Ultimately, I was listening to Friday's show.
And you were talking about how EarthLink was going to go to a listener
based advertising generation or something like that
that you were going to have listeners creating the ads.
And I think that'll be exciting looking forward to Monday's or Tuesday's show
to hear about how it all shapes up.
What are the things that I do want to say that EarthLink did well
was brand their sound?
Yeah, the sound that EarthLink has three times in each commercial that you play.
And I bring this up because your burp has been disassociated from its senseo origins.
What I mean by that is, you know, every time you used to burp or say senseo.
I got it.
I mean, it made sense.
The link was there.
You burped and the senseo made it happen.
So you said senseo.
And that was all part of the great pod casting advertising experiment.
However, when you burp, now and say stuff like
download.acview.com.
It just doesn't seem to work for me.
Now, I know that download.acview.com doesn't have its own sound,
but EarthLink certainly does.
What if you burped and played the sound like burp?
I played the wrong sound.
Burp?
You see what I'm going with this at him?
I think they go well together.
In burp?
Yeah, you've got to get a better copy of the sound, I think.
But yeah, I think it'd be cool.
I kind of like the idea.
I don't know.
You do with it, which you will.
I want to say thanks for doing all that you do and helping me
to spend my harder and money looking forward to the pod show
network coming online and seeing how that integrates with cast
blaster.
I think that's going to be exciting.
So thank you.
And I think that may be just the thing that I need to motivate me to
actually start recording a show on a regular basis.
Thanks Adam.
Keep up the great work.
Yo, dude.
Thank you very much.
I really appreciate that feedback.
I want to talk about this a little bit about the sound
advertising and the Vulcan mind trick linking.
But unfortunately, folks listen to this podcast on star
serious 103.
We'll have to download the podcast to hear the whole thing.
PCH is next.
Everybody, thanks for listening.
As we continue.
I got a whole bunch of other comments about the burping.
And by the way, I'm really just trying to just try to
jumble it all up and disassociate it because for all the
people who who said they liked it or
works or whatever and think it's kind of cute.
There's a lot of people who are really, really
inspired by it because they are programmed.
And either I, you know, we linked you to a spot on the road,
but really with the burping thing.
It was just trying to show how, you know, that you can
associate it anything with anything, I guess.
Let me just give you a couple of pieces of feedback that have
come in.
Billy Adams says Adam got to tell you that the reprogram isn't
working very well.
Every time you burp, I immediately think Senseo actually
I tend to think Senseo whenever I burp.
As you can imagine, I get several weird looks from my
friends when they hear this.
But it gives me the opportunity to tell them about the
Charlie.
I'd love it when you guys call it the Charlie.
And podcasting in general.
Most of them respond with the usual, I don't have an
iPod, but now of course I can send them to no iPod
required.com.
Thanks to your show.
It gives me a reason to get up in the morning just to
hear while I'm getting ready.
Would like to ask one question though.
You keep preferring to registered listeners.
How does one become a registered listener?
Ah, I'm glad you asked.
That'll be a part of Pod Show Plus.
This is the whole listener interface that we've been working on
so hard.
And I think that that's, you know, it's this month
that stuff is going to start dripping out.
We're finally going to be able to show our wires.
You know, now that we've got everything in place,
which is, as obviously, what took a really long time
was getting the podcast delivery network in place
that we'd have top notch.
You know, I just don't want to have to worry about
bandwidth and crap and stuff not working.
I want to make that, you know, that's not our expertise.
Guys who really worked very hard on figuring that out.
Some more Birp and Simran Sharma.
Hi, Adam.
After that comment from bedtime stories.
Oh, that's when bedtime stories that a whole bunch of
Birp stuff, right?
Everything got real weird with me.
Every time the ting in the Earthlink ad played,
I hear a Birp.
God darn, there you go.
You were right, dude.
It was like Earthlink, Birp.
Come meet our internet experts.
Birp.
Your info should be just that personal.
Seriously, no kid in here.
Your podcast rules.
Thank you.
What's this last one?
Bob Canna.
Adam, I've had enough of your birping.
It's very insulting that if someone burp at you.
If it happens by accident, that's one thing that you're
definitely overdoing it.
I'm no longer a listener of your show.
It's not worth it.
One too many birps.
Grow up.
Disgusted.
Excellent.
Ah, man.
Sorry about that, Bob.
The thing about the sound about the earthlink
sound branding is, of course, completely true.
You know whenever you hear the intel inside sound, you know exactly what
that's about.
And that is, of course, something that the definitely, you know, is important.
And stuff we got to think about.
Oh, man.
The jet lag is kicking in quick.
Somebody saved me with some feedback.
Hey, Adam, how you doing?
This is push real quick.
Hey, which?
Yeah, I got something to say about all this advertising.
I'm hearing it on almost every show.
You know, I have a podcast.
And I totally agree with what you said yesterday on the Thursday.
Got the Sierra Charlie.
Somebody's going to pay me to, you know, just a little something that
was like a 15 second thing out there.
I would do it.
It seems like everybody that's calling up and complaining on these shows
or leaving messages and stuff like that was saying to sell it out.
I mean, did it to the Gilmore gang.
And, you know, I heard something on your show yesterday about it.
It was like, what is this?
Like, some kind of sanctuary podcasting that you can't,
can't be influenced with what a commercial here and that.
Got about it personally.
Is it about the podcast?
I would love for someone to throw me a 30 second commercial or a 15 second
commercial.
You know, there'd been like no big accomplishment to me
than having like an autonomous podcast.
It pays for itself, you know.
I don't have to pay a lot, you know, for my host or whatever.
But still, I mean, just to have everything grown between that,
between hosting for my podcast and my website.
Yeah, it could add up a little bit, you know.
So if they fill me like 30 bucks a month, I put them on every show.
You know, that'd be like the ultimate compliment, like I said.
It just seems like people with negative comments all the time.
It just seems like the same thing with the blogosphere.
If, you know, the people that write all these negative comments
or send all those negative comments about podcasting,
they don't have one.
They don't have a blog and they don't have a podcast.
I'm talking to a lot of different new podcast.
It's an essence to be like a great camaraderie.
And I'm all for it.
If you want to put something on your shirt and find, listen,
I got like one of these fancy MP3s.
Just fast forward if I don't want to hear it.
You know, right?
I don't even have to listen in.
You know, like people don't listen to device shows.
You know, like everything comes in.
But I just wanted to say that, you know,
your show, you do what you want.
My show, I do what I want.
And, uh, right, I'm right.
People don't like it.
But that's fine.
There's 6.4 billion people that don't listen to my show right now.
So you can be wonderful.
It's no big deal, you know.
I just can't join anyway.
I'm just going to keep listening and enjoy your show.
Take care.
Bye bye.
Hey, which, thank you man.
I like that.
That was really funny.
You made me, I heard it three times already,
and it still may be live.
I'll do you one better, man.
For this earthling thing,
let's, um,
we should do like,
uh,
maybe I just call it a contest.
Why don't we, um,
do a contest.
And, uh,
you know,
create the earthling ad.
And of course, the, all the,
the fun is playing the submissions, right?
Which all work as, uh,
as commercials.
And, uh,
and then we choose one.
And then the winner gets some fabulous prize.
I don't know what the prize is yet,
but, um,
something like that.
Something we should definitely,
I mean, that's, that's,
um,
I haven't really had a chance to hook up with the,
with the,
the sales and biz dev team to discuss it.
But when we've had some email back and forth,
so I know that this is what we're going to do.
Um,
but I,
I don't have details like,
you know,
if we do this,
we know what kind of prize we'd have.
But it will,
we'll figure something out.
We'll figure something out.
It will totally make it worthwhile.
Um,
so start thinking about it.
So thinking about,
you know,
the ultimate podcasting earthling ad.
Everyone's got tools.
And, you know,
this is not going to be about how will you produce something.
It's going to be about the message, right?
Here's our opportunity.
Here's the chance to show how it really works,
how a community,
um,
how a community integrates marketing and advertising.
Let's try it.
This is,
and this community, by the way,
is the daily source code community.
So I'm,
I'm looking forward to the members of this active community to join in.
And then maybe you can spread some love to other communities.
Oh my gosh,
even like the Gilmour Gang.
From Westport,
Connecticut.
Bringing you the juice.
It's across the sound.
The new marketing podcast.
With your host,
Joseph,
Jeffy.
You've just entered the no bullshit zone.
Hey, Adam,
it's Jeffy here.
I've got two statements and a question for you.
Here's the first statement.
Uh,
was very intrigued with the whole Howard Stern,
Randon Ramble about,
uh,
Dissing podcasting,
basically what?
A load of crap.
Here's the one thing that I was thinking about.
His whole mission,
that basically podcasting,
will never be what radio is because of the live.
In fact,
and I was thinking of myself,
how long will it be
before iPods have some kind of Wi-Fi
and some kind of Skype or VoiceOver IP functionality
that ultimately will allow pod costs to be downloaded near live
and eventually with some kind of streaming capability
to be downloaded and streamed and even produced live.
That has got to be coming down the pike
sooner rather than later.
So that's comment number one.
Okay.
Actually,
I'm going to just jump in here
because otherwise I know I'll forget the first comment.
So it's two comments and a question.
Across the sound,
it's a good podcast,
by the way,
if you're interested in the stuff that we're talking about.
You know,
this is changing advertising,
etc, etc.
Um,
what the hell was your question again?
What was this comment?
I wanted to say something about it.
Oh my god,
this is horrible.
I'm kind of streaming capable.
Oh yes,
to be downloaded and streamed and even produced live.
That has got to be coming down the pike sooner rather than later.
So that's comment number one.
So,
yes,
I totally believe that.
And we will soon.
And with soon,
I've learned to say five years from now.
We will live in a completely connected world.
I'm totally with Steve Gilmore on this one.
Um,
you'll be able to connect any device to the network.
Anywhere,
anytime.
We can already do it on certain
airlines as broadband connectivity.
So the idea of actually storing stuff
on your computer will,
you know,
we'll kind of be outdated or storing stuff anywhere.
Um,
and it's not like,
you'll just be able to download this stuff and just listen to it in real time.
The economics will be there.
Um,
the infrastructure will be there, which of course means the economics will be there.
and everything will just be connected.
It would whether it's through edge or EVDO or UMTS,
or, uh,
Y-max or Y-Fi or whatever it is,
it's going to be completely connected world.
We'll just be able to connect anything
anybody anytime anywhere.
And that is totally happening.
And so,
yeah,
I think we could probably easily predict that there will be handheld devices.
Um,
the first versions of course will be cell phones that have MP3 capability.
And they're going to turn it around.
And there will be boxes that don't even have a phone built into it.
But we'll have high, high bandwidth connectivity to the network.
And then be able to access,
you know, your,
your,
your stored stuff somewhere and whether it's stored on your own server or your own space or someone else is,
you'll just be able to access it.
And it really will be the,
I truly believe that that,
that that will happen and that we won't have a need for,
um,
creating copies of all of this stuff before we can,
and then before we can play it.
So that's just my feedback on comment number one.
Comment number two,
uh,
I've been blocking about this whole notion of podfading and about burnout both on the side of production,
as well as consumption.
And I actually went and created the term in wiki pedia.
But for some reason,
the term was challenged as self-professed,
near,
nearology,
whatever.
And, uh,
and it was actually deleted and I just wanted what you thought about that,
why that would have been called self-professed,
nearology.
To me.
What?
That just seemed very, very suspect,
and I wonder who had a problem with that term being coined.
So that's statement number two.
Dude,
you're asking me about wiki pedia.
I'm not the right guy to ask.
I can't,
you know,
I was editing stuff that was getting deleted as I was writing it.
But anyway,
if you look at podcasting now,
wiki pedia,
it turns out Tristan Lewis has discovered all this stuff.
He's the first name that pops up at the top.
I'd never heard of Tristan Lewis in my life.
Here's a question for you.
I think you know what I'm going to say.
Cast Blaster and Skype.
How long before we see some kind of integration and capability and all patch,
because I think that when you do that,
we're going to have a phenomenal product that ultimately
becomes the gold standard.
At least from a PC standpoint,
in terms of facilitating and enabling any pod costs
that has a dialogue going in terms of an interview or co-host type format.
So anyway,
those are the two statements and questions.
Thanks so much.
Keep up the good works,
and I will see you across the sound.
All right, buddy.
Yeah, this is,
so there's an issue there,
is that it really has to come from Skype's end,
because we have to be able to split the,
I'm just using layman's term here.
We have to be able to split the internal audio stream.
So these are the streams that run through the CPU
and the digital sound processor,
whatever,
to be able to do that,
so you don't get this horrible echo and feedback stuff
to be able to integrate it with Cast Blaster.
Now there are other applications and other vendors of applications
that we've been talking to,
who will essentially allow the same thing,
and who will work with us on opening up the streams
into Cast Blaster,
and they will have dialogue,
like a Skype out functionality,
but it's not Skype.
So, you know,
the part of the beautiful thing of Skype is,
it's Skype, you know,
and you can just,
everyone has Skype or most people have Skype
and it's kind of become a podcaster thing.
So these other clients,
it will be the same thing,
it will be free and you'll be able to download it
and you know,
I'm trying to,
it will be great to have something integrated into Cast Blaster.
And maybe that's,
maybe that's the answer,
you know,
to have some of these other clients integrated into Cast Blaster,
but it is a problem.
Now the way I've solved it,
and I haven't actually used that,
but I will in a show in the near future,
you know,
I have this laptop and I have two sound cards.
Now if you have two sound cards,
then you can always route Skype
and separate sound card.
And of course I also use an external mixer,
then you can kind of all patch it together,
but not internally in Cast Blaster right now,
and that's really just a matter of,
you know,
not that Skype didn't want to do it.
In fact,
Skype was,
we talked to the Cast Blaster,
Mike and I talked to some of the dev guys
and were the hell were they in,
not least the way any.
Was it Lithuania?
A lot of you.
Shoot, I can't remember.
Now but then the whole eBay purchase
came down and everyone,
it all kind of like fell apart.
So that's kind of unfortunate.
We'll try and start that up again,
but I don't know if everything's kind of shaken
out over there yet.
All right.
One more comment,
then a piece from a podcast,
I want you to hear,
I love this podcast so much,
and then one more podcast,
safe song,
and then a matter here,
because work to do,
work to do.
Hey,
this is the podcast I'm from Zilkost.
And Megan from the Sheep to your podcast.
And we've got some ideas for you, Adam.
Firstly,
I think that we should forget all the vlogging,
the video podcasting,
and only have a silly names,
and come up with one.
Recasting.
And I think on the podcast,
music network,
there should be a remember me button under the login spot,
because sometimes I'll just get logged out randomly,
and if we ever return to the homepage,
we get logged out.
So I find a song that I like,
but then I'm not logged in,
so I can't add it to my playlist.
These are our ideas.
Our websites are Zolv.com,
and Sheep to you.blogspot.com,
spelled SHEP,
the number two EWE.blogspot.com.
Thanks, Adam.
All right, guys.
All right, bye.
Thank you very much.
Okay, so,
V casting.
Yeah, maybe.
I don't know.
I just like to take a video podcast,
that just kind of works better for me.
Now, about the remember me button,
you are so right about that,
that bites so much ass.
Yes.
That was number one on the list of things.
And you're going to see lots of changes coming
with the pod save music network.
One of them will be that your login
at the pod save music network
will stay persistent,
so you don't have to keep logging in.
You can, you do the whole remember me thing,
that'll work for purchases,
as well on the pod save music network.
And we're also merging it.
So, you'll have one sign on it,
pod cast alley,
same thing for pod show plus,
same thing for the pod cast delivery network.
So, yeah,
that's just a little bit of program,
well, not a little bit of programming.
So, major programming that had to take place
to kind of integrate all those pieces.
But that will be part of one of the many,
many things that we've been working on.
Now, I don't know if you heard the latest pod finder.
Oh, it actually, yeah,
you can find that in the iTunes pod cast directory.
And we feature a pod cast on it
that I thought was just so funny.
I love this pod cast,
that I wanted to play the same clip for you.
It's just two minutes.
It's all about customer service.
And, you know, you've heard the stories,
you've heard the,
I'm sure you've heard recordings before
of wacky customer service.
But to hear this on the podcast,
and service,
but to hear this on a serialized basis,
and hear it all the time,
it just makes you feel so good about,
you know,
not being the only one that has to go through this crap.
My PC freezes up,
so let's give our buddies over to Delicol
and see what we can find out.
What the,
what the numbers are.
Anyway, let's see what we get.
Welcome to Delicol.
Here we go.
And please press one.
To make a purchase,
get pricing information,
or complete an online order.
No, I just want to do money.
For technical support,
or for software and technical questions,
press three.
For all other issues related to a purchase,
already made.
Press four.
Let's try three.
Technical support.
Let me ask you a few questions,
so I can get you to the right technical support
represented.
All right.
This new system,
you can use your voice to respond
rather than pressing buttons on your phone.
Feel free to interrupt me at any time
when you know what to say.
Okay.
And if you ever get stuck,
just say help or repeat that.
Okay?
Let's get started.
Okay.
Are you calling to check
on the status of a service request?
Please say yes or no.
No.
Sorry,
I didn't hear you.
No.
If you've made a service request,
and you're calling to find out
when the status.
All right.
Are you calling about a product
that has the Del logo on it?
Yes.
Please say or enter
the products on the American Express Service Code,
or say, help me find it.
Help me find it.
Sure.
First tell me what product you're calling about.
You can say the Del product name like Dimension,
or something general such as Desktop or Printer.
Okay?
Go ahead.
PC.
Sorry.
I didn't understand.
PC.
A DVD drive.
Is that correct?
No.
Talk about service.
Talk about service is the name of the podcast.
It's full of gems like that.
You know, the world that we live in.
This could be.
It could be goes so far beyond customer service.
I mean, just the automated.
Messed up world we live in.
It just fits.
It's beautiful.
Okay.
Last piece of pod save music.
For my buddy Chris Rockwell,
who's been been working so hard on getting the pod save music network ready to.
To launch with with our sales and my gosh.
I mean, he's not the only one.
But I just wanted to highlight Chris because.
Well, shoot.
I got a song for him.
So here's a stucky and Murray.
I'm feel free to sing along.
Some people go on smoke breaks.
Others serve the web.
Some people get up and grab a coffee.
But I'm not one of them.
I don't like being a net.
All I smoke is grass.
I prefer to spend my time sitting on my skinny white ass.
I've been some life's all around the room.
Just right before I start.
Sometimes I'm in there for 30 minutes.
And all I do is fart.
So if the facts machines on the fritz.
And that'll cop here's going berserk.
Don't ask me to play Mr. Repairman.
When I'm taking a dump at work.
Or I'm taking a dump.
I'm taking a dump.
I'm taking a dump at work.
But don't bother me.
You can't just see him.
Just a taking a dump at work.
I go in and ride 11 o'clock.
I go back in after lunch.
Every time it comes out right on the dime.
And it looks like a nestly crunch.
And I'm afraid to use the journey.
But that's all in my floor.
There'll be a 10 minute layover.
Before I really want you to open the door.
I've been he's been taking a dump.
I'm taking a dump.
I'm taking a dump at work.
But don't bother me.
You can't just see him.
Just a taking a dump at work.
And if I'm not at my disc.
And I'll be on the porcelain throne.
I'll waste my day on the crapper.
Until it's time to go home.
I don't talk to me through the storm.
And you break my concentration.
The last thing that I need right now is a case of constipation.
And I'm a fan of the courtesy flush.
I like my ass tape of three-plot thick.
You know I sat on the shit of this afternoon.
And red male bills won't be dick.
Twice.
So you can call me Ishmael bitch when I'm taking a dump.
But taking a dump.
But taking a dump at work.
I don't bother me.
You can't just see him.
Just a taking a dump at work.
I don't care if the boss is looking.
I don't care if the phone is ringing.
I'll be in here dropping the news.
And you'll probably hear me singing.
Then I'll take a dump.
But taking a dump.
But taking a dump at work.
I don't bother me.
You can't just see him.
Just a taking a dump at work.
I'm proud to be here.
I'm proud of you.
It's very dope.
He's popping his hair.
And then he's going back to you.
Yeah.
I'm proud of you.
You can't anybody Fun.
The Windows Psych permitir ideally.
Cho, take it a dump and work!
Podsafe from the Podsafe Music Network.
Music.podshoes.com.
All right, everybody!
That's it.
I will be back tomorrow.
Let's see, whensays going to
be a whole day,
it's serious.
I'll probably record something there.
And that's probably the best.
Maybe a Phil the hotel, I don't know.
Um, and then Thursday, let me see Thursday this, I guess if there's a go back home right there's
a go back home Friday I'm home Patricia then leaves Friday evening for Rotterdam I'm home
with Christina for the weekend and then Sunday I'm off the San Francisco for a week, my
goodness. Life is good. Adam at curry.com for your feedback and promos.podshow.com
for your promos and daily source code.com for all the rest. Bye bye everybody.