This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
64.
All right, let me see what's this here, right?
No, no, no.
We do things different in Jersey, right?
Listen, we got the D.
Dan Allen, yeah, that's a good Jersey city.
Then we got the S.A.C.C.C.C.C.C.C.C.C.C.C.C.C.C.C.C.C, right?
Curry.
Yeah, that's where that is.
10 hundred radio stations used to be.
Yeah, they used to say they were at the top near private stable.
But they really weren't.
we're in Jersey in Chicago. Then we got C. Clifton. Yeah, so we got to Nellon's
the cook is Clifton, four, six, four, right? Yeah, yeah, yeah. You've
for Jersey, I've for Jersey. We got a lot of podcasts for Jersey. There's that
Jersey jam cast. We get Jersey tide. There's that, let's show it that no
cold girl. Something missing, that Bernie guy, the anti cast. Blue Jersey, who's that
Bob Bickley guy? Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. And Matthew Bishuff, a lot of nonsense. Jersey
B-Oh yeah, we got tons of haunted New Jersey hometown tales, scrap cast, Pete
Renee, Martinez shot, I can name a mall. Yeah, macatak. Yeah, the same for 64.
I was $16 million worth of airplane scrapped to my ass. Then the next
generation radio content in my ears. I like to think I'm flying to the
damaged church. I'm just hitting this male Kori.
This what you take.
I know that I stopped and began again
There's a big sand in the middle and with the fresh season
With the land of M&M
Such a beauty, lost in the melody
Like a fairy dying, back from the solid dream
This mystery of a body
Stops the body, should be fell in the air
It's kinda hot on me, cool with the water
What the matter, many of you love
If you can imagine how I wanna get you
Love in the bottle, maybe I should be shown
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Girl, you will miss me
When you're booking down sick, like crazy
And I try, but my knees get lazy
When you're bringing around somebody said, man, said, man
Everybody's just standing back cause
There's a thing up the night when I'm in the front of us
Can't battle in a team or something
Because you got to learn that, I'll make you want to battle in this
When you're recording, mama, there's many of you
Love, if you can imagine how I wanna get you
Love in the bottle, maybe I should be shown
In the bottle, maybe I should be sure
Love in the bottle, maybe I should be sure
You could, what if you can, same sex
Maybe it doesn't look modern
I know I just couldn't get it, so I didn't have to stay
I got it, so you can go go
Wanna talk about me, so sit down, you and me, yeah
Getting silly and just to kill an end
I know what I've been beginning again
There's a big sand in the middle and the branches
With the land I came in there, I'm such a rude and lost in the melody
I can't forget you back from the thought of you
Just a mystery of a body
Just a body should be a felonist
I got it, so you can go go go
Wanna what you're like, I got it, so you can go
Wanna see what I've been trying to show me
I'm in my heart, so you can go
Wanna what you're like, I got it, so you can go
This is kinda how I'll make you walk with them
With the motto, with the man, I'm a mini-eat
The music, I'm out of sitin, I'm rapin' your love
To be held by all, if it is to put your love in the car
Really explore the studio space with the cowbell
Everybody how you're doing is the daily source code
Coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey
known as Gilford in the United Kingdom
Once any other gardener's just left you guys missed it
Got a bit of a late start today
Christina announced last night she was not feeling well
So we decided to keep her home from school today
Which of course when you know, 16 is like, like we have any say over it
It's clear when you're the 16 year old doesn't want to go
She really doesn't want to go and she does like schools actually
So we got a little bit of a sleep in today until I was like quarter to nine
That's a big deal in the cottage
So of course, I'm running around behind myself already so much to do
I had some tapings, I was taping this morning in my bathroom
But of course, that is the true luxury of podcasting and independent production
Alright, thanks for all the opening show opens
For four, six, four today, 464 episodes and counting
Daddy cast the Jersey clan and of course comic strip blogger
He left an interesting comment yesterday in the show notes over a daily source code dot com
Let me let me read this for you
You didn't play intro four six three for me probably too scared you were you chicken. I well no problem
I've just sent you intro four six four actually comics are blogger
I just completely spaced on and I'm sorry. I wish I could do it over again
But you know, send whatever you want. I love playing openings and then he goes on to say regarding getting an
EEA visa for the UK as you know now the Christine and I are officially on on mom's co-tails
We're allowed to stay in the UK. He says maybe you could for once say in public. Thank you
You're well, let me do it. Let me let me say it once in public here
We go. I have to say this so yes, be commands it and I will read verbatim
Thank you European Union for freedom of movement so that I can't live in UK
Thank you
Yes, thank you European Union. That is kind of cool the way that works. I totally agree
Yesterday had a couple of German listeners check in and he's guys had a very serious question
Now, you know, I'm not a beer drinker. I definitely get my kicks from the sticks
But they wanted to know where the best placement is in a refrigerator for a beer for keeping it
For keeping it cold and drinkable and well, I knew this would happen all you have to do is throw it out on the Charlie once and the comments keep rolling in
Daniel from a stoic growth was done on Ontario here. I was listening to DSC463 and was rather concerned when I heard the comments from the two German listeners
Being a German expert myself. I referred to my handbook the
Deutsche Spundelskop Public Handbook called for Russia or poor
Guide to German living when you're not there anymore and it's beer handling section. It does refer to the correct temperature at which to
As a sort of store and drink beer and it has really nothing to do with the whether the fridge is colder or not
It where in the fridge is colder or not. It is more so concerned with the quality of the taste of the beer
That sort of mitigates the the bitter after taste
So the beer is to be refreshing but not freezing as otherwise. There is no taste all right and done on your reason that you would really
Sort of want to freeze it at the point of incomprehension is that
Is is because while the beer is too cheap the trick is to spend a little bit more money and get something that isn't as horrific
The handbook list is a good start any kind of beer that that is advertised on television and if you dispose of that you're sort of on your way
So I just thought I had no clue you could talk about beer like that
Just sort of mentioned that and then I'm sort of prepared to revoke the citizen service over that so
What the file note scruncher. Oh post-cript
Remember in school when they they tell you that that that the human brain is is based on is
Has the sort of wrinkles in it and that this provides additional surface area for where you blend just a flow
So to put yeah, I think I missed that particular class to be quite honest. I don't really remember
I've seen a brain it does look wrinkled the ability for all of the neurons and such the function and
Then if it were to suddenly you know smooth out then then you really wouldn't be able to so sort of support the kind of activity that
That the brain does
So and I'm thinking that this sort of applies in a similar respect to two to those scrunching folding business
I mean with your folding you sort of wrap it around a couple of times and you don't really get you sort of have a
Fixed surface area, but scrunching on the other hand and this is a sort of the magic science it work
I think
So to permits additional service area for the paper in which to sort of dispose of the adverse material that what otherwise
Well create a sort of a squishiness that that's
Don't even like so
That's sort of my pseudo scientific analysis. I thought you might enjoy that take care
Dude, of course. I completely
Appreciate you taking the time to send in a comment, but two things one
What the hell did you just say?
Two
Decaf sent say oh my friend. It definitely exists. Oh no
Just when you thought you were safe
It wings on by a
Can't do for you
Sneak it in under that satellite window before closes PW Fenton host of digital flotsom and producer of the pod show on serious
Hey Adam speed up
On Tuesday you played a comment by a Brit named Charles
He is now my new best friend because he absolutely loved the only thing I've ever done
That people almost universally complained about
Two people thought it was funny
Me and apparently Charles. So I love the guy. He's also right about digital TV
But it's not the fault of digital TV as much as the cable and satellite companies that keep adding more and more
Money generating content to a limited amount of bandwidth
I totally share Charles frustration. I have an enormous cable bill and the picture quality gets
Crappier and crappier every day
Charles, I feel your pain and
You should know you are clearly
Adam's brightest listener and a scruncher no doubt
Peter, what are you man? I forget have you told me?
Yeah, I got to tell you though. There's something different going on here. Peter, but we don't actually
Cable is is not very
Well penetrated throughout the UK because of the landscape, et cetera
And we do have these boxes over here which are called free view and these are digital
Boxes that take an analog signal off of your roof antenna or sometimes even if you're in a in a
Good reception area you can even just stick like rabbit ears on top of it and it receives one big fat analog signal
But that contains you know 20 or 30 different digital signals and that actually works quite well
It's very popular. I think there's like 15 million of those things sold in the UK
You pay once you pay like 50 50 pounds or whatever, so it's like let's just say 80 or 90 bucks maybe
And you take it home and you've got instant channels instead of your BBC one and two and and maybe you get your channel four
All of a sudden you got 20 channels to choose from and it does work and the reception really is quite okay
I forgot to tell you by the way at the top of the hour a top of the hour of body
All right, I got to go shoot myself
At the beginning of the show is what I meant
I
Played love and a bottle by Lee coolter and I just I don't want to say that it had a very just and timbre lake feel to it
Didn't know what you think and it wasn't someone bringing him over to the UK. I wouldn't mind seeing one of his shows
to reach Adam in America
now
plus one
six
one
six two five six three five seven
oh
For Adam in great Britain
dial
two
six eight one three seven five three
plus
four
two
six
seven five three
Thanks for calling the daily source code goodbye. Oh, oh, hold on a scruncher
Hi, Adam. This is Whitney Hoffman from the LD podcast
I've been noticing that there are a lot of people wanting about lack of link love or where's their pod show contract and they're doing such a great job
How come you're not noticing them in different comments that they're sending to you and I thought really what we need here is
List of rules or etiquette rules that we can all abide by to just trying and keep everything polite and
Step here's my version see what you think
Welcome children to the church of podcast and we have put together the following command and said that we all
milleted peace and harmony in the pod us here
Adam Curry is the pod father who helped bring us a pod show in the pod safe music network
There shall be no other pod fathers beforehand
That shall not work so false promises of other networks and shall honor the daily source code is the origin of the pod us here itself
That shall work to the name of the pod father and bay your tape for friend and any intention
Jesus to bestow up on you or your shell
That shall not covet thy neighbors touch a contract given time good content and audience
You too, maybe 14 enough to become part of the holy network
Remember the importance of the PME in pod camp and other podcasters need us and keep such gift together's whole way
Honor the pod father and lady Patricia said that your days in the pod school will be long and it may win the favor of the pod
Father and spouse
That shall not implicitly discytler podcasters no sending the spam
But you should fill up podcasters as you would want them to change you in time
That shall label that podcasters clean your own simplicity so they may be deemed safe for the workplace
Or of small fry in the car
That shall keep thy parameters between 30 and 60 seconds in the pod us fear so that all may play a listen with
That shall respect thy own talent and manage thy own brand and not leave it to others to do so for you
That shall respect the podcasters community elite when they show you love and thank them accordingly
That shall not cover thy neighbors listeners, but see to improve the podcasters and cultivate it by own following
That shall be honest and in particular with any dealings with fellow podcasters and see to bring
Harmony in the podisphere and
That shall not batch of the pod father, but contents are linked by our and shall be prepared to deal with
Bansions from the Holy Land of the D.A.C. if you break this command man, so ended our lesson
Anyway Adam, that's my view on things that we should all be treating each other
Kindly in the podisphere and
If you're doing a good job eventually everything else that you want will come
Thanks again for everything and for playing my past comments on the air. I really appreciate it
oh
Well just like the real ten commandments. There's some flaws in yours
I do appreciate it by the way. I did of course have to think of Joseph Jaffee
Not did you think bend over bitch?
I had to think of Joseph when I heard that. I disagree
You know, I think that's very much taking pod casting to through a blogging route and I don't really like that
That's what I think a lot of you know what pod casting has become which I think is a shame really
Because it's you know
I'm doing this for listeners if those listeners happen to be other podcasters great of course
And there'll always be something relevant for I hope all listeners and I hope listeners who aren't
Interested in making podcasters or what pod casting is just want to listen to show or some entertainment or just a half hour of whatever
You know, that's the people I'm doing it for and and I think that everyone will want to listen to a little bit of
Information about some other makeup of the audience
To me pod casting and really independently produced media whether it's video whether it's audio
It's about the audience and blogging which is you know, we have a blogger sphere that's where we have a pot of sphere
That seems like a little clickish, you know like a circle jerk of people just talking amongst themselves
I say yeah, I listen to your show. You listen to my show. Yeah, I read your blogs read my blog. Yeah, link here blog. Yeah, that's like
I don't come that's not in my DNA. That's not where I come from
Everyone who's listening is a listener and I know for darn sure
Thank you by the way for keeping those profiles coming into the voicemail
I'm saving him. I'm gonna do a show one day just all voicemail profiles just so we can all introduce ourselves to each other
So if you haven't done so send one in because it'll be a long show
That's for sure
It'll it'll probably be a separate podcast. I'll have to break it up into bits
So anyway, so yeah, I'm not too down with with all that yeah, just the circle jerkness of it all
Hey, you know David Epilito is that guitar man from New York who I like very much
I love the I love the songs he does. I love what he does in central park although I've never seen him perform live
I know I will that won't be too long when you know we will hook up eventually and I talk about him
Frequently on the daily source code and I got a piece of feedback that really blew me away
I would not expect anyone
To respond like this hey Adam this chat from Plato's Bullet hope things are going well with you
I just wanted to chime in on a few things actually just one thing really
But every show you do you promote this
David Epilito that guitar man from central park you always compare him to the Bob Dylan of our time
Uh-oh, no, I say he is the Bob Dylan of our time
I never said that I never compared him to the Bob Dylan of our time that would mean that there already is one
No, I think he is you know Bob Dylan he had some very catchy tunes, but I think it was really about the lyrics and what he was saying
And and having the balls to say what he was saying and I think you're wrong on that after listening to a bunch of his shows and everything
I really don't I don't see any comparison the Bob Dylan at all Bob Dylan
Created some amazing lyrics back in the day and I hold on dude
You're gonna tell me the Tom Cruise scares me isn't a fantastic lyric of our time of today
Sorry to say I saw him in Springfield at the Illinois State Fair a couple years ago
And I must say it was the worst concert I've ever been to but I did like his original stuff and and back in the 60s when he he was really when he's lyrics
Men something David Epilito doesn't have an ounce of talent that Bob Dylan ever had
David Epilito is the weird alien anchor Vic of our time. I think that's oh no, no, no, no, no
Now weirdo yankovic is something completely different and weirdo yankovic of our time is still weirdo yankovic
meant to say
But he comes up with some good guitar licks, but that's it really his lyrics are just parodies
Just like weirdo
He doesn't really have any talent. I think a third grade of dude just as well
But he does something for some reason have a great following and he's just that guy out there who hates the bush administration
And he wants everybody to you know make love not war and all that bullshit from the 60s that died out fast and
Obviously doesn't have a place for it. I'm gonna make a guess right now
Just listening to this I listen to how harsh you are dude
A third grader could do what he does. I don't think so. I don't think a third grader could come up with this kind of material
He has no talent all he wants is that hippie bullshit about make love not war. Oh, I'm sorry
I'm so sorry. I'm kind of for that and I'm no hippie
And he's just one of these guys that hates the bush administration. Well, there's a lot of these guys
That hate the bush administration and I'm not even counting myself as one of them, but
You know, there's a lot of people that disagree with the administration. I'm just going to guess
I'm gonna take a wild guess and say you're a scruncher in today's society
So if you want to hear other viewpoints like that
I encourage your listeners to check out Plato's bullet on the Potio network
Thanks a lot. I'm a scruncher. Yeah, told you
Scruncher. I'll check it out dude. Plato's bullet. Okay, I'm glad you're on
Potio plus on the pdn. We'll definitely check it out
Have to agree
No, actually I can't I can only disagree and by the way
He has pretty cool friends
Hey Adam David a belito here in New York City from thatcaptardman.com
I know you'll appreciate this a friend of mine called me up. He's a musical legend and
He wanted to say something on your show. He wanted to say something to anyone who would listen
He told me because he knows that with as much laughs and as much fun as I love to have
And as much as I love to find new music and get it out there that we want music to make a difference again
And he's the guy that brought the Beatles to America. I told him the daily source code was the best bet in town
So here he is
But David a belito is doing it
But I do love the company
It's so beautiful purpose
The new we knew yorkers
Hopefully have discovered it had to take you to go to the home
Central Park
Thanks Adam man. Look me up when you get to New York, right? Definitely dude
Definitely cool. It did burn steam
I
Wonder has he actually listened to anything on the pots? How old is Sid burn steam these days?
He's got to be pushing 70
Oh, we totally totally need to get him involved with the pod save music network. How cool would it be?
Let's do a Sid burn steam show
Well, he just pulls out the songs that he likes from the pod save music network David. We've got to put this together man. That would be so awesome
We'll get a producer for him even just having listen to stuff and if he likes it then
We put it in his show. Wouldn't that be awesome? Sid burn steam dot pod show dot com da a girl can dream
Yesterday I was asked to talk about my dad which I
Admittedly don't do very often on the daily source code and I talked about a lot of my feelings and if you want to you should probably go back and listen to four six three if you want to hear that and I you know
I was talking about listeners
And whenever I'm speaking, I really do feel like I'm talking to a group
The group I visualize is much smaller than than the group that is actually listening and I forget I forget that
Well, even my sister and Italy is listening
Hi Adam. It's your sister willow from Florence
I'm sending an audio comment since you specifically
Said that you wanted audio comments and not emails
Okay, anyway, it's obviously commenting on our father and what you said
I'd have to say that I agree with most of what you said
One thing struck me as odd that you said at a certain point now
I can't really remember I was listening to it on the way home. I was in a car with the kids
I think you said talking about kids. I think you said that he wanted
more other kids a wife other kids now that never
Never seemed to me to be that way. I mean, I always had the impression that the whole idea was yes
Reboot new life, but new life, you know, having being the single cool bachelors, whatever and
I always had the idea, you know that after a couple years like hmm right in my art sort of like, you know
Having a wife wasn't too bad after all and so
You know, he got his himself a wife, but I really don't think that
He was waiting for more children. So that the fact that that of course, then he does have another child, but I
I never had the impression that he would want it, you know, like he was when he was a child
Once the fact occurred once you know he thought he was gonna
Be a better father just time around. He was gonna have a second chance and I don't think that worked out either, but
Doesn't matter what I also wanted to say that yes, we've tried a lot and we've all given him, you know, whatever
We could give him and in the end I haven't given up
I've just decided not to expect anything anymore maybe that's
Maybe that is giving up and in my from my point of view, it's just you know if I don't expect anything
I won't be disappointed you have one big disappointment today that you sort of decide
I'm not gonna expect anything anymore, but you know once you do that you just free
You know, and I feel you know, I feel I
For me that's the solution. I don't expect anything and so I don't know if your listeners care
You care
This was just my two cents. Okay. Oh, and and a quick promo
From the hills of Florence at idly dot podge show dot com or to my personal website where you can find links is
www.curry.it
Okay, have a nice day. Bye. Joe Bella
Man, this to me is a true historic moment in podcasting. I mean, I could not
It was so cool yesterday
Yeah, it came in last night and I heard this and I like wow, man
This is awesome. This is really cool. Thank you Willow. I
Really really appreciate that
Yeah, and and you know what in hindsight, I think you're right
It wasn't a reboot for new kids, but once of course we knew that that they were gonna have kids
And once that came along. I think you're right. I think he had his and if actually even said that he even said
I'm gonna do better this time. It's like well fuck you
But I think you're right. I think just
Learning to not expect anything is probably the best way
To deal with it, but I'm not alone then and I knew I wasn't and
But wow, what an interesting way to have this conversation
I love you fantastic
More comments about this about this discussion came in as well
Hey, Adam, this is the philosophy guy. I wanted to comment about your comments about your dad
I too a child of divorce my dad decided to
reboot his life when I was six so it kind of let us
High and dry and he went out and
Did his thing and left my mom and
My self and my sisters alone for a long time and
So we never I never really knew him
We did a few things together, but nothing that I would
Write home about
So I feel I feel you're you're paying sometimes
But you know what it taught me it taught me that
What's important is how
I treat my own family, you know my my three kids in my wife and
When I feel like
Rebooty my life you know, I just have I remember that
You know, it's not about me. It's about the family and I mean we smack that kid in the background
Tell the kid to shut up. I never want to have
I never want to have
Sorry about that. I had to
I never want to
Leave my kids the way I was left. So
I get that sense
Adam that you're the same way that you sound like you have a wonderful relationship with
Christina and
Your wife Patricia and
And that it's it's family that matters and
I wish you all the best and
I can understand if you don't want to talk about those painful things
I know that sometimes I don't but
Sometimes it's it's good so take care
And God bless all right philosophy guy
Yep
You know what I think we all do have that if you've never had the feeling of wanting or needing a reboot
Maybe you should just try it the trick of course is to do it with your family and we've done that several times
We rebooted from the United States to
Europe and after
Patricia got ill we definitely did a full-blown reset you know delete the email
Cut the credit card sell all the crap. We did a major reboot when we came to the UK
And that is a lot of fun. We really enjoyed and it may be it's not for everybody but we really we really do enjoy it
And yeah, of course
And you know and every parent has that moment where you mouth opens and your own parents come out, you know, it freaks you out
But a lot of it is good and of course I got a lot of values from from my both my parents
But I don't know maybe maybe I was expecting to maybe I was set up incorrectly by trial literature
As of what to expect from the the perfect family life. Hmm. Yeah, that's possible
Not everybody has the nine to five job my my dad certainly didn't
So you know, I guess it is a balance of everything and sometimes it works and maybe sometimes it doesn't I you know
I'm it's not painful for me
It's just I like I don't know what to say it's like that's it. I guess. I just accepted. I'm I'm I think I am more of a guy who just accepts stuff
Like
The the need I have right now to tell you about the accurate target cast for the
RDS SUV
It's like an infomercial only
We're not hiding it and it's actually good content
We're not just selling you a car. We're telling you some cool stuff and some interesting insights into the manufacturer and in this case
Particularly the sound system
You can find that target cast that accurate out to podshow.com and
Let's see anything up
One more song before I leave you for today
This is just something I found on the podcast music network. I thought oh, it's Japanese
Let's try it
I don't know if I'm gonna attempt it. It's the free trans ensemble
It's how to condom on hot
How to condom on a rama
Hey
Don't know
If I'm not
You don't know
paulin hyer sin ni ka
ad kara kusawa itzari lado kiwi
daen ladai ahhashari imaku komiro dao
you
Perhaps you've never seen such aot
The power of a dream is according to a good
I don't know if there's anything I can do
Now, I'm going to be here
I'm going to be here
Now that I'm off, it's gonna be I'm gonna be here
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you...I love you, I love you, I love you,, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, like I love you, like I love you, I love you, I love love love, I love, it, I love you, I love you, I love, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love, I love you, I love, I love, I love, you, I love, you,
Now that I've got a lot of my friends in it, and now I've got a lot of my friends in it,
I'm gonna try again.
How the condo mama?
There we go.
Free trans ensemble, you can find them at the Podsit Music Network, links, of course, in the
show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Even though we have another cottage that we think we're all good to go on, we're still
looking in more just in case because we've learned our lesson now that it can be pretty messed
up here in the middle of the UK when it comes to purchasing a home.
So we're gonna go look at something else today, and tomorrow will be food bar, wait, when
is there a Thursday?
I was already thinking it was Thursday, okay, so tomorrow will be food bar Thursday, please send
me all your songs, suggestions, dailysourcecode.com, Adam and Podsitio.com, take care
everybody.
I'll see you tomorrow, bye-bye.
Another Pod Show Podcast, stick it in your ear.
Get this Podcast and we're great ones like it on the Hyperformance Podcast delivery network
from Podshow and LineWite Networks.
I love it.