This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 3-8-6
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Hi Adam, how was it?
Just catching up on a few daily source codes.
I'm going over behind.
And I just want to call and say thank you for the podcast, man.
It's brilliant and this is the Friday morning.
I'm walking home with work through the summary London and I can't really see any better way
of starting a weekend than yeah.
Yeah, I'm going to go into my ears and enjoying it.
Thank you, man.
Bye bye.
It's not all that she thought it was.
It's out on the right.
It's all down.
Every time you come around and tell me all the things you do.
But these are cheese.
I'll be ready to regret that you will stay the same,
unless you just not get it through.
In the morning sun, I roll the fat blood just to wake me up.
Sometimes I find it's hard to understand the way it can.
It's out on the right.
It's all down.
Every time you come around and tell me all the things you do.
These things are cheese.
I'll be ready to regret that you will stay the same,
unless you just not get it through.
It's out on the right.
It's all down.
Every time you come around and tell me all the things you do.
These things are cheese.
I'll be ready to regret that you will stay the same,
unless you just not get it through.
The link is in the morning sun.
I started up, woke up, rolled up a flat, was it fat blood?
How can you go wrong with the song like that?
It's Friday, everybody.
How you doing?
Coming to you from Curry Cottage, another beautiful day in the United Kingdom.
It is the Daily Source Code, the Friday festivities,
got some cool music lined up.
We're going to keep it light today, some funny stuff.
I cannot believe I didn't open up phone lines much, much earlier in the show.
I'm enjoying this so much.
Actually, I do know why I didn't do it.
It is because you couldn't get a reliable MP3 email to you.
The quality was always crap.
Now, the quality is always going to be crap with a phone call, of course.
But this J2 connect service that I'm using.
They email it to me in a format.
The quick time understands.
I was able to write a little apple script.
So when it comes in, it just converts it to an MP3,
and I can drag it right into my show prep outline.
And I'm loving it.
It's so fun to hear what everybody has to say.
If you want to call in, and this is, of course,
it's listeners who are calling, which I love hearing from podcasters.
They've always got something very astute to say as well, or most of the time.
And always get their plug in.
But it's so cool when listeners who have no desire to be a part of podcasting,
just are enjoying what we're doing.
That's what really turns me on.
A number of New Jersey, 201, 625, 6357 in the United Kingdom in London,
O2076, 813753.
Actually, I'm doing that wrong.
How do they say that here?
O207, 61813753.
I think that's, I'm listening to all the different radio stations here.
Trying to pick up as much local slang, which is possible.
Wow, it totally feels back to your topic that you've been discussing about describing
breast and the masculine.
You know, this is quite disturbing trend I have to say.
I have received at least five different voice mails talking about guys who name their
women's breasts.
You know, actual names.
I had a girlfriend in high school and we used to call her a skill and tech.
And let me tell you we had many x ones again.
Anyway, nice listening.
I really enjoyed it. Keep it up.
I'll see you subscribe.
Alright, buddy. Thank you very much.
Now we're from our sponsor.
It's the yanks.
This is the Brits.
We'll drive each other crazy, but everybody knows that it's a parent to see.
They're just like you and me.
It's the yanks and the Brits.
The yanks versus the Brits.
Mind the gap.
On our continuing journey to investigate the true differences between the yanks and the
Brits, we find a call for help.
Good morning, Adam.
I've just listened to the Charlie from Bayer.
So I'll go.
This is Logan and Southwest Florida.
I'm going to have to do some flying.
And I was thinking of a second that you could do on what to.
I have to lead the country to do flying.
I've never been outside the country in that 50.
I'm not exactly crazy about flying.
I was wondering if you could get chips on how not to be an ugly American when you go
overseas.
And what type of electric they use, what adapters do I need, all these types of issues.
Just a thought.
Anyway, a lot of it when Patricia's on with you, man.
You are so married.
And by the way, I have the same problem with the night's.
Let's do.
Just think of it as male, metapods.
You'll be okay.
Calculator five.
Well, okay.
So you didn't say where you were flying to, but I'm just going to presume you're
flying to Britain.
So I hope you are.
And hopefully we can get some information from our British friends and fellows and listeners
who can tell us exactly what really irks them when you're walking around as a tourist.
And all that other stuff.
That's pretty easy.
You can get a lonely planet guide and figure out what adaptor you need.
That's easy enough.
And a shoot.
Just go to any store at the airport.
And they'll the point in the right place.
But really, it's about the behavior.
I am, I too am very interested in that.
More about the night sweats in a second, as well as we continue with one more piece here in our
Yanks versus the Brits.
Alex McCordys sent me an email.
Which he thought would be entertaining.
It's actually he says sorry, just the final audio contribution which I found entertaining
might rock a few DSC listeners who've now found themselves in a chilled space of calm and relaxation
thanks to your brain wave generator.
Yeah.
I think I've given people the permanent migraines.
A sales call on this piece of audio that shows that Brits can actually get riled and
an angry and dump a lightness right out the window.
You Yanks will love this.
This is someone from British Telecom, a telemarketer calling.
And the recipient of the call is also British and not happy.
What the hell do you want?
We're calling today to ensure you're getting the best vangiven service.
Beat your corner for them.
Fucking horn, call up your pissin' ass and get me off this.
It's an extra friendly horn, an alcohol.
Fucking British Telecom.
Okay, say that fucking bell now.
Get that fuck up my phone line.
Deal, all the time.
I understand, sir.
That's good.
We're making it.
And now we're making it.
We're making it again.
I wanna ride our carmen.
When you're calling it, fucking neck.
And I'm in.
Typically nobody will copy it.
Yeah.
I'll only take it.
You're a couple of seconds.
Oh, don't go.
And fuck up.
No, fuck up.
No, come on.
We end.
Yeah, no problem.
Thank you.
Don't.
You're dead.
Again.
Right.
Thank you for your time, sir.
Thank you for using these things.
Thank you.
I got it.
Jesus Christ, Diane.
Could you do me a favor?
Listen, sir.
Let's call for me.
Of course.
Diane, could you leave me a favor?
Listen, let's call for me, please.
I must say that we got a lot of telemarketers when we just installed our phone line.
And indeed, a lot of it is British Telecom trying to get you a better deal.
And when you say, look, I'm just not interested in whatever you have to say.
I don't have any time right now.
They're truly surprised.
But it'll cost you less money.
I don't care.
Leave.
And please take my name off your list.
I have found that when you ask that, they really do take it off the list.
The bank.
Barclays.
Also, they were calling all the time.
And then finally, I turned around and said, OK, I'll take your damn savings account offer,
whatever.
But then you need to go fix the following things for me.
And he did.
So it does.
Yeah, some of it really works well.
But this clearly pissed this guy off to no end.
Back to the night sweats for a second.
Hey, Adam, it's Kelly, a listener from Malibu, California.
I was just listening to the Charlie from Tuesday.
And I wanted to comment about something you mentioned on a lecture,
sexual moment.
It was about night sweats.
You know what?
It's not just the guy thing.
Throughout my adult life, I have gotten them just completely randomly.
Might have at one night and not have it again four months.
But I can wake up and be totally drenched.
And I have to go get a towel to put down on the bed.
So I have something to dry the lion.
Of course, my husband thinks it's totally wacky.
But I have no explanation.
It's just the way I am.
So I just want to pass that along.
Keep up the good work.
Let the show love Patricia.
Bye.
Thanks, Kelly.
You know, I think we've hit on something here.
This is not a small problem.
We could actually start a club.
I can just see the public service announcements now.
Millions of Americans suffer from night sweats.
Just to actually had a thought about that.
I'm sorry for not putting this in Tuesday show comments.
But I'm hoping you'll see this.
Just listening to Tuesday's episode discussing your body overheating problem.
Yeah, the spontaneous combustion.
I had the same issue.
And the thing I found the problem was me being dehydrated.
So the coffee and the splits would certainly hydrate.
Drink plenty of water.
And it will bring you in Patricia together.
So I've been taking everybody's advice.
I've been wearing boxers and wife beaters to bed.
No problem at all getting the sleep.
I thought I would never be able to get to sleep wearing clothes.
But that's actually working.
And I tried to hide the hydrating bit.
Drank three big glasses of water before I went to bed.
Actually, even since wearing the boxers.
I haven't had any problems at all.
Hold on a second.
Sorry.
I don't have time for that.
Whatever it is.
Just interrupted my train of thought.
Okay.
Well, it seems like more people have this.
And that seems to be a pretty good fix.
But what it comes from?
I don't know.
I know there's doctors listening.
I'd love to get some insight in some analysis.
Just to why this happens.
Is this a direct result of the brain processing information?
I'm sure Patricia has also said that.
You know, my brain has to do a lot at night.
As true.
Is that a part of it?
Is it actually a symptom of spontaneous combustion?
Let me know.
Please.
Voice mail.
And I still can't figure out how to get a message on there.
So if you just hear some recorded message saying leave your message.
You got you're at the right place.
201.
65.
Or 0207.
681.
3753.
That's if you're in London.
Hey, Adam.
This is Darren from Southern California.
I just wanted to say that.
I love your show.
I've been an avid listener of the DSC since about January 2005.
And hey, whatever happened to the drum cadence of the day.
Yeah, that's a good question, man.
In the beginning, I found that just about everyone in America certainly has been in a marching drum band, usually at high school.
And we had a little segment called the drum cadence of the day.
I think we're pretty tapped out on that.
But if anyone has a great cadence, you know, of course.
I'd love to hear it.
Love that stuff.
Well, anyway, just wanted to tell you about a great experience I had over it.
And before I also, there's another issue there.
A lot of the songs weren't pod safe, so that people playing hits.
But you can't play it.
Okay, so I think you're going to say you're over at Curry Castle in second life.
The castle in second life.
I was hanging out at the castle this morning, chatting some of the visitors and talking to this one guy about Jim Kramer's mad money.
He's a show on CNBC.
And what do you know, this guy that does the mad money machine podcast?
I work in the finance industry, but haven't had a chance to check it any financial podcasts.
So about 10 minutes after this happened, I went over to iTunes, found this podcast, and then hit subscribe.
So podcast, you get to new subscriber, and I, and listener, get a new podcast.
It's a cool podcast, by the way, check it out sometime.
And I'm sure this is all part of what you're doing there in second life.
And I got to tell you, man, it totally works.
So thanks again for what you're doing in second life.
And more importantly, thanks for what you're doing in real life.
And I hope to see you soon.
Thank you.
That's really sweet.
I appreciate that.
Isn't that nice?
Most importantly, thank you for what you're doing in real life.
That's nice.
Of course.
I'm going to take two minutes to finish right now.
Second life, man.
What is all this stuff?
Is that a thing?
Because one of the cool things fans but I've got so little fun stuff.
All we really do is you can easily hold the eels.
But they won't just stay even more busy and stuff, but it's better to stay.
And simple things.
So what is all this stuff?
No, watch it all right, man.
I just hold your part and you have fun.
It's better to do it all right.
Right, the castle is closed,
but it's a huge lie.
I'm adding it.
It's crazy.
Jeff Smith, you're genius.
I think I've got it figured out.
Yes, I do.
Because what you just said about meeting someone at the castle,
now it's all come together.
Finally, I see it.
And if you haven't tried it,
maybe if I explained it in this manner,
you'll understand better what's going on.
First of all, we're very accustomed to using internet technologies for
asynchronous or synchronous communication.
So an example, but podcasting is asynchronous.
I make it, you hear it some other time,
whenever it's convenient for you.
Which, of course, is a revolution in media,
just all by itself.
Then we have email, which is also a synchronous by nature,
which was a revolution.
And now, of course, some people like myself hate
because it's an open,
it's an open hole in my communication life where anything
and everyone can get through,
unfortunately, because it's that way,
the opportunity and all the other crab come at the same time.
So we don't have to talk about that now.
Then a chat, which we've been using for many, many years.
And the culture of chat, if you have kids,
look at what they're doing with MSN,
they're probably on MSN or on Yahoo or on AOL,
Instant Messenger, or all three at the same time,
very possible.
Excuse me, Sensei.
At the office, we use Skype,
because we use Skype as a communications tool for voice a lot.
And therefore, it's usually everyone has it open,
and that's kind of the office.
Oh, quite excuse me.
That's the office, Instant Message System.
I see second life in my real life.
Almost no different than show notes,
or no different from comments at curry.com.
We have ongoing conversations about stuff discussed in the show,
which doesn't necessarily make it back into the show.
Some of it does.
Now, that, of course, is asynchronous by nature.
You can always check in and see other conversations.
But when you really want to chat with someone,
and by the way, marketing executives used to cream over the idea of
having a celebrity in a chat room.
It still happens.
It's the AOL, this is all the time,
and it's very, very successful.
You know, an author, a musician, an actor,
some real life form of celebrity shows up
in this cyber area, cyber life,
where you get queued up, and you can chat,
and you can ask questions.
And, of course, you're not in the same physical location,
but you probably never would have that opportunity anyway.
So, it's only enhancing to what you didn't have, I guess,
because you are actually communicating with that person.
So, it's the same thing.
In second life, which is this virtual world
for those of you just hearing about it for the first time,
when you log in there,
you can do a lot of stuff that emulates real life.
You can build things, you can buy land,
you can interact with people,
but a lot of it is really based on chat,
and it's slightly done.
But a lot of it, I think, is also a platform
for communication.
I'll get to that in a second.
What is the main difference here?
As a pilot, you develop a skill,
maybe it's almost a sense,
but let's call it a skill called situational awareness.
And situational awareness, you may not realize this,
but the windows in the cockpit really aren't used
that much in flight.
They're important for landing,
certainly, to get your bearings to the runway, et cetera.
But really, it's the reverse of driving a car,
where in the car, you're looking at the road,
looking at your mirrors, looking at all the other idiots,
make sure you don't bump into anything.
And once in a while you make glance at your instruments,
usually the speedometer see how fast you're going.
And there's warning lights and stuff,
if your petrol is low or your oil,
you know how that works.
So, it's the reverse in an airplane,
where you're really looking at the instruments,
and as a part of your scan of the instruments,
you'll also scan the outside,
you'll scan your whole peripheral view of what's going on in the sky.
But because of the radio communications you have,
and remember, this is just,
it's a form of chat.
And in fact, the way we talk on the radio and aviation
is just like chat except it's all in a book.
You know, so we know what we're going to say,
and we know what the response should be,
and we understand.
And it's oftentimes, and I do that a lot,
you'll break the format.
So, for instance, if I'm leaving raw,
if I'm arriving at Rotterdam Airport,
and I haven't done Rotterdam more than three, four times in my life.
And, you know, sometimes I'll have to ask something like,
okay, look, I think I'm over Oscar reporting point,
just could you just confirm that.
And the tower will jump in and help.
And then when I land, you know,
after I said that I vacated the runway,
you know, I'll usually say something in Dutch,
and I'll thank the controller for helping me out,
and you kind of break format.
And people do that all the time.
But it is a very strict means of communication,
and it gives us a lot of information in the air
as to what else is going on, who else is in the air,
and where they are.
So, you kind of have this mental image of every single aircraft
in the vicinity of where you are and what you're doing,
and actually far beyond that,
depending on what you're doing and where you are
and what you're what frequency you're on.
And it's funny because you develop this mental image,
and if I had radar on board,
the force is way too expensive for an aircraft.
Like this, you know,
I could actually see that situation around me.
But you still, as a pilot, you get trained,
and you have this situation on awareness.
And that's what it is in the second life.
Because unlike chat,
when I'm chatting to a couple of people at the office,
I actually know where they're sitting.
I don't know if they're sitting there at that moment,
but I know where they're sitting,
so I have a mental image,
and I have some situation on awareness.
Sometimes actually in a place where you can see it,
then the conversation becomes much more natural.
People who want just want to listen in,
will stand back a little bit.
People who want to break off the conversation
can actually move away,
if they move away far enough,
that chat will no longer cross over into my view.
And there's also,
people express themselves with different gestures.
And it's just a part of your personality,
which really, really helps.
The way someone has decided to dress themselves up
in a virtual world does tell you a bit about their personality,
the same as it does in real life.
So, for me,
it's an extension of this situational awareness
that I already,
well, I don't really have it.
You see, I think that's why I'm so interested in it,
because I hear feedback from people.
Now when they say,
when I get a voice mail saying,
hey, I'm walking on the streets of London,
got it, you know,
got a mental image,
no problem at all.
But if it's just comments from people,
you really don't,
there's less of a connection there.
And it's much harder to keep a multi-voice conversation going.
So when you bring all this together,
and my expression, of course,
is that I'm seven feet, six inches tall in second life.
And I have a castle where people come and hang out,
and I've got all kinds of place to sit
and to hang, and last night,
I tried to drop by twice a day,
usually early in the morning here,
so I can clean up whatever crap was left overnight,
and I can change and modify stuff,
because once you get like 50 people
in your general area,
the system really slows down.
You just can't do much more,
and you can't edit stuff,
and move stuff around,
let alone replace the castle,
which I did yesterday morning.
So last night,
I had a call on 11 o'clock with a pod show call,
which was also cool, by the way,
about that earthly stuff,
getting very close to that.
And so after that, I figured I'd check in,
and so I'd drop in,
and there's probably 15, 20 people on the roof of the castle,
and a lot of them were listeners,
and here's how it goes.
Hey, Adam, how you doing?
I'm a listener.
I've never been in second life.
I came in because I heard about it on your show,
and then we have maybe it'll be a comment.
Lots of people saying nice things about my mom,
wishing her well,
and it's really nice.
And for some reason, it just works.
Then I have that situational awareness.
People understand if I'm not typing back for a second,
because my avatar will actually walk over somewhere else.
It works.
It really does.
So it's not something that I want to get completely immersed
in on the level that some might,
but I can definitely see a use for it.
Oh, shoot.
Right in the middle of something good, too.
Always here to spoil the fun.
I'm a satellite repair man.
I'm coming after you.
What's he gonna do?
He'll fix your misconceptions,
and answer questions, too.
There's nothing in the universe
and he can't do for you.
A satellite repair man.
Here I go.
Show.
Which means satellite listener series stars 102.
That's it for the show for you.
Download our data source code.com.
We'll see you back on Monday.
PCH is next.
And we'll just continue a little bit on the second life.
Because last night,
it's too bad the satellite folks can't hear this.
Last night, a listener from the UK drop by.
Her name is Emma.
And I'd never met Emma before.
Now, Emma has actually been listening to the Charlie.
What did she say?
Since January 2005 or something.
So almost a year and a half.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
She's exactly what I was talking about.
Oh, man.
It's Friday.
You can tell.
I'm done.
I'm fried.
I'm toast.
So she said, you know, I heard you talking about this thing.
So I figured to come check it out.
Emma, totally, totally let loose.
She's putting on a ripped t-shirt, a wet t-shirt,
put on a pod show t-shirt, was dancing around.
And of course, I got my, my, my CDs out.
And none of this pod safe.
And I'll talk about that in the sec.
And, you know, we just started jamming.
And then she said, oh, I need a stripper pole.
Well, I tell the ported out.
And this was telling us a lot about Emma.
I tell the ported out.
Got a stripper pole.
And she started dancing on it.
And then I threw down the dance pad.
And everyone was, and people generally were having a good time.
I can't make it up.
And, you know, and these are, you know,
people who listen to financial, who work in financial industry.
You know, doctors, lawyers, goofballs,
losers, winners.
Everything was there.
We just danced.
And having a good time.
And all the while kind of chatting along.
And much to my happiness this morning.
A voice mail from Emma.
Hello, big boys.
This is, I'm not nasty to go.
You may dance a little pole for your pleasure.
Last night.
You bad boy.
I hope we can do it again sometime out of.
Oh, understand.
I promise not to grab your cock and public.
So technically, you didn't.
And technically, you can't.
I've turned all that stuff off.
So you can't just access that area of my avatar.
But it told me a lot about how you were thinking Emma.
Okay.
But you touched my ass and then that got all excited.
So I forget about that.
You know, I know because I had some private conversation with Emma.
She would never be like that in real life.
But I think that she really let loose.
And she like being the center of the party for a little while there.
And it was fun if we really had a good time.
Okay.
So here's, um, getting positive music into the system.
And this is just a little tin foil hat moment.
Oh, oh, Jeff Smith.
Oh, Jeff.
I can, I think I want to commission that one.
A tin foil hat moment or something like that.
We've got to think about that.
Oh, that's a good one.
The way, so you can, so you can set a streaming URL.
So that anywhere within a parcel of land,
you will, everyone will hear the same stream.
Now, I, I like that because it's pretty reliable and it'll work for concerts.
But I don't like it for just playing something in the world.
And the way you do that is you can actually play way files.
And so I figured out a script, which, uh,
now the way files are limited to 10 seconds each.
That's all you can upload into second life, which, of course,
bites major ass.
So, um, so I, so I figured out if I upload a song and
chop it into like 30 10 second bits, um,
then I can have those play in sequence.
What's nice about it is if you walk away from the source that's playing,
it'll get softer if you walk closer gets louder.
And so it's, it's a, it's a much more real, uh, vibe to it.
So if anyone out there can, is it either an apple script or anything else
that'll run on the mac, you know, of course,
some unique thing will be fine too.
I need an easy way to just drop an MP3 file into a folder onto a,
script icon or whatever.
And have it automatically be chopped up into, um,
uh, 10 second bits in waveform.
And then ideally, of course, from there, upload automatically into my
accounted second life, but I guess I'll have to do that manually.
Then I can import it into an object and make it play.
It's a horribly, horribly tedious process,
not cheap because it costs you 20,
linden dollars to upload every sound.
But I, I, I really want to experiment with that.
And I just don't have the patience to go through trying to
script that and, and cutting it manually into,
into all those pieces, forget about it.
Okay, so that's it for second life.
And Emma, thank you so much for sending that in.
I, I really appreciate it.
Nice to meet you.
Come back anytime now.
Yeah.
Come extra.
You see?
Or should I say controversy?
Between comics, drip blogger and Roger Smalls.
Now, we heard yesterday from Roger Smalls who is back,
that he was really, really upset with comics, drip blogger.
And I saw on thecurry.com comments,
CSB had posted an entire apology,
and it doesn't stop there.
I, I'm carry.
I would like to apologize to Roger Smalls publicly.
That's true that I have drawn a comic strip,
where it was suggested that Roger is not
Roger is not meeting up with you, Adam, Kerry, because Roger is ugly and all shy.
I apologize for that, and I have just removed the part of this comic strip where Roger
was featured, albeit as fictional character called Roger Squalls, not as Roger Smalls.
Anyway, I was wrong.
You are one handsome, handsome, handsome Roger, you are not ugly, you are beautiful,
Roger.
Okay.
So, the other smalls, please accept my apology, so remade, peace, okay?
Finally, anybody who is offended by any of my comic strips or by any of my tabloids
style writings, please contact me directly, and I will remove related pieces that are
offending you.
I will accept, however, requests only from people depicted, not from sad parties.
Legendary of this, sometimes people like art or publicity about themselves, no matter
whether it is good or bad.
According to the motto, there is no such thing as bad publicity.
So, have a nice weekend, Adam, Kerry.
I wish you, sincerely, a good health to your whole, whole, family.
Ciao, Adam.
Bye.
Yeah.
People say to me, why did you do the comic strip blogger?
You know what?
I just treated him like any other person who shows up at the Daily Source Code front door,
and lo and behold, there is a pretty nice intelligent guy underneath all that rough
exterior.
Now, unfortunately, Roger hasn't heard this public apology because he sent me something
this morning before I did the show.
So he may have changed his feelings about you there, CSB, after what he just heard, but
as of this morning, he was definitely definitely not pleased.
Let's listen.
Hey, Adam, Roger, here.
I heard that one of your listeners mentioned on last week's show, that's the international
masturbation months at the moment.
Now, not sure how this works, does it mean I get to enjoy myself for this month, but
then have to wait 11 months before I get to square my care again.
And can you explain?
Wait a minute.
What did you say?
Wait 11 months into what?
How for this month, but then have to wait 11 months before I get to square my care
again.
Oh, Roger.
Did you actually say, Scort my curd?
Can you explain this, please?
Thank you.
I want to say put the send you some songs in about masturbation and I found something.
Hey, you know, I think there was a, wasn't there a piece about comics, Drew?
I don't know.
Is this yesterday's piece?
I don't know what they had I'm doing.
Now I'm all confused.
Hold on.
Is this still the masturbation?
Yeah.
I won't care.
Hold on.
Just say this.
That's the song about wanking.
Yeah, this is the one he sent me.
That's right.
It says one person who knows about easing the loneliness of an empty life.
He's come to the nano magazine.
Then it's the comic strip blogger.
I don't think it's international masturbation month within now.
I think it's more like international masturbation 52 years.
Because I think that guy's been a tougher all his life.
I'm sorry to say.
It's also like the man.
Don't agree with his policies or creed.
Bye for now and happy masturbating.
The financial aid podcast isn't just for college students.
If you have views or like money, the financial aid podcast is for you.
Learn whether it's better to rent a buy house where you live.
Deal with credit card debt this smart way.
Get great tips to land the job that you really want.
There's even the occasional tinfoil hat moment.
And terrific podsy music every weekday.
Of course, if you're looking for information about how to make college affordable as a student
apparent, we've got that too.
Tune in every weekday at financialaidpodcast.com.
And if you have iTunes, visit financialaidpodcast.com forward slash subscribe to be automatically subscribed.
The financial aid podcast.
You can never learn too much about smart money.
Yo, right off.
Sorry about that.
I was queuing something up until I had the mic open.
Um, okay, pod save music now.
Uh, what was I going to say?
Something else.
Who knows?
It's Friday.
Who cares?
It's not important.
Hey Adam says J Murphy, knowing your affection for cowbell.
There is a great blue song at the pod save music network that has plenty of cowbell.
Remember by Bob Kirkpatrick from top cat records.
Think it's just right to your Friday party vibe.
When suddenly I played it on Murphy's saloon episode number 23.
Thank you very much, Murphy.
Dude, you are so right.
I think I need to break out my own cowbell.
From the pod save music network, Bob Kirkpatrick.
Remember, baby.
Remember, I'll feel to feel alone.
You wake up.
Wake up and find me going.
Listen to me to me.
I'll handle the ball of blood.
Listen to me to you.
Don't cry.
Baby, it's your time, though.
Now I'm going back home
I'm going home
The way you don't get sick is
I'll be better off alone
With no fun
I'll feel you feel home
The way you don't get sick
And you'll wake up
Wake up and find me go
Oh yeah
Remember from Bob Kirkpatrick
A name that is hard to mess up
But sometimes I do
Hey Adam, this is not a big break podcast
Coming from New York from Charleston, South Carolina
I was just listening to the Charlie 3-5
And just want to make a comment
Sophia Romos, she pronounced it
Romos rather than Ramos
I did the same thing first time I played her music
If you get a chance, check out my show The Big Break
On www.lowcountryradio.com
I did an interview with Sophia
A few weeks back
We're going to interview you
So you might want to check that out
Love you, show
www.lowcountryradio.com
Yeah, thank you
And it's important I want to say this stuff right
And of course, all the songs played on the daily source code
Become available for purchase to the pod save music network
Once they're played, if the artist agrees of course
That's how we're slowly rolling this out
And I think we'll start accelerating in the next week or so
It's music.podshow.com
And of course you can find all the links to the individual
Artists pages from the daily source code.com show notes
Or from curie.com where I post it as well
If you're on the pod show plus system, go
It's really there now in it
And the Jeff Smith, the guy is a genius
Talk about them all the time
He does all the whole bunch of songs and imaging and stuff
He can't throw a Jeff that he can't do
And all the time all the while he's spending his own time
Coming up with cool things and telling him to me
We pay him for some stuff when we ask him to do something
But he does a lot just because he's cool
But he did something tremendous yesterday
I think he has a
Two-year-old daughter
I don't know how old she is
She seems a little older in the video
Maybe she was three
I don't remember
I think that you are already set for when she's a teenager
Because you've got the psychology down my friend
I've tried Patricia's tried, listeners have tried
To get Christina to finally start with her show
She has the name for it, pod save the queen
Which I love the bits, pod save the queen
She has pod save the queen.com
She's got a show blog up there which she hasn't done anything to
She doesn't know how to edit WordPress and I understand that
And I said I'd get someone to help with that if she won
And of course she wants to do that herself
I got something yesterday from Jeff
And I knew that this would do it, this would push her over the edge
And she was on the phone with one of her friends
I said, come here, hold the phone up to the speakers
I want your friend to hear this as well
Because Jeff wrote her a theme song
I mean, what kid wouldn't be motivated to have their own piece of
I'd save the queen
Need something new
Before me and you
Don't make me wait
I owe my friend
I'm not saving the queen
Yeah
I'd save the queen
I know what I want
I know what I need
I know how to ask for it
Down on my knees
Everybody dance
No, no, no, no, no, no
None other one
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
Yeah
I'd save the queen
So, you can imagine Christina went nuts as did her friend on the other end of the line.
Of course, I'll cut it down to make it into a real intro, and she can use it as an outro
as well.
I'm pretty sure she's going to start now Jeff, I can't thank you enough.
And of course, we'll teach her about real-world economics because when she starts her
show, I'm going to tell her she has to pay for the use of that.
Now she can't afford the normal rates, but Jeff, you understand what I'm saying, right?
Well, she's just wanted to understand that there's social and financial reward, and it'll
be a good lesson for her, and she'll do it.
I know she will.
But first I'll get her started with the show, then I'll hit her with a bill, okay?
Hello Adam, this is Tokyo Dance on WhatsApp, I'm ending in Tokyo.
I noticed that you're opening up the podcast using network to musicians that you're playing
your show for payment.
I'd like to ask you to play Dike in Little Wing, sparkling woman.
It's a great reggae tune, you know, someone's coming up.
He's also got a great R&B tune up there called Dear Friend, that's Dike in Little Wing.
He's been up this year's, the end of December, so I think he'd really appreciate you playing
his song and opening it up for him.
Well, take it easy Adam, check that again.
Yo, Tokyo Dance, thank you so much, man, for turning me on to Dike.
This song is so fantastic, it was like Japanese music, it was mixed together with jazz and
reggae.
It's cool, sparkling woman, check it out.
Yo, my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight,
oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh
my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh myed eye taka display, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, I don't want to talk, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh mypod, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, ohMy spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my Paulo, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight my spotlight, oh my spotlight, oh my spotlight, I brilliant I
Lushy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy-hy
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah boy blessed Tercy, stop themy dough, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah
Oh, my, oh, my, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,?
What's this thing?
I'm about to lose it, yeah, yeah
So put that all up, walk me, gosh, you seem dead,
I don't talk you, I'm not gonna stop there, you're home
Keep me to cool it out, you can't lie to me,
But don't talk to me, oh, let's go and love a corner
And don't talk to me, oh, let's go and love a corner
And don't talk to me, oh, let's go
And don't talk to me, oh, let's think
Let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see
let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let
let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's say let's see, let's see, let's see, let us just let it see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's know, let's do it, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see and let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's
Charlie's for you next week of course we'll be back in the here for another week and then
Patricia and I leave on Saturday to go to New York so the in laws are coming Sunday tomorrow
I'm going to my mom and I'll be there with my two sisters Willow is in from Italy
Tiffany will come in from South Amsterdam and hopefully we'll have another weather here
is not going to be too good we'll have some clouds and perhaps some showers hopefully
it'll be a little bit better over there we can all sit outside and hang out and have a good
time and be together some RL stuff you know real life it's important too
portions of the show brought to you by Acqueview Contact lenses check out Heather and
Janelle a download.acqueview.com two girls talking about girl stuff you might be into that I think
you'll totally like it and of course if you want a great deal on a domain name go to godaddy.com
and upon checkout if you want it for $6.95 that's all little cost you use the promotional code
dsc3 okay I wanted since it's Friday and we're reasonably on time I'm just going to throw out
one more song because it just tickled me to hear this thing those who aren't interested you
don't even have to shuttle to the end because I'm not going to say anything else after I'll just
say goodbye do a couple lighter clicks and get out of here good ready for the weekend but I just
wanted anyone who is interested to hear this gangster hack a song and introductions are baked
right into the mp3 file hey Adam this is far corner from the kzfo podcast we came across something
recently that I thought you might like now picture gangster rappers rapping about hacking and computer
science that's basically what we've run across the artist name is mc++ and we hope you like it
uh this is dedicated to all the hackers on the track
three they set us free I'm downloading windows at me right now on ftp you bitches will never find me
because I'm everywhere see yo don't you got something new it me all like i see cute i help you back
and jy I got some time not shit on i try you shut one site down we multiply like a phoenix from a
different place we rise then you got the squares you're new you're stealing don't you care
LOL bitch I got a terabyte of wears I like my files sit sit or rare I'm downloading 700
segments from a bowels site I'll break coffee snore speed I'll stay up all night I'll have you
company site with blank and white those ISPs find me leave dedicated to the hackers that track us
this is dedicated to the hackers and the crackers one set us free next year the second
three this is dedicated to the hackers and the crackers I see in binary I speak source code
step on my toes I'll post a million jays if you want a fact post and your digital stance
getting my world home because I'm riding the net in my sixth home I will predict with my fifth
and sixth now with my cable I'm able to get that stable on the out my name is a son of a Leo
on the digital highway my name is Neo when I'm a hero in a flash I'll screw you on my
dreamcast you need some isos let me do my hard drive rifle or exchange with him stay for
in a digital hug you just caught the love hug I bootlegged a CD I caused the fight between on
in jz and you see jays it's all gonna be free whether we take it by force or we take it nicely
you feel that rally in your bones when I tell you we just hang out gones and now stack
me jiff loud in your back because I am he who loves to hack and crack and I am the he who loves to hack
and crack this is dedicated to the hackers and the crackers serial code the source code I
know ran six six this is dedicated to the hackers and the crack your encryption is primitive
Egyptian all the more with a 46 set of flexed or we've won one six billion dollars longs and we
tell each other how to get it on cyber armies and the Pentagon was storming I just found out
who killed jfk the smoking gun will hide it within a day all the lies in the faster go check the
name through for Napster digital disaster the practical never find me in the matrix a million
keyboard voices all name obvious this is dedicated to those who set me free got a buzz you always
my cousin radium if I can only say to them thanks police don't you know you're topia
and all my digital stones my nick dines my cyber gangsters my wild boy and my computer
comrades this is for you this is dedicated to the hack and the crack is
I know you're up I didn't feel you know I know that you're afraid you're afraid of us
you're afraid of change I don't know the future I didn't come here to tell you how this is going
to end the came here to tell you I was going to begin going to hang up this phone and then I'm
going to show these people what you don't want to see I'm going to show them a world without
a world without rules and controls without borders or boundaries a world where anything is possible
where we go from there it's a choice of you to you hope you like that Adam now of course I would
love to shamelessly plug my podcast but unfortunately I can barely afford the bandwidth we're burning
at the moment keep up the good work with podcast Adam and remember hack the planet
by cast last week have a great weekend everybody see you Monday another pod show pod cast
stick it in your ear get this podcast and more great ones like it on the high performance
pod cast delivery network from pod show and limelight networks I love it