This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
Want Killer content with a bad ass domain name?
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta's Yeracharly 423 Times Zone Pacific.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
But yes, dear.
It's an old curry.
The other end.
I'm going to give you a moment.
It's not something that you just don't something out.
It's not a big drive, right?
It's a series of tools.
Tools.
Time to let tools.
I just the other day got in and I was set by my staff at 10 o'clock in the morning fighting.
I got it yesterday.
Time to let tools.
I keep up my sense.
Because I've got time to let with all these things going on the internet.
Conversely, I think it's absolutely essential.
This is the tip for my streaming stuff.
I have to go out and down and down and down and down and down and in and in.
That's a bit strange.
I don't have to have that kind of speed.
I don't think anyone here is to find what the net quality is.
It's not a big truck in the series of tools.
And here we have this one situation.
The streaming process that internet.
I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I
I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I stop, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't I can't, I can't, I can't be
tubes. Why did we do that? Why? And normas tubes.
Massive tubes. It really is in that consumer-bill of life. Because it got tangled up with all these things and going on the earth.
The world has turned against this. Everybody how you're doing. I love that song. I found it a couple days ago. Now it's on the pod save music network.
From the bold headed pod cast. It is DJ Ted's techno tubes. And there's also extended version. I'd love it so much. I was on the plane.
I should let me see if I have that for you. I was on the plane coming over from London to San Francisco.
And I was digging that so much. I actually came up with a tube's cowbell remix. Hold on a second. Do I still have that here?
I probably already trashed it. It wasn't all that good. So maybe I should remake it. Anyway, how you doing everybody coming to you from Northern California looks like it's going to be.
Well, not too short. It's not going to be a super sunny day, but it could burn off pretty quickly. I'm in the curry condo.
Here for another another stint on the oil rig. But boy, it's going to be a lot of fun. Today we've got board meeting, which is the first one we've had in a while. Of course, it coincides neatly with
with the unleash of pod show plus and a whole bunch of initiatives that are going down. There's so much happening. So much. Not just in my life, but in your life as well. And I cannot believe. I cannot believe. I fuck this one up.
Check it out. Hi Adam. Danny Boyle here. I just wanted to wish the pod safe music network a happy birthday on July 15th. And question why you hadn't mentioned it. Is it something in the branding? Is it going to go away or change names or become something else? Is the pod show plus kind of the be the future? Anyway, happy birthday.
Well, let's say happy birthday to all the artists on the pod safe music network. All of the podcasters who are a member of the network. And of course, extra mega special thanks go out to Chris Rockwell, Sioux Fleming and CC Chapman. We really worked hard. And that was more than a year ago at launch the year ago on July 15th. But it was so funny. This was built via Skype before pod show existed before even Ron and I.
I decided to go on and create a company. Well, I guess it was kind of at the same time. We knew that this had to happen. And we were just excited.
It only took a couple of months to do. And the site looks like it. But it it fulfills the prophecy. And that's what I like about it so much. So congratulations to everybody.
Well, up onwards to the next year. And then the next. And who knows how big we can blow this mother out. But I'm very excited about it. And of course, no, we're going to leave it the pod safe music network.
Obviously, we need much better integration with pod show plus. And we made some decisions early on. Let's get to pod show plus out.
Then we'll start integrating everything because you have all these databases that got to talk to each other and do all kinds of things.
And, you know, why do you with that when you can listen to wonderful messages like this one?
Hey, Adam, and everyone at the daily source code. This is Lindsey from Carlisle, which is in the north of England. Just wanted to tell you something Alan.
Who's Alan?
Adam. Sorry mate. I just wanted to say, Adam, that our first child was conceived to the sound of the daily source code. My wife is just announced that she is pregnant with our first child.
And it's all down to you and Patricia. Yes, it was playing there in the background as we made sweet words.
People could work here. Adam, and I'm going to be a daddy.
Yeah, baby.
Okay. So a couple of things about that comment. First of all, it was sent through the voice mail numbers.
And if you're in the car and the train or on the bus or you're anywhere that you can grab your mobile phone.
And once you grab it right now and punch these digits in so you have them because you know that's going to be a point when you just have to say something and you're not going to have the number handy.
So entering plus where you could do, yeah, just do plus that's easier. Two zero one.
Six two five six three five seven and we have a UK numbers well in London plus four four two zero seven six eight one three seven five three. So you call me with this fantastic news and I got to tell you that is great.
I love hearing this story, but I need a little bit more detail. You know, it's like was it a Wambam. Thank you, man. Was it was it. I mean, we actually were you listening and laughing to what we were doing while you were doing.
Or were you totally ignoring us? Do you remember which episode it was? Was there something in particular at the right moment that really made it work for you?
In acquiring minds need to know you got to call me back buddy.
Oh, yeah, it's been way too long. Thank you, this the man is back on the scene.
Hello, I've been Roger here. Now you mentioned on your recent shows that you're interested in looking at women's rest in public, which coincidentally something that I enjoyed doing too.
Hold on a second before you get the wrong idea. No, what I mentioned is that it's so nice in the UK when the weather is so warm and we're going through a virtual heat wave in most of the world, but in the UK specifically we're looking at 92 93 degrees is like 30 to 35 degrees.
And then what happens in the UK is particularly in London that while they just start popping out is women just love showing them. So I guess I guess I do love watching him, you're right.
And when they walk into the freezes section, they tend to pop out like this, but if you want to be conspicuous, then I recommend that you wear some of those back sunglasses and not those rose colored ones that you've got as the way you might get kicked out for harassing customers.
Also, if you wear your sunglasses, it means Patricia won't know that you have in the pervever and I'm sure they're coming you for when you drive past all the types on the street.
I'm sure there's nothing better than staring at a couple of jeans, toes sticking out, rather you're out buying fish fingers. So he wants to meet up in the magazine section, number lunch break, and then I can show you all the best places for high.
What do you do? Don't go down between 9 and 11 in the morning because that's when all the pensioners go shopping and I think the only thing you want to see are a pair of shoes that fry eggs, press that against delicate housing counter.
So that's my suggestion for this week, go and check out the flags it's saying it's bris.
And I also wanted to let you know that I'm a squenching off-road, because it's a lot more so, right? And it doesn't get as much new sprint round you ring.
By now, Russia!
Oh yes, sometimes you'll stock here, sometimes you'll just throw you some love through the phones. It is Roger Smalls, ladies and gentlemen.
Yeah!
Greetings, Adam. This is Chuck Palm, once again calling from Tampa, Florida.
One of the lets you know about a new show we're putting out on ESP Productions, shameless plug.
That is the casting couch, a pot show plus network show.
We wanted to let you know about it. The host is my boy Flash from a country station here in Tampa.
The 19th market is what he wanted me to say.
It's a talk show style format, and our first episode we started talking about the podcast phenomenon,
and who was involved, and we mentioned the pod, father. I thought I'd put that out there to you.
There's about two minutes at the end of this, feel free to edit for content.
We wanted to let you know that we really appreciate the pod show plus network.
I think it's a great thing. We've got three shows up there right now.
My URL is chuck palm.podshow.com, and you'll see the casting couch is casting couch.podshow.com.
Check out that show. I think you're really going to like it being a reform DJ yourself.
You got to listen what happens when you put a couple of country DJs in the same room, put a podcaster, a producer, and a voice guy,
and a couple of cases of beer. It was an absolute riot. We had a blast.
Take care, man. We'll shout out to you soon.
All right, dude. Thank you very much. Casting couch.podshow.com.
You can go get your own piece of that internet if you want at podshow.com.
You can find all kinds of shows. You've got a program guide.
You can collect your own channels. You can put stuff together.
You can create an entire, an entire radio station of your own,
just consisting of podcasts that you'd like to listen to.
Share them, show people what you're listening to.
Dig people. Do all kinds of fun stuff.
Excellent, dude. Excellent. Thank you very much for the feedback as well.
Told that I was flying over the weekend, and how busy it was on the radio.
I mean, this is the busiest corridor in all of Europe, where in all of Western Europe,
where we happen to live and where I'm flying.
So I'm confident enough now to do it, but I got this wonderful piece of feedback here.
Let me see, this is from, here we go.
From Dwight Dunlop, from, where's he from, from Ottawa in Canada.
And of course, the saying does hold true.
If idiots worked here, we need air traffic control.
Hey, Adam, you ever have days like this?
I'm talking to the numbers. I'm counting on you to go down the runway.
Now, don't touch down and show it to ZK.
You know, I got to say that.
It's good fly. We need air traffic control.
Listen to that. Listen to that.
Listen to that control.
I'm going to go hide somewhere and see if they've all landed.
I love that.
Don't land short. Use the whole runway.
I got someone coming up here, but okay, forget about it.
Just do it. Go around.
Yep. That's the stuff you never hear when you're just flying around.
Is it passenger?
Hey, wow. The feedback on shadow falls has been outstanding as I knew it would.
Gosh, and I listened to the final mix.
Because I only heard a rough edit that Patricia and I listened to.
And I listened to the final mix on the plane right over.
Wow, man. That was just awesome.
And I had the big Sony headphones on.
You know, the ones that Patricia bought for herself that I stole from her.
And people are digging it.
Really are. I've seen responses to shows before.
But this is this is beyond belief.
You can check it out at shadowfalls dot pod show dot com.
It is an originally produced drama series.
It's audio only. So you can listen to it anywhere you want.
It's about 24 25 minutes each episode.
And this first one really sets the tone.
I'm totally totally excited about this.
Can't wait to see how the story of Molly unfolds.
Also, big news today on the pod show front.
We released pod show pro.
Of course, you have the pod show plus.
Now you've figured out what that is.
And we've got a pretty cool deal with with aim.
I don't know if you've ever seen, you know,
A well instant messenger, of course.
So there's an aim pro version, which is completely without,
you know, without all the wacky colorful.
It's a business thing. Really.
It's a business instant message application.
It's aim for business users.
And what's cool about it is now that we've released pod show pro,
which is for a small medium sized businesses.
I guess big business could use it as well,
but they'd probably want a more custom solution.
But it also, it really focuses on business podcasts.
You can find that it pro dot pod show dot com.
And I believe today as well,
if you download the new A well instant messenger pro client.
So that's aim pro.
It'll work with your existing aim account.
There's a little, a little icon at the bottom.
You click on that.
And I think you can listen to some streaming channels.
But right there, pod show pro.
And you can have your, your channels set up.
So they can play right inside your instant messenger.
So this is just another example of,
of really what we've dreamed about.
You know, having a place where you can manage all the different places
your podcast go to.
So whether it's on your iPod, your MP3 player, your cell phone,
your TV, your, uh, your instant message client,
you know, it can go anywhere.
And you can manage it all from one place.
And I'm really, I can tell you how much stuff is just coming at us.
It's now it's starting to happen.
This is the point where we wanted to get to.
Sure, we've got at least a couple more weeks of clean up to do on,
on the pod show, plus side getting all kinds of just bugs,
stomped on.
But also some thought mistakes we made,
which, of course, is a, is so beautiful now that it's,
it's still in beta.
We can, we can, we can mess around the night.
Of course, appreciate everybody's patience as we do that.
But shit, it's coming together now.
I think the channel bug is working.
So shows don't fall out of your channel.
Um, and, and I was amazed this morning when I woke up at, like,
five, thirty quarters six.
You know, there it was.
All these shows that I, that were just sitting there,
ready for me to play.
I was like, yeah.
Finally, someone helping me listen to podcasts.
Hi, Adam.
I'm, um, this is counselor.
I am the French speaker.
Yeah, it's like a blur.
It's one of these lazy French bastards, isn't it?
I'm, um, between the UK and Ireland.
I just want to give you two feedback today.
The first one is about a biodiesel.
I run a pleasure field six.
So what is all?
And I pour biodiesel in it.
It's, it's great.
The crown's better.
It's cleaner.
It's smoother.
You can feel it, you know, the engine is more,
no performance.
And the best thing is that it only costs seventy five
pounds a liter, um, which is a bargain as far as I know.
Now, the second thing is,
Louis, on the elephant land, um,
there is something special about them,
a place over here.
Sorry.
And all in the place have to include
better M from other.
And N for November.
Um, so, you know,
you know, the place could be A, M, N,
1, 2, 3.
Now, what happens with some people
have related P for Peter.
So, day in November,
3, R, P, M, N, 1, 2, 3.
And, uh, without knowing that,
therefore, I've utilized the process,
music network.
I thought it was quite funny, um,
enough, I mentioned it.
Unfortunately, you cannot put those P,
M, N, or M, you know,
in November, place on a UK car.
Because you listen to me,
you're French lazy bastard.
What are you doing on the island, man?
And get me one of those license plates.
I want the PM, N, 1, 2, 3 license plates.
Please.
The French aren't really lazy bastards.
That just got stuck from that other guy.
Where is the French lazy bastard?
Actually, he used to check in a while.
He was telling us all about that,
you know, the iTunes stuff in France.
And now that that's changed,
I don't hear from him anymore.
I did hear from the podcheck.podcheck.com.
It was also on the podshow podcast network.
And she's doing a lot of really interesting stuff.
You know, she's into sky diving.
And she's been sending me, uh,
she's really never, uh, KFC.
She, uh,
KFC.
I don't think it really has a lot of experience with video.
In fact, when I first met her,
when she was first doing podcheck.com,
she didn't have a lot of experience with audio either.
And so I helped her kind of get rolling on that,
and she figured the stuff out.
And now she's editing these videos.
And so I'm just giving her some ideas as to,
you know, how you can make a show flow.
And I know a little bit about video,
not much.
I know a lot about jump cuts and wookie cans.
But she's,
that it's really the content that I'm so interested in.
What she basically has is hot looking chicks who are skydiving.
And in the, in the most recent clip,
she sent me.
I was like, yeah, you know,
I can really get into this.
It's exactly what it is.
It's hot chicks who go skydiving
and do other dangerous,
Daredevil things.
You might want to check it out podcheck.com.
This month on BFBS multimedia,
you'll use a friendly guide to computing technology,
and the internet.
It's a very special show.
Yes, we're celebrating our 100th program.
And to mark the occasion,
we've got to cake some sparklers
and the biggest competition give away in the show's history.
We've got not just one or two,
but 100 prizes in the multimedia competition.
More chances to win than ever before.
We've got a lot more chances to win than ever before.
Plus the usual blend of news reviews, interviews,
and downright sensible advice from me, Dave Raven.
And from me, Mark Phillips.
So subscribe to the BFBS multimedia podcast at BFBS.com.
That's BravoFoxTrot BravoCera.com slash multimedia.
Or via iTunes, and you could be one of our lucky winners.
Mark Phillips and Dave Raven, BFBS, multimedia.
Congratulations, dudes.
It's 100 episodes, it's very good.
It seems like a lot of that is coming around.
Now, folks have been podcasting for a year,
or they've reached some kind of pillar,
which would be the 100th episode,
and I congratulate you.
If you've been using the Podgeau Plus dashboard,
is what I call it.
You might just call it the player,
but you'll see that this player has a lot more under the hood
than just playing stuff.
In fact, if you click on any Podgeau podcast,
you can have channels set up.
Just go to your Podgeau Plus tab on the dashboard.
And you'll see your channels right there,
and you can open them up,
and you can play them from there.
So no need to go back to the website.
You'll also see that the dashboard now plays
enhanced podcast.
Now, it's still a little bit hidden.
We're not doing all of the, in fact,
right now, I think the chaptering is what is available.
So if you subscribe to a show that is enhanced,
and has chapters,
and I believe sometime this week
will finalize the, you know, all the enhanced stuff,
then the pictures will actually rotate
in the, in the dashboard player,
and the links will be hot.
Already now, I think the links are hot
if there's chapters put in there,
and I believe that the images will rotate.
So go ahead and find your favorite
enhanced podcast,
and it will just work.
It's cool stuff.
Just like this show,
the popped up on Podgeau Plus.
This one blew me away.
It's so cute.
A mom and her 11 year old son.
Hello.
This is Dan.
And this is Shayna.
We're bringing you the mind and body cast.
This is our promo podcast.
We're going to be talking about our show
and what we plan to talk about.
Yep.
And we're going to be talking about vitamins,
skincare, all kinds of beauty,
you know, all that good stuff.
Are you going to cover the beauty stuff, Aaron?
Yes.
I'm going to lovely.
Aaron is my 11 year old son,
and we're both huge podcasting fans.
And we've just been listening
for over a year and decided to finally put
together a show of our own.
Check us out at mind and body cast.
Com.
Shoot us an email or a question,
mind and body cast at gmail.com.
Yep.
And so I'll be looking forward to young emails.
And feel free to send us any link
to anything that sounds good.
And they think my help is in a new podcast and experience.
And what did you want to listen
or check out on our website, Aaron?
The funny junk link.
I have a funny junk.com link,
which is links to funjunk.com,
which is some pretty funny stuff.
You can just click on the funny Aaron's funny junk.
And it'll take you right there to the links.
Click on one to view it.
And yeah, pretty funny.
So we're looking forward to that.
All right.
So we'll be talking to you soon.
Again, mind and body cast.com.
I'm Shayna.
And this is Aaron.
See you later, peace.
Yeah, this podcast.
Yeah, peeps.
See you later, peeps.
How cute is that?
You know, when I hear that,
I have this only one thing I really think.
I miss my mommy.
I really do.
And last time I was in San Francisco,
she was still alive.
So it was beautiful to hear that podcast.
Aaron and his mom on the mind and body podcast.
Find that on pod show plus.
Adam, see the piece.
London.
You said enough to use Charlie to go.
HD.
We don't have HD.
Adam on behalf of everybody.
It doesn't live in the state.
Just let me say something about you.
Sirius, we don't have serious.
We physically can't get it.
Even if we talk for it.
Why?
Keep on going on.
Everything left about serious.
I know you've got a commercial relationship with them,
because it means you can put your podcast on the serious.
That's fantastic.
Not a problem.
But surely peed up and sorted out for you every time.
And you can quite leave a small gap.
Rather than continually telling it every single day.
I'm a little listener.
I love the show.
But please, still going on about serious.
Adam, serious.
We don't have serious.
Dude, the whole reason I say that is to build the bridge between the listeners in the
United States who have the capability to receive serious.
And who can listen to Pacific Coast Hellway, which is coming up next.
It's just the bridge, my brother.
That's all that it's about.
Really?
Hi Adam.
My name's Nathan.
I'm calling from Australia.
It's one of the, say, been shooting in since about the mid 300.
Love in the show.
I think it's great.
I can't wait to get my fix.
I work away in the mine site.
Working two weeks on and one week off.
So I've got a way to travel with you to get my fix.
I think so.
I can take my trust as a little MP3 player and my laptop.
And while I don't have internet access to speak of while I'm there.
I can at least play with things on the MP3 player.
Had a question for you.
And you may or may not be offended by this.
And I apologize if you are.
Sadly some of us are old enough to remember.
And you can say that a like, a song from the 80s called,
We built this city by Starship.
Now, there's a bidding that where there's a DJ talking about.
He's from San Francisco.
Now, my question is in fact you.
I know your affinity with San Francisco.
I don't have to say I've listened to it recently since hearing your show.
It sounds like you do.
Great.
And could I see if it is?
That's fabulous.
It's not my apologies.
I don't want to offend anybody.
I know you're probably going to play it because it's nice and smooth.
But I wonder whether you could just play that little snippet of the DJ talks about it being a lovely sunny day in San Francisco this year by the day.
The city would be a bittersweet or that stuff.
Anyway, I hope the show is going well.
I'm loving it.
I'd love to do it from you more.
I'll be shooting him.
We're saying he liked it.
Maybe some sort of inspiration to your mind podcast and attack.
So the flyer needs tailwind and I'll text you soon.
Thanks, mate.
Bye.
All right.
All right, mate.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, it's interesting you say that because, well, the first of all, no, it's not me.
But when I was doing the countdown show,
and that's not the same as old Molly used to host there in Australia.
He had a show called Countdown.
I had the show in the Netherlands and in Europe called Countdown.
We had Starship visit the studio.
And this was around the time they had Sarah, was their head and we built this city.
So, of course, it was a grace lick and Mickey Thomas.
Mickey Thomas, who you might know from fooled around and fell in love.
They were the two main people in Starship, which, of course, was a
derivative of Jefferson Starship, slash airplane, et cetera, et cetera.
And when they did that song, they actually,
the camera cut away to a shot of me in a radio studio,
lip syncing that actual bit.
From San Francisco, the city by the bay, the city that never sleeps.
It's funny you mentioned that.
I just brought back a whole bunch of memories.
But no, it was not me.
I've done a couple of different things.
I did a Vandenberg album, I did some stuff,
and I should have, man, there's so much I've lost.
I wish I had all that material now.
See, I never gave a shit about it back then.
But, of course, we didn't have digital archiving.
We had huge real-to-real tapes that had a lug around,
or really shitty cassette tapes that just always had that hiss on it.
Frank Barnico sent in a comment.
He's been listening.
He writes for CBS Market Watch on the site there.
And he has his own weblog, Barnico.com.
And it's nice to hear his voice for a change.
Good morning, Adam.
Frank Barnico here from Barnico.com.
I think this data is bogus.
Right you are, Ollie.
I ruffled with that release last week from Nielsen that ratings,
which had lined about six and a half percent of web users
have downloaded a podcast in the last 30 days.
Something like 9 million people that 5 million or so had downloaded video cast.
Well, the first clue is something wasn't right, certainly.
And it was one of the words, podcast and podcasting were used in fairly confusing ways.
I call the analyst on the report and the company's PR person when he wasn't available.
After asking me to wait a bit while she checked, she came back and said,
yes, podcasts were podcasts.
Podcasts were people who listened to podcasts.
And podcasting was listening to podcasts.
Then I asked a bit more about the survey.
And the next day the analyst said, well,
the question about podcasting also mentioned music.
As in, have you downloaded music or a podcast?
So he said, the answer may well have been not as specific as we would have liked.
Now I think the problem here is this release wildly overstated how many podcasts
have been downloaded and how many people are listening to them.
We can't help but believe the answer included a heck of a lot more music responses than podcast.
Now I certainly believe there are a lot more podcasts being downloaded now than a year ago.
But any advertiser who takes this at face value and a podcast or ask for the order?
Well, does it as what they don't get?
But then the release was full anomaly.
It wasn't that Apple's browser the most popular for instance.
Reports I've seen given in that Explorer 85% of the market,
Firefox as much as 15% doesn't leave a whole lot left to Apple.
Think back to your TV and radio days, Adam.
Remember our ratings report that was screwy?
We call them fluke books.
Nielsen net ratings has given us a fluke book.
Sorry back to you Adam and by the way I am a folder for crank market go at barnico.com.
You know Frank there's never too much information about you my friend.
Yeah I agree.
I you know it's I've never really paid much attention to ratings.
Not during television.
I was kind of trained that way.
MTV was the same way in fact it still is kind of the same way.
Typically there are about 300,000 people watching MTV at any given moment.
And in fact that was definitely when they still played music and then the whole and if you're interested
It's the YMT doesn't play music anymore. They were paying attention to the ratings
Because what would happen is they put on a show like it started actually with the remote control
MTV's remote control with that Ken Ober and Kari were and Colin Quinn
Colin Quinn. Yeah Colin Quinn and Steve trick us in the band. Oh, guys. How are you doing?
It's been a long time
Those shows would get like a 1.0 which meant
You know almost
Often twice or three times the amount of people who would be watching
During any other hour on MTV and so they said hey shit this short form stuff is getting as better ratings
It means we can sell more advertising means we can make more money and that's that was the death now of music on MTV
However, I think that what MTV's strongest property really is is the brand. It's a it's affinity with its viewers
And you know that of course changes over time and and people grow up and move on et cetera and you're supposed to flow right into VH1
Who now are playing metal video? Metallica is on VH1. I don't know what happened there. Maybe we're just all getting fucking old
But really it's the brand it's the big am the little TV and and I and I think that that really showed for me at least that advertising is not all
Just about reach. It's not all just about the numbers
It you know we're changing advertising as media as a media landscape is changing and it's of course the shotgun blast approach is a big deal
But advertisers are very very smart that we've talked about this before
They understand what influences they understand what a relationship is between
Content between programming and
It's audience at how audiences are now interacting. It's not just you know calling phone numbers
It's talking about it. It's posting about it on your web blog. It's linking to shows
It's actually buying purchase, you know purchasing goods and services that are discussed on on the show
I've sold so much stuff on the daily source code without ever intending to sell any of it
You know if I came out today right now right this very minute
If I came out with the folder scruncher toilet paper, I know it would sell
Hey Adam Dave from South Florida here
Just got an email from crews that I always go on called the rock boat and saw that at the bottom and had the logo for pod show on it
And I was just curious what was going on. You guys a sponsor or what it didn't really mention anything other than having that logo there so
How about some information on that man?
This is the my sixth one on there. I've been on all of them and it'll be a great time. January
Had not a lot of day will go into turns and cakeos for anybody who's interested. It's sold out
But I know they have a waiting list. Anyway
About some info man. Thanks a lot. Nice
Dude
Interesting. I don't know anything about it. Maybe
I really don't know rock boat. I've never heard of rock boat like I can imagine what it is
But send you more info dude send me a URL or something so I can figure it out
No idea. I'm sure it's someone with good intentions, but let's figure it out. That's a
Shoot if we got our logo on it. Can I get a free ride perhaps?
Hey good morning Adam
I was just listening to source code 422. You mentioned that the podcasters will be able to click and see
Did our listeners are how many of us pinnors they are see their faces in a rank with them
Is there a way that I as a listener can go to these podcasters not only
See some of the other listeners, but see how many people are listening to a certain show
Just curious of one or time to time how many people actually listen to this show along with me
Is that possible? Thanks
Yo
Well, if you go to podshow plus
There's a module you can that any podcasters can put right on there on their page
Which is
listeners and what it does is it not just shows you how many people are listening and that of course means
Who who got the show through podshow plus and I think I've got over a thousand now is just unleashed and in people are now starting to use it
But so not only can you use that number for yourself, but you can also see the actual pictures
See who those people are what other shows they're listening to. I like it as a podcaster. I like it a lot
But also as a listener I'll be listening to a show that it's just like the pod save music network
This is exactly the same thing that worked with that
Is you you hear a show you hear a song you check out the song what other shows are playing the song
Hey, they might have some other songs. I like it's the same thing
Who's listening to what show and you can see you know you can go through all
1000 people who who have gotten the daily source code through podshow plus
You can see what other shows that listening to what they have in their channels. It's it's it's pretty spectacular
It's exactly what we wanted it to be
Let's see. Oh shoot. I I did I not queue up the song. Oh, man. Oh
Oh, I saw a colonel second let me just load up this song here. There's a beautiful email
that I got from
Jason Miller from the finer points.net
How he says he left me a message on the voicemail, but I couldn't find it or couldn't retrieve it
And he said that he was going to send me a couple songs
And this is in regards to my mom. He says his mom died of cancer when he was 17
I wasn't able to be with her and that was very hard but it inspired the following song
So I want to play that for you as the last one on today's Charlie
To be there with you
It's where I should have been that day
If I was there I could told me that I loved you
Could have fell the hand in the water
I know that never could save you on that dark summer night
But I know that I could have been there
And if I was there we could talk all about you
Should have left me send you a sing up all the game
And I would have surrounded you with flowers
Try to think about it like it's a new beginning
And I would have given back some of the gifts you gave me
Make the best out of the first you'll find away
And I know that it could save something to make it easier on me
Should have known that it came from me
I could feel your blood and I feel your soul inside of me
You know I think that's who makes me strong
And I know that you're lying and I know that you'll still love me
I feel in my heart I hear in my songs
I feel like I'm one to get you
Maybe that's why I'm not afraid of dying
That's why I'm here and California
Maybe that's why I'm never stopped trying
If I was there I know things wouldn't be different
I mean I know it wouldn't have ended any other way
I could have done nothing to be there with you
It's where I should have been that day
Jason Miller
Not afraid of dying Jason I'd love if you would put that up on the podcast music network
If not you can find that at the finer points dot net and I was fortunate to have been there when my mom passed
So I think I was able to say everything and more importantly I perhaps she was able to say everything she wanted to
Which was very nice and I listen that song and I think about your story
I'm just like wow you know I feel I feel really lucky really lucky that it you know what the inevitable went down and it went down on the way it did
Okay to wind it up a couple things you'll see new show notes today
This is I hadn't even seen this new feature in cast blaster
But there's an automatic show notes feature that we've talked about for a while and now it's it's actually in there
The minute you fire up anything any any audio element or a song or just anything you've got loaded up
It'll throw that into the show notes with a timestamp which I know a lot of people have been asking for and I've been wanting so I'm gonna
Put this out there and see what you think
It the spacing is a little bit a little bit wide forming or you know as like double spacing or whatever
But it doesn't matter. I think it's a very cool feature
In addition
So nice of cast blaster mic to hook up my sister willow willow.podshow.com with with a key for cast blaster
So now she's off to the races man, you know she could she could do the 10-minute podcast on with a free version
Now she's finding a Italian pod safe music and she's playing that and and she's taking the opportunity to tell me how fucked up
Podshow plus is that Bob who was a mom's husband
He bought himself an MP3 player on a USB stick and
He used to just download stuff via the direct download link and he couldn't find the direct download link
So yeah, we're putting that one in in fact
I know exactly where I'm gonna put it so that
You know we just make it as easy as possible for anyone and everybody
Alrighty
Time check we've got 739 which that's AM by the way
Which means I gotta get shoured up lathered ready for the board meeting which will be the afternoon
It's gonna be as I said. It's always a always a lot of fun to meet up with the the guys and gals and
Exchange ideas and and look at the strategy and where we're going and and how we're doing and how we're feeling and just so much love in the room
And and I'm sure there's gonna be a lot more. Oh, I'm gonna try and hook up with Andrew Rummit and do a dev cast this week as well
There's a lot of shit we got to talk about there because now we need to developers to come on in with your modules
We got lots of modules. We want to push through and there's a lot of requests for more
So you have yourselves a great day everybody
Talk to you tomorrow bye bye
You
At this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from Podjo and line-white networks