Hey, this is Dan Patterson from the Creepy Sleepy Show.
You want creepy without the sleepy?
Check out Shadow Falls, Pod Show's brand new audio drama series.
It's terrifying.
Terrifying.
Go ahead.
This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
Want killer content with a badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Episode 436.
The Daily Source Code is on.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I say it's you again.
Almost to lovely.
You want to grow from my friend.
What you said, you say goodbye.
Should try and prove you right.
Was I wrong?
Tell me how long it's gone wrong.
And I thought that you're wrong.
You're done if I'm wrong.
I thought that you'd be wrong.
Go.
Almost to right.
Maybe you've been there.
Maybe you know.
Here's a spreadsheet.
Maybe you've been breastfeeding.
Looks like a hole.
Oh, my God.
And you never said it was a pleasure
when I served with it just so I think it works well in the party.
If you're repressing to myself and I tell this remote,
I'm done to have that touch up on this show.
No, I know the Lord hears the Lord.
I hate my enemy.
Oh, Mr. Lovely.
I'll say yes to you again.
You want to grow from my friend where you're at.
There's a window in my yard and can't wait.
There's a slave in the morning.
There's a sworn in the rain.
There's no sin in the rain.
There's no love in the day.
I'm okay.
That one in your morning pipe, huh?
Week of the daily source code, everybody.
How are you doing?
Coming to you from a kind of a muggy, uh,
affluent suburb of Surrey, uh,
known as Gilford in the UK, um, from the Curry Cottage.
Yeah, you can hear the fan of the background.
Just trying to keep the air circulated.
Wow, hope you had a good weekend.
I certainly had a restful one.
It was our 18th, um, 18th anniversary on Saturday,
which we don't really celebrate anniversary.
In fact, um, uh, we've actually both forgotten at once or twice.
Um, so it's more like, uh, you know, like a card exchange or some horrible flowers from, uh,
from the gas station.
Which is exactly what I got her on my way back from flying, uh,
uh, all of a sudden, um, Patricia felt that the 18 was an important number.
And we should have celebrated 18.
Of course, she said that one day later,
and so I guess we'll make up for that, uh,
sometime during the week.
Oh, hey, uh,
um, hey, learn something really, um, interesting over the weekend.
I learned how to fly without my air speed indicator.
Those of you who are pilots are going,
really, yeah, here's what happened.
The air speed indicator basically tells you what your air speed is, obviously.
And it's a pretty critical piece of equipment, um,
mainly for landing because, um,
every aircraft has a stall speed,
which means if you go below, um,
that particular speed at the particular settings that you have with flaps, etc.
Uh, the aircraft will actually just fall out of the sky.
So you kind of need to know, you know,
what your, what your speed is.
And also, you don't want to,
arrive too fast because, well,
the plane will want to keep on flying and, uh,
you'll need a lot more runway to slow it down.
Uh, so upon take off, um,
and, uh,
uh, this was, uh, for a trip to, uh,
just a quick flight, uh,
uh, over the channel and back,
just to drop off some letters in, uh,
the most expensive, uh, postman there is, uh,
uh, upon take off, uh,
I saw that the air speed indicator had failed.
Um, now Captain Dan was with me.
I have to, I have to say that.
And so what should we do?
Shall we abort? He says, no, this is good exercise.
Uh, so, um, we pulled up and, uh,
off we were, uh, although, you know,
we did a couple of circuits see if, uh,
if the thing would come unglued or whatever.
This thing, there's no real mechanics to it.
It's all kind of, uh,
system, so it's almost impossible for anything to fail on it.
Um, I guess, is there any electronics?
Uh, yeah.
Well, in essence, there's no mechanical things that could really go that wrong.
So, um, so there's nothing to let's,
let's do a landing without the air speed indicator.
So of course, you know, I came in faster than
I should have, obviously, because I'm, you know,
uh, worried about going too slow and falling out of the sky.
But, you know, but set her down,
made the landing smoke the tire a little bit.
I have a, I have a little square spot on my left, uh,
I'm a left tire and then, uh,
we decided we could go figure it out, uh,
uh, later and we could just fly without it.
Um, now what typically happens is so stupid.
What typically happens when your air speed indicator doesn't work is because
there's this tube that sticks out underneath the wing.
You'll see this on on commercial airlines as well.
They look like, um,
almost like with little machine gun turns sticking out with
a little hole in it.
That's called the Pito tube and the way it measures your air speed is
by literally the air that, uh, that you're flying through gets
jammed into this thing.
And then, you know, the pressure that's jammed, uh,
into that tube will make this, this needle indicate the,
the true indicated air speed.
So sometimes a bug can crawl in there,
particularly if it's been around for three weeks,
and I didn't have a little, um,
red Pito tube cover on it, which, of course,
now I do have.
So the only thing I do is really suck it and try and suck
whatever's in, suck it out.
Ah, yes.
There were quite a few laughs as I stood there
underneath the wing of my Cessna 182RG,
sucking furiously on the Pito tube.
Oh, yeah.
Comments were made for sure.
As it turns out, actually, um, uh,
the needle was stuck.
Um, remember the last landing I did with Patricia,
which was wasn't beautiful, but was kind of a little bumpy.
Somehow the needle had gotten stuck on that.
And so when we were actually in our way back,
and I just knocked on the glass about the six o'clock position,
the needle came alive and it was working.
So good.
That means I can fly a solo this week and, uh,
get some more landing practice in.
See if I can keep my tires, uh,
uh, a lifespan a little bit longer than what it is now.
Lots of stuff to do today.
Got a whole mess of comments.
Patricia's really busy going back and forth to the vet,
and she's got stuff lined up.
We have to go check out this place where Christina's going to have her.
Sweet 16 party on the 27th.
So, um, she's,
a little too busy to join the show today,
but she's assured me she'll be back tomorrow.
And if you want to hear more about sweet 16 parties,
Christina just released a new episode of Podsave the Queen episode number six.
She talks about it, uh,
in detail, particularly about the MTV, uh,
television version of my fabulous,
or was it my sensational sweet 16?
Uh, that's over at podsavetheQueen.podshow.com
or podsavetheQueen.com.
Yes, it's a long distance dedication.
You.
I.
Real.
I'm.
Adam Currie, what's up, man?
It's a boy AB from crowcrackradio.com
We just want to let you know
that we just posted a show all about the only her.
Ashley songs about the only her.
Anyway, man, it's dedicated to you
and all the other folks working hard out there
out there to post this podcast movement for it is appreciated and we just wanted to
get this little shout out. All right, peace.
Right on A. B. Thank you. You know, we're doing a little test on podshow.com, testing out
the network effect of our network, which is exactly what we built for listeners, trying
to get the best stuff to listeners, trying to turn listeners on to cool things to
explore and participate in shows. And so one of the pieces of content that we've invested
in a podshow is a production that podshow LA is making called Shadow Falls. It's an original
drama series, audio drama, we're reviving an art that barely barely still exists on, well,
the BBC still does audio dramas, but it's something really from the past, but with today's
technology and the amount of talent floating around that is willing to work and just do
something creative. I'm just amazed at the result and really, really pleased with the response
to it. Excuse me, this sincere moment, brought you by Shadow Falls at Shadow Falls.podshow.com.
So part of the test that we're doing is involves the homepage at Podshow, where now in
the flash that starts up right there and there's always new stuff in the program guide there
in the flash opening montage. We're promoting Shadow Falls there under the music tab where, of
course, promoting monk with IAM, which is Molly's theme from Shadow Falls for the closing credits.
And we've also inserted these very short, yeah, little promo plugs from some of the podcasters
around the network, which is actually our first network-wide D-Gap insertion campaign, if you
will. So every single show that's on the podcast, on the podshow podcast network, using
the PDN, the delivery network, has a little short blip up front sometime. Was it soccer
girl, did one? Cali, did one? Creepy Sleepy Show, did one? We have the regular trailer, all
in rotation, and they just fire up right before the actual podcast that you requested if it's
on our network that is, and it's really working the numbers doubled in two days. I'm so
of so pleased with this. This is the stuff that I've been dreaming of, to be able to put stuff
into the network and make stuff grow, and it's just happening. Yeah, please, very cool.
Let's see. Hey, today we've got to announce the winner of the Troy Wantsen iPod contest.
Now, of course, this all started off with Troy, needing an iPod, who registered a
main name called Troy needs an iPod.com and he was soliciting donations and I picked up on it
and I said, well, it's certainly we can do better with that. And tied into the DSC promo code
you use on checkout at godaddy.com. And a lot of entries, all of them posted in comments at daily
source code.com, which is pretty much where I'd like you to go if you have anything to say about
the show. And it was very hard choosing a winner. Now, of course, you know, I'm the soul judge
and Voidware privated by law, etc. But I had a couple of basic criteria. First of all,
it had to be a domain name that, you know, kind of, you know, the actual name itself had
to strike a chord. I guess I was looking for humor more than anything. And extra points, if it
actually was registered, it didn't even have to be registered with a daily source code,
check out code or even godaddy for that matter. But it did actually have to be registered
and extra points, if you point it towards a fun domain. And it was very, very hard. I mean,
I would have loved to give in everyone and I've got participated. And this is a pretty ad hoc
thing. It's coming out of my own personal pod show production budget. So it's not like a
network wide thing, but I really appreciate all the participation. And I think that the one that
I like the best is, I don't even know who the hell posted this whole on a second. This is actually
it is a person with a pod show plus account, MZ Marty pants, MZ Marty pants. Here's the URL
that I liked. It's a domain name. I have a goddamn shuffle and I'm a cheap whore who wants to
promote other podcast.com, which by itself was pretty funny. But it points to what is it transadvocate.com
slash scrunch my poop, which is this whole site that he built about folding, folding and scrunching.
And don't hate me because I'm hoaring for an iPod to hate me because I'm a scruncher.
So let me see if I can find out who this actually is. How well there's a fantastic, a fantastic
banner as well on this site. So I'm going to get the info on MZ Marty pants. You just want
yourself an iPod. Congratulations. Maybe it's just the mood out. The mood I was in over the
weekend, but it really caught my fancy. And here by we close the entire Troy needs an iPod contest.
More contest coming soon for sure, because we got some great sponsors and advertisers who are
coming in with some very creative ideas. Stay tuned for that. Rishab Kumar says, hey Adam,
I love emails like this. Well, I was taking a dump in the bathroom today and idea dawned upon me,
instead of having rolls of toilet paper, why not have pre-folded toilet paper? We could make a
little machine that would fit in the toilet paper roll area. And when you took one pre-folded sheet,
another one would pop up. I bet there's some money in this business, Mr. Curry. Your thoughts?
This is Shubi, of course, from the Shubi show. Hey, Shubi, I love the entrepreneurial spirit,
dude. And actually, I love thinking about an infrastructure like that and how it can be used differently.
I mean, there's some very successful stories of people who reinvented things like the vacuum cleaner.
Can we actually reinvent the toilet paper roll? Think about how many toilet paper rolls and
toilet paper roll attachments there are in the world. It could be a huge opportunity.
Flesh it out a little bit and send me a business plan. Hey, Adam says a Tom Rock hold.
I'm one show away from episode 100 on bucket drive time. It would be most excellent to get
a quick mention on the Charlie that I can then lift and put into the show.
Thanks for the positive music network. Without it, there would be no bucket drive time podcast.
All right, congratulations, dude. 100 episodes. Very cool. Although I think we should stop celebrating
all these, you know, you can do a, you can do one at 50 at 100 at 150, you know, 200,
500 to 1000. And quite honestly, I want to stop with a numbers at a certain point. I mean,
how high am I going to have to count? Do we, will we actually wind up with one day daily source
code episode 10,397 seems like a bit of overkill to me? Your thoughts would be appreciated.
Just a quick thing that I'll put in a link in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com. Did you see
this roiter's picture of, I think it's a, they root and this was going around the internet quite
a bit over the weekend. It's just in case you hadn't seen it, you have to see that this, uh,
I think it was in a roiter's photographer, or probably a freelance photographer who sold the picture
to roiter's doctor the photo. And it's not the first time he's been suspected of doctoring photos,
but he literally used the Photoshop clone tool and made the, the black smoke coming from shell,
department buildings, twice as bad, even darker than the original photo. You know, this is just
and of course, you know how this worked out, right? The guy needs to sell a picture. So he wants to
sell the really gruesome picture to roiter's and there's something that going, what's, what's gruesome?
This is not enough smoke. Can you know, yeah, that one. That's a good. Oh, wait, maybe I have some
with some more smoke. I'll get right back to you. You know, this is how the war is being reported to
you, my friends. Enjoy mainstream media, please. There's definitely other places and other sources.
You can get a heck of a lot more information about what's really happening over there. Hey, out of this
philosophy guy on DSC 435, you had mentioned that you wanted to know a little bit more about
your audience. Yeah. Well, I don't know if I'm a typical DSC listener, but I'm 42. I married
had three kids, have a computer programmer from Milwaukee and I've been a podcaster for about a
year. You know, I got to say that all the people who've been calling in with kind of their
listener profile and I'll be highlighting one later on in the show today. As I promised, you know,
we've got got to make these t-shirts. I don't even know what the heck is going to be on the t-shirt.
Yeah, let's come with a good slogan for it and I'll have them made up, but I just love hearing,
you know, your profile who you are, where you are, how old you are, what you do. You know,
stuff like if you married or not. And of course, if you're a folder or a scruncher, that is
critical, that is really the scientific portion of the of the survey. And once I get the t-shirts in,
once we figure out what the slogan is going to be, I want to have a featured listener of the day. I
already have a featured listener of the day for every day this week. So retroactively these folks
will get t-shirts. Also got to figure out how to find out who you are after you've called in.
And then I still need a mattress to send you stuff. But I did want to ask you a question.
What was the logic in Pod Show Plus that you used to determine the similar shows and related
feeds that show up as part of the Pod Show Plus page for particular Podcast?
Yeah, I think I think we took an idiot pill on that one. That definitely makes no sense. And if you
haven't seen Pod Show Plus, go to any Podcast on Pod Show Plus. And you'll see that there's a box,
there's fans, and there's another little box that says related feeds. And it makes no sense.
What is a feed? Is it a show? Is it a channel? That's going to change. I think it should be
related shows. But it could also be related channels, which I'm, you know, I think is probably
even smarter because how do you come up with related shows? You know, we have some recommendation
engine, you know, four out of five dentists subscribed to this Podcast. Therefore you might
like this one. I don't like that at all. That seems, that's never worked for me at least.
However, I do see if someone makes a channel on Pod Show Plus and has a certain show in it
that you may be interested in other channels that contain that show created by other people.
That I think would have some value. So I think that's where it's going to go. And so we'll
probably say related channels. If you let me know that would be great. Yeah, you got it.
And here's the obligatory plug. Of course. You can listen to me, the philosophy guy.
Either one of these podcasts, the philosophy guy show at philosophy guy.net or the
Podsafe Comedy Countdown at PodsafeComedyCountdown.com.
And Adam. Yes. Well, this call complete. Holder scruncher, holder scruncher.
I'm a scruncher. Yeah. There are no secrets. Only information you don't yet have.
The Pod father has spoken. Are you listening? Get your dosa daily source code with Adam Curry.
Check me out at myspace.com slash Sofia Ramos Rocks.
Oh, love me tonight and make me feel secure.
Oh, love me tonight and make me hope to live.
Oh, it's a night and let me feel love. I never want you to hate me, but you're so tight.
I've carried on the world. I just help you, but I'm just a girl.
Oh, love me tonight and let me feel love. I'm just a girl.
Oh, love me tonight and let me feel love.
So, Sofia Ramos, love me tonight. You can find her at the Pod Same Music Network links to that in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Those of you checking us out on Serious Stars 102 coming up next, Pacific Coast Hellway, followed by Dawn and Drew Jersey Todd Show,
DVD Weekly, CC Chaping, East Radio, and Scott Sigurdall talked to you guys tomorrow.
Hi, Adam and DSE listeners, Ed from Ed's Mixbag here. I just wanted to send the biggest thank you I could to Adam.
The promo you played on DSE number 435 inside of the satellite window, no less,
was put together at the very last minute on Thursday at 5 p.m. East Coast Time and then
dropped it into your inbox at Pod Show, probably around 4 a.m. Friday your time. As I don't like doing stuff at the last minute,
you're playing it on the show made it even more special. As I drove to Denny's for breakfast,
I figured I'd miss the deadline for the Charlie. During breakfast, I popped my iPods ear buds into my ears,
and 14 minutes later had a grin so wide I felt like I had to tell everyone on the restaurant
my promo on behalf of Sofia Ramos made it to the show. This definitely made up for the previous time
I ate there, and I listened to you and Patricia discuss which category we fall into folder or
cruncher. That took care of the appetite on that time, but not so today. You've outdone yourself my friend,
but then something else happened. I proceeded to the car wash and a stop at my local grocery store.
The ride from their home is a short one, so I popped the earbuds back into my ears,
something I don't usually do while driving. And as I got home to my condos parking lot,
there was this beautiful lady unloading the trunk of her car. It wasn't a red sports car,
but as I listened to you, closed out the Charlie. It was as if you were narrating everything I was
seeing through my windshield. The first thing I heard you say was, I think it was you were referring
to the song you had played just prior to that. And you said if I had one of those every month, I'd be happy.
Uncanny to say the least what I was seeing here for the listeners. This is what I heard from
Adam while I was drooling at a blonde neighbor that I had never seen before.
And you can see from miles and miles and miles, but not really, there is a cloud day, so I'm like,
oh, there's the hot look in the neighbor. We have a neighbor and she's an aerobics instructor,
and she has a hot red sports car, and Patricia's always a bag in honor. Oh, man, I wish Patricia
were here. We could talk about her right now because she always has a belly shirts on.
Yeah, let's see. She just pulled up into the drive and her little red sports car. Let me see
which is wearing all of it. And as I walked up to my door, the narration continued,
giving me a cause to chuckle. Some comic relief as I face preparing more for the upcoming
Sophia Ramus special on Ed's mixed bag available as of this past Saturday, August 5th. By the way,
as I follow up on August 12th, I'll have a Skype interview with the rock goddess that will not
rehash any questions we've all heard before. I have a unique angle, I think,
having grown up in Brooklyn, New York and Ramus in the Bronx, New York. That should I'm hoping
create sort of a rapport with Sophia. I haven't done the interview yet, so wish us luck.
The URL is edzmixbag.com, and your support item is very much appreciated. And, uh, oh yeah,
yeah, bolder. Yeah, of course. Of course you're folding my friend. It's a scruncher, not cruncher.
But as you were telling me that story, I thought back to the many podcasts that I've heard
that somehow strangely interacted with the surroundings I was in at the time, and I think I've
got the, I think I've got the new slogan. Now, it's a stolen one, of course, but all, you know,
it's better to steal something good than to make up something bad. Potio, the soundtrack to your life.
Another, the topic of folder versus scruncher has officially been closed, but it gave rise in my mind
to an issue which I feel is the number one health issue facing men today. You see, many men just
like you and myself suffer a terrible, painful issue, because of societal pressures and stereotypes
and embarrassment, they're afraid to talk about it. You see, I, among millions of other men in America,
I'm a sufferer of hemorrhoids, and I'm coming to you under the conditions of anonymity because
of those societal pressures, stereotypes, and the embarrassment. The embarrassment I'm having to
buy special creams, taking extra fiber in our diets, Adam, it's time we talk about hemorrhoids.
It's time that the daily source code become a beacon of light to an area that is so dark.
Adam, please help me in raising hemorrhoidal awareness and smashing down the embarrassment
that's so many men face today. Let's talk about hemorrhoids together. We can wipe out hemorrhoids.
Oh yeah, and I almost forgot. Folder. Well, of course, you're a folder. You kidding me? You can't
scrunch in that condition, my friend. But maybe you want to send this over to a mad wine scene
who, of course, has been fighting yeast for years. I think she could easily attack on some
rides. Are you troubled by nagging itch between the ears that in your ear,
dribble that cute tips and drive time hosts just don't seem to clear up? You may be experiencing
BMS planned media syndrome. True BMS does not respond to quick channel changes nor earplugs
without proper care. BMS can lead ultimately to shrinkage of the brain among other things.
However, thanks to the makers of InsightWorks.com, a revolutionary new diet has just been shown
to permanently cure BMS. A steady low fat high content diet of podcasts combined with
show notes comments feedback and forums has been shown to increase cognitive functioning humor,
co-tour, and overall satisfaction. Dry new podcasting for that. Oh, so refreshing and soothing
relief from BMS. Contact your doctor for everything else, but listen to podcasts for instant relief.
Brought to you by makers of InsightWorks.com and other fine podcast. Some side effects may include
constant walking around with earbuds, jammed into your ear and loss of all contact with the
outside world. I've been talking to a couple of big-name artists who are considering
managing a channel on pod show plus. So it would really be a whole channel about them and
their community. And I can't tell you, I just can't talk about it yet because it's too
premature and I want to mess it up. But it does have to do with pod safe music, obviously,
or music that could become pod safe. And really, as I said, an entire channel, go look at the
program guide at pod show plus and then imagine what a channel could look like by single
artist. And it may not necessarily be an artist who sings. I'm not going to give you any hints,
but we're working on a couple of different things. And I have to say that people are doing such
innovative daring and explorative things with pod safe music. It just blows me away. Check out
what's happening with the Jonathan culture. It's kind of the Jonathan Colton project. I mean,
a huge Jonathan Colton family, which is why I started the Jonathan Colton project, which is a video
podcast. It made videos for Johnson Colton songs. As if that wasn't enough, I've now decided to
fire Jonathan Colton over to the UK to form two gigs between November 10th and November 18th.
I've had some interest from senior universities, but I've still got a long way to go to make
the survival plan. So if there's anyone out there that like to help in any way, ideally I'm
looking to be able to help with venues and publicity, but general assistance will be appreciated.
To find out more, visit www.jo.co.com and press the tour button. And Adam, thanks for the
fun Javie's story. Oh, I don't want to forgot. Yeah. Oh, we got it. Fold it. No, I was the
one. There wasn't a time team. There's no alternative of course.
So if you want to help Jonathan Colton out with a Joc, video.com, it's cool man. He's flying him over
to do dates and they haven't even been set up yet. This is awesome. I just love how people
get involved with the artists at a ground level. This is what Christina was talking about.
I'm pod save the queen. She said, it was funny. She's saying, this is just like the 60s, man.
Everyone can put their stuff up on my space. Of course, I crunched and cringed and said,
oh, I dream of the day when she says, you can put it all up on the pod save music network. She didn't
listen to me. All right. I got about seven or eight minutes. I just wanted to run through a
couple of different voicemails that those of you that called in over the weekend had another
30. So I can only roll out seven or eight of them. And of course, I chose the listener of the day.
And also a model, let me give an example of what I'd like to hear, a model listener who calls in
and does the perfect call in explaining who they are and and well, I have a listen, check it out for a second.
Hey, Adam, I'm just calling up down. You wanted to know about your listeners. The game is Brian
Plansky. I'm 31 other than Edders Pennsylvania, which is right outside of Harrisburg, the state capital.
I'm a new dad with the son at home. He's four months old. I work at a health desk for the
probation board for the state of Pennsylvania. I do have a podcast that I don't think
more than a handful of people listen to. It's the bulk of see her podcast at
full-to-sever.logspot.com. I am a folder and I listen to your show. You can't try the first podcast I
ever listen to and I've just been hooked on podcasting ever since. So I'm just telling all my friends about it.
Oftentimes they look at me like I'm not. She thought I'm doing the podcast. I love it.
Hope in the here. I'm more cool stuff from you guys. See you later.
See, almost almost perfect. Isn't it gave me the folder scruncher info told me what he does,
how old he is and what I'd love to know dude is those friends who look at you like you're nuts.
Show on podshow.com and then tell me if they understood any of it, if they got anywhere, if they could
figure it out, if they were delighted or if they didn't give a shit. Either way, I'd love to know.
Please, let me know. Hi there. My name is Kent. I'm 37. I'm a copilot at a major airline and I live in
New Hampshire. It listening since October 2004 and who has time to fold. Spencer.
Disappointing. Disappointing. I should give you the number to call and I really appreciate it.
I'm learning so much about you guys. The age range is all over the place too, which is just fantastic.
It's grab your phone now, put it in first hit little plus, which is somewhere down the bottom
of your keypad. One, two, zero, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven or in London,
O2O, 76813753. Hey, pod father. This is Greg. A couple of things, so this will be a long
message. First of all, you ask listeners to call in and say the age and stuff like that. Well,
my name is Greg. I'm 18 and I don't have a job right now, but I'm doing podcasting and what's kind
of funny about that is I never knew I could love anything so much as to getting on a little
penny microphone, a $20 microphone, I'm spilling my heart in my soul and all my funny, horrible,
30 little stories about fat people like grocery stores and different stuff like that.
It's creative, though, isn't it? Isn't it fun to do that to create a show? This is what I like
hearing as people who are just fans of podcasting listen to the favorite shows and they start
their own little show and it's made for just for their families or for just preventing or whatever.
It's real simple and it's free. But the other thing is, you're talking about that. You're going
to give out special t-shirts. Well, that sounds awesome that really does, but on a t-shirt where
it's as listener in the day or the week, it should mark folder or scruncher. And I ask my mom
you tell me that she wanted to know if she was a folder scruncher. She was way too embarrassed to
call, but she, indeed, is a scruncher folder, so two scrunchers and a family. And honestly,
I really, really don't want to know what my father is and a few of the scruncher are not.
I think he uses their fingers really too much. And the other thing is, well, okay, you've been
telling people to go over the daily source code.com to leave their entries for your iPod. Well,
I went over there and there's like nowhere to enter for your iPod. I don't freaking understand.
Oh, dude. If you just go into any into the episode, this comments right below.
I'd love to find out why people can't figure that stuff out. We got to make this better.
Got to make it better. Yeah, just, just, did you read the comments? Did you find the
comments at all that had people like entering the Troy News and iPod.com contest?
I tried to message a couple of different people and they don't know where the hell they're going to
language. And by the way, Shadow Falls, the best podcast ever. But, you know, you can't tell
about it. That because they're going to kill me. And the other thing is, well, that's at the end where
it says, this has been another pod save pod gas, a pod show pod gas, speaking your ears and
goes, I love it. The fact, Dawn, I want to know, please tell me for the love of, for the love of
zombie Jesus. Is that Dawn the Sally at the end where it says, why why it is? Okay, it says,
limelight, not long with limelight, limelight. No, it's not Dawn the Sally. I do know who it is.
I wonder if we should make another contest out of this. Okay, I think we should. I'll think of a
prize. I'll make it worth your while. Who is the female voice? At the end of every pod show pod
cast where you hear, get this show and other great shows like it on the high performance pod cast
delivery network from pod show and limelight networks. And then you hear, I love it. Who is it? Who is that
mysterious female voice? If you guess, fame and riches and valuable prizes for you. It says, I
want. Because it's so, I think I'm a super genius that I taught that and realize that.
Yep, that's about it. You know what? I love the Charlie. It was that French guy. I forgot his name
right now. French French lazy bastard. That's the awesome thing you get to do in any of the
of them. That's not it. What do you mean, come extra blogger? Today, what I'm not sure if
I say on London. One more thing, you have to frequently think about coming to the podcast
episode because I really wanted to go there just so I can meet you, pod father. Because you've
done so much for test pod cast. That's the only reason I wanted to go. And I went to the last
year and I couldn't get to because there's just so many people, but please seriously think about it.
Okay. And if not, I would dare, you know, bye. All right. Okay, now we learned a lot in that one
didn't we? New contest started. Who is that female voice? Diable cash prizes. Well, maybe not cash,
but a valuable prize. I promise you that. Pod cast the expo. I don't know I did. I really don't
know. I'm going to see if the timing works out. And then if I go, then it'll be, if I go, then it'll
be, we'll probably have to get another hotel suite. Because it's just like, there's nothing,
you know, I walked two steps and there's a million people and no one's ever happy because
either I didn't talk to you where I talked to you for three seconds. I hate that. I hate it.
So that would be the only condition that I could go, but it really depends on the timing. And then of course,
we'll make sure that we hook up for sure. Hey Adam, this is Mark and Austin Texas. I just wanted to let's
know that I really like the channel feature on the Pod Show Plus. Making a channel for my device is great.
And the cool thing about it is that it actually, uh, let's me add everything to my playlist all
once. I don't have to go dig it around and everything that ad shows to play us. You just add
everything in the channel directory and you're good to go. Well, anyway, that's all I wanted to say.
And if anyone has a chance to take a listen to a tasty logic at tastylogic.podshow.com,
that is all. That folder scruncher. Too bad. Dude, you figured it out. This is this is one of
the things that we're going to be using channels for. So imagine using the same interface and just
by dragging and dropping as you've probably already figured out to be able to program, not just
what goes on your iPod, but what goes on to your Tivo or perhaps if you're in the United Kingdom,
what goes on to your it's a big expensive word, IPTV, which is something we'll see all over the world,
which of course is television that comes in through an internet protocol or better known as
broadband. And then no one's here to answer the phone. Oh, maybe Christina is here.
So indeed, so you'll be able to sit at, you know, you can sit at the, you can actually make another
channel for when I'm sitting at the office and just play that in a web browser. So you're going to be
able to configure these channels in any number of ways you could do it by genre or you could do it
by device that you want to play it out on. Exactly right, glad you just glad you saw it and glad that
you are like it. And now we're from our sponsor. It's the Yanks versus the Brits. We'll drive
it, show the crazy, but everybody knows that it's apparent to see that just like you and me,
it's the Yanks and the Brits. The Yanks versus the Brits. Mind the gap.
Had a my major again just filling up on the cool from last week, as a reserved
introspective, some might say tight asked Brits. There are three things that I can't bring myself
to do. One is to refer to anybody as dude. Another is to admit that I did anything,
that's with 1G or 2. And a third is to reveal my bottom wiping habit. This is a world
that's what you might be happy. So I guess my best adjustment here, guys,
folder. Thank you so much. All right, one last song before I get out of here, brand new to the
podcast music network. Lee Rocker. Rockin' Hada.
I got you tell you that the day is getting near, baby, baby, there ain't nothing left to say.
Baby, baby, I want you to get on where I'm looking at, and then I haven't been there before.
I want to want you down, feel the moon through, a baby, baby, let you know that it's true.
You told me that I'm gonna sit in a train, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby,
let's jump on the car, baby, baby, baby, baby, don't you know what, feel it's true? I'm not gonna
sit in a train, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, don't you know what, feel it's true? I'm not gonna
sit in a train, baby, baby, don't you know what, feel it's true? I'm not gonna get on
this.
Looking at my  we call him.
I wanna What is all the proof, baby, baby, don't you know that it's true?
We're talking now but it doesn't take, baby, baby, baby, I didn't pay.
I want to tell you that the day is continued.
Baby, baby, they're ain't got to let me say.
Baby, baby, I want to let you get away.
I'm not gonna let you say.
I'm not gonna let you fall.
We're not gonna let you fall.
The rocker, rock and harder.
He's branded the pot save music network.
The first track up there, which, and if you don't know who,
who Lee Rocker is, he's the bass player from the straight cats.
Remember the straight cats?
Of course, many of you probably heard of Brian Setser,
who I think also did, had some solo success.
I've thought of the straight cats.
And so this is the bass player.
And according to Patricia, he was the cute guy anyway.
Lady Patricia will be on with us tomorrow.
I guess if all goes according to plan.
One more thing I just wanted to check out if you have the time.
I told you on Friday about the strip podcast, the strip podcast.com,
another pod show podcast.
And these guys are in Vegas.
And so they interview all these folks who come in and perform in Vegas
and sometimes for weeks or months on end.
So the one I told you to listen to was Tony Braxton,
but then I went and they listened to their current show,
which is with Chubby Checker.
And you've got to listen to this show.
Chubby Checker is so frustrated about mainstream music
and mainstream media, really.
Because he feels that, well, as you'll hear in the interview,
every other sentence he says, I don't get no airplane.
I don't get no airplane.
The reason why I don't get no airplane.
And just goes on and on and on.
And he says some really valid things.
Like, you know, he feels that if you look in music,
you should say, well, in reverse chronological order,
the people who made it happen,
the Beatles, Elvis Presley and Chubby Checker.
And he says that actually a lot of what he did.
All the way up to his influence music,
all the way up to hip hop.
He says hip hop, that's just the pony.
Chubby Checker did that, but Chubby Checker don't get no airplane.
That's why no one knows about the history of Chubby Checker.
And I'm sitting there listening to this going like, dude.
And I don't know if you own any or you're stuffed,
but get it up on the Podsade music network.
Become a part of this community.
We'll get you some pod play for sure.
Look at what James Brown did.
You better believe it.
So if anyone knows good old Chubby Checker,
living in Pennsylvania these days, I believe.
He should definitely check out what's happening in podcasting.
I think people would give him more than the props he deserves.
And we'd love to be able to play your music.
Are you kidding me?
All right.
Wow, almost 50 minutes too long, too long, too long, too long.
Okay, got lots of stuff to do.
Looking for the crap here to the lighter.
Can't sign off without that.
See you tomorrow, everybody.
Adam at curry.com.
We're better yet.
Adam at podshow.com.
And all the show notes for today's episode at
DailySourceCode.com.
Talk to you tomorrow.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this podcast.
And we're great ones like it.
On the high performance podcast,
a delivery network from Podshow,
and line-white networks.
I love it.
Thank you.