Now, Delta Sierra Charlie 358.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass,
then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Justing here's an angry.
Why didn't think that he would all be less or not stuck comedy?
I didn't know that every night will make it the best to me.
Well, I'll just gotta get through this world.
I'll just gotta get through this world.
When new lessons feels like getting pushed in some of that to me.
Keep hanging on to the old that it might all come back for me.
Well, I'll just gotta get through this world.
I'll just gotta get through this world.
I'll just to lonely girl.
The tip of the love is hidden everywhere in the darkest nights.
With lightning bugs at shine, feeling you can't see your light.
Well, I'll just gotta get through this world.
I'll just gotta get through this world.
I just gotta get through this world
I gotta smile at any time
I'm just the one who's going on
I'm not just the one who's going on
From New York, very coral, an aspiring angel
From the Podsate Music Network, good morning
Everybody are good afternoon, good evening
Wherever you are, wherever you're listening to this podcast
It is the daily source code coming to you from Curricondo
And once again, not a sunny day
It's really hard, you know
I, last time I was out here the weather was so beautiful
And it was so much easier to be up
And really energetic because, you know, the sun would be rising up over the bay
And just throwing its rays all the way to the mountain range
All across the city
And today it's just grey, grey, grey
And I'm a little bit bummed down
In fact, that's song by Barry Coral
I want to dedicate that to a good friend of mine
Amanda Monaco of the Bitties
And here's why
This is Amanda Monaco from the list of serious bitties and bitty cast
Here are 2005, I was diagnosed with multiple sclerosis
An autoimmune disease in the central nervous system
Multiple sclerosis can create trouble walking, vision loss, numbness and loss of cognitive function
Among other things
Thankfully, I'm doing very well
And living my life in the most part is I always have
But there are many others who are less fortunate than I
So please join the bitties and our team, team bitty
An April 23rd at New York City, South Street, C-Port for the MS Walk
New York City 2006
Go to bittycast.com, B-I-D-D-Y-C-A-S-T
To join the team or make a donation through team bitty
Our goal is to raise $10,000 from this research
And we're sure we can do it with your help
On your percent of the proceeds, go to research programs
I can use support for people with MS
Thanks
So again, here's something like that, man
It's just like
Bums you out this early in the morning
I heard CC Chapman's
I think it was on U-Turn Cafe
CC's gonna go, sorry
He's going to New York, he's gonna help out
I don't know where I am if I can get to New York
Of course, I'd love to participate
But I think I can help out
In other ways as well, so I'll definitely do that
Love you girls, love you Amanda
Alrighty then
Hope you saw the video
That I put up last night, I'm on a roll now
Now that I figured out I'm movie
Which is still not quite the system
Man, I guess I have to get Final Cut Pro loaded
I'm machine, so I can really do some editing
I movie doesn't let you do all the chroma key stuff
And mixing things in, it's very, very
It seems more basic than it used to be
They get simpler for some reason
That I'd lose some of the features
Or if they've been hidden and I just can't find them
So that was the, the iPod implant video
That, that I rolled out yesterday
And I guess pretty soon I'll start putting this on on its own feed
But for right now, I'm really kind of enjoying the distribution
That the daily source code feed has
And only one person, well no one is complaining about
We're putting videos mixing those up with the shows
And you can understand why I'm doing it, right?
Because if I have to start a whole new feed
The question is, you know, do I get the same exposure?
Well, that many, actually it's a good experiment
I'll start a new feed, okay?
The minute the pdn goes live, I'll have a new feed for the videos
And then we'll see if we can build up a new feed in the meantime
If you got something fun just to share
With the source code audience, if it's a short clip of something
Send it off to me, I'd be happy to play it
And of course, really looking for the music videos
And I already have a couple of enough to, I got enough stacked up
To take me through
At least through next week
If you're checking us out on serious stars 102, this is the pod show
Line up four hours every single day
From 6 pm to 10 pm eastern 3 to 7 Pacific
We kick it off with a daily source code
It's always followed by Pacific Coast Hellway, East Radio, Don and Drew
And of course, I don't have my satellite repairman, Uncle Jesse
PW offense and line up here
So I don't know what the hell out
Oh wait, tonight I think is a DVD weekly tonight
I know he's sitting there listening to this going
Ah, curry you idiot, I should send you a message every single day
Hey Adam, I'm loving the videos
But I'm a little concerned about the one dated for March 22nd
I'm almost afraid to ask
What do you plug in to charge an ad media?
Hope this action isn't performed in the same port where biodiesel was produced
I don't think that you would input through an output port
But you know, you never know
So let me know what the deal is there
And hope you have an a great day
And safe travels my friend, take care
This is so much hot for the piles
I don't know, we'll talk to each other
There are so many horrible comments I could make about that
Who's at crushland.com
But I do kind of like a bidirectional ports to be quite honest
If you haven't seen the video, you gotta go check it out
To really appreciate the full spectrum of that particular comment
Let me see, I had another piece of feedback
And one of the short stuff was really nice
Hey Adam, just watch the day at Potcho
And wow, too many transitions
Holy crap
Other than that, it's pretty good
But damn man cut back
Cut back on the transitions
Well, you know what else you can't really do overlapping video
It's very hard to cut up
I mean, what you want to do with videos you want to be able to separate
Well, you can separate the audio from the video track and I'm movie
But you really want to, it's hard
Because it does all this automatic, you know, connecting bits
That you've just cut and then your audio gets out of sync
And it doesn't, the program for as good as Final Cut Pro is
I'm movie does not think the way I think when it comes down to editing
So, and God, that's hard stuff
That takes a long time
Rendering and waiting and transferring
And it's not, you know, I was talking to you to Cali
Yeah, you saw some pieces of pieces
You saw some of Cali's bits, the UK podcast
Listeners are laughing now
You saw some of Cali's bits on that video probably
And it was interesting
We had a conversation
Oh man, it was it with Cali and I think it was
Yeah, it was with Cali and I knew we were talking about video programs
And they said something really interesting
They said, hey, you know, do you have any plans to make a cast
Blaster for video?
And it hit me like a ton of bricks and like, wow, that would be really interesting
And if you consider the way cast Blaster works
Which is not a post-editing, but it's a real-time tool
It may actually be very possible
I have no idea because, you know, quick time
Of course is not really a native Windows product
So, excuse me
Oh god, would I love a sense sale right now?
Oh man, in fact, I'm just homesick in general
If you don't mind me saying
I'm really ready to go back home
But got a couple more days, Saturday is when we travel back
And it's just, I miss talking to the girls all the time
You know, we're so limited to like 15 or 20 minutes a day
Because when, you know, by the time that I'm done with the show
And I've gotten my morning started
Then I call home and they're about ready to go to bed
And you're always in the different mood
It's very, very hard to coordinate
As you know, Patricia never listens to the show
So sometimes I feel dumb just spent on talking about
Life out here on the show
And then I forget all the things I was going to tell her in real life
And I can't wait to be back home and have her on the show
That'll be even better
And I get so many people asking me to get her on the show again
She definitely is the big surprise of the source code
Hey, it's very exciting day today
You may have run across an announcement
In the past day or two
About a brand new promotion
Actually I have my little info sheet here
We had a name for it
It was, oh gosh, I don't have it on this sheet
It was like one brand of thousand voices or something like that
And many voices
It was something really good that we came up with
What's happening as of today is we have about 50 podcasts
On the network now on the pod show network
And today everybody who is a listener
To the daily source code
Can get all kinds of great deals at GoDaddy
GoDaddy.com
When you register domain name
And I've noticed that this is almost addictive to some people
There are people who go to go to GoDaddy
Almost every single day
Just to see what domain names are available
And they come up with great ideas for friends
Giving away a wacky domain name
And putting a web page up
And there's all kinds of services that GoDaddy has
That make it help you do that really easily
And the way we're doing it now is every podcaster
I mean this is a part of the quit your day job campaign
And there are some people who based upon their downloads
They're actually going to make some nice money on this particular promotion
The way it works is in my case
If you're listening to the source code
And you want to get one or not one of these great deals
Which is what do we have?
10% discount
On anything you purchase from GoDaddy
We have five dollars off any order of 30 dollars or more
And we have another one which is
Domain name for just 695 a year
So for either
You know, let's just go with the domain name for 695 a year
Because that's probably what most people go after
When you go to GoDaddy.com
Enter DSC3 as in Delta Sierra Charlie 3
And then in my case I'll actually get credited for you buying that
This is like an affiliate program almost
In fact it's exactly what it is
Now you don't have to fill out DSC3
Because I'll never see any of that money
Because whenever we sign someone up
Then the podcaster who who's code is used makes money
So listen to your favorite podcaster
Find out what their code is
They'll be talking about it and enter that
And then you actually support that podcaster at the same time
If you're going to buy a domain name anyway
You might as well do it
For instance, you could enter the code for these guys
Hey Pearl, what you doing?
I'm starting my own website
How do you do that?
Well first I go to GoDaddy.com
And register my own domain name
For as low as 695
A year
I just registered Pearl but go for
GoDaddy sounds easy
After that goDaddy.com can help me with the hosting
And the website building
And when I'm all done they put me in traffic blazer
Which submits my site to 200 search engines and directories
GoDaddy sounds good
They are
They're my number one overall for web domain registration
By the domain name wire survey
How do I get started?
As a podcaster podcaster
You can get special prices at godaddy.com
You can get 10% off any order
Or you can get $5 off any order of 30 dollars or more
Or you can get your domain name for just $6.95
Since a year
Get out of the way Pearl
I want my piece of the internet at godaddy.com
Get your piece of the internet at godaddy.com
And there are really no rules
With how the podshow podcasters promote this
So if you have any great ideas for different way of
Advertising that
Let me know the go first is just one way
Speaking of advertising
Now here's some blatant advertising I received in email
Hey Adam
It's Andrew Grummit here
Oh no it's Andrew Grummit
Oh no!
The man behind juice
The man behind iPodder
The man behind gigadil
Her listeners may know
I recently moved my family across the country to join up with podshow
In San Francisco
With that behind an absolutely killer condo
And some of El Massachusetts
And it was a tough call
But we decided to put it on the market
I'm sending a link along in case anyone out there in the
Boston corner of the podosphere
Is looking for a new place to call home
They may be interested to know that the property in question
Was the birthplace of gigadil
An incubator of the iPodder lemon software
Now known is juice
Well that's all for now
Thanks Adam
See you tomorrow at HQ
You mean see in a couple hours at HQ
And he sent this last night of course
Hey you know
Have you ever been to Thomas Alva Edison's home
And New Jersey and you know it's a museum now
And you see his laboratory
That his workshop and where he slept
And you know there's like some some of his inventions
Like a rubber rubber rubber rubber
Indian rubber
He was he had something to do with the invention of rubber
Thank you Thomas
Thank you so much
To imagine
You know you could actually have
The home of Andrew Grummit
Just like the museum that is now
Thomas Alva Edison's former home
You could own that
I'll put the link in the show notes
And yes this time I actually will put it in the show notes
We've got to tell you over the weekend
We had a lot of fun
I hooked up with Mark Yosimoto Nemkov
And we worked on a new pod show production
You know we have pod show LA
Which is essentially this shack on Venice Beach
Which has a lock on it
But you know there's not really a lot of equipment in it anyway
But it seems people do seem to kind of use the shack
Sometimes when Mark isn't there for other things
But that's where we're working on a couple of different shows
One of them is a game show called Boned
And I think we'll be starting that in a couple of weeks
And the game shows are fun to figure out and put together
Because you need some really good elements
And in this case it's going to be a game show between two contestants
I if I want to understand Dawn and Drew
We're actually going to be on one of the first episodes
And it's a trivia game show but you can bone your apartment at your apartment
You can bone your opponent
And you can only imagine how much fun that is
And as a Mark and I were actually the first two test contestants
And unbeknownst to him I'm actually very good at all this trivia
I'm a great at jeopardy and any TV trivia quiz
I love doing that
So let's just say
I boneed Mark really really good
The latest show
Hi, I'm Kanty and Jose's here
And we're inviting you to come listen to our weekly podcast
We talk about cooking the Bible opera with interviews
I talk about Brendan the star
No one else does that
Sometimes fitness I always have some commentary
I talk about my life and more
The flight of show can be found at iTunes and at Q-border
And other places on the web
Just do a Google search for the flight of show
And you'll be sure to find it
See you there
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do
We're our flank
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers
We believe your personal information should be just that
Personal
And we believe your internet should be a friend
Not a fo
We're our flank
Make this smart choice
Visit earthlink.net
And discover what our internet experts can do for you
Earthlink
We revolve around you
As interviewed on Eat This Hot Show
Which is from Q-border.org
It's a Madge Weinstein-Ragan Fox
And Wanda Wisdom
And I actually I didn't had no idea how the show
What's going to turn out
And they edited it as a triple ender
So everyone records their own piece
And they put it together later
And they do edit it down to about 30 or 40 minutes
And I think we talked for probably an hour
So some pieces we're missing from the actual recording
We're not missing but we're taking out
But in hindsight the show is kind of good
And it's interesting to have a conversation with this particular trio
Because they really don't hold back
But one of the things that came up
Was about promos on the source code
And about members joining the network
You definitely should check it out eatthishotshow.com
And at a certain point I said hey you know
This is great community of queer cast
There's a Q-border.com
But just so you know I rarely
If ever receive a promo from from the homo
And so and I say that because literally
In my email after doing the show
There's just tons of emails coming
I mean you should see my I'm amazed
My spam blocker isn't kicking in
It's like hey you know
Queer over here
A homo with a promo
So I really appreciate it
And I'm rolling them out for you guys and girls
Do you ever think that everyone in Texas
Fux their sister
Don't that night
A big and fresh
Big and fresh
Welcome find out
What really happens in Texas
With Mikey Pod on the Bayou
With Michael Heron
That Mikey Pod.com
Michael serves as listeners
Even in a face of danger
When Hurricane Rita approached
Mikey Pod was there
Look at the waves
I can't just sit here anymore
We've gotta go outside and cover this
I'm gonna take my recorder outside
Are you?
I have to bring in my O to my listeners
Michael now
We're just gonna go outside
I can't just sit here and let this happen
Without people knowing
I've got to
The real deal
Mikey Pod on the Bayou
Count on him for more
Unless he's at a hard night
Before and then
Well it's kind of heavy
Mikey Pod on the Bayou
He's welcoming you right now
Subscribe at Mikey Pod.com
We're looking up in iTunes
While that promo was running
I got a fuck
Let me see if I can retrieve the voice mail
You've got to hear this
This is too funny
Yeah, we work weird hours at Pod Show
Let me see if I can get this
Hold on
It's gonna sound like shit on the black barriers
I think
So
I'm trying to get
I don't know if you could hear that
But that was
K2
Kevin ready
Who's working on our
Mashboard development
And so I guess he went to the office
Around 7, 7, 30 or something like that
7, 20 actually
Looking at the time
And we just had the alarm
Installation put in
Sounds like he opened the door
The alarm went off
And he's just called
Any number he can
He's probably going to get arrested
And when they see this guy
They're not going to believe his story
They could say, yeah
Sure you work here
Sure
Well absolutely
I know Adam Roger here
I heard your concerns on
Daily source code about the power cuts
Fortunately we don't get that many of them in
Go for it
But if you do run out then you're more than welcome to come
Round to my house
We've got lots of candles
And plenty of blind kits to cut a lapini
If he wants
I might not want to leave Trinity
Sooner any candles
Will that me fain around
She might blow up
I'm sure if he doesn't have any of
Your own parts before
Then you'll have witnessed that phenomenon
Anyway
It was nice to hear your little interview on
Eat this hot show
And so
Goodbye to now
And made the wind be with you
Roger so good to hear from you
Actually I think
I have to be honest
I don't think there's a guy in the world
I'm only talking about guys
But I'm sure there's some girls too
Who haven't tried to light one up
You know
Why do we have to do that
What is it about us
And how old were you when you last tried that?
I know exactly when I last tried it
And it wasn't all that successful
But I know it wasn't all in the 50
Yeah
Roger
Ready
Go
There's another message
Roger
I'm looking
Actually there's a lot of UK feedback
I've been getting
It's really noticeable
Not quite sure what happened
But all of a sudden
In fact, I'm going a lot of email from people saying
Oh, yeah, I decided to tune back in
And see what's going
And that's fine by the way
I'm happy, please go away
And listen to another show
Instead of mine
And come back once in a while
And here what's going on
If you want to know what's going on
And you're listening to us on
Serious Stars 102
All you got to do is go to
Potchow.com
Or better yeah, go to dailysourceco.com
Download the rest of the show
Which you're about to miss
Because up next
We've got
Mark Yoshimo to Nemkoff
And the hell way players with PCH
There we go
Now taking care of business here
Everybody
I've got another good promo check
Follow your internet
Enter team
Source
We're gonna tell her
Love you
What's up everyone
Out there, Potman
I'm a side
And I'm Jason
Where are your hosts
To the Hat Show
And on the Hat Show
We spotlight
Undiscovered artists
As well as
Give you our Outlook
On the World of Entertainment
So Jason
Why aren't you letting everyone know
The website
www.TheHashow.com
And tell them to listen to the show
Because you just know
My line
That's why
Oh
It's like a hundred new shows
Coming out a day
If you attract it on podcast
Ali is unbelievable
How many cool podcasts are out there
And of course, I'm gonna fall
By the wayside
But wow
That episode is really really good
Email here
Came in through the
G-mails
From Mike Martin
Adam found an interesting
Connection between your recent
Discussion on Oil
And your Uncle Don
Recently I saw the film
Seriana
Which is all about the oil industry
And I liked it
Enough that I picked up the book
On which it was based
The book is called
Sino Evil by Robert Bayer
Basically it's an autobiographical story
Of a CIA operative
Becoming frustrated
With the CIA's
Increasing dependence on technology
Base surveillance
Overmore traditional methods
And we all know how that worked out
It turns out this is just one of three or four
Storylines running through the film
Who should pop up on page 29
During training in 1976
But Uncle Don Greg
So here's a quote from the book
And I have not read the book
Nor have I seen the movie
Yet I think version has it
So I'll look at the movie
I guess it's not in the movie
And only in the book
Shoot
I could watch the movie
And read the book on my way home
Here we go
Quote from the book
The most impressive person I met
Don Greg
Don would go on
To become security advisor
To then vice president George Bush
And ambassador to South Korea
When Bush became president
Back then though
Greg had just been reassigned to Washington
From Seoul
Where he had been
Oh text removed
I guess it was CIA chief
I'm not sure
For most of two hours we talked
He described what it was like
To live overseas
For most of one's adult life
The isolation
The alienation from family and country
The physical hardship
Just like it might be interested
I get the feeling though
Says Mike and he's from Melbourne
That Uncle Don might have gotten cold
Feed about doing an interview on the DSC
If that's the case
It's a bummer I was looking forward to hearing from him
No, not at all
Believe me
Uncle Don is now 78
As I said he's the CEO of the Korean Society
The Korea Society
And he's very much involved
And a lot of the world politics
They're taking place right now
And he's become
He was always very outspoken
He tells great stories
Because he does character voices
And he can do
He does character voices
Not only of
Humanaries that you know
But also of ones that you don't
Not necessarily know
Like the Korean Ambassador
Or South Korean President
Just all kinds of
Interesting stories that he's gotten
I've listened to them all my life
And now that he's 78
And he's really kicking some ass
And he's just taking no prisoners
I told you that he
He as a Christmas card
There was a picture of him
Aunt Meg who was his wife
And I think the South Korean Ambassador
And President George Bush
The senior
And so it's beautiful
Card and Christmas tree in the background
The whole thing
You know it's and they're all dressed up
And they're Tuxedo's
And he had sent that card
Out as a Christmas card
And wrote on it
The Good Bush
With a little arrow towards
George Bush senior
And a lot of people didn't take that
They didn't take that very kindly
But that's the kind of guy he is
He's just screw it
You know I'm just going to lay it out on the line
So he really does have something to say
He will open up
The problem is I just have to get to New York again
That's really the only issue
This is not something I want to do
Want to phone call
This is something that
It will take several episodes
To get through
I'm sure
And in fact I'm bum
That I don't live any closer
Because I think I would rather go back
Three times
But it's coming
Believe me
It really is
It's just a matter of coordinating
And everyone being in the right
Time with the right place
So look forward to that
And I'm definitely going to read the book
Thanks Mike
Appreciate the tip
Adam, hi
It's Paul Nichols here
I'm supposed to be just giving you
Some quick audio feedback
Right
This is podcast ball from the UK
It's into a recent Charlie
And I have this
I've been British
Particularly being English
That brings with a highly
Creative cynicism
But what?
Hold on a sec
That's just continue to listen
You know
Yes, I would have to say
If I've noticed anything
There is a certain amount of cynicism in the UK
About certain things
Usually about the government
And about
You know, larger organization
So
I'm sure there's some cynicism
About me as well
Let's hear what you have to say Paul
You mentioned previously about the podcast music network
Only was
Hold on, it's the pod
You know, I hear this a lot
It's the pod
Safe
Music network
Not podcast
Not pod show music network
It's the pod safe music network
A common mistake
A bit concerned really
Because I thought
Oh, here we go
There's going to be a record label
The artist is going to lose that again
So I was absolutely
Why do people always think that of me
I'm your friend
I'm not trying to
You know, it's like, you know, we've talked about that roller coaster curve
When you're in the limelight
And gosh, I wish fame and celebrity on every single one of you
I feel like we're kind of in the upswing on the roller coaster
Because people are starting to look a little bit further than what they read on
You know, on a forum or a message board somewhere
Or what they thought they heard
They're starting to think a little bit
And they're starting to learn a little bit more about me
And as you look a little bit further
You'll see that there's actually some good things we're trying to do
So, you know, I think
Paul, you probably tuned out and stopped listening to the show a long time ago
So you've missed a lot of the conversation
I don't think a show goes by
Where I'm not talking about this
Because I'm very passionate about the pod safe music network
It is an unlabel
And I've been very clear that, you know, this is a community resource
That we're financing and so far we're really happy with the results
Because all it's doing is making pod casting more fun
Getting more creative people involved
All right, let's listen to the rest of your comment
You've delighted to hear that the tracks we're going to start at
99 cents, which you say, I think a very good price
And you're talking about nine cents or whatever
Just covering administration costs
No, no, no, no, let me just discuss the
Let me discuss that one more time
Just so you understand
99 cents, we just chose that
Because we feel that there's no reason to undervalue
Any type of creative art, you know, so if something
And iTunes is 99 cents and something else where is 79 cents
I believe we believe, I must say at Pod Show
We truly believe that that only makes the other, you know, the 79 cents
Seen like cheaper, therefore maybe not as good
Because, you know, what really does it make?
Does it make that much difference to a consumer?
79 or 99 cents? No, I don't think so
So we didn't set the standard there
But I feel that it's important since, you know, we're trying to teach people
That there is another way of buying music and that you can buy music
That is unrestricted from how many copies you make
And where you want to play it and what you want to do with it
And you can always go back and download it again
The nine cents is not an administration fee
It is the fee that is charged by clicking by
The cheapest one that can do worldwide
Transactions for us and we did a lot of research on it
And we're still working on being able to pay
Through SMS, you know, cell phone text messages
But that's man, the operators get into there
And they take 50 cents almost right off the top
So that nine cents is not administration
It is the cost of the transaction fee
There's another piece in there which we've only talked to
I think we've touched on it briefly
If you sell to many foreign countries, unlike the US
On the US there's no tax, no sales tax on internet commerce
At least I think that's still pretty much true for the US
But there's value added tax or VAT if you were to buy it
For instance in the United Kingdom or many other European countries
Which can be as high as 18 or even 20%
So that VAT also has to come out of the 99 cents
We really believe that if a podcaster puts a link in their show notes
Or if a listener, a fan of an artist puts a link on a website
And someone clicks that and purchases the song
Then that person should be entitled to a piece of the transaction
Now here's what we've done and we're going to make that pretty high
I think it's going to be at least 10%, maybe 15%
We really want to make it worthwhile
But that person will be able to choose to either take the money
Or donate it to the artist
And we're also working on a third donation
Which could be to a good cause
Maybe something like music cares
But that we still haven't figured out
But you will definitely be able to say, hey, I just want the artist to have this money
I don't want any piece of it
And the rest all goes to the artist
We're going to try this out for a year
Which I think is the best thing to do
Because you know who knows what's going to happen
Pricing may need to change the world could change within a year
So for a year that's the way it's going to break down
Podshow will take nothing
We feel is valuable enough to have people
Coming into the Podsafe music network
And being part of what we're doing
And let's just see if we can see if we can make this work
Let's see if people are really going to support independent music
In the manner that we believe they will
So that's what it's going to be
Got it?
Get it?
Good
I'm working it all out
And actually being very evangelical about saying this is for everybody
I was really pleased to hear that
I mean to say that without wanting to patronise or whatever
But really tough to hear about that
Also I was a bit concerned that podcasters might
If you like the stopped from playing bits and pieces
Because I don't know about you because
When I auditioned music I listened to I'm being serious now
Probably 30, 40, maybe 50 tunes before I get that one
And I auditioned it very carefully
I want the musically integrity to be there
And the production quality as well
And I was thinking well if I'm going to spend 99 cents every single time
You know as a podcast producer too
But then I know these things that's mad
Amazing where these things come from
I've heard this before
Someone said oh well you know curry's now turning this whole thing into
You got to pay as a podcast or to download it
Where did that come from?
Point me to where I said that
No there's the beauty of the pod save music
Not work as it's creative people in pod casting
Working with creative people in music for a common interest
You know it's so never ever was there
A thought to charge podcasters for downloading music
And of course there's one reason you know you would be paying
40 bucks to prepare your episode
I think that what got confused is my shout out to
These licensing organizations such as
Now in the UK they actually do have a license
The full license is not published yet as far as I know
But the basic high level details are
And this works for both the performance
Right as well as the mechanical so all your bases are covered
I mean this is great because they are putting a license together
Where you don't have to worry about someone else coming after you later
But they start off with like
12% of your gross revenue
And I really would there's a lot of mainstream stuff
I'd love to play you know as I've said many times
I'd love to bring back the hit test
Happy to finance it
But I'm not going to give up 12% of the gross revenue
Of this program just know there's just no way
No freaking way
Okay
Obviously that's not the way it's pan down
I'm really pleased about that
And lastly just one very last thing now
You mentioned on your iPod that you had all 80s music
Great so do I
You thought when I actually started I started off as the 80s podcast
And then realized hang on a minute
Things are going to get me in hot water here
What's a bit about that
I'm actually looking at the MCPS and PRS Alliance license
And I really want to see if I can if I can do that
And I can place my stuff right along the side
The pod safe stuff
So there we go
Anyway listen thanks for your time
All the best
By now
You know so I'm just hit me there
Well I was thinking about it
So my whole point was I would be happy to pay five
Dollars to play one song
Just one song one time license
Let me play it and be done with it
And I was just thinking wouldn't it be interesting
The 12% is just so incredibly high
I mean that's just way too much money
From this show
Of course pod show might be able to negotiate a much lower fee
For any podcast within the network that may be possible
But at the end of the day you just got to think
What am I willing to pay for the privilege
The privilege of promoting
This music
Over which I have no influence really
I have no direct contact with the artist
You know
I don't know
It's just I just feel it
Whereas I would have been really really excited about a license like this
A year ago
I'm just not that turned on anymore
Hey there's a long it's actually it's a longer piece of feedback
But some fantastic information
Because I put the call out about Mother's Day
I only really got one or two email responses
But nothing
Nothing as concise is what you're about to hear
So if you wanted about the global Mother's Day
DeLema
And wanted why it's not the same in every single country
Your answers are coming up
Hello
Hi Adam
It's Andy Taylor here
Andy
Just thought I'd drop you a quick line
For a couple of reasons really
Firstly
The discussion that's been going on regarding the Charlie
I found that quite interesting
Especially since
Over here in the UK
I'm not sure about elsewhere
But Charlie is a slang term used for cocaine
And therefore
When you say that you've enjoyed doing the Charlie
And that people are getting addicted to Charlie
Then
Yeah
Isn't this show like crack for you?
To lead
Indicates or could indicate that people are getting addicted to cocaine
To the Charlie
To another
Explanation
All right, get to the Mother's Day thing
Slime terms for the word
Charlie
My name
Andy, come on
Second
The
History of Mother's Day
Was originally brought in as the Spring Festival
Which
Breaks and Rowans dedicated to the mother of their gods
And was then
Taken up by Christians
To celebrate on the fourth Sunday in Lent
In honor of Mary
The mother of Christ
And in England
This whole day was expanded to include on with us
It was called Mothering Sunday
On the fourth Sunday of Lent
Which of course is this coming Sunday
26th of March
In the United States however
It was only about 150 years ago
That it all started
When a woman called Anna Jarvis
Organized the day to raise awareness
Poor health conditions in her community
And she thought that would be best
Advocated by mothers and she called it mother's work
Day
And it went on from there
And people then started observing
Mother's Day writing letters
Sending cars, presents, flowers, etc
And that's when mothers actually came from
That day in America is celebrated on the second Sunday of May
And that's also
So that's this Sunday is the 14th of May
And that's Australia, Austria, Belgium, Brazil, Canada, Chile, Colombia
Czech Republic, Denmark, Finland, Germany, Greece, Holland, Iceland, Italy
Luxembourg, New Zealand, Norfolk, Panama, Paraguay, Puerto Rico, South Africa
I could go on the USA, of course
I have every single one of those countries on my
Frapper daily source code map
But over here we like to be different
And therefore we celebrate it on the 26th
It's Roger Smalls calling
March
Sorry about that
Now the other thing, the final thing
Before I say goodbye
Is about the court case
And I'm sorry to
This is really interesting
You gotta listen to this guy
Because I don't know how he does some amazing research
You heard about Mother's Day right
Now listen to the research he's done
About the European Court
Which, of course, had supersede all local courts
Such as the one I went to and Amsterdam
For the Creative Commons case
But the distress that you've been put under
And I'm actually studying for a devolved law
Course at the moment
And I found it quite interesting
As I was reading through
The European Convention of Human Rights
Which, of course, overrides as far as I'm aware
Any local jurisdiction
And there is a limited rights
To write liberty and security
And qualified rights
Which are right to respect for private and fun lead life
Surely that comes in the yor
No, no, no, no, no, no
You know what?
I think you need to continue looking at the law
Because there is certainly in the United States
But also this is kind of what the judge pulled on me
In the Netherlands
You do not have that right if you're an entertainer
You're a fucking court jester with one of those freaky hats on
You automatically give up that right
That's why I say to people
I really wish you fame and notoriety
I really do because you'll see
You give up that right
But of course
And I've been through this rant before
There's a trade-off for that
And there's a number of different types of rewards
That make it worth it
Both social and economic
But sorry
I do not know a country that does not treat celebrities differently
Which of course it's illegal
But you know, hey there's celebrities
Fuck them
Area
If not
We have the data protection act
Where
The rights of a data subject
Rights to prevention of processing
Lightly to cause damage or distress
Such as
Obseting your daughter
Sure with this or something to do with it
Well
Thank you very much for listening
And I look forward to
Coming on listening to your show
Oh, yeah, they need a promo at the very end
Yeah, that was kind of weird
Dude, you should just
Just mention it right
That wasn't meant as a promo
I don't know
For my show whatsoever
But the promo in there
If you wish to give me a plug
You can do
I do
Get to it
I should do a little plug for that
Guys full of information
But oh man
Here we come
So that's what I think
Anyway Adam
And if you want to hear any more
Interesting and amazing facts
Especially
I like
About Mother's Day
And all sorts of other
Yeah, fantastic
Debates that go on
You can visit my podcast
Which is the
Runtings of an old and
Blok podcast
And the website is
www.Runtings.ShortURl.com
Alright
Dude, thank you very much
I appreciate all the research
You put into that
Very helpful
You know
And it's too bad
That we're in this
The spiraling funk
With comic strip blogger
Because there's a guy
Who I think actually knows
Quite a bit about European law
And
I don't know if we can pull him out
Of the place that he's in
Right now
He wants me to apologize
Look
Comics are blogger
Let me say this
You have to
You really have to be careful
About things you say
Because
I mean, listen
Just about the pod save
Music network conversation
You know, I've never
Said that podcast
Or would have to doubt
And you'll pay for downloads
I've said quite the opposite
I've never said that it would be like a
Store
In fact, I've said quite the opposite
Continuously and consistently
So people hear things
The way they want to hear them
And a lot of people heard your comment
And heard what I heard
So I will
I will say that it's very possible
And I think I even said
When I played it, you know
Is this a language thing
Or I say that often
About you comic strip blogger
Because
Sometimes
I even Patricia
You know, she's not a native English speaker
And her English is impeccable
But sometimes things will come out
Very rude sounding
Almost just because of
You know, the translation
That's going on in her head
Between her native language
And the language that she's speaking
But you have a knack
Of definitely
Talking about people
In a certain way
So whether you call
Ron Bloom my
Slavemaster
Or whether you feel it
Necessary to point out that he's Jewish
You know, I don't know
Man, you really got to watch out
With that shit
So I didn't, by the way, call you
And anti-semite
I didn't call you a racist
That I can recall
At least I have to go back and listen
But I think everyone agrees
That you have to be careful
With the words you're using
You've got the stage my friend
You do
Everyone's paying attention to you
And some people are very interested
And what you have to say
My wife even said that she's
She's starting to understand you
And like what you're saying
So you know, let's just reset everything
All right
Yeah, because it's
It will be fun to be able to continue
A conversation with you
But not when you keep
Yeah, it's just this tomb
Just look at what you're writing
And it's abusive
I know you wanted
Don't want it to be called abusive
You wanted to be called
Candid
Whatever, you know, stop it
This particular community
Called the charles
We don't
Just it's too much, man
And dial it back a little bit
You're on eleven
Turn it back to five
Or something like that
No, it'll be okay
Hey, let's play one more song
For I get out of here
Speaking of Candid
A lot of the language in this song
Is very Candid
Families, you are forewarned
Thank you for holding
Your call isn't wouldn't do us
Please stay on the line
God damn it
I can never fucking talk to any real people
And these things
Please continue to hold
To hold
They have been holding
For like two fucking hours
Cat suckers
A customer service representative
Well, you should
Hold on
I'm fucking barely holding on
A fucking sanity
I'm fucking fucking crack
You got to do
Thank you for staying on the line
Please hold
Your call isn't important to us
I'm sorry
But our offices are now closed
Please call back tomorrow
What?
Closed
It's fucking twelve thirty in the afternoon
Fucking you call
God damn it
I love this cheap name Murphy
He's got his own law
If I ever see that cracker
I'm a jack of him in the jaw
Just when I think that shit is gonna get better
I get soaked in a million problems
Like a fucking bed wetter
I read a letter for the city
Saying I owe them some cash
And with a splash landing in a sea
If that was no stash
Don't laugh
Even though Murphy's probably laughing
You knew all along
That the shit would fucking happen
I don't know
It doesn't work for sure
That fucking law
Puzzass
And while he's at a special place
To a plate of fucking glass
You can see I don't like them
He's always mistreating me
I playin' Murphy for the times right
And a myth of feeding me
He's cheating me
How many people got they on law
We're fucked up
He ain't stopping DB from being wrong
That's right
Come on man fuck that bitch
DB is comin' through
Y'all's time to get rich
Something we're wrong
Must've been Murphy
Never tried to help me
Always trying to hurt me
Telling me I'm hungry
When I'm only thirsty
Feelin' someone cursed me
Nasty
Something we're wrong
Must've been Murphy
Never tried to help me
Always trying to hurt me
Telling me I'm hungry
When I'm only thirsty
Feelin' someone cursed me
Nasty
In this world
There's always an evil hand attempt
Like I gotta go
A thousand miles on my tank
So empty
Running all night
Trying to rob my rights
Just to roll the dice
And I see Murphy again
He's stopping my happiness
Letting sorrow come in
To my girlfriend
Don't me and my fish dropped dead
I got fired
From my job lost the feeling
In my legs
But that's just the life of sleazy
I got Murphy on my back
And he ain't leaving me
He's a dead eye shot
When it comes to pain
Tragedy said this misfortune
No one's got better rain
But it's just the game
And it's always the same
Some days are good to see
Others are lame
It's a shame that life had to be this way
Some smokey or we
And drink young
Trains of family could die
Tomorrow some fuck
Who people think
Something we're wrong
Must've been Murphy
Never tried to help me
Always trying to hurt me
Telling me I'm hungry
When I'm only thirsty
Feelin' someone cursed me
Nasty
Something we're wrong
Must've been Murphy
Never tried to help me
Always trying to hurt me
Telling me I'm hungry
When I'm only thirsty
Feelin' someone cursed me
Nasty
Waitin' two hours
For the boss like a bomb
You decided to show
And then after you leave it comes
Like a car for a minute
Just they hit up the bank
And get a $40 ticket
From office to bank
If something can go wrong
You know what fucking will
The only way to fix it
Is bruised weed and pills
It gives Murphy thrills
It gives Murphy chills
To see my mother
Fucking coffee table covered in bills
But I've all let it bother me
If I'm victim of a robbery
I lose the fucking lottery
Start crying
It'll swab or eat
Cause I don't give a fuck
I look you right in the eye
And say I'm ready to die
Now that last part was alive
But we really need to stop
We're eating about big Murphy
To stop worrying about
The rifles on our turn
And that's it
That's all I heard in a song
D.B. coming through
And we break in Murphy's Law
Something we're wrong
Must've been Murphy
If he never tried to help me
Always trying to hurt me
Tell him me I'm hungry
When I'm only thirsty
Feel it someone cursed me
Nasty
Something we're wrong
Must've been Murphy
Never tried to help me
Always trying to hurt me
Tell him me I'm hungry
When I'm only thirsty
Feel it someone cursed me
Not as only Murphy
You know there's just aren't enough songs about Murphy's Law
We all know what it is
We've all witnessed the law
Where does it come from?
Andy that's something you can go research for us
If you wouldn't mind
Was Murphy really a guy
Dislocated boner from California
They got a whole bunch
They got three pages of songs
On the Podsave Music Network
Music.podshow.com
One more thing I want to say before I go
We've talked a bit about Heather and Janelle
Download with Heather and Janelle
Which is underwritten by
AccuView contact lenses
About that podcast
Well
Something must be going right
Because the show has been picked up for sponsorship for another period of time
I think it was six weeks
Something like that
So it's like the sponsorship is continuing
Of that show
And that would be against some of the wins
So congratulations girls
Download.accuView.com
podcast
Last week
Everybody I'll see you tomorrow
Take care
The Pod Show podcast
Stick it in your ear