I've got 16 pounds of porcelain toilet strap to my ass.
It was a curry cottage, your curry condo.
It was curry vinda loot.
Some way beyond scrunching or folding.
I'm gonna need a mop and bucket.
Why don't you listen to daily source code for eight five while I clean up this mess?
I'm on screw.
It's built this here at Charlie, 45.
Right, right at Murray.
The issue with the third screw will be D.S.C.485.
Like a flower waiting to bloom.
Like a light bulb in a dark room.
I'm here waiting for you to come home.
And turn me on.
Like a desert waiting for rain.
Like a school kid waiting for spring.
I'm sitting here waiting for you to come home back home.
And me on.
Like a flower waiting for spring.
Since you've been gone.
After all you're the one that turned me on.
Now you know I can turn me back home.
And I have eyes waiting for a new tune.
And my glass is waiting for some fresh ice here.
I'm just sitting here waiting for you to come home.
And turn me on.
And I have eyes waiting for some fresh ice here.
Now you know I can turn me back home.
Now I have eyes waiting for a new tune.
And my glass is waiting for some fresh ice here.
I'm just sitting here waiting for you to come home.
And turn me on.
And I have eyes waiting for some fresh ice here.
And I have eyes waiting for you to come home.
Perfect.
Perfect for a very lazy Wednesday.
Grace skies outside, heater on inside.
Feeling like crap, my friends.
I think the flu is still with me.
I've carried it back.
Maybe it's the second day of jet lag, but I just woke up.
I just feel, you know what I mean?
Who cares how I feel?
You got your own problems, right?
This is from the pod save music network.
And Jersey Todd, I learned me to the fact that it was up.
Of course, nothing special there.
This is job as the official musicologist of the Charlie.
Nina Simone, turn me on.
The Tony Humphrey's vocal mix, Nina Simone, of course,
superstar in a row and right.
Gosh, what is the song that's it's commercial now here in the UK?
My baby, isn't it?
Nah, I'll have to look on the Napster find that for you.
Hey, it's a daily source code episode number 485 coming to you from a curry cottage
in the affluent suburb of Serino as Gilford and United Kingdom huge
Outage last night here at the Gilford Exchange.
Of course, that always comes when I'm doing a video conference with the
Office.
We had a really interesting day yesterday.
We had our first management off site, which means court yard
Mary out down the street, but it's off site, right.
And it was just amazing to see all the people who are helping us build this company.
And in fact, I thought it was a pretty interesting TV show because I was literally
sitting here with my with my power book.
I have to say we used I chat for the occasion much more stable than
Skype video.
So you know, basically use two power books and that works very, very well.
Using a speaker phone for the actual voice communication just a lot
clear.
And it was fun to to sit and watch everybody.
And everyone, we started off by everyone telling about their background.
And some of them, you know, and myself included started from you.
I was born in Washington, D.C.
And then what they had done and how they derived to where they were today at
the show.
And it was, it was a fascinating, it was, I think that's a TV show.
It's a format right there.
It's called the, the away show.
There you go.
The management away show.
I would love to see senior executives of many, many companies going on the tip.
Don't you have to talk about the business of the company.
I'd love to hear the backgrounds of the people who were involved because it really shows
the DNA of a company and helps you understand what that company is capable of because
it's that DNA that makes things happen.
It was fun.
That started at three in the afternoon, UK time and then around six boom.
No more internet.
And it was like, you know, I could trace route into the exchange.
And so I knew it wasn't a problem with the, with the line,
between the cottage and the exchange, which as you know,
is a dedicated line, took new months to get.
And it didn't come back on until around 10, 15, 10, 30.
And then we continued until about 115.
My time.
So that's you.
Maybe that is something to do with why I feel like shit possible.
Here's something you won't believe.
I think, why know you've heard this.
You know, Jeff Smith, thegefsmith.com is the guy who's doing just tons and tons of great
jingles and imaging and sound stuff for, for many, many independent producers across the podcast landscape.
And our buddy Slow thought it would be a nice idea to make a jingle for him.
Because, you know, it's, when you're the guy that makes all the jingles,
it's nice if someone does something for you.
So let's just revisit the sound of that jingle that Slow made for Jeff Smith.
So I went wild about that and I love that old time, hokey, classic stuff.
And I even said I said the Slow is it dude.
I would love to have those girls sing.
And from me turns out it's, it's all Slow.
That's him. I don't know how he did it. I'm sure there's some digital trickery involved and then yesterday
And this is this is nuts, man. This is I love this. This is this is so much what we're all about
Jeff Smith created. Thank you for slow. Oh, yeah
I like to mingle with a very best
Now, maybe I'm losing
I'm singing along
Thank you so much
I'm playing that song
Thank you. It's loud. Oh, making this sound
Thank you. It's loud. I'm singing along
Thank you. It's loud. It really was this
Thank you so
It's like a jingle off
It's the war of the jingle makers
But all in brotherly love fantastic now go make some shit for me like that got damn it. I love that
Again back into the fray of what's going on in Europe and we've talked about this
So I've talked about this before that the United Kingdom was planning on putting restrictions on immigrants coming into the UK from Bulgaria and Romania
And the reason for this is because when when the EU dropped all the borders
So called all the borders and really
Trying to make it like the United States of Europe which means you know you can move from Jersey to New York or from New York to
West Virginia
You can cross the borders. You can cross state lines and you can work there
You can immigrate into those states and the fact they call them European member states
There were such an influx of immigrants including myself my my dad from other European countries
That the UK which is an island and can only how's so many motherfuckers
Got a little worried. You know, they got like a million people waiting in lines and hey, we're here
We want permanent residency. I'm I'm number 998,274
And
Looks like they're gonna do it looks like the UK is going to put certain restrictions on
European
Residents who want to immigrate into the United Kingdom if they're from Romania and Bulgaria
Well, you know there's one guy out there who's got something to say about
Comic strip
Comic strip our resident EU correspondent come to strip blubber blubber
I was supposed to be really slick. Our resident European correspondent comics strip blogger checks in ways in on the situation
Wow
Hi Adam carry
It is Halloween time
So here's a scary story from me
Last week UK decided to block free movement of vampires
Who are joining European Union next year in me it means the Chancellor vanja, which is a home country of vampires
It's in Romania in Romania and Romania joins European Union January next year
So if you are British, I mean not you but you know, you should check your neck whether a vampire
beaten you out of vengeance
Vengeance and then data for blocking
Fimo movement of vampires within European Union anyways as far as I'm concerned. I will only welcome vampires
I mean people of Romania and my historic brothers from Bulgaria into European Union
I'm not scared of vampires, but you braids you should because your government not only is a puddle of Joji W
But your government last week just pissed off vampires
And what is your Halloween costume Adam carry?
What is your what are you wearing?
Mine is monkey as always
I don't participate in Halloween. I find it unhumorous
Our whole family doesn't find very humorous because my wife is a witch
You know a white one, but she's a witch so do we don't mess around with us shit, you know?
Yeah, there you go. So this morning I read in the newspaper that
Romania and Bulgaria are now saying well, that's good. Okay, we'll reciprocate all of your fuckers who are over here
We're gonna block them out and put restrictions on their freedom of movement. It's just so wonderful isn't it
I
Do understand from the UK perspective though. I really do understand
I think the the unfortunate thing here is that they're putting restrictions on certain member states and not all member states
I did make a mistake. I said that yesterday I said that the
That the US was not a colony of the UK well of of course it was initially but only briefly and then we kicked your sorry asses out
And you know what I was talking about
Let's see what else I've got here. Oh, that's if the different james coming in
Oh, Franco is that Franco?
Looks like he sent this. Yeah Franco from broadcast the tallya says Adam as of now a tallyan artist registered with the S i a e which is the
Italian version of Ascat BMI can go pod safe without worry new S i a e rules permit
to exclude online uses from the contract
That's fantastic
That is very very cool
So just like in the US even if you have
An agreement with Ascat or BMI
It's up to you to provide a special license which is exactly what join the pod safe music network is
Special license
So that other people can use it under the terms of that special license which would be the pod safe music network agreement
Yeah, it's great news Franco. Thank you
Jomical Auckland says dude Splendid.co.uk and I found it in Sainsbury's online store
I think the problem is I'm looking for the flavor blends. I have not seen those over here
Yes, Splendid is apparently available but I don't think they have the French vanilla the mocha and what's the other hazelnut
And he suggests looking at the baking aisle
brand new to
To the pod show network. This is cool kick kick to sneak in with that is kick to sneak is
Dude, he he put the high in the high fee movement
He's now on the on pod show plus
Keep the sneak dot pod show dot com. He's got a great video
Preview of his DVD which is coming out these guys rule the San Francisco Bay area you got to check it out
I'll put a link in the show notes, of course
Hey the new
MacBooks came out yesterday
Aren't you sick of it now don't you see how I'm so happy I didn't buy
You know the first MacBook first of all. I of course would have been one of the apparently 10% of people who have this random
You know shutdown syndrome
Overheating frying your nuts crap not working stuff blowing up
All the hardware issues that the and this is why I why change to windows not because of I love OS X
I love OS 10. I love the Mac interface. I love the way it displays
I really love everything about it, but the hardware is just freaking me out and then this is what the third generation out of the MacBooks you know
There's no upgrade paths. You said to keep buying a new one and you and you get so frustrated because the one that you just bought sucks
So bad that fucking breaks all the time
Remember that that sound problem that's stuttering sound that really that's really what got it all going for me
So anyway, I'm thinking maybe you know if Apple would would just
Release one and say hey, this is it, you know, this is the state of the art and
And it's out there for half a year and it actually works and you know, and I'd love to know if there's another faster one coming out
I mean you don't you can't release three a year it makes me feel like a dick
Do one a year I'll upgrade once a year if the shit works and don't do this interim new product releases it makes me so mad
Like I should have known like I wasn't in on the in the it would the in crowd
Let's see oh
Remember Giselle who called in from I think it was San Diego
And she really got me going by saying that we had a connection and she really love hearing me in our ear
And
It was a very
sexually oriented message that she sent me I've got my doubts now about this
I think I'm being set up listen to Giselle who checks in again with us. Hi Adam. It's Giselle
So I was out of town until yesterday
But this morning I'm out jogging out by Pacific Beach listening to my iPod and Friday's DSC comes on and I got so excited by the sound of your voice
But it literally made my knees weak and then I heard you play my message and here I was jogging down by the ocean
Yeah, so far so good, right, but it's it starts. I don't know you tell me, but well, I'll I'll I'll ask you the question after you've heard her whole
Her whole voice message freaking out
And I wanted to grab strangers off the street and jam my earbuds into their ears so they could hear it
And then you started talking about touching yourself
And I literally got so worked up that I couldn't even think straight
I started thinking about you touching yourself and then started thinking about you touching me
I'm thinking about it right now and
I went into a Starbucks right off mission boulevard and I went into the bathroom and I re-round the show and got myself off
Spray there in the bathroom
Biting my lips a whole time for that nobody would hear me
Yes, I'm a freak, but I'm starting the things that I really want you badly
And yes, I would absolutely do a three-way with you in Patricia any time
Maybe I'd even let the two of you time me up and do stuff to me
Maybe I'm getting ahead of myself
I gotta go, but when I get home, I'm gonna get into a nice hot bath
Listen to your show from today. I can't wait for a little bit
Catch your later sexy
Now listen to that last bit. Okay. That sounded like she was reading from a script. Listen any time
Maybe I'd even let the two of you time me up and do stuff to me
But maybe I'm getting ahead of myself. Get this. I got to go. But when I get home
I'm getting in a nice hot bath. I don't know show from today. I can't wait for a little date
See now I'm a little disappointed. You're sexy
Catch your later baby. I don't know now. I'm a little disappointed now because I think someone's having a run at me
This doesn't sound real anymore
Still kind of turns me on though
I'm a fucking freak
Greetings Adam and all daily source code listeners. This is bicycle mark citizen reporter of the
Internets
That's right. I'm one of the many reporters that look at the world around us that report on issues in ways that the
mainstream simply won't using the wonderful technology of podcasting and video blogging
I just wanted to put a call out there for all citizen journalists if you're doing a program
I'm interested in hearing about it and if you're interested in citizen journalism then perhaps
Come over to my work at bicyclemark dot org that's bicyclemark with a k dot org
This week I'm doing a special tribute to Paul Wellstone remembering the man
What made him special and how much the world needs him nowadays and what would he say if he saw what was going on now
For the more I'm doing a series on global mayors mayors who are out of the ordinary for their profile or for their
Policies or making big change in their cities in ways that the national government never could
So for all the citizen reporters and the people concerned about the world around them hope to hear from you Adam take care
and I use a bidet
Just a bidet
Just a bidet man, just a bidet
bicyclemark citizen journalists no less and not a big fan of that
Of calling someone a citizen journalist or a group of people a citizen journalist
I think it's I think it's a waste it's a waste of
Great resources the bicycle mark has a fantastic audience
As does here's one for a Richard blue sting another person who I think would call himself a citizen journalist not coincidentally
They're also good friends
Richard blue sting who is currently
Apparently temporarily sitting in from edge wine steen on yeast radio
Is going to release an interview actually I call it a conversation because I already heard it a conversation with Cindy she had
Of course the mother who lost her her son in Iraq and that stage of protest against that again
The war and against the administration specifically against the George Bush
And it was a it was a fun conversation to listen to I think he's going to release it on the next Monday on the 30th of October
I wouldn't go as far as to call it an interview because it was just like you know Richard and Cindy talking and
You know there was no controversial questions. He was just kind of pulling stuff out of her
It was nice to listen to because
It was the first time that I've actually heard Cindy she and talk
You know as herself in a relaxed atmosphere, you know, just a good conversation and so that was interesting
And I'm not going to comment on it until you've had the opportunity to listen to it as well
I'm also not sure if Richard's going to edit it or
Plenty pieces out. I don't think he will
So I'll I'll I'll I'll hold back on on that conversation but the whole idea of citizen journalism
You know, it's like we're we're educating an entire
Generation of people who know how to sound off, you know sound off
Be media talk like media and I'm not talking about like traditional media, but you know
Just exposing it's all about the exposure it's all about the communication of the issues
But they're very few people who are using all this technology and
These these vast audiences that we have and these social media networks that we're creating
To actually go and do something, you know, I would much rather see someone say
Hey, I'm running for office and I'm going to
My platform that I'll use will be the new media platform because let's be honest if you want to be president
I guarantee you even I can become president if you give me $500 million
Because I'll take that $500 million. It actually costs about
300 million in the last election. So that's why I'm going to give me a little little margin there
I can be $500 to advertise because that's how we choose presidents. It's how we choose this so powder that we buy in the supermarket
It's how we choose which gas to buy it's
It's how we choose what other crap to watch
It's how we choose presidents marketing works television advertising works. I personally believe that
Independent independently produced media and the way we're distributing it is much much larger
much more engaging and I'd love to see
Was Barack Obama interesting guy. You know, I saw him for about an hour and a half on Larry King
And I think he's got the charisma. That's really what we need. We want an actor in the White House, you know
Someone who has is reasonable and can act that that's what we as Americans wanted the world wants that really you want a strong
Dedicated leader. It's all that that's what a lot of leadership is about is how you position yourself and and how you lead by
Example and he'll make mistakes if if he ever gets in the office everyone will fuck up
But that's okay, you know, just say yeah, I fucked up
That's the easiest way to deal with it and we're going to do better next time
But why isn't he
You know using this new platform is because he knows that he's not ready his organization is not ready
It's just going to be a traditional campaign. I have to say on all this. I'm really with Dave Winner on
How we should be using this. I'm just not interested in people exposing how horrible government is and
The atrocities of everything in the world and how unsafe it is. I want people to go do something and here's something that I've always held to
A country gets the government that she deserves
Really does what we have now in in the White House is what the United States deserves it really is in the UK
You've got Tony Blair you don't like it you deserve him
You know, you everyone has the individual power to go and change that. I'm personally not all that unhappy
And the main reason is because I know that it's only going to be two more years, you know
And then there will have to be a change one way the other that's going to be a different president. That's for sure
I would actually call to arms and go to arms if there was
If somehow and I've I have heard this pop up before that all you
Bush administration's gonna try and prolong the the term limits
I tell that's gonna happen, but yeah, I'd actually grab a gun if that happened
But if you want to change the world if you're so unhappy then you know jump on the platform
Use this stuff and run for office run against whoever's running
That's that's how you do it that is the only way we're we're teaching people we're teaching our kids
How to communicate about how unhappy they are. I think we're kind of forgetting to teach some how to run
For something how to run and compete and debate
At any rate it's going to get a lot better
Mainstream media at least that is because it is finally dying out the final
Signal is here my friends. What is that final signal you ask well
I've said before that when any industry is about is just about on its last legs
There's a technical term for what happens. It's called consolidation and
Essentially all the small companies roll up into one big one
You see this with oil
You see this with the the record business
Only a few huge companies at this point conglomerates made up of many many many smaller companies
And then there's only one step after that and that is what's happening to clear channel communications clear channel
Of course owns 1200 radio stations owns many outdoor venues
Really owns a large chunk of the US media landscape
They are now in talks with KKR. That's right the famous guys if you're read the book or seen the HPO movie
Barbarians at the gate about
RJR Reynolds in the bisco
Then you know that these guys are in they'll take
The company private which means they're going to buy the company from the shareholders
So we'll no longer be publicly listed and then they're going to split the fucker up thousands of people will lose their jobs
They're going to split these divisions sell them off to individuals or individual
Other companies who feel that they have a need for a piece here a piece there and
This is it they're going to destroy it. They're going to break it all down. They're doing it for themselves
They make huge amounts of money
On the on this type of process particularly the people who are running the company make huge amounts of money
And of course with the loss of all of these jobs people getting nervous
They start looking for jobs elsewhere and I think they're going to find that there are many alternatives
I would welcome many radio professionals to join the pod show network
You know we pay for for people who want to work no problem come on over sending email happy to have you
So it's just another you know a little little little mark on the wall there as we see mainstream media
Crumbling before our very eyes again the question is what are we going to do with it when we have all that power?
All right, so I'm in mistaken Michigan right now. I'm a skig in Michigan isn't exactly a great town
Quite frankly it's a shithole. I can't fucking stand it
I mean there's nothing to do here. There's nothing but bowling and drinking and drinking and bowling
And I don't drink anymore because I'm an ex-alkaholic and I'm not going to go bowling without drinking because it's bowling without drink
Just fucking stupid
All right, so I'm walking home and I'm trying to cross a street. It's a one way four-lane highway
It's really not that busy. You know what I'm saying
If it had maybe like five cars on it, I'd be impressed
So I look I see the cars are stopped at a light down the street and across in a little street. No big deal, right?
Well, I'll behold them on the other side of the street and a cop flashes me over
You know you really shouldn't cross in the middle of the street kid
Hey, I'm from New York City. I got the street court crossing think hovered
Well, it's really not safe to cross in the middle of the street. You should use the crosswalks
Listen, I'm from New York buddy. I've crossed eight lanes of rush hour traffic
I've had yellow cabs almost hit me because they're too anxious to get a jump on a green light
I've had more on jump red lights while I'm in the middle of the street and I've weaved in and out of midtown rush hour traffic to get to work on time
I know how to cross streets buddy
They smile that me gave me a $75 ticket for disturbing the peace and then told me have a nice day
Now that's fucked up
Oh, and Adam your New York phrase it a week. Yeah, watch it more on I'm walking here
Watchin more on I'm podcasting here. Thanks buddy
Uh
See two things I had written down. Oh, yeah a lot of people sending me this email about jet blue
Experimenting on it and in fact the email is actually coming in experimenting on passengers
Well, they weren't experimenting on passengers apparently jet blue tried out an experiment and we're monitoring
Their air crew to see if there was any decrease in performance
Flying 10 hours instead of the current maximum, which I have not been able to confirm that that's the maximum
But the current maximum apparently of eight hours of flying
And so of course people are outraged that this was being tested well passengers were in the plane
I don't think I have enough information to comment on it right now because it's just a lot of he shed
He said she said here say there, you know a low level FAA official granted the the test
They had the third pilots in the cockpit and you all this stuff
And of course there's lots of agendas in here
Primarily the pilot's union
Who may not want to have
Their pilots flying longer this you know be very careful with spouting off about this one thing
I'm pretty sure of you were in no danger if you're on jet blue and I'd get on any jet blue flight at any point
Because I just don't believe that you know, I just can't believe all this noise you know I saw this with the cori-lightle
Reporting how completely incorrect it was so I'm just not gonna jump on board here and say
Yeah, yeah, jet blue did a bad thing. I'll keep my eye on it, but it's just oh
We're so quick to judge hey one cool piece of software I wanted to tell you about this TV unit works. Have you heard of this yet?
It says some I think these guys are in somewhere in in Asia East Asia
Maybe it's China. No, not China. I can't remember who it was well all of course I'll put a link up TV unit works
And this application which as far as I can tell is windows only
You started up and it's it's appear to appear streaming video application and
Essentially you can watch American television
It's very cool because it's got ABC and BC CBS it's got ESPN it's got comedy central
It's got a whole bunch of basic you know channels basic television channels
Unfortunately most of them are the San Francisco feeds so
Really with the eight-hour time difference it makes no sense for me to try and watch anything in prime time
But just the whole idea that I can flip it on here and I'm seeing a San Francisco signal literally
I'm seeing the San Francisco local affiliate of each of these stations
It's fantastic. I'm sure there's a huge lawsuit waiting to happen here
although I don't know if I were ABC and BC or CBS I'd be fucking delighted
You know you're you're it's not like the commercials aren't being aired with it the commercials are being aired with it
It's free extra distribution you're marketing to me and I'm loving it
Something you may want to try out though because it's cool and and they will also let you broadcast using their infrastructure as well so
Keep a close eye on that
Lakuna coil that's the last song I'm gonna play for you today. I didn't even know this but
Lakuna coil who has appeared on cover rolling stone magazine and
Let me just see if I can find I'm in the pod save music network right now. Let me just click through here
Here we go look on a coil. Let me see what the bio says
Look on a coil exhibits a miraculous eloquence in their collusion of melody and metal
They also maturely exhibit and chanting Gothic overtones and point melancholy to build their ethereal ethereal ethereal
ethereal musical landscape. Oh, I really butcher that
So this track has been released before the official album
Fucking A you better believe it because they've seen the light this is Lakuna coil
And closer
It's actually called the radio edit go figure
What it comes are
Yeah
Falling in the far, then something real
Tell we're in the city, the streets, but I'll go to
Won't you get close, I'm in to you
No, no, I'll do it so then
There is just nothing to get changed
So I'll face you, you last rich, you scorn
No, we need to get lost
I'll get far, far, far, far
Which is to find a son ofków, you scream
T Sound on my flame
Sogue wundernia
I have a gun
Let alone in the redgads
Let's stop
Break it to the dry
Let alone
Shake your brush
Blow it down
And then the flames
Will create the redgans
Be theㅋㅋ
I love you, I love you, I love you
I love you, I love you
I love you
Closer, La Cuna Coil, now on the podcast
I'm using that word before, you can hear it
Or buy it anywhere else
Cool
I like that little outro there
I don't forget to give me a call
201-625-6357
Put a plus one in front of it
If you're entering it into your mobile phone
Look forward to hearing from you
Hopefully it'd be feeling a little bit better tomorrow
We'll do it all over again
DailySourceco.com
Adam at podshow.com
Oh, and I just want to remind you
If you're looking for a really really good deal
on a domain name, go over to go
打.com and use the checkout code
DSC3. Take care everybody
I'll talk to you tomorrow bye
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
Get this podcast
And more great ones like it on the high performance podcast
Delivery network from podshow
And line-white networks
I love it