Never regret. If it's good, it's wonderful. If it's bad, it's experience. Victoria
Hold $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Delta Shira Charley, 3-1-0. We're closing down the weekend everybody.
It's party time.
We're closing down the weekend everybody.
I've got a boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom
boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom,
I didn't mess up, messed up, broken it up too, I didn't know
I was pretty tough to admit it to you, when I'm wrong with you
Hey, hey, hey, hey, I'm still wrong with you
Maybe, there ain't nothing other move, I'll show up on the floor
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah. yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, how you had your也 now, oh, yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah like yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah yeah. Yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Music of people creating music and we got some great really well-played tracks and the sound is decent
You know, and messed around actually I gave it the AKG microphone to plug it instead of the one that came with it
And so I was kind of planning on doing a sound seeing tour
We're not for two things first. So I've always been way too much time fooling around second of all
I only have two nine-volt batteries and I need in order to do the sound seeing tour
I need two of them for the wireless transmitter and receiver and one of those nine volts was now in the
AKG microphone because it needs to fan some power now that you give a shit, but I you know
Anyway, it's soon to come and of course that will be completely non-pod safe
Let's see we got some interesting bits of feedback today
I good buddy
Roger Smalls going to show up again with an audio comment that he sent in and
I think we'll squeeze in a bit of a metro sexual moment
Joe McLaughlin
sent me a link to an article about billboard magazine
I have to be honest that I didn't really read the whole article, but his comment caught my eye and a new I could comment on it no matter what he says
I bet
Pods sake music network and podcasting itself was sold more music than Starbucks last I checked the only reason I went there was to use the Wi-Fi to download podcasts and get a cup of chino
Well, it's a widely known fact in the music business that Starbucks puts the music business to
Shame when it comes to selling CDs. They move an incredible amount of product and you know what they're doing basically is
They're putting together compilation CDs stuff that really you know if they know their audience and it is really moving an amazing amount of product
Which just goes to show you know if if a coffee chain and as you put it a Wi-Fi chain and coffee chain
Can do a better job at selling music than the record companies? Well, there you go
And see the one day have any updates on the positive music network actually we're looking for another developer
For the with some specific skills
For the positive music network. So if if you're so inclined and you live in the Bay Area
Give me a shout because we're we're looking for someone to do some work with us on the APIs for the purchasing system
That we're putting into place
So all of that is coming up and we got lots of talk about
I'm gonna switch two things here. I was gonna do
Something about viral marketing. I want them to do is I'm gonna switch it around. I want you to hear this comment from Roger Smalls
Because he's he's not going through my trash anymore. I think he got the message there, but
Well listen in for side
Hello, I'm Roger here. I had on the telly sauce coat. There was a problem with any of the companies
You recommended then you'll listen as she let you know
Now as you mentioned that you visit Guildford's branch should the same species market
So I've started shopping there. They solely on your recommendation and this day it's very good quality food and so
It and I didn't pop by there since I'm seeing now don't actually find anything because you said you like it in there so much
But I do have a minor complaints. I'd like to draw your attention. So I've noticed that the carry-backs break very easily when you put a lot of groceries in them
Maybe you could pop down there
That's what words with magic. I'm sure now that you are straight away
That's I could give out to carry-backs for heavy items. You know, I just just read the love a little bit. I'm not sure
Oh, and then what I'm calling I thought I'd mention your idea of getting a tattoo
I don't think you realize the body parts do tens change shape of the years
I worked with this woman who has a suit just above
She started off with a lovely tattoo of her me, but hovering over a cuff where it ended up looking like a totally trash in a fishing net because of all the ways that she
For some maybe just gave some more saying tattoos on you with the
Because that is not not a tissue of Christina
And maybe just a lucky listener could get their name mentioned on your body
Anyway, how do you know you're at them?
Okay Roger how about if I get Roger tattooed will that make you happy?
He's right actually the
The bags that they give you it's saying's bury here in guilt for to carry your groceries home and you really need to double bag of me because they're really not so that's strong
Which kind of freak it's kind of weirding me out a little bit because I've actually been
People have approached me in saying's bury a more than one occasion said hey excuse me
Are you Adam Curry
Because you know they'll see me with the leather jacket with the with the with the hair waving around from side to side
And
You know they see me hammering out shit on my blackberry they see Patricia so they put it all together kind of and I
Wonder if Roger was one of those people who introduced themselves to me at saying's worries
Anyway, happy new year to your Roger. It's a pleasure to have you
Listen to the show as always
One more day for this week and then as you know Sunday, I'm off to San Francisco and then we're going to really be heads down
We may even go to Atlanta a week later
So what would that be? I'll be some around the 16th I think
To go to talk to a company there now. What's in Atlanta you say?
Hey Adam Bob from the Bob show
I keep me need to record that thing but I never do
Part of the problem is that I listen to you doing what you do and go. Yeah, that's what I'd like to do and fuck he's doing it better
And I can so I just listen to you and keep thinking about making my own
Wanted to weigh in if I could unto the topics that have been coming up on a regular basis all right on the
DSE and that's the future of advertising in the sense sale. Yeah, I got to tell you Adam the future of advertising is this
Yeah, this me talking to you right now
You're getting feedback from actual users we can try to reformat the 30 second spot
But you know they've been doing that for a long time. I mean back in the days of red skeleton they had 30 second spots
The difference is we're not trying to put a jingle or a comedic piece together and fit it into a little piece of time
With an a larger piece of time in which we try to sell someone to some a shite
We felt through that shit out man when we've trained ourselves we know we've got so much time spot comes on we start thinking about
What's for dinner or not what you're trying to sell me because I know you're trying to sell it to me. It's like that's really funny
You say that I just want to jump in for one second
John Bon Jovi once told me that when they were the top of their game in
And I guess it was the early 90s late 80s early nine days
He'd actually be on stage playing singing and thinking about a meeting with his accountant
You know about his car about his playing that it was really not pleasurable
Okay, let's continue. It's like when you see the guy walking up your driveway
Get ready to knock on your door with the big old pharbess the big briefcase in his hand
You know he's gonna sell you something so you pretend like you're not home or you're nicely sent him on his way
That's what we mentally do with advertising
Now segue to send sail
Here's a product that you like and you talk about on a regular basis
Dude
My wife wants an eye dog. She's gonna get one. I have an MM50
Or whatever they're calling that now based on your recommendation and I got a send sail now
I got one minute. I wasn't gonna get one. I went to give value
They've got a pod based coffee maker and I ordered it because if I order their coffee on a regular basis
They give it to me for free
But I kept hearing you talk about yours and it sounded different
So when you were angry at them even an anger atom you sell since they are or their products anyway
You were pissed off because they were giving away send sales
So of course I had to go get me a free send say I took a picture it took me about 10 minutes of my old coffee pots
Send it to him. They sent me a nice red to send sail machine didn't know it came in that color, but it looks
Pretty good and I put in my medium roast. Do we eggbirds coffee and damn? That's good stuff in it
Love the foam it comes out just right. I don't waste coffee like I used to make it a whole pot when I'm the only one who drinks it
And it's good coffee now recently
In answer to something someone said on your show about
Send sail or whoever owns them being an evil conglomerate
No, they're they're not an evil conglomerate. They're a business not a charity
So they want to make money so by the pods if you like the coffee and if you don't want to buy their coffee
See this how I couldn't find any reason. Yeah, what on Amazon did a search for send sale?
I was looking for some coffee pots because I couldn't find them locally and
You know, they have when I ordered them, but they also had this thing that was called an
Environmental friendly refillable pod now. I don't know what the
Environmental friendly thing is it's plastic, man, but if you get it you can put whatever you want in there
So that means you could go down to your favorite specialty shop buy
By sir making blue mountains right at yourself put it in there and I bet you that'd be pretty good and the things are like nine dollars
So if you're out to save money or bust up the monopoly. I guess that'd be a way to do it
Well, I think that's exactly what's happening. We're and and a lot of these advertisers that we're talking to
We're working on doing campaigns like this the eye dog was actually where we kind of stumbled upon it when
You know the the concept of having user generated
Advertisements makes a lot of sense to me particularly if if I'm
Promoting a product talking about a product we're having a essentially we're having a conversation about a product when you send
Audio feedback back back my way if you if you like it if you purchase it if you don't even
I mean that of course is the is the tricky part is to put the good in the bad in there
Which you've actually done on now on more than one occasion with with with sponsors on this show
What I like though the thing that I like hearing the most is no one has said I hate advertisements
People said I don't like advertisements this particular way that's really exciting to me
And maybe if you purchase the product maybe you shouldn't hear the advertisement. I don't know
That's a so much stuff to work on there really is but we're getting somewhere and you know luckily we have
People on the other side of the equation who were willing to work with us and come up with some of some of these interesting
Concepts I had another
Great brain wave the other day and I think that what you're going to see is as we start
Campaigning to bring in more listeners right now. We're getting everything set up for the podcast
But simultaneously we're getting it set up for listeners because
Listeners are podcasts are some vice versa
The concept of a registered listener. I think is going to be very important
So that's not just a subscriber someone who actually gets the show through your
RSS feed but a registered listener who you can reach out to and they can reach out back to you through multiple forms of media
I think that's where we're going to see a lot of excitement
You know, hey, maybe if I said hey if you're registered listener
To the daily source code, which means we have some way of communicating with each other and I'm not talking just about email
That would be pretty fucking lame
But maybe you'd like to have a a Gillette M3 power sent to your home to to try it out
Wouldn't that be interesting that they listen companies do that all the time?
So that has stuff to think about so much stuff to do. I can't wait to get the San Francisco one one stuff is up and running and rolling
That's when you can really start to play you know then it's like you can think up
And I know I can think of 15 new
Features and cool things that we'll make the whole experience better. I can do it a day. It's oh
Yes, very excited here in the country
I need that I'm hi Johnny it's Steve Williams a podcaster from the 21st century
I just wanted to give you the skinny on Cindy Snops tell a pod my weekly podcast every week
I tell a pod through the time space continuum and discover motion pictures that have somehow slipped outside the cinematic mainstream
Cycle beach party the big empty million dollar hotel the monkeys mask and welcome to woop look
You know the really great but overlooked films that the white poloi weren't exposed to now
I'm waiting I'm glad Johnny as I said Cindy Snops tell a pod is a weekly podcast that can be found as
Cindysnop.com that's c-i-n-e-s-n-o-b dot com and if you happen to run into bogey or Anne Sheridan
Would you please let them know too?
Thank you Johnny
And welcome to the Mac of Zerers Mac eat get it's day and John hi up in the macum server towers
I had no idea to success it yeah be aware of it while it's a very cool feature they have yes
And I've come across it when I've been looking at fast backwards. No, I wouldn't recommend anyone try to beat it
I'm not gonna try and beat it. We got some feedback
My name you show the great idea actually I learn if you have any stories you'd like to share with us
Not even gonna go mad. It's got mad skills, baby, and don't forget folks next week is macro
John and I'll be podcasting live from the show floor on Tuesday afternoon talking about the keynote and what we saw there
And then we'll be podcasting from the hotel in a couple times after that and hey Adam if you want tickets to our rock and
Cirque du Mac party with the Mac world all star band on Wednesday night hunt me down and let me know
Does it make you get dot com
That's right man's big big good who'd manny going on in San Francisco
Which I'm just gonna catch the tail end of
um and of course
Monday the ninth Howard Stern starts on on serious. I'm gonna be in San Francisco and I'll be able to get up nice and early
And I've got my serious satellite receiver. It's gonna be very exciting
Let's pose and buddy mind we email back and forth and keep each other up to date on stuff sent me
a very interesting link if if you want to get involved in podcasting and and I think I actually see a whole business here for this stuff
Certainly if it catches on
Ain't you know you don't necessarily want to create a podcast me want to contribute and and unfortunately
You have to have a Macintosh and at this moment in time
He sent me a link to something called iStarcomposer at uh scriptsoftware.com
I'll just read from the synopsis. iStarcomposer creates synchronized lyrics on the Mac to export to the iPod and iTunes
iStarcomposer finds lyrics but more importantly allows you to sink them to a song and then allows you to
Export the synchronized lyrics into new music file, which is AAC that will play and display and iTunes and on the iPod
Okay, so there's another feature though. It'll actually allow you to put time code based show notes
Into the file now it's gonna output an AAC file so it will only work in
Programs that recognize that so quick time of course and iTunes
But here's here's a suggestion I could make you know
And most people don't catch this show on the day that it's actually created it's probably a day later
Lots of people play catch up so I don't think and I really don't think the day matters that much, you know
That's the whole point doesn't matter when I make this show it's just the next show it's the most recent one
Don't listen to the show if you ever want to know if they find a sound of been laden, okay wrong show to listen to wrong medium
But wouldn't it be cool if the day after a show when the the show notes the wiki show notes have been completely populated
If someone then and here's where the opportunity lies of course if someone would take those show notes and synchronize them using this tool
synchronize them into
Into the file into a new AAC file, which of course we could make completely
Subscriber bulls so you'd be able to
Subscribe to the the extra bonus show note file and
I mean I would have some benefit I guess would be kind of cool
It would be enhanced as well
So when you hit a spot in the
In the show where it talks about or perhaps when I play a song, you know, then there will be a picture there of some album art
Of course you can't really link anywhere, which makes it a little bit unfortunate
But it could be cool you could even put the listener comments in there
So
Just a thought just a thought it's a way that that you could get into doing something interesting with podcasting
I know I certainly don't have the time for that to be sure
Uh
Oh my goodness, so we have like three minutes left on the on the satellite window
Which is not gonna be enough we might as well get it started
That's right
This is the spot where we all gather around his guys and talk about
Gurly type stuff Steve Harris says hey Adam talking about moisturizer and smaller containers being better
Here's a good one I've been using since summer nivia for men intensive moisture cream
Yeah, I've used that one myself actually comes in a tiny pot
So you don't need to use much and because it's for men
You don't smell like a girl or feel silly at the checkout that lots of moisturizers out there for guys these days
It would be good to know what others are using happy new year Steve from reinvented software
I really feel proud doing this, you know, I just point it now that I feel
Something really good where we're up to here
Let's see
Hey Adam says mark bars another listener to me that you don't use an electric razor
You're the gadget man. Well, I always use my fill of shave and it works fine, but honestly
I think manually shaving will be smoother, but then I'm lazy and always
Inner hurry
Nivia started a couple years ago here to again with their four men product line and tried some of the product my favorite one is
The Q10 cream. I'll see you use the off-brands they work as well
They make my face feel nice and soft all day it's supposed to give your skin energy when you missed a couple hours of sleep
But I use a daily and it feels a lot better compared to the other moisturizers. I've tried
I combine that with a weekly facial mask. Oh, we haven't even gotten the facial mask
I tried the four men facial masks
You know mark your Shimodo nemcoff of the Pacific Coast hell. I always wanted to give me a facial mask and
Just so glad we haven't shared that yet
Anyway, Mark doesn't think they're all that good. So yes, I go into my girlfriend stuff and use a cheap off-brand facial mask
It really makes my skin look softer and nicer just want to share this Metro sexual experience
This is fantastic. See I have one more here Kevin Flanagan nevermind the Metro sexual bid
I haven't used a razor, but a few times since 1980 and that really makes the blades last
I used one two times in the first half of the eighties each time I decided to grow the beard back
The very next day. I used a razor one time in the 90s to trim my neck from my wedding day. That's it
I never cut myself shaving never give dollars to Gillette Wilkinson or whomever. I think it's better than shaving besides I'm lazy
And I will tell you from my own Metro sexual momentary experiential
Testing I think I've gotten the hang of the M3 power razor. This is the the vibrating razor from Gillette
Have not gotten to replacement blade. Yes, so I don't know if if the blades which are different on the outside
If that's gonna make any difference when I use those, but I've learned that really have to take slower strokes to make it work
And I had it today. My first shave that I really enjoyed and if you'd like to know more about the Metro sexual moment
And you're listening to serious stars one or three tune in tomorrow. We got to say goodbye to you for now
All right, we can just continue here. There was actually an audio comment that came in for the Metro sexual moment
And you know, I'm always looking for more audio comments. So I'm gonna open it up here. Here we go
I think
Oh, man, what is this? It's like
Volume and zero. I totally suck so I can boost this up a bit
Audio settings go volume up to full
Can't believe that
Audio's okay. I'll pull this one all the way down
Okay, I can't make that one much softer. Let's see if we can get it now
Come on
High-given sort of podcast and they just wanted to
Step in and talk a little bit about your Metro sexual
segment that you do on your on the daily source code
I do shave part of my face. I should say my neck
I do wear full beard
I also shave my head and for both of these I use each of that mock three turbo
Is the best item that I've found for this
I don't use your traditional
Laddering shaving creams
For the most part I use stuff that I got off of headplay dot com
This is a site that is for men who shave their heads
It is
They have a shaving device it works wonderful
I do believe they need to update their blade system null. They need to at least get a three blade system and
Right now they'll have a two blade system
But they do have some shaving cream and a moisturizer that I use and I think it is in
Redouble one and I plan on
Continuing to use it and I continue to tell people that shave their heads all about them
Very good site and very good product and
I think everybody ought to check it out
But then once again, this is
AJ from the high-given sort of podcast
Have a good day
Yo AJ fantastic man. Thank you very much. Let me just read just the levels here
Okay, there we go. That's better
Yeah, I didn't even thought about that. Of course, there's lots of guys who feed into our metro sexual category who shave their heads
Damn
Okay, well, I can't really participate in the in the whole discussion, but I'm more than happy to
To facilitate it. Okay last one for the metro sexual moment for today
This is from
The hell is this from
our careless
Doesn't say who is from three things I'd like to fill in
I'm a mechanical engineer specializing materials in manufacturing also pursuing side interest in chemistry
To test blades simply hit one with the other taking a pack in blade and replacement blade
Bang the cutting I just together of course you'll have to cut away any plastic guards and shells by definition
The weaker blade will be dulled by the sharper blade
There's some natural variation from blade to blade so you'll have to take a bunch of originals and a bunch of refills
Log the results and do some averaging man, sounds like a lot of work now. Oh, so I do know fewer than five hits
Not including any trial runs. Oh, okay, so I was I was like I do a lot more hits than that
Okay, no more than five hits not including any trial runs needed to get the hang of it
A truly definitive test
Might need hundreds of blades brought from different stores at different times. What did you're bombing the out, man?
All right, that's it for this stuff for this week
Yeah, all right, baby, man, that always makes me tired that Metro sexual stuff
Let's see what are we into how many yeah? I've got a couple of different pieces of feedback here
But you know they're both about Senseo and I really don't I really don't want to do that right now
What should we do I've got
now
Can you hear the birds outside
Which turn it up I can hear a home in my mic
The sun just started shining a little bit and the birds just came alive
Now, I have enough sense say of stuff for today. Well, let me just scroll down
I did want to mention that
Business week has a podcast had their green host that she's had myself on she's had Ron on before and now she had
I forget if it was the president of
Interactive for CBS for CBS television
But very interesting to listen to
Listen to what the the quote mainstream industries thoughts are right now on
on podcasting both
From a audio and visual standpoint and
The way they the way they operate he even talks about you know how how really how it works
What contracts are needed at what stage of transactions and who owns what and it's really it's pretty fascinating stuff
So I suggest you listen to that and I want to leave you I guess with just
One more song from the just gotta upload it to the podcast music network. It's the bitty's live
In my head of my five speed. Oh, we'll drive that man cherry red love
Well, we want to be famous
New York
Well, if I imagine we're getting out of the city and go to where it's pretty by the
Graces of my truck like Charlotte when I have my truck. I believe I have the dinners
The robbers and the wonders by the increases of my truck. A dream is always
You live
That comes from your very song
In dream
There are no stuff like that all and every one is beautiful
Oh
One more in my truck
We never have to worry because we're never in hurry when we're driving in my trucks
And we're in my truck
There's no such thing as my vehicles the only ways the highways
Straight to heaven in my truck
Oh
Love
We want
They must
New York
I guess
Just more
Be it's all lucky
Well, we want
They must
New York
Just me
My honey and my truck
That's what I knew man. I need a bitties karaoke DVD
I give it up now girls doesn't she seem like an angelly and a fantastic love them
That's from there with the evening at the muse in Charlotte to North Carolina
The bitties in my truck and that actually reminded me that I thank you very much for all the different people who sent in
Links to video files and and torrent files of the discovery show dirty jobs where the host actually
Went through the entire process of getting
Used oil from a Mexican restaurant taking it back to
Some guys biodiesel manufacturing plant in his garage
All the way through to filling up the pickup truck with it and it really got my brain moving
I mean, if you look at the cost of the equipment, which I think is about five
Hundred bucks something like that to have a full set up to really to be able to supply yourself with your own
House with heating oil
And your car
Probably at a monthly basis
You know you're looking at maybe
What did they say I think that with the depreciation of the gear that they he was looking at 50 cents a gallon
So obviously if you didn't have to depreciate the gear
Then you'd be making your stuff pretty cheap. I was thinking you know, wow, this is it's so beautiful
We could like put together
Almost like a corporation actually could be a corporation. You know Bay Area biodiesel
Baby co there you go
Babe co babe co that's even better babe co be a yb
CO babe co
Yeah, and
It would only take two people really to run a full-time
Operation one guy picks up while the other guy is
You know is it's clean and shit out. I don't know and then they make the biodiesel or someone else man's the pump
Throughed we could totally do it and I wonder what the with the regulations are
Environmental regulations for just opening up a gas station
But it seems it's like it's very very doable and
You know it's just how many restaurants do you have in your neighborhood that use
a deep fryer probably every single one has it and they probably clean it out at least once but more likely two to three times a week
Fascinating we could build a company. I'd gladly fund if we we'd like franchise if someone could come up with the design specs and and we could actually create
Create the refinery part portion of it which is really cool and it's relatively simple but it does take some time
You know does take some work to come up with a you know a good oil drum full of
Biodiesel but you can pour this stuff straight into any diesel car
Okay
Now of course results may vary due to road and weather conditions and but even the newer diesel should not have a problem burning this stuff
These you can get a hold of that a copy of that of course. I can't post it online
Of dirty jobs the biodiesel
Edition it's one of the segments on the show from Discovery Channel or if you can see it
If it's gonna come up again on TV definitely take a look at it because you'll see
How cool it is and besides it having environmental benefits
It's independence man that's what really what I like about it just independence from the man
All right everybody I'm gonna get out here tomorrow the thank god. It's Friday edition of the show
Maybe some karaoke I will see certainly I'll start with another
Motivational quote of the day so take care y'all bye bye
Another pod show podcast stick it in your ear