Delta Sierra Charlie 312, hey everybody, how you doing?
That's my take-tax right there.
Welcome, I'm in the curry condo, actually.
I'm about 40 feet underground.
I got in a couple hours ago, I'm back in the bay area, and I'm looking forward to a couple
of weeks of getting a lot of cool shit done, and I'm jet lagging just a bit.
Now of course when you come back to the bachelor pad, you've got to make sure everything
is still operational and everything is right, and so I'm down on the garage to check on
Trinity, and she's still here, you do a quick external scan, everything looks pretty
much the way it was, with those rear lights out, let me see, a warning parking violation.
That was that, parked over the line into another parking space, what was this all about?
Okay, I see, other people have a parking pass, all right, oh man, I'm like,
right on the line, I'm not over the line, it's a freaking boat that I have to park in here.
God, and how about this murk?
No, what is this a G500?
That's parked over the line, did he get it?
Citation?
No.
Okay, all right, anyway, so what we're really here to do is to see if she'll still start.
Because it would really suck if I needed, if I needed her services and she wouldn't crank
up.
So here we go, yep, looks like this battery left, plugs are glowing, I'm going to wait
for the glow light to go off, here we go, oh my God, can you believe that?
Holy, holy roll, oh my God.
Smell that biodiesel, baby, I have it all figured out, by the way, I know exactly what's
going on with the biodiesel.
Ah yes, you can buy this kit and it costs about, what is it, $3000.
And with that, you can make up to 40 gallons of biodiesel per batch.
And I found out that this is the stuff that is mixed with methanol and lye to basically wash
out the oil.
And then you can use that, except the refined oil basically, the refined vegetable oil, which
you can get from Mexican restaurants, Chinese restaurants, all kinds of restaurants.
Anyone who deep fries basically, and how this is so cool, I can't believe she works.
Anyway, so it's exactly that, that is the stuff that you can throw right into the tank.
Now, the groovy thing is, you don't really need a conversion kit for it.
You can throw it straight into any diesel engine, any diesel engine.
The Trinity has, I think most cars, pre-1985, have to have this.
You need different hoses that are made of, I guess it's, what is it, an acrylic versus rubber.
That's the only difference that Trinity has because Trinity is, that's the car that I
mean if you're, if you're new to the show, is from 1984.
So, how badass is that?
Starts after, what is, oh, smells so good, french fries, loving, now what is this?
I'm quite full of all these doors again.
It's stupid.
So I guess what I'll be looking for pretty soon, somewhere in the Bay Area,
the preferably south of market is a grime space where I can have some floccal.
There's some kind of central unlocking, but no central locking system.
Now, she's a view.
Hey, I'll tell you what, why don't we get the show started right now?
Another day is here and I am still alive.
I'll say these words aloud, they speak from the inside.
And every time I see you, you just walk away, still the world is done in.
I want to hear while you, what you've got to say,
hey, hey, hey,
Oh, my mug is all made up, I'm through it all I can, I'm trying hard to think but I can't understand why every time I see you you just walk away
Still the world is dying, I will not complain
My head is spinning around, I don't know what to do if I'm so happy I got everything to use
And every time I see you, I can't understand why every time I see you
And now you're always waiting for the right to see you
And every time I see you, you just walk away
Still the world is dying, I will not complain
I want to hear what you, what you've got to say, what you've got to say, what you've got to say
Oh, are these kids?
It's the subways I tell you, I want to hear what you've got to say
From a young three turn to date
All of a sudden they just showed up in the podcast music network
I'm like, whoa, where have these guys and apparently gals been hiding out
Hey everybody, how you doing?
Welcome to the Daily Source Code, it's Monday, it's a great Monday
I was up very early this morning
Yep, because I was in the right place at the right time for once
I've never once heard our shows on serious on stars 103
I've never heard the pod show line up because every time I'm here, I'm always busy during the day
Because it airs between 3 and 7 p.m. on the west coast
But this morning, got to brighten early to listen to Howard Stern
We started today
Yauza
He is in a way he is kind of the original podcast I have to say
But he's always had the restrictions on so this is a whole new era that has opened up before our very ears
Anyway, so Trinity's running just fine, I was walking upstairs and I was looking at this citation
I'm here in the condo, so I don't have the regular set up
I did bring the Heil microphone this time
I still like the sound so much better of the Heil microphone
But I don't have the podcast complex
So I'm back to my bending over and kind of leaning on the open kitchen bar here where I had to set up
You know, leaning on my arms, leaning over everything, this is very uncomfortable
Here we go, so I guess what happened is I got a parking violation
So they say I was improperly parked
I was like right on the line, okay, I mean I got these really fat tires on the Trinity
This eggnog, yellow, Mercedes, station wagon, 300 turbo diesel running on biodiesel baby
And it also says that I did not have the metropolitan ID, that's the building that I live in
So I don't have the proper ID and I did notice that every other car in the lot ID
So I guess I got to get one of those but probably what happened is they clamped me because it even says here
It's not checked the box is not checked that it'll be told
Let me see when was this ticket written on the 16th of December
Okay, right, but then here there was another card attached to the windshield
Harry Shin, Harmony Construction Management Service
Well, I guess that would be part of the building management on the back of it written in pen
Want to remove wheel bumper call Harry
You left this cell phone number, but I didn't see anything what didn't what I did my walk around
So I don't know, maybe they just took it off because it like man, the thing was on there for weeks or whatever
Let's see, quote of the day for you today from Diane Frolov and Andrew Schneider
I like this one a lot
A man should not leave this earth with unfinished business
He should live each day as if it was a pre flight check. He should ask each morning
Am I prepared to lift off and I like that one a lot Raymond Port if you remember Raymond
He's the guy that was listening to the daily source code in a traffic jam
Well, I was recording one in the same traffic jam and we caught up with each other and this was
How was that a year ago? He had more than a year ago, I guess he sent me an email
He said that he had the exact same. I did a quote of the day the other day. Was it Victoria Holt
Yeah, I think it was Victoria Holt. I don't remember what the quote was and he said that he had exactly the same quote on his weblog
And of course, we both the obviously subscribe to motivational quotes of the day, so that's kind of how that happened
Over the weekend before my trip because I left Sunday morning. I was
I kind of got dragged into something that I usually don't partake in, but I really got enthralled by a whole bunch of new videos that are out
And available online with new 9-11
Quote evidence and
There's this one that was done really well. It was it was compiled out of a whole bunch of different news reports and
Amateur video photographs, but it was all basically done on a timeline and I was thinking to myself
This is something really cool, you know when you have an event like 9-11
But you could really it could be a ball game any event is okay
If you can time all of the media
And this is really like this is matrix shit
You know this is what you get when you sit in the cottage for weeks on end and you know smoke go
So let's just take a football stadium for that matter
And again, so a football game
If everyone who took pictures or video or audio or any other type of media of that event
If they could sync it to time code
Then you in theory will be able and it was all uploaded to a central database of course
In theory you could go back and you could kind of restruct events based upon material that is there
Just imagine like a big
Final cut pro timeline or Adobe addition
Excuse me, that's tea not sincere
But really a multi a huge infinite number of tracks
And if you want to be cool, you could scroll back and forth through that
And then see the images all these different ones
Of course you wouldn't be able to see thousands, but you could choose ones
And in this total Tom Cruise futuristic thing that I have in my head
You'd be able to scroll up and to the right and basically three dimensions
But wouldn't it be interesting if we could put something like that together for any kind of event
It really would work and I think that most cameras now are pretty good at adding metadata to their digital pictures
Which includes time code
Of course you could you could do it from multiple dimensions because you could also have let's say an airplane flying over the stadium that airplane could upload it's GPS track
I don't know if it's something about it just kind of start buzzing in my head and just want to throw it out there
Let me see I have a link here, I want to show what this link was to let me see
Oh, this is it. Yeah, it's the loose change 911 the Alex Jones conspiracy. I found it on the Google video
And it's I'll just play a little bit at the beginning of it
I think it's a complete amateur job, but it's very very well done and apparently all done in Final Cut Pro
Well, then it gets in all these titles and stuff that I'm not going to read for you
Let me see where am I here okay lots and lots of feedback about the power books sound loops apparently this is
Now this is a problem that I was able to demonstrate to you on Friday's show
I have a brand new it's one of the brand new Apple Macintosh power books. I have the 15 inch and there seems to be some kind of problem with the audio
Where inadvertently and not really replicable, but just at any given moment
Your audio of all sudden can start looping it goes into this like this echo this repeating dead
Almost like the CD is skipping in fact. This is exactly like a CD skipping. It doesn't really skip, but it just hangs there
Well, man, I got a lot of feedback about this
It seems that this is definitely a problem
Lots of people have it. Let me see Tim from Latvia
He sent, but basically a whole bunch of people sent me links to pretty much the same solution
Scott Tyler said he thought he heard it managed had that problem
Let me see
Okay, I think was Brad here
So there's this link on MacLife.com. Is it MacLife?
No wait
MacILife.com
There you go, possible fix for the 15 inch power book. Basically, and if you have this problem
You got to find that link and of course it'll show up in the show notes in the time code they show notes for sure
You go to your preferences and you have to delete a file basically it's your Apple audio preferences file
And then you reboot when the file is recreated automatically, but I guess that there's something that can get really messed up by
Using some combination of applications that I don't know it just gets confused that seems to be the fix that's working the best so far
And I haven't had the problem of course I haven't really been doing a lot of sound intensive stuff over the past couple of days
But it is working so far so fingers crossed and I'll keep you up the speed on that
Hey Adam, it's Michael's whirling the owner of two independent talk radio stations KSCO and KOMY in the moderate bay area
But please don't hold that against me
Fact is listening to your podcasts with all the great audio clips from other podcasters has made my bay area power walks so wonderfully entertaining and amazingly enlightening
That I'm seriously considering selling the broadcast boat anchors and doing true real innovative unbridled and unstifled original podcasting full time
What a revelation not only do I not need no stink and transmitters?
I really don't need no stink and ask cap BMI and C-SAC fees no stink and public file maintenance no stink and EEO reports
No stink and transmitter readings no stink and FCC inspections no stink and discontented and resentful employees no stink and enormous power and telephone bills
No stink and license renewal and no stink and constant engineering headaches
Now I know all that makes me sound like some bitter negative person, but I am truly thankful to be a very proud independent broadcaster
Who is beholden to nobody because I discovered a much more powerful way to make money than selling 30 and 60 second spots in radio
And this is made it possible for me to thumb my nose at clear channels and infinities of the world and more than support my radio have it
I just love being able to tell the big boys to shove it when they try to bully us what's most exciting about podcasting though
Is that it offers all of the fun and virtually none of the headaches of broadcasting and I think the same innovative alternative money making principles
I have successfully employed as a small independent broadcaster would work even better in the world of podcasting
Check out www.fireyoursalesstaff.com and please feel free to share with your listeners
Tailwinds continued success and peace of mind to you and all podcasters and podcast listeners from MZ
Yo dude, y'all there you go there you have it guys leaving radio at least that's what I understood from the comment he's leaving radio
Owns two stations in Monterey
Isn't that like a stoner surfer dude paradise out there in Monterey isn't that what kind of goes on out there?
I should check out these radio stations. I wonder if he actually did sell them that would be very interesting
That's for sure, but wow, do you hear that list of shit that he has to go through?
I'd forgotten all about that and of course you had the official sign-ons and sign-offs and the logs
Oh man boy so much to do there
He said tailwinds at the end
You know that's our pilot speak for a hey buddy
I know you're a pilot I'm a pilot too
Guess what I ordered by first item off of eBay and it has to do with aviation
I was looking for a Garmin GPS map one nine or five which is all the pros use it. It's actually an older model
Of Garmin GPS they have new ones which are really actually very beautiful collar ones with terrain mapping and stuff
But all the pros use this old one this and it could I think basically because it has the largest screen
To date still of any handheld GPS and it's a pretty big unit
But I was able to pick one I found it on eBay. I was looking for one and eBay actually had a whole bunch of them for sale
And I'd never bought anything on eBay before in my life
And since the item said and of course this is one of these buying now
So I guess just a dealer of second hand GPS units. It wasn't really an auction per say
It said we'd only ship in the USA so I gave the condo address and there it was man when I arrived today
Waiting there for me and I put batteries in and it powered up and it was really happy with my purchase
So I have to go tell everyone on his on his profile that he's a good eBayer
And now I'm an eBayer too, I feel so incredibly proud of myself
Christina was eBaying the other day on tickets for panic at the disco
Have you heard of those guys?
I don't think I can play him anymore
They were pod safe for like half a second and then they got signed
I think they're signed now and they're on tour and it's like some grungy tour
She wants to go and so I said okay, I'll drop you in your friend off
Like all those parents do they sit outside and drink drink coffee and smoke cigarettes and read books
If you're listening to this podcast that daily source code on serious stars one oh three
We have three and a half more hours of pod show on the way for you Pacific Coast Hellway is next
I want you to listen to this for a second. This is pretty funny. Derrick had a question
How's it going? I know how you love
Love audio comments, so I sent you one. I really love your show. I'm a new listener
And I'm kind of dabbling and podcasting myself not with it
Like with not much success though, mainly due to content but I'm working on it
Anyways, I was just wondering where you get your really cool
Intro is for your segments, you know like the mental sexual moment and also your
Trinity moment
One that I saw in your last episode
So yeah, I just wondering where you got those thanks
I dare
Well, just so happens that when I get you know what the cool thing is that I barely have to do anything myself
For the what we call the imaging of this particular podcast
Dave Fox has done a whole bunch for me Marcus couch from
The scenes scenes and a lot of stuff that I use and Jeff Smith showed up just recently
He did the Trinity theme. He did the Metro sexual moment theme
And he actually came up with something new for me. I don't have
I don't have anything to play in the item for today
At least I don't have anything cute up for you, but this is basically I asked for it
And I just kind of set it off handedly and this is what I love so much about this stuff
Your audience actually helps you create the show. This is really total interactivity
One day
Here it
It's Yadsey
YADC yet another
Another drum cadence
Yadsey
And he has a cheer
So that's what's cool about this stuff is it just kind of pops up people make stuff send it in. I love it
And that's what makes it really work and I see this happening all over the place
Imagine as people make entire songs for it's outrageous
I mean Dawn and Drew listen all the feedback they get that they put at the end of their shows
It's and Dawn and Drew also coming up on stars 103 in about what is it about an hour from now
And we'll see you guys tomorrow enjoy Howard and enjoy the rest of the pod show
And those of you on the podcast stay tuned and wave goodbye to the satellite folks
There you go
I'll just talk about Roger Smalls
Michelle
You know this has happened a few times now with this Roger guy I didn't mention anything but after this last time this one Roger sent me a
He sent me a comment that
He thought the plastic bags it sainsberries where we do our shopping are a bit weak that you really need to double bag everything
So Michelle says here's my reaction whenever you say that you have an audio comment from Roger Smalls coming up my skin starts crawling my heart starts beating faster
I get immediately tense we have a word for guys like him and Southern California it's called stalker
You completely creeps me out the fact this bad enough that he goes through your garbage I only did it once
But that he also hangs out at the grocery store you shop at and hopes of running into you is just very scary
You do seem to have him at bay and I'm sure you've probably had stalkers around you for a long time no not really
But nonetheless I wanted you to know that I'm sitting here in California having a visceral scared reaction to just even hearing Roger's voice
Half the thing he's done would already warrant a restraining order out here
Come on my experiences
You know guys like Roger and girls like Roger they just I'm sorry Roger didn't mean to come out like that
They're fans he's just a fan of the show and he's really into it and he's podcasting in this cool. He seems he seems like a pretty cool dude
Match has my back on that too
What is this I had one two more things I wanted to share with Patty San
Tanjolo what was this about I just oh right
Yeah, I don't know if you heard about this Patty San Tanjolo
Here's the here's the headlines mother of five fighting record companies lawsuit on her own mother goes solo and fight with record companies
Mom fights downloading suit on her own internet illiterate single mom takes on recording industry
So you've got to read about this woman who got a call from the settlement center
You know this is the record companies the RIA they just have like a like a boiler room operation where on behalf of the record companies there
I guess they
They figure out that people have been sharing
License music through their computers how they exactly find that out is unclear from any article I've been able to read
But they said look you know we're gonna sue you because there's music has been shared from your computer, so you're a pirate you're a thief and
Apparently it was what was being used because I think and she had some great quotes in here
One thing that was pretty interesting. Oh, I was that she had a funny quote
Well, basically she said she had no idea what what cuzaw was and she'd never heard of it and then she says
I very sure
I very strong feelings about how if this did happen on my computer cuzaw could allow a child to obtain an account that could be potentially dangerous to the child
Cuz of course the RIA is going after kids now as well
Dangerous to the child and the parent without parental authorization or the authorization of the person who owned the computer, and of course
He's right about that
But the whole point is
That they said they were well, you know you can settle for three and a half thousand dollars which of course is ludicrous and she can't afford a lawyer
So what she's doing is she's gonna stand up for it in court. She's taken it all the way and she's gonna defend herself
And even her lawyer who she can't afford anymore said she'll win this thing, but this is just crazy. So Google it patty Santangelo
And I think that even I've seen several different PayPal donation links pop up here and there so you can help her with the fight
I think it's actually a Dutch group who had done a group of Dutch people who had done that as well. I'll look around for it and hopefully that also show up in the show notes
Okay, one last song from the podcast music network from so that's music.podshow.com
A lot of hip hop showing up and also some stuff from Germany. I think podcasting is actually starting to pop open in Germany
For a number of different reasons you know it's a big ass market
They're really not happy with their with their broadcast situation and I'm just amazed by some of the stuff that I've been hearing
So this song will be in German obviously
You know, I just had some kind of cool to it. I've was that the name of this group is Simon says and that's S-A-I-Z
I guess they mean Simon says they have a whole collection on the on the network got some reggae got some rock got some funk pretty interesting
This is Echt de Lieber from a find out of Deutschland
Now which boring thing is going on because in the near mile
I think I'll do it twice. I'm amazed
You're the same as I might as well.
You're the guy who killed my killer?
I kept asking,
saying you're my cứ red sphere,
saying you're not that hungry,
so should't be screwed up and asked.
He was in my Arab court for two years,
trying to get my school no less,
go for 5 to 15 weeks to Serves
and three miles out.
Shut up, I have no idea what's going on here.
Now there's 23 points one last time
Again we can be tryin
Now again we can be a down
Caution and bones
You're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can
you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, and you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see, you're the only one you can see,
It's the truth, my guess is the truth.
It's the content that not better more than that.
It's the truth.
All right.
So, I am jet lagged out of my skull as you can imagine.
So I'm going to cut a short for today tomorrow we back.
Well, we're going to have some fun times in this coming week.
Coming two weeks actually.
Lots of stuff that I'll finally be able to talk about.
able to talk about, we're gonna have stuff that's gonna be opening up to the world, it's
gonna be a great time. So thanks for listening, stay subscribed if you are, bye bye now.