Delta Sierra Charlie 352
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass
In the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into the future
I'm just a kid's fellow curry
Well, well, well, I heard you got the mood
Yeah, I heard you got the mood
It's like they went stuck on you
Well, you better not forget
They had left you yet
You still got trinity and all the best damn coffee
And the whole white world and you're well on your way
More hundred million listeners
And don't forget that rhymes with blogger
Would still be around and probably got your back
And hey, you got the pot safe dudes
And you know that the chase away the blues
So you know what comes around but go around
You know what I'm talking about
So let's all light up a nice piece of love
And smoke their blues away
Yeah, once upon a time
These lines went broken down
And on the ground
Walked up on a time
And when I was faithful
The years passed slowly
Once and once again
I'd smile at her
And say it's gonna be okay
Yeah
A pizza that I've never seen
That looks so wild and clean
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I see that we'll let she not be
I've never been so tempted
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I think it'd be my job
Look at that she's mild to me
I know I think I'm headed for the center of the world
To take it into the center of the world
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Hey, make her a lot of Kevin time
A dawn in the city
Hey, yeah, yeah
She's my city, she's my thing
And I'll be sending her
Hey, yeah, yeah
I'm gonna put her on my plate
Oh, I think I'll lose some weight
And that if I'm the center of the world
To take it into the center of the world
I've been all the way along
And I've to pick out cutting bay bay
Oh, what the fuck's the man like me
So real and real man
I'm really ask you, sister
I'm doing all the same
I've been with this up to man
You and I got to find a change of plans
And that if I was better
That if I was the center of the world
To take it into the center of the world
She's gone real to me
Whatever and I've done that do
I oughta have my head
Except for her
She's under
Twenty-two
I think I'm closing dream
Of that you can't deny
It's been long
Long
Time
Is that a wacky hook or what?
Hey everybody how you doing?
This is the daily source code
It is officially still Monday
We got back late
I know I promised a promise to y'all a Charlie today
And here it is
But it'll also have to serve us Tuesdays a show
Since I will be leaving on jet plane tomorrow morning
Brighton early
Off to San Francisco
I'll never make any satellite windows whatsoever
And we're back
It was a fantastic weekend
I know I kind of told you guys a little bit about what we were up to
And then we were going away
And I had mentioned some of the pieces of one
It might be happening throughout the course of the past few weeks
And really after Friday's show
I realized didn't tell you what we're going to do this weekend
So I just left it at that
And we went to Amsterdam
The three of us it was really nice
It was really good to get away
We haven't been away
The three of us in our last US trip
Which of course was in the middle of the
The heat wave in New York
Patricia and I both got really sick
We had to skip Vegas
Went to San Francisco
Where it rained of course
It was not the best of all vacations
But now that Jesse
Our big dog is gone
It's a lot easier to find someone
And of course, you know, you just don't want someone else
Taking care of a sick animal while you're gone
So it was a little easier first to go away
And we've got someone to house sitting
Look after the two cats
And Svabber
Our little Yorkie
Which really doesn't qualify as a dog actually
And it was great
So I'll tell you a little bit about that today
Boy, I'm tired
It's just been a whirlwind
A whirlwind of excitement
And it really started with Friday show
And I have to say
I didn't almost instant any email
It all during the entire weekend
I tried not to log on it all during Saturday
A little bit during Sunday
Because I know that the real rule is
If you don't want to receive a lot of email
Then just don't send email
Or certainly don't reply to email
And then it kind of stays within boundaries
And it really started with the show Friday as I said
And I got so much positive feedback
A lot of people saying that they are doers
And want to get going
And let's stop talking
Let's get something cranking
That was really uplifting
Very exciting
Plenty of feedback
Still of course on the outcome of the lawsuit
And just a whole bunch of energy
Spitting around
But I have to say
Overall pretty positive
So a very appreciative
Also on the common boards
Or on the comments on at curry.com
It's just it was good
It really felt good and I really appreciate it
Adam
Yes
What?
You are on fire
You're angry
You're pissed off
I like it
It's Derek Miller from the Penn Machine podcast
Here and that Friday
Delta Sierra Charlie
That man that was awesome
You were just cheesed off
I haven't heard that for a while
Anyway
You know so many people say that
So many people say yeah we really like the show
And you're angry at something
But it takes so much energy
And I don't want to be angry
I don't want to be cheesed off
I'll just have to say
Maybe we should always
Maybe Friday
We do a thank God it's Friday
Maybe Friday is the show
We just let it all out
All the shit that was bothering us
During the past week
That may be the way to do it
I think I can do it once a week
I thought it for me too
And I just wanted to tell you that
Okay
And suggest that
Maybe you weren't smoking enough that day
You know
It's true
That will happen on a Friday
And it does make a difference apparently
Maybe you should do some work
You imagine if I if I didn't smoke during the rest of my life
How incredibly
Not nice it would be
It is nice when you're when you're common
And mellow as well
Anyway just want to let you know that
And I'm at Penn Machine.com as always
And I just finished listening to that
And now I'm going to go calm down
So thanks a lot
All right do
No thank you
I appreciate very much
As I said lots of feedback
Like that came in
I'll probably on the plane ride tomorrow
You know the typical nine and a half hour commute
That I make to work
I'll probably find a couple more hidden in
In the Gmail
Oh no I won't find it because
I won't be connected
Hmm
I'll have to do some pre-preparations
Before I hop on the plane
A couple more that I did
Really in that thought
We're pretty funny you wanted to listen to
Worker Tom
Who's apparently now
Religious
Yo pod father
Trucker Tom here
I pray this finds you and your listeners
Well wanted to comment on the recent podcast
For one one interview
Specifically in regards to some of the
Comments that Ron Bloom made
Ron is right on the money
When he says it serious podcasters
Need to begin to develop themselves as media properties
Rather than simply someone putting out podcast
And perhaps sticking in the add or two in it
This podcasters we need to begin to ask ourselves
How can I help out my fellow podcaster
How can I make positive contributions
To the overall podcasting effort
How can I make the overall listener experience better
We as podcasters need to do whatever we can
To help out others
That may mean giving a bit of constructive advice
Or it may mean sending out audio files for others to play
Whatever it involves it needs to be part of a collaborative team effort
There's an old saying if you row your neighbor across the river
You'll get there yourself
When you help others you're also helping yourself
Oops here comes the plug
I'm now part of the pod shown network at
TruckerTom.podshow.com
Tom Tom
Don't stand behind the exhaust when the engine running
What's the MTV bit in there
All right this week so it's a if those were the only two pieces of feedback
I got there was a hundred more like them just so you know that that's how positive it all was
That was fantastic
So the whole reason for us going to Amsterdam
And this was kind of you know kind of weird timing or uncanny timing
I should say
With the whole picture lawsuit because it was actually going to be Christina's debut on the catwalk
At a fashion show in the Akura hotel in Amsterdam
It's a pulse filter
Otkutur
And now Christine this is something Christina's wanted to do for a long time
She actually wanted to be in the show a year ago
But everyone thought she was a little bit too young
And this year well it was finally her turn
She was going to make her debut on the catwalk
This is a big show
I mean there's a couple hundred people
You know it's it's just like any Paris or London or New York fashion show
It's just as elaborate, extravagant
As stressy
As musical theatrical
It's it's really it's a show
But it's you know it's short it's like you know 35 40 minutes
But it's these things are always a big to do and all the celebrities come out
And
And I have to say that Christina was very very calm, cool and collected
Although there was a small sudden it was kind of weird on Friday
About about 25 30 minutes before we left
There was a short panic of I'm afraid to fly
And all airplanes crash and I'm going to die
And I've been dreaming about this and you know
This is the kind of stuff that happens with any human being
With intelligence who starts to grow up and starts to use
Their breath and start to think about shit that we take for granted
And so it took a little bit of convincing
But the fact that you know I have my papers helped a lot
And I said look you know I'll talk you through everything
And really what I noticed is that
It's really about all the sounds, the unknown sounds
And even sounds that I didn't know about probably two or three years ago
So now I was very easy for me to say
Okay now we're going on the runway
Now I was going to test the engines now I was revving the engines up
And say oh that sound you hear is the gear coming up
And you wait for about seven to eight minutes
And now the flaps will come up and look you can see
And you know I was just talking through the whole thing
And it really worked
And I was so proud of myself that I was able to calm her down
And get her through that
And I think that it's pretty much over
Even on the way back today
Even she was looking at the flaps you know
And now try to identify the sounds
And it seems like that is a big factor
With fear of flying
So anyway besides that
Everything else was just was great Saturday
So we went it over Friday night
Didn't sleep out or sleep in Saturday morning
Because I was scheduled to go flying
With wind commander William in the Delta Shira
Which of course now has the brand new interior
So we met up around 1130 at Laili Stutt
Better known as Ugly Town
And that's in the colder lands
Kind of the mid north of the Netherlands
And it was great
The weather was fantastic for what we were planning on doing
It was like it was sunshine
But it was snowing, it was 30 knots of wind
So it was going to be some good flying
And wow it's like it's a whole different airplane
Besides the fact that you know it looks like an Italian sports
Turn out on the inside with this plush white carpeting
And I've got the black and brown chairs
Really it just looks like the cats meow
It has that new car smell
Like leather and glue and stuff
But also the new engine
Which has completely been balanced
In flight balancing and all this technical stuff
And it is so stable and you can really tell
I don't have a vertical hold on my autopilot
Only a directional hold
So you kind of have to play with the trim
And if you know what you're doing
You can get the trim working just as good as any autopilot
Almost except it won't take commands from a GPS
But you could even tell how well balanced it was
It was just sticking right where you wanted to have it
And it was total joy
Although it was kind of crazy
We got a ramp check
Which means you land and you come up on the ramp
And you know there were the cops or the airport police
Or whatever you call
And that had a camera crew with them
Oh my god what the hell is this
And it was one of those shows
Like one of those follow the cops around shows
I thought that's kind of rude when you think about it
You know it's like all of a sudden
Be with just taking cameras in your face
And while you're doing whatever you're doing
And of course we're clean as a whistle
But still it was a little bit of a shock
And boy it was going to be a lot of cameras during the weekend
Because particularly because of the lawsuit
As I said that the timing could not have been more
Any more uncanny
There was just everyone was trying to find us
And trying to sneak pictures of us
It was nuts
Absolutely nuts
And so the girls did all their fittings on Saturday
And we just kind of hung out Saturday night
And Sunday I'd gotten an email from the Prince
It's funny how this goes
Prince from the Prince Bernard
Actually of the royal family
And we've known each other for a couple of years
And he said
You know once you come over we got a new place
And come over Sunday has some coffee
And it was kind of a surreal scene
I hadn't seen him in a couple of years
And he said he now has two kids
And his brother came over and he has three kids
And his business partner came over
They have some business in Serbia
With IT consultancies
It was just fun
Just to hang out and get a little bit of inside dirt
On the family and what's going on
Just talk some crap
And then got back because the fashion show
Was going to start at five o'clock
And I kind of stayed away from all of that
Because I was just getting more nervous
Not just the fact that Christina was going to debut
But she had to wear these high heels
Which would just
I mean these were easily
I don't want to say
Seven
Seven inch heels maybe
I was like oh my god
I just had this vision of her
Feeling over or slipping or falling
Extremely scary
But she did a fantastic job
She really did
She kicked major ass
Had the complete
Attitude that you need for the runway
In fact you know
I think she has a whole different slant
I call it the my space attitude
Totally one of those my space pouts
And she's prancing down the runway
It was awesome
It really was just totally cool
And she enjoyed herself
Honestly we were of course a thousand times more nervous than she was
But it was it was great
It was very successful
And she looks forward to making some cash on the side
She told me
In fact you know what I was thinking
Since I'm getting everything packed for tomorrow
I have all parts of the studio
Well it's like here's what we'll do
Let's do a little sound seeing tour of the cottage
On a Monday night
Let me just hook myself up here
Hold on this should work
I've got it's getting
My my kid is getting better every single day
I've got
You know my microphone set up
My wife walks in
Let's see do we have this
This should go
Turn that one on
And hello hello hello hello
Okay
Let's just
I think that
Is it sound okay
Sounds a little
A little hollow
Let me okay
There we could dance better
One two one two
Okay
Let's just
Oops
Just go for a little walk
Let's see what's going on
How many minutes do I have
Before the satellite window closes
Five minutes okay
Oh you folks on the satellite
Getting a little sound seeing tour
Let's see what everyone's doing
And the whole I thought Patricia was
Hi
I'm wired
Oh
Yeah
Hi
I won't explain what I'm seeing
I just want
Yeah
Tell us about what you thought about the show
The show from Christina
Okay
So now everyone knows
Yeah
I told you I was wired
You didn't have to do that
No we don't have to throw it away
I just want moms impression
No it's not with what they think
No it's not
Mm-hmm
Well I was very proud
It was very special
You're talking to my nipple
She did very very well
Yeah
Unbelievable
With a poker face
Mm-hmm
And they said that she walked like a Chanel girl
They have a certain walk
Mm-hmm
Those young models so she was great
She's natural
Thank you very much
Can carry on
I'll go find her now
I know what you're doing baby
It's Christina upstairs
In her room
Hello
You're on the show
Just tell me what you thought about the show
What show
Your show
My show
It was fucking awesome
Okay
Are you talking to Owen?
Yeah I'm talking to Owen
Okay
Hi Owen
Okay here
What?
Yeah can you hear him? Owen?
Adam
Your girlfriend was a superstar dude
And I see that
Okay I'll leave you alone
I love you dad
You too
Good night
Good night baby
There you go
You're on the podcast she says
All right
Oh you're you gonna stay here
One
One and a half
Another three minutes
Hold on hold on hold on
What do you mean just go ahead
It's not well if you're gonna stay here
Then you have to be on the microphone
Okay
I'm cleaning my face
Is my eyes right now
Yes
Because it's late
It's late
I didn't even
I'm leaving you baby
I know
I'm leaving you again for ten days
Oh
We had so much fun this weekend
You know what we didn't have this weekend
Yeah
What?
You know what we didn't have this weekend
That's fun
I don't know
Now we didn't
Yeah
But it was a lot of fun
Wasn't it?
No but this was a lot of fun
It was what
And what a bad hotel
It sucks
So horribly bad
I know
Yeah
They they say it's good
You know what all those Japanese
Businessmen stay there
Yeah
They must have like no no demands for nothing
And that food
You know where the Japanese
What do you say?
Well they had like modern pea soup
On the menu
Now pea soup
Which is a very
Typical Dutch traditional
Also on the market
Yeah, but really air to soup
The really the heavy
Pretty soup
Like the almost like yogurt
I was reading
I was reading the menu
And I said you know what is modern pea soup
Yeah
Nasty
Okay
Do you have nothing left to contribute?
Let me say
For the peeps for the peeps
Check in the cas
No not really
No really
No
I'm tired
Yeah here we are
And I'm very happy to be home
Because my animals
They really missed me
Yeah they didn't miss me
Only you
No me
Because I feed them
Oh I feed them too
Like triscuits and things
Mm-hmm
Okay
So you had a nice show on?
I'm not done yet
Oh
What do you think?
I always want to talk to you for a month
I thought it was the end
No
No because I have like
Three more things
I want to play
I have a comic strip blogger
Oh yeah
And you know your friend
Yep
People really think it's mad
But it's coming
But it's coming my friend
What?
Comister blogger?
Yeah sure
Why is that?
I don't know
Really?
No I am getting to know him a little bit
Do you understand it now?
Oh really?
Yeah
What do you mean?
What do you...
All in the beginning
I don't know
I thought you know when I saw these
The drawings that he makes
Yeah you must hate me
Mm-hmm
My god
I think I have a figure
Yeah
I think he's firstly
He's probably very intelligent
A lot about politics
And
But because
Probably because
His command of the English language
Isn't where he's why he'd wanted to be
The way he gets attention
Yeah
He's saying really horrible things
And then once he has your attention
Then
Then he actually
Then sometimes he actually says something kind of interesting
Yeah
Would you like to hear
Okay
First thing you have to do
Is raise your right hand
Can put your right hand up
And you're like that
Yeah
Now we would from side to side
And say goodbye people on the side light
Goodbye people on the side light
Alright yes ladies and gentlemen
He is here
Once again
Comic strip
Blogger
The lovely
The Jeff Smith
He also did the blues opening for today's show
Okay here comes Comic strip
Blogger
Hi Adam Kerry
He talked recently a lot about Netherlands
A country of Dutch people
And I know that the Charlie
Has a lot of listeners in Netherlands
But the Charlie is people now called
The Daily Source Code
The Charlie
Don't ask it's a long story
Oh okay
Okay
Clearly because
Love of your life
Is a Dutch diva
I will not comment anymore
About your fucking lawsuit here
But I have a speech to nation of Netherlands
And I would be grateful
If you could let me plug it here
And now
Here it comes
My speech to Netherlands
Dear Netherlands
Dear Dutch people
Ladies and gentlemen
And you
Mark van der Linden
I am talking here to you
People of Netherlands
Not to Frenchmen
And not to Germans
I am talking to you only
Dear Dutch people
On May 1st
Two years after Big Bank
European Union
Anagement are passing
And Netherlands will be considering
Whether to prolong restrictions for new
EU citizens
It's something
Something about open borders or something like that
I think so
How are you listening to it?
How are you hearing it?
I already heard it
When did you hear this?
I didn't put it on the show yet
No, but you played it for me
Oh okay, I'm sorry
Well I couldn't remember
No, I said to you
What does he mean?
He said
I don't know
Oh there you go
I still don't know
What's listening
Spain and Portugal
Finland and Sweden
Already decided
Not to prolong these restrictions
Beyond May 1st 2006
Netherlands
Have not taken decision yet
On this issue
But everything indicates that
Unfortunately
Netherlands will prolong these restrictions
I hereby would like to ask people of Netherlands
On all levels
In government and people on the street
To take action and ensure
That Netherlands will not prolong restrictions
On a new EU citizens
Beyond May 1st 2006
Okay, again
Dear Dutch people
I am not threatening you
I am just saying how it is
If you will prolong these restrictions
Now after two years
Review period
If you will not lift these restrictions
Then you will lose forever
Opportunity
To gain respect and friendship
Of myself
And of millions of other new EU citizens
Okay
So they're not letting new EU citizens
Into the Netherlands
That's right
That's not the borders
But there's a European-wide
Lift of that restriction
Which is coming up
First of May
I guess so
But the Netherlands hasn't voted on it yet
Well he wants to go to another country
I don't think he wants to be in wherever he is
I think
I'm sorry my blackberry
Shit
I'm saying
I think he doesn't want to be where he or
Maybe he wasn't allowed to
To give him to
Maybe it had nothing
Maybe it had nothing to do with the EU
Maybe it had to do with the comments
Yeah, that's what I thought
Maybe he wanted to live in
Do you think he was passport
There's instead of a picture
There's a cartoon
That is just drawn of himself
Maybe that's a problem
I'm sorry this is a picture
Doesn't look like he's here
Sumer or later
At the latest in year 2011
You will have to lift these restrictions
Because this is EU law
But by then it will be too late
Let me put it this way
If Netherlands will not lift these restrictions
On May 1st 2006
I'm starting to boycott Dutch products forever
Which is like herring and cheese
Okay, no more cheese
Do you want to say something?
No
Remember
May the 1st 2006 is your last chance
Dear Netherlands
Dear Dutch people
Ladies and gentlemen
And you, Mark van der Linde
Thank you for listening
See you in heaven or in hell
The choice is yours
Do you think he has a white cat
That he's stroking while he does that?
No, do you think this is really his accent
Yes, yes, yes
He has his own podcast
Like this
Yeah, and he talks to like CEOs
He's a big company
Yes, no, no
No, this is him, man
This is really him
Don't make fun of it
This is how we talk
I'm not making fun of it
Okay, this is the way
This is the way he really talks
So, to anyway
Man, he does not like the Netherlands
And Mark van der Linde
That's fine
It's good
It's separate
No, no, no
Mark van der Linde
You're leaving?
You don't want to hear Roger
Hello, I've been Roger here
So, you haven't sent you any messages recently
I also hit to put stuff like that
So, I could have come extracts like a thing
That's the about me
So, no way that come extracts like reviews me
It's been racist
So, some of my best friends working course censors
And they don't think I'm racist
Anyway, about your satellite repair man
Who looks like Uncle Jesse
I want you to say that
I think he's wrong to tell you how to speak English
Now that you decided to thank you for the rest of our lives
Then I think he's only righty
He was up to British accent
Now, another most of the words in America
No, the same is the English one
So, I think he's only a method
And before we start speaking properly
Like the rest of us
We say tomato
You say tomato
We say oil
You say weapons of mass destruction
I certainly don't think he should be using the word charlotte
Because that means a drop of the supermodels here
So, you'd better be careful
As I've said, he's finally arrested for distributing drugs online
And I've certainly never thought about calling my private parts charlotte
I call mine said Jane
I was wondering if your cousin name at all
Anyway, I've got to go
So, bye for now
I made a win to be with you
Oh, Rajano, no, I don't have a name for it
Great piece of feedback there
Good to hear from you
It's okay to send your message whenever you can
I appreciate it
I especially like the bit about my satellite repairman
Who looks a bit like Uncle Jesse
I presume you mean from the dukes of hazard
Yeah, that would be PW
Who started this whole aluminum aluminium aluminium tomato tomato thing
Yeah, well, PW has some feedback
Based upon the feedback that I'll play for you right now
It's outside the satellite window
Because we all know he really just wants more airtime on the show
So, and then I'll weigh in with my thoughts
Okay
At the risk of starting something so endless
That I need my own theme song and believe me
I don't want that
To Susan from Grak Radio
Yes
I've been to Italy
Or should I say Italia
I want to Florence
Or should I say Firenze
I've been to Venice
Or should I say Venetcia
I've been to Munich
Or should I say Munich
I've been to Canadia
Or should I say Canada?
However, I adjusted my communication methods to suit the environment I was in
I didn't change my own personal manner of speech
Now on to Steve Webb who spoke about aluminum
The element aluminum is pronounced and spelled that way in the United States
The element, not an alloy
Just check it with Miriam Webster
In the United Kingdom, a country that has no
Boxite mines
The ore we get aluminum from
They call it aluminium
Both the element and any alloy
Check your Oxford English dictionary
On average, the United States produces about
3 million tons of aluminum a year
While in Jolly Old England, they produce about
300,000 tons per year
This means that your frying pan
Is probably made of aluminum
And not the identical aluminium
And now on to Adam
Adam, I am just so pissed
At the Netherlands court decision
The way I look at it
If I walked into a camera store
And reached around behind the counter
And grabbed myself a thousand euro
Nikon
And ran out the door
And got caught and convicted
I would wind up in jail
And in this case, somebody reached in
To flicker and grabbed a thousand euro picture
And winds up only having to pay for it
If they do it again
It's mind-boggling
I'm sorry, my brother
It's okay
Just go fix some more satellites
Uncle Jesse, it'll all be fine
The only thing that's kind of a bummer
Is I have not heard one peep out of creative
Comments
Or a professional lesson
Maybe they have to get the judgement translated
Or something but come on
It's been over a week now
We could easily have at least something
And something else
I think Com extra blogger pointed out
That no one has added this to my wiki pedia entry
Now don't make me go do it myself
And regarding the pronunciation
I gotta tell you
I'm on the side of the brits with a lot of this stuff
I mean come on
We know where the language came from
And I live here
So yeah I adapt
I watch East Enders
It's like you can't help but just fall into the lingo
What's crazy about it though
It's the Madonna
I've talked about this before
It's the Madonna syndrome
Madge does it all the time
She falls into her English accent
Which you know
She's just trying to be a part of the culture
And integrate
And she gets, oh man she gets burned for it
So severely
So maybe that's why I'm doing it
Maybe I'm just trying to poke a little bit of fun at the same time
But I really do like
I like the English accent
It's sexy
I need like some
Husky voice English chick to read the phone book to me
It'll be nice
A couple of things going on over here
With the UK podcast scene
There's
The podcast Paul
And Adrian Pegg
A couple others
I'll sent me this information about
Let me see how I can find it here
The MCPSPRS license
And it first I thought it was just a performing right society
But actually the MCPS and the PRS together
Here it is
They
Actually I'll read it from the website for you
The PRS collects and distributes license fees for the public performance and broadcast of musical works
And the MCPS collects and distributes mechanical royalties
Generated from recording of music on too many different formats
This income is distributed to the members, writers and publishers of music
So it is really the two licenses
That we've been talking about when it comes to being able to play license music on a podcast
And they have come up with an experimental license
And the highlights
are definitely
Now I have to see if I can find this page
Damn it
Why did I
I thought I had
Save that
So you don't have to go to the website
Shit
Okay
This website is a little bit funky
Let me go to
To have to go to what's happening
Then go to news
Okay
So let me just read you a little bit about this
News update
There we go
A little bit about this license
Here it is
Came out on actually March 3rd
So this is not really
As new as I'd like it to be
But it's very interesting
So they've come up with a scheme
The royalty rate for the Alliance Music podcast scheme
Is everything here is a scheme
Which is kind of funny
Because in the States a scheme
You know is usually negative
Will be greater of 12% of gross revenue
Or the minimum fee
Per track downloaded as part of the podcast
The full track
Will be
Well it says here 1.5p
I think that's pounds
I don't know
1.5 half a track
Will be 0.75
Oh no, okay
Now there you go
So let's see if we get this right
The royalty rate for the Alliance Music podcast scheme
And they have millions of songs
In their library
Will be the greater of 12% of gross revenue
That part I understand
Or the minimum fee
Per track downloaded as part of the podcast
A full track 1.5p
So that's
What's that like 3 US cents
Or a half track
Which is less than 50% by duration
At 0.75p
Hmm
And then it goes into all kinds of minimums
So I'm not quite sure if that is
What you play per track per number of people
Downloading if you have to multiply that
Or that's a little unclear to me
But here's what
Here's the stuff that I really didn't like
So you have to obscure at least 10 seconds at the beginning
And end of each individual track
By speech or a station ID
See and sure that music constitutes
No more than 80% of the total length of any program
Your program has to be at least 15 minutes
And length don't like that at all
And take all reasonable steps to ensure that
The individual tracks within a podcast
Not capable of being ripped or
Okay, blah blah blah
Makes sense
A podcast or shell not
Produced podcasts that contain
Recording from a single artist
That have more 30% of the musical works
Blah blah blah
That's kind of like the DMCA
Playing individual track more than once
In any single program
Providing electronic guide
To the podcast which contains tracks
Play it in corresponding times
That means no show notes
Insert any flags or markers
That makes sense
Incorporate repertoire works into advertising
Okay, so there's a lot of restrictions there
Which seem to a bit unenforceable
But just it seems to be some restrictions
12% of gross revenue which I guess is where
Where I would fall
I don't think I want to give away that kind of money
For the privilege
It really sucks
I think let's turn it around
Why don't you just make it so much easier
Let me pay you know five bucks or ten bucks
Just so I can put a track in my podcast
That's a much easier way of doing it
And probably a lot more profitable for everybody involved
It's just a thought
So there's a couple other little bits in there
Which did cause some alarm
Particularly podcast Paul who as you know is a lawyer
And somewhere hidden in here
It said that they were still going to take a look at
What kind of license they would be for
And this was such a contradiction in terms
Here it is
Non-music podcast
Example predominantly speech with very little music
We'll be licensed under a new on-demand scheme
For non-music services which is being prepared
For launch at the end of April 2006
So you can take that two ways
The way I read it is that maybe there will be a way
To just license one song one off
Not to have to do a you know
I guess that clearly making a distinction between
A podcast, a music podcast
And a non-music podcast
The kind of like the daily source code I guess
We use maybe one or two tracks
So we'll see what they come up with
But at least there's movement and the cool thing about this
Is that it is coming from both
License source
So for the mechanical rights and the performance rights
So that does make a lot of sense
But still it seems like an awful lot of money for the privilege of playing
Well the first thing I do if we could actually license that
I would completely and totally bring back the hit test
That's what I would do if we can do the hit test
And it stays within
And if young pull out is willing to do it of course
If it would stay within the rooms of affordability
I would bring that back in a heartbeat
So keep in my eye on it
There's still no place you can sign up or anything
And I believe that the guys from podcast user magazine
Are going to go and see what the complete details are
So exciting
Now one last thing about about the bridge here
There's been some a talk at Britcaster.com
Which is kind of like it's a forum for UK podcasters
Who for some reason feel that they don't get the attention they deserve
I'll just call a spade a spade in this case if you don't mind gentlemen and ladies
And I don't know why because I'll tell you there's more Brits on this show
Then there are any other nationalities
Seems certainly the last couple of months
But Neil Dixon sent me a drop in email and said
I thought I might draw your attention to a heated and contentious discussion
On the perceived need for podcasters to be represented
By an official association over here in the UK
Might be something we'd like to talk about blah blah blah
Okay
So they're actually talking about organizing
And I will just say I don't think that's a good idea at all
I don't think we're making a club out of anything
Ever
I've never
I've joined clubs before of stuff
And it just turns into like meetings and stuff
What I think we can do as podcasters and creative and
And creative individuals very smart individuals
If there's a if the need arises I think we can
We'll be able to form some kind of task force or emergency
Whatever we need when we get to it
I don't I don't think there's any need for it right now
Certainly now if we're just going to sit around and say oh you know
We need more recognition or whatever
We need some freaking doers over here who get into the
Advertisers pants and start figuring out how to get some cash flowing
I think that's what needs to happen
Okay
Let's see
I had a promo and then two more pieces of comments
Then they'll get out of here
Okay
This was a couple of folks that I met at the Donna Drew
Hangout
During our Fubore Friday last time I was in San Francisco
Hello, this is Naughty from Naughtysheets.lipsen.com
Are you in between lovers?
Let Naughty and her friends relieve the stress of the world for you
I will penetrate the intoxicating world of erotic stories
Which are submitted by my Naughty Naughty friend
So grab your charlie
Set the mood by lighting candle
Pouring something fabulous into a glass
And flipping between the sheets
As they take you on a central journey
Eberotic story telling
And Adam
It would be great to set up a private reading next time you come to San Francisco
Maybe Patricia would like to come along
Mmm
Sounds really nasty
And quite frankly I like it
Alright 45 minutes already
Screw the rest of this stuff
Let's go straight into our last song
It's from my buddy Bill Albert
The Vlad Meister, the Vladinator
It's the Miss Prince, in perfect harmony
I'm asking my loving address
My personality
They come out with our mistakes
People think I'm out of there
I see my face when you bust
I can't breathe out from the world
My friend
And me
We live together
And he perfect harmony
And I am
When free
We live together
And he perfect harmony
Mmm
Cherry, the rest kind of travel
We go over stone
We sing in the guitar player
Look to get all too far
What do they live inside me
What could they work for me
What's up with them
Find out
My true identity
They come out with our mistakes
People think I'm out there
I see my face when you bust
I can't breathe out from the world
My friend
And me
We live together
And he perfect harmony
And I am
When free
We live together
And he perfect harmony
Mmm
They come out with our mistakes
People think I'm out there
I see my face when you bust
I can't breathe out from the world
My friends
And me
We live together
And he perfect harmony
And I am
We live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together
We live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we each have a great generation of us and we live together and we are happy and grateful and we love to work together and we work together and we live together all together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we lives together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and I live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and have a great generation and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and put together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together and we live together all together and we live together and we live together and
I'll be back with you Wednesday morning, probably with the Sunrise, over the Corri condo
and San Francisco California, was it going to say anything else?
No, it's more than that, if I guess.
DailySportsCode.com, Adamacore.com for all your feedback, and I will talk to you on the
other side of the world literally.