Delta Sierra Charley, 3, 2, 8.
Oh, yeah, sure. We're halfway through the week, but I got the feeling we're only just getting started.
Yes, it's the daily source code coming to you from the Curry Cottage at Gilford Surrey.
Back to the wall, back to the wall, back to the wall, back into the curry where I'm new training.
We're still in like a snow, many miles traveled here, many, many more left to go.
And I guess I'm afraid of the things I've found.
No, no, but I won't be afraid to find stars flowing down.
And I'm just far from the wall, back into the wall, back into the curry where I'm new.
Back to the wall, back to the wall, back into the curry where I'm new.
I just give it up, and take me proud of you, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And believe that when I'm done, I know I've been depressed.
You saw the rest, saw the rest, saw the rest, saw the rest, saw the rest, saw the rest, you saw the rest.
You saw the rest, saw the rest, saw the rest, saw the rest, saw the rest, saw the rest, saw the rest.
You saw the rest, saw the rest, saw the rest, saw the rest, saw the rest, saw the rest, saw the rest, saw the rest.
Skimming like a stone, over the circumstance, before I know.
I've moved across the mountain, my home got a half stone.
And I'm just looking for my home, I'm just looking for my home.
And I'm just looking for my home.
I'm just looking for my home, I'm just looking for my home.
Mike Erica, skimming across the water from the pod save music network music.potshow.com.
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
It's Wednesday.
And here at the cottage it's kind of an overcast day.
Tomorrow I will be leaving.
It's confirmed going to visit my mom staying overnight in Amsterdam, returning home Friday.
So I don't know if I'm going to be able to do two episodes or if we'll have to skip one.
We'll just have to see anyway.
Feeling good today.
Despite that there's just no sunshine in the air whatsoever.
This is your typical British weather, I think.
If you're thinking of typical British because it really isn't usually it is blue skies and sunshine.
But this is what they always take pictures of and always refer to.
I watched actually this morning more problems.
The easy net dedicated lining to the house was, I don't know, it was broken.
It was, I was connected, but I was seeing 50, 60, sometimes 80% packet loss.
And so that was, of course, rather irritating has been a long time since bandwidth was a problem.
And then all of a sudden you're pushed into the harsh reality of, dude, bandwidth is a big deal.
Luckily one message to support got him on the case and there was something wrong within their networks so they fixed all that.
And watched the state of the union address after I got my bandwidth back.
Pretty bland actually. It was everything that I guess I expected to hear.
Boy, now that I've seen Commander in Chief, West Wing is one thing.
But watching Commander in Chief, I think that's probably a little bit more realistic.
Somehow I think it's a bit more realistic about, well, maybe not the problems per se.
But for some reason, I felt like it was more a part of the, actually it was taking place in the White House and how things must be.
And, you know, there's a reason why they call it the Commander in Chief for the CEO, the Chief Executive Officer.
It's very much like running a public company, actually.
No sleep, always something going on in China, somewhere.
Ooh, maybe that's why, yeah, that's why so many people are so pissed off at Google because we feel that our own civil liberties are being suppressed.
And shouting at the government doesn't seem to change very much or doesn't seem to get the desired response.
By the way, you know, Anthony Robbins always says if, and I, and I have learned a lot from Anthony Robbins.
If you keep doing the same thing, you're getting the same result.
Maybe it's a try time to try something different, you know, a different approach.
We'll probably yield in a different result.
But Google certainly, they got there, their slams, not for the China thing, but.
And after our trading after they miss their projected earnings by like a mile in Wall Street terms.
And after our trading, I think the stock was down 15%.
Now, Ron and I ran our last company as a public company for, I was at three years, three, four years.
And it's really tough. You know, every single quarter, you have to, you know, bring all these, you have to really get everything all together to report and you're going to be judged by pennies.
I mean, we literally want to miss one earnings statement by a penny.
Of course, you know, when it's the difference between profitable by a penny or not, per share, it makes a big deal.
But boy, did we get punished for that? We really learned the hard way about that stuff.
You can only imagine. And really, it's not so much about what analysts do and what the stock price going down doesn't.
That's never really bothered me one way or the other because, you know, we're just growing a business.
But what happens is, is when you have this euphoria.
And of course, even though we went public in 96, we didn't sell until 99.
There was definitely a year and a half in there when, you know, it was bubble mania, even our stock just, I mean, we didn't enter in the bubble.
We had, and we had real customers and real business model.
But employees who were brought in within, you know, during the euphoric period are feeling really good.
You know, when the stock goes up, 5% 10%, 15%, 20%, you know, then all of a sudden your options, which is, you know, really the secondary currency, certainly in the technology business, definitely in Silicon Valley.
You know, you get it at the price that you enter when you enter the company, the current stock price.
And so now those people are seeing, you know, maybe they had 100,000 or maybe a million dollars on paper, all of a sudden it's gone.
Now let me tell you, there's nothing more, oops, that's the blackberry sorry.
There's nothing more demotivating for a company when that happens, you know, because there's always people walking around going shit.
Look at that guy, you know, he got an earlier, so he's, he's made it.
And it's funny the way human nature works that way.
Even more interesting is that time Warner, the quote, old media guys, they reported a 21% increase in their profits.
And I guess they exceeded the numbers that Wall Street was looking for from them.
So just goes to show.
Google still did 1.6 billion dollars or whatever, but you know, I think everyone got just a little bit ahead of themselves.
Lots of feedback on this timer issue.
I have discovered that keeping time on a PC is troublesome.
And actually, I think, and Pete up came up with, well, he thinks the problem is.
So the issue at hand is I'm running three countdown timers in total.
And these are two of them are, one's based in Casplaster, one is based on countdown clock, a Windows application.
And I'm running one called Shimu with double Oscar at the end on the Mac.
And, and I'm just not, you know, I'm, I'm usually long by about 10 seconds on average.
And I've tried everything, even these clocks amongst themselves differ in timing.
So a couple of theories have come in and just some feedback in general.
Ian says, Adam, in general computers make terrible clocks to co-figure.
I work for a hardware manufacturer doing kernel support engineering.
That's hot.
My user response to complaints about slow clocks is to install an NTP client or go to our goes for a Casio watch.
Right, just for a little, a little quartz job.
Yeah, well, that obviously would do a hell of a lot better.
P.S. and Sayotip, well, warming it up, microwave half a mug of milk for 50 seconds.
Makes a great latte with the Kenyan Brazil pods.
Yeah, I actually, I've noticed that, you should warm up that milk because, you know,
depending on how much you put in it.
If it's cold, it kind of neutralizes the heat from the sense say it when it's gone within a couple minutes.
Dude, there's a fairly simple explanation says,
Garan Hebert, Casplaster and Countdown Clock are both, are both right.
How could this be?
Well, it's because they're using different clocks.
Casplaster is using the sound cards clock and the countdown clock is using the computer system clock.
Let's see, the problem is still, you know, when I deliver the file to P dub,
when I stop at 24 minutes and 30 seconds,
that's when the sound goes for the sound like window closing,
you know, it's still 10 to 15 seconds over time.
So we have to look at it somewhere else.
Sample rate is, is one area we could investigate.
Andy Armstrong says it may not be the clock that's wrong.
It's possible that the recording sample rate is slightly out relative to the playback sample rate.
I don't know.
I don't think in a 24 and a half minute segment,
you can shift by 14 seconds based on some,
I don't think sample rate is really going to be it.
Here's what I think it is.
If you're basing all these time calculations on,
if I can blackberry stop it, I'm so annoyed with that thing.
That thumb wheel is just driving the Apes shit.
And I'm having to find all the keyboard shortcuts.
P dub suggested that maybe it's because I'm recording using,
indirectly, I must say,
and that's where it kind of breaks down from me.
Indirectly on a 60 Hertz alternating current system,
which is here, which is what is used in Europe versus,
no, that's not right.
It's 60 Hertz in the US.
50 Hertz here, I think, isn't it?
I don't know.
Either way, I think the best advice is, indeed,
the Casio Court's wristwatch from Argos.
Hi, Adam.
It's Dennis from the Daddycast with a really funny name.
You know, come on, say it with me.
101 uses four baby wives.
Man, I just had a heart attack with excitement.
When I got the QIDJ memo,
but, you know, then I heard you say on the daily source code
that I'd be a beta tester for pod show.
I started thinking, beta tester,
that all I am to use a beta tester.
I'm not a freaking lab rock.
I am not an animal.
Ah, then I came to my senses, dude.
Pass the cheese.
I am so in.
Yeah, 101 uses for baby wives as a pretty messed up name,
but I deliver serious news and information parents can use right now.
But hey, wait, it's not all heavy stuff.
I have guests, interviews from newsmakers,
and music makers.
So look, there's lots of fun here, too.
It's real simple.
If you love your kids, then you will love this show.
Your kids will love it, too.
101 uses for baby wives.
proud to be a member of the pod show family.
Thank you, everybody. Bye, bye, bye.
Oh, man.
I knew someone was going to take a fence to that.
When I said, oh, we're having a beta test, too.
No, I'm glad you're digging it.
I saw a guy in a girl, a bottle,
had set up there, a show site,
and it's really starting to look cool.
I went to bed last night and was on with Kevin.
Who was developing from home,
and we passed a couple of messages woke up this morning
to take Christina to school.
He was still on, of course he's in San Francisco.
So it was only like 11 p.m. or whatever.
But it's getting there, getting very, very close.
And once we have like 25 people that are going to come in first
and then we'll start to open things up.
Yesterday we made all the final decisions on what would be
called the terms and conditions.
But I think it would be happy.
Show up willing to work and have fun and grow an audience.
And if you're interested in making money too,
you're going to have a lot of fun.
I promise you that.
No audio feedback today.
However, we do.
No audio feedback.
Yeah.
I'm working on the different sound settings on CASBlast.
I think the music and effects, as I would call them,
and promo's and stuff, were going through some kind of audio chain
that was making a sound of it bit crappy.
I got several reports for a piano.
And it's hard, you know, because you record the show on your headphones
and then you listen on speakers.
Then you listen on your iPod.
and, you know, before you know, you have no reference point anywhere.
You don't know what sounds good or not.
Anyway, today's Metro Sexual Moment is pretty much all about
the new Gillette Razor, I think everyone
and their dog sent me a link to this thing.
It's called the Fusion.
It is, let me see, there's a Reuters story here.
Now, this is the one that they jumped from three to four
to five blades is where they're at now.
And of course, Proctor and Gamble posted a 29% jump
accordingly profit driven by strengthened its household
and beauty businesses and the addition of the Gillette business
it acquired in October.
The company which makes Crest to paste,
to herself batteries, and most of other products also
raised its earning and expectations for the year.
$2.55 billion do, that's a lot of shame.
So let me see if I got some information on this thing.
This wonderful new Fusion Razor, I guess the concept
is kind of the same.
It has a battery, so it vibrates, but now it has five blades.
Here's the, oh, in the crazy orange packaging.
Pandemonium, everybody.
Let me see.
Here's a testimonial from a website from Ismoto.
I got my Fusion last night, Houston.
I used it and I think it's a winner.
The blade cartridge is much larger,
but the individual blades are about 50% smaller
than the mock three turbo.
Huh, the shave feels much different than the M3T.
Maybe it was because of the new cartridge,
but the shave seemed closer with less razor burn.
The single blade on the back is a great idea.
They've got a blade on the back.
Oh, that's so you can get underneath your nose there.
Ooh, that's dangerous.
If you're cut right there, the right in your nose,
God, this sucks ass.
Fusion review here, John Flowers says,
I thought you might wanna check this page
and he sends me the free stuff page,
which is where you can also read more
about the fusion.
And then, thank goodness,
we have to wait for a Brit to do it.
Neil Conqueron says,
I got some Metro sexual haven in the UK for you.
Listening to the show for a while now,
realized that last weekend is a place in Glasgow.
You might wanna go, it's called the men's store.
You can get everything you need there,
quoting from the site,
we do haircutting and colorizing.
Open razor-hot towel,
wet shave, relaxing facial stress,
busting facials, business manicure,
and that sometimes necessary backwax
to name but a few.
So that's everything except Botox and one shop.
City's about an hour and a half from London.
By plane, there's an online show.
Maybe a good sponsor for the Metro sexual moment.
Maybe that's, maybe it's not a sponsor,
maybe it's a destination for the Delta's urine.
Can you read Metro's sexual moment?
Yeah.
Hi Adam, this is Mark Curtis
for the Military Bratch Registry podcast.
Before I give you a sample of what I do on,
every brat has a story,
I want to hit you with some aviation bragging rights.
Have you ever flown in the cockpit of the Concord
as it takes off from JFK to Paris or I have?
I've ever flown the 747 simulator at Quantas and Sydney,
flying with three engines out,
then landing at night in fog on instruments.
I have, I've ever flown a British strike master jet
over Cape Town, South Africa,
doing loops, rolls and spins.
I have, not bad for 500 hour private instrument rated pilot A,
each yard out.
Well, then maybe I just shouldn't play your promo.
Dude, or is there something to this?
It's gonna make me really happy at the end.
Okay, and I'm gonna give you the benefit of the doubt here.
What does all this have to do with the Military Bratch Registry podcast?
Yeah.
Absolutely nothing.
I just wanted to make you jealous.
So what is the Military Bratch Registry?
Dude, yeah, I'm also an army brat, by the way.
Just so you know, so let's be careful here.
Podcast about, it's about interviews with people
who grew up in military families all over the world.
Military Brats, which is a positive term that we embrace
because the definition of brat is child of.
So we are children of the Military.
It doesn't mean we're warm mongers.
It just means we follow our parents to bases around the world
and sometimes lived in war zones,
as well as exotic locations like Thailand or Morocco.
The stories are fascinating.
Imagine living in Vietnam as a 15-year-old girl in 1965.
Or how about attending the Nuremberg Driles
as a high school field trip?
Those are just a sample of what you'll hear
on the every Brat has a story podcast at militarybrat.com.
Search for Military Brats in iTunes
or your choice of software.
I'm a little jealous, but I'm happy for you, my friend.
Happy.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
We're our flank.
We believe in an internet that's safe from virus,
hidden scammers.
We're our flank.
We believe your personal information
should be just that, personal.
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe.
We're our flank.
Make this smart choice.
Visit earthlink.net and discover
what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
Me and met me, you.
All our life will take them.
We want to go free, want to go free.
Interviews.
Hello, this is Bob from France for Nand.
And we're all looking to hope to bring them.
I want to come to Netherlands.
Now, don't do it.
I'll do Martin's up to pay say,
met me through podcast.
Check the site and what's it.
We've a very good met me.
He'll put an L.
Robonae.
That's my old radio buddy from the used to be a radio
Veronica with me.
Now he's on Radio 3.
He'll fainst, right?
And I guess I don't know if he's making
a podcast of his show.
I'm subscribed to some feed that he puts out,
but usually it's interviews, some chick does.
And I don't like the chicken of use.
I want to hear my buddy, Michiel.
But then of course, it's all the rights and royalties issues.
Ah, which on the podcast, the extended podcast version,
the extended finals of the show will be talking about
some interesting stuff going on in the rights world in Europe.
So stay tuned for that.
And more audio feedback.
Well, I made a mistake.
I let my kid listen to the D.S.E.
and now he's accusing me of copying your show.
You see, I have a podcast called The Vap
or vintage air stream podcast where we talk about
RVs, motorhomes, trailers.
And of course, those riveted together aluminum pods,
known as air streams.
Now it could be that he thinks I'm copying your show
because I had a sound scene tour in my last show.
Or maybe it's just my show's opening.
rivets, we don't need no thinking rivets.
With two tons of aluminum hits to his bumper.
Who's in down here in a super highway?
The Vap is streaming right to your ears.
And now you're host for the vintage air stream podcast, Tim Shepard.
I'm a man in a loon, not good.
Could be he's on the something.
Everyone else can decipher themselves by going to the Vap.com,
that's THE, VAP.com and give us a listen.
Thanks, Adam.
I don't think that was a mistake.
Did you kid that it's a sincerest form of flattery?
All right, I'm going to do some of this European copyright stuff.
EU is the anti-trust regulator.
I think that's a Dutch woman, Naly Smith Cruz,
is about to issue formal charges against the societies
responsible for collecting music royalties across Europe
for breaking anti-competitive rules.
And this is thanks to Jam J, who sent this into me, Joe, Joseph John.
The charges are a response to a complaint brought by RTL,
Radio Television Luxembourg in 2000.
It's argued that it should be able to get rights to use a piece of music
across Europe by going through a single collecting society rather than having
to negotiate with a different society in each country in which it broadcasts.
Here's the European Union at work now, guys.
They very close attention because they're going to make rules that will work
for every country.
So if we've already seen that the rules vary from European state to state,
let's just call it that, now they're going to consolidate all that.
It goes on, the case has raised concerns and smaller European Union countries
that their collecting societies could lose out to more powerful bodies,
such as Gamma and Germany and MCPSPRS in the UK.
The European Commission has criticized the fact that the authors are forced
to transfer their rights to the collecting society of the country in which they reside.
Ah, so there are an our side, apparently.
And the users of those rights must acquire separate licenses for each territory.
It is also critical of agreements between the various EU collecting societies.
You know what, what is happening here is all the crap is coming to the top.
Now there may be more crap they're going to put in place,
but I think that all these inequalities, inequities, all these differences
between countries and all these weird little rules that we found out about
where even if you have your own music that you want to play on your own podcast,
you can only do that if you pay the performing rights society money.
I mean, this is, this is crazy, this is crazy.
Now, hopefully we've done a little bit better today on the timing.
And we're going to fit just inside the satellite window.
So those of you checking this out on serious stars 103,
you know what, I'm seeing cast blasts are already said that the window closed.
This is ludicrous.
This is crazy.
This is absolutely nuts.
Look at this now.
The countdown clock is only kicking in now.
Well, PW, I'm sorry, my friend.
I hope you didn't have to work too hard and put them all back together today.
I got to figure this out.
There's something very, very wrong.
Well, at least we have another chance later on this week.
And here's a thing that came in that, from Mark Bars, he sent me this from the Netherlands.
And this is really interesting.
Now, we've talked about royalties or levies that are fees basically that are taken,
or you pay for them when you buy blank media, like blank DVDs and blank CDs.
Because, of course, you can, you know, just like cassette tapes,
you can record music and that's a loss of a sale for the music industry.
So, and there's this organization called Stifting the Divescopy in the Netherlands.
And their job is to collect these fees, which actually, the money's pretty amazing.
Let me see, a 4.7 gigabyte DVD, 60 Euro cents.
So, that's about 75 US dollar cents goes to this organization.
And if an audio CD or a regular CD raw, I guess they mean 42 cents, so that's about 50 cents.
That's quite a lot, actually.
What is the blank one cost, like a buck?
So, a lot of that money apparently goes to this organization that is supposed to
divvy out the money according to, you know, special secret codes and decoder rings and all kinds of
way to figure out who deserves what money from that.
Because, of course, they don't know actually what it was used for, but they are, let me see,
who is doing this, which ministers pissed off about this, the justice minister of justice.
And he sent a note to Parliament saying that he's going to make a big deal about this,
because they're taking way too long to pay out.
And apparently the reporting systems are not up to par.
In addition to this, I guess he's fighting for more discussion, at least, about having similar
levies put on to hard drives and other devices such as MP3 players.
Got to keep an eye on this, guys, because this will be shoot, I didn't want to do that,
I mean, doing it.
Got to keep an eye on it, because, you know, this could be something that is eventually
whatever is decided in the Netherlands, particularly because Naly Smith Cruz, who is the anti-competition
minister, is Dutch, you know, this actually could be some of what the law making the European
law making in process before a very eyes. Now let's play this song. It's bubble and sparkle star.
Telling a panic crazy, silence is your price, I can sit in your eyes, now tell me are you
yourself again, crashing on your dust, smiling in my hand. I always walk away, every time I look at you,
I can't believe I'll ever love again.
Do me the make-up, make it up slow, and do me the make-up, say goodbye, bye-bye, bye-bye,
shaking on my phone, come on still not slow, the world's just getting out too soon,
so then, we're seeing a good make-up and it's there now, so then,
we're always walking away, but every time I look at you, I can't believe I'll ever love again.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
You're just the star, the star always gets inside my hand
And I'm not you on the way
Because every time I need you
I can't believe I'll ever die again
I can't believe no no no no no
Maybe I'm just the boy
I'll be your base that will stop
Just like you
Do me make you cry
Make you fall so
Burn it down and turn it crazy
Never feel I'll make you feel
All I wanted you to feel
Bubble, sparkle star
Think I played up was there Christmas here on bars
One of the songs I bought a little bit
I played like it very much
Is that a cab?
Hold on a second, let me check and see
Is that it?
I think Patricia's going into town
Here's something cool, Rocket Boom
Has put up a week's worth of commercial airtime
On eBay, very novel like this a lot
So what they're guaranteeing here is
Hold on a second, I think is a million
What do they say here?
The advertisement reached for this auction
It's currently a minimum of 1 million views
They say that they get 130,000 people per day to watch each day's video
Over the course of several days
Each one receives over 200,000 complete views
So that's how they come up with 1 million views
The flight time as we say in the biz
Will be the week of what is it?
March 6 through March 10th 2006
Each day that we could different commercial
That they create for your company
Will be played at the conclusion of the Rocket Boom episode
And they're going to make them, they're going to make the spots
They'll be about 15 seconds
They will also own them, they will be responsible for the creative
So I love this because this is a complete reversal of the way advertising works
This is fantastic
And I was kind of wondering why no one had tried this before
Why no one had done it
In fact, I would have expected to do something like this
But I guess this is in essence what I've always hoped for
Is it baby?
Are you going? What are you going to do?
I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it
Okay, I'm going to do it
All right, we'll figure it out
We'll figure it out
I love you
Oh boy, she wants to go to
Her sister is opening up a store in Rotterdam
I think it's on the 18th February
And I told her I would be in New York
The week of the 12th now, you know, just taking air travel, etc. into account
It's probably going to be very hard for me to get back before she has to leave
In fact, you'd probably have to leave the 17th
And, you know, it's like who's going to watch the house
Who's going to watch Christina?
Is Christina going to go where there?
We still have a dog, you know, all that stuff
Sometimes work and play just do a not coordinate
Sex, we'll figure it out as I told her, we'll figure it out
So current bid is up to $7,602
And the reserve has still not been met
In advertising terms, that would be about a
Seven and a half dollar CPM or cost per thousand
Which is definitely on the low end of the scale
Which is why I'm pretty sure that the reserve has not been met yet
45 bid, let me see who's bidding
It's pretty interesting, it's like the internet guys
5% card dot com has really been bidding it up
See what else?
Blog ads, capital learning
You know, and like Dave Texas and Ed Cole, these are all
Guys who have all kinds of stuff going on
The eBay guys really have stuff going on with sales
But you know what, that's a perfectly fine market
And we'll be interesting to see if courses
When they sell that one out, when they, and I'm sure that this will sell
I'm hoping that they'll then immediately put up a new one
For the next week, because to make it sustainable, they'll have to do that
Imagine making 30, 40 grand a month, just by doing your show
And having eBay people bid on eBay, you know, it's all contained
Wow, a whole new economy of advertising, oh boy
I love it, fantastic, and more good news for Amanda Condon
She will be, I guess she's playing, I don't know if it's a bit
Part, if it's a walk on, if it's a cameo, which will be on the
Let me see, tomorrow's episode of CSI
Oh, playing herself, all right?
Cool, how very hip of CSI to do that?
Excellent thing, okay, those things I didn't get to yesterday
Wouldn't get to say it get to today, so when we may go a little bit long
But I should be able to blow through it in about 10 or 15 minutes
Let's see what we have here. Oh, this is good, you're like this
Hey, Peter
Hi, this is a special edition, a very brief announcement about digital
Flatzom, I'm PW Phantom, the next edition of digital
Flatzom will mark its one year anniversary, I almost missed it
I was searching for a digital Flatzom file today
When I suddenly realized I was looking at files from January 2005
So my plans for the next edition went out the window
Next edition will be a one year anniversary retrospective
And I invite everyone who would like to send me an audio comment to
Please send it to audio stuff
That's one word, audio stuff at gmail.com
Or if you don't have a way to record a comment and stick it in a file
Call and leave a message via this Skype button on my website at digitalflatzom.org
Please, if you're going to do it, do it soon
So I can get a new edition of digital Flatzom out there quickly
I'm actually excited about this
I hope to see you all very very soon
With the one year anniversary edition of digital Flatzom
Yeah, I'm on
And PW, hold it, the Mark Kerson
So funny when PW says
I'm actually excited, like I want to step back from the speakers
You know, for all the excitement that's oozing out
Congratulations PW on your one year anniversary, I love you
There, now you can put that in your show and then I don't have to cut something separate for you
Isn't that perfect?
Okay Adam, this is Michael kicking me out with the indigenous people's music podcast
I've been listening to DSC pretty much for about a year now
Or a little more than a year
And some of your more recent shows
Talking about pod shows plans
For revenue generation to artists and podcasters
Through the podsafe music network
I agree with everything that I've heard so far
And anything that can help benefit both podcaster
And the artists, I think are good ideas
But my question today actually deals with
A different side of podcasting that I don't
Really feel as getting as much attention as it really
Shouldn't really wonder if pod show had some ideas around statistics
And how we measure our audiences
I'm currently with Libs in right now
And they have a pretty good tool set
Compared to a few others that I've looked at briefly
But they still deal with a lot of generalities
In terms of new listeners, verses
Maybe listeners that we've had for a while
And I was wondering if there was actually a way
To measure our audiences based on unique IP addresses
So that we would know or have a way of tracking independently
Who was a newer listener
Versus people that actually had been subscribed
To our podcas for a while
For say at least six months or more
And I haven't seen any tools address this
That much but I would find that to be pretty valuable
Information when it comes to trying to market our shows
And things like that and gaining new audience
It's always nice to be able to speak to our older audience
One way and then when you're welcoming new listeners
That you simply know that based on your stats
And you can speak to them and market to them a different way
So it's something just having stats alone
This specific I think is a benefit
Something I don't believe the music industry can produce
Other than maybe iTunes in terms of numbers of people
Downloading music and their IP addresses or something like that
So I was just curious what podcho may have might be having
Or might be planning rather
In the area of listeners statistics
So I don't know if you can share anything with us right now
But I was just curious about that
All right great thanks Adam appreciate it
Again my name is Michael kicking bear with indigenous peoples music
All right Michael, thank you
Yes, I think well when it comes to statistics
And I think it's no secret at this point that we've
Going into partnership with limelight networks
To create the podcas delivery network the PDN as we call it
And so at the network level is where you can get the best
Statistics about you know all that stuff that I'm sure
Libs and provides equally as well because they're also
Sitting at the network level
What we've learned is it's really not so much about the
Information it's about how it's presented or how it's
Analyzed and
People process information in different ways
So the tool the last time I looked at it was really really
Really really spiffy you can actually create the report the way you
Want it in order segments
You know pie charts color bar graphs whatever all that stuff
You know so and we have a couple of examples of of layers
You get a dashboards when you log in
You can see the highlight reports that you're most interested in
And all that stuff I think is pretty well defined
And any statistical package with what's available
In weblog in for data as well as some network data
And maybe others some as a couple other things that
Most I think is all captured in the web server log
You know that that's one part of the report
The tools that you're talking about are much more interested in
Because I think what's really missing here is you know now you're just talking about
Computers connecting to a computer and passing off information about
It's about about about about the computer itself
It really doesn't say much about the operator
That's why we spend so much time on giving a place for your listeners to go
So that they can become involved with the show and with each other
And it's you know a very rudimentary form of that of course is a forum
You know where you can see who's active how long they've been active
If they're online right now, you know that kind of stuff is are the beginnings of tools
But I think we've taken that to a whole nother level
That's really where for me all the excitement comes in
Is that that you're going to be able to you know
To speak to your listeners know who they are or who they want to be
Who they want how they want to represent themselves
Again the connection between listeners themselves is great
And those those relationships
Really do create metrics that you can you can look at over time
And it works equally well with with the simpler
With you know proven stuff actually like forums
You know don and Drew have what 40,000 registered users at the forum all of whom are like 30,000 are active
That's a tremendous metric and then you can start to correlate stuff with the downloads etc
But I think the big the big thing that a lot of people are missing is everyone's talking
Still about subscriptions because of the underpinnings of podcasting and podcast delivery with RSS
And a subscribing to a feed but that really is not the same as a magazine subscription
First of all there's no cost involved at least typically there's no cost involved
And there's no information known about the subscriber
Very little information and no more than would show up in a web server log
So if you really want to connect and you really want to do things with your audience
Then you know we have to give you tools so that the audience members can make their own place within your show
Does it sound cryptic enough?
We're really working hard on it. Oh a quick blog for Heather and Janelle
If you haven't heard the show it's sponsored by a active view underwritten by a qview
I should say it's an active view show
But it's getting a lot of a lot of downloads a lot of people checking out their show
You can find it download.acview.com
Hi Adam my name's down long time listener
I've been interested in getting my own podcast going as has many of your listeners
And today I thought I'd have another browse around the PMN
Just something that you might want to get your voice to have a look at
When I was looking at the artists page
The page title is coming up as untitled document
It would probably be better and cleaner and more professional looking
If it had either the track title or perhaps the artist title coming up at the top
Surely it's just something that's been overlooked
I'm currently using Firefox. I'm not sure if that's the issue whether it works properly in the other browser
Following on from your conversation the other day about people listening to the daily source code
And other podcasts on devices other than iPods
I frequently use my Sony Ericsson K750
And play the daily source code through the speaker on that not using the headphones
But actually just having it set on the desk beside me
What I found recently and this may be since you've moved across to using cast blaster
Is that the volume of your show in general seems to have gone down a lot
I don't know whether this is something you can measure against a previous show
And either put me right or wrong
But I seem to have to have the volume turned a lot louder
In fact thinking of it
Even when I'm playing it on my computer now
If I'm listening to the daily source code and then have that ubiquitous you've got mail come up
It's always a lot louder than your recordings
Something you might want to look into
But thanks very much for the daily source code and great work you're doing towards podcasting
Thank you very much, bye
Well, I've been working on that
Ever since I started using cast blaster been very careful about the levels
And trying to get the sound to be just right and so a lot of people are given feedback for me
As I said it's very hard to get a reference
After you've recorded the show you hear you know on your headphones for almost an hour in a certain way
And then you know then you're listening to a speakers that sounds different on ear buds
It sounded different so I'm working on it
And I've been very careful because the first couple shows I did people complain about over modulating
And the sound was clipping so I'm really learning the meters inside this thing
And I'm not hitting zero db and in fact I'm probably around minus 10
According to the meters I'm just being really careful
So apparently it could still even be a bit louder yet
So keeping in the loop I've turned it up a bit let me know if it's better for you
Hey Mr. Adam curry what's up man
This is Simon Smith from the new music lab dot code
I'm not looking for a plug on your show
In fact I want to plug your show
So is there a promo for the daily source code
You would make my listeners really happy if I could give that a play on the new music lab
That would make them extremely happy if the pod father himself
To introduce the team from the bond safe music network
That's up to you
That's all I want to mean don't worry about
Rock on
Oh, you know there is no promo for the show
And I should do when I guess
It's a part of the new show site actually to have a promo so it'll look a lot better
Right now I'm also looking up a flight some virgin Atlantic see if I can make it back before Patricia has to leave
Let me see from New York to London
Departing on see if I departed Friday how late could I go Friday could I make it at the end they got triple miles this month
Hey hey wait let's go
Oh shoot
Oh no from London
Okay one way right from New York to London 17th February fine flights okay
Upper class
Oh yeah baby
Virgin upper class triple miles throughout the end of March matching the be it British airways promotions love that
Okay, come on website hurry up
Oh what's the latest one I like to go it
I could go at
Well Patricia could just leave if she could do if she could leave
Saturday morning I could arrive Saturday morning would be okay
And then she'd come back Sunday and then but then I might have to go back to San Francisco the week after
But at least I'd be back in and be able to help her out in the weekend
Okay
Oh shoot
Sorry we already did it one here's the
I had almost a lot
I'm in about the pot saved music network
Now I know a lot of people have been talking about pricing you know what the splits gonna be two ways splits but how about a three way split
That's right a three way split
I love three ways
Because you instead of affiliate links that go on your blog that lead to the pot saved music network
So if someone used your link they would get say five cents per song
Which may seem steep or may seem like now a lot but that'll definitely add up over time
Let's take your podcast for example in the source code you usually play about two songs per episode
It's two songs per episode five episodes per week if you're getting five cents a song
And someone is using your link every song that's 50 cents per week for doing basically nothing
Now I'm not gonna do the math but if you can give people the incentive to buy music from the pot saved music network
Why not do it?
By the way Adam using a brand new Intel iMac
20 inch cord duo and the brand new garage band bundled an iLat 06 to record this audio comment
All right, cool nice little fade up there
What a testimonial fantastic. Yeah, well, that's exactly the idea
So why don't we split it in half and split it in half and split it in half something like that
It doesn't matter we're gonna get this roll and so along with the previous comment about about the artist page on the pot saved music network
Yeah definitely and jersey Joe and Dan they are doing they're sending the whole right now
I think they're doing with podcast alley, but then they're doing going to the same thing with the pot saved music network
Sending it back to what we call the jig and aviation and they're going to rewire it all completely
You know massively scalable and and often and often running and we'll have a lot of the hopefully most of all of those things fixed
We're definitely tracking all of it and we'll eventually get to what what I call an affiliate link
Absolutely, but it's really a part of the larger idea of an unlabel and unlabel is not a record label
It's all the pieces of a record label all connected through you know one or multiple systems and I think that's exactly what we're putting together here
And just like rocket boom getting advertising primarily from people on the internet who's livelihood is on the internet on eBay will also be able to start our own economies
You know, this is important stuff and tomorrow
Just think I want to do it today just in case I am I'm not able to get out of show
Because of travel or whatever and I'm going to go see my mom. I told you that
I want to say a very very happy birthday to my long distance lover on the podcast and GB
I like the picture you said
It's love spiral loves your eyes
Let's play how it helps me so you just don't care the solid truth
You know what's in your mind I still smile
This kind of reminds me of the early days of the new millennium in Amsterdam with the chill trip hop
It's love spirals love survives you can find links to that song and just about everything else you hear on the daily source code of the pod save music network music dot dot show dot com
And that'll do it for today I'm kind of excited about taking cast blaster on the road with me because I'm just going to take the the wireless microphone which I'll be able to clip on and head set and the the Toshiba portujey
Without any extra weight so no mixers no CD drives any that stuff that's all I need I'm even considering not taking along the Mac actually but just so slow using the windows interface it's just so weird
Daily source code dot com is where you can find all the information about the show updated shows of course and the podcast feed or way to subscribe and add them to curry dot com is the email address for feedback check my web log as well curry dot com
And I'll see you guys tomorrow at some point after the flight bye