Delta Shara Charley 351, this podcast is brought to you by Earthling.
Some versions of this podcast mean being defensive, and it is intended for mature audiences only.
It's Friday everybody, time to party down.
Now we're better than a bit of a red guy.
We're better than a red guy.
This is the Daily Source Code.
Tab Lloyd vs. Corey, 2006.
All-rise.
Court is now in session.
This is an action news special report.
Now we take you live to Gilford England with
Our special car responded Roger Smalls.
What's that?
It wasn't loud out.
Alright.
Now we take you to our special car responded.
Commitage strip plugger.
Excuse me? What do you mean? He couldn't. All right. Let's take you live to the
podfather himself. Here's Adam Curry with decision 2006. Our green scene. Thank you
very much man. I came in through promos.podshow.com. Appreciate it. Perfect.
That's staging for the show today. Well, for those of you who've been following
the court case yesterday, the judgment was handed down by the court in the Netherlands
by the judge. Remember, it's a professional judge system. So not a jury of peers,
but a judge who was clearly not as well informed and had not gone into depth into
the material as I had hoped. And we're going to talk about that today. In fact, I just
got off the honker with Pete up and asked him to keep the satellite window open longer
today. So the folks on serious satellite radio can hear this as well. On that point,
for the serious folks today, we have Pacific Coast Hellway, East Radio, Don, and Drew,
also, which at all, rather for an NCC Chapman in this four hour block of time on serious
stars. Okay. So if you're new to the podcast, let me just run through the issue very briefly.
I know I have to reiterate this stuff once in a while, or more than once in a while. A Dutch
tabloid published pictures that were taken from my flicker account licensed under the creative
Commons attribution non-commercial share like and they publish those. Clearly a violation of copyright
and at the same time they published information about my daughter's school and the path that she
takes to school and how she gets to and from school, which I felt was and my daughter as well.
And most parents who have emailed me agree that that is definitely endangerment of a child.
So here's the verdict as it came down. And I'm paraphrasing. It's available in Dutch online in
many different places. Essentially the endangerment of Christina was completely dismissed and the
reasoning and I'm also paraphrasing. The reasoning according to the judges, you're in the public eye,
so you can expect that. On the what I still consider and what is basically the truth,
the theft of my property, which they used for commercial purposes in their magazine,
the judge ruled us following. Don't do that anymore. And if you do, you will be
find 1,000 euros, which is about $1,200, for each time you do use copyrighted work from Mr. Curry.
So I presume that that can be used in future case law against anyone who has protected their work
on the internet through the creative Commons license. So while it is a win for creative Commons
because it did hold up in court. And of course, their argument was, well, you know, it said this picture
was public and so we were confused. The judge says, well, you know, your professional organization,
you should know better. When I find very, so obviously the endangerment of Christina is unforgivable,
I feel. And the fact that the judge did not take my work, my property into protection
for future protection, I should say, by somehow sanctioning or penalizing the publisher or the magazine,
I think it's a bit of a loss. Now, I wasn't looking for money. Of course, all court cases,
at the end of the day usually civil cases revolver on money and that's kind of how you determine
whether you win a law. So the fact that I got no damages can be seen as a loss.
Now, here's my view on this. And I obviously have quite a number of things to say.
First of all, I believe the judge did a great disservice to the court, to herself and to the country
of the Netherlands. So this starts by a contradiction. How can you say that you have no protection
over your well-being or the well-being of your family because you are famous, because you have been
featured in magazines, television and other mainstream media? But at the same time, how can you say
that that is not valuable? These magazines clearly profit from highlighting celebrities,
from showing celebrities, from taking pictures, telling stories. It really takes the court and
its opinions back to the medieval times of court gestures. You know, court gestures were funny and
great and they got all kinds of cool things from the king. But they would chop us head off if they
felt like it. So I feel that there is a huge contradiction in what the judge is saying.
Now, a disservice to our country comes into play. You know, I'm outside of the Netherlands a lot
and whether it's in even as close as the United Kingdom but certainly in the United States and most
other countries in the world when they talk about the Netherlands and it used to bother me because I
know that the people of the Netherlands are not like this, but you know, on an individual basis.
But collectively, they're pretty quiet and don't really stand up for a lot or for themselves
very often. They talk about it a lot privately. But the Netherlands is primarily
note. If you say to anyone, hey, you know, how about Holland? What do they say? Oh, that's where you
can, that's where drugs are legal and prostitution is legal. Yeah, yeah, that's that's great.
Well, now you can add disrespect for art and creativity to that mix. And I believe that
this judgment, just looking from the comments that are public on my weblog and the email that I've
received, and this is coming from all over the world, people are saying, wow, this is not really
good for creative comments. This is not really good for protecting our content. Whereas the courts are
extremely good at protecting content of mainstream media and scaring people into submission. And
I should clarify something. You know, these lawsuits that you hear about these huge, you know,
$150,000 lawsuits, they really ever go to trial because here's how it works. A big company,
if you take their pictures and publish them, if you breach their copyright, if you, if you download
an MP3 file on copy it illegally and distribute it, what that usually happens is you get a call.
Now, the call is not from the judge. The call is from a collection agency, which works for the
big mainstream media companies. And they will scare you, scare you into eventually paying a fine,
which I think people wind up usually paying between $5 and $15,000 just to get the court case off
their back. So it's a settlement, but they scare people into it. Now, I don't have enough money to
scare any, any large publisher or, or, or, or, or magazine into submission. So I took the
recourse that I had and that recourse was through the courts. And well, there you have it.
If you take all these things into effect, it's no wonder. And this is the fact that people are
emigrating, are leaving the Netherlands in the highest numbers ever. Every year, there are more people
fleeing the country because of issues like this. Now, let's talk about talk versus action.
I'm a guy that comes from a long history of doers and in my view patriots. My family has
extremely extensive history of government work, public service, work at universities, education.
In fact, we, we have a word for it in our family. We call it the need road syndrome,
which is, uh, you have to be useful. You have to do something for your country.
You know, my parents grew up listening to John F. Kennedy say, ask not what your country can do,
ask what you can do for your country. And many members of my family, even my immediate family,
have gone through great sacrifice to be a doer and not just a talker. In fact, 99% of most people
I feel are all talk and no action. I'll give you a few examples of how I like to be a doer
and like to take action and not just be all about talk. The MTV lawsuit is an interesting case
where a huge corporation came down on me, tried to take something from me that they had allowed
me to use legally and I fought them and I fought them with everything I could, which at the time
consisted a lot of media, a lot of bad press, David and Goliath tactic was about all I had. I
certainly had very limited funds compared to Viacom. It's still wound up costing me about $400,000
to combat it and we settled. Other instances of doers, of doing stuff and not just talking
in the Netherlands. And by the way, one of the reasons I'm gone is because the following things happened
for years ago. I saw this user generated content coming together. I saw it happening. I knew
that what we had was tons of audio and video recording and editing equipment all within our own grasp.
I knew that it was only a matter of time before the bandwidth and the infrastructure would be there
for us to all have. And in fact, people in the Netherlands listening will remember me,
remember that I said, someday in the not too distant future, everyone will have their own radio
and television station. This was actually pre, it wasn't really pre-blocking or certainly pre-blocking
in the Netherlands. And so of course, with that comes their own print publication. I started a company
called Jambi, an acronym for Just Anarchy Made by You, invested millions of my, literally millions
of my own money in that. And we had a client for the Veronica Broadcasting Corporation. We had a
three-year deal. Think about it. Think about these guys. If they had stuck with the deal,
they put, there was some lawyer. They made their, their chairman. And he just decided to stop paying.
And he said, you're what courage you got so much money. One and two pay for it.
So he broke the, broke the agreement, a three-year deal, which would have put that organization
at the, at a leading position in the world of user-generated content and distribution.
I feel that I really, really worked very hard. And they pulled out, and of course, when you have
30 or 40 people and you have only one real source of income for that, things fall apart.
And what happens is all the people who talk and don't do, jump down my shit and call me a tremendous
failure. Another thing I did, I saw after terrible, terrible fire in Volandam in the Netherlands,
on New Year's Eve, where scores of children died and were burned beyond recognition,
that because of the laws in the Netherlands, emergency services helicopters could not get to these
children because they were not allowed to take off at night because they had the helicopter located
on top of the hospital in a residential area. They're not allowed to fly after 7pm.
I went to the authorities and I said, you know what, I mean to this helicopter stuff,
I have a little helicopter company. It would be beneficial to me, but I think even more beneficial to
all security and beneficial to all people if we could have a separate helicopter in Amsterdam
that did have 24 hour a day access specifically for issues of medical emergency.
What would what did the talker say? The talkers jumped on me and said, you just want to get some
place for rich people taxi cabs. Something to that effect. And by the way, that heli port is there.
It cost me hundreds of thousands of euros to go through all of the red tape. It took me
almost five years, but it's there. And you should go take a look at what lands there. Very few
rich people actually. Mostly it's incubator flights with children who need to be rushed to the hospital.
There's also they do a lot for it. It's crazy. They do a lot for baby seals. And that's where
the helicopters are stationed. And you know, and no one has ever said, oh, that was kind of good
you did that. And I'm not looking for that. I don't because that's my internal satisfaction.
Same thing with the MTV dot com domain name lawsuit. That was precedent setting.
Anyhow, people will look back and the way the record is usually written is whoever yells the loudest
or has the biggest megaphone can determine what history is, can write history. And so I'm not
someone who stood up for his rights or for a new territory that had to be discovered within
a cyberspace. Now I became the first squatter web logging in the Netherlands. I did a lot.
I was one of the first webloggers. I can't say the first because I wouldn't know that for sure.
But certainly I worked very hard on building the infrastructure for web logging in the Netherlands.
If you look at web-log.nl, which is in a way kind of the blogger of Holland, the blogger.com.
It was just a guy who would just start it up some stuff. And I was very quick to say, hey, you know,
you should really do RSS feeds because that's really what makes weblogging. Yeah, click and connect.
And he said, well, I don't really have a money for the bandwidth for people scanning all these feeds.
And I said, you know what, dump them on my server. So I really help get that going.
Now, the downside of all that is with the internet, talk has become even cheaper. It's even easier
to just talk. It's not, you can't just sit around and hang out at the bar. You know, you can.
But, you know, just saying, oh, oh, we should really change something. This is no good. This is really sucks.
And on the internet, now you can actually just sit at home and do that or do it from your mobile,
or wherever you feel like. And just talk. You know, and talk is cheap, my friends.
Doing is what it's about. So let's get back to the lawsuit.
This lawsuit was for two reasons for personal reasons. And I can't help the judge's decision.
Yeah, I could go to a higher court and try and prove the judge wrong. But that is really the culture of the
Netherlands. The culture of the Netherlands is, and you can ask any Dutchman about this,
they compare the population to blades of grass. And they say, if you stick your head or if your
blade of grass is a little bit higher than the rest, it will get chopped off. And they say that
with such conviction like it's almost a rule. For creative commons, I went to bat this time. It's not
just for me. It's for creative commons. We need to know that this stuff that our stuff is going to
be protected and that there is a value on our content versus the content of the mainstream media
companies. The cost of this lawsuit for me, I estimate, you know, I haven't received a billion,
but probably between six and eight thousand dollars. And what this lawsuit resulted in is pretty
much a pat on the head for all creative people on the internet. They are there. Okay, we understand.
In fact, the judge specifically said, because the pictures were actually really cute pictures
and vacation pictures, she didn't see any harm in the publication of them. She completely missed the
whole point. So it's clear that through the mainstream system, I'll just have to call it that,
we have no real recourse. And I still believe that we have to set some precedent about the power
of we the media and the power of what we can do with these tools. It's funny, I was reading
some, actually some gossip sites yesterday who were all reporting on the lawsuit.
And one of them recounted a story. Let me see, the story is probably, it's 20 years old this story.
Even more, maybe even older. This had probably happened almost 23 years ago. It was on the radio.
At the time, there was only one popular radio station throughout all of the Netherlands.
Forget the pirate radio stations, which, of course, I'd done all of my doing at as well.
Trying to change the media landscape. And at that time, Patricia and I had just hooked up.
And she was actually living in my apartment in Amsterdam. Now, there are rules, there are paparazzi
rules in the Netherlands, not very many. But one rule is you cannot take pictures or you cannot
publish pictures that are taken through a window into someone's home because that is then you are
violating someone's privacy. Now, in this particular case, this one photographer, a paparazzi photographer,
his name is Yopfunk Tellingon, hit out in garbage cans outside of my apartment for, he says two
or three days. It probably was two or three, at least two, but maybe three days. And he waited
and waited and waited until Patricia was on the sidewalk and I was hanging out of the window.
And I think I dropped the keys down to her. He got the picture. It was huge for him and published
widely. Now, of course, you feel, you feel shitty about that. And by the way, I have deep respect
for doers like that. I also have respect in a way for paparazzi in general who will go after
their target and take pictures. Now, there are limits. And I think I'm very clear about
following my daughter who really is outside of, you know, anything that you should be following
around at all. But I do have respect for someone saying, hey, I'm going to go get this picture
and I'm going to go travel to the United Kingdom. And I'm going to go wait until Patricia goes into
a parking lot and then I'm going to take a picture and I'm going to send it back and I'm going
to make some money off of it. Now, I mean, it's not a big social, you know, something that is
is good to society in general, but I do have to say I respect people who do something. Anyway,
so, of course, I had no recourse, but I figured at the time, you know what, let's have some fun
with this. Now, remember, this was the only popular radio station which had full national coverage
at the time. And so, I'm a radio show, which is called Curry and Fun Inkel.
I said, hey, you know, since I can't really do anything against this, why don't you
listeners, why don't you go down to his store? He had a photo store. And why don't you hang
outside of his house for a couple days and then take pictures? And the send-up to me and, you know,
the funniest picture will reward, I think, with a t-shirt or whatever. Gosh, it was amazing.
We got thousands and thousands of pictures and this guy was completely overrun. What he felt
for the first time is what it's like to be stalked by paparazzi. And I must say, we've actually
become quite friendly with each other throughout the years and not a meeting goes by that we don't
bump into each other that it doesn't say, man, you remember that? That was really funny. Boy,
I learned to lessen that. So, to the people of the Netherlands, and again, I have complete faith
in the people of the Netherlands in the individuals and people who are online, people who have
grown up with weblogs, people who are in cyberspace, who are actually overturning important
or digging up important facts and bringing them into the mainstream eye.
I've never asked for anything. Ever. And I would like to ask you to do something for me, just so
we can have some fun with this whole situation. And maybe, just maybe show the gossip magazines,
show the paparazzi's and show the court that they're sorely mistaking about the power and the
value and the values of what we're doing online. And I'm looking at, I'm looking at, I'm looking at
fuckpuntanelle. Webstrapeurlochpuntanelle, vidhate.com, rate to cool.com. You guys,
dipspotting.nl. Why don't we show this mark from the Linda, what it's like?
He feels that he can send people off to go stalk my daughter and follow her around and publish
where she goes to school and how she gets there. What if we did that to him?
Now, it's very easy. He works at an office right near the highway at Outox. He goes,
I don't know where he lives, but it's not so hard to follow him. It's the same thing they did with
my daughter, follow him home. Let's get some pictures of him and his Russian boyfriend.
Now, to make this a little more interesting, I was thinking, why don't we have a little competition?
And let's place the same value on this material that the court places on our material, which is
a thousand euros. So that would be $1,200. So we'll do a competition.
Get me pictures of this guy. The best picture, which can be judged by fun factor, by
by a whole bunch of different factors, but it will be judged by the number of comments
placed next to each individual picture on the weblog. We'll win $1,000 euros. From me,
I will pay it to you. I think everybody knows that I'm good for it and you can ask around,
I always pay my bills. Then we'll have a second part of the competition for people who are
doers, but maybe they don't want to get out of the house for the best photo mashup of Mark
Fondalinda, a thousand euros for that as well. And again, it'll be judged publicly the most
comments win. And that will be the best therapy for me. That's all I ask. It's real simple.
Let them know the pod people are here.
Sing up the fee. Be in the right to me. Everything I need. Better than the old dead frequency
from underground, hooked on the sound. Come set the fire, burn the old dial. A lot of time is now.
To the bottom, sick will call you and show you even time to take it away soon.
Can you find me for taking it over? Can you find me for taking it over?
Can you find me for taking it over?
Can you found me for taking it over?
I knew I'd take it all out
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I was gonna bring it with me, be with me, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
solicitor or lawyer for the daily source code said that just might not be a very good
idea.
Uh, thanks.
Jersey Todd.
I appreciate it.
More history in the making today.
Someone is torturing Perry Dosse.
Cutting into him, piece by piece, slicing him open, spilling his blood, removing parts
of his body.
A little bit at a time, who would do such a thing to poor Perry Dosse?
None other than Perry Dosse himself.
If he doesn't start cutting faster, he won't make it through the day.
Infection is the horrifying new podcast novel for me.
Scott Sidler, author of Ancestor and Earth Corps.
Infection drops March 11th.
So sign up now at scotsiggler.potshow.com or subscribe to the feed directly at feeds.
Dotfeedburner.com slash scotsiggler.
You've heard of Web 2.0.
It's publishing 2.0.
Scott Sidler, burning a path, a trail for all of us to follow as how publications, how books
are brought into the world.
What is it?
It drops tomorrow.
I love the infection.
Drops tomorrow.
Subscribe now.
You can find it at scotsiggler.potshow.com.
If you rewind your MP3 player, then you can hear the feed burner address as well.
I'm subscribed.
Cannot wait.
The daily source code has this quite a genesis to the name of the show.
Of course, daily source code was originally made up to appeal to the developers of
the podcast receivers.
Primarily, I think when Andrew Grummit came on the scene with his team for the lemon receiver,
which now, of course, is juice.
I thought to myself, after having gone through the pain of first learning how to code software
and then building a podcast aggregator with basically almost no content to test it against,
at least not regular content.
I thought to myself, gee, you know, what a good deal.
If these developers are so gung-ho, why don't I give them something to work with every single day?
So that was the daily part.
And source code, duh, that appealed, hopefully, to the developers.
Now, as we as podcasting grew and as many,
the nano came on the scene actually, I think that's what we started the nano, which is a screenless
not the nano.
I'm sorry, the iPod mini.
Was the mini?
Yeah, the mini, the one without a screen.
As those came on to the scene, we started tagging our podcast.
So I used to call it, you know, daily source code for, and I'd give the date.
And I didn't even start with numbers.
I think as I wasn't tracking the episode numbers until somewhere on 150 or whatever.
And that just became, you know, such a long intro.
And then I said, you know, why would we just call it DSC?
And then as I was more into flying, I started using the pilot speak and kind of as a,
as a goof, I said, all right, it's the Delta Sierra Charlie.
All I would car is that pulling up.
No, it's not for us.
I called the Delta Sierra Charlie.
And of course, people took that and started saying, on the Charlie, which is also by the way,
very common in aviation, where as long as you're in the right air space.
And you know, the tower knows who you are, you know, people will use all kinds of different
identifications.
And from the Charlie, we got to the Chuck John, to the Chuck and to the Charles,
and all that.
And then, of course, we found out that some people use Charlie to describe other things.
And this is not entirely family's safe what you're about to hear.
But worth listening to regardless.
Hi Adam, it's Charles from Petictionary,
but the word Charlie and penis and vagina.
Two tracks here.
I look at my enormous collection of dictionaries and I find that the word Charlie has been applied
to quite a few choice things over the years.
A style of beard, a woman's breast, the North Vietnamese, during the Vietnam War,
a stupid person, a white person, if you're black, cocaine, a night watchman, a fox, a backpack,
a coward.
No, where do I find it used to refer to penis?
Which brings me to the second track.
You advocate that parents should use the correct names for children's sex organs.
I couldn't agree more, but you, dear Adam, are using the wrong word when you call the gross
privates of a vagina.
It just so happens that this very morning, I began a new podcast in addition to my daily
one.
The new one is called Carnal Knowledge, and here is a sample that speaks directly to the
point.
Here I'm talking about that really successful show of the vagina monlogues.
The whole thing is based on the wrong word.
Listen to this.
You cannot love the vagina unless you love hair.
Many people do not love hair.
My first and only husband hated hair.
The thing they're talking about isn't actually the vagina.
The vagina is an internal part of a woman's body.
The vagina is named from an identical Latin word that the Romans used to describe the
scabbard they kept their knife or sword in.
Obviously, the vagina is named as a sheath or scabbard in relation to men's penises
representing the sword.
The vagina on a woman is not visible.
It doesn't have hair.
It's the passage between the uterus and the visible and hairy.
The reason the show is called the vagina monologues isn't that Eve Ensler didn't know
the difference.
It's that she was a smart marketer.
The correct name for the body part and question is the vulva.
I'm sure you knew that.
But as Dr. Harriet Learner says, most people think a vulva is a brand of Swedish car.
You can hear the whole thing by looking for it at podcast alley.
I've submitted to iTunes too, but it's not been about six hours, so it hasn't shown
up yet.
Go on podcast alley for being so fast.
You can search on Carl Knowledge or on Charles Hudson.
Thanks for listening.
Yo, Charles.
Thank you very much from predictionary.com fantastic.
You know, speaking of vulvos, just briefly just want to stray for a second here.
That new or a gummy thing that Microsoft announced yesterday.
I watched the whole scobal video on Channel 9.
That's the Microsoft developers network Channel 9, which I think is great by the way.
What a great way to market a product.
Have a scobal with this camera.
Go talk to the product manager.
Although it looks very interesting, and it seems like it might be just perfect to combine with cast blasts.
I'm not quite sure because I don't think it has audio in and out points.
It does have built in microphones and stuff like that, but I don't know if it'll take it.
I don't think it'll take an external sound card.
It'll take USB, but USB always has latency, so that kind of bites.
Why does that thing look like a vulvo?
This is the one thing that a company like Microsoft does not have in its DNA.
Style, style, and beauty.
That's what makes the iPod so cool.
The iPod now, of course, has become cool for what's on it, and not what it looks like.
I was like, yeah, I'll probably buy one of those if it has the right inputs, but God, it's just so ugly.
So non-stylish and typical, typical.
By the way, on the daily source code, we break for network members.
Steve Webb has something very important he wants to share with us.
Hey, out of Steve Webb here, man, $5,000 a night for a hotel room and average hotel room.
I tell you what, man.
Come to Southern California.
I will rent you my house for substantially less than that.
I'm in Southern California, as you know, I'm about an hour from Palm Springs.
I'm an hour from the beach.
I'm an hour from the mountains.
I'm about an hour from Disneyland.
I'm about an hour and a half from Universal Studios.
I've got a brand new pool of my backyard.
You're welcome to use, man.
I'm telling you, I can really cut a deal for you.
So think about that.
Number two, as far as aluminum and aluminum goes.
Aluminium is an element in the periodic table.
So if you're talking about that element,
Aluminium is the correct pronunciation.
If you're talking about the alloy that most all of us come in contact with everyday,
that's aluminum.
It's ALU-I-M-N-U-M aluminum.
So the Brits are right when they're referring to the Aluminium,
if they're talking about the element.
But I have to say that, you know, I've got lots of British listeners too,
and I don't want to offend anybody.
But aluminum is the correct way to talk about the alloy.
You know, actually, I've gotten so many feet.
First of all, thank you very much for the offer Steve.
I really appreciate it.
That's very kind of you.
But we can't even get flights to California.
That's how bad it is.
All of London is like, well, all of Britain looks like they won the lottery, man.
There's no more flights available even in that direction.
Patricia did call her record boss,
a villain from Cote.
He has hotels and golf courses in Portugal.
Of course, he's a mainstream record guy.
And used to be really active.
They have a long lasting love affair.
And he said that he would hook us up,
and I can definitely get to transportation down there.
So I do appreciate it.
Many, many people sent in, many, many dictionary entries,
and apparently aluminum or aluminium,
whether you're talking about the element or the alloy,
are both correct.
It's just a difference in pronunciation.
Let's see.
Next, one other thing.
You've often talked about how words are just words to you.
And for the most part, I would say that there are some words
that I choose not to use.
But when it comes to using the name Jesus Christ,
Adam, he means something to me.
That's a real person.
How would you like it if every time,
you know, I smash my thumb or something like that,
I go, oh, Adam Curry.
I mean, you didn't have anything to do with it.
And in most of the cases where you've used that name recently,
he didn't have anything to do with it.
So if you could be just a little bit more sensitive in that area,
I would appreciate it.
And I'm sure that there's lots of other listeners
that would appreciate it as well.
So just to be a little sensitive there in that area,
I'd appreciate it, my friend.
Thanks, Adam.
Thank you very much, Steve.
Well, first of all, I apologize.
Didn't mean to offend you.
And I do understand what you're saying.
Let me tell you where it comes from.
You know, having been in broadcasting and having to have lived
with broadcasts, rules for half of my life.
It's so liberating to do a podcast that, you know,
I kind of drop all the filters, you know, everything.
And that includes speech that I might not use in a public place.
And of course, although in smaller groups,
I just tend to speak the way I speak.
And that using Jesus Christ's name in vain,
I guess is the correct way to put that.
I can understand that's offensive to you.
However, Steve, I do want to say I think that that was a brilliant
marketing play by Jesus Christ.
Think about it.
For all these years, whenever something bad happens,
when you smash your thumb, people say that.
And of course, I didn't, you know, it was in,
I've been influenced by my parents or a television or whatever.
So, you know, I didn't make this up on myself.
This has been going on for, oh, let's say maybe 2000 or some odd years,
perhaps.
Personally, I would love it.
I would love it.
It would be fantastic.
People, the next time, something happens.
And you want to say Jesus Christ, say Adam Curry.
Please, I beg of you.
If you smash your thumb, yes, say Adam Curry.
Because it is one of the reasons I believe that his name is still out there.
So feel free to do that.
I do not mind.
I really don't.
I would see, in fact, I would, it would be, I would find it a great honor.
And I'm not comparing myself to anyone else.
I'm just saying, I would find it an honor.
If in 2000 years from now, when something goes incredibly wrong,
and they say someone smashes their thumb or bumps into something or
stubs their toe or whatever, they say, I'm Curry.
I hope I was successful in that programming.
Steve, I appreciate it.
Point well made.
Adam, this is season from Gragradio.
I was listening to DSC 350 today.
Okay, make that Charlie Cha Cha, Charles 350.
And I heard the feedback about your pronunciation of controversy.
Now, I'm just wondering if I were to move to Italy and started using, say, the term
Chao?
Would I piss off a bunch of Americans?
Or if I moved to Japan and started saying,
how crazy is it to think that one would not pick up some language and accents
from one's own environment?
If only because it's fun to do so, my son is a Colorado boy,
but it didn't take long after his move to Texas for him to be saying,
y'all, he's using other Texasisms.
So, Adam, do your thing, baby, we love it.
And here's a little shameless plug for Gragradio.
After you've finished listening to the Chuck E. Chuchu,
come on out to Gragradio.com and check out an episode of Gragradio with Doug and Susan.
Right on, Susan, thank you.
I like your voice, by the way.
Very husky and sexy.
Very, very nice.
Ah, Adam Curry.
Reminds me of Denny Crane.
Okay, let's see, we're almost at the end of today's show.
Um, we're going to close the set.
Yes, I paid up saying that we have about 30 seconds for the satellite window to close.
So, those of you check it out on stars and serious.
Hope you enjoyed today's podcast.
There's lots of cool stuff going on with podcast and come to podshow.com,
dailystoresco.com, to find out more, to listen to more.
Or just stay tuned right now for a Mark Yoshimoton M.Coff
and the help players coming up with Pacific Coast Hellway.
Um, Madge Weinstein with East Radio, Don and Drew,
and then Wichita Rutherford and we wanted up with CC Chap,
and you guys have a great weekend drive home safely,
and hopefully we'll meet back here on Monday.
So, everybody, wait goodbye to our satellite friends, bye-bye.
And Steve, you may want to turn the, uh, you may want to turn the sound down.
Hello, Adam's Curry.
It's Madge Weinstein of East Radio.com.
You're favorite lesbian on the internet.
I have a boner to pick with you.
What is all this bullshit about calling your show the Charlie?
That is the most annoying, heterocentric, male oriented society,
divergenating, well, I want to say the opposite of demasculating,
but you're divergenating me.
I think that's the word.
I mean, why do you have to call your show Charlie?
It's so stupid.
It's just so macho, bravado.
It's so soccer.
It's so I went to Iraq, but I didn't fight anything.
I just combed my hair and rode on a helicopter.
It's just so ridiculous.
Don't call it the show.
And besides, the Charlie, he's what they call stop for a second.
Madge, uh, I beg to differ on the Iraq thing.
I don't care what you say.
Again, I did go to Iraq.
I did meet with the Iraqi people.
I did form my own opinion, and you didn't.
Pain in the England.
So I don't know if you're making one of these drug references or what,
but it's got to be stopped the Charlie.
Why can't you call it something feminine like, um,
like the god, the Esther or the goddess or mother nature or my vagina.
No, you can't name it after my vagina.
I mean, whatever, it's bullshit.
Anyway, and the other thing is this,
it's so, your show is becoming more and more sexist.
This Metro sexual business.
What is that about?
And why, um, why do you have to talk about shaving for men only?
How come you don't talk about vaginal shaving?
How come you don't want to know how, what are the things I have to go through once a year
when I shaved my vagina to go to the Bahamas?
How come you don't want to know about that?
All you want to know is about men shaving.
You know why?
Cause you're a tranny fucker.
That's why you're a fucking tranny fucker.
You're a pervert, Adam's curry.
You're a goddamn fucking pervert.
I'm sure Patricia will appreciate that.
And I'm sure that she'll have plenty to say to you,
and by the way, why don't you come back to me
when you actually have grown a charlie worth mentioning?
Okay?
Oh, one other thing about,
remember we're still talking about doers and talkers.
A lot of banter on the boards about download with Heather and Junel,
which is a podcast underwritten and sponsored by AccuView Contact lenses.
It's gotten so bad now, particularly people who hang out at podcast pickle,
which I've decided I'm just not going to read any more boards,
podcast alley or podcast pickle.
And the people who are doing this, they know what I'm talking about,
they talk so much trash about this podcast.
And it's so evident that they have never even listened to it.
They're so lazy.
They'd rather just spew off a few lines of garbage
without even having listened to the show.
It is not scripted.
Yes, it's completely underwritten by AccuView.
There's a reason for that.
These girls, and you're so hurtful to the talent on the show.
They are just doing a job, right?
That's nothing wrong with it.
No one died and made the podcasting rules of what can't.
Podcasting is a technology.
It's not that there's certain rules of what you can and can't do.
Go listen to it for a change.
Listen to the show download.acuView.com.
It's not for 13 year old boys.
It's for 13 year old girls.
It's a fun show if you want to talk trash amongst girlfriends and talk about boys.
And yes, they talk about acuView lenses.
They're sponsor.
So stop it already.
Grow up, please.
I had a visit to Joe from the small world podcast here.
You know, every time you hear your listeners talk about things like DRM,
wiretapping, or companies like AOL, taxing, or emails, I get so mad.
I want to hurt my eye-potted someone.
Let me take a deep breath.
That's better.
Today, in the small world, I'll be talking with Mitchell Shapineck who wrote the end of the
blog sphere about a topic that's been discussed in the DSC.
How telecommunication companies are pushing for a legislation to create a multi-tiered
internet, effectively owning the web.
So I thought I'd turn excerpt of the interview with you.
My fellow Delhi source code listeners.
There's a very serious threat, really right now.
In fact, as I speak, and in the coming next month or two, the legislation that's being crafted
in the halls of Washington, D.C.
that would take the bulk of the control of the internet away from in users,
and into the hands of the major table and telecommunication companies.
Companies like AT&T and Verizon and Comcast and Balsal,
who basically want to turn the internet into their own kind of private commercial
feast up.
I think the biggest thing of what people can do is to learn about the matter and spread the
word.
When people know about these issues and know that people can do something about these issues,
it's pretty much gravy after that.
If you feel, as I do, that it's an issue that net neutrality and related issues
regarding the future of the internet and ultimately the future perhaps of the entirety of the
United States, get involved in some of the organizations that campaign for the working
on these efforts.
I'll mention freepress.net.
National lobbying group called Common Cause.
Their website is common cause.org.
Then more and spread the word about the issue about its importance,
no matter how you might feel about it.
If you'd like to hear the rest of the interview, you can download the show at smallworldpodcast.com.
Thanks Adam, and I hope the vacation works out.
Yeah, thank you very much, buddy.
The podcast Paul here in the UK sent me a Skype message this morning.
I replied, but I guess he was already off to work.
The message said, Adam, have you heard about this?
The UK government wants to all podcasters to register themselves.
They'll have to pay 100 pounds, and if they don't, and they're caught, then they will have to pay
1000 pound fine.
When does it start this registration?
Well, April 1st.
Yeah, Paul, I don't think you're an idiot.
Please don't think that I am.
That's clearly the lamest April Fool's joke I have ever heard of.
Just going back to, back to download with Heather and Janelle.
Doers and trash talkers.
Okay, you can sit there and talk and say it sucks,
and the marketing is bad, and it's a horrible idea,
or you could get up off your lazy ass, go out, and go do your own show,
and show how it's supposed to be done.
And many of you do that, and I choose not to listen,
because I don't think that what you're doing is cool,
but I don't trash you for it.
God, that's so stupid.
You know, here we are all infighting on these stupid message boards.
It's just, ah, they disgust me.
And I'm just tired of it.
I really am.
Now luckily, you'll all have something to talk about.
Hey, let's end the show on a high note, shall we?
This is a song that always gets me feeling really good and pumping for the weekend.
The natives of a new song.
And people.
Yeah, that's you too.
Out there on the pickle and on the alley.
We're all just people.
People are in using your hand.
There's music playing in your head.
So listen.
Oh, listen.
You're out of reward.
I said.
There's music playing in your head.
There's tension.
Oh, you got to use your tension.
You got to keep lagging about music, but
So listen.
Well listen.
You're out of reward, I said.
There's music playing in your head.
Now with that, we come from.
Is it all in the mind?
Is it the reasons to my whole, the act of imagination?
Disign, you see?
It's completely in the mind.
There's that soundtrack to my activities.
And it was in the breeze, at our first birthdays, all in knees, in now.
Singin' this song and you can't hope what's singin' long
No witchers, it's one of those demons that let you know
You were born, yes it's a
A stand-roove that's guaranteed, all you mood
Every school starts realising children
Deeply consume my people
We both are who people are in music in your head
They're music playin' in your head
So listen, all the less I do, I will refer to them
They're tension, all you can't do
You're the 10 times you'll keep that music
They gotta keep that music fit
So listen, all the less I do, I will refer to them
They're music playin' in your head
Why can't you stay, you'll find a tool
Then all come, go, man, add a tool
You've got to check the coordinates
I've got a lot to learn from you, got to learn from the limitations
And hit rid of your expectations except
I've got to learn from you, got to learn from the limitations
I've got to learn from you, got to learn from the Principality
And hit rid of your expectations except
I've got to learn from you, got to learn from the limitations
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah yeah, no, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, sure, yeah
Oh yeah, okay, that's it. Boy, this was really cathartic. I felt really good. That's what I do it for. Just get some shit off my chest. I feel wonderful
Hey, I'm looking forward to a great weekend. I hope you have a great weekend. If you think I'm a dick, just remember
I'm only human
Adam at curie dot com daily source code dot com and if you see all kinds of weird stuff with file names and stuff like that
Obviously what we're doing right now is working on the podcast delivery network. So things might break things might fart all over the place
But that's always what the daily source code has been about it's a great testing ground. We've got some volume
So we can really see if things break apologies for that. We are working on on everything. See you on Monday everybody take care
Get this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network from podjo and limelight networks
I love it