From the Kuri Cottage Hill for the UK, from the Kuri condo, San Francisco,
more from the Kuri cockpit and skies above, wherever Adam might be.
There's always the daily source code in source code.
This is episode number 42 with Adam Kuri.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass,
then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
It's all okay, so don't worry about me
Cause I can cheer and find a way to make you feel alright
So here we go, I think I'm ready
Here we go, here we go, here we go
I think I'm ready, here we go
I think I'm ready, I think I'm ready
I think I'm ready
I can't just see how we all run down here
I'm flat to me, so I'm gonna make you risk to me real
You think it's all okay, cause you can see the light
Life and death, through the days that I get straight to the night
You think it's all okay, so don't worry about me
Cause I can cheer and find a way to make you feel alright
It's all okay, so don't worry about me
I think I'm ready, I think I'm ready
You think it's okay because you can see the light
Lock it in, do the days when I can't sleep in the night
You think it's okay so don't forget about me
Cause I'm gonna chill and find a way to make you feel alright
Make you feel alright
Oh yeah
Yeah
I make you feel alright
That's what I'm talking about
Bang tango
It's all okay
From the pod save music network
Dude
Good to hear from those guys again
Bang tango
Late 80s
I think late late 80s
Somewhere in a box
I have a bang tango leather jacket
I think I have it
I might have given it away at one point
I don't know
I had so many leather jackets
I was like my thing for a while
Everyone would give me these awesome leather jackets
Jeff Hamilton
He's still around
Make leather jackets
He's one of the most beautiful others
Bang tango
On the pod save music network
Everybody how you doing
It is a very, in fact it's so sunny
There we go
We're gonna pull the shade down here
In the Curry condo studio
Beautiful day in San Francisco
Which of course is typical
It's the last day that I'm here
I'm feeling actually pretty damn good
Which is also typical
I'm seeing everyone
I'm seeing them dropping like flies now
This freaking flu
And it's a rough one
It's one of those where you get a throat ache
You get stuffy, you get a headache
Your body starts to ache
People are just dropping left and right
With this crap now
So if you feel it coming on
Get some of that
What is that shite
That everyone told me I should take after it was too late
The airborne
That's right, airborne
I guess I'll pick some up for the trip back
I think now I'm immune for the bug
Foo bar Friday
If you're new to the show
Foo bar stands for fucked up beyond all repair
And when you hear the stuff that you guys have made
And sent in today
You're gonna feel like you're a part of the Foo bar
Festivities for sure
Thanks to young pull-out by the way
For the opening of today's program
A nice generic one
I can use it anytime
Just let me lay down kind of
Not, well I would take ground rules
But just basic premise for an opening
I love it when you send me different openings for the show
And if I have more than one
I just play them all
You know, I love them
They're short, they're funny
It's not a plug opportunity
A lot of people heard my call the other day
And yesterday and said
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah
We're gonna send them an opening for the show
And then it starts off like
Hey, this is so and so
From the so and so podcast
That's not how I want to start my freaking show
You know, if you send me something
And you know, something that I can use on the show
I'll plug your stuff
But just send that separately
Don't put it into the opening
It just doesn't work that way
Oh shoot, yes
It's Friday
Amy Mac
Here to shape up my ass
Before I go home
So Patricia can
Adam
Yes
Amy Mac
Amy could meet up for another live show
But as you were returning to San Francisco
I was heading home to Nashville for a few days
Not a problem, honey, bud
What do we got going?
Like sighted, it's always good to be home
Even if it is just for a few days
Not here
I know what you mean, I want to go home too
But anyway
I was flipping through a fitness magazine on the plane
And found today's move
Oh, okay
What's today's move?
So good, I'm excited
Alright, I'm ready
However, it does require a prop
Oh shoot
What?
What do we need?
Do you have a chair handy?
Uh, you hold up
A kitchen or desk chair would work fast
Oh my god
I got myself all situated
Wait a second, Amy, I'll take off my bathroom
Okay
Ready?
Yes, what am I doing?
Good, now stand facing the back of the chair
Uh, okay, let me smooth the mic
Take your left leg over the right side
And swing it over the chair
Bring it back down to the left
What?
Back to the back
Now the right leg goes to the left
And swings over the chair
Oh yeah, I feel that already
Okay, now alternate back and forth
Eight times
Yes, eight times
Let's hear you count
Go
Try not to use too much momentum
Really control that leg that flies over the chair
For bonus, squeeze the stomach too
Are you breathing?
Yes
You can keep your hands fisted
And close for stability
But number you want
Keep it strong, don't whip out
This is a whole lower body workout
So you should feel it in your butt, legs, stomach, and your heart
And your heart rate should be off to the races
All right, great job
Remember, if you need a mattress course
Ask hercise.podshow.com
Launches on Tuesday the 24th and starts with day one
Yes, thank you Amy
All right, this is Amy Mack
And until next time
Thank you so much
Oh, Amy
That was kind of fun
I have a rather high back chair
I have
Of course I have long legs, but oh man
That was a
That's a real workout there
Okay, put the bathroom back on
Oh, don't worry
I had
Other clothes on underneath
You don't have to be too grossed out, okay?
I was not sick, I just got to catch my breath
I had been a very ill man, you know
Takes a second here
Okay, let's check the phone lines
265-6357
Put a plus one in front of it
If you want to be able to reach that from anywhere
In the world from your mobile phone
Plus one two one
265-6357
People talking about some stuff
Hi Adam, so it's just a very windy
And traffic just picked up a bit
I took all of that
Listen, Spender
Okay, look fun, you're going to get yourself some
Okay
And the time you haven't used someone so far
I respect that, that's a real good
I'm sure Bill Hitch wouldn't have approved
But hey, he's dead
So
You've got people floating in now
I'm a massive fan of diet coke
But I have to say it's really not good for me
And I hope in the one day I will find out
That I'm not shooting blanks
And they'll have to have some kids
But if you have diet coke and you're adding
Another fake sweetener
What I'm telling you is it can someone else me that
And they've been health system
On this sweetener
That are independent of the manufacturer
I'm just curious
Initiatives are really good products
Then I might end up investing in it myself
Let me tell you something
I love that product
I really do
We have it at the office
And we have
Hazelnut in the French vanilla
For some reason we don't have
All three flavors
But I have
Particularly now that we have had this
We have one of those copper chino machines
Where you put in
If you want to make copper chino, you have to put in a
Creamy packet first
And then you've got to put in the espresso packet
After that and we were out of the creamy stuff
So that's kind of what makes it
Part of the taste with this particular coffee machine
So I spent some time yesterday
Mixing up the
French vanilla
And the Hazelnut
And it kind of gave me on a regular
Cup of coffee, it gave me a
almost like a pseudo-copuccino taste
Which is kind of nice
I do have a complaint though
We have the
The long
Splendip packets, which are
The kind you'd probably see
In a cup at a restaurant
The long thin ones like a tube
I can't get these freaking things open
I literally wind up using a knife
Two times out of five to get this packet open
I know there are other packets that
It comes in but I don't know if this is the
Industrial size or the enterprise version
But I just can't get them open
I just can't get them open
The old confused me don't French vanilla
Why is it what's French about vanilla?
Why is it called French vanilla?
You know the US
How shut up?
It's not so safe
You know what I do
I have a friend across the pond
Call it French vanilla
I guess someone did want to know
Everyone does
Any road
I don't know
I would sell you on a folder
But I already told you
And
I guess I'll just sign up with any of the
I'm
I know who this is then
PW biggest fan sure I know who you are
Yeah, that's a very good question
I have no idea why it's called French vanilla
I'm sure someone out there has an idea why
Yeah, why isn't vanilla
Is more something for the
Coco producing companies I would say
And the vanilla producing companies
Contra companies countries
I have no idea
French vanilla
Well, I'm sure there's some history to it
I'm sure there's plenty of coffee drink
Because out there who can help us
Okay, so this morning I woke up
I was really really excited
I saw an email from Carmen Tyler
With an attachment
Now, of course, we know who Carmen Tyler is
She is the former Miss Louisiana beauty queen
And she has a couple of songs
And the positive music network of players
Several times on this show
And of course, I've been known to ask her for naked pictures
And so when I see an email from Carmen Tyler show up
With an attachment, you can imagine
I was like, I think I'm just going to lay in that a little bit longer
And open up this email and see what
Because that's what I prep my show in bed
Like 6 a.m.
Let me see what Carmen is sending
Oh, this would be perfect for Fubar Friday
And well, it wasn't a picture
But it was this
Hey, this is Carmen Tyler
And I have no idea what I am doing
So I'm trying to do podcasts
Just go to Carmencast.putshow.com
Bring on the Velcro
I don't have ADD
I just get bored releasing
And my brain goes in million different
Corrections at one time, which is just absolutely crazy
No one wants to be inside my head
Oh my god
That is so crazy
I can't believe you just said that
M-Y-N-K-A-S-T dot putshow.com
Carmen Tyler doing a podcast
Welcome, girl
Welcome
Fantastic
The Carmencast
I love it
And you've got the voice for it
And I love the
You know the promo
I was rocking out
Fantastic
Love it
I'll be sure to put a link in the show notes
The Carmencast
Yeah
Early in the week I told you that New York State is after me
Has it worn out for me?
Not from my arrest
I don't think I haven't heard back yet
From my lawyers
Yeah
You know the kind of lawyers where you got to send a big check first
They're trying to get back taxes from me
Which would be interesting since I already proved to them
Four years ago that I haven't lived in New York since 1987
And I think I've paid all my taxes since then
So of course I was kind of curious
If anyone knew what's going on with New York State
And oh yeah
Oh yeah
You've been tracking the IRS
I haven't been working in New York
And I just didn't know about these New York State tax guides
They're so desperate that they go sit down
And enjoy these shopping malls
And try and collect sales tax
That happens every year
It's Christmas
Crunchy
Bahamburg
Yeah
And I think they're just they are over zealous
Yeah, it's good I guess
We don't want people evading taxes
It's just a little tiresome when I have to keep proving that I don't live in New York
And I've not lived in New York and don't own New York anything
Yeah, when it comes to taxes
I own New York a lot
But not money for taxes
I'll keep you updated on that
Played that Jason Calacanis imitation of me yesterday
Oh man that really sets in people
Come extra
Hi Adam
I see that Jason Calacanis is keeping your ass
So let me tell you about this piece of scum
He not only posted lies about me on his blog
But he also stolen my comic strip
Remove copyright from it
And play stayed on his server
Furthermore
Stilling is repeating pattern in life of this Bastard
Jason Calacanis
Some examples
Why Jason Thif Calacanis claims that paper post is wrong
He said it was from an gadget
Accepting bribes from Microsoft
And I have proof of it
Wow
Come extra blogger
Them's fighting words man
Hold on a second
He's a thief
He steals content
I've heard you complain about that before
I have heard you complain that he took one of your comic strips
And hosted it on his own server
And took out your copyright
But what he's saying he takes
And gadgets taking bribes from Microsoft
I mean
I guess that would be to put in stories about their stuff
And you have proof
I say bring it on out
Bring the proof out
Come extra blogger
Jason Calacanis never did anything himself
He just steals other people's content and ideas
Like it is with sitting content in the case of an gadget
That is destroying blogger's fear
And many other web blogs of the web blogs in component that now is owned by AOL
He's destroying the blogger's fear
Jason Calacanis
I had no idea
You're so evil
He is sitting also other people's ideas
Like it is in the case of Netscape
With money of our always trying to kill dick.com
I got to stop you there
CSB come on man
That's not stealing an idea
That's improving upon an idea
That's what the world is built on
Is building on other people's ideas
He didn't steal it
I got a disagree with you there
But I do like the fact that you're laying into him like that
Jason Calacanis is a crook on many levels
And he was and is destructive to blogosphere
I understand Adam that you need to keep contacts
Jason Calacanis for business reasons
But please take into account that he is not a good guy
That he pretends to be
And fuck you Jason Calacanis
So bye Adam
Strawberry Kerry
Yo
I hope Jason responds with an audio comment
For someone who doesn't like being called a stalker
CSB
Yo you got some pretty harsh words
A crook criminal
I like Jason Calacanis
I'm sorry I can't help but I don't know him as a crook
That's for sure
I know him as a guy that we've butted heads against a lot in the past
But I got a big a great amount of respect for this guy
And I don't think he's a crook
And I do think he has worked
Very hard to get to where he is
But CSB
You're always out there on the edge man
Always out on the edge
Oh
So good
Oh yes
No
Oh
Are you going to come?
No, not yet
Oh
Yeah
I'm coming
To podcast Con you can
Satirane November the 18th
At Smithfields in London
An all-day conference
Feature in the hottest in podcast action
With a range of hosts from CC Chapman, Chris Barnes, Neil McIntosh and Mark Hunter
The day runs from 10 a.m. until 6 p.m.
With live music from Jimmy Golding and Elie Miles
Are you coming?
What tickets and more information?
Go to podcastcon.com.
Podcastcon.co.uk
Oh yes
I am
Oh
Are you coming?
Podcastcon.co.uk
Register.com
Put a bit of bread
In your pod
Oh, I love it
That's a great promo
Now did you make that with your wife?
Or did you rip that from some porn movie?
Because she sounded really hot too
That was very good
I actually kind of got a lot of
Tingle out of that
I think I'm going to be able to make it
It looks like I'll be in the UK
And yesterday we had a
A meeting with
Or the
Marketing Department with podpimp
And I know there's a couple of
Sponsorship packages available
And we're going to sponsor the podcastcon
I really hope I can come
But I think it is a good initiative
It seems like a very grass roots type of thing
Kind of semi-organized
And the last minute they're pulling together some
Sponsorship stuff
And so podshow is definitely going to try and help out
And if it's shit
We want to because we're entering into your market
Yeah
Put a little bit of bread in your pod
A little bit of yank in your Brit pod
Speaking of which
This Saturday evening
At midnight
On Channel 4 in the UK
The Digital Music Awards 2006 airs
And I'm on the show
With Ron we present the award for a best podcast
Now we went through this before
We weren't really a part of the nomination process
And there was a whole bunch of mainstream
Podcasts that have been nominated
And one independent one
No, I guess I shouldn't give it away
That they won, huh?
Because you got to watch tonight
But the show was on tonight
Midnight and what we're doing
Since the show was taped a couple weeks ago
And we did the whole red carpet
We're going to rerun the entire
It's like six hours of red carpet
Of just all the stars
The sea lebrides, the d-lebrides
And the e-lebrides coming in the door
We had Olivia
On the red carpet
We had max roaming around
By the bar area, we had OJ
Doing interviews
You know, it almost gets into a fight
With totally boy band
It's a very funny to watch
It's a great stuff
And we're going to rerun that
Let's see starting
12 noon
At BTpodshow.com
So go to BTpodshow.com
At 12 noon on Saturday
UK time, which would be
Was it?
That's 4am here in San Francisco
And we'll be rerunning the entire red carpet
Extravaganza
Multi-camera shoot
All stream and all live, baby
And then we're going to rerun it
Again at six
And as I said, it's about six hours
That'll take you right up until
The actual awards started
So it's kind of funky, you know
It's like a delayed live event
Which is really the only way we could do it
We don't control the television broadcast
But we did have a shitload of fun
Doing the red carpet event
So BTpodshow.com
To check out the red carpet arrivals
Of all of the C-Lebodies, D-Lebodies
And E-Lebodies
That's great
People from like big brother in the UK
And celebrity love island
And we kind of
We have fun with them
We take a bit of the piss out of them
But there's also Peter Gabriel
So it's
And the only interview he did
Was for the show
What else was I going to say?
Yeah, folks on this series
You're going to miss this really
Horny Call I have
And aren't you lucky that you subscribe
To the podcast?
I could not believe my luck
When this came in yesterday
This next phone call
It's something that I've been
Wanting to happen for
Let me see, let's just say
I've been thinking about this
For 482 episodes
I've always said
You'll really know
That podcasting has broken through
And that we can really do something
Do some real damage to the media landscape
When producers of podcasts and other independent media
Can get laid off of this stuff
I think
I'm getting very close
Listen to this
Hi Adam
This is Desell and San Diego
I have a confession to make to you
Kind of new to podcasting
And a friend of mine who's all into it told me all about your show
I was getting bored with everything on my iPod
So I thought I'd give it a try
These sides
You're kind of cute
So I figured what the hell, right?
So one day I was sitting at home on the couch
Reading a magazine
Listening to the SD
And at first I was kind of bored
But then something clicked
I started to key into the sound of your voice
And it really started sounding extremely sexy
And the next thing I know I'm touching myself
To the sound
Let me just say for that moment
For a second
I just got to rewind that
Hold on
I want to make sure that you hear it
Say it again
Remely sexy
And the next thing I know I'm touching myself
To the sound of your voice
I've never been a voice person before
But I got this picture in my mind
If you're talking to me right in my ear
All of a sudden I was fantasizing
You were inside of me
I know that's kind of graphic
But there's something about the sound of your voice
So now I'm completely addicted to your show
And to your voice
Adam Curry you're one sexy bastard
Oh yes
Folder
Oh
And she's a folder
Was her name?
Isel
Let me just see
Was her name gazelle?
When it was
Hi Adam
This is gazelle in San Diego
Gazelle in San Diego
Okay
Guys
You may not want to listen to this
Some guys might
Gazelle
I really really love that comment
And
I think maybe you should tell me what kind of things you want me to say to you
We could
You know try and experiment
Where
You have a fantasy about something I'm going to say
And then I say it
And then while you're listening you know you can really enjoy the Chacha
Oh
Man
That's hot
Send me more
Please I beg of you
That's so I love it
That's so cool
I can't wait to tell Patricia this one
She's going to love it too
Maybe you could have a fantasy about it
You know like a three way
Maybe I could get Patricia interested in participating in our little experiment
Gazelle from San Diego
And
Send me a naked picture really
But how was that?
Hey
Shit
My
So, I am her sister.
Yeah!
Okay, I thought the Banglins got aNo algorithm.
Hi Adam!
Steve here from podcast and Dossai.
Remember I was talking to Wallyur forearm with Tanya.
I hope you feel him better.
I know when you're in America you speak American and you're picking up little British terms and slang
You should really get into the memory away of things
When you're finished with this one, I'll send you over some from Clark and if you get really good at
I'll send you some from Dublin and then you'll be set for over here. I hope you're fun
I'm sure you can share it with your listeners. Maybe they might come over and see is
Okay, bye Adam
Wait wait
Hold up
Welcome and thank you for purchasing language phones English sham dictionary sounds like fun
If you plan to visit Limerick and you find yourself at a bar our restaurant
These simple phrases will help you interact with your native hosts
Before you hear those words and phrases in contact
Test yourself to be sure you really know them. I would like to purchase your finest house ale and a drink for my ladyfriend
Two points of calling a bottle of blood and if I can arms from my butt
Two-mind of calling a bottle of blood and a bottle of blood
I know that was pretty good. Do you serve food on your premises?
You don't need to ask this how much it's good. I don't need to ask this how much it's good. I don't need to ask this how much it's good
I'm tired. Could you direct me to my room, please?
I'm not going to waste it. We're out of my question, bud. I'm not going to waste them when I'm in a question, bud
Shit, I'm getting good at this. This is area provide nighttime entertainment
penny clubs aren't going to make booch
Please
hey
What I've learned is that the generic word for biarch, wife, girlfriend, or significant other is
BOD, BOD, is that from the BOD is in the body?
I must say your city certainly lives up to its reputation.
If there were, go back and listen again, if not, continue with the next dialogue.
Alright, I got to come up to Ireland.
I'm not going to meet these girls.
I'm like a lot of fun.
On my way, ladies.
Yo, what's up, avis Jersey Todd, the official musicologist of the Chacha.
Except no wannabes, I'm the original baddest musicologist, the Delhi source code has ever
seen.
And the only substitute that should be on your table, well that should be Splenda.
But listen, I've been on trial this whole week.
I've been in all these different courts.
I just walked in the door from night court and well I've got to go deep into my bag
of tricks tonight.
Because the artist that I'm playing for you this week on the Friday food bar, Chacha,
is none other than Phil Ayub.
Phil Ayub's last album, School Bus Window, Paper Heart is one of my absolute favorite.
And you can find a lot of it on the positive music network.
So check this out from one of my favorite albums.
And hopefully it will become one of yours.
This is Phil Ayub with no heartache.
You don't love it.
You can never walk out into your good neighbor.
You won't last forever.
She's a flaming your the candle.
She tell you that it's cold out and take your own jacket.
You can never walk out and take your own jacket.
You can never walk in direct ways in direct ways in direct ways in direct ways in direct way.
She's literally a turpentine power to people
Suppressing a more hopelessness, she's registered to see her
To cliff-hanging in your waiting on the seagull
She lets you overlapped, but she won't let out
You know the fact that I'm talking about
She won't believe in a ropey
Think the way it's supposed to be a life she's got to keep
She's just the egg with no heart in our shell
She'll make you wait all night
And she'll pay you no money
No shoes, poison but you take a shot
She's just the egg with no heart
She
she
She's a drunk guy, she's the next
You wanna never ending train, right?
Last line of poem
You just can't get the rhyme, right?
You don't stand a chance
She's got gun at it, it's a fistball
She's a guy who now before the star
You know she'll
She'll make you wait on that
You sure?
Yeah, you know it, right?
No she's
Boys and boys, you tell you the show
She's just a drunk guy, she's the next
She's just a drunk guy
Filio?
The body's at music network, thank you very much.
Jersey Todd official musicologist of the Cha Cha
Bring it to us every food bar fried
I do appreciate it, my friend
Especially because you got paid back late from nightcourt
Let me just see a couple more things
Before I go
Oh, I wanted to mention Jeff Smith's day job
He's doing a video show
Which you can find at
What's it?
Shhh, Jeff's day job
And that's G-E-O-F-F
Jeff's dayjob.podshow.com
You got to see this
You know he's a working musician
He's a traveling pianist
Does the crazy pianos
And he's the the most recent episode I saw
Which I think was episode
You know she don't know
I don't know which episode it was
He had this whole audience
You know, yellow
Whether they were a folder or a scruncher
It's really cool
Excellent. I'll put a link to that in the show
No today and see what else
Russell, what did Russell say here?
Adam, please stop comparing a power book G4 with a new dual core
PC
It isn't a fair comparison. I have a MacBook Pro
And the screen is beautiful and it is fast
I use both windows
You know what?
I would agree with you there
That's not a fair comparison
You know, but I did buy the power book
You know, within the past year
You know, so and look how quickly that got outdated
That's really angered me
Particularly after that when it broke
And
As a magazine called RAPUP
RAPUP
And they're also doing a show now on the podcast
Network, the pod show podcast delivery network
RAPUP.podshow.com
Let's see
What do they have?
They've got like a music video shoot
Did they have on on their first episode
RAPUP.podshow.com
You definitely should look at that
And keep your eye on the
You know the podshow.com homepage
Lots of video stuff happening there
And you'll see a lot more happening in the next couple weeks
And of course
Tomorrow night we have the red carpet event
From the digital music awards
So
That said, it's time to wrap things up
What day is it today?
It's Friday
Well, final thought of the week
It's no secret that I really really love living
In the United Kingdom
I love everything about the folks there
We love the area that we're in
But I guess my final thought would have to do with the United States of America
And if you look at the news
You kind of get the idea that
It's all messed up over here
And that everyone is kind of
The country is
No one's at the helm, no one's steering this big ship
But that's not really true
When you get down, and of course the same is for
Civilizations and populations all over the world
You can't really take what you see on the news
Face value, it's just all messed up over there
People don't know what they're doing
One thing I have to say about the United States
That I really really really love
And it's been shown to me
Time and time again during this past trip
The past two weeks
Is the work acumen
The drive that people have
We have about 60 people now at our office in San Francisco
And we've got people in New York, we've got people in London
But particularly what you see here in the US
People just want to get shit done
They really really do care
There's no sense of
I had never had to ask anyone to stay late
To do extra work, they're doing it
They've been at the office for two hours
People love showing up early
Just to get the stuff done
Because they really believe in what they're doing
And I should almost have some kind of patriotic
Stars and stripes on going on the background here
But it really really is true
The way people like to work in America
I know it doesn't
It can't compare to any other country in the world
And I'm really proud to be in America
And when I see that, you know, there is nothing
And that's probably the big secret of the United States
There is no problem that we don't feel we can't fix
And we know that at the end of the day
It's going to be all right
And we are going to fix it
And we are going to make it all right
And we're going to correct our ways if we have to
And we're going to work hard to get to where we want to be
As a country and as a people
I'm really sure about how much we can help
Ok, great
I really deserved to keep my passport now
Don't I
I myself
I'm not going to do anything
I think that's what we appreciate
Alright
Yes
That's it for Fubar Friday everybody
Thank you very much for listening
Hope you have a great weekend
Of course today I'll be back on
The Lady Patricia has promised us
Drupai and we eat a lot to discuss
A lot to catch up on for show
all the great sex we have during the weekend, which I'm also shooting here's going to happen.
Adam with Curry, Adam at podshow.com or dailysourceco.com for all the show notes.
Have a great weekend everybody. Bye-bye.
I love it.