This podcast is brought to you by Pancho and GoDaddy.
Want to hear content with badass domain name?
This show will give you a special code.
Get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie, three, six, nine earned.
$16 billion worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
You threw up just this much.
You'd be flying a cargo plane full of rubber dogs here.
And different from the way I was before.
To grab the brush and let's your glory for now.
Call of me outside outside the light.
You don't need to realize I am defined.
Take me beyond all the things that I know.
To call of me outside outside the light.
Well yeah.
Call of me when I'm so black and white.
Reflections of your mercy.
Reflections of your side.
I know I need something different from the way I was before.
To grab the brush and let's your glory for now.
Call of me outside outside the light.
You don't need to realize I am defined.
Take me beyond all the things that I know.
To call of me outside outside the light.
And different from the way I was before.
You don't need to realize I am defined.
I have to search you for closer and more.
And deep in my hair light.
I'm there.
But four, one, one.
Since now I could be alive.
I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I
I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming for you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you, I'm coming with you
me outside the lines in the pod save music network actually a submission from a listener
from David Peterson who says a friend of mine has a band. This is how it usually goes with
the pod save music. I convinced him to let me set up a page form on the pod save music network.
The band is called 10th Hour Calling. Leave singers been safer and they've received some local
radio play. Most people like Colour Me in Ancient Butterfly. That's why I played Colour Me. I like
the two of them and very much. Thank you Dave Peterson. You can find David dipstick.com and 10th Hour
Calling at the pod save music network. Hey everybody it's Tuesday and I have a horrible confession
to make. I'm addicted. That's right. My name is Adam Curry and I am addicted to second life.
Have you ever seen this game? This stuff. It literally is crack for your mind man. I'm telling you
this is a I've heard a lot about it. I've seen people blog about it. I never really have been into
gaming at all. I'm totally not even flight simulators about the the farthest I'll get into gaming.
Which of course is pretty advanced and not really gaming. But the second life it's if you've ever
read the book Metaverse by Neil Stephenson which is a book I think I read in 1993 maybe a little
late in that maybe it was 94 somewhere around there. This is exactly what the book describes.
The Metaverse is this place where you jack in and now we're jacking in now through laptops and
desktop computers and through screens but on the on the Metaverse which is really not that far
fetch you put on goggles to jack into the system. I can't wait to build a sense say oh,
shack in the second life. But you get an avatar. You look like a person and you can dress yourself
and it's a real world that's going on in there. It's unbelievable and I don't think even though
this was these ideas have been talked about and conceived of for decades really it hasn't been
until now we have all the connections we have the internet everyone can get online. It works for Windows
and for Mac I was happy to see and you can actually you know create a second life. The name is
extremely appropriate and I was just blown away by this. Also my computers were blown away.
Gosh man that stuff really it really harshes the process. But you know you're downloading
worlds and you can teleport to places and you can hug people and wave and talk and chat and then
you can pick up all these gestures and objects and of course there's an incredible thriving
adult community in this in second life and they have a currency which actually translates to dollars
it's crazy. You should check it out secondlife.com and you know the thing I was and I definitely
want to investigate this a more but I have to be very very careful because it's so easy to sit
down behind the computer log in and before you know it three hours have passed. What I'd like to
do is I'd like to build a podcast shack you know a little place out by the sea maybe where I live
in the shack and then I have a hole in the ground and underneath is where I have my my evil
podshow podshack empire instead of high on a hill I want to be down below and it would be great
if people would come up and you could you could get a podcast right from the shack. I mean there's
all kinds of stuff streaming video streaming audio works in these worlds so I'm sure there should
be a way to exchange podcasts and maybe even build an aggregator build a pod catcher right into
second life. It's just some thoughts man but wow I was completely blown away.
Um my uh what is my name in second life? Oh Adam Newman with double end. It's funny when you
sign up you get to use your real first name but they assign you a choice of last name so that's
November echo uniform Mike Alpha November November I'll see you there.
Go I've got listen it's bro hi dot com it's all hood I we drop off they call me the post what my
elis mega joy I hail from the sun set zona just hold out we got that source code updated
Adam Kirby give it to you on a daily pass and I'm hurry I can't wait for them to play me
all serious that I like the sun's fine hype and I'm a serious man with Mike's damn
always till I die keep your head over it's you're not rocking with the best but you already know it
transform and courtesy of the major to be all about courtesy and hitting this paper oh
I'm currently I take a terrible fellow frees in that nature disaster mislike Katrina
if I say yeah I got that everlasting flow to call me now a native of the haters
the hate lanes and you can stop him to teach me on the paper countdown I'm out now top one two
three I'm going to take that spot now where you can jot down the jiffy story on the
piece of tv and I'll add to the jiffy you want to come get it you the best how you said that
I'm serious with my fault the fact is that they kill me it's a lie I have to
industry for the style that they say it's your house and he like dice we strike pipes
and take it in the ass well me over here me it's keep it in the cash well
I think they've done something similar at hoodhype.com for the source code I want to make sure
got on serious satellites all the big wigs could listen to it definitely the stars of the
underground at hoodhype.com check it out I'm going to be a rather short show today Patricia
wants me to go to the garden center yeah the weather's nice here spring is finally arrived
blossoms are a blossoming and that means it's time for me to go slip all kinds of plants and
crap and bring them back to the cottage it's not my favorite past time but I got to do that
before 4 p.m. right now it's already after one again second life is is to blame for that
reason being we're getting the dev cast set up now I'd said that I'd hope to have that
up last night UK time but I think something with a DNS that wasn't propagating properly
anyway by the time you hear this you're probably be able to go to devcast.podshow.com
that's dv delta vector vico cast dot pod show dot com and that's where you can subscribe if you
are developer if you know some HTML and PHP then you'll be able to get into pod show plus
and the podcast little re network start helping us out create stuff there's actually some
some ways for you to help us and get paid for it and all of that will be explained in the dev
cast of the SDK and all that stuff can have Andrew explain that to you and Kevin and I think
we'll probably do hopefully I'll get to dev cast out this week and included in every single one
of the dev cast will be golden tickets we're going to try and get 50 people in at first glance
and judging from the g-mails have gotten on the topic it won't be much of a problem so
stay tuned for dev cast dot pod show dot com and we'll see you on the other side of the fire wall
Metro sexual metro sexual metro sexual metro sexual it's an encourage metro sexual moment
and carries metro sexual moment yeah no just kind of a disturbing trend when it comes
to metro sexuality apparently this word metro sexual is now on every single outlist or every
in and outlist on the outside that would be on the lame side that I've seen anywhere in the United
States I don't get it it's like okay maybe the label metro sexual doesn't fit anymore but the
the act of it you know as to post a being big macho man that seems to be still going strong just
you're not allowed to call yourself a metro sexual anymore well I'm sorry I'm going to fight it
tooth and nail we're going to remain metro sexual here as we pendelled back and forth between the
US and the UK apparently though according to Paul Nairick Nairink who sent me
the way he emailed this link was pretty funny this article is pretty interesting regarding the
surgeon metro sexual behavior in Japan now it sounds like it's like we're sexual deviance
but there's a whole article and of course I will put a link in the show notes to it about
Ishi Toko who's one of a growing number of Japanese men investing time and money to approve their
appearance for them applying facial lotion and wearing nice clothes not just enough many are trying
things once the preserve of women manicures spot treatments even underwear their enhances the
body shape or gaining popularity I yes so we have to go to Asia all right I have a feeling that
Tokyo Dan might be checking in on this topic any other listeners in any other listeners
in Japan just let me know how what the state is of metro sexuality okay hey Adam just in here on
DSC 357 you were talking about a city that was using dog crap to generate power oh wait a minute
live in a small aggregate and it that's not a metro sexual content that get in there that's a
Trinity comment crap now I've really done it hold on afters for a second yeah all right then we'll
just try this one we'll do a two for one on this Tuesday that's what I need to produce her for
okay ready let's do it again hey Adam just in here on DSC 357 you were talking about a city
that was using dog crap to generate power a lot of in a small agricultural community and we've got
a similar system my town of Lyndon is surrounded by dairy farms a cows crap a lot more than dogs
so we got a lot of crap around here recently Washington state's first methane digester
was installed at a local farm it takes the ways from about 1500 cows and turns it into electricity
which is then added to the local power company's grid it provides enough power to fuel 180 homes
and that's just from a fraction of the cow crap we got around here anyway thought this might
be an interesting addition to your dialogue of alternative energy thanks Adam bye oh dude thank you
and of course this immediately raises the question if it works with cow crap will it work with
human crap just imagine the possibilities of heating your home with your own produce
yeah I just wanted to talk one second about this whole notion of quiet birth and I'm reading
more about it which is why I want to pick it up as a thread here on the Charlie this is being promoted
by Tom Cruise and Katie Holmes and it seems like everyone is writing about this what is this this
is the Chicago Sun Times I guess mainly mainstream and I just wanted to want to stop for
second and talk about it because what is very apparent to me now this is all a part of
Scientology the concept of a quiet birth maybe I should tell you what it what actually is now
wait a minute here's the here's the thing the bothers me about most of these articles it's
apparent to me that almost no one has actually read the book dynamics by El Ron Hubbard who was the
father of Scientology and the brains behind it and who I truly believe had a bet with some
buddy in a bar it said hey dude I bet you I can become the Messiah with my own religion and then
all of a sudden he did it based on a book but you know reading through the book you know you think
that you know based upon these what are those things they have those testers your stressometer
and you know and and of course the horrible stories about who about the the cultish nature of
the the Church of Scientology you know I read the book and I was pretty disappointed because there's
no cultism in there at all there was quite a bit in fact most of the book is about you know
childhood and how it affects behavior and I found it to be quite entertaining I read this book I think
three maybe yeah three years ago probably on a vacation in Jamaica and that's probably why most
journalists haven't read this book because if you if you've seen it laying around in a bookstore it's huge
it is a it is a big ass paperback book I'm sure you can get the hardbound copy but you know it's
it's quite a it's quite a read that you have to commit to to get through it all but the whole concept
of quiet birth is not all that stupid actually and they go into into great depth about you know
the trauma how how an unborn child even can be traumatized by loud noises by bumping etc
and how that can affect hearing and sight and general attitude and I thought it was some pretty
interesting things and there was some space outshed in there as well but I thought that almost seemed like
logical just logics and the quiet birth concept is that you don't talk and there's no screaming
or yelling during during the birthing process the same by the way goes for operations
and I'm seeing more articles about that as well that doctors if they were to follow
dynamics would say nothing during an operation where of course if you were watched you know ER or
what's the plastic surgery TV series can't remember you know that the people are talking
all kinds of trash and it's not like your ears are plugged up you know we really don't know a lot
about how much information gets into you while you're asleep or while you're in the subconscious
level apparently according to dynamics a lot does so you know this it doesn't seem weird to me
if anyone has any opinions on dynamics and and forget the church of Scientology because I don't
only want to get into that because I may be there totally misinterpreting what what El Ron
Hubbard meant to begin with I have no idea but the whole concept of what's in dynamics it's
pretty as I said pretty interesting and yeah and to me very normal stuff in there and and
and to with this journalist you know if you're gonna write about it don't just hop on the
the Tom Cruise bashing bandwagon he's no butt of mine but you know maybe read the book first
so you can write some informed articles you said I was not all over you know another hood
you know I got you ready yeah oh no I know this is a to the d to the a M U to man
what's up Adam a welcome back from vacation uh it sounds like you had a good time you got to do
that man you got to clear your cranium uh we really really appreciate your shout out last week man
it was on the money uh as for Portland a Aladdin I went down there we had a blast right awesome
had a wonderful time it was throwing down you know it was uh it was uh it was uh it was uh yeah
give a kick it was a good time it was like Lewis and Clark discovered it yeah Aladdin OT put it on
the map put it right on the map this time it's ready yeah and what we're gonna do we're gonna kick
you some um potsafe hip hop in the R&B music oh we're gonna try to keep it family safe you know
we try to stay away from you know from the you know slap my bitch up type thing right right and
Aladdin you know he's my boys at DJ yeah yeah I've been spending the cuts for a grip since I was
like 12 and I want to try to now just push a potsafe music out in the club that's one of the
things that I think needs to be done because people don't get to hear it you know there's a lot
of radio stations that play music that's everything that's out they won't play the whole album but
right and these cast from potsafe don't really get heard that's what I want to do so if anybody
knows anything about it give us a shout out at alpha maker oh yeah alpha dash omega cast dot com
dash right give us a shot let us know what you think places we can go and if it would be something
that you think we're working to club I know it will I mean there's a cut call blow your whistle
right to check that last year buy it off the move right and hit us up yeah hit us up she can hit
you hear it on our what show is that you hear it on our number one show number one show so
all right hey Adam take it easy and uh keep doing what you doing alright man thanks for
hookin to stop I think make a piece you alpha mega cast hold on a second what they say blow your
whistle was that with the the track that we're talking about let me just see if I can find it
blow your whistle as a moth okay hold on it's find out this is what I love about the potsafe music network
boom as a moth who's played this artist I'd like checking that out first oh my gosh I've
art now I played them yeah Jesus Christ excuse me
see I'm slipping I promised I wouldn't do that anymore but I was totally blown away here
by the amount of podcasters that have played that song which one is it blow your whistle
let me just hear for a second I look like I play it yeah it looks like I played it on the source code as
well well know what that would happen there where to go come on yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I remember I remember you know it's important I'm trying to highlight all different
to genres of music to make sure that you know we're not just talking about potsafe music and
potsafe music showcases that are only for the rock alternative rock modern rock but also for
hip hop for R&B for blues country and western christian music we got to make sure we get it all out
there and I love the fact that these guys are trying to get some stuff into the clubs that's
very cool and just touching back briefly on and I posted a note to a link to a slate article
yesterday you know which of course related to that quote from AT&T CEO Whitaker who said that
he's going to make sure that you know big media companies who use their pipes quote on quote
will have to pay for it and what I'm seeing still is a lot of confusion from people saying
well I already pay thirty bucks a month I already have my ban how can I have to pay more let
let me just reset that for a second this will not directly concern you as a consumer
of course indirectly it will because if content companies have to pay extra money to get
high quality high definition whatever the hell is supposed to be done with with more pipes to get
that to you well you know something they're going to pass it on somewhere they'll pass it on
to advertise it advertise or pass it into the price of products and and round around she goes right
so it's not going to impact you directly this is this is something separate in fact I believe
I believe what what the what the what the big telcos and there's only a few now AT&T is
really so big I think you know sixty or sixty five percent of of all communications money spent
will go to AT&T in the United States at least oh man I'm sorry I'm gastronomic today
uh he's hydromatic and gastronomic gastromatic um I think that the AT&T guys are thinking that
they're going to connect these pipes to Hollywood so that you know they're all talking about movies
no one is talking about the upload the upload part gosh how hard is it to see that I think they're
all looking at iTunes and saying yeah yeah yeah we can make that successful we can we can do that
too but they don't understand that Apple is making money on selling iPods and Macintosh computers
not necessarily huge bundles of cash on on the music sales and then not doing too bad but it's
not like that's huge amounts of money it's just not if you're listening to this on uh Syria stars
102 you're going to have to download the whole show to listen to the rest of this thread this conversation
daily source code dot com what is coming up for you in just a couple seconds pch
mark your schermody macamono nmcoff with pacific host hell way east radio after that dawn
a drew Gilmore gang and then tonight it's the pod show music rewine i think episode number 29
i found not mistaken so that'll be a real treat that'll take you from nine to ten eastern
that is a six to uh was at six to seven uh pacific time and we'll be back with the hump day
addition of the daily source code right here tomorrow same time on Syria stars 102 so i'll catch
you guys then now back to our little story so it seems to me like the telcos and specifically
AT&T are trying to hook up you know fiber to the home and of course that has to be paid for you know
as someone has to pay for it and they're going to charge their customers and i think that they're
probably looking more towards Hollywood which i think will be a huge disappointment for them
and i certainly do not believe in the concept of uh routing information based upon priority which
is another big thing that you hear everyone talking about saying okay well so you know if you have
you'll have like the dirt road of the internet but if uh if you're content provider the person
you're getting the information from uh pays a premium or what some are calling attacks
in that case then your packets that actually come into your home or computer or whatever will
have some form of priority and they'll be delivered faster more reliably i mean but when you look at
all the information traveling on the on the net to actually put in place this could create a whole
new dot com bubble by itself just to have the machines powerful enough the routers powerful enough
to be able to segregate on an individual packet level what has to go where and what has a priority
i think and i'd be happy to pay for this by the way i think 30 bucks a month is a good deal
is cheap and i'll i'll pay 60 a month if you can give me a big honk and fat pipe and i'm sure
that um even as pod show we'd be happy to contribute if we had more bandwidth you know to uh and of
course we talked to through our pod cast delivery network you know we we remove much of the
public internet already if your pod cast is being requested uh through the pod cast delivery network
onto let's say a calm cast is your ISP that file that data does not travel any other route
then directly from the pod cast delivery network to the calm cast network it's called peering that's
the beauty of the network that we've set up so you don't traverse over any of the public portions
of the internet other than the ones that are directly involved in the request and the delivery of a
file so to have more uh capability at that connection yeah right on so i'm not totally against it
what i am seeing though is this wittaker guy he can't buy the right PR he really really really
messed it up with that statement and uh and he's gonna have to put i think he's gonna have to show
what he's talking about before people understand it and he's gonna do something quick they're talking
2008 when they want to have some of this in place which seems very quick to me but he's gonna have to
show what he really means and he's gonna have to get some partners who are going to stand next to him
and explain it otherwise this will just result in oh man everyone's jumping on this and i think
it's just purely because it's it's being poorly explained and he probably doesn't understand what he's
talking about either which is not a typical of of a huge company CEOs um i and i'm not too sure of
his background but i don't know if he really understands all of what he's talking about but for now
i wouldn't be too worried about it i see it really is okay bigger pipes on the way i hope i hope
and i really pray that someone thinks about giving the upload portion a little more attention you know
we need to be able to distribute stuff out he's got to push stuff up that's where it's all going
to come from it's the same thing with second life you know second life is a fantastic game engine
and the people in it build the whole network i mean you can't have any better example of of how
media is being and the second life to me is 100% media you can't you can't build any better
example and by the way hey how would you like to have more bandwidth for your second life connection huh
mm-hmm and congratulations to Steve runner he made it he completed the Boston marathon
it was so cool to see uh these automatic emails coming in here's the last one i got at
617 pm Stephen Walker i should say Steve runner has finished pace 7 minutes and 55 seconds per
kilometer finish time 533 42 and Steve bought me off notice it was an amazing experience thank you
for the shirt i weren't probably got plenty of shouts for pod show and he'll have audio on
that in a couple days and he finished as i said 533 42 not as best time but he was played with
stomach cramps throughout the race still finished had a great time and he says i think my next podcast
will be pretty damn compelling because that's the one that'll be coming from uh the marathon
where he was actually doing the podcast wall running Steve runner dot com congratulations man i'm
i'm really blown away by uh by the whole concept and it was fun because i think i got five or six or
seven different emails and so it's actually sitting down just before i had dinner a pop the email
it was like oh i see Steve's uh you know got about an hour and a half less to go is it incredibly cool to
see hello come on in it's at here oh hello you're attention to a site called you shop you give
which is the letter u then shop then the letter u then give dot com now this site was set up to
let charities make some money from the affiliate links that different uh companies give and they've
gone out of business specially because some certain websites and quite famous ones that you can
work out have decided that they don't like the fact that people keep on going back to the new shop
you give to make to give the charities and money and it said they must prefer people go directly
to their site once they've gone to you shop you give once so you shop you give have had to go out
of business because the these particular companies have decided not to continue their affiliate links
anymore where if you shop you give which is a great shame that everyone involved and i'd just
like to bring this to your attention just to ask that similar type of thing just doesn't happen
with the put show charity affiliate links which you mentioned in the past thank you and thanks
for picking this up on the copy comments delicious feed bye okay sorry about the the audio levels
there i actually had to jack it up a bit so this is about the pod safe music network which is a part
of the unlabel and i've said that for the first year of sales leave it just goes to a period
so we can evaluate it but i'm pretty sure that this will be the status quo for the pod set music network
pod show is taking no none of the the money that is received for a sale there's a transaction fee
which is nine cents and that goes to a clicking by and then there'll be an affiliate fee so if
if you put a link on your show site or on your weblog wherever and someone purchases a track
through it and we're thinking of making that nice you know like 10% or maybe 15% and the choice
here is that you'll be able to donate that money to the artist so you take nothing isn't affiliate
or you can donate that money to a charity and i think the point of that comment was to say be
careful because sometimes when you use an affiliate link you can lose your affiliate status
because what these affiliate systems really want is for you to come to their site
and not just have one link that doughnates through them or something like that and i said don't
worry about it because we have direct contact with music cares which is for old beat up retired
musicians that's where musicians go when they're down and out i think Tony Bennett is the
chair of that so we'll make sure that that gets routed properly and if we have problems with
affiliate links which i don't think will actually be using i haven't heard from Chris Rockwell yet
with the dealers if we're going to go live with this simultaneously with podshow plus or if we're going
to do that with we're doing outside of of of the unleashed i'm not sure i have to get in touch
with the office to find out later on today by adding this is Dennis from the dedicated asked
hundred one uses for baby wipes checking in with an audio comment i'd send an audio comment
sometime back about using podcast is a form of community service by playing PSA's well a public
relations firm representing the centers for disease control contacted me asking for my help
getting the word out about their autism campaign kind of sounds like podcasting is being
recognized as legitimate outlet for delivering a message done it now i used to chase
organizations down that i wanted to support and asked for permission to play their PSA's
now they're coming to me a podcast or asking for help to get their message out how cool is that
anyway my latest show becomes a shameless plug i got to interview an expert in developmental
disabilities from the cdc and talk about their autism awareness campaign c april is autism awareness
month so i'm gonna have experts on my daddy cast all month to talk about it now i know that the
lascivious bitties are using their voices to raise awareness about MS and here's just one more
example of how podcasting can really help make a difference shameless plug again find my show at
101 uses for baby lives dot com iTunes and of course at the podcast music network megaplex
yeah the podcast music network megaplex yeah like it yeah you're right people are seeing it and the
minute the non-profits uh catch on this latch on to something you know what's happening because
those people know how to make money and not making it for themselves but they know how to raise money
and if they see an opportunity they jump on the bandwagon real quick so that's good for podcasting
and general appreciate the information tomorrow by the way i think we'll do a different type of source code
since the weather is so nice today i'm expecting it to be good tomorrow as well i won't
know until i read the matars and taffs later on tonight but but when i uh uh if if i'm in luck
then tomorrow morning early i'm gonna head off to uh the airport and gonna fly for an hour so
i'm gonna take Jason from the control tower along with me just to show me the area he's uh he's
about eight nine hundred hours on the single engine and he definitely knows the area and i was
thinking maybe you'd like to come along for the ride so i'll bring along the i River and the wireless
mic set and we'll uh we'll do some sound seeing from the sky over the affluent suburb of of
gilford so that's on tomorrow's show uh still a few more things left for today source code
hi Adam this is Phil this is Tony and together we do the soccer show podcast available at
soccershow.com we've been here all about this upcoming meetup between yourself and the
brith cast a crowd we'd love to be there but we just can't make it because you see Tony and I
are straddlers but what straddlers we straddle uh not really sure i want to be a straddler so
no no it's not what you think we're brits and we talk about bridge football but we live in America
and we've got green cards and everything uh right i'm getting yeah so we straddly see we straddled
the brithish and the American podcasting uh we straddlers exactly straddlers it's not as scary as
it sounds Adam we hope you have a fun night out with that crowd they seem like a good bunch of guys
if you are any of your listeners are interested in a soccer stroke football podcast we we straddle
we put out a new show every weekday morning in which we'd live a match reports match reviews
and a summary of the days news if you're interested in that you should tune into our podcast
at soccershout.com bye Adam bye yeah all right so catching on to that the draft and
darts so we have a time and a date this coming Sunday the 23rd of April 3 p.m. and there's been some
suggestions uh this was the the most interesting suggestion i heard of and a couple people seem to
agree that the Texas embassy rooms in Trafalgar Square would be the perfect place i'm like
we're coming to the UK to sit in the Texas bar i mean i you maybe you guys are trying to make us
feel at home or something like that but i do they have darts in the Texas embassy rooms anyway
i've left up the uh the venue to the pod pimp Aaron Aaron Brazil he's going to take care of that so
um sometime today i'm sure we'll have all that arranged and hope he'll set us up and i'll give you
the venue by tomorrow but definitely you know it'll be in London it'll be this coming Sunday the 23rd of April
and it will be at three p.m. it's just a couple hours just want to hang out you know we're not
going to do anything extravagant we just want to meet you guys and what i could see there was a wiki
set up somewhere that might have been a brick i think palpine field set that one up
it looks like 20 people have already said that they're coming so i'm expecting 30 and i think
are going to have a good time hi Adam it's uh Matt Moran here i just want to make some comments
on dsc 368 you were talking about bark is bank online banking i don't think you give them enough
credit really for the way they look after your money um i like the fact that when you send money to
another person online that it disappears for three days i've asked my bank where this money just
appears to but no one seems to know um i don't know who's making money out of all the interest but
it'd be good to find out some time anyway i just wanted to make a quick comment also about pod show
in the UK um the podcast and community in the UK is reasonably small um people are going to be
protective over the work they've created and also their position within that community which is why
them meet up in London is a good idea to actually sit down and talk about some of these ideas over
a pint anyway it'll be a good to meet up with the some of the other British podcasters and
yourself and some of the guys from pod show next Sunday so uh catch it in right now looking forward
to it i hope to see you there i don't know ma'am when i pay something through bark lays online um i
said you have a little checkbox it says remove from my account immediately uh yeah it's gone
immediately but usually the next business day it shows up as as transferred in paid so i've never had
anyone complain and no one said who haven't seen it for three days i have had that happen with
large amounts though much larger amounts uh in fact when we bought the uh we bought the the jag
had money transferred from the Netherlands it took over a week and it seems like the larger the amount
that's when you get someone's attention is all of the people start to wake up all of a sudden
when you transfer big amounts and and that does often get kind of oh you know just like lost in the
shuffle yeah i'm feeling so bad oh yeah baby from the pod say music network it exposed you to
on it feel so good with my little Forbes
i'm just wallowing low down the dark alley is in my neighborhood
oh
don't tell me the park don't tell me the spark i'm loving every minute of this
don't copy me oh oh i've got this black heart blue
oh
you say i'm a
you say that my demons are will be perched
you say i can change
all i need is just the earth
you want me to smile i've got ball in my throat right now i'm in hell and i'm
singing up my cup baby yeah
let no soft got them black heart blue
oh it's one in once more
guess what i've had a change of heart
it is no longer blue
the pump in red and red need a fire
oh go get a lift in sense a shift in pieces flow it over me yeah baby
i mean again how sad is american idol when you hear this talent
Melissa Forbes black heart blues you can find at the pod save music network she's from
australia winter the best female solo artist award of the 2006 international online music awards
most of Forbes soulful voices drawn comparisons with the likes of dinacral sarday i need a baker
at least a stance field now they at least a stance field thing they just did because of her hair
but then i click on who's played this artist what a list this is USA hacks studio sea border line
and jubies chill cast with the angels rock and black i mean there's there must be
fifty different spins here and again the math is so simple add daily source code to that
and you've got a pretty high average of people who actually heard the song and i wonder
how it's doing for so Melissa if you're listening first of all the pipes the pipes are just too much
fantastic portion of this podcast brought to you by a
acu view check out Heather and janels show their podcast the download on acu.com
and if you want a great deal on a domain name and there's three different special
special offers we have once you go over to dawn and drew dot com check out dawn and drew's podcast
and they have three codes i'm not sure is it dnd dnds you have to listen to their show they'll
give you the codes and you'll find that you can get a domain name for six ninety five you can
get ten percent off all kinds of great offers i'm just kind of going to spread someone to
love to the other podcasts in the network and i hadn't talked about dawn and drew in a while
i wonder how they're doing dawn you still my girlfriend are you do you believe anything is possible
we do where are flink we believe in an internet that's safe from virus hidden scammers
we're earthling we believe your personal information should be just that personal and we
believe your internet should be a friend not a fo we're earthling make this smart choice visit earthlink.net
and discover what our internet experts can do for you earthling we revolve around you
right after the UK pod show hang look for some new stuff regarding earthling
okay tomorrow the daily source code will come to you from somewhere between fifteen hundred and
two thousand feet as we circle around a gilford and bits of serri and who long you know's where
we'll wind up you know within twenty five minutes we could be over the island white so we might
even do that and you'll be along for the ride so i hope you enjoy that tomorrow uh when i'll see
you again at amercarry dot com is for feedback daily source code dot com is for the latest show show
notes course crazy dot com for the ongoing conversation about the european union with com extra
blogger and other friends take care everybody see you
get this podcast and we're great ones like it on the high performance podcast delivery network
from pod jo and limelight networks i love