For the first time ever, the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr. in one action-packed DVD collection,
own all 27 episodes, the cult hit, including all new interviews with Carlton Koo.
First thing that Brisco did that impressed us was, we're not only to come in and really read the dialogue well as an actor,
but he also did a standing flip in our office.
You've flipped too for Brisco County!
If you like the kind of TV you can't get on TV, get your copy of the Adventures of Brisco County, Jr.
Available now on DVD.
DSC movies presents Adam in the Wild West.
This is a true heart and story of the boy they called Adam Curry.
And they're so excited about it.
I'm so incredibly happy.
It was great, didn't even take a taxi.
Adam Clark Curry was born on September 3, 1964.
He is a broadcaster and internet personality well known for his skin from 1987 to 1994 as a video jockey on the music video channel MTV.
He pilots his own airplane.
He is married to Dutch singer Patricia Puy.
And they have one daughter, Christine Puy.
This is the Delta Sierra Charlie, 480.
I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to
hear that, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this and hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but I don't want to hear this, but why don't want to hear this, but I want to hear this, I don't want to hear this, but I don't want you hear this, do I want to hear this, but I don't
I want to hear this
It's easy, I want to keep falling on my head
If they keep falling, they're good
I want to hear this
Dead, yeah
We're that
I don't want to hear this
I want to hear this
Okay
I don't want to hear this
I really don't like this
I love a wake-up
I've got to wake up
I really don't like this
I love a wake-up
I don't like this
I really don't like this
It's been a while since I played the space rocks you've fallen on my head.
It turns out that I've got a few new songs out there as well.
Hey everybody, how are you doing? Welcome to the Daily Source Code.
We are back again in a beautiful sunny Northern California at the Curry condo.
Hey yeah, how you doing? I love the song.
You know, go ahead, come up with it, really.
Space rocks keep falling on my head.
Away with the ferries.
Away with the ferries, type of that one.
Apologies for yesterday, lack of a showage.
I have been so incredibly sick.
New York was completely different than I had imagined.
Everything I wanted to do turned out differently.
And that's just because crap, man.
It happens once a year to me and I get the flu or whatever it is or whatever the heck I picked up.
It must have been something I picked up on the flight over from London.
And I didn't get to see David Palito.
There was a couple other people in New York that I was looking forward to hanging out with or meeting with or at least having coffee with or a phone call with.
I spent so much time just hooking up my lungs essentially that I had just didn't get to anything but the business at hand.
New York was beautiful, by the way.
Man, and I wish I could have told you this yesterday, but it was so nice when you walk out of your hotel and it's got that crisp.
I don't know if you've never been in New York.
There's something about autumn that crisp kind of feeling in the air.
They didn't quite have the chestnuts roasting outside on the cart yet, but the sun was shining.
It was a nice mild, like just around 70 degrees in the morning.
And you kind of have that really crackling fresh feeling.
And it was really nice to be back in New York for that reason.
I really, of course, the lady Patricia and I lived there for a year and we lived in Jersey, which was pretty damn close enough for 12 years, whatever.
So going into New York every single day, just it reminded me and New York is kind of always like New York.
It's just always kind of the same.
Now the hotel we stayed at was the, another one of these fantastic botic hotels.
Yes.
Made by the, I think the same people that did the Sanderson in London.
We talked about that.
The hotel with the fucking egg in the room, the big egg.
So this, it's an E.N. Shreger hotel, which means that they get an old piece of shit building.
And they dress it up with oversized furniture.
And an old furniture that they throw sheets over to kind of mass that it's old.
And all of a sudden it looks hip and you put some interesting chandeliers in.
And then you got to put some, some beautiful people who run the place, which is really interesting when you have beautiful people at a hotel.
This is the Grammarcy Park Hotel I'm talking about, which, by the way, as E.N. Shreger hotels go, the, the decor was nice.
It's my kind of decor kind of a plush, you know, red velvety type vibe.
Man, the hotel is so dark inside, you know, the wind, everything's just dark.
It's all artificial lighting, so it really made me nuts after a while.
You know, I'd get up, I'd do a breakfast meeting, and then go back and kind of like, you know, hang out kind of like a zombie.
I've tried every single cold medicine known to man, and it's just, I was so stoned from Tylenol, day quill, night quill, oh man.
And then sitting in this, you know, red velvety plush, very dark hotel was, yeah.
I just want to run a bath and hop in, dragging the toaster almost.
So when you had the beautiful people at the hotel, that means service is shit, because they're way too, um, concerned with looking cool for the people at the bar downstairs.
And what is this with room service? It says now right on the room service menu.
For your convenience, we will charge you 18% gratuity plus a five dollar delivery charge.
So if you just want to have breakfast like 50 bucks and like, no, I'm going outside.
This is New York, I'm going to go find something outside.
Go get a night, you know, get something at the deli.
Uh, anyway.
Uh, so I am feeling a little bit a little bit better.
Let me see, um, let's see if I can re retrace the steps.
Oh, I flew on jet blue for the first time, which I had no idea what it was.
Um, they're using the airbus 320, which is, I think the same aircraft that easy jet users only.
If you've never been on jet blue, it's kind of like, you know, it's the service I'd like.
It's the bus, just like the, well, the name says at the airbus.
And there's three seats on each side of the aisle.
And, uh, it's like the nice gray leather seat.
And it's not that wide, but it is.
It feels like it's probably two or three inches wider than your normal, uh, real packed-up,
sardine coat seat.
And the, the leg room between the seat in front of you and your, and your seat is really, it's sufficient.
So even I could stretch my legs out without my knees or my shins hitting the seat in front of me.
Um, and you get your, uh, direct TV, you know, 36 channels of live television,
which actually, you know, I found could get me through most of the flight.
They don't serve any food, you have blooper-tated chips and, and water and coffee and stuff.
Uh, but I liked it.
I really, you know, I'm, I'm a big fan of, you know, just give me a comfortable bus
that everyone can just, you know, get on and get off him, and that's perfect.
And I have to say, great service.
And, uh, relatively inexpensive.
I think, uh, what was it round trip was like five or six hundred bucks, which, uh,
uh, now that's value for money.
I really enjoyed enjoying paying that.
That's cool.
Uh, a couple of things I'm going to tell you about New York.
Uh, first I got a, I got a correct, uh, mistake.
Well, I didn't really make a mistake, but, you know, I said the other day, I think it was, uh,
either Monday or Friday.
I was wondering what, uh, what the currency of Ireland was.
And of course, I said something stupid like,
Dubloons.
Yeah, I've got a lot of love email these days.
Hey, Adam is pretty awesome.
And I'm sure you're getting eight thousand messages about this.
But the currency in Ireland is the euro.
They're part of the European Union.
And the only thing that makes it tough is when you're doing the UK Scottish
Ireland tour on those wonderful brick rail passes,
that what you do all of it and see all of the
Isles there together is that there's a different currency and a different
print in each place.
Uh, the bank of Scotland has their own notes.
The ulcer banks and everything.
And Northern Ireland have their own notes.
Each bank issues their own.
In fact, some of them are actually made a plastic.
It's quite strange.
And then you go down to Dublin.
And everybody uses Europe.
And then back again.
So, hope that's helpful.
I'm sure you're getting eight thousand messages.
Take care.
I hope you're feeling better.
And try that airborne stuff.
That really works to sort of hit off cold.
When you start feeling that congestion coming on.
It works like a charm.
Take care.
Bye bye.
It's amazing.
So many people have said that to me that airborne stuff.
And there's a million different versions of the airborne brand.
And of course everyone's telling me to take it after I already have contracted.
I stopped that type of airborne virus.
When you're breathing the same air as everybody else for 10 hours in a row.
Recycle air.
But appreciate it.
Yeah, of course it's the euro.
I knew that.
I was kind of thinking what wasn't before then.
And that is true, by the way.
If you've never been to Europe that we all would.
So now we basically everybody has the same monetary unit.
The euro except for the UK and Sweden.
I want to say Sweden didn't participate.
They still have the corona.
But every single bank note is minted.
Well, I think it's minted in individual countries.
And they have their own pictures on it.
Excuse me, Sensei.
I'm going brought to you by Splendid.
DestinationSplendid.com.
Now destinationflavor.com.
That's what I was.
I got a chance out in the show notes too.
And the hell was I saying?
Yeah.
So actually in, I think the most euro currency I've seen is all been German.
Because there's just so much Germanness in Europe.
And I guess the German is travel a lot because you see a lot of German euro coins everywhere.
Actually.
So thank you.
Thousands of you who sent that message to the same message.
Oh, I got my Mac back, by the way.
Yeah.
This is the power book G4, which was the third in a series to blow up successfully.
And I got so fed up with it.
And that's when I got the via laptop.
So Guillermo at Podio HQ the other day, he said,
Hey, dude, we got your power book G4 back.
And all your data is intact.
We were able to save all the data.
In fact, you almost have an entirely new laptop.
So what are you talking about?
Well, I look at the parts list of all the shit they had to replace.
And I was really weird.
It was like they replaced all kinds of encasing around the drive and the power unit and the memory.
And all these different, really structural bits.
And, you know, if you look at this list, it does indeed almost look like they gave me a whole new power book.
Of course, this gave me immediately gave me the opportunity to, you know, to play around with it.
And the first thing I know, well, the two things I noticed,
yeah, you cannot beat how nice everything looks on the screen on a Mac.
You just can't.
Although, I think the luminance,
the luminance,
is that what's called the luminance, the brightness that I'm getting from the via screen.
Man, that's, it's so much more light that comes off that thing compared to the Mac and Taj.
But there is something really nice about that.
I guess it's the courts overlay.
And then the next thing you know, it is almost immediately,
it's how slow it really is compared to this dual core intel,
dual core pro,
fuchum, flakum, whatever it is.
Even just using a browser, you know, if I just use Firefox over Firefox,
just how things open and how things scroll, it really is.
It feels like it's probably not half a slow, but it really does feel like it.
So now I'm using both now.
I'm, I'm just by.
So the whole reason we were actually in New York was for this conference.
Of course, we took advantage of the fact that Ron and I were there,
and we had a sales Weasel Gregg,
we had our new sales Weasel Andrew,
Bedowski,
who else do we have there, pod, pan, pan,
brousel was there.
Yeah, it really was the,
the go out kick ass and,
and sell stuff team.
And it was a, I guess it's symposium or a conference.
I'd like to call it symposium actually,
which was organized by an agency that we work with OMD,
and they were doing this this full day for their clients.
This is typically what we do for your clients.
A look into the future of, of internet, a series of tubes.
It was called White Hot and Digital,
but what's kind of cool about is they did it in the NBC studios,
not just the NBC studios,
but these Saturday night live studios,
which they had basically, you know,
the set was all there.
They just converted a couple pieces,
so it could be a stage.
And it was essentially, you know,
a full day of listening to speakers different,
from different backgrounds, different disciplines.
And I was on a panel,
and this was a lot of fun.
And by the way,
we weren't allowed to take any pictures there.
You know,
so only the NBC staff photographer,
I guess it was taken,
it was allowed to take pictures.
So I'm waiting to get some pictures back.
But I was on a panel,
which was moderated by Josh Quittner,
who I've known for 100 years.
And I think he's another editor and chief of business 2.0.
But I know him back from the MTV.com days.
He had actually,
he wrote a lot about the domain name dispute
that I had with MTV,
and he had registered McDonald's.com, I think.
So, you know,
we kind of share some history there,
and he was moderating the panel,
and the panel consisted of myself,
of Christopher Wolfe, CEO of my space,
I think so.
And Chad,
the co-founder of YouTube.
So, you know,
this was fun.
It was fun for the three of us to be sitting there,
and really talking about three different ways
of how our businesses work,
and they really are three different types of businesses,
fascinating,
we've had Chris, by the way,
from my space.
Dude, I think this guy's got an inch on me.
It's fucking tall, unbelievable.
It's like, you know,
three, you know,
dirty, blondish, geeky boys on a panel.
Oh, shoot.
Yeah.
It's like I've been hooking up a lung.
Oh, hold on.
Do some for yourself.
People talk about it, baby.
Sam, doing it wrong, doing it wrong.
We don't you worry, baby.
Don't worry.
Cause I'm a wife,
and wife,
and my bum.
Cause I'm a folder,
I'm a scruncher,
I'm a roller,
and I'm a buncher.
I do my business on the throne.
I'm a sitter,
I'm a standard,
I'm a left-to-right tender.
It's nice to know I'm not alone.
Yeah, I've noticed that,
you know, all that gunk and stuff,
it only really kicks in when I'm laugh.
It didn't happen on the panel, luckily.
Although I did get the audience to go for a second there.
It was,
what we're talking about,
it was, oh, you're talking about advertising.
Oh, how,
you know,
I look at advertising as content,
something to do something with.
Like the splendid stuff we've been talking with,
what a fantastic example.
All the stories you've been sending me about,
Splendon,
the mix as you've been making.
And I said,
you know,
when's the last time someone called you up and said,
hey,
fantastic direct mail piece you sent me.
You know,
I love the way you started that,
got pulled my name out of the hat.
You know,
when's the last time someone called a company and said,
hey, man,
it was,
thanks for letting me click through.
Great banner.
You just don't hear that stuff.
So it was a good conversation in the audience,
who,
unfortunately,
also due to just the illness and the weather was crap.
We had to go,
you know,
it took us two hours to get to the airport.
When it rains in New York,
you know what happens.
Joseph Jaffee was there.
So it was nice to meet him in person.
I unfortunately,
I really didn't have time.
You know,
the morning just say, hey,
how you doing bend over.
So we'll have to catch him another time.
It was good to see him though.
Let me give you this one promo.
And then I got another song for you for today.
You like this, I think,
hold on.
Check this out.
The rustling leaves
and increasing darkness
herald the approach of all Hallows Eve.
It is a time for ghouls,
goblins
and spooks
to roam free among us.
This year,
the window to the magic dot com podcast
will be playing host
to these specters
as they bring you an all new
Halloween show.
This will be unlike anything
you have heard from them before.
Join us
Sunday, October 29th
as the window to the magic dot com podcast
travels to Disneyland, USA
to present the all original radio drama
secrets of the wooden door.
Your favorite window to the magic personalities
and some very special guests
will venture forth into unknown
environments of the famous
haunted mansion.
Listen in
if you dare.
All right.
And of course,
with Halloween just around the door,
you can also organize a shadow
falls listening party.
We got to figure out if we're going to do
another season of shadow falls.
I feel like I don't want to be left hanging.
That's for sure.
You haven't heard it yet.
Episode six is out.
Shadowfall. podshow.com.
Very good.
Very good stuff.
Okay.
So anyway,
so we got back last night.
Of course,
everything was delayed by an hour.
Got into Oakland at 1 a.m.
in bed by around 2.30
and you can understand just how
crappy I feel today.
If you listen to us on
serious stars,
one or two got a fantastic line up
with the podshow on serious
for you for the next
three and a half hours
taking up until 10 o'clock eastern.
And for those of you
checking us out on the podcast.
Oh,
I got some cool music for you.
Dennis Gray from
101 uses for baby wipes.
Probably remember the podshow podcast network.
It sends in dude this song
from Kelly Le Evans.
She's cute clever.
Songs very mellow.
It's fantastic when you're night
not feeling too well.
It's quote nice jazz
to blow your nose to you.
You don't call me anymore.
I just as I play.
Finally I can be alone.
Things were so out of hand.
But these minds are cold without you.
And every day I still dream about you.
How can you get along with them me?
How dare you love again?
Who is she?
How can you get along with them me?
When I still need you,
I still need you.
So let's just say that I miss both.
We can start love again.
We can pretend it was all a joke.
You can get a ready on your friend.
Because these minds are cold without you.
How dare every day I still dream about you.
How can you get along with them me?
How dare you love again?
Who is she?
How can you get along with them me?
When I still need you,
I still need you.
I'll be so sure.
I'll be so sweet.
You won't recognize me.
Can you ignore what I said last week?
You always said I was crazy.
Crazy.
I'm crazy about you.
How can you get along with them me?
How dare you love again?
Who is she?
How can you get along with them me?
When I still need you,
I still need you.
You're right, Dennis.
Thank you, man.
Kelly Lee Evans.
How can I get along without you?
Now on the pod save music network,
you can find a link to that in the show notes today at dailysourcecode.com.
All right, so I'm going to regroup here.
Blow my shnaz a couple more times.
Get dressed and then it's off to HQ.
I am kind of ready to go back home.
I have to say I'm missing the girls very much.
The in laws are they're going back today.
So I missed their visit.
Which I'm sad about because it's always fun to hang out with my in laws for limited period of time.
Um,
crap, I don't know.
So much stuff.
So much stuff to do.
I always feel like I'm short-changing you guys.
One amount here because there's so much that goes on.
My head literally swims.
Okay, well you got to run down from New York.
And tomorrow I'll tell you what's happening here in San Francisco.
Because we got new people coming in, new things we're doing.
We're getting very close to the official official unleash of
BTpodshow.com.
So we're all going to be back in the UK pretty soon.
It's just a lot of shit going on.
But it is a lot of fun.
Hey, give me a call.
I haven't gotten a lot of voicemail recently.
And I think it's probably because I haven't been hawking the numbers much as I used to.
Um,
plus one 20120163.
What the hell is it?
Yeah, that's it.
Now everybody.
Talk to you tomorrow.
Adam at podshow.com.
See you, bye.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.