It's time you've got in the game.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Get a domain name, frequent blog, and complete email.
Get in the game at GoDaddy.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie 5 to 8.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm suggesting kids that are great.
Dear star, mood, apathetic.
My life is spiraled like that word.
I couldn't get enough of mine to go to the bloodbed romance and suffocate me dry concert.
It sucks because they play with my favorite songs.
Stop my heart because I love you and rip apart my soul.
Of course, stab your ribs, stab, stab, stab.
It doesn't help that I couldn't get my hair to that flippy thing either.
It's like that guy from that band can do.
Some days now.
I'm an emo kid.
I'm not informing as can be.
You've been not informing too if you look just like me.
I have painted my nails and make it on my face.
I'm almost emo enough to start shaving my legs because I feel real deep.
When I'm dressing in drag, I call it freedom of expression.
What's this called me a bag?
Because our dudes look like chicks.
Nerd chicks look like dykes because emo is one step below.
Transvestite.
Stop my breathing and slip my throat.
I must be emo.
I don't jump around when I go to shows.
I'm dark.
And sensitive with those of a steam.
The way I dress makes everyday feel like Halloween.
I have no real problems but I'd like to make believe.
I stole my sister's mask here and now I'm grounded for a week.
And writing poetry or my hobbies.
I can't get through a hollown heights up and without sobbing.
Goes keep breaking up with me.
It's never any fun.
They say they already have a pussy.
They don't need another one.
Stop my breathing and slip my throat.
I must be emo.
I don't jump around when I go to shows.
Dying my hair and polish on my toes.
I must be emo.
I play guitar and write suicide notes.
My life is just a black abyss.
You know, it's so dark.
And it's suffocating me.
Craving a holl for me and tightening a strip.
Tired of the pair of little sister's jeans.
Which is a great update for the lady.
When I get depressed, I cut my recent every direction.
Hearing songs by getting dumped give me an erection.
I write in a live drill and where I think we're in blasts.
I tell my friends I bleed black and cry during blasts.
I'm just a bad, cheap imitation of God.
Digging me catcher in the right and watch me jack off.
I were skinned tight clothes while hating my life.
If I said I like girls, I'd only be half right.
I look like I'm dead and just like a homo.
I must be emo.
Screw Xbox.
I play old school Nintendo.
I must be emo.
I'd like to wine and hit my parental's.
Me and my friends all look like clones.
I must be emo.
My parents don't get me now.
They think I'm gay just because they saw me kiss a guy.
Well, a couple guys.
But I mean, it's a 2000's.
Can't two or four dudes make out with each other without being gay.
I mean, chicks dig that kind of thing anyways.
I don't know, Dari.
Sometimes I think you're the only one that gets me.
It's Adam and Andrew.
The emo kid.
Hey, everybody.
Talk us.
How you doing?
Welcome to the Daily Source Code episode 528 coming to you from Curri Condo.
I am crippled.
It's perfect.
Quabar today is in full effect.
I got no connectivity at the condo.
Oh, man.
No connectivity at the other place, which we still haven't found the name for.
Worked in on it.
Yeah.
Oh, I hate it.
I hate it.
Apparently, what's been going on is Comcast, the incumbent.
And you know, I don't have a telephone line in here at all.
I have, I don't need a telephone line.
I got a cell phone.
I just all I needed was a cable modem, cable connection.
Someone I arrived to yesterday.
Was it yesterday?
No, the day before yesterday, Wednesday.
I rolled into town and the minute I walked in, you know, I fired up the eye
Mac.
I fired up my, uh, my Nokia to connect it to the network.
It connects to the Curri Condo network and no connectivity outside.
Turn on the television.
No television.
Well, that's a pretty big clue right there.
What's been happening is Comcast is now.
This is what they say.
I'm not quite sure what it means.
They've been changing quote provider.
I didn't know that Comcast had to deal with their own provider.
But the provider that, uh, I guess brings the lines into different buildings, including
the condo.
Three floors were out for a week apparently.
And so we had all kinds of people running around because yeah, without connectivity
at the condo, I might as well go to a hotel.
You know, it makes no sense for me to stay here.
It's really pissing me off.
So the, uh, Wednesday afternoon or Wednesday evening when I got back, it worked.
Television worked.
Everything was fantastic.
And then in the morning yesterday morning, uh, I had, you know, no connectivity.
And about, um, a third of the channels that I normally get on television are coming in.
So clearly, there's something wrong with a throughput in the building.
I guess it's just, I don't know, but it's really pissing me off.
You just forget how incredibly dependent you are on on some type of real connection.
And so I've been trying to pair up my vio, uh, through Bluetooth to my, uh, E61, uh, download stuff from the edge network.
Man, that's, that's, I'm telling you, that, that really is football.
Which, of course, stands for fucked up beyond our repair.
Trying to make one of those connections.
No way.
I just can't figure it out.
Then you've got to have all these logins and data.
And it's fucking seven o'clock in the morning.
So I'm having a wonderful day.
How about you guys?
Really pissed off.
But at least it's weekend.
So, um, I guess we'll just get someone on the case and keep calling the help desk all day long and trying to get this shit squared away.
Because I really, I will go to a hotel.
I can't stay here if I don't have a connection.
Now there's all kinds of connections.
And you know, people are getting a little tight estimate.
And you know, I, I love to keep my wireless connections wide open.
I must be seeing at least 15 different networks from here.
And, uh, all of them are closed and locked up.
There's a couple that are open.
Now, one of them that I used to try or used to use when I just got into the condo before Comcast had delivered any type of connectivity.
Ben Bo 7.
I think is, uh, is the network name.
It's gotten real flaky.
It's probably this construction that's going on outside, which by the way,
that building that they've been putting up next to the condo is now officially at least at least 50 feet taller than my building.
So it's blocking out some of my view now for the first time.
Can you tell them having a really good day?
Ah.
What's been interesting is that lots of people have been sending in suggestions for the new place in Guilford,
West Side of Gtown.
Of course, I don't really want to call it the Curry condo anymore.
Uh, or the Curry Cottage.
I'm sorry.
Because we already had one of those.
We come up with Camp Curry, Curry Compound.
We got Curry Casbah, kind of like that one.
The Curry Complex, and people are calling in with ideas.
Hi Adam, it's Rowley from the Dark Compass podcast.
I'm just listening to the SCI-27.
I don't know fact on five to six you mentioned them as well.
The idea of your Adam Curry, Curry condo Curry Cottage.
Well, that's a curry.
I don't know if it's not exactly British.
But thank you.
I just want to push that your wife and the same wife.
Yeah, Curry Casa.
Yeah.
I don't know.
If I had a place in Spain, it would be perfect.
It would be the Curry Casa, or the place in Portugal.
They would work most excellent.
But no.
Uh, let's see.
By the way, it took me about 45 minutes to get these voicemails in.
Here's what I did.
I downloaded them through the tablet.
Uh, the internet tablet, the N800 through the GSM from the E61.
Then transferred those via Bluetooth over to to the via.
So I could load them up.
And of course, I still had to transcode them from the GSM format.
Whatever that file format is that J2.com uses had to transcode them into MP3.
So it was a nice, you know, you're going to listen to all the freaking phone calls today,
because I spent so much time getting them.
I had them as party checking in from a rather grey, cold and miserable London.
There you go. That's life.
Just quick question.
Um, what happens to your parents on Twitter?
I was really looking forward to that.
I appreciate an update.
Check it.
Yeah, that's a good one.
Um, it kept getting messed up.
We were, there was a first I came back.
I was, uh, was it four weeks ago.
I came back on a Sunday, uh, which meant I would have had to stay up until midnight.
Because I think they tapered three or four in the afternoon.
And then it was Christmas and there was new years.
And then I forgot a week.
And so here we are back again.
I have kind of a standing invitation to just call in.
So, uh, depending on what's happening this weekend.
Uh, we have a, there is a photo shoot going on at the office.
With one of our new, uh, new hosts.
I'm not going to tell you about it just yet.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh...
Since sale was a damn nice splendor on top.
So maybe Sunday afternoon I'll call into, I'll call in to Twitter.
James Newcastle.
Uh, Adams antique a boat.
He feedback.
All right, like that.
The trip away.
Adams antique a boat.
And maybe we should move away from the C.C.
It's just, I like saying, curry-
Something, curry, condom.
Creech, Creech lost in me bag, you know, that kind of stuff.
It just kind of feels good.
Hey everybody, it's Friday.
Let's make it work like a Friday and roll out some food bar tunes
from the archives of course.
I couldn't download anything new.
Deck of Jones.
First date.
Electricity.
When you walk in, you set my circuit tree.
Back it up.
We've got to do it, we're people swearin' it out,
you always play it cool.
I think I know you, I'm gonna bet,
if you like super joke,
and don't get, get your quick fix,
in my car.
You got a sweet truth, then I'm your trippler boy.
And it goes on.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
And I say hey, hey,
do you kiss for the first date?
Do you kiss for the first date?
Cause I do, cause I do, cause I do, cause I do, cause I do, cause I do, cause I do, cause I do.
New York, down.
On the catwalk, I like to play it to spring.
You don't want to show, sway, pain you.
Touching you.
And who's yourself?
Don't be wrong, don't take it chance.
Give me your shot.
You think I'm bluffing?
I think I'm not, get on your hideeal.
Give me your hideeal.
I got a question for your sweet ass.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
And I say hey, hey,
do you kiss for the first date?
Do you kiss for the first date?
Cause I do, do you do, what I do?
And with you, if you do, what you do, what I do?
Well, hello, baby, you look so hot tonight.
Can I hold your hand?
What the heck?
Now, this is what we're going to do in our date today.
We're going to do all the things all the couples like to do.
We're going to go to a movie.
We're going to have some dinner.
Take a walk, look at the moonlight.
Anything you want, but baby, I got a question.
Do you kiss for the first date?
Let's do it off a first date.
Hey!
What do you do, what the first date?
Do you kiss for the first date?
If I do, I do, cause I do, cause I do.
Cause I do, cause I do, cause I do.
Thank you Jones you can find them on the pod save music network. You can go to
podshow.com slash music and just do a search on Danko Jones. We got a couple of
awesome new artists on the pod save music network, which of course I was thinking about
playing for you on this wonderful Friday afternoon where the sun is shining in northern
California. It is beautiful. It's very cold though. Apparently back home or back on the island
from member the united kingdom. It is the new Caribbean with global warming. We've had
exactly the opposite. It's been peace soup. It's been 80 mile an hour winds, trees falling
down. The girls give me reports through email. We second still receive that.
The hell was I going to say? Anyway, so a lot of people sent in email
and said, why didn't you come in on the weekend? Why did you come to San Francisco
midweek? That's because we had our presentation of our 2007 plan
for our board of directors, which I love doing these meetings. This is so much fun because
these are smart people. Very smart. And what I get to do in the meetings, I get to do lots of
demos. I love doing the demos. Yesterday I showed two things I showed podshow TV and you're going to
love this. This is our interface for podshow plus the runs on IPTV or media center.
So when that's done and when it's available, you literally will be able to load up podshow
into your television. Hence the name podshow TV. I think it's so amazing to play around with this
stuff because we've totally come up with a different interface than what people are using,
or typically using for media center or for IPTV. IPTV isn't really rolled out yet anywhere,
but BT British telecom is rolling it out this year. Of course, that's the target.
And there's lots of stuff to do still, but man, I love showing that because all of a sudden,
just browsing through people's profile and seeing what they're subscribed to,
what they're listening to, what they're watching. That becomes fun just all by itself.
When you're doing with remote control, there's something awesome about it. And of course,
we showed a lot of programming. We've got a brand new Marie Claire episode out,
which is a one up yesterday, the mast head. You can find it at MarieClaire.podshow.com.
What else went up? brand new in the attic? Let me play the intro from, I know that I played the
shit. I hope I have it. Did I delete that already? Oh, that would suck.
Hold on, I have to plug something in and don't I see if I can get this running through the mixer,
hold on. This is the show with the Rachel Fuller and her boyfriend. Oh, a guy named Pete
Townsend. You might have heard of him before. Okay. I wasn't quite set up for this, so just give me
a moment while I open it. I got a just all kinds of volume controls. I want you to hear the opening
of the show. It's episode. What does I think? It's episode number eight. What is it here? Here it is.
Okay. Now with a little bit of luck, it should actually play. Let's see if it works. Hold on.
Yeah. Hi, this is Rachel Fuller from in the attic with my special guest. I'm Pete Townsend of
the hoop. And in the attic. In the attic on every show. Anyway, you are watching podshow.com
and you are about to watch episode eight of in the attic on the road in Europe. And in this episode,
it features the cokes that lovely boys. Yeah, very well. Some mother them, they're so
young and lovely. And it's like spotty herb. They're very, very sweet. And they played a song called
Ula. And this was at the paleo festival in Switzerland earlier on this year. And we also have a
track from you from the new album. And I'm not going to tell you what it is. You're going to have to watch it.
Yeah, it's from the new album in this one. It's me doing an acoustic version, extended version
of a certain track. Of a certain track. And I'll say your brother comes on and play something. Simon,
my brother does he? Oh, good. That's good. I was here. You're like this show. It's a good show.
Here it comes. I enjoyed it. I enjoyed it. Welcome to podshow.
Don't come. Ah, that's the money shop, man. I love it. You're going to like this show.
It's another fantastic one from the in the attic folks. Got another show that we're launching.
And we're doing it in video, even though it highlights a video and audio. We've got a brand new
host in the UK. Her name is Josephine Lawrence. And she's doing a show specifically for the UK,
but US guys, in girls, you might enjoy it too. Check it out. Oh, you can't see it, Canyon. Well,
just listen along. Hi there, guys and girls. Welcome to podfines. My name is Josephine Lawrence.
And today I'm going to be reviewing a sum of the best podcasters. Josephine. Josephine Lawrence
doing podfinder UK, podfinderuk.podshow.com. So I was showing all of this stuff through a
cast blaster video. And I didn't tell him about it. And I had a cast. When you see this thing,
it's in beta now. You're going to shit yourself. It is perfect for people who just want to
upload stuff. It is perfect for people who just upload a video. Don't do anything. There's uploaded.
It's perfect if you want to send something to a friend, a clip and want to add a little intro
through your webcam. Or if you want to produce a show, it's exactly the same theory as cast blaster
audio. So all they saw really was what like 12 different small windows. Every single time I
played a clip, it would show up in the big, what we'd call the program window. And down the right
hand corner off the side, there was a little window, which was my built-in camera on the via. When I kind
of had the lid position, so you didn't see a lot of movement, so it didn't distract, so people weren't
really seeing it. So when it came time to talk about cast blaster video, I'm tilted the lid and
I said, and I threw my, my built-in camera actual. And then in the meeting, I plugged in a second
USB cam just to off the shelf thing. And I pointed it at the board, who were on the other side of
the table. And I switched back and forth and they were like, wow, and I said, yeah, and check this out.
And plugged in a third one. So we had a three camera shoot all of a sudden running from my laptop.
And then I recorded a little bit. And it was so cool to do video shows this way. I think it's going to,
I think the people who are really like this will be vloggers as well. It's a fantastic vlogging tool.
Now, we're doing something interesting. Cast blaster mic, and I've been talking for quite a while
about video and video on the web and how, man, for 20 years, everything's been completely
fucked up. Thanks to Apple and Windows, fighting each other, quick time versus Windows media.
So, you know, if you ever wonder why an MP4 file will play on your iPod, but won't play on
something else, like Windows media player or vice versa, you can have an MP4, which will play
fine on Windows media player, but not on your iPod or in quick time. It's because
MP4 is just kind of like a container. It's just, it's like a box that you put the quick time video in.
So it's, none of that shit's compatible. And of course, if you look at the real success of
video on the web, it's flash flashes work and just about everywhere. What is the problem with this?
What is the problem with flash? This is what we went through here. Some of our thinking.
The problem with flash, if you upload to YouTube or Google video or pod show at this moment in
time, you know, we've got our viral video stuff. You can upload your videos. Actually, they have
the the share codes in the now too. So they truly are viral, not just flash videos.
Excuse me, Mr. Petita. The problem is you upload something. The quality turns to shit. It takes
a long time, sometimes depending on how many people are uploading stuff. And doesn't matter
what service you're using, whether using pod show or Google or YouTube or Reber, whoever it takes
some time for the video to be transported into flash. It's painful. So Mike and I came up
with a pretty evil plan, I think. And the idea is to hook up cast blaster video to the
PDN, the pod show pod cast delivery network, the same way the audio version works. So it's one
click publishing essentially, but to do the transcoding locally. So you'll be able to output
different formats, including flash. So we're setting it up. So you can have top notch top quality
fantastic flash videos that you can then with one click upload to pod show and then MP4 will be
put into an iPod compatible MP4, I'd have to say, we'll be put into into the feed. I mean,
we can go anywhere with this. Since this thing can literally shoot out anything out of the back
end of its ass, any format. We could have, you know, you can have four different versions,
all with one click of the button. So I'm very excited about that. Of course, you have to have
connectivity in order to actually use it. But the awesome thing about it is it will eat anything.
So you can throw in a Windows media file, an FLV, a quick time movie, an MP4, anything you want,
it will take and it will play. So all that transcoding and all of those formats and all that
shit is taking care of right before you're very eyes. And on the back end, you can just produce
one file that has awesome quality. And you can, yeah, as I said, you can use it as a production tool.
And in fact, Father Roderick, I saw was using it a very interesting way, using little
pre-packaged bits. And he was basically linking those together by switching back to his webcam.
You got to see this thing. I don't know if you can still sign up for the beta.
But if you, if you have a chance, go to castblastard.com. You will not be disappointed. I promise you.
All right. It is time to get out of here for food bar because I got to go to the office and upload
the show. And hopefully, we'll have more new music to play and more comments and promos on Monday
as connectivity is restored to the Curry Condo. Leave in you with the bitties. He's a hell of a boy.
Well, his song is true, but his head keeps getting in the way.
Now it's not like he's got a nasty disposition.
Once to keep you locked up tight and knocked upright, barefoot in the kitchen.
He's a hell of a boy. Only, only half of a man.
No, it's not like the boys about it. Born on the wrong side of town, under the wrong wall, on the wrong day.
Just what do you think you will get every person's thinking? This is the best you can do.
Say no to your life girl. I'll be fine. You know it. Your life's going to say no to you.
Easy call, easy call, life's too short to live. So, no, it's not like it's more than you can say
to have that pretty boy sitting next to you kissing you, holding your hand.
He's a hell of a boy. But only, only half of a man.
I like it, I like it, I like it, he's a hell of a boy. But only, only half of a man.
The city is British. He's a hell of a boy. You could find him on the pod save music network
and regularly here on the daily source code. Before I go, one more thing I wanted to play for
another new episode of a show going up called Who's on it? O.J. Borge, host that show,
you can find it at Who's on it.podshow.com. We got a whole great series of shows coming up.
Our episode is coming up for that show. We've got dirty sand chessal beyond Rachel and Pete. I think
are going to be on and they had the shakes on. Now, the shakes, as you know, debut their new
single. I want a better life to the pod save music network before radio, before the albums coming out.
This is the second, oh, this is the second one they're doing off the album.
I know, of course, Liberty Jones we all know, but now they came out with
I want a better life. And these guys, they know how to use our network. So they've got their
songs up on the pod save music network. They get tons of pod play. They're using our uploader
to upload their videos and live performances. You can find them because they're doing their own
show at the shakes dot pod show dot com. The shakes dot pod show dot com. And they're also
guests on the, on the upcoming episode of Who's on it, which I think might go up this weekend or
today, even. And they did something really cool. We had them come in and no, they were chatting away
with OJ and OJ pulled out these toy instruments, like a little toy guitar, a toy keyboard
and a toy drum kit. And they were game for it. And they played a version of I want to better
life, which I'll play a little bit for you here on a second. They've got a sign on the drum kit.
All right. And I want to better all the learnings, but in these small worlds, I'm my
living life, I want to better. I want to be your man. All right, you should go check out
who's on a dot pod show dot com for more about that. All right, I got to get out of here. I'm going to
go to the office. We got a lot of stuff going on today. Actually, we're doing something for another company.
I'm doing a video thing. Guess what company that's for? If you want a great deal in domain
name, check out GoDaddy dot com. Use check out code dsc3 for a fantastic deal. You know,
all about splendor. Of course, they don't have to promote the stomp to stomp the art anymore.
So they're in one movie. We did our job exactly what you expected. I told you it would work.
It's working. I'm so confused here by everything that's, uh, this is the one. Yeah, that's the one.
Okay. Hey, everybody. Adam and pod show dot com and a daily source code dot com. I'll
get the show notes up there. And if you, uh, if you have any connectivity for me, just send it my
way, please have yourself a great weekend, everybody. I'll talk to you on Monday once again from
Northern California at the Curry condo. Bye bye. Another pod show podcast. Stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds and content delivery.
Pudge-o in line light.