Hey, Kathy, what you doing?
Oh, I was just getting the bedtime stories.
My kids love intro ready for daily source code 541.
Fulger's coffee.
Wait a minute.
Did you just say Fulger's coffee?
Yep, what abouts in sale?
Things have changed again.
And now, every time you burp, it's Fulger's.
Really?
So it's not like...
Splendor?
Nope.
It's not Fulger's coffee?
Yep.
All right.
Fulger's?
Very good, Pearl.
Now it's time to introduce the show.
Daily source code 541.
With 15 bags of Splendor stuck in our pants.
Sugar!
And 15 bags of toilet paper hanging from our cracks.
We don't need no sticking sugar!
I'd like to think I'm right.
For the future.
I'll be honest if she is so serious.
I need somebody else.
I'll just anybody else.
You know I need someone else.
When I was young, I was so much younger than today.
I never knew if anybody's helping anyway.
Now that now these days are gone, I'm not so selfish.
Sure.
Now that I find the gym mind, I don't burn up the doors.
Help me if you can, I'm feeling down.
I'd like to appreciate you being around.
Help me if my feet's right on the ground.
Won't you please please help me?
I've found out my life has changed so so many ways.
I have deep breath and seems to vanish in the days.
But if I'm now in my heart, I feel so insecure.
I know I'd just be right.
I never done before.
Help me if you can, I'm feeling down.
I'd like to appreciate you being around.
Help me if my feet's right on the ground.
Won't you please please help me?
I've found out my life has changed so many ways.
I never knew if anybody's helping anyway.
Now that now these days are gone, I'm not so selfish.
Sure.
Now that I find the gym mind, I don't burn up the doors.
Help me if you can, I'm feeling down.
I'd like to appreciate you being around.
Help me if my feet's right on the ground.
Won't you please help me if you can, I'm feeling down.
What's this?
Am I out of my mind?
Am I crazy?
Have I finally flipped my lid?
Have I smoked one split too many?
Oh my goodness.
Do I want to go to jail?
No, my friends.
You just heard the future of the legacy of Steve Jobs.
Yep.
What happened yesterday was monumental.
And I want to talk to you about it.
And I'm not worried at all about playing the Beatles.
One of the most protected copyrighted artists of all time.
I would have to say, most well-managed.
Most one of the most profitable catalogs.
Because things are going to change very rapidly.
I've probably seen online in the headline and newspapers all across the globe today.
An essay that Steve Jobs wrote called Thoughts on Music.
And it really focuses in hones in on the use of digital rights management.
And he makes an argument.
And quite a compelling case that selling music without digital rights management.
In other words, restrictions, which means, well, to cut through to it.
Eventually, everything would be on MP3.
And you could copy to any device and you could share it around with friends.
You could do whatever you'd want with it.
But it will actually sell more music than the current state of the union, if you will.
Excuse me.
Fulger's Coffee.
And it's only part of the story.
And this is a very carefully orchestrated strategy that Steve Jobs has been working on for,
I believe, quite some time.
We came more or less apparent to me a few weeks ago at the Apple keynote at Mac world,
where Steve Jobs slipped in a couple of Beatles tracks during his infamous keynote.
Not only did he do that, but he announced that Apple computer wouldn't be known as Apple Inc.
And lo and behold.
And of course, I don't know the details if it's a true acquisition or exactly what the deal is.
But believe me, Steve Jobs is an excellent businessman.
And the deal that he did with Apple Records is completely to the benefit of everybody, including Apple.
And of course, indirectly Steve Jobs.
And let me see if I can explain this to you because I see this strategy unfolding clearly before our very eyes.
So Steve Jobs knows what the real money is in music.
It's in the publishing.
It's in licensing.
And he knows because he's been on the payment end of this by paying for Beatles cataloged to use in Apple commercial.
I think maybe he used a revolution that may have been a couple others.
It probably were.
So he knows what kind of money that's, what kind of money that can mean.
At the same time, he also knows that the money that he makes on sales through the iTunes music stores,
pretty much negligible.
Of course, 2 billion of anything is a lot of money or it's a lot of anything.
But it's really just to spit in the bucket if you compare it to Apple's core business and where they're headed.
Let me see if I can get this all down for you.
So what he's pleading for and in this memo and of course, there's a link to it.
If you haven't read it already, there's a link to it from the show notes on today's podcast daily source code.com.
You'll see that he's making very,
a major plea to the other major record labels or to the major record labels to sell DRM free because he's making a comparison.
You really got to read the words carefully.
He's making a comparison between CDs and the iPod.
And certainly with the way pricing is working and more is law and all that stuff.
The iPod without a doubt is the CD of the future.
People are always going to pay for packaging.
And we know that there are more honest people than there are dishonest people.
We've proven that with podcasting artists who are member of the pod safe music network have contributed their music free.
And clear, of course, it could be by definition.
It's being downloaded by podcasters.
They're using it in their show, which creates another copy, which of course, if you really wanted to, you could go and rip it off.
People aren't doing that.
And because it's very simple to go and buy a track through the pod safe music network or garage band or CD baby or iTunes music store anywhere,
because that process has become very simple.
People are doing it because they, you know, they'll buy a CD from CD baby.
Why do they want the packaging?
How successful do you think that you too iPod was?
I have a feeling it was extremely successful.
And so of course, of course, Steve Jobs knows that the way to go is to package the content.
In this case, the, I would presume the entire Beatles catalog to package that into special iPods.
Perhaps even preloaded on on max that you buy in the store.
I believe that in the future, you may even have an iPod for your Beatles music and iPod for your commute and iPod for your podcasts,
maybe nice.
I think that's very possible.
And they'll be completely interchangeable.
What's the difference?
You're just picking up a piece of plastic.
You know, a little piece of plastic.
You slip it in.
You stick, you're jam the buds in your ears and you're off.
And you've got whatever you want.
You can easily carry a couple of these things with you.
And they'll become just like CDs.
And that's that packaging is what Jobs knows so much about.
He knows exactly how to sell to the, to the, to the customer to his customer.
So the way, I think this is the next step for him.
And if you do the math, I think it really works out.
I believe that now that Steve Jobs has, in effect, become a record company and owns, at least owns the rights to do something with the Beatles catalog.
He will put that out free and clear of DRM.
It'll be his choice.
And I'm sure he's, he's talked it over with the, with the Apple, formerly former Apple records people.
It'll be free and clear. It'll be packaged in max. It'll be packaged in iPods.
And that's where the money's coming from.
And it's going to be huge much more.
What, what do you hear the Beatles on the radio anymore?
Where do you hear it?
You don't, except on Beatles specific stations.
I've paid for this for these tracks 10 times in my life on all kinds of different collectors, CDs, vinyl, all the packaging.
It's all about the packaging.
And you know what, of course, I'll buy a Beatles iPod. Are you kidding me?
But by doing this, and this is where I think he sees the light, his, his legacy.
By being the first big quote label to step forward.
And to say, you know what, here it is. This is how it's done.
Watch the money come on in suckas.
He's going to break it wide open.
And you'll see every single record company selling through multiple channels.
It'll play on any device. You'll be able to do anything you want with it.
Because the real true money when you have a hit record, a hit song,
is in the licensing. It's in the publishing and to get it to people.
They'll gladly pay extra money if you put it into the right packaging.
And that is why I'm not worried about playing the Beatles on this podcast.
Well, that, and of course, the fact that it was such a crappy video version.
I stole off of my space.
But I don't think anyone would ever want to go and rip that one out.
But this is going to be a very exciting year.
I'm, I'm convinced of it.
And just listen to this.
Here's some of the reasoning that I love.
Today's most popular iPod holds 1,000 songs and research tells us that the average iPod is nearly full.
Listen to how he's talking about the iPod.
You know, this is like, it's like me who with Jaguars and you know, the ash trace full up,
time to buy a new one.
The iPod's full up, time to buy a new one.
I don't want to take tracks off.
I don't want to have to manage that.
Look, it costs me 40 bucks to buy the Beatles in the iPod.
Maybe it's 60.
Maybe it's 100.
Who cares?
And you'll buy, you know, the next yell and bands will be releasing their albums on special iPod.
This is, it is so clear that this is where it's going.
And there are lessons and not just lessons, but there's also a place in here for podcasting.
So, what can I do?
Let's have some fun with this.
Oh, yeah.
I don't, this is Gabe real one of your listeners in Dublin, Ireland.
Now, I was reading the news recently.
That the UK charts for the top singles have been revamped.
So, now that any downloaded track, as long as it's registered with the system, is in the
running to be in the chart.
And I was, as you might have heard, this is caused a bit of, you know, dramatic or people,
you know, old TV teams going into the charts and Chris Moiles ran a little campaign to get
someone back into the charts and he succeeded getting into number 17.
All I was thinking is, is there any plans for podshow music network?
To register with the system so that podsafe artists could potentially get some recognition on
the charts.
You know, this is a very good question.
I'm glad you bring it up in the context of, in the context of what we're talking about in
Holland.
Sorry.
I turned something up a little too far.
Okay.
It's better.
I don't want to blow your ear drums out.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, it's not going to matter because the only chart that is going to matter is going
to be the iTunes chart.
iTunes will become the largest record company in the world.
It's all there.
They've got the marketing.
They've got the distribution.
They've got the customer base.
What else do record companies do?
You know, nothing.
So, of course, you know, the hope is is that there will be enough exposure for indie artists.
But once this starts to build out and once DRM is removed and everyone's comfortable with
this equation, you're going to see all kinds of players and stores and wonderful ways to package
and distribute music.
And it will no longer be on this track.
Of course, people will buy in a track by track basis, but there's so much.
But people love music.
There's so much money.
And finally, this shit is being broken.
So, for us, what's important because this is where podcasting does play a very big role.
What's important for us is the pod play chart.
If you go to podshow.com slash music, any genre you click on, you'll see a chart of the
top songs in that genre as determined by pod play from podcasters who are member of the
pod safe music network, that's going to be a very important number because they're still
nothing more powerful than hearing your song on podcasts all over the world.
There is no more powerful marketing message when your friend, even if you're a group of
a thousand or a hundred or ten thousand or five hundred thousand, if someone says, hey, I like
this song.
Check it out.
That's the type of endorsement that radio it gives in mainstream media today.
And it's the type of endorsement of the future.
Or the qualities there.
And I'm quite sure that, you know, if you had the distribution now because there are two.
And you have all these people playing these songs.
It would be nice to get these artists directly nice on a wider level.
You know, outside the podcasting world.
I thought that might one way or two.
Alright, now I appreciate it.
So there you go.
It's all going to change.
God, I'm so excited about this.
Okay, let's see.
Where are we at right now?
Hi, Adam.
It's Eric Bergen.
You might remember my name.
I'm the host of Green Room Radio in Arts and Entertainment podcast.
And in fact, we were one of the first podcasts to feature a theme song by Jeff Smith.
Anyway, here's why I'm sending in this audio comment.
I was very involved in the podcasting world almost since the beginning.
In fact, that was one of your first listeners.
And I was a dedicated listener. I listened every single day.
In August, I made the decision to stop listening.
This was in about early to mid August.
And the decision came out of the fact that my other life, which was that of an actor,
actually started picking up steam and I started getting work.
And I was in rehearsals all day and doing shows at night.
And I just didn't have time for podcasting anymore.
I haven't done an episode of my own podcast since May.
Don't worry. We're coming back next week.
But I just, I just need to know.
I need a little update because I want to rejoin the daily source code listening experience.
But I need to know what's going on.
I can't just join the show and not know what's going on.
Did you move? It sounded like you moved houses?
What's this free Trinity thing?
I need if you could just give me or maybe one of your listeners could give me just a three minute update
of everything I need to know that's been happening in the daily source code world since I guess mid August.
The last time I checked in in August, the pod show website had just gone public.
But I think that was really the biggest thing that was going on then.
So if you could just, just let me know, just catch me up on everything.
I'm sorry to ask you.
I just, I want to rejoin, but I can't just rejoin and not know what's going on.
It's like trying to join 24 in the middle of the season.
You don't know what the hell's going on.
Also, next time you're in San Francisco,
I'm here for a while doing a little show called Jersey Boys playing at the current theater.
And I know Adam that you sort of are a Jersey boy because you lived there.
Now, the show isn't about you.
The show is actually about Frankie Valley and the four seasons.
But I'd love for you to come.
We're playing at the current theater right on Gary Street.
It's right near Pod Show HQ.
So why don't you come on down.
I'll pay for your ticket.
I promise.
Okay, that's all.
Just someone give me an update.
Please.
Dude, you got to stick with it.
Although I really do appreciate the comparison with 24.
Oh, that's nice.
Well, there's a challenge.
Anyone want to put that together?
It might be necessary.
That is a good point.
And I really appreciate the invite.
Yes, of course.
I'll take you up on it.
I think I'm in San Francisco the week of the 19th.
So let's say if we can hook it up, I would love to come to see that.
It's, you know, I've had my eye on that production for a while.
And I didn't know that, you know, there really is kind of a theater district in San Francisco.
Is there any good?
Is it, are they, you know, what are the things that we're going to find out, I guess, aren't we?
Planting a Jamaican get away?
Fly stone.
Our stone attendance will see that you arrive with a load.
Stone Airlines to Jamaica.
Fly above the clouds and arrive with a head full of steam when you get there.
And save money with our specially economy flights, only 29.95.
Jump once you to fly.
Hey, Adam.
It's Seth Harwood, longtime DSC listener.
After hearing the first few chapters of Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff's kick-ass pod novel,
Number one with a bullet.
And Scott Sigler's awesome, the rookie.
I thought it was time for me to bring my podcast novel, Jack wakes up over to pod show.
Jack wakes up is about what happens when Jack palms.
A one hit wonder, X action movie actor hits the streets of San Francisco
to help a group of check drug buyers make one big score.
A drug deal that he hopes will set him up for life.
But when things turn difficult, he has to decide what side of acting and action he's on.
Thanks, Adam, for all the great pod show podcasts.
And I'm looking forward to getting to know more people in the pod show community.
When you get a chance, go check out Jack wakes up at Jack wakes up. podshow.com.
I shall do exactly that.
Thank you very much and welcome to the show.
Absolutely.
This is a format that we haven't even talked about.
The stuff, Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff's doing, Scott Sigler.
There's a podiobooks.com.
This is really an interesting audio format.
And we're seeing people create books in an audience online
and then selling the physical hard copy again.
We're back to my favorite word of the week, packaging.
In our continuing quest to find out if posh people are potty pigs,
we find out some more interesting tidbits today.
By the way, I'm in my training period now.
I am now officially a folder and a sitter.
I got some interesting software the other day.
I'm going to try out its SMS software so we can do voting here on the chat chat.
So you can just SMS, it would be folder or scruncher,
sitter or standard.
Actually, let me just, well, I'll mess with you right in a second.
Hold on, let's see.
Our first posh poddy comments.
Hi, Adam.
I'm Darren from Beautiful Melvin and Australia here.
Just thought I'd like to chime in on the posh poddy habits.
Three.
I work for three years at one of Australia's most prestigious financial institutions.
There's some very smart research monkeys, investment bankers and the like.
Without doubt, it had the most disgusting tolls of any place that I'd previously worked.
We had a fandom sprayer as well.
It was not unusual to walk into the stall in the morning and find,
well, sheet in places I didn't think you can normally get it.
He obviously didn't have much of a fire in his diet.
He didn't hear for a while, then returned.
Unfortunately, we were unable to track down the culprit.
On the Trinity project, let's get her around the world.
Get her into a container and on a ship from the Mead to Perth Western Australian.
We'll pick her up and dry her across the Malibu plane to Sydney.
That's the equivalent distance of about London to Moscow.
We can pop her back into a ship to New Zealand and get my other key.
We guys to cut a lap in New Zealand and then back on a ship to Auckland for Los Angeles.
Us can play in a second navigation.
There is a challenge.
Thanks for the show.
I've been listening since about the first six months of the day.
I still look forward to my daily day of sea fix.
Cheers, Mike.
Alright.
I miss Australia.
I really want to go there again.
Of course, of course you'll make it to Australia.
She's not going to stop. She's going to keep going around the world.
I know it because there's enough people who are going to fix her up and keep her running.
I can't wait to get there on the road and get this project started.
It's going to take a couple more weeks, but it will happen and we're going to get her rolling.
We're good for bad.
Trinity update coming in just a couple seconds.
I am.
It's Melvin from Seoul again.
You asked for more toilet towels in the Orient.
You might think that South Korea's economic success has been built on manufacturing
motor cars, ships, electronics, or even knockoffs.
But no.
Don't actually build on oral healthcare.
Trinity hours of 12 to 2 each day.
About 20 million Koreans in factories and offices in construction sites will brush their teeth.
In my office you have to force your way past the 3D cure at the sinks.
So I think that's 4 sets isn't that much.
To get anywhere near the men's room.
Then you arrive at the store.
Here you get the usual smells and noises.
The creep out from underneath the toilet door.
Sometimes you get something a little bit extra.
You get the sound of brushing teeth.
It's really quite weird.
Cheers.
Wow.
You sounded like a Brit.
Yeah.
Just to be stereotypical.
For Brits, it may be weird to brush your teeth after lunch.
But it's a pretty good habit actually to have.
I want to add there.
Okay.
We learned a little bit.
Not an entire amount about.
About the problem at hand.
But it does seem that worldwide.
People have the strangest bathroom habits when they're in public.
While their bathrooms at home could be impeccably clean.
The quest continues.
Defined out.
Are Posh.
People.
Poti.
Pigs.
Bik.
Gosset is a fine.
Question.
Yes.
It is.
Are Posh.
Pigs.
C'mon strip.
I beat you.
Hello.
Cary Adam.
And the same to your charming madam.
It is me.
The C S B.
as B and tomorrow in London I will be.
Please be nice and don't be late so that I won't have to wait.
Fortunately, World War II is over.
So my German airplane will not be shot above tover.
This interview will be only about mobile phones
and I bring two stereo superb microphones.
See you tomorrow in the meeting.
Please remember this reminder greeting.
Oh.
Yeah.
Did you hear that?
The satellite window closed right in the middle of CSB.
Yep, tomorrow.
Oh, it's all this excitement that's going on.
And by the way, today we're picking a Patricia Smart Roadster.
Yeah, she's so excited.
She's like a little girl.
She has a whole day planned for tomorrow.
She wants to...
She has like a Barbie card.
It's perfect.
That's what all girly girls want.
She's got a day of driving.
She's going to the nail salon.
She's going to drive and see how much shopping she can get in.
You know, grocery shopping.
That's very cool.
So mixed all of that tomorrow in London.
To PM, I'm meeting with online superhero of the interesting comic strip blogger.
And we're going to shoot it.
We're going to do some video.
Because I think a lot of people are very curious to see what he looks like and to hear him talk.
Is this real voice?
Is it a real guy?
And I am myself quite excited about it because how long have we been communicating
with each other.
And even though sometimes he goes off the rails for, you know, for the rest of the audience,
he's, I think he's a reasonable guy.
So, you know, yes, he's interviewing me.
You know, I'll be able to slip some questions in and we'll learn lots of stuff.
You know, that's going to happen.
Beautiful day to day again.
I hope it's going to be the same on Friday.
Blue skies.
Very, very cold in the UK.
Minus six degrees Celsius this morning when Christina and I got into the car.
And the predicting snow for tomorrow, which, of course, could,
could kind of ruin Patricia's day of barbie car driving.
Hi Adam, it's Eric.
West with the beach happens to go.
I just wanted to make a couple of comments.
You had the best song ever that I've heard on your show with Beat Hopkins a yesterday
on the DSC.
I think it was by 40 actually.
Congratulations on over 500.
I don't know if I'm going to take this further down there a month.
And I'm starting up my podcast again.
But the other thing I wanted to comment on was on, I believe,
in the spot 39 where you stated, you leave your machine's arm.
It is actually a noted fact that most systems are made for continuous run.
That includes elevators, computers, just rides.
So, leaving them on actually last longer than turning them on and off.
But the actual turning them on and off, that actually,
short and very light.
Anyway, just by giving you a comment and thanks for the DSC.
I listen every day.
You're first thing in the morning.
And when you're the only chef in Cisco,
please keep doing this show at 11 o'clock at night.
Because that way I have it first thing in the morning
when I'm on my way to work.
Talk to you later.
Bye.
The eye man, you got it.
Thanks for calling in.
And of course, you've opened up the geek box of Pandora with this comment.
Because I think there are equal opinions on either side of the
leave him on or switch him off debate as it pertains to computers,
to tubes, to light bulbs, to just about anything I think.
But I have to say my personal experience.
And that's just because I'm old enough to seeing crap die along the way.
Is leave him on.
For those of you not familiar with Raymond, Raymond Port.
He's a good friend of the Charlie.
And he was the guy that while I was recording a daily source code
on a commute from Amsterdam to the Curry Castle in Belgium.
That all of a sudden he pulled up alongside me.
He was honking his horn.
We were in kind of heavy traffic.
And he says, dude, I'm listening to you right now.
And listen to daily source code.
And I was like, dude, I'm recording one.
And it was like a loop.
It was a connection.
It was a really interesting moment in the history of this show.
Certainly, maybe a podcasting in general.
And Raymond's made some pretty big decisions in this life recently.
I think he's leaving his current job.
And he's trying to find out where he wants to go and what he wants to do.
And he was in traffic recently.
And what else you're going to do when your name's ready?
Hey, Adam.
It's Raymond from the Netherlands.
I'm on a road trip today.
That can post Germany.
Most time in the car.
And the traffic jam is all over.
Since it's starting snowing here.
Where are you?
I miss you on the lane.
Let me stuck in the same city traffic jam.
You're all the A-A, or the Shigwar V-A, or Smart Roadster.
Or Trinity.
I'll have some time on my hands.
I totally dig the free Trinity project from early March.
I'll have no, they jump.
Why don't you go up and drive around for a day or so?
Let me know what you think.
And it might happen.
Okay.
Fine.
Out.
Holder.
That's right, Ray.
Actually, we're changing it now.
No longer are you a folder, but you're a folders.
So next time you do your business, you'll think of my sponsors.
It works.
You can't help but sing along.
The Trinity, Trinity, the quintessential luxury.
Trinity, Trinity, Trinity's at the bio diesel set.
You're free Trinity.
That's right.
We're taking my baby poo colored Mercedes 300 turbo diesel.
Station wagon from 1984 running on Veggie Oil.
Better known as biodiesel across the USA and around the globe.
We're signing up.
We're getting the group together.
There's a link at the show notes daily source code.com.
To the Google group, you want to join.
You want to let your presence be known.
We're collecting all your data.
We're going to be mapping out Trinity's root pretty soon.
And of course, everyone gets your chance to drive.
Everyone gets a chance to fill her up.
Everyone gets a chance to repair her along the way.
Trust me.
I know cars.
So that's the concept.
And of course, she'll be sending back GPS coordinates and video and photo at regular intervals.
And all we're looking for now really is to find someone who can build a strap on box that will perform these wonderful functions.
I think we might have someone in the prolific programmer.
I've asked him to send me some links to some of the work he's done.
But anyone who calls himself the prolific programmer either is a damn good programmer.
Or he's got elephant-sized balls.
Of course, I wasn't completely correct about what I told you about him yesterday.
So he called in to correct me.
Hello.
I don't know who's coming here.
I just wanted to tell you that.
And email me at first.
We have that to you because that's relevant part.
Um, I was immediately 540.
I'm having a good new girlfriend.
You're glad to request me the prolific programmer involved for you.
But through Trinity project, I would love to.
I did, however, I just bought sent to a friend to send a dinner and to a camera.
Okay.
I can't think that's the effort in any kind of the present.
Then you mentioned that they were doing a machine level and I realized that's right.
Colin.
So I'm nice to join you on the other way.
Um, I would also because you come to the area often enough and I'm usually in the area.
I would love to be able to.
We should discuss the city by other projects over a day or some time.
Either let me know to the DSC or you can't.
I mean, blog at post it for them.
And come such a little bit.
Thank you.
Awesome.
I love you, man.
I don't think anyone can understand what the fuck you're saying.
But I do love you.
I think you're a true character.
And okay.
Here's the deal.
I got no time to have dinner with anybody.
I'm sorry.
I just don't.
You know, that's just not the way my life works.
Certainly not when I'm San Francisco because, you know,
dinner is like something from the, from the takeaway or it's a frozen food dinner.
And then I do the show at night.
Yeah, just don't have the time.
But I did talk to my friend over at Nokia.
And if I'm convinced and then I'll convince him that we have the right people who
actually want to build on this wonderful open and 800 Linux based platform.
He does have some development machines available.
So let's get the group together guys.
Let's, let's, you know, communicate it all through the Google group.
Again, you can find a link to that at dailysourcecode.com.
I don't.
Thank you, Jeff Smith.
I love you, man.
Okay. So as a part of the quest to get Trinity on the road.
We're in the midst of hiring and I'll just call it a producer.
For a couple of things for the entire project.
And then a whole bunch of shit that goes along with the project.
And that is Barbara the Palo Alto podcaster.
Dear diary, you know that dreamy Adam Curry.
I'm always telling you about.
I think he's trying to kill me.
We're Trinity and I think we should get our going.
And a week or two when I get back to San Francisco.
I think we're almost ready.
It's ready.
Hey Adam.
It's Barbara and Palo Alto.
Trinity's Galpel.
You know, the one who almost had a coronary when you said the road trip was close to starting?
Well, we are making a lot of progress.
And I love your enthusiasm for the project.
There are still a lot of pieces we have to put into place before Trinity can get rolling.
So please, let's wait until we have more than a handful of invitations.
Before we start talking about a time frame.
Okay?
Oh, man.
How about helping me get my heart started again with a little music?
So I guess this means David came through for you, huh?
Well, now.
Chocolate cake makes my poor stomach ache.
And listen.
Next time you get a hold of some KW that send you off into fantasy land like that.
Dude, you got a share.
The coffee and refill makes me feel alright.
First of all, method making you hide.
But I've never liked going five days without sniffing.
As it makes you say stupid things like,
I'm sorry.
The coffee and refill makes you feel alright.
It's all that takes you high.
It takes you low.
The beans are making fly.
All the mud will make you slow.
Shooting speed balls will make you sell your stereo.
But you never heard of going in hawk.
For a cup of Joe.
You know the crank will end you right in the crank.
Smoke that nasty crack yet you want to rob a bank.
Forget the nicotine, it can't even be.
It bends a dream.
Try golfing and refill full a real mellow seat.
Yeah.
I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going
to take a look at this, I'm going to take it, I'm going to take a look at this, I'm going to take a look at it,
When you're smoking on a level
The cop to channel, hey, how's everything you need?
X to C, what calls a man to level off?
Love you, who is give make you love a girl you never touch it on
Nestling, what turned you into a little pinky racer
Stock cappuccino, with a mellow gauge taste
Oh, fang, fang, fang, fang
One sunshine
Ferguson
Ferguson, Apollo
August, August, Barbara
Sorry about the coronary, my dear
Coffee and refer, love that song
Awesome
All right, everybody, that's enough for today
Perfect timing, under 40 minutes the way I like to have it
I hope you have a fantastic day
Know that this is the beginning
Today marks the beginning of a new era for music
The way we'll be able to
Share it amongst ourselves
What we'll be able to do with it
Where we'll be able to put it
And how we'll be able to contribute to it
It's going to be awesome
DailySourceco.com
Adam at podshow.com
If you want to send me something
Hey, you know what? Why don't we meet back here tomorrow?
Either before I meet comic strip blogger or afterwards
And well, talk about
Some more important things
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear