The number one online police drama series is now available, subscribe now and get the
entire first season on your iPod and get ready for an action-packed season 2 coming July
2007.
Hort City Day, podshow.com
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
Another Japanese group just what I need.
We'll take a picture while we smile.
The self-sorry I ain't got no time.
Got your eyes on my soul.
Great tip like I'm somebody else.
Standing here and far of you.
Doesn't make me feel so good to smile.
Everything that everybody got smile in.
Everybody's got the right to say.
Cheese will come from God.
With the friend that's walked the line for a ride.
You ride around in places of no.
A walk-up is from the way to go.
So smile and say hello.
Missed out the mess I wasn't in the deal of mood.
It's my fucking set way to put your hands on from the wall.
You'll be laughed all the way.
Would you have more or more to do?
Yes, of course, got to write to me smile in.
And I would have a fight just smile in.
And when you go and change about our smile then.
And when they take you make the same.
Cheese will come from God.
Cheese when they call smile.
When you're shooting a girl.
Cheese.
On your wedding day.
When you go street, cheese, if you wear a rubber, smile, when you cheat a rubber, cheese, when you miss me hate, smile, I'm in your face, smile, every day, every night you smile in, everybody's got that right to smile in,
People say, I'm in your face, I'm in your face, smile, my man, everybody has everybody's got to say the cheese moves you got the right to me, I'm in your face, smile, I'm in your face, smile, I'm in your face, smile, my man, everybody's got the right to smile in, everybody's got that right to smile in, everybody's got that right to smile, smile, I'm in your face, smile, my man, everyone's got that right to smile in, everyone's got that right to smile and smile, smile, I'm in your face, smile, I'm in your face, smile, smile, Mahwith a worm, ho เดraction, oh, this is fucking right!
Paul music, who functional football, I mean, what can I tell you?
Yeah, I'd say music never didn't have any songs titled Shedder
Lots of cheese though
It's a source code episode 641
Dude with molten cheese
That's right the cheddar is loose the
Pod Show channel editor
Finally up and rolling have you had a chance to play with it yet?
Of course I'm gonna talk about that today and this what I think will be relatively
Short show on my way out the door to the London office staying in London actually tonight
For some early morning meetings, so that means that to Fubar Friday will be at the end of the UK day
Oh boy, and I guess I just got to say it
When it comes to predicting the weather I I suck at least my long-term forecast really sucking. You know as a
As an aviator or an airman
50% of what's important in flying is what the weather's going to be where you are
Your destination and of course on route and so
Whoa, almost I got my headphone just crapped out for a second home
There we go. So, you know, that's that's pretty important stuff now. It's much easier to
predict the weather for the next 12 hours. They even I'm I'm getting kind of good at 24
But only for certain regions that I really focus on because you know, you'll say okay
What's it going to be at the manner and you can look at airport to whether a terminal area forecast
So airport terminals. You can look at Heathrow stands to
I can look at born myth I can look at
Gatwick obviously and I can get a real idea knowing as well
You know, which way the wind's blowing and what speed I can get a pretty good idea of what's gonna happen in 12 to 24 hours
I definitely have to work on on the longer range forecast because man
It's coming down again. It's really really bad today. This country is in a crisis
You know the next show you here from you. I'm going to be on the freaking roof
You know the temps is overflowing the water just keeps coming down from the skies. It's it's not good
So I'll just say right now. I have no business trying to predict the weather week ahead
If I could I'd probably be the wealthiest man in the universe, but I'm practicing
I'm practicing and just to show you how tough this stuff is this is a fantastic comment
from a a new pilot and a spiring airman
You know Adam David from Colorado listen to DSC
three
Oh, sorry
DSC six three five hey
Just was listening about that weather. El Niño, La Niña stuff. I got an embryo
I'm gonna be a pilot sometimes here soon. Actually. I got my license
about a month ago and
I guess like you said you got to know a lot about weather and I've taken a few weather classes
And we've talked about El Niño and La Niña
a couple times and
Really it only affects the winter weather mainly, but it also affects normal summer time weather sometimes
But what it is is it's a difference of pressures on the
At least it's been down to effected in the United States. I don't know how it's affected in UK
We didn't talk about it
Well obviously, let me just say that the overarching
Things that determine the weather are things like the jet stream and and really it's a lot about wind
Where the wind is going from going to where it's coming from?
The jet stream has huge influences and it changes by seasonality by leap here
And there's a lot of stuff to weather. I'm still in search of the perfect savant for weather in Europe
We talked about how it affects the United States and it really El Niño
I don't know if it's higher low in the Pacific or like it's it's like well it's different in pressures on the
On from the
What's right of China and Indonesia area and then high pressure
Could any American in the class point to Indonesia or in a difference in pressure on the
West the East
Start over because I really kind of find a thing. Yeah, I appreciate it tried dude
It's a difference in pressure in Indonesia and then the Western half
the Western side of
the Americas and
What happens in El Niño is
Seattle and all that that there's kind of a more of a northerly storm track over the United States and
There'll be
weather weather
more near Seattle and
And more toward the south it'll be really dry really really dry and then an El Niño is the opposite of course
Yes, where
where you got
You know really dry weather
Really weather you've a lot you've lost me right weather up in Seattle and it just the storm track really in an El Niño is
Sutherly and in it lining it's northerly so I guess that's really I was listening to that and I thought I'd explain
Anyways
Good work dude. I appreciate it. I guess what it's just gonna rain tomorrow
So for instance for here's how here's how I can give you a pretty accurate weather report
Looking at London
Heathrow right now light rain 2300 foot ceiling winds
23 knots
Gusting to 30 so a lot of wind that means you can probably see some temporary action
Depending on the cloud cover you could actually get some sunshine in that case and you'll see what they're predicting up until nine p.m. this evening or eight
8 o'clock UTC
No rain and some broken clouds a
2000 feet and then temporarily during the day because of the wind of course it's gonna you know probably be about 30% chance you'll see
Broken clouds who have some sun and then heavy rain showers no thunderstorms though it'd
Protect predicted and and that's always very important for aviation
So if I look at Heathrow and it looks I got week
I mean it looks pretty much the same although the seeding it seems like the rain is going to stop and then
Let me just check yeah, so somewhere between
In the afternoon today it's gonna get nasty. It's gonna be a really heavy rain showers
But there should not be any thunderstorms associated with it
Which is usually a good thing hot camp is coming to Cape Town South Africa on Saturday the 20th of October
Come and join us for podcasting blogging new media social media social networking online video sharing
Collaborate community share connect social bookmarking virtual presence
www.podcampcapetown.com
If you want to learn more about podcasting blogging social media online video
Sharing and anything and everything new media come and join us at podcast
Cape Town on the 20th of October 2007
Experts will be on hand to help you want to learn how to podcast or if you're ready a veteran blogger
Everybody is welcome and best of all it's free if you're not from South Africa
Not only do you get to network with some of South Africa's top new media minds
But also enjoy a splendid and unforgettable Cape Town holiday experience
It is a trip you will not regret to register and get more details visit www.podcampcapetown.com
or join the podcast on Facebook today
You media in South Africa is gearing up for an explosion and we want you to be part of it
So sign up now
www.podcampcapetown.com
Was that Dave Fox? Sound a lot like him
Hey, high production values coming from pod camp Cape Town
Oh man, I want to be nice to make the trip down there
It will be awesome if I took the Delta Sierra down
I wonder, probably
3 days maybe
Hmm
See if I can get a safety pilot for that trip, huh?
Well anyway around 115 AM
UK time London time
Cheddar was released the channel editor functionality for podshow.com
Now anywhere you see a channel you have multiple options to play it
Put it somewhere and of course in in days or maybe a week or two depending on how this
portion of the rollout goes
You'll be able to get that channel and do other things with it
It's been code name cheddar that's for those you're just tuning into the source code thing
What the hell is going on with this cheese stuff?
Cheddar being cheese cheddar kind of sounding like channel editor if you say it fast a couple hundred thousand times
Which I've said certainly at least that many times in the past few weeks
Hey, it works as advertised now we got to figure out what we want from it and if there's a different types of playouts
We can create a party
Actually, I'm trying to track some of this stuff on my blog at curie.com
I've already figured out that would be awesome is to have a play option for the iPhone
That just renders the channel
You know in the iPhone like in the Safari browser so that you could listen to stuff right there
You know just and the pictures would show up and of course you'd have to be connected
But as you know my hypothesis is that in the
Not too distant future within five years. I think that we'll just have
connectivity everywhere we'll just be so jacked in with broadband at a affordable prices that it really won't matter
If you are listening to it live over the air or if you've downloaded it of course
You're in particular situations
Yo Adam, let's Peter listen up from Australia
In some of your recent DSCs you've been talking about your channel editors and how
Eventually we could all be just direct streaming at podcasts
I can tell you that down here in Australia that's not real likely made after all we've got a land mass the size of the continental
United States
And only about 20 million people at it
Um
Most of the time your heart press just finding a Wi-Fi connection that works let alone one that you can log into
And yeah keep that with show mate you're doing good. Yeah another play well
What is happening today something is something is messed up
The headphone you know Christina borrowed my headphones and I think she
Did something with the jack probably rolled over it with a chair or something. Okay. There we go
I'm not the place I desperately want to visit. I need to go back to Australia because there are only 20 million people in a land mass the size of the United States
But the women are so good looking
The guys are kind of good looking too. You never really see really ugly Australians. Do you?
Well, I think that there are some solutions coming now and I and yes, I do know that
You know when you get outside some of the
The urban areas yeah, I mean and I really don't know if a lot of those 20 million are concentrated around the places like Sydney and Melbourne and Perth
I just don't know I think that there's probably a good chunk of them there
But yeah when you get out
Yeah, this headphone crap when you get out there on you know what you guys call a station
You know it could literally take you three days by car just to get from you know get to the neighbor's house
Yeah, there may be some issues with wife
The wife I there and I know that infrastructure in in those cases is complicated
But there are some interesting solutions to that on the horizon
Hey, this is Jared from Central PA Harrisburg actually
I was just listening in at 638 and the conversation you were having about cheddar and the
broadband connectivity and not doing it over sell them at work and those kind of instant
That's we're looking at Twitter yesterday and
They're talking about the whole thing in the Google and the seven of her megahertz
frequency that
be all the
local and national TV networks for these and
It's broadcast over in Google purchasing it and and making it a nationwide free
network
That would be really
Incredible a type of network broadband speeds for downloading and all we have in the connected
You'd be looking forward to have your handheld device iPhone
Blackberry whatever whatever they come out with in the future that's all Wi-Fi that can
automatically connect and download and have your updates all the time as far as what you're want to listen to and
Your podcasts and even if you want any go on in browse music and now on music
It should be a really really neat concept and I just want to know if that was something that you've already heard or which have been looking at with that
And so I was something that you know
Could be integrated into what you guys are doing and so forth. That's on the guitar
Yeah, thanks
Keep it up. Thanks. Yeah, man. Thank you
Actually, I heard that Twitter episode as well and I think I had the same aha moment that you had oh by the way
I figured I was wrong the headphones the wire was crawled around the
The volume knob
So every single time I moved my head the volume was being cranked up. That's that's what the feedback was about
Yeah, those 700 megahertz frequencies, you know, so that was always the intent was to
Move all mainstream broadcasters to HD
And using different frequencies and then free up the 700 megahertz
I know I got to say the TV signals man. That's it really blast through all kinds of stuff through walls
You know, huge humongous distances
I'm not quite sure what kind of power you need to power a handheld device to to be able to handle the 700 megahertz man
I don't anything about that
I an RF is really tricky business, but there seems to be a lot this is the frequencies the Google is after and and probably they're doing it for the right reasons
You know, hey, we could create our own wireless network. Whatever happened to citizens band
You know, I mean, of course CB radio still there, but you know, why not make this the new citizens band?
There's there's a you know the CB radio network was what 70s break a break a good buddy got you rears
only got ourselves a convoy
I think it was mid 70s
So 70s when the citizens band was created that's time for an upgraded the citizens band could can't we call for that?
And maybe it just should be given free you know opened up. I don't know
So those are definitely potential
Potential solutions on the horizon, but all of that as I said within the next five years nothing's gonna happen tomorrow
It's just a slow news period. It's everyone's you know raking all this shit up now
Anyway, what I'd like you to do is if you have created a channel
And remember you can put individual episodes in you can anywhere on podshow.com where you see a get button
You can select the channel you want to put that individual episode or show into
You can edit those you can rearrange the order and then of course you can
Determine for yourself how you want to play it you can put it on your iPod you can stream it
You can play it in our dashboard and of course anyone who comes along and checks out your channels can do the same
I'm looking also
It there must be some real easy RSS widget. I asked if it the furf
You know Chris McIntyre podcast Ali guru. I asked him to create a widget a channels widget. I think you know
I like kind of the style of the the module we have in our profile pages it would be cool if if you could have something like that
It could be an embedded widget, but you could resize it and make it smaller maybe
Cool stuff so I'm
Please send me an email out of it podshow.com. Let me know
What you've created so I can start promoting that and of course we really need a page that
Highlights all the cool channels and don't forget you can search for channels so there is some context and it does appear to work
Although the search definitely has to improve and oh and all just a part of sucking less
I can't tell you how incredibly excited I am and already you know tons of feedback and and questions and
Messages send me your audio feedback as well and give me some channels to try out. I need's my chetta
Or this yesterday a specific hostel way Mark Yoshimura and him cough got it from iota promo net and I was like dude send me that file now
You had them figured out a while ago, and I know it's not exactly breakin' news
But it's all in a little like a trial for you and a bunch from talking won't make it
I'll come on go while I take out the trash and once you get it out tell him not to come back again
No, why not give him the sling get the hookin' straight get the hookin' good and go
So play that he's just makin' it up and he's still got you comin' back for all more
Why you never ever think of breaking it up tell me what the back is gonna close that
Top of a comma now while I take out the trash and once you get it out tell him not to come back again
No, why not give him the sling get the hookin' straight get the hookin' good and go
I'm not sitting out but tries out the same but the borders are sitting in a place up
and I'm not sitting out but ones are sitting up but somebody's on the same and I's staying
I'm not sitting out but one's on the same,but somebody's on the same band
Why not take out the trash, and once you get them out, tell them not to come back again
Go back out in the gym, after what you said, to everything you did
Now why not take out the trash?
Come on now why not take out the trash, and once you get them out, tell them not to come back again
Now why not get them out in the sling, and they will come back again
and they will get them out.
I've never been a fan of they might be Giants, but I heard the song I was just like,
whoa, dude, that's awesome. It's from my auto-promenet. I'll find the link and put that in
the show notes, of course. I looked and see if it was on the pod save music network. There
is a, they might be Giants song up there, but it's not this one. Take out the trash. I love
this song, man. Maybe I was missing a lot of they might be Giants. Maybe I just didn't get it,
or I was in the wrong type mode or whatever, you know, early MTV days. Okay,
DailySourceco.com, Adam at podshow.com, and finally, before I leave you today, some very
sad news, but I was asked to pass that along to the listeners, the DailySourcecoat. You recall
that a young poet was very excited about, this is so fucked up. He played the sound of his
unborn baby's heartbeat on the hit test. On the last hit test he did. And yesterday sent me
a message that, unfortunately, his wife, Victorine, Miss Carried, and so you can understand
that things are kind of messed up over there. He did actually already have a hit test created
for the footballer Friday, but since so many people were calling and emailing him because they
heard it on the show and were congratulating them. They both want to be to pass that along to you.
So, of course, young and Victorine are in our prayers and in our thoughts in what's going to be
a tough time for them. Okay, tomorrow, we'll celebrate the food hardness of the week,
meet you there.