Pearl, what you're doing at the brand new Pod Show HQ on the recently moved Pod Show Island
in Second Life, and why are you dusting that furniture?
Happy, you're not with it, you don't pay attention to anything.
Pod Show Island is grand opening, this Friday with a huge concert by Jeff Smith and the
fun goes all the way through Sunday night with Pod Show music network favorite, the
Sarah Mac Band closing out the weekend with a big show.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know all that M.B. has been doing things all over the island for
the grand opening, he has me setting up the stage for Jeff, he had me put furniture in
a curing manner, but why are you cleaning up in here?
Adam may be coming to the grand opening, I want to make sure his office is perfect, and
if Adam wants to be a mayor, then he's a mayor, and now he has the office to prove it.
Wow, Adam, mayor of the island?
Wow, what a great office.
Very, very cool.
Ta-da, and I'll pee out.
Hey, bro, let me introduce the show.
DSC 5 9 4.
What's out of sound, fast, build up, everybody round, build up, make it be no big,
what's up, build up, make it smooth, move my feet, fast, build up, sit my bones, and it's
out of me, looks like cam is on, I feel like rhythm, if you like to dance, this is your
chance, I can't keep it still, the bungalows playing, I know everybody feels that way,
but it's in their boat, and it's out of music, cam is on, oh feel like rhythm, if you can be
strong, know that you want to hold those pain, and I'll dance all night and day, and I'll never
fall in my bones, it's out of me, looks like cam is on, I feel like rhythm, I feel like
rhythm, if you can be strong, know that if you want to hold those pain, and I'll dance all night
and day, and I'll never fall in my bones, and it's out of the music, cam is on, I feel like
rhythm, if you like to dance, this is your chance, I can't keep it up, if you can be strong,
you can be strong, know that if you want to hold those pain, and I'll dance all night and day, and I'll never
fall in my bones, and it's out of the music, cam is on, if you like to be strong, if you like to dance,
you'll never guess who that is, never guess, give up, would you believe it if I said the
Jeff Smith, the one and only Jeff Smith, with the impressions, attracted it over a year ago,
it turns out that song is now number one on the beach music charts. I love it. Fantastic. You
know that that's the kind of song that makes you feel cavo-k, which of course is the opposite
of fubar. Cavo-k, ceiling invisibility. Okay, I'm having a cavo-k day. How are you guys? It is daily
source code episode number 594 coming to you from the curry manner. I've got the windows open
up here in the attic. The wind is just kind of flowing by just wasping and wasping, wasping,
just kind of flowing in, trying to make it sound romantic. It really is another beautiful
day, a little cloudy this morning, but I think it's going to be good throughout the weekend. Good,
because of course I'm planning on flying over to the Netherlands, the Lady Patricia, performing
and dancing with the stars. I'll play the song tomorrow on the maximum music fubar friday. I'll
play it again for you. The new version of the star sisters proudly presents. It's fantastic.
Now she's on the road and kind of the way I do it. I'll call in once a day, usually in the evening,
so she calls and she calls Christina and then she'll call me, of course I'm always second banana.
But man, she's having a good time. When the Lady P is on the path man, she's like getting up at
seven doing radio interviews. She's got a huge interview in the National Paper coming up on
Saturday. She really wants people to watch. And of course there's a special surprise in this
performance that they're doing, which obviously I can't tell you about. And I know things are
heating up because I can see by the caller ID that the gossip television shows are now calling me,
trying to mind me for information. Of course, they just get rejected. I'm all alone once again,
and I think the dog is barking downstairs. So see, you hear that? Swabber! Swabber!
What happens is, I leave the door open so all the animals can go in and out and he walks out,
but then he doesn't have enough power and his hind legs to kind of vault himself back in
through the doorway and he stands that kind of like going, P, let me in!
I'll see if I can get a song going and I'll go downstairs and grab him real quick.
Hi Adam, this is Lisa from Orlando, Florida. I've been a take her for far too long,
and decided I should start giving something back. I did have a few points though.
To all the podcasters complaining about the PMM, shut the heck up!
The pod show helps make your show as possible with financial and technical support to say nothing
of those incredible bandwidth bills y'all don't pay for. Show some gratitude and stop complaining.
It's really not becoming. Number two, three words, more Patricia please. She is so talented and gracious,
and it's a real treat when she's on. Please let her know that.
Number three, I love podcasters. They have changed my life. I rarely watch TV, never listen to the
radio, but do listen and watch dozens of podcasters each week. One thing I'm really happy about is my
dad. He wrote a book 20 years ago and then did nothing with it. When I heard Scott's
saygler of earth core fame, almost two years ago on the DSC, talking about his potty of book,
and how authors were making their books into podcasters, I urged my almost 65-year-old dad to make
his own potty of book. I'm proud to say he's in the final stages of editing his first few episodes,
without you, his dream would still be sitting in a drawer. And finally, this new format is fabulous.
I'm really enjoying it. I'm always astounded at the people we have in our lives who have some secret,
or sometimes not so secret knowledge about something. Be a copyright law, how to care for
African violence, making to die for a whole week bread or whatever. I think we all have savants in
our lives, and thanks for reminding us of that. Have a great day, Adam.
And Adam? Yes. Folder. Oh, send a naked picture. Will you please? Nice voice. Thanks for
contributing, Lisa. Yeah. Well, absolutely. Of course, we all have savants in our lives. That's
the whole point. Today, not a new format, savant from the circle of savants, because today's show
more about a savant of the musical kind, we started it off with Jeff Smith, with that song that
he did with the impressions, which I just love. Jeff does, I think I should do a show with Jeff.
And all of this is just, it's all, every topic, there's a song. Every little, you know,
I really can't, you know what, I don't normally do this, but I'm all alone. Hold on one second.
Sorry about that. I just paused everything to run downstairs and let the dog in.
And now, of course, I'm out of breath from running up and down the stairs so quickly.
I really got to get this dog like an invalid ramp or something, you know, because he can
hope, is it going to be one of those days? Let's see. Okay. Oh, man. Yes it is.
Why? Why or why? No one has used to my new format yet. Okay.
Uh, so what was I saying about, uh, oh, yes. No, no Cirque de Sivant, uh, Ojo Dwi.
Is it Ojo Dwi? Yeah, I think, no. Today, whatever. Oh, you too.
Instead, uh, got something cool coming up from the Jeff Smith.
Man, I'm really out of breath.
So I don't know if you followed the story about the, uh, copy protection key code to the HD DVD.
Disks. I'm, I'm going to try and explain this because it's very, very geeky, but it
had already showed up in the New York Times because it's something just things happened.
So there's this code and this code literally consists of, um, I don't know, like 15 or 16 different
pairs of letters or numbers. So like, you know, hexadecimal code to like F0, um, three A, you know, so
it's like 16 or 17 of those pairs. And that is the actual key that allows you, um, on, um,
on the player on Linux to actually crack the HD DVDs, uh, copy protection so that you could then
copy them. Now, as a part of the digital millennium copyright act, uh, and this stems back to an
original, uh, DVD code crack I believe. I'm just kind of paraphrasing in here. I'm not exactly
sure of the history. Um, there was a similar code. If it, it may even be the same one to hell to
I know, uh, but in this, in this law, in this, uh, DMCA on this act was put that no one has allowed
to publish this, uh, this key because this key essentially allows anyone under the right circumstances
with proper knowledge, uh, to copy, uh, HD DVD discs. And so you're not even allowed to publish it,
or, uh, or even dream about it, it seems. You just, you can't have this, this code, this string of,
of, of numbers and letters. You cannot have it anywhere in your possession. Certainly not put it
on a, uh, on a website. So this got posted to dig.com. And, uh, so by now you probably, if you're like,
uh, kind of geeky and you live in the blogosphere, there's no way you could have avoided this story.
If not, then, you know, here you go. It's one of these stupid things. And it also really showed
what the dig audience is all about. So it's, it showed up on dig and, um, uh, and the guys at dig
removed that story. And so the, the audience of dig.com revolted and then every single story was basically
this code that was being put up and people were putting it up in picture format and pointing to it
in different places and using face folk, uh, fake subject lines. Um, and so it was like pandemonium
for a while and then it kind of died down. Um, so now people are starting to come up with all these
fun ways of, uh, of, uh, of mentioning this code, uh, and trying to get it published essentially.
It was, it's kind of like, uh, the equipment, like, uh, I'm going to light off a bottle rocket in school.
You know, it's not, it's not really a huge deal, but it's a really geeky thing. And it was a
talking to Mark Yoshimo to name coffee yesterday. And I played this, this fantastic comment.
Uh, I got a set of them up right home.
So this, of course, is, uh, one of our ubers of aunts and, uh, prolific program will
wouldn't be pp if, if he didn't try and sneak the code into one of his collins.
I haven't been programming it from dad runs to scope. I just noticed that dig is going to
ship shit. Apparently they, they are censoring the HDD code, namely, O9 F9 1 1 0 2 9 day 7 4 E 3 5 B D 8 4 1 5 6
C 5 6 3 5 6 8 8 C 0. Now I, I suspect the cops are going to look as arrest me. So I get very, very
going. Cheers. So, some parking lot cracking up over that. Like, I mean, I can't believe that.
So difficult, a prolific program to call the code in fantastic. Now we're all going to the
big house boy. And then Mark says, oh, man, you know, someone should make a make an edit a song.
I don't know that. And I said, shit, a song. Let's call Jeff Smith. He should totally do a song.
You know, he'll do a great job. So already we've gone from like prolific program or
to Mark and Adam to the Jeff Smith. And the, and the this morning, now available. If you go to
geek brief TV geek brief dot pot show dot com, you will see a video clip a music video for the song
that Jeff Smith wrote this happened all within span of like 18 hours. It's been unbelievable. Do we have
a fucking network? Do we have a network? Do we have a network? I love it when this stuff happens.
And Callie and Neil did an awesome job. Have you ever seen the the Dylan video? I think in
access that it as well, where the basically holding like cue cards with words on it. And that goes
along with the synchronized with the lyrics. I think you know what I mean. Anyway, I'm going to play
the song for you. You'll hear the code cleverly hidden. So it can live on in perpetuity because,
songs have an interesting knack of yeah, you can destroy the original file. But once someone's got
the song in their head, then we're all going to have this code embedded in our minds.
It's called Dick the Code. No BDI WG. Jeff Smith added again. I guess we can't publish the lyrics
and do the top to memorize it.
I want to be just like you. I want to be taking it true. 10 down the walls. It's something new.
Yeah, I'm digging you. I'm digging you. I'm digging you. I'm digging you. I'm digging you.
Give me your karte Den & WWE. You see, it's great. It's a match for me. The six Lats fixed,
AUDIO definitely makes me so much.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, god be careful, why can't they hear the sound and sound?
So you've got to go check out the video that Callie made and now besides the fact that it's cool how this all came together and and how she's basically
Embedding the code in our brains as well
Oh, she's fantastic. She looks so hot at the end of the video and she's doing little dances and stuff
Man there's stuff going on deep down inside Callie Lewis that I even I haven't figured out yet. Uh-huh
Links of course in the daily source code. They had the show notes portion of
Of that site. Yeah, let me see. Oh, there's more from prolific program
See what he has to say now
Your French is a bit off you you went this time on because that's
Cool and effort to win
Which I think should we do so wrong, but you may be because vendors are a bit off it and remember my gender's very well
That's all
Man, what is it you don't know your gender's very well. Yeah, okay. I thought that what he said
Okay, so you're gonna do some on we'll keep it at that for now
All right
Time to crank it up a little bit getting ready for our maximum music food our Friday tomorrow
Boy, I'm ready. Hey junior
What was I thinking
Mama's quitting car
Yeah
Getting hammered on my way to school
Walking in thank you man
My teacher get me as because he was up here and she said I made you a little man
You have to make me sick
In the morning you will realize and on the 9th you won first prize
Drinking games naked
Twister
But you're clever
Now I can't stop must come back down
So you're banging out of town
What was I thinking
What was I thinking when I got to try and get shaped my head
Drop on my best friend's been
What was I thinking
What was I thinking when I got to try and get shaped my head
You're up on my best friend's been
I was half naked in my head
And I woke up
In the back of my neighbor's bigotron
What was I thinking
What was I thinking when I got to try and get shaped my head
Oh God, with her mom
What was I thinking
What was I thinking when I got to try and get shaped my head
Drop on my best friend's been
What was I thinking
What was I thinking when I got to try and get shaped my head
Drop on my best friend's been
You
Junior what was I thinking from the pod save music now we're wrapping up a shorter episode of the Charlie today
You know like I got all like a lot of stuff to do
And also I really want to get prepared for tomorrow's football Friday
I have an appointment in the city at 2 p.m. with the one and only come extra blogger
We finally shall meet face to face
So we got to prep the office
Got to make sure everyone's ready and we all have our shields up and on and of course
I got to get the cameras ready to roll because there's nothing like
This type of meeting of the mind. It's it's going to be outstanding. I hope
Okay, daily source code calm. I'll also put an embeddable video of
Dig the code in on the home page your daily source code dot com in the show notes link to it
And of course my email addresses adam at podshow.com
portions of this program brought to you by Tylenol PM check out Angie B's awesome show which I've been looking at the feedback
The people are misunderstanding they really love that that show
It's unbelievable
The unwind out put I mean, it's not unbelievable because it's Angie, but it's just there's a lot of great response to it unwind dot podshow.com
Hey, I'll talk to you tomorrow
For the football Friday. Bye. Bye. Bye another pod show podcast stick it in your ear
You
The best and the brightest
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering podshow and limelight