Delta Sierra Charley's 6-0-9-er.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding.
It's a battle curry.
These shag and scuba watchin' the tube,
Shag said,
Like hey, scuba look at her bones.
I was glued to the tube,
Like a bad habit.
I got a heart on for Jessica Rabbit.
I had to have it till I changed.
The station can't believe I'm any tunes.
I had been craving masturbation.
Oh my god.
Yeah, you know what?
Eat the moths of all three girls.
Power pop.
I do the little mermaid with legs of fans.
Take a swim, get laid.
Then throw it back in.
Sift Jasmine from Aladdin.
Need to stab it.
No white, I do that whole right all night.
So tight she make that overturned white.
And sticks in the rela.
That dismissors say Chao Bella.
And do her step sisters.
eBay her slippers.
Get me a stripper and make her go.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Like flipper.
These are the cartoons.
I like to burn.
Come on, mother and children.
Come on, mother and everybody.
I personally like blue.
And laugh, mother and son.
Come on, mother and children.
Come on, mother and everybody.
Now I don't know if it's wrong.
Do you want a shag?
But I think I do bugs bunny and drag.
Uh, maybe not.
But I'd love to get some wet pun from Miss Judy Jetsun.
Let Josie and opposing cats get me wet.
I'm the only one in the village doing smart fit.
I can wonder woman time me up with your labyrinth.
You fiddles through the queen and the prince of Egypt.
Sherriette.
Betty Rubble and I could do it on a boulder.
And I'd be fucking pebbles if she was a little older.
Oh, I need a tasty piece of bill from beauty.
And the beast and tell Kim possible I want to come in
and take the form of a dildo with the female Wonder Twent.
Yeah, these are the cats.
I like to burn.
Come on, mother and children.
Come on, mother and everybody.
I like blue.
And laugh, mother and son.
Come on, mother and children.
Come on, mother and everybody.
Yeah, I'm a horny sun.
Is I do that robot made from richy rich.
I like the princess from trectow.
What I mean so far rough that asked till my tongue turned green.
Then Macme deafening from Scooby-Doo.
I had her too.
Then hop on top of Charlie Brown's teacher.
Walked from the front.
From behind it from beneath her.
But the ultimate kill that I've been craving is the hot brunette.
Bitch on the bunch of sun made raisins.
Please, I like you.
I like you.
Come on, mother and children.
Come on, mother and everybody.
I like blue.
And laugh, mother and son.
Come on, mother and children.
Come on, mother and everybody.
Yeah, I'm a horny sun.
Come on, mother and children.
Come on, mother and child.
Come on, Mother and children.
Come on, mother and children.
a nice start to a memorial day, uh, bank holiday weekend to play a song like that, uh,
it's on YouTube. I'll put a link in the show notes. I, if it's not pod save yet, I really hope
it does go pod save. You gotta see it in context, uh, with the actual cartoons you're singing
about. Uh, so it's, uh, yeah, it's pretty much been three days of the same, uh, for this long weekend.
It's bank holiday here in the United Kingdom. It's Memorial Day weekend in the United States. I'm
not quite sure what it is in other countries, but it seems like every country has something
going on today. The Netherlands has, um, I believe a religious holiday called Pinkstudent,
no idea what that is, which is pretty atrocious actually. I've certainly celebrated the day when we
live there, taking the day off without knowing what it was about. Let me just open up the window
a little bit for you. I'm in the, uh, in the attic on the third floor, the curry manner, uh, get
another weekend at home, which was now I always feel guilty though when you have a Monday that's
a long weekend. I feel like I should be doing something, you know, not just lounging around, but it's
really tough not to with this weather we've had. And I think it's, everybody I know that had this weekend,
you had great stuff planned. And of course, we'd had some wonderful weather in the, in the past couple
weeks. And really, I think it just doused everyone, uh, formula one. See, did, uh, there was
chance of rain for formula one in Monaco. There was definitely rain at the Indy 500 in, uh, Indian
apolis. In fact, I, I don't even know who, who won yet because I had to just tune out. There was,
they were showing the last 20 races of last year's race. It was, so, so rained out and just,
it kept coming down. So I'm up here. I've got the, because it is significantly colder in the,
in the previous couple days. I've got the fire place on, uh, Cindy, uh, the cat that I found in the,
in the gas station trash. He's up here, sleeping away on the couch. And it's really, it's kind of
mellow. And I'm figuring, besides maybe the, uh, the sills at the beginning of the show, maybe,
uh, you know, just play a little bit of chill music, shoot the, shoot the bull. Uh, hopefully
most of the people who listen to show have the day off. Listen to that outside. Listen to that rain.
Ooh, that's not thunder. That's, uh, that's the wind blowing against the second microphone. I
cleverly placed in front of the window to give you the impression that I'm sitting here. Well,
actually, I'm sitting here with the window open. Listen to what it does kind of have a nice vibe to it.
Anyway, I caught that video from, uh, self off of John DeVorex, uh, blog, John C. DeVorex blog. Yo,
Adam, trucker Tom here. John C. DeVorex, joining pod show. It'll never work. Just kidding.
Welcome John to, uh, pod show. I've enjoyed John's articles over the years and, uh,
glad to see him coming to pod show. You know, it's really been interesting since this news came out.
And I was listening to, uh, to twit, uh, which is this weekend, I guess is this weekend's episode.
I think it went up today. And at the, and I saw I already saw on the show notes at the end of the show.
I listen to the entire show and indeed, near the end of the show, um, they talked about, uh,
John joining pod show. And I think John was a little bit surprised at, um, at the, uh, at the level of
joking that took place amongst this core group of, of twits. And I don't think he was entirely prepared for it.
It was pretty cool. He, you know, they, they kind of snowed him under. I liked it. He did a shitty job
of explaining what he's going to do, by the way. And, you know, what, what we did when John was on the
show, um, was it, uh, Thursday, you know, went through the press release and kind of smiled about how it
was written in all these fantastic quotes. And you know, that's exactly what, uh, what, what, what Leo
was doing is like, yeah, of course. You got to be prepared for that, man. You know, when you're with pod show,
you know, you, you, you're with the Death Star. He has no idea what's coming. He's going to wish
he had danger pay. And, you know, I've read all kinds of stuff around, uh, around the blogosphere
and the pod atmosphere, I've been hearing things. It's in blog posts, um, the, a very complimentary
thing. It's a great thing. Uh, the John is, is joining pod show. I don't think people really understand
why he's joining. And if you think it's for the money, then, well, you'd have to ask him about that.
Um, I think he wants to figure out how the Death Star works. I think it's some personal
satisfaction he wants to get. And he was on Twitter, which was great, because of course,
that was the entire deal. You know, if he, uh, he can continue with cranky geeks, if he wants,
um, which I, I encourage him, I really want him to do that. It's a great show. Um, he can, uh,
do Twitter, his, you know, the, the columns he writes, you know, the, hey, this is,
he's doing a certain number. We don't know him. He's asked forever. Like, and like anybody,
am I asked his own? Here's something funny, though. I'll see who sent me this. Um,
Brent, pod show radio. So I was watching Leo today on stick cam, stick cam, doing his live
KFI show. Okay. So I guess he has a, uh, a webcam in the studio while he's doing his, his radio show.
I did not get the entire conversation with Leo started out by saying, I'm not a big fan of pod show.
At that point, I thought, this might get interesting and started recording. What you are hearing is
Leo talking to someone during a commercial break, possibly as producer. So you'll only hear Leo's
part of the conversation. I've enclosed the recording. I think you might be interested in this.
And, and I, you know, I think that Leo is exactly this kind of guy. He's a sweetheart, you know,
and he'll put webcams and, and any, you know, live streams all around him and he'll, you know,
just put his life out there and with that comes stuff like this, which is pretty fun.
Greed if, if I asked him at any time, not to, you know, he said, I won't plug pod show at all.
You know, I don't need to plug pod show. So we'll just see, I mean, I, you know, I'm not going
to fire him. He's, you know, he's a critical part of Twitter. I might use him a little less.
What I'd love to do is find some replacements for him. There's nobody like him. I need to find,
I mean, he's got a great sense of humor. He's got a great pacing, you know, he understands bro.
I mean, I just hear what Leo says. This is so amazing. I need to find someone to talk
how to place him. He likes much form. There's nobody like him. I need to find somebody like him.
I mean, he's got a great sense of humor. He's got a great pacing, you know, he understands broad casting.
His knowledge, you know, is, is fantastic. And he's got this great well-known persona.
So it'd be very hard to replace John. Just like it'd be very hard to replace Merlin on Mac
Breakweekly. I mean, I think John or, you know, J.R. Youwing, you know, that's just when you have that.
And I agree with you, Leo. John's going to work has that. I was just watching the show on channel
four last night. Guy went out and interviewed different actors on Dallas and J.R. Youwing.
I mean, you got to hear that guy's story. He, when they shot J.R. He literally held out and said,
okay, well, you have two ways to go. Either you can replace me or you can change the story line.
But I'm not coming back until you let me do this, this and this, which included in essence,
a large part of control over the show. And he held out and he got it.
And why was I saying that? Oh, yeah. Because, you know, it's like some people just aren't replaceable.
Absolutely.
Agreed. Merlin have kind of the same roles on those podcasts. They're really the, the kind of the focus of the podcast.
Pixel Core is not competing because Pixel Core doesn't. I mean, they're a little bit competing,
but not really. They're, I don't know what he's talking about now about Pixel Core.
They're doing different, the fringes of the stuff we do.
What, my biggest fear of John would be competing if, you know, already he's competing with cranky geeks.
Cranky geeks is basically a video of twit. I don't worry about people doing video.
I don't think video competes with audio. I don't think that's fair to say either, you know.
Cranking geeks is not exactly a video of twit.
Well, unless you take into account that a lot of the vibe of the show is because of
John Devorek podcasting. But if John decided to do an audio
roundtable news podcast on pod show, that would be it. And then I might kind of feel like,
well, he's doing his own thing. You know, but Kevin started Dignation. I was unhappy about that,
but he's always welcome on Twitter. He does that turns out he doesn't come on ever.
Patrick's doing DLTV. That's more like the screen savers. I mean, everybody's got their own thing.
We don't have a deal with these people not to, you know, that they can't do their own thing.
I don't want to be in contract.
So I don't guess he's listening to the producer saying something because it's just a gap in this in this recording.
Well, there's lots of people who say get rid of Devorek. I would never, I love this.
Everyone should have one of these little hidden recorders in their house.
But this is, I don't think he's saying anything bad. This is fantastic. This is Leo being completely honest.
And the way I think he always is. If someone asked him this, he'd probably say it the same way.
Not sugar code. I'm not going to do that. I John and I go back way back. I mean, he got me my start in the tech.
So, all right.
And so then there's another
exactly tech girl. I don't pay these guys. I can't fire them.
I could use him less or Twitter using them not at all. I think he's important.
Yeah. All right. So that's kind of the end of it.
That was pretty cool. Listen in on the stick can.
All right. Keep that vibe going that I had with the fireplace and the cat make on the cat.
Oh, the growing light. I slow up and breath the sea.
Burn and ride, I can sense the heat. Deep inside.
Don't play with fire. I love her. He'd hate this more.
That's the aspercesome. I don't get too close.
It's taking me so far. It's just a joy to protect you.
Yeah.
Tanks spoke with words that inspired the stars.
Wild winds spread of forest fog with hands so hot.
Give me the degree I can barely breathe.
Listen your heart on me.
Don't play with fire. I love her. He'd hate this more.
Wow. It's the aspercesome.
I don't get too close. It's taking me so far. It's just a joy to protect you.
And the pleasure. Love her. He'd hate this more.
It's the aspercesome. I don't get too close. It's taking me so far. It's just a joy to protect you.
Don't play with fire. I love her. He'd hate this more.
Wow. It's the aspercesome.
I don't get too close. It's taking me so far. It's just a joy to protect you.
And the pleasure. Love her. He'd hate this more.
It's the aspercesome. I don't get too close. It's taking me so far. It's just a joy to protect you.
It's the aspercesome. I don't get too close.
It's taking me so far. It's taking me so far. It's taking me so far.
You know, it's not entirely perfect, but it's just something about it.
It works really. You can go to a page on the positive music network. Let me see.
I remember now. Yes. That's a Rachel Pearl. Don't play with fire here in Curie's Jell's cafe.
Just with Tennessee. She has a couple of very interesting songs. You check it out. Rachel Pearl.
Of course, a link to let me get the outsides back in there. Oh, shit. See, I got all my
production here. Trying to bring you into that mood. That's really what I intended to do for today's show.
Just talk a little bit. Play a couple of mellow songs. See how far we get while the rain just
keeps on pissing down literally. I was planning on perhaps even going off to Germany today or tomorrow,
but it seems like the entire world has just come to a grinding halt. I hope that by the time you
hear this, you're at least in a portion of the type of vibe that I've had for the past couple of days.
There's only one thing that I'm really bummed out about today. That's that I've promised myself
and really carry who is maintaining my schedule here at the UK crash pad, which I'm going to tomorrow.
I have to do the administration here at the manner. I've already started all the
bank statements, which I get so many bank statements. I hate that. The majority of them just call
an opened, but then the pile of stuff to do, there must be at least 50 envelopes and I'm
dreading that. I asked you like a... Speaking of Germany, a whole bunch of people responding to my
call is to, you know, what kind of what city should we take a look at? And I think that in general,
it's come down to Cologne, Cone, as they would say, or Hamburg, and a lot of great response.
Seriously, and here's an example of one. Hi there, and it's Mark from Hamburg Germany,
good to hear that Pacho is coming to Germany, and hey, of course, you'll be choosing Hamburg.
Hamburg is a beautiful city with already music scene, we have lots of water, and of course, we have
Hamburg International Airport that's 25 minutes from downtown, and we have a couple of smaller
airports around. So, come on over, check it out, it's Mark from Hamburg plus 49. Okay. All right, Mark,
see, that's what I mean, that's extremely cool, and I'd be getting so, so many of those,
and suggestions and podcasts that, of course, I've never stumbled upon yet, you know, and I'm
learning the landscape, and I also do have to get back to San Francisco, though, it's just like,
so much to do. There's a lot of stuff that comes from Germany, and in fact, one of the original
Mac Datties of the Podsafe Music Movement comes from Germany. Do you know that? Can you guess
who it is? I mean, his stuff has been around for a long time, and on the network, some of his
stuff is performed by Mario Agiero, and you probably recognize this. This is the, the Moonlight
piano sonata of the 27 number two movement one from Ludwig van Beethoven, a fine upstanding
Podsafe, German citizen.
Now, bad, huh? Especially when you consider a man Ludwig van Beethoven through that one down
over 200 years ago. I don't care why you say any song that's being played more than 200
years after it's been released, you know, there's something going on there. It's just, I think
about these classical songs, that was long. I was like six minutes, it doesn't fit into my,
you know, my three to four minute format, but we've morphed into. But of course, he would have been
happy to know that listening to this on an iPod or in a web browser or almost anything you're
listening to it on, you could just fast forward through the boring bits. I wonder if he would have
minded, and by the way, for those of you that think that he's from Austria, he moved to Austria
when he was around 20, but he was born in, I think was born in, he born in Bonne, another candidate
for Partio HQ. Hey Adam, this is Chris Mahquard from Germany, host of tips on the top floor and
a proud member of the Partio family, and I hear you talk a lot about Darmstadt recently, so it sounds
very interesting to me, and I'm really looking forward to all the news that you're going to bring
home around that. I'm also an active podcaster in Germany for the German market, so
we might want to talk about a few things here. I've also just released my show number 200 of tips
on the top floor, if you want to see Drucker Tom as an alien, Don and Drew Dancing,
CC Japanese singing, and of course the Jeff Smith who wrote the theme song for the show,
then yeah, go and over to tips from the top floor.com, lots of photography tips in that show as
well, and by the way, I'm not even going to go into what Darmstadt actually translates to.
Anyway, didn't I only translate this? I know. Oh, I did.
I think I played that, you know, I'm fried, man. Did I play that on Friday? Like an idiot, I'm
rolling it. I doesn't matter. Crab, I know this one didn't go out on Friday.
Hello, Mr. Adam Curry. I've just been to the Partio Sutlus Zone. I finished the survey, and I'm
pretty pissed off because I think Partio is beautiful. I love what you guys are doing. I love the fact
that you will host my podcast for free and you can put your ads in and whatever I don't care,
but, you know, these are doing a great service. But the main problem that I find with the Partio
site is that it's very complicated. It's cluttered. And I think it needs to be nice. So here I go
into the survey and I'm answering all these questions. And that ones you talk about the design
so come on guys, you got to get into a six-glistan design, make it easier, make it, you know,
let's cluttered. That's all I ask. Hey, hey! Yeah, I know! Now, obviously if you think that
this juncture where we have the sock-less zone and we're surveying as to how we can sock less,
if we didn't know that something needed to be fixed with design, we would have been in a very
sad state. So you'll see that there are a number of questions that have to do with the
functionality of the design and that's exactly what you're talking about. And of course we have
I mean, this is, there is a plan, believe it or not, there is an actual plan and people
say search sucks. That's right. New search being implemented across the board. So it's
things like that and it just takes time. But I do appreciate you for completing the survey
and I hope you'll continue to work with us just to help us suck less and get some real data
to the people who produce this stuff. I'm dying to know, I'm just dying to know what some
of the answers to this survey are. And everyone, you know, gets to everyone who participates,
particularly all the producers, what do you have? Like, I don't know how many we have. It's like
8,000 shows on the network or something like that. It doesn't matter, even if it's 80 or 80,
just getting that information is fantastic. So I really do appreciate it. And then I got this from
a couple of people. Sinclair was the most recent one who sent it in. No carmers and the CEO,
yeah, the CEO of Syria satellite, radio, who of course is trying to come together with XM to create
one big satellite monopoly. Make no mistake. That should, of course, never happen. These companies
probably should just go away. I mean, it just makes no sense to have, when I suppose to have
monopolies, this is not the way it works. There's probably too many, too many people who've got
options and shares in their pockets. So we'll see what happens there. It doesn't matter. No carmers
and said, well, it's about to talk about the stock prices versus value. Each of these companies
I think loses $600 million per half here. It's just an amazing amount of money. But he said,
no, well, we suck less than XM. That can't be a mistake. That can't be a coincidence,
either. It's not. And if you think that big media isn't listening to what, not just what
Pod chose doing, but to what we all collectively are doing, you're making a mistake. Of course,
they are. Of course they're listening. They're not stupid. And of course, they've heard that
fricking suck less. So many times. I think a attention, Jeff Smith, we're going to need some,
let's do a country version. Let's do a hip hop version. We already have different podcasts
with doing, we've got to do some shorter versions because I will have to shoot myself. Or at least
until we get, you know, like 7,000 people who said, let's do that. Yeah, we could always turn the
suck less zone around. We won't turn off the suck less sawing until, until you've all taken the
survey. Post the name of that movie. It was some horror movie. Was that, or Friday the 13th or
Nor was Halloween. It was some kind of thing that kids had. It was a wristband or a toy.
And you'd hear the song on television. Nine more days, tailhandle, a wean, something like,
what the hell was the name of that movie? Kind of helped me out. This fine team is quality.
So actually, the art of music is the art of speaking with this fine team is quality.
Yeah, definitely. Yeah.
Wow.
It's like 1 in one, and you put it around and Defce your.
To run to different