Hello, these is Fabio, and as you know, I love hair, I love long flowing hair.
That's why I love it when the lady Patricia is on the daily source code, because you can just hear all the wonderful hair,
Adam's hair, Patricia's hair, it's wonderful.
So for the DSC, 574, please let me hear all of her hair.
Sometimes an Adam's all alone, and he needs his love right there on the microphone.
So here she is, yes, the lady Patricia.
The say to have some better than one, and with this angel from above,
There's nothing that they both can't do.
But make you wildest dreams come true, to grab your earbuds and jam them in.
And let the fabulous show begin.
It's Adam and Patricia.
Yes, Adam and Patricia.
Adam and the lady Patricia.
I never meant to cause you any pain, oh my love.
For my love.
When you said I think I knew it before then, why love?
I never thought that I could take it anymore, but you got me coming, going like never before.
And now I wonder if it's all over now.
Yes, and now I wonder if it's all over it's how.
Because I'm giving up just a little bit, but when I stop that's when I'll quit,
I wonder if it's all over now.
You say you think we need to grow more, oh my love.
Why love?
I think that we could grow forever together, my love.
For my love.
You said you got me, it's a dream of your life, but you just remember that.
Daisy never became his wife.
And now I wonder if it's all over now.
Yes, and now I wonder if it's all over it's how.
Because I'm giving up just a little bit, but when I stop that's when I'll quit,
I wonder if it's all over now.
I can't take it.
No, I can't take it anymore.
She told me, oh she told me.
I can't take it.
So you know I will be gone by the morning.
I never knew I'd be born.
I never really said it till I was alone.
No, I'd be the life I'd be born.
To go on living it if I'm alone.
No, I wonder if it's all over it's how.
Yes, and now I wonder if it's all over it's how.
Because I'm giving up just a little bit, but when I stop that's when I'll quit,
I wonder if it's all over it's how.
When I sleepucity it's all over the world
It's all over the night
All over the night
Dude yeah, I checked out the daily shortage card like you told me, too
Yeah, but Adam had his wife on yeah, he's married
Yeah, I thought so too. My gain arm must be off, but man you gotta go to flicker and check out these pictures
She is so hot and man the voice is so sexy. It's awesome
Yeah, so listen she's supposed to be on the show today
So I'm gonna go download it so I'll talk to you later. Bye
Daily source code episode 5 74
Do you think she's on do you think she's here?
Hey baby voice is so sexy. Yeah, baby ladies and gentlemen, please welcome the lady Patricia
I think I have to
Talk like this then yeah, well, it's not that hard to do because it's Sunday night in Adam's attic
We're here in the curry manner on the third floor
Yes, and the affluent suburb of Surrey known as gulfard. Yeah, we are in G-town west side represent
It's my whole thing. I know you don't listen, but I've been doing that for like a year
Represent yeah, hey baby. How you doing? Yeah, I'm doing fine
I appreciate you coming on the show because as I told you if I weren't doing a show with you tonight
I would definitely would not have done one you would have collapsed. Oh, man. I'm so tired. Yeah, you didn't even once
Wanted sex yesterday. Uh, no, I didn't you're right?
That's right. I put on my sexy voice and didn't and actually no, no, no, no, no
That's not how it went. We were at home
Christina was at the movies with a friend in her first. Let's go to bed. No, you said
Well, what time is she coming home? I said I don't know you should be home like quarter 12 12 o'clock
Something like that and you said well, but we could have sex and I said well, no, I'm really not
I said why
Say what? No, but I had to get it really early this morning and and I was right after the fact she came
She came home like 10 minutes after that. So I'm quick, but yeah, not that fast
Don't take it the wrong way. Don't take it personally
You know that I'm very relaxed about it. Okay. No problem. No problem. So this is a really weird show to do
First of all because we're doing it on Sunday night and it's the first time I think in
Since you've ever been on this show that there are at least well no, but there are three things that I know
I can't talk about and it's like it's really hard for me because there's all the stuff that I can't talk
Not going on. It's yeah, really there is and I hate it one one thing is we're never going to talk about it
Which one was that
Help me remind me of course my brain hurts. What was that the one we're never ever going to talk about or or just not now never
Oh, no, we're not going to talk about that one now. We won't talk about that one
All right
Yeah, that was a personal thing. Yeah, very very personal
No, because you actually you said yesterday. Oh, that's a nice thing for on the show. Oh, yeah
This is this is my new threat. This is what my life has become is that the only power I have in
You can talk about it. It's like well, I'll talk about on the show. You know, and I know that they'll never verify because you don't listen
You know, it's not a Christina listen, so
No, but I can say whatever I want. There's a lot of people listening that yeah, the problem is is that you know the all the the rags
Listen in Holland and then and they just make up stupid shit, so that's not worth it
But you're working on a great project and what it's nice to see is for the past
Week almost for almost the past week couple of months
I don't know when you're going to say oh no not couple of them now. I was gonna say
What do you think I'm going to say are you are you high are you high again?
I'm not the one who's high. Oh, okay, no for the past couple of days almost a week
You've been very excited and you know you're doing something very creative and you came up with an idea
And you've got some people involved and then that's it and I like this to you doing that. That's really cool
I like it especially because I don't have to do anything
I just said I have no responsibility in this project
At the same time. Well, that's because you're dancing. Yeah, I'm dancing and and I'm walking
Walking yes and the down walking yeah, every day
You look great you and you know what in this light? I you notice I have the dimmer set nicely for
Vol I is it only in dimmers? No, no, no, no, no, you look you look wonderful
But I just said notice how I even made it even better with all the light up here in my lovely
My bachelor pad. Did you know I lived up here like this that I had such a nice place
Nice place
So I I went flying today. Yeah, which was really nice and I had my hair done. That's basically I had a choice
Yeah, because of the wind commander brought the delta shower over here then I flew it back with the
And flu William and Captain Dan yeah back to Antwerp and back captain is asleep with his mouth open kitchen flies
You know, there's something about four guys in an airplane that's just wrong. Was it four guys?
Yeah, because I'm the day the
Yeah, he flew over. Oh
With William. Yeah, it's like all the everyone who has an airplane
We're all in this club, right and then it literally a need is helicopter
Anita yes
You flew with her so she's also kind of like in the William club, so yeah, I was offered hey
We can go fly the helicopter today
Yeah, I was like oh, I really want to fly the helicopter but I had that my hair done so I had I had to choose helicopter or fly to
Rotterdam and I had my hair done and and you know what I was yes, I chose for the hair
A bug flying helicopter because you are so vain gay
Or they use me. No, no, no, no, what is that supposed to mean? I know you always say that
It's not because you're so vain. It's just because it was too long it was way too long
Yeah, it was out of control and you would already cut it. Yeah, yeah, you already cut it in the mean time
I'm very particular about who touches my hair. I know
But actually I still like it when it's long. Well, it's not short. Is it too short? No
There's still that MTV guy in there. Yeah, but
Really yeah, but is it too short one that I love hello hello
Is it too short now? You don't like my hair? I noticed you guys weren't overly enthusiastic about it
It's always like he come in it's like of course I had a you know headphones on all day
So it looks like shit, but
You don't like it?
I have to run my hands in my fingers. Well, you better get up at six thirty tomorrow morning because I'm leaving at eight
No, I will. Oh, baby. Yeah, oh by the way, it was the firerapes at the top of the show
From South Carolina with Wonder which they just put up on the ponts eight music network. Was not an awesome song
That yeah, we didn't talk about that, but I really really love that song. There's so 70s
And I hear there's a lot of 70s
Going on yeah, well obviously yeah, there are influences the beetles the pretenders the kings oasis the doors
Yeah, don't yeah, and sort of Gary in the pacemakers a little bit the Gary or Jerry
Jerry the pacemakers that Jerry in the pacemakers, and then there's a little four chance to remember the four chance
Silence is golden you got you got my I got my troubles. You got mine
No, it's uh you've got your trouble. Oh, yeah, you've got my
Something like that
So I do I do I do I do
Oh, man, but in the song that you just play do just one thing that irritated. Oh, really
Okay, guys pay attention here comes Patricia
The bass the bass you didn't like the bass no because it's kept on doing that
You know and and and there is a moment that you expect you know
When the chorus and the chorus came that the bass changes into some other
Down a little bit and lays down and really that would have relaxed it a little bit
Yeah, I'm so amazed when you say I mean that that that is so amazing to me that you understand how that works
Because I I don't even hear I mean of course I hear the bass but I'm paying attention very hard for me to
Explain it in English, but that you didn't damn good job. I get it. I get it, but that's like
You're a studio animal is what you are you love making records in the studio and you know what I can tell that on the internet at the moment
There's a lot of discussions going about
Christina Aguilera's candy man. Yeah, what about it the candy man. Oh, we have a candy man on the show
Yeah, the Luke who gives me all the Nokia stuff. Okay, but he's the candy man
All that the candy man of that's a new song of
Christina is it new? No, it's sort of yeah, it's from our album and it's sort of a
Andrew sisters kind of a thing
Everybody is
You're discussing it and and and talking about it. That it's very very much based on Andrew sisters and the star sisters
So that would be that would be me the star sisters as in you. I am I'm all the star sisters
Interesting me and my really where they said where they're talking about that on the internet
Yeah, on those series of tubes. Yeah, you saw it. We're in there. You know, I got to watch out because
Patricia these days is
Creedian proficient with the with the computer. Yeah, hold on a second. I got a peek. I got it here
One here piece of it of Aguilera song
Oh man, it's tough
Of course, it's not but but not not only the song
In her video clip yeah, she has the same outfit on as the star sisters
She does the same things with her hands on her cheek as the star sister
You know as our album sleeve and as our
Then CD
Do you think she was inspired by
You know who was looking and you never know
You never know
Okay, I got it. I hear right there
That's cool. And of course, doesn't listen to that sound
Oh
Dancing damn
Right
But is that a new song is that that's not a new song but very much
Boogie will give you a good boy, and yeah, yeah, from company be from company
Yeah, does sound like
Okay
Well, there's one thing of course a long time ago, and then you know it is different
Well, then she needs the full package doesn't she she needs the full inspiration
She needs to
I don't know try I'll send it to her
No, she has to just to come drop by me if she wants to have the full Patricia pi experience of your your video and you
I think that's it
Yeah, what you she should have that she should have what I don't know the full experience
How much is what
But it's amazing and people are talking about it and which is of course. I'm proud of that
It's true though because there's so many things now. I should play your song. I don't know where so many things I did and I think I've been there done that
Yeah, have it up here
How did you do with it?
Yeah, there must be another one. Oh, no, it took it down. That's all I'll get it for you. I'll get it for you
Yeah, oh wait, I got a copy. Yeah. Oh, this is a CD copy
I know we've we've played this before on the show haven't we? Yeah, okay. This is from almost
Although actually the yeah, this is from 19 UK
There's also UK
Mix on it
Which one the the mega mix you want to play the mega mix? Well, would you rather play that?
Well first you have to the first one is of course. Well, it's not the Patricia pie show here
You know I'm just I'm just being nice to my game over
Just being courteous to you. What do you want me to play? I didn't say anything you
Yeah, that's right. I want to play it. You said no, but you have to first play this when they play that one
No, no, no, I said there's also a UK mini mix on there or right and I said she'll I play the UK mini mix
No, because that's not the the okay. This is the one
But you have to see this this is 25 years old, of course. Yes, yes
Your sister
I'll do two harmony
Yvonne just one
Now
And that's you
Oh, I was going to say what a fantastic bit a little break there. That was well produced
I want you the mega mix is bad. This is the I like this one
This is the UK mix, right? Yeah, but that's different songs and Mal and Montenegro
But it's amazing
And no, but and actually nobody ever saying all those harmonies on this song
Which we did
Yeah, that's right
Nobody ever did. That's nice. Well, Agreleiro will do it on our next record. Don't worry. Probably
You're doing Mal and Montenegro. I speak in of
a homemade music
courtesy who sent me this
This is from Louis Pitz
The ungarage band you can turn off the vocals and then make your own lyrics like karaoke
I want to be
Like that
Look my best teacher
Good
I got to go to God
Tells it out to a shiara
It's a
That's one nice
I should sing that's at the reunion
There we go
Oh
We'll light up all the time
It goes on for quite a while actually
Oh my god. Isn't that funny? He could be heroes. He said. Yeah, it's Bowie song. Yeah. Yeah, it's got it's really good at the end
The guy really gets into it. Fantastic. Hey, so um
You are the proud user of a sling box
Yes, why don't you tell the peeps about your sling box? I don't know what to say, but I
What I know how's your sling box baby? I have on my computer
in the kitchen
TV
Wonder and it's easy to operate and everything works easy just one click
And it's on and it's there
It's amazing. Yeah, I mean you and it looks good
It's it's beautiful. It's clear. It's it's one of what you don't need another
TV because I had two of those screens there
My computer and of course
But they're like a little bit closer bit and the TV and
That was too full too much
Okay, and now I have only the computer and there's TV on it and you and
So you're digging it. Yeah
Would you recommend a sling box to any of the listeners do I get money for they
Do I have to say yeah? Oh, no, they're not sponsoring the show
What's going on
I'm just asking you no because
You know
This was a big problem because I couldn't take away your television and I had my TV on in kitchen it was
Constantly
You are on the computer. No, no, it was not me on the computer. Who was it then? No, listen
You it was actually it was you not on the computer. Oh, it was your computer sitting right next to the television
Your computer was trying to cook
But every time Christina came home and she was, you know on her computer
It started right and well, if you came home too
Right any computer basically that comes out of sleep mode and and has to find the the network
It's gonna it was it was made. It was causing interference
What's farting in your kitchen basically horrible? Yeah, yeah, so you're just just coming
When's the I'm very excited
When's day she's come until the next Wednesday and you're leaving so that's great
That's awesome
That's awesome. It's really great. You're late. It's naughty. It's so nice. You're leaving. Yeah
Yeah, we miss
Oh, not as much because you know, yeah, you've on us here
What are you guys doing? Um, well, then there's my birthday
which we're not gonna do
I'm not gonna really think about it, but
He said you said to me what do you want him for your birthday and I said I want a shopping spree and by things for my sister
You so nice yeah
She's a woman alone and it's okay as long as it's under 75 pounds
I love to give. I don't like it when people give you give me presents, you know, birthday
Bullshit stupid. No, maybe not your but you love presents. What are you talking about?
Christmas you give presents
That is my birthday. What is so funny about getting older getting closer to death?
What is so funny about that? What do you think it's funny at all? But no one said a birthday had to be funny
You're you're celebrating your life you're celebrating that you're still here isn't that isn't that good?
Isn't that I'm celebrating that every day? You know that it's so undudged
A birthday for me is every day. Yeah, I know. I know you're special
But you are you're almost anti-birthday now. Yeah, I'm anti. I'm going backwards now. I'm not going forwards anymore
I'm a stop count. Excuse me, you know
The last couple of days of keep asking people what do you think they're talking about me about my daughter over
This and then I said yeah, I'm too old for that. You're not old and I'm now I'm trying to say you know to find out what do they think how old do they think you are?
Do you think you are most people think you're a 35? Yeah, 35 sure. I found out 35. That's great. Okay
Well, just keep it that way then
Yeah, it's it's it's it's quite a job. No you but you're a biological
I'll tell you that before it it's I'm you are the the dick Clark of uh
The House of ladies
Series satellite listeners more pod show on the way for you
Being I can hear all the good stuff. No. Yeah, they got to go. Well, do I have a secret?
I'm sorry. Yeah
Yes, how do you do this your secret is moisture eyes?
Moisturized and moisturized moisturized moisturized and
exfoliate and have a young husband young husband who gives you no sex one when request
Who would rather have his hair done than fly helicopters? Yeah, yeah, you know
Doesn't matter
There's more in life
Okay, and I'm not gonna be here for your birthday and and it's not like first time. Yeah, but you said it was okay
You said it didn't matter. No, we had a true head of choice, right? That's true, right? I had a true true
But I don't like it anymore, so that's it. Yeah, that's it. Birthdays are now over there no longer envelope
No
So when I come back the week after next and of course I'll have I'll have completely missed your sisters visit which I'm I'm bummed about
I was supposed to come home
next Monday, but it's gonna be two to two or Wednesday
Then we're going on vacation. I haven't yes. Yeah. Yes. That's some this
That's a long time ago a year one year ago. We were in Portugal. Yeah, and it's the same thing everything
This is what happens with we do you know it's summer and
You know we enjoy the house and we enjoy the backyard and we enjoy the flower nature and each other and it's all love and
It's so and yeah, and where's it going?
Well, so what I'm saying is so we usually don't go away during the summer holiday
Don't give a shit. No, we don't
We don't give a shit about the we already haven't a good time. Yes, like it's like our own holiday
I need to go right, but then after the winter and this always happens and for 20 years that we've been together
After the winter you you have like cabin fever and you just go and nuts and you need sun
It's your like a flower a bit of sun. You need you need sun big time
It's gonna be beautiful. So we always wind up like freaking out because everything is always booked
Christina only has you know or her Easter vacation of course the whole rest of the freaking country is going on Easter vacation
Yeah, so this time and I and I want my chain is stuck this time. I wanted to go to Jamaica because we could
Actually we wanted to go to Jamaica because I really miss Jamaica
Yeah, because we could fly for free. Yes, actually with you know with all my virgin miles. Yeah, why don't we go to Jamaica?
Because it's too short, but it's not it makes no difference and no no no no where no flights
That's what you said
That's right, you know flights during the east of vacation. Yeah, now you have to book a year in advance or someone's
So it will be nice. It will be nice. We're going to
Taneary fe taneary fe taneary fe taneary fe taneary fe. On the roti and taneary. Okay, we're going to taneary fe
The hotel oh, I don't like Spain. No, I'm sorry
I mean the- But you hardly notice it there you will we you will
You will notice that. It's very, very unspain.
What kind of people are there?
All sorts of people.
Okay. People who can afford it.
Any hot chicks?
Yeah.
No, really?
What?
Most hotels we go to are like family.
Not cheap, because you know...
No shit.
You know what the girl said from your wife?
Was it your bank or was it?
Yeah.
She said, are you buying the island?
No.
They're horrible.
But, you know, for people who never go, it's good to go.
Once and good.
Yeah, that's true.
Right.
So that's why I'm not going to do a show.
I'm totally unplugging.
Yeah.
And I really want to enjoy it.
I'm very busy.
I'm going to do...
Then you're going to be gone for a week, aren't you?
You're doing a photo shoot for a glossy magazine?
I have another TV show to do.
And I have two days of photo shoot.
I think a couple of pages we have to do and a big interview.
Really?
Yeah, for glossy.
So, it's going to be very nice.
Yeah.
All right.
Can you tell me what you're going to do?
Is it the theme or is it naked?
I might show myself.
No, really?
No, you're kidding me.
I don't know.
You're not really going to do that already.
Maybe.
You're kidding me.
It's all about...
What are you going to show?
I don't know yet.
Wait a minute.
This is not being discussed with me.
I didn't know you're going to...
You're not going to do naked pictures already?
No.
You said I'm maybe going to show myself.
No, no.
It's going to be very sexy.
Yeah.
Very sexy.
Very glamour.
What's very sexy?
I don't know yet because I'm not going to tell you before people listening.
I know.
They steal my idea.
I trust you.
I'll galera.
Stop listening.
I'll be honest.
You stealing her idea.
But it's all about girls over 50.
Okay.
It's a new 30.
And it's a girl's under 60.
Yes.
No.
Girls over 50.
And horny is hell.
Sort of.
You know?
Because it's not over yet.
No.
We're starting.
It's beginning.
Really?
It's a new journey.
Yeah.
And who's going to satisfy all your needs for this new frickin journey you're embarking on?
I'm over my sexual peak baby.
I definitely.
I think we're getting it back.
The girls are getting it back over 50.
Oh, man.
I really don't know what you're just just going to be doing.
Well, I'm gone.
I don't trust it.
No.
You shouldn't.
Shit, man.
It's 11.30.
We got it.
We got to stop.
Another song I wanted to listen to before we leave.
Okay.
This is another one.
Just showed up on the podcast and music network.
Let me just tell you this kid.
It was pretty interesting.
Hold on.
Ben Vega is his name.
He began studying piano at the age of five and composing it 10.
Since then, he's been involved in performing, arranging, teaching, conducting and recording.
He writes his own music and lyrics, performs all the instruments, and synthesizes the sounds.
Can I have his telephone number?
Well, the send of an email.
He's on the podcast, he's a network.
No, man.
Listen, but listen, it's pretty interesting.
This is, uh, take me away.
From this place right now, I want to go.
Take away all of these main feelings I like and call.
I want to be free free free from myself free.
Take me away free free.
Wanting to be what I can and I'll be with my mind.
Dreams that I should have never dreamed where I'll be now.
Take away all of these main feelings I like and call.
Life is much better when you're on the side.
I want to be free free free from myself.
Take away all of these main feelings I like and call.