Well, hey there, I'm Mr. Curry, this year's Elvis, Elvis, I don't know if you saw me
I was standing out in the front yard of Graceland, you're flying overhead going to New
York and I was waving, in the case you didn't, I would just wanted to tell you that there's
really nothing I like more than sitting back listening to the Daily Source Code with
Priscilla and the Colonel in the jungle room, it's really exciting to listen to all the great
music you have to chronic or our lives and the preservation of our lives is the very
important thing for Elvis.
More so is to hook up with just Smith one day, if you can get out here to admit this, we'll
make some great jingles for the DSC, for now Mr. Curry, on with this show, shows what you
got for the DSC, 663 of Fubar Friday, from the King to you, Mr. Curry, I wish it
Best.
Amen.
I'm a street or a game
Dr. Lissie
Do I believe in God?
Do I believe in me?
Or I believe in God?
Some people want to die
So they can be free
Dr. Lissie
Do I believe in God?
I just can't believe all the things we will see
Don't let me see, am I play all right, am I straight or gay?
Don't let me see, I can't understand you, man, to reassity
Don't let me see, but it could see you, was a much more mundane way to be
Don't let me see, don't let me see, don't let me see, don't let me see
Don't let me see, don't let me see, don't let me see, don't let me see, don't let me see, don't let me see, don't let me see, don't let me see, don't let me see
You can't hide, but you can't be cry
Some people wanna die, so they can be free
Don't try to see
I can't understand, you meant a real city
Don't let me see you
Was it to see you?
Was I what you wanted me to be?
Don't you see?
Do I believe in God?
Do I believe in me?
All I believe in God?
Some people want to die
So they can be free
I said, the love is just a game
We all just the same
Do you want to play?
Don't you see?
Don't you have a seat?
It's special thanks to James Thompson.
We found this on YouTube.
Not quite sure how it got through the video got through the YouTube sensors.
Very, very, no, no.
Let's just say smoking hot video.
It's kind of a mash up of, I think the original Crystal Water's Gypsy Woman and some version of Prince's controversy.
Controversy Controversy.
It is the Daily Source Code.
It's Monday from the manner.
What are we out today?
The 17th of September 2007.
Boy, it's good to be back home.
Good to be talking to you guys.
It was even a little bit worse than I thought.
I thought I would at least be able to get a footballer Friday out last week from the Curri condo.
No way.
Man, it has, and you know what, it's going to be like this non-stop probably until the Christmas holidays.
So be prepared.
What's interesting though is it, it really doesn't make much difference in, like my weekly numbers,
which I check from time to time.
It seems like if I do less episodes, more people listen to them, which is interesting food for thought.
Maybe this whole daily thing doesn't really make any sense in the, in the scene dependent media.
I don't know.
Unless it's really short, maybe it's too long for a daily program.
Stuff to think about, but oh, so much to talk about today.
So many things.
See, when did we last talk?
Was it the 11th of September?
Oh, God.
Since then, of course, I've received tons and tons of feedback about 911 videos and 911 inside job.
And I think even the 9, was it, what's the name?
There's something on there's now a 911 podcast on pod show.
I got to find that for you.
So again, I'm not really big into, hold on a second.
I'm wearing the Al Jazeera Bathroom a little bit warm up here today.
And I know that I have Amy standing by, so I need to see here.
There we go.
A little more freedom of movement.
Okay.
So should I recap what I did because it was messed up man.
We went, see, Wednesday, Wednesday night.
Ron and I flew to New York.
We had a couple meetings Thursday in the apple.
Including, this was a great meeting we had with Ted Leone.
So do you remember Ted and he's, I think he's still the vice chairman of AOL.
And I know him, I'll shit Ron and I both know him because back 10, maybe even 15 years back to,
what was it?
There was the greenhouse project and early days had a great chat with him.
That was a lot of fun to hook up with Ted and New York.
Did the other meetings?
And we've been busted and asked.
We've been talking to all kinds of advertisers, you know, the Christmas season coming up
and we're working at really, really hard.
Had to go back Thursday evening back to San Francisco because we had on Friday,
I met with, this was a cool meeting with the will Hearst of the Hearst Family Empire,
who owned tons and tons of media properties, newspapers, magazines,
and the editor of the Chronicle in San Francisco.
Bronstein, you know this guy.
He used to be married to Sharon Stone.
I don't know if they get a divorce or not.
I didn't ask him, obviously.
So that was kind of fun sitting in the Chronicles offices at San Francisco,
which was really old world like Daily Planet.
You expected Clark Kent to come walking out of the woodwork at any moment.
That was very interesting.
And, you know, just actually wound up, but by the time we were done, it was like nine o'clock.
And Ron and his lovely wife, styled even Marta, moved to a house outside of the city.
So I hadn't seen it yet, even though they've had it for a,
well, maybe a month now.
So, and even during this two weeks, I hadn't even seen his wife in so incredibly busy.
So we had some nice Chinese food, eight to the beach joined us.
We hung out.
It was really nice.
And I was like, all right, you know,
I'm, I'm so relaxed.
I'm starting to unwind.
By the time I got back, which was, I don't know,
I was back home at the condo around 11.30.
Quarter 12.
I just didn't have it in me.
I did not have it in me to do a football Friday.
I really apologize.
So, and of course, the trip back on Saturday with Virgin Atlantic.
And we just has absolutely no resemblance to Virgin America.
I'm not even going to get into it.
If you want to, I was so pissed off about just the experience on Virgin America,
but also my most recent experiences with the transportation safety
as it agency or administration agency, I guess, part of the Homeland Security.
Oh, man, this is so frustrating.
It just takes shit.
You know, I think they just look at,
it said, hey, wait a minute, this guy's got some nice colon.
Yeah, I think I need that.
I think I'll take this from this guy.
So messed up.
And you can travel around with my bag,
it's filled with transmitters.
We don't need no stinky transmitters.
You know, my wireless mic transmitter,
tons of wires, batteries, all, you know,
four different Nokia devices,
lighters,
possibly some other contraband.
But oh, no, what can we have to take away
the guys to deodorant?
Shit.
I meant this one.
Hi, it's Arthur's Iron from the SNS.com site.
Just a little bit about the aircraft security
and how they seem to help people having my own face.
Well, the main reason behind that is
it's so called binary liquid explosives.
We've got two separate liquids that are found on the run,
but it makes them a bit complicated.
The majority of it, however, is bullshit
because it's difficult enough to touch
the transport, well, produce and then
transport these things when you're an expert on it.
And you've got all of the relative stuff.
And I'm a chair that's going to be,
that's going to actually be trying to put this on to an airplane.
Doesn't stand the fucking chance without blowing themselves up.
It's total.
And it's bullshit.
Well, so leave you with this one.
See you later.
Bye.
Now, I'm, of course, this bullshit.
And it would be okay if it was a little more consistent.
You know, we traveled in New York.
I didn't want to check a bag.
So my carry on bag, and I had my toiletries in there
because, you know, I was going to take a shower
when we got to New York.
And so on the way over, what did they take from me?
They took my mouth wash.
It was, you know, a clear plastic bottle of
Listerine.
Clear.
You know, as you can see right through,
you can see what's in it.
Had never been open, still had the seal on it.
Oh, no, it's too big.
You know, it's kind of unclear what the size,
what size you're allowed to take.
Apparently, if you have like little samples from hotel rooms,
it's okay.
But if you have like a, and this wasn't like the family size.
This was just a personal size, you know?
Nope, got to take that.
Uh, what else do they take from me?
Well, everything else was cool.
But then on the way back, and then it was also,
I think it was like trainee day.
I was in the line for 45 minutes.
So besides, you know, taking off your shoes and all that.
And, you know, then it was like, well,
no, you can't have your hair gel.
You can't have, and with small sizes, right?
You can't have your deodorant.
You can't have your, uh,
uh, what a have clinic happy.
Uh, what else do they take from me?
Uh, moisturizer.
You know, just all the shit, but the,
the thing that really hurts me is the,
is the, is the way that this is done.
Now it's getting so clear that this is a fucking power trip
from the TSA, not all TSA, of course.
But, oh, man.
And now that these guys are government,
this is the same people who used to do airport security before.
So now they have nicer uniforms and,
and their government officials.
So you can't, like, fuck with them.
You can't have a big mouth.
You got a big mouth.
Oh, that's what, then all of a sudden,
shit really starts to slow down.
And, oh, we have to run your bag again.
Meanwhile, you know,
Ron was at the gate with his foot in the door of the airplane,
trying to keep it,
prevent him from leaving without me.
This was just horrible, man.
It's just horrible.
I can't even get into how stupid it is.
Look, either we really do security,
or we just kind of, you know,
just do the standard stuff.
You know, look for guns, weapons,
other things.
This liquid shit is out of control.
It's so stupid.
All right, okay.
It's been a while, and I've had a big star next to this
in my Gmail.
I've been trying to do a show in general,
but also trying to do one with my babies.
Yes.
And from all that airplane ride,
and I got to tell you,
my ass is fluffy again.
So Amy Max here to firm it up for me.
With the gluteus Maximus portion of the bag.
Hey Adam, it's Amy Max.
It's been weak.
Yes, I know.
My emails were continuously being rejected by your email account,
which has clearly decided on its own
that we should no longer communicate.
No, no, no, no.
It's not correct.
We should.
And so happy we were able to straighten everything out
that while you're in town.
So now that we're back on track,
let's get down to business.
Okay.
You're going to be lying on your back today.
So switch mics and get yourself situated.
Okay, I'm situated now.
I'm on my back.
Now put your legs straight up in the air.
Okay.
And then put your hands behind your head.
Lift those shoulders off the ground.
Oh, ow.
Now lower your right leg and twist your right elbow towards your left leg.
Oh, yes, I feel that.
And then switch.
And to the left.
You should be squeezing your butt and your stomach.
Make sure that you don't pull on your neck when you twist.
Okay.
Switch again.
You should feel the butt flexing every time you switch those legs.
I can feel your butt flexing.
Don't forget to breathe.
All right.
Now a few more switches.
One more squeeze.
Breathe.
And squeeze.
And breathe.
Okay.
Last four quickly.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
And relax.
Great job.
Now to make up for no butt squeeze this time.
Since we were feuding a little bit.
All squeezed twice.
Next time I see you.
I promise.
Oh, I can't wait for that.
All right.
Hugs to the girls.
Oh, and one last thing.
Yes.
I've started a 90 day fit life challenge to anyone wanting to shape up a bit before the holidays.
So if you could pass on the link to the training group site,
which is free to join, I would love to invite all the DSC listeners to join us.
Right.
Until next time.
Oh, baby.
Thank you very much, Amy.
Yes.
She refused to squeeze my ass at the office.
She said, oh, no.
Well, you haven't been doing the answers.
I said, I don't know.
I didn't receive it.
Or I got it.
And I lost it in the email.
I don't know.
Send it to me again.
So there was no squeezing.
So she couldn't really mark down progress.
But I'm pretty sure I've gone into remission.
With all this sitting on my ass that I'm doing.
Really, as it's like sit on my ass in the studio.
Sit on my ass in the car.
Sit on my ass in the condo.
Actually, the condo.
I don't sit on my ass that much.
I don't have any place to sit.
I have the couch.
I'm on the couch that I'm left.
I'm left.
I'm walking around standing.
Thank you.
That feels very good.
I miss so much cool stuff.
And if only I had known what was going on this weekend,
I might have even considered at least extending my stay.
Adam is running.
And that's the airport on my way to Reno.
I've got a long way over in Reno.
And you know what's going on this weekend?
The Reno air races.
We're planning on my part.
I should have called you a long time ago.
Yeah.
I hope you're still around.
And you know what?
If you can make it to the Reno air races,
it is absolutely something worth seeing.
Seeing a piston powered airplane fly at speeds faster than the red line of the
810 that I used to fly.
That's pretty amazing.
Hopefully you can make it.
Like I said, short notice.
But I'll give you an update from the air show at the Reno air races.
We'll talk to you soon.
Tailwinds.
Tailwinds my friends.
So that's Robin, of course.
From inside works and produces diva cast.
And he is a pilot for a major US airline.
I actually thought I heard him the other day when I was at San Francisco as a.
When I took United to San Diego for that.
I media thing that I was a lot of fun, by the way.
Yeah, I thought I heard him on that.
Because United has Channel 9 from the flight deck.
I sure was Robin.
It wasn't.
So I guess he was off to Reno.
And of course he called in, you know, just to rub it all in that I wasn't there.
Listen to this.
That's some hard hit and fast pace.
Nitro burning piston power.
The final phase.
Reno air races.
There's Robin's sailing.
Yeah.
Again, it's really time to get behind the controls of the Delta Sheriff.
Mine actually be going to Friday at to Friday on Germany to Germany on Friday.
So that'll be a nice trip to make.
And I think the girls have some kind of a ward show they want to go to.
So there could be some flying in the near in the near future.
Really hope so.
Because the weather, of course, is going to start get pretty shit pretty soon.
Which will limit some of the possibilities.
Not all, but some of them.
Some days of flying.
And so of course back here in the in the in the curry manner with the girls.
Good to see them and you know, we had a really sad.
Past couple of weeks is our darling Cindy was was killed.
Just outside our door.
And you know, of course we've been sharing this throughout the past few weeks.
Mainly over over the phone or a couple times an eye chat.
And but we really didn't have a chance to be together.
Yeah, and and grieve, I guess.
And Raymond poured y'all know Raymond.
He's a part of a podcasting legend certainly for the daily source code.
He's the guy that very early on is I was recording a show on a highway going towards Belgium.
He was honking next to me. He was listening to the previous day show.
Real moment in podcast history.
I'll see if I can find that episode stick it into the DSC channel.
He put together a beautiful kind of slideshow a quick time movie with pieces from the show that I dedicated to Cindy with the song.
Thank you for being a friend.
And and he sent a copy to Patricia and and I knew what was going to happen.
So she fired it up and it.
And so it was very emotional obviously.
And you know, it's kind of a personal thing and there's a lot of Dutch in it.
So it's not something I put out publicly.
And Raymond wants to that's obviously very cool and then I'll put a link.
I'll check I'll see if he posted it and I'll put a link to it.
But that of course got us both going.
And it actually was really a great moment because we needed some kind of catalyst to, you know,
to kind of get get the emotions out there and it worked.
I appreciate it Raymond.
It was I know that wasn't exactly why you intended to do it,
but it really did work and it was important.
So I appreciate that.
And we have a new cat.
And I'm happy that the girls went out and did this because I know it helps.
You know, I've had many, many pets.
We've had many pets.
None that have come to their end in such a dramatic tragic and sudden fashion.
So the hurt is is very deep in the shock is still very prevalent.
But they went out and they got from the from the animal shelter.
They got the cutest little black pussy.
Black pussy cat.
He is and they call him Mickey.
Mickey, the mixer, the mickenheimer, the micken dick a ding-dong.
He's I don't know how he's the only couple, maybe a couple months old.
I'll have to ask Patricia, but he is so cute and so sweet.
And he of course is filling a lot of the void here in the house.
Now ginger, other cat is not quite on board with the program.
And also, you know, he's also traumatized.
So you know, we got a, we got to give out lots of hugs and lots of stuff we got to do
with our, with our little animals.
I was going to, I'm just looking here.
I was going to play something for you.
I hear it is.
I'm not used to using the two button mouse anymore.
Hold on.
Here we go.
So what I was going to say, speaking of of pussy pussy cats.
Mark Yosher motor nem cough from Pacific Coast hallway.
I'm not quite sure what the deal is.
And I'm sure you'll listen to PCH and they'll give you the low down.
But he came to me.
He came to me several weeks.
Actually, before I left for for the States and he said, look, we're doing a,
a musical.
It's called pussy, the musical, an audio book.
And there's a, it's, so it's a musical.
And he got like 10 songs.
And he got people from around the net to to sing these songs.
I guess he wrote and he played the instruments.
And see, he's got Angie B doing a song.
He's got to PW Fenton doing a song.
He does a song.
He's got this is like, like 10 different.
So it is.
And you know, I call it his version of, you know, I call it help.
Was it a Pacific Coast hallway musical too.
And I guess it's coming out soon.
Pussy the musical dot pod showed dot com.
And so he asked me to do a song.
And I said, ah, what the, I'll do one for you.
And this is what we came up with.
It's kind of a boy band sound.
And of course, please recall that I'm not a singer.
Come over here, girl.
There's a part of me that's the kind.
When I'm with the boys out drinking, there's some special.
About you, girl.
If I'm not thinking about all of you.
I'm sure I'm thinking about part of you.
Snatch.
My heart belongs to you.
I love you darling.
I'm here dreaming every day.
To be snatched by your love.
Overwhelming.
Snatch.
I love you.
Even if you're not here with me,
I want to be the one who has this feeling.
Inside of you.
If you're just given a link to me.
Maybe someday, girl, you will see.
Snatch.
My heart belongs to you.
I love you darling, true.
Some guys would probably pay
To be snatched by your love.
Overwhelming.
If I'm chasing you without too much haste,
Please, girl, don't think that it's in better days.
Snatch.
My heart belongs to you.
I love you darling.
I'm here dreaming every day.
Snatch.
I love you darling, true.
I love you darling.
Snatch.
My heart belongs to you.
Oh, I love you, not in truth, the singing that song makes me feel gay, let me be snatched by your love away.
That's right, from pussy the musical.
Snatched.
And that is, of course, the lovely lady Patricia, they're doing background vocals for me.
That's right, it's a family affair.
Find it at pussythemusical.podshow.com.
God knows what it's going to be about.
This is your daily source code episode number 663, where we discuss maybe anything.
And everything, including toilet habits.
Adam is narrows calling from Sydney, Australia.
Night regarding the toilet seat-out toilet seat-down scenario.
I think it's a damn good idea that you're working on the toilet seat-down practice for all members of the family.
Not just the actual seat itself of the holiday.
My wife was reading an article reading a book of the wall back at that junse.
And scarily enough, I recommend a toilet seat-out when they flush in the room.
The junse in the ball, which they would probably be 20, can be slung out knitted by a huff flushing action.
So, leave them, damn good idea.
That's disgusting, dude.
And I have read this before.
So, there's another piece of the protocol, close the lid before you flush.
Which, of course, is exactly how my iPhone got fucked up in the first place.
Hey, how about that, huh?
Did a whole trip...
Was in the United States for two weeks?
Did not visit the Apple Store?
Did not pass go?
Did not buy in a new iPhone?
Yeah, I think I'm kind of waiting for the iPod Touch.
But, of course, I re-invigorated my use of the Nokia N800.
And I got to tell you, I've been enjoying it again.
I enjoy the battery life first and foremost.
And now we've got the special channel set up.
There's a new application for the N800.
It's the video center application.
And so, we've set up two channels.
You can read more about it at Nokia.podshow.com.
And we've got some pretty cool, pretty big plans.
Also, if you have an N95, there's also a special feed for you there.
I've got a call schedule with Luke the Candy Man later on this week.
I think we're, we've got some...
It looks like we're finally getting some traction here between our two companies.
And one day, Nokia might actually be a big company.
You know, they might have to acquire them.
Hi Adam, it's Angie P.
I saw you on cranky geeks the other day at the live feed.
And, gosh, you are such a charming devil.
Oh, darling.
Couldn't take my eyes away from you, baby.
You did a good job.
Oh, man, I'm so behind on everything.
I know I haven't talked to you in forever.
And I feel so bad.
So this was like a really great excuse to give you a buzz.
And then what?
Was that it?
That's not possible.
What happened?
Oh, crap.
Oh, hold on a second.
Let me go back to my Gmail.
Now, this sometimes happens if you...
If you get an attachment through Gmail and then you...
Where's cranky geeks audio comment here it is.
And if you...
If you say save it instead of playing it first and something happens with your network connection,
I get how it's told on people.
You know, I don't mind listening to Angie again to you.
Other day, the live feed and...
Gosh, you are such a charming devil.
Hmm.
Couldn't take my eyes away from you, baby.
Oh, baby.
Oh, man.
I'm so behind on everything.
I know I haven't talked to you in forever.
And I feel so bad.
So this was like a really great excuse to give you a buzz.
I'm actually...
I've been going insane because getting ready to put out Los Balls third CD.
And it looks like I got everything together.
And we're on track to have some advanced copies at the new media expo.
In Ontario, later this month.
Yeah.
And I was thinking, I wish you would make good on your little promise to come and give me a hug.
It would be so awesome.
Oh, boy.
You know, me and the other girls are going to be there at the awards ceremony to pick up our...
You know, podcast award with who my first.
And if you saw awesome to see you there.
And we're actually trying to get together like a little meat and greet afterwards.
So we can meet the fans and everybody right after the award ceremony.
So I'll let you know if we get that together.
And it will be awesome if you can make an appearance.
Anyways.
Hope and see you later this month.
Bye, baby.
Oh, baby.
Yeah, so here's what's going on.
I have to be in Chicago on September, I think, 26th.
Now, it would be reasonably easy, I think, to hop from Chicago to Ontario, California
for the 27th.
At least the 27th.
I don't know if I can do the 28th.
It's 27th to 28th is PME, right?
And I really want to go because I want that hug.
That's what I want.
You and the girl is going to be there and we could have such a good time.
And then I have to fly back like a crazy MF bad out of hell.
Excuse me.
Because we have the digital musical awards happening October 2nd in London at the roundhouse.
And it's a funky show.
You know, British telecom are part and over here sponsors the show.
And so we set up a whole party, party palace basically downstairs.
And we got the free open bar.
So guess where all the bands in the artists are hanging out after they pick up their awards.
Uh-huh.
Near the bar.
You know it.
That's good.
It's going to be cool.
We got all of our UK talent.
We'll be representing, I think.
And that'll go County from Textra is in town anyway.
So she's extending her stay to do a couple things.
And this will be in a way kind of a, I guess a soft launch of the plus TV,
which if you haven't seen it, check out the plus tv.com.
This is, this is a project that we've been working on for quite a while.
It's essentially, it's a, it's a video channel of, of crazy shit.
The whole idea is, what if, if MTV hadn't gone to long-form programming?
What if it had stayed with music videos and crazy shit?
And that's basically what we're trying to implement.
The plus tv.com.
And so we'll be live from the digital musical awards on October 2nd,
with live updates coming directly from the red carpet,
from behind the, you know, backstage, essentially behind the scenes,
and at our open bar extravaganza.
So it should be fun.
So it is very possible that we can connect for that hug, my dear.
Fantastic.
With Adam Curry.
Adam, are you ready to be stumped?
Mr. Friday.
Use the makeup on Mondays.
With young problem.
Hey, Adam, this is hit this number 87.
And again, we're going to start right away.
So here we go with the drone.
No one.
That's, uh, I'm, I'm going to guess, uh, you got me hanging it loose ends hanging on a string.
I think something like that.
And this is number two.
All right, y'all, you got me stumped on that one, buddy.
I have no idea what that is.
And the final one is number three.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, it's on the tip of my tongue.
Oh, I can't remember.
Oh, y'all, you're killing me.
And times up.
And these are the answers.
This is from 1981.
Y'all, bro.
People.
And don't stop the music.
Oh, y'all.
You're ready.
Watch all you've got me messed up.
With the beat.
I'm always mad aside.
I'll keep stopping.
Yes, really watch that.
Oh, don't stop the music.
It's answer number one.
Oh, is this one?
And this is answer number two.
The hell is this?
Oh, the pleasure prince.
Oh, man.
From 1987, it's Gena Jackson.
Oh, suck.
I can't believe.
Did you get it at home?
No.
Did you get your budget in your ears?
The pleasure prince of all has a number two.
And this is also from 1987.
Number three.
Get down on it.
Oh, so nice.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no.
Got me.
Just do it to me.
And Spania and call me as answer number three.
And that concludes this week's hit test.
And it's number 78.
Nice.
Nobody.
Well, it's about it for this week.
Thanks for playing Adam.
Yeah, the mall.
No.
I had none of them.
Very ready, and answers and of course the iTunes links can be found at this dot
bar'sshell.com.
So thanks again until next week.
Take care.
Bye-bye.
To test that gmail.com
hwnpul.com
and p-o-l-g-t- the-o
It's such a wall of sound.
You know, when Phil Spector goes to jail,
we're not pretty sure he will.
beyond you can slip right in with a new wall of sound.
That's for sure.
I didn't get a single one right.
Slow moving on a Monday here in the manner.
Bad times.
Right, so we implemented a few new things.
This past week, it was good to hook up with all the
geekyzoids in the back, all the engineers.
Oh, we got some great new cheddar functionality coming for the
channel editor.
You'll be able to get channels now and put channels into channels.
That's all on the way.
Dutches doing that for us.
Andrew and Paulina have been working on the new search, which is now live.
It's not perfect yet, but they called in.
And you remember, well, of course, we know Andrew Grummit.
And then you have Paulina who is just about the sexiest voice.
And she's going to tell us, it's too bad Andrew is talking.
And it just close your eyes and envision Andrew in his jammies.
Paulina in her 90, given you an update about Pacho search.
Hey, Adam, it's Andrew.
And joining me is Paulina.
Hello, we're just checking in from HQ to give you an update on a new
feature that went live Monday evening, actually, but drum roll.
It is it's search.
So we've we've updated the site.
Yes, yes, we are.
We have updated the search both actually the back and front ends of the search.
It's a brand new platform.
And it's it's amazing.
It's well, it will be.
It's got the the really neat thing is that it it transcribes
all the podcasts and figures out the language for you.
So let's say that you're, you know, lying around at home.
Having a glass of scotch.
That happens regularly.
Who's doing a podcast on gay porn talk?
Right.
Oh my god, there's one in Africa.
Gay porn talk.
Yes, you'll see that there's this, you know, when you search on shows,
there's this whole refined by category column on the left.
And the, so the language is just one of many sections.
And the language is actually surfaced at the bottom.
But you can also refine your searches by categories or tags or rating,
which is in the form.
Yeah, it's funny.
I got a couple emails from people saying that that they tried the new search.
But for some reason, there's a banner on the right hand side that pushes
all the search results to the bottom or something.
If you have having problems with that, let me know.
I'm still trying to figure out what's going on.
I'm not seeing that here.
But it is pretty cool that, you know, we've kind of got the basics now covered.
Where we're also doing a search based upon the transcript of the individual show.
Yeah, format video or audio.
And the ratings is it's actually just kind of a rebranded iTunes explicit tag
that would be more familiar to your, I guess, average TV audience.
Um, what are we calling them?
We're friendly.
That left hand now.
We had a name for it.
Cluster.
Ah, yes.
Right.
So, so those things are actually populated by the larger, you know, you cluster me.
10 or 15,000 results.
And, um, and that those lists on the left are actually sort of, you know,
if you want to subdivide your results, those lists are categorized by the larger are
calculated from the larger results set.
And we have another view, um, we have the list view, which just gives you a quick hit.
Yeah, that's really nice.
Now you have different views list view.
You're going to see a lot of this come back in the new interface when we launch
that end of November, uh, beginning of December.
Oh, we have so much cool shit to show you.
Also, the episode matching is very cool.
Actually, that's really powerful.
I think.
Yeah, so let's go into those one at a time for a second.
In reverse order.
So if you're the default view in our, in our search results is, um, what we call the detail view.
And so for each row, you see some album art and a list of categories and a lot of descriptive information.
Nice big fat rows for each search result.
And, um, we, uh, we're actually doing something kind of interesting.
We're searching not just the shows, but the episodes also.
The UI around this is little rough.
Some people may not immediately grok to it.
Um, but in any case, if you, if you do a search on a word,
and the result doesn't contain that word in the show title, just direct your eyes over to the right.
And you'll see a section called Episode Matches.
And it may be that, uh, the match for your term actually is over in one of the episodes.
So that's pretty cool.
Um, what was the other one, Paulina?
Uh, I think so, uh, the list view is the other one.
It's not you, uh, yeah, tell me how to get there and what's going on in there.
So there's an icon on your right right below the page and that you can just, and it's,
a little spew. And basically, it just, it gives you all the shows,
and none of the fluff.
Get right to the shows that all the shows.
No, no, no, no, no, no more on the page.
I think something like 25, a little bit of info.
Something like 25 hits per page instead of 10.
Yes, no, 25, right?
I think if you hover over those little icons at the upper end.
To the tip, next to search view, it actually has a little tool tip.
Mm-hmm.
Tell you, you know, what our names for these things are.
And so we're still refining it.
Currently, it's only, you can only search shows with this new engine.
But very soon, you'll be able to search our entire catalog.
Yeah, so this is just the first, you have some baby steps.
Let's just show us first, right?
Pretty exciting stuff.
We have coming down the line.
So we wanted to thank everybody for checking this out and give a couple of shout outs to our team.
Yeah, we have a Devon, Jeff, Michael, Tom, Jacquesite,
Vaishali, Shrikant, and our contact over at the search engine company calm.
So, all right.
Thank you for everyone's attention.
I hope everybody enjoys it.
We'll be listening for feedback.
And I think that's it for now.
All right.
Good night.
Mm-hmm.
You know, these guys recorded this on cast blaster.
And that'll leave a temp file if something goes wrong.
So, we're going to find a little outtake from Paulina, listen to this.
Oh, wait a minute.
A second.
I got to load it up like this here.
This isn't outtake from that recording.
Ah.
Beautiful.
Andrew and his jammy's Paulina in her 90.
Ah, yes.
It's the gang from HQ.
What a bummer now.
The gang at the office.
But a bum just saying hello.
But a bum to the gang from HQ.
But a bum to the gang.
And I'd show.
Jesus.
With me.
Come on.
Hi, Adam.
It's Matt from Games Resil.
On this week's show, we're reviewing Tigerwood's PGA208 on the Xbox 360.
We jump out of an hour plane with a new Medal of Honor game.
We also go behind the scenes with a team at LucasArts.
So, look at their brand new game Star Wars, The Force, and Least.
And you can win copies of Alien Syndrome for the PSP.
Check it out.
Gamesweasel.com.
Hey, Adam.
It's Jay Mac from TheHootHeight.com show.
I'm hoping this gets to you before the recording of Who Our Friday begins.
Oops.
I just want to drop a message with you and let you know that we actually were selected
is one of the best underground hip-hop sites by VH1 hip-hop honors,
which is a huge thing for us.
And they're actually, they got us up against four other websites.
And people can go and actually vote on what the best underground hip-hop site is.
We don't know if we win anything just to say that we won for the VH1 hip-hop honors.
It would be just a huge, huge deal and a really good look for podcasting as a whole
because we are the only podcasting site up there at any of the categories being voted on.
So, if you could, I'd really appreciate it if the listeners who are going to help us
reach that number one spot.
Go to www.hoodide.com and there's a graphic on the front page on the right side
that says VH1 hip-hop honors.
Just click that graphic.
It's two clicks, no registering or anything like that.
Two quick clicks to vote for us.
We'd really, really appreciate it.
It'd be huge for us.
We'd be huge for podcasting.
Thanks so much for your time and talk to you soon.
Yeah, and on a problem, do.
Happy to comply.
I love that show,hoodide.com.
It's been around for a long time too, a couple of years, fantastic.
So, let's see.
We got lots of stuff happening here in the UK.
This week is going to be very busy.
Although I've tried to work in some morning times, so I'll be able to do some shows.
Thursday probably will be messed up.
Friday, not sure, may have to go to Germany.
You know, that's the way it goes.
As I said, up until the end of this year, it's going to be nuts completely, completely out of control.
Ron's coming.
Wednesday morning, we got some meetings at BT.
It's just going to be crazy.
And then, so Patricia and I have, so I got a meeting.
Today at the office, Patricia is going to come with me because we have some kind of social
function tonight.
We're going to.
So busy, busy, busy, busy, busy, but enjoying it.
Hey, Adam.
It's Jimmy Lee from many, ready to do that.
Just listening to Delhi, source code, six, six, two.
The young folks, dude, I heard it on clear channel station here in the US just a few days ago.
That's just totally amazing.
I mean, the pod show network.
I think has much more impact in reach.
And I hear you're coming up on the DSC666.
Yeah.
Can we expect to hear from you?
Or just another test test.
Test type show.
You wore the evil spirits off.
Anyway, take care of Adam.
Catch you later.
Yeah.
People haven't been standing me stuff for 666.
Feel free to send more because I'll gladly roll it all out.
Lots of deals above and loose it for stuff.
A lot of fun though.
So send that on in.
Yeah, man.
It's working.
This pod safe music network.
And by the way, it's the pod safe, not pod show music network, pod safe music network.
A comic strip blogger continues to call bullshit on that.
So it's not independent.
Fuck you, comic strip blogger.
And send it a comment.
Will you?
Because your jingles get an old crusty and old.
So along those lines, this is from John from photo walkthrough.com.
He said, give these guys a show, a showing on the DSC.
He asked the bar.
If you believe it, say it loud.
Ask the bond, say it loud, they perform live at Pod Camp UK.
Apparently a great show, which of course I missed as well.
Life just gets in the way of all the fun stuff doesn't it?
Alright, so I gotta get dressed, go to the LG Zero Bathroom and off to the office.
I'll leave back tomorrow, all things considered, all things going the way they should.
DailySourceCode.com is where you can find the show notes for today's episode.
Links to everything that was discussed or played.
And of course I'd love to hear from you, Adam at podshow.com.
I'll get to your email eventually.
I got some catchin' up to do, hey, talk to you tomorrow, bye.
Another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear.