This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your fruit-whip log from GoDaddy.
Thank you, Lord Nine.
You're a little bit of truck atomic at your years old.
This isn't Jack Rabbit. We're headed on down to DSC 595.
You're ready, boys. It's football Friday. We got ourselves a con board.
$60 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
Do the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
$30 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
It's twin' tight and I thought I had a football Friday match in my music.
Let's go home.
$30 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
It got me so long, my good time.
It's better like a silver plane.
It's time and I've been here long.
I've been here for so many days.
She's got it.
Yeah baby, she's got it.
$30 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
$40 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh
oh
You're strong, you're strong, you're strong
You're strong, you're strong
Grandlatic smoke and mirrors I gotta tell you there's nothing like a big
barrel of over-modulated sound on a Friday that makes me feel better than anything.
Of course it's almost Monday now in Australia. I'm so sorry I'm late bringing you today's
a maximum music football Friday episode. Everything went wrong today. I thought I was
going to be ready to record the show at 9 o'clock. The electrician shows up at 9
the housekeepers here. I got to get to the city because I had a very important meeting
comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip yeah that's right that's
because I had a meeting with comic strip blogger at the UK crash pad at the
shortage office in London. I must say a meeting like I've had no other meetings.
We sound for about three hours. Hey I let me tell you something right off the
comic strip blogger is not a bad looking guy. He even showed me in fact he showed me quite
proudly. He showed me his driver's license and he said look this was me without
all the weight and he's not a bad looking guy. I was there with Lydia and with the
carry in the office and man it was so funny because exactly the way he is on the
show that's the way he is in person you know. He even had a PowerPoint presentation
which is so awesome. I should actually ask him if I can publish that because it is a
true work of art. He said some really smart things about what Pod Show should and shouldn't
be doing in mobile and in mobility. I think was his word and you know basically like we're
lazy. We're insufficient. No good. The presentation had it like beautiful. It was
beautifully put together like fuck you Adam Curry. It was just I was completely blown away by it.
And even though I don't know if we can and you know philosophically we agree and we disagree on
some things. He interviewed me for a long time and I'm sure he's going to put that up at
comic strip blog.com but boy oh boy did it food bar the rest of my day because I didn't get back
until let's see almost seven yeah the trainer arrived at 705 so yeah I got to feed the animals
and Christina's like off to some gig and yeah oh man the perils of a parent alone I tell you.
But I hope you saw Curry dot com you saw the lady Patricia's spectacular performance last night
on one of the top talk shows in the Netherlands. Of course you couldn't understand any of what she
was saying anything that she was saying but just look at that entrance man. Just look at how she
she came on stage it was fabulous so can't wait to go Sunday to see the show dancing with the stars
in the Netherlands. Hey a lot of emails been coming in throughout the week now that we're no longer
a simul podcasting on serious sidelight radio. A lot of folks want to know what's going on
with our very own satellite repairman PW Fenton and well you know I figured I could tell you
but then again maybe just pose the question directly to the man that would be uh much easier perhaps
Peter. I hope you can hear me okay this is Peter. I know you're getting lots of questions about
what happened to me you know now that I open clothes the satellite window anymore. I know some
people think I've been fired but I just want your listeners to know that you and Ron have been
very gracious to give me the chance to stay employed. As you know I've taken over the pledge to
T-shirts shop and I think I'm getting the hang of it. I could put out several hundred T-shirts
today and when my left hand heals I'll probably wait a second I got to start this on the back.
Uh yeah when when my left hand heals I can I can take this bandage off and I'll be able to
make a few thousand shirts a day so it's not as glamorous as the satellite was but it's worked
and I appreciate you and Ron keeping me on. Have a good time with the charge. Oh and for the
time being you know what with the hand and all I've had to switch to scrunching.
But it's gonna be just fine. It's gonna be just like it's a meeting maybe what you got to do
I want to be just like you. I want to be taking the truth. 10 down the walls and something
Yeah, I'm digging you. I'm digging you. I'm digging you. I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you
I'm digging you, I'm digging you knew, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, not digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you yes, I'm digging you, I'm digging, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging, I, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging, I'm digging you, I'm digging, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm digging you, I'm
You know how I talk about the soundtrack to our live. This is a pre-mo example. How in years from now, you'll hear this song. You think, oh, yeah. I remember that was when all the dig users played the song.
Oh, yeah. I remember that was when all the dig users put that illegal crack code up on dig.com and then Jeff Smith made a song about it.
And then Kelly Lewis did a video about it. Oh, yes. In that nice.
We're building our own soundtrack to our own lives right here before you're very eyes happening on a football Friday with maximum music and that's some crappy promos.
Let's take the mid-a-tarsal. I'll go with the cervical.
I'll take the mandible. I'll take the scapula. I'm going to say B, New York Stock Exchange. I think that was Paul Young.
Let's take the fibula. Oh, I'm going to go for the pelvis like Elvis.
I'm going to say B, 25.
Check out what happens when Natalie Delcante and share from rock and roll TV come to Johnny Todd's house.
I think they're nasty. I'm going to say gonorrhea.
You're playing with it the long got thought you're not coming.
You're out there. I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out.
You're out there. Please don't bang back yet.
Do see John Joe.
Todd made a quick update job, baby.
Do see Todd.
Do see Todd. Do see Todd. Do see Todd. Here for you.
Yo. What's up, Adam?
Do you see Todd? The official musicologist of the Chacha.
Dude, what a week it's been here at the Deli Source Code.
Oh, my lord, there's been so much going on.
And I got to play something on a full bar Friday that I'm absolutely thoroughly excited to play for you.
I found these guys out on my space a couple weeks ago and I sent them an email and you got to be on the positive music network.
And they said, nah, you know, it didn't work out for us.
We couldn't get a confirmation email. There was all this kind of controversy.
I don't know. I didn't get it all.
But I said, dude, you got to get up on the PMN.
I'll play you on the Deli Source Code. How about that?
And I'm really, really psyched because I think you're going to love this song.
The band is called the brown horn that's out of Ontario, Canada.
And it's kind of like this black crow's meets a cdc kind of sound.
I don't know. I just like it a lot.
Check this out. The song is rooftop sniper by the band.
The brown horn is on a vubar freaking Friday.
Check this out.
She snuck through the alley and dropped the bells and do her good girl.
She rocked a button, blocked us like green, coming off of everything.
She's alive.
Find another.
She moves in for the kill.
To back aim us and walk through.
I see it out, out now.
Oh, it's out, out, out now.
She's a bumpköprice sniper, ignite sniper, fire gun.
She's shocked.
She's sup they're cated into thanks
towards the dark.
A funiless guy.
It's a new era for the tale
To pack my life and all the deal
This is how all night goes
And I'll know about my heart
To get a half-form of needles in the shop
I'll find you out
So I'll have to go through the work
So I'll have to take out a half-form of needles
And I'll know about my heart
To take my life and all the deal
And still I'll know about my heart
Oh yeah, see, that's what I'm talking about.
Surgeersy Todd, music colleges of the Charlie comes through once again with a brown hornet
son of Maximum Music, who are Friday.
Damn.
Ah, there's all kinds of football stuff in the world.
What's up now?
Hey Adam, how's it going?
This is the shit, that's the wrong guy, here we go.
Hi Adam, it's a prolific program in the game from San Francisco, but had two things,
number one, it was due several, the few we discussed the last seven, and because
the pluralized address to you, they savant, but up to you.
Okay, thank you very much.
There's a story on the BBC about a Boeing 737 stuck in a city road Mumbai India, apparently
the driver was driving it to the city at the weekend when the driver got lost and abandoned
the plane.
I'm including a link to a story in my email, take a look at it and if you'd like, say
next show.
Cheers.
Cheers to you prolific program, awesome story, great pictures, it is weird.
His guy just dumped a few dislodges of a Boeing 737 on his flatbed truck right in the
smack in the middle of Mumbai, a prolific program, what would I do without you in the
rest of the savants?
I would be nowhere.
So as with most of what we play here on the Chacha, it's all part safe, of course, Venus
from Shocking Blue, I had to get special permission to play that.
But every Friday, I also want to roll out the first gen high pod, we all have one like it,
it's one of those really thick ones, you could put that many songs on it and you kind
of filled it up with all your favorite tracks, maybe from your Napster days, perhaps
you ripped off all of your CV, ripped off, you ripped all of your CDs, in order to get
all your favorite tracks out of, maybe you just like, some schmucks like me, went over
and you bought all these favorite songs of the iTunes music store and it happens anyway.
You're never gonna, you're gonna archive it, you're gonna keep it on the device, right?
So I've got my first gen high pod right here on the monitor, now what we do is we just
put it on random and hit play and see what comes up.
I gotta tell you, I'm cheating a little bit, because I do have a playlist called Friday,
so let me just see what comes up when I, yeah, oh, yeah, baby, it's got to give you a
smile, doesn't it?
I'm sorry, I just have to break the lawn, play this entire track, it just sounds too good
and reminds me of my youth at the 80s with the cure of Friday, I'm in love.
I don't care if I'm next to you, you say it's great and when I say to you, I don't care
about you, it's private, I'm in love, I'm there, you can't fall apart, you say when
I say break my lawn, all Thursday, doesn't mean you start this Friday, I'm in love,
Saturday, I'm in love, Sunday, I'm always concerned, Friday, I'm in heaven, heaven, heaven,
I don't care if I'm next to you, you say when I say hard to tell, Thursday, I'm never
looking back, it's private, I'm in love, I'm there, you can't fall to me, you say when
I say in bed, I'm thirsty, watch the walls instead, it's private, I'm in love, Saturday,
I'm in love, Sunday, I'm always concerned, Friday, I'm in heaven, heaven, heaven, heaven,
I'm in love, Sunday, I'm in love, Sunday, I'm in love, Sunday, I'm in love, Sunday, I'm in love,
Sunday, I'm in love, Sunday, I'm in love, Sunday, I'm in love, Sunday, I'm in love, Sunday, I'm in love,
Friday, I'm in love, Sunday, I'm in love, Sunday, I'm in love, Sunday, I'm in love, Friday,
My daughter still listens to the cure, how awesome of that.
Friday I'm in love, from Adam's first gen I pot, and of course you heard my pilot
earlier I played the wrong feedback.
Now it comes from a guy who we know as a podcast listener.
I think we should bring him into the circle, disavone, and just call him the pissed off podcast listener,
or maybe the angry podcast listeners, specials.
Okay, it's a time for our Savand from our series of The Circle of Savand.
I'm the Sultan of Savand, Savand.
I think I'm going to be able to get at least once a month and episode.
And I hope to be able to talk to a Savand every single day.
And by the way, I want you to know that this format change doesn't mean that I don't
want to make a picture, make a picture by the Sultan of Savand.
Adam, how's it going?
This is the Cha Cha listener, podcaster, whatever you want to call me.
Yeah, we'll fuck you for cutting me off last time.
Even though I guess I understand your frustration, you were having with your computer,
while I went on with my sorry-ass comment.
So I guess it's fuck me.
Fuck you.
Whatever.
You know what?
I'm over it.
But hey, listen.
Here's what I wanted to ask you.
Mr. Potter, father of the podis fear.
Oh great, Sultan of the Savand.
Should we worry about the ruling by the CRB?
I mean, thanks for having Brian longest, on episode 592,
explaining the statutory license for streaming web radio.
But out of that Savand segment, I understood that all music, not just streaming,
is threatened by this ruling.
Is that so?
If it is, then perhaps we should make a calling to all podcasts listeners and podcasts
to unite again on a boom rush to charts.
Yeah, I know.
You don't want to use podcasts.
He knows the medium for social movement.
Come on.
After all you've done for music and podcasts, which, I mean, I thank you.
I never mind talking to you, Dan.
But I thank you just like Lisa from Orlando on episode 594.
I appreciate all you've done with podcasts in general.
So shouldn't we stand up and be heard once again?
Shouldn't we stand together, support HR-2060?
You know, the Internet Radio Collective Act introduced by two representatives,
the House of Congress?
Shouldn't we read up on Savandetradio.org and help save Internet radio?
You tell us, oh, great one.
What should we do?
Yeah, well, thanks for listening, fucker.
And yes, bolder.
Actually, double-folder to be precise.
Hey, man, let's say, listen to me now.
All right.
You clearly didn't listen to the advice.
I got two lawyers on the show for you.
You didn't listen to what they had to say.
It was very clear that you can give anyone a special license or special permission.
And the only thing that would have to come into play is actually obtaining that piece,
which is not that hard because you can just make it an opt-in when you sign up.
Like, oh, gee, what a where does that happen?
Oh, the pod save music network.
Now that bill is very fine.
All that bill does is reduces the price.
And it proposes new pricing.
And that's nothing to do with the statutory license.
We're way behind the eight ball on that.
That was put in place with the first time the copyright royalty board came around.
No, no, no.
And by the way, I love using pod casting for social movement.
I never said that I didn't want to do that.
I may not want to do it through my show in particular,
but it's a fantastic mechanism.
And by the way, who's doing a really good job at that,
please point me to shows that are really making a difference
through political movements.
It's Foo Barman, my brain's hurt.
And I can't think about that.
Hey, hey, hey!
Yeah, I love the sing along.
My life of ways to win.
And a man in blue, her name.
And a man in blue, well they're good.
So I got a job for you.
You want the greatest combat man, won't you come to play?
I can't get a focus now, there's no one else in the play
He wants a job, man, and it's a prayer
But then his number came up, and he was gone with his breath
He's in the only now, I'm going round the lead
He's a boozy, who could give a boy company beat
I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I
I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do,, I do, I do,, I do I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do I do, I do, I do, I go, I do, much
Okay guys, grab your gal and hit the floor because he's that big human waiting to swim too
Along the bedding with the beautiful eyes, I want to be with my client's eyes
I just found a baby once saying to me, yeah, hope it's down to baby
I want to ring you for me, yeah, hope it's down to baby, I want to ring you for me
I want to do already, baby, what am I gonna do?
I'm gonna do the movie, yeah, hope it's down to baby
I want to ring you, hope it's down to baby
I want to ring you for me, yeah, hope it's down to baby
But it's all I got, it's all for you
I got, I got, I got, I got
Bitch, you know, man, you're so kind
You know, man, you're so kind
You're so kind, you know, man
You're so kind
I got, I got, I got, I got, I got,
Bitch, you know, man, you're so kind
You know, man, you're so kind
Some place where you don't like
You're gonna cry until I've never loved, so I'm gonna try to move a true bond to the truth of me all.
Now the lady P and the star sisters.
Are you able to see that performed live on Dancing With The Stars?
Sunday evening, I think it's like a 8 o'clock on RTL4 if you happen to live in the Netherlands.
I'm sure it'll be on YouTube within a few hours.
It was so cool yesterday I knew that Patricia had done this talk show and I couldn't see it.
Because we don't receive the station over here and one of her super fan.
I think super fan Rick had put the interview up in two parts on YouTube, fantastic.
I love it when YouTube works by ripping off content in my favor.
That's when I really love that stuff.
I had MTA for a few days ago.
You were just rock man.
Just put my way back to Brussels.
It's 18 evening, just got out of a traffic jam.
And catching up on your shows because it did some traveling.
And what do I hear?
Made our love.
Man, that is good stuff.
I think I even had it probably get a ticket in the middle.
But luckily in Belgium we just paid him to get it over with.
But it was well worth it.
Thanks man.
And keep up the good work.
I love the shows with the salon.
Bye.
Thank you buddy.
Yep.
We'll have more savants.
The upcoming week.
If you've got any suggestions or recommendations, add them at poncho.com.
I'd love to hear from you.
That would be no good is just the food bar request line
Well, this is big pop of pilgrim embossed and and I like to put a request out of my little girlfriend and San Francisco Trinity
Hey Trinity me in the boy when we've been thinking about you all the time and we don't hear from you
I know your dad has got you locked up downstairs in the geerauch and
But you know your radio might be working so I'm gonna put this request out for you on food bar
It's brother love lost weekend. Just think of you girl. Bye
Yeah
Tell me that you love me
Wow
Time flight my way
You
I'm so scared that a man is real, but I can't face my soul at all
And I was my brother, I lost my lover, the friend I'll see, I'm still in love
You can lie to yourself, and you can waste away, you can die alone
I'm just a one thing that's here, I'm almost lost, I'm lying right
I love to fight, don't listen to me about it, cause I'm always right
I'm a stubborn man, I'll push you down, yeah
I'm a man, I'm so scared that a man is real, but I can't face my soul at all
And I can't face my soul at all
And I was my brother, I lost my lover, the friend I'll see, I'm still in love
You can lie to yourself, and you can die alone
I'm a stubborn man, I'm a stubborn man, I'm so scared that a man is real
I'm so scared that a man is real
Tell me how they're good things, cause I'm hiding behind you
Tell your brother, do you?
Like a child from the world
I'm so scared
Than a man that has been
And I can't face my sin that I'm
I miss my love there
Than a love that has been
Than a friend that has been
And I can't face my sin that I'm
I miss my love there
Than a man that has been
Than a friend that has been
And I can't face my sin that I'm
I miss my love there
By special request from Doug Pilgrim
We all know who he is
For his lovely doll and Trinity
Yep
Yeah, we got to get the registration
I'll sort it out now
This is what I miss
I was brought a love with lost weekend
On a maximum music football
Friday edition of the daily source code episode
Number five, nine or five
And let me see
What did I have in anything I wanted to tell you about today
Oh yeah, so this is good
Sinclair Santas to me
The seventh annual master beta thaw
And it's coming to San Francisco
That'll be on May the 26th
The Center for Section Culture
The only publicly available non-profit sex
Education Center in the United States
Is proud to announce the seventh annual master beta thaw
Or is it master beta thaw
Master beta thaw
Let's just just say it that way, okay
Because then people don't quite catch it right away
Saturday, May 20th Saturday, Saturday, May 26th
13,000
Quivering
Nevermind
Yeah, it's almost like a
What do they call it?
Like a walkathon
A lot more fun and a lot more exhausting
Through individual sponsorships
Participants generate revenue in this live group event
For every minute they masturbate
Or for each orgasm claimed
And they raise money for a good cause, obviously
Well, that's just nasty
What do I get there today?
It's Friday
I have a spinal fund
Well winding it down, I got to tell you
And I know I've talked about this before
And I've said it before, but I don't think you can say it enough
Since I've been with my wife for 20 years now
It's one thing to be in San Francisco for a week
And to miss her
And to not have her around
Really have her to talk to
I have to admit that's what we enjoy doing most
It's talking and laughing and having a fun
But when she is off
And of course I want her to do all of
Anything she wants to do
It's all her creative
Juices that are flowing
And she's a good pointer life to be doing something cool
Of course she's been away for a week
That was really bad, you know, because I got teenager
I got the cats, I got the dog
And then as I said, you know, it's like
All the stuff that just kind of happens around me
That I have to admit I take for granted, you know, even food
The simple essentials in life
So, you know, why don't you send your significant
Other, your partner, your boyfriend, girlfriend, husband, wife
Whatever, send him away for a week
Send him away, let them do something entirely
That they love to do
Having a call only once a day
I'm just trying to get the experiment the same as ours
And then you will see how much you appreciate what they do
It's all those things you just completely forget about
So let's all think about our significant others
Shall we?
Because you know when you're going to the weekend with a smile
It's just the best medicine
Okay, why don't we just metal the mood a little bit
So we can float happily into our Saturdays and Sundays
With Stephanie Hardger, the very thought of you
It's just the fight of you
And I before get to do
And those old and narrow things
That anyone ought to do
I'm living in a kind of daydream
I'm happy as a queen
And foolish
Though it may seem
To me that's everything
The mirror I do of you
The longing here for you
You'll never know how slow the moments go
Till I'm near to you
I see your face
And every flower
Your eyes and stars above
It's just the thought of you
My love
And I before get to do
Those little ordinary things
That anyone ought to do
I'm living in a kind of daydream
I'm happy as a queen
And foolish though it may seem
To me that's everything
The mirror I do of you
The longing here for you
You'll never know how slow the moments go
Till I'm near to you
I see your face and every flower
Your eyes and stars above
It's just the thought of you
The very thought of you
My love
All right, go ahead
It's just the thought of you
The very thought of you
My love
Whoever it is
Give them a hug
Give them a sweet
Have a dance around the room for Christ's sake
Enjoy life
And that's it for the Daily Source Code
For this Friday the Fubar Friday
Maximum Music Edition
Every link you could do
Want is in the show notes a daily source code
Comment of course you can email me anytime
Adam at pot show dot com
We'll be talking again on Monday
Take everybody
Just stick it in your ear