Do you really need Mobile One Extended Performance Mode Royal?
Take this simple test.
It's time to buy a grill.
Do you get A, a nice little charcoal number, or B, 100,000 BTU stainless steel unit with
an infrared sear burner?
Okay, that's it.
If you answer B, that means you don't settle for a second best.
And you deserve Mobile One Extended Performance, a fully synthetic mode royal with 15,000
miles worth of guaranteed protection.
That's five times longer than traditional oil change animals.
When it comes to engine protection, don't settle for anything less than Mobile One Extended
Performance.
Delta Sierra Charlie, 662.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, and the next generation radio
content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just taking this out of Korea.
And now, a message from the President of the United States, George W. Bush.
I have adopted the sophisticated terrorist checkfix, and I'm a dangerous dangerous man with
dangerous dangerous weapons.
I want to bring the coal resources in America and force the critical out.
I have a weapon or mass destruction.
I'm a brutal dictator.
Now I'm the evil.
I have a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for
a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time
for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a time for a
What's wrong with you?
So you're hungry?
You're avoiding it because of my dependence onрудrum
I will ignore it because of money
We will sell something less and Dick黨
Dick..
We will sell something less than those withdrawals
Let's go!
Let's!
Oh, wow, I really missed you guys.
How am I peeps doing?
It's kind of an interesting day.
Well, so I'm gonna turn off some of that noise there.
Interesting day in the United States.
We all know why in the world, I would have to say
on the six anniversary of a horrible tragedy
that happened in New York City.
I gotta tell you, my eyes have been very open.
And there's been so many videos.
And I have to admit that I've watched
just about every single 9-11 video
and people talking about all different kinds of aspects
and conspiracy theories, which has almost started
to receive a negative connotation,
which it really shouldn't.
And my mind is just swimming around
with all kinds of thoughts, particularly how I,
now that I know and the world knows how inept
the central intelligence agency really is,
I'm not thinking at all that it's improved.
A lot of the documents that have been
that are published in this book
or have been declassified in 2003, 2005,
30, 40 years worth of documents.
And it's all crap, but they just suck.
And there, anyway, besides that,
I'm seeing a movement, and I think the movement
is loosely called 911 or 911 was an inside job.
I'm seeing people show up in public places
where there's television cameras.
I hear people talking about it.
And I received an email from my good buddy,
a lot of second, we just got a email here.
Here it is.
The official biographer of all things curry media,
Tom Scuding, a clog walk down, down under.
And he sent me a link to two links, actually.
One, which was very interesting.
And yes, I will remember to put these links in the show
notes at dailysourcecode.com, that very similar
to previous to 2001, there were a huge amount of put options
out there in the market, particularly on airlines.
I think Americany United at the time.
And someone or somebody's or some entities
made out like bandits because of put options basically
gamble against a stock or against the market or against anything.
I guess you could really make a put option.
So according to this link at theinteldagely.com,
I will just grab that for you.
By the way, for today, I plan, I'm just going to talk a little
bit of shit, then you guys are going to talk a little bit
because there's plenty of cool comments that came in.
Here we go.
A huge downside purchase of put options
by an unknown investor or conglomerate in Europe
has both investors and NWO, not quite sure what that stands for.
NWO watches a buzz worldwide.
Someone has placed a $4.5 billion bet
that within 30 days, the European stock market
will take at least a 33% nose dive.
Such an event would be 10 to the market crash of 1929.
So there are 60, and this I presume is traceable
on is just fact.
I'm just going to have to take it at face value here.
There are 65,000 pending contracts at $750 in this,
oh, it's betting against the standard and poor index.
This controls six and a half million shares.
So with the put option, you basically,
you wind up paying a fraction of what you could make.
But of course, you stand to lose your entire investment.
The six point five million shares at $750
or $4.875 billion.
The entity or individual offering these sales
can make money only if the market drops 30 to 50%
within 30 days.
If the market does not drop, the entity or individual
involves stands to lose about $1 billion
just for engaging in these contracts.
And I know that's a be true.
On the other hand, if the prediction is correct,
the reward could be over $2 billion.
So does it have a date on this?
I think it's before.
Maybe it says it here.
Anyway, you got to read this article.
But that would be valid.
Here we go.
All right, doesn't say it.
Shit, I thought I read that somewhere.
Maybe it's in the,
that's how one was supposed to the seventh of September.
So anyway, so a cataclysmic or catastrophic event
could clearly cause that.
Of course, this doesn't have to happen in Europe
to make it because this bet was placed in Europe.
The standards in poor could pretty much affect,
will affect markets worldwide.
So that was the first link.
And I did check that out.
And then he sent me a link to another video,
which is a two hour long video.
I watched the whole thing because, of course,
look, Tom is a damn well trusted source for me.
Now let me just get this.
It's from 911Blogger.com.
It's a video by a guy named Richard Gage.
And he is an architect.
And he goes through two hours of methodical
dissection of the collapse of World Trade Center tower
seven and one and two.
And I would have to say, has presented,
because he doesn't present a conspiracy theory,
he presents architectural evidence
that this was a controlled demolition.
And of course, he backs that up with,
and it's great because it's power point, basically.
But he has all kinds of video and things from new sources
and what people were saying.
And it's very, very convincing that these towers were brought down
at least by controlled demolition.
And not by aircraft or jet fuel.
I'll just say there's one thing that he doesn't mention.
He goes through all the temperatures
and what jet fuel burns out, et cetera.
And the steel, what kind of temperatures
the steel needs to melt and all kinds of inconsistencies
and reports, particularly by FEMA.
Now, there's a surprise.
I don't know, I think FEMA are the black box guys.
That's probably what they suck so bad at Katrina.
It help in people because they're too busy
being the new CIA.
Maybe, I don't know.
And I just want to remind you,
because he doesn't mention this, this Richard Gage dude
that jet fuel, it sounds really explosive
and really massive, right?
But it's diesel, basically.
It has the same very similar properties to diesel oil.
And I'll tell you how I know that
because I have actually, this is some while ago,
I have had an occasion where we had a choice
to make in the helicopter.
And this was in the turbine helicopter,
so jet engine, the choice was land
and have someone come out with a truck to help us refuel.
Or we could keep trying to make the airport
and risk severe consequences.
Or we could land near a regular gas station
and fill it up with diesel oil, which we did.
And yeah, it smokes a little bit more than normal,
but it certainly did work.
So I just want to add that.
You should check this video out as well,
of course, I'll link in the show notes.
And it will give you a different perspective on things.
I guarantee you that you'll be thinking long and hard
about what's going on.
And I mean, can you tell?
I'm in total red pill mode.
It's really a big time red pill.
Thanks, by the way, to Vadim Saliva,
who sent me the artwork for today's show.
It's like an old school 1910 version of podcasting.
Very cool, Vadim, I appreciate it.
So you'll only see that if you play the show on an iPod
or some kind of program application
or device that can see the album art,
but I think you could kick out of it, it was very, very cool.
Let me say, so Friday, no wait.
Friday, we spoke on Friday, right?
No, Saturday I spent all day preparing my presentation
for the IMedia Conference in San Diego,
which is about an hour and 10 minutes flight from here.
And the idea here is, and this is really,
this is the part of my job.
I hate, I really, really hate selling.
I just hate it.
I hate sucking up to people,
but you gotta do it.
Because we're just not in the position yet
to be fighting people off.
And no one is these days in media quite honestly.
Except Google, but that's a different type of advertising.
So the whole point of this IMedia Conference
is there's a brand there, so brands, they don't pay.
People who are selling pay to get in,
it's very, very typical model.
So we paid for our visitation,
and then of course you get to present,
although they said very specifically, it's funny,
because this is a parallel to the tech world.
No commercial, you're not allowed to, to pimp your company.
Which I was okay with, because I actually,
I had a great time.
And I hope, they did videotape it.
I hope they're gonna put that up on the web
and I hope it kind of looks okay,
because I was having a great time.
And I was playing all kinds of amazing shit
and just freaking them out.
And when I was done,
you know, there were like representatives of big ass brands,
like AT&T and Nissan and Cadillac,
what else was there?
I don't remember.
They were like, I'll jump an up and say,
and cool, and I was playing some of your splendor comments.
But they were getting it, you know, they really were.
It's so easy, you play a splendor comment
where someone's talking about splendor
and they said, you know, when's the last time someone
called you up and said, hey, man, thanks for that banner.
I really enjoyed it.
That pretty much hit home.
So that was good, you know,
but it was two days of schmoozing.
Yeah, stay overnight.
Nice hotel, I'll have to say, bandwidth sucked completely.
So, you know, even thinking of doing a show
was out of the question,
I missed the MTV Awards, right?
And you know, I saw just like the tail end of it.
Of course, it's very clear how that went.
I guess I did get an increase in the rating.
So that's good for him.
But, you know, the whole Britney Spears thing
is like, you know, come on.
That's, it's just below MTV standards, I feel.
The way they set that up and the way they did it,
it just didn't really feel right.
But then again, you know, it's about money.
Most of the media businesses.
And, you know, when they started doing remote control,
that's when the ratings went from 0.3 average.
And, you know, 0.4 was kind of 0.5 rating point.
Was a big deal.
Went to 1.0 and 1.2.
And that was the end of it.
And from there on out, it was just long-form content.
So, more people are watching it.
It's just alienated the core group
and the core demographic.
But on the other hand, you know,
you can get your videos from anywhere these days.
Anywhere, so where's the business, you know?
But it does, I do feel ripped off.
Like I completely understand people who were upset about that.
Oh, dude, by the way, if you don't watch Kat's cast,
which is kat, c-a-s-c-a-s-t Kat's cast.podshow.com,
you should definitely check out the most recent episode.
Now, I know Kat, you know who does this show.
But you've got to see it.
It's, I think it's episode 19.
She's in the South of France, all by herself.
I'm not gonna tell you the whole story.
All by herself.
And she's sitting at a pool with like long blonde hair flowing.
She's got some kind of negligee nighty thing going on there.
You know, the big dark glasses.
And oh, man, it's like, I'm gonna watch a porno.
It's really a lot.
And then she goes into this story,
which is just unbelievable.
About what happened to her in the South of France.
Now, you gotta know, this beautiful woman alone,
by herself, the South of France, known for topless beaches.
And yeah, she got a pretty bad experience.
So I suggest you check it out.
I'll put that episode into the DSC channel
for those of you following along with that.
I wish I had some time to update the DS.
I wish I had time to do lots of stuff.
Man, it's killing me.
It's so busy and check this out.
So I thought it was gonna be here
to the end of the week.
Ron and I are actually gonna fly the red eye tomorrow, Wednesday night.
We're gonna take the red eye to New York for one meeting.
It's an important one.
And then we're gonna fly back for more meetings on Friday,
back to San Francisco.
And then on Saturday, I go back again to London.
I hope I wanna go home.
I wanna be in my girls.
I really do, we're still grieving for Christ's sake.
We had him, it's the Doctoroe here.
She's got so much dirty, full of clothes to catch up on.
I've got like two months, I was an outfall fan at home.
And then I was like, I've got cable.
So I'm just catching up now.
Let's just listen to the last couple of dirty, full of clothes.
And I just want to say, I'm so sorry to hear about your sister's cat.
But rest assured she is in the same of cat heaven
that we're still through what they say.
And it's endless happiness fly.
Anyway, I can't wait to catch up on the rest.
And I just wanted to make a request from
mashuptown.com, which I absolutely love and it's taken me
to see it work while I'm trying that I head around
a whole bunch of new stuff.
But if you can play a razor head ceremony,
I think it will look great.
That is brilliant.
Anyway, speaking.
All right, baby.
I love it with Dr. O'Calls.
And she's got a hot voice.
Yeah, I look for that one.
I looked for a razor fish, whatever you call,
or whatever it was.
And so I wound up, I found that what I opened with Tom Tom
Rio Grande, Rio Grande mashup.
I found that on seekpod.com, which is an awesome sight.
If you're looking for illegal MP3s,
Sierra Echo, Echo, Quebec, Papa Oscar Delta.com.
So you can search for their Tom, oh, two, two Tom.
Sorry, T-O-T-O-M, two Tom.
And the song is apparently called Rio Grande mashup.
So I couldn't find that Dr. O, but I know that Dr. Art
heard your request.
And I'm sure he'll work on that for me over there at mashuptown.com.
Yeah, thanks for the, I know you're a big,
you're a big pussy person.
Oh, man, I gotta tell you, I gotta tell you
about the new pussy musical.
I won't do it yet.
I gotta get approval to talk about it.
Anyway, thank you so much.
And I worked through phase one, I think of part two.
I mean, first of all, it's like when you get a new bike
or you know, something you really wanted
and throughout the day you'll think, oh, what was that?
Oh, yeah, something in my stomach, I feel something,
oh yeah, that's right, I'm really excited.
I got a new gadget, you know, like gadget porn.
It's exactly the opposite.
You'll be walking around and I'll say,
what was, oh, oh, I feel really bad
because my pussy cat's gone.
Anyway, the girls went out and they went to the catch shelter.
I think they have, and I think we have new family members.
I'm not gonna talk about it just yet.
So I wanna make sure, I gotta get the full load down.
I think we have some new family members.
And by the way, in the UK, they don't mess around
with that stuff, excuse me, no sponsor today.
And they don't mess around with it.
So when comes your house to, to, you know,
to scope you out and make sure everything's okay and kosher.
They won't give you a cat before that.
It's like a whole program, which I think is really good,
but I'm sure it's really hard to get homes for cats.
And of course, just to love that you guys are sending in
has really been helpful, particularly when you get
the homeboys calling in.
Adam, it's Chuck from Jersey.
It's just hard about your cats, Cindy,
and very sorry to hear that.
My family and I have a dog that we adopted.
I think it's been nine years ago now.
Since then, he's gone blind and we've had two children
who are now five and two and he's been great.
And we still refer to him as our first kid.
And we had a little scare, a little while,
I've got six months ago and he turned that okay.
But yeah, I mean, pets are part of your family.
And we love them dearly and they love us back unconditionally.
And I'm really sorry for your family right now.
And some people may laugh at the whole idea
of being sad about pets passing,
but they're part of your life and they're irreplaceable.
So again, I'm sorry and hope you guys get over this soon.
Take care.
Man, Chuck, appreciate it, dude.
Hey, women, if you want a real man, go look in Jersey.
That's where all the real men are.
We're tough, we're rough, but we know how to show our emotions.
And I was thinking, you know, we're spinning up a show,
called Spirit and Messenger with us.
Guy called Gordon Smith in the UK.
And he's the real deal.
He really does talk to the dead.
And now I've had a couple of meetings with him
and I've never asked him anything.
But he has told me on numerous occasions
that to help people really ease into believing him.
He can communicate with their pets that have passed away.
And that usually gets people on board within seconds.
I'm thinking I'm going to give him a try on that.
But I'm going to record it.
I think that'll be pretty interesting experiment.
Okay, so as I said, I talked for about 20 minutes there.
So I want you guys to give me some more feedback.
You know, I was looking for a free to call in.
We've got a number in the US.
And we've, of course, we've got a plus four four number in the UK.
Hey, Adam, it's Jerry from anapolis.
And I just wanted to mention something.
You just, I don't know what the SD is.
But most recent one, anyway, you talked about
the resource being where he is.
And I had just recently read an article in the post.
I think it was Washington Post about the resource being.
And he's kind of been doing his own thing for a while.
And he actually, by training, I think,
is a jazz musician.
And he's got a new jazz out milk.
And he used, there was a big ride up about that.
And I don't recall the details.
But I think if I'm guessing it's probably on iTunes at this point,
I think that he's sort of resurfacing.
And I'm always not using a fantastic piano player.
So I'm thrilled to hear that he's actually out and about again.
And so I just wanted to mention that to you.
And you know, how people may be looking up.
Holder.
Red pill.
Yeah, you know, that's a guy who should be on the podcast
of music network for real, you know.
This is very talented.
Had one or two really big hits in a decade ago.
She was a guy's got lots of great songs.
And I'm sure radio doesn't give the fucking time a day.
So we should be all over that.
One song that is really like broken out
was just blowing me away is this Peter Bjorn and John
with young folks.
I know you've heard this song.
It's all over the place.
And of course, in a region that on the podcast music network
is five, I'm concerned that's where I was exposed to it.
If I took you friends that did before, told you I used to be,
would you go along with someone like me?
If you knew my story were forward, had a lot of my history.
Would you go along with someone like me?
Had it before and had my share, it didn't lead me away.
I would go along with someone like you.
If you knew my story were forward, had a lot of my history.
Would you go along with someone like me?
Had it before and had my share, it didn't lead me away.
I would go along with someone like me.
If you knew my story were forward, had a lot of my history.
All right, I've got to figure it out.
I just went through the pot-saved music network.
This is the label Wichita, these guys are awesome.
Let's see, they've got to, where they put up on the network so far, let me see.
Block party, the cribs, Simeon Mobile Disco, Esper's, the Bronx, the drips,
Kempestinos, euros, child, Saul Williams, Peter Bjorn and John, which had just heard
her space, holiday, blood brothers and clap your hands, say, yeah, awesome, it's, uh, I think
yeah, UK label. So what I'd like, you know, now that this is like a hit, I'm hearing
the song everywhere, it's huge. I can't get away from it. I'd like the Poncec music network
to take credit for that. I really would not pod show the pod safe music network and all the
pod casters that have played this song and producers using it, integrating into their
productions, um, which it's odd dudes. If you're listening or uh, Peter or Bjorn or John, you know,
call in, man. Let's, uh, let's do this. I mean, I'll, I'll, I'll get the publishers I'll pay for that.
It'll, uh, we, you know, we can totally get the mainstream media to go, oh, well, it's quite amazing
you know, the store, all the internet, not a really bad bad bad bad. But really, that would be
good for us, trust me, I'd like to do that. Hi, Adam. This is Janice from New York and I'm
calling with two comments. Um, first comment, you mentioned in DSC 660 that it might be a good idea
to have a comment channel on Podger Plus. And I've been meaning to ask you about that since, uh,
about a month ago when I had what I thought was a brilliant idea, which works. Uh, I've been
listening. That was, of course, the brilliant idea was like, I think I need to send Adam
naked pictures. DSC since before the phone line. And so I kind of had it my mind for a long time to be
able to send you a comment in MP3 format without having to attach it to an email. I've recently discovered
audacity, a free program, easy to download and easy to use. Oh, girl, are you reading? Are you reading
your comment? For recording MP3s. And I tried to use it to record a comment, um, which
in here, I'll explain, when you announce the cheddar would enable people to put any type of
file into a channel. I thought I could use the cheddar to paste an MP3 format message. Oh,
I got to tell you something. We have something so incredibly cool.
Oh, crap. I don't want to tell you. If I did, I'm not going to tell you because someone
else is going to fucking do it before we're ready. I don't think what we've ready before
November or December. So, uh, not exactly for that application, but yes, something, uh,
something cool. And then email you the link to the channel. Um, but I wasn't able to actually
paste the MP3 file. I'm not sure why. Maybe it was just my incompetence. No, no, no, no, no, no,
you've got exactly the right idea honey. You've got exactly the right idea stick with it.
Well, I've had it in my mind to ask you whether that's a feasible way to get you DSC comments.
So, those of us who are not pod gestures, but would like to be able to leave you a pre-recorded
comment. I know you like the spontaneity of the phone line. But let me just tell you one thing that
we're doing. Um, I've seen it working internally. Um, you'll be able to, uh, to leave a comment
for each individual show, uh, just by using your built-in microphone or your webcam or whatever you
want. You actually, you can do video, too. So, it's not like this is some incredibly new
fangled thing. Uh, excuse me. No sponsor. This book was purely air. Not paid for.
Um, yeah. So, that's common. So, that will make it a lot easier. Some of us might, you know,
ordinary listeners might want to actually pre-record a comment and we would leave it to you
that way. Anyway, quickly, my, my second comment. Uh, here's a suggestion. Um, for the next time
you feel down in the dumps about the DSA. Create a folder on your computer and save the messages
you've been receiving since DSA 654 about how much your show means to us your listeners.
Um, you know, at least the most meaningful comments. I'm a high school teacher and I keep a
file of notes. Oh, wait a minute. Oh, wait a minute. Yeah, I'm saving this one. That's for sure.
High school teacher. Oh, tell me you have long hair that you wear up in a bun.
And you pull out the bun and just shake it off for you, baby.
To set me over the years about how much they've enjoyed my class and what it's meant to them.
Every once in a while, I need to consult that file to cheer me up and remind me why I do what I do.
So, um, anyway, just a suggestion, maybe you do that already. Um, and, um, in that, uh,
in that vein, um, I wanted to mention that most listeners appreciate the showing us that we always
forgive you when you miss a day or two or three. In fact, before those days are helpful,
we'll only get behind and want to catch up. Um, I'm a listener that listens to every single
episode. And I don't know what that says about me, but every once in a while, when I wonder why I
listen to every episode, you'll play just a great song that I'll just love or say something that
makes you laugh out loud. Um, and that reminds me why. So, anyway, I want to also mention that many
of your jingles have become the soundtrack to our, um, whenever I hear the Friday jingles,
and that also makes me laugh out loud. That's nice. Thanks so much, Adam. Uh, take care.
No, no, no. Thank you. Hold on. I just, I got to get your name again. Hold on.
Yeah. Hi, Adam. This is Janice from New York. Janice, of course. Oh, Janice.
This is why I do it. This is exactly why I do it. It's for that. Thank you so much.
Yeah, now I'm a happy guy. I was just telling my, my buddy, cut you, actually. So, I'm pretty happy
guy. You know, I got people who, uh, who think highly of me. I've got high friends in low places.
Hey, Adam, this is Dave. I may not look like Elvis. I may not talk like Elvis.
And I may not sing like Elvis. I sound exactly like Elvis. This is eating a peanut butter
Nana sandwich. Later. Rock on. Yeah, rock on. We're still looking for a younger sounding Elvis.
Actually, you know, just keep calling in you guys. And you know, we're, we're getting somewhere.
We got a lot of people with, uh, with some talent out there. It's cool.
Hey, Adam, this is Eric, compartment. I just call it about, uh,
Madeline McCain. Uh, yeah. I first heard about the little girls of
Duccia on your show. And in fact, I had her picture in my album art on the show.
Uh, that's one of the reasons I would like listening to you is the, the international
content that I get that I don't get elsewhere. And it preceded it being on meteor networks
and television by a good week and a half. But now, now I see that, uh, there's a hundred
recent DNA match of little Maddie's DNA and the rental car used by the parents. So, uh,
it just reminds me of, uh, John Bony or ANSI and, uh, other sad things. But, um, you got the word
out fast and early and then that, that could help. And it could have been a, uh, deciding
factor. And I just want to thank you for, uh, bringing it out. And, uh, now that we,
no different things are going on, we can recognize that as well. Thanks, Adam. You're doing a great job.
All right. All right. Thank you. Well, it's interesting because, uh, for many weeks now,
I've had information that came from, uh, now I've built up a pretty interesting network of, uh,
of peeps in, uh, in London, particularly through super agent Keith, who I still have to get on
this show, uh, he'll drive you nuts. Um, if you won't be able to understand him,
please, not if you're, unless you're British. And, uh, so through this network, I've, uh,
come to learn many things, but the allegations were so severe about, uh, what happened that I,
I really just didn't feel comfortable talking about it because, you know, I've had people talk
shit about me that wasn't true and it could be very hurtful and certainly wasn't on this level.
But here is the story that I have understood, uh, and you should Google this story,
Madeline McCain. So, uh, briefly, two parents, they're both doctors. I think good general practitioners.
And, uh, they're in Portugal and they're in a hotel hotel until they've got twins and Madeline.
Uh, and I guess Madeline is the eldest. And she was what like, uh, I've got how old, four, five, six,
five, something like that. And, uh, so they're having dinner nearby, like, you know, like,
like 30 second distance, not too far. And they go back, this is the story, and they go back
once the wall and they check on her. And they come back and, uh, she's gone. And, uh, so they can't find her.
And this is now been what? A couple months, something like that. So this has been a huge,
huge story. And, you know, particularly when they, you know, they look at the next door neighbor.
And there's no clues. There's nothing. Um, and now there's DNA evidence that was found in the rental
car that they drove, uh, that they rented 25 days after Madeline went missing because they've actually
stayed in Portugal. What's been interesting about this is they went to the press. They, you know,
they visited with the pope. You know, there's, uh, a David Beckham has started a fund for trying to
find Madeline, you know, huge, huge, huge publicity machine. And I have, you know, and,
that's okay. So please don't take this the wrong way. Um, but you look at them and, you know,
and she's kind of hot. And you, and that, and that did strike me right off the bat. So what I heard
is that they're swingers. And this has been a rumor on the internet for a while, but this is the
way I heard it before I even went looking for a story that they're swingers. And what they do is
when they go swinging, they basically, and they're, remember their doctors, the GPs, since, you know,
this is something that can't get out and they really really has to be quiet. So they're, first
they do it in Portugal, I presume. And that they drug their kids. You know, give them some kind of
sleeping shit so that they go to sleep. And apparently something went wrong and a little girl died.
And so there's this cover up. That's what I heard. And, you know, then all of a sudden I hear that
she's being listed as a suspect. And it's a DNA evidence. I'm like, Holy crap. I mean, like,
holy, holy crap. So it's, uh, it's pretty naughty stuff. Speaking of crap.
I had an, it's off of Zion from the, uh, pissidnow.com. Uh, I didn't, I hadn't, I just running through a lot
of the old podcast because I'm still playing catch up. And I came across the, uh, you're coming
about being toilet trains. Now, you're on halfway there. The next bit you need to be changed
on the subverted toilet training. Basically, uh, the first part has already been trained to,
as you said, um, uh, is even the toilet seat down. But you don't want to make it too easy for
the, uh, the lazy female from our species. Uh, what you want to do is put the toilet,
lid down as well. You can say, I'm still following your orders. The toilet seat is down.
Well, it stops them from backing up like a truck. I'm just going to tell you what,
just pointing down. Um, uh, truck. That's your, uh, he's returning from the subverted. Um,
uh, people are rolling. See you later. All right, I'm, and actually, I, I think I even talked
about that. I, I started doing that. Like, yeah, you know, if you want the toilet seat down,
if you want me sitting on the toilet, that's fine. But you're doing some work, too. And I
have said, look, here's the general rule. Everyone closes the lid. And if you close the lid,
of course, the seat is closed. So that's the rule. Everyone leaves with the lid down. And I do
it even here. I'm all of myself. There's no one watching me. Or are you?
I mean, this is my buddy from New York. And I've been meeting to play a song of his and I saw
that lots of people have been playing the song in the past week or so. So right now,
it feels like the waves are crashing. And the cold winds roar. You've been tossed and
think you've lost your way. You know I've been there, but there's a lighthouse flashing
on that distance shore. And when the going gets rough, if you look hard enough,
it's still shining to show us the way. And if you look for that light,
when you're lost in the darkness of night, you'll find that that's when the slightest
star shines brightest. Look straight ahead, then hold on tight and you'll sail safe and warm
through the middle of a mighty storm. You'll get through it all right, and you don't lose sight of the dream.
Right now, I know what you're thinking. You're wondering how you'll make it through another day.
We've all been there. It kind of feels like you're sinking. And there's no way out,
but when you're strength nearly gone, keep on keeping on. And just know that you'll get their one day.
Cause if you look for that light, when you're lost in the darkness of night,
you'll know that that's when the slightest star shines brightest. Look straight ahead,
then hold on tight and you'll sail safe and warm through the middle of this mighty storm.
You'll get through it all right, and you don't lose sight of the dream.
Like your heart's desire be your guide at all. It's a wild exciting ride
straight through the middle to the other side. And there we look for that light.
When we're lost in the darkness of night, you'll know that that's when the slightest star shines brightest.
Move straight ahead, and hold on tight and you'll sail safe and warm through the middle of this mighty storm.
We'll get through it all right, if we don't lose sight of the dream.
We'll get through it all right, if you don't lose sight of the dream.
I thought it was just perfect for September 11th, 2007. Couldn't go to more New Yorker kind of guy
to do it too. David Epilito, that guitar man from Central Park, you can find him at iLoveTheCompany.
IOTC.podshow.com, I think it's that guitar man.com is another one of his addresses, and please,
you can of course a link in the show notes to the song on the podcast music. Now where you can buy it from the
podcast music now work, and then all of the proceeds go to David. I'm sure you can get it on iTunes,
and please, you know, do that or listen to his show. It's one of the, the few music shows I listened to,
very, very regularly. He does a lot of them, but there's always something cool, and always it's,
he's not quite a new jersey guy, but you know, he got that jersey emotions thing going on, which is cool.
And I'd really like to make him some money, so he needs more listeners, and so either buy a song or
listen to his show or do both, okay? All righty, so I have no idea when we will speak to each other next.
I just don't know what's, what's going to happen because of all the travel.
I'm going to try and work in something somewhere. I promise you. So I hope you enjoyed the past 45
minutes. I surely enjoy you guys being along for the ride whenever you can, and I'll talk to you soon. Bye.
This podcast is brought to you by Ponshow and GoDaddy. The show will give you a special code to get
great discounts at GoDaddy.com. Got something to say? Walk it with your fruit-whip log from GoDaddy.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds and content delivery Ponshow and
lightlight.