Hey Peter, can I ask you a question?
Yes, do you?
Who would you say our calls important?
After 20 minutes of being on hold, I'd have to say now.
Please continue to hold.
Your call is important, do I?
Yeah, it's very correct.
It's very important.
Then we'll hold music.
Unified communications.
Or by Cisco.
Hello, Mr. Kerry.
This is Ed Schwartz with the properties on as association in your building.
Mr. Kerry, I know you only hear once a month.
And so it's easy to get over the smells.
Like the French fries smell in the parking deck.
And the incense emanating from Yacondo.
We can put up with the noises.
All hours of the day, something about as a sizing.
But if you wouldn't mind Mrs. Ebstein, down the hall,
is having some friends over for tea.
And she would like to know if you could remove your laptop
and your router from the hallway.
She's afraid some of her friends might trip over it.
Thank you, Mr. Kerry.
We'll show you understand once you finish with the DSC 532.
You can remove your equipment.
Thank you.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Today is the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
This is Delta Cia Charlie 532.
A podcast of Adam Kerry, the potpimp,
who gives job, money, and condoms to many potpards.
Isn't it carefully?
One day, the May-Begravity's hall too.
This is Delta Cia Charlie 532.
This is Delta Cia Charlie 632.
Next are Delta Cia Charlie 534.
This is Delta Cia Charlie 536.
Let's live on these because I know they'll be back
One eye open in case of attack
If I make it through this, I'll never do it with this again
And let's roll my new nail
And let's bring my nail
And let's bring my new nail
And let's roll my new nail
I think you joined the hotseam music network in June of last year
I think I've played this song but it showed up as a remastered version today
Oh, yesterday, like, oh man, he came back with a vengeance
God, that kicked so much ass
Everybody, how are you doing?
Daily source code episode 532
Coming to you from Northern California, the Curry condo
And I'd like to say right off the bat
Whatever they're growing here in California, it is of excellent quality
Much better than we're getting back home in old blighty
I've had another, well, state a pretty late last night
Because, of course, I've shifted my schedule
I'm staying up, you know, doing the show
Anyway, between 10 and 11 o'clock at night
Getting up a little bit later, the normal, but still around 3 o'clock
The jet lag just come with hits me like a ton of bricks
And, um, at the day, of course, was no different
I actually did wind up staying until, like, I don't know
7 o'clock or something like that
But at the end of the day, I was so punchy
I just had my, my Napster open
And I was playing every single 80 song imaginable
I hooked up some speakers
And people who were in a meeting with me
They could stay, you know, and talk more about whatever it was
Only if they could guess the, you know, like a hit test
If they could guess the, the artist and the song title
Then they could stay and talk some more
It just, I was tired
So it came back tonight and, uh, wow man
American Idol, two hours special
I just got done watching it, so what is it now?
It's about 10, 25
I love that show
I love that show so much
And not, you know, not for the singing
Because I really don't care
Sometimes, like, well, you know, there's someone who can really sing
But it is just the, the emotions that are shown
On that television program are so beautiful
Unfortunately, they're only of one variety
Well, yeah, mostly there
Well, that's not entirely true
But it is either extremely sad or extremely happy
And unlike any other reality type television format
You know, they can do a lot of editing to make their story
Which they obviously do
But, you know, just to see someone
You can't act that, you know, that's real life
And in fact, any actor who can act
Like those people is a damn good actor
Ah, it's just, it's beautiful to watch that
And, you know, I've been thinking about reality shows a lot
Because they've become so commonplace
And, you know, there's so many different distinctions
Really between, for instance, American chopper
Tuddle, Paul Tuddle, senior, Paul Tuddle, junior
That's one type of reality show
Big brother is a whole different type of reality show
American idol is yet another type
But, but the, the point is
The reality part of the show is there
The things that are slipping through
The things that we're seeing
Are these intense moments of emotion
One way or the other, some type of emotion
That we share because we understand exactly what that emotion is like
We have been there
Is that identification with ourselves that makes it so incredibly addictive
And yet you hated it at the same time
Because, of course, you hate a lot of the behavior that you're seeing
Because you recognize that in yourself
And there's a lot of deep shit going on here
So, this is a common point
Because it's a very deep, deep, deep, deep, deep, deep
That's a good point
I don't even know what's really true
It's a very strong point
Yeah, good on what it is
It's a very good situation
So, it's a very good situation
Whenever a person says
If anyone wants to stay healthy, you need to understand
A lot of people, people else are excited
I've heard that the people on stage will enjoy it
Sometimes you don't have a consensus
We can speak softly
And outside there, the people are not afraid
What news papers are you eating, your fish and chips out of? Come on. They've canceled
her perfume line. She's had to go on every single show and do every newspaper interview
she possibly could to pour it on to apologize. You know, she's totally being scapegoated
here. Because that's what's going on. I think that truly is what's happening. People are
recognizing a lot of what they're seeing in themselves and projecting that on to Jade Goodie.
And again, it's not just the UK. It happens everywhere. It happens in every culture. I think
we need to get over ourselves a little bit. Just a teeny bit. I come out. We can make fun of people's
accents. You know, and bullying it happens all the time. It's what humans do. Don't forget. You're
watching a reality show. Key word, root, real reality. This is the real life. And you know,
let's not go blame, uh, endable and channel four. Take a look at it. You know, don't forget. This is
not completely baked up entertainment. There is something real stuff going on here, which is
really, really human. Let's just not forget that. It's important. Study it. Learn. I find it, you know,
this. I love it. I'm a student of this shit. I love it so much. I'm jazzed in general today because
I've got so many responses to the free Trinity idea. We're going to get to that in a little bit.
I mean, just take the sky as anything else. I think she already did that. I think that,
now, first of all, you're probably right that she lost big brother. I was wrong. It doesn't matter.
If she comes out and people still know her several years later, she won big brother somehow.
She won something. I think people go into to win fame in general. But I think the
Indian trip, I think, I think that just added insult to injury because she had done that
previously. I think that's an old trip that you're talking to.
I'm so much tougher. I'm so random, I'll also be able to be racist because I can't
another girl on this trip so much together. I think it's kind of simple. I could be
correct. Problems, I think we're seeing that. I don't have any problems with what five
months before we've been playing, so we watched a lot of them. I think that's a lot more
slavery. You see.
Ah, come on. We all know Lesbians are sinister. They're sinister because they taunt me on all
these websites yet they never show up here at the door of the condo. That's sinister. That's evil.
Stop it. Leave well Lesbians. Don't do that.
Come on, Lesbians. It's a couple of times here. That's a nice little bit too.
It's all up to people's voices. It's a silly thing.
Well, exactly. Except when a comedian does it, it's funny because that's a quote
appropriate circumstance. We're geared up for it. We're keyed. We've been conditioned to
know, okay, this guy is about this and here's what it's going to say and we're ready for it
and we're going to just let our emotion go. We're going to rebound that in laughter.
Sure, but it's based on reality because real life is funny. It's great.
I Chris, thank you. He was so afraid. I wasn't going to get that comment to email
it to me five times today. Okay, so I would say that I'm all for it. Put it all on television.
I think things have to get just a little bit worse before they get better. It's okay, you know,
but let's just face it. This is the, in fact, I think it will reduce racism if if you show it
because everyone, when you when you hear or see racism or very inappropriate behavior or bullying
or whatever whatever it is, when you see that and it's a real life situation, it's shocking,
but it's shocking to everyone. There's not a single person who's going at that very moment
we see some shocking video. Believe me, there's no one in the world that looks that that
and goes, cool man. That was fucking awesome. That's not their immediate reaction. Maybe
after 30 seconds or after 30 hours. So it'll help us understand. We can't cover it up. It's real
life. It's called reality for a reason. My own reality is I miss my girls. I want to go home.
I can't wait for the new schedule to kick in. I stayed a little bit longer this time because I
didn't want to just leave midweek because I arrived midweek, but I want to try and stay a week
seven days. And it's been seven days. And it would be absolutely perfect to be on my way home right now
on a, you know, like a Saturday, arrive Sunday, hang out. And I talked to Patricia today and
everything's, you know, great. They're having a good time. And it's funny because, you know,
she's definitely, you know, well, she's, I think she's almost done with everything that she can
do at the moment with the house. So, you know, she's now, she's chilling out. So she doesn't have
a hell of a lot to say. And when I talk to her, you know, it's like, I've only slept while she was awake.
So I have nothing to say. I got completely nothing to say. So it's really hard, you know,
and we just, so we just talk a little bit of shit. Maybe you have 15 minutes a day.
And then I got this comment and I was like, oh, man, I really wish I was there.
Hey Adam, Kevin from Cambridge just letting you know that, uh, over here in old blighty,
we're getting snow coming down this morning, uh, since you're over there in San
Trent, you miss an hour. Wanted to let you and the DSC listeners know, it's beautiful.
So, talk to you later, folder out. You know, it just felt like, oh, man, finally got some snow,
but she was telling me about it. And I, it didn't really register until I heard this call,
and then I could really visualize what the new house must look like. And of course, I missed that.
Although they say they might get snow again tomorrow, but I doubt this going to be, um,
I doubt that it's going to be snow when I get home on a Sunday.
I haven't flown for six or seven weeks, mainly due to weather, of course.
And by now, you know, with all the moving and everything, I haven't had sex in
the wild as well. It's getting desperate here at the condo, my friends. And then to know that
this is going on, meanwhile, back in Guilford, Roger Smalls is completely off as rocker
and he's organizing some kind of, you know, I'm just going to play his latest podcast. It's
only a couple of minutes, but this guy is unbelievable. You know, it's, so I've let's see
as be comic strip blogger, you know, yelling at me on email that, you know, I'm an asshole because
I won't do an interview with him in person. And you know, he doesn't want to interview me
in his, and he's angry and I'm, I'm a horrible person and I come on and then, and then this
from Roger Smalls. Hello everyone, Roger. Hey, yeah. I've got some announcement to make. I'll just
give you a brief history lesson first. Two years ago, European immigrant, Mr. Adam Kerry,
fled Belgium, and moved to England for tax reasons. He settled into a house in Guilford where
he spent many, a few years in what he calls the Kerry Cottage. So that doesn't think to find
work as a sister, the electricians, stripper, or bricklayer, like a lot of people from Europe.
Adam got a job as founder of the multinational podcasting company post-show and then
bought a car pad by two. Recently, however, Adam running some more tax problems and this time
with his car. So to keep one step ahead of the authority, he's been forced to change his address
yet again. So it's moved out, which means out of this weekend, the Kerry Cottage remains empty.
And I'm proud to announce the new business that I'll be launching along with my friend who's
an estate agent who was used to remain anonymous. Yeah, just a second here. I'd just like to say that
for those of you who may not know about Roger Smalls, I mean, I've never met this guy. He's gone through
my trash. He knows where I live. He lives in Guilford. I think he works for the NHS. That's the
National Healthcare Service in Britain. And please, don't take like what he's saying there about
why I moved. I just had a really frightening thought. I have to go for a physical.
Wouldn't it be horrible if you know, what hospital does Roger work at? I got to make sure that I
don't go to wherever he is. Anyway, so I check out this commercial he's got for his tour of the
the former Kerry Cottage.
Gilford Helmet first has to, in this unique 20 minute guided tour, you'll be able to experience what he's
like to be. Adam Kerry in his old house. You'll be able to see firsthand the luxury space
attached family home with ample of road parking. Where Adam has broadcast his groundbreaking
shared for the last two years. Based in a rural setting in the Surrey area,
nearly a short walk away from local amenities. You'll be able to look at the mirror laid
an ensuite bedroom where Adam used to make love to the lady Patricia. Although it's now an
empty house, there are still some remains of the legendary park caster that used to live there.
Imagine if you will the opportunity to fund the door knobs that have been grabbed by the
very saying show bit hands to touch Michael Jackson on the body. And if that's not what it's
the 1000 pound entry fee, then I don't know what it says. You'll be the envy of all your friends
when you tell them that you've used the same toilet as Malina Epocasting Tycoon, Mr. Adam Kerry.
Although it will cost extra to use the toilet, due to the water's been shut up and it's
described as hassle getting one down after. He wants to know what he's like to walk through a famous
person's living room, sniff their seat, so just lay on a discarded sponge mattress in the garden,
and this door is for you. You're interested in taking this once in a lifetime tour with your family
than email me, Roger and the school's small and I hope mail, okay, that you can. You have to
access to this property, we'll soon be occupied again, which is we do like it to remain a broadcasting
history museum, sadly it isn't. Back to now, Roger. Guys, unbelievable. Roger, what are you doing,
man? Before I forget, big love to PD love the Daddycast Daddycast.com for the opening there,
for the Properties Owners Association. I PD loves always sending cool shit, man. I'll
open up the show with. Okay, a couple things before I get to Trinity and the free Trinity campaign.
Even though everything's been solved, you know, Comcast, rejigled the wires, so Lord knows how
long it'll take for the wires to come undone. I will say though that the telco closet is still open.
The guy was nice enough to insert my piece of cardboard again so that I can get access to it.
I'm pretty sure that it was just a loose coax. But anyway, I was complaining about
not being able to connect anyone's Wi-Fi anymore because, you know, the Wi-Fi's are all closed up,
no one's leaving their boxes open. And I received an interesting comment from the man.
Hey, Adam, this is David. I'm listening to episode number 529 and I'm calling in regards to your
comments about leaving access points open on wireless. Adam, I'm a sheriff's deputy at a agency
in Southeast Texas. And I could say that leaving your wireless open, your AP's is not really
a good idea because we had a local family that had done that, you know, they bought these
with the router from Best Buy or For Eyes or something and took it home and fired it up.
And, you know, Woo-hoo, we're on the wireless internet out of the good old time. Well,
unknown to them, the person was downloading child pornography from their AP and it was tracked to that
internet connection. And so, lo and behold, the police show up that they're door and discover, you
know, I was in a Wi-Fi and a kid, then obviously none of that going on. They had their computer
checked and it turned out okay. Well, what was happening was someone was using the wireless to
get that sort of stuff off the internet. So anyway, there's not a better reason to lock down your
AP out on the what is. So anyways, just my two cents worse. Joy to show. Thank you very much.
We'll see you. I just realized I'm completely hammered listening to the deputy talk about child
pornography through wireless access points. Just kind of hit me funny. Your deputy. Appreciate it, man.
Yeah, obviously that can happen. But, you know, I think there's a lot more we can do for society
by leaving him open that seems like, you know, and particularly when I get to the Trinity project,
which I'm getting to, folks, you understand why. What's going to say something about that,
which of course, no, oh yeah, deputy. Hey, man, you know, send back a comment or call in again.
And tell me where you listen to the show, do you listen to the show while you're on the
beat while you're in the cruiser? I want to know, seriously. That's pretty cool.
Okay. Well, we're getting very close.
But first, it's a combined sponsored content message. I had it. It's all from the fire of items.
Potwork.potshow.com. I'm sitting here at my favorite coffee shop and I'm in myself a couple of
letting. And I just got to think about these, the sponsor of yours. Splendid. I can't find it anywhere.
I tried to buy it on Amazon, but the computer says now.
And, um, let me try to buy it on eBay, but I ended up buying Cubans.
And later found 50 pieces of French vanilla and 50 pieces of hazelnut and no markers. I don't want to
buy 100 pieces and not get all flavors. So, I got a suggestion for you.
Ship Trinity to the fire violence and filler with Splendid. Have a Splendid day and I'm
quite a way music used in the intro and outro is stingray with the song last night and you find it on
music and watch other. And one last thing folder here. Stingray? Okay, I got to check it out.
I hadn't actually caught that the first time I listened to during show prep. That was his music.
So I'll have to check that out. I'll play it for you dude. So that was just one of the many
suggestions that came in. Of course, what came in the other day was a dog. I think his name is Doug.
Once it takes his 18 year old kid or 19 year old son on a drive across country and
in Trinity from San Francisco to Boston. And everybody pretty much loves the idea.
There's been just like the end of the day and I even got I haven't got some some emails from
people inside HQ who also came up with a similar concept. Obviously, this is from
Yorus from Flanders in Belgium. He says, wouldn't it be cool to have her Pendle coast to coast
and back for a certain period switching drivers at each coast? Trinity could promote biodiesel as
well as the podcasting along the way with interviewing, I'm reading it for beta, obviously,
with interviewing or giving interview to from all kinds of people. Maybe you can draw attention to
the stunt by traditional media to get the podcasting biodiesel known in a far greater group of people.
Also, great promotion for Podshow and very nice content too. For example, daily or weekly
updates in DSC and how things are going besides the Trinity feed of audio video content made
by the drivers of the project itself. So I received a lot of things just like that and
I still want to explore it and I don't want to anyone to get their hopes up. It's just on a
kind of exploratory phase here. But I think this could turn into something reasonably big.
What if we did kind of a version, a podcast version of tagging someone or passing the baton that
you see on, I don't participate in them anymore. Someone tags you and then you have to,
what's the latest one? You have to blog of five things and nobody knows about you.
Yeah, it's like okay. I haven't had time for masturbation. I'm gonna go write five things about you.
Yeah, there's one. There's one of my five things. Okay, so I think we could work together and
the more we work together, the cooler this would be. So what if we started in San Francisco? And this
is I'm just ideating here. We started in San Francisco and then we said okay, we're going to get
across the United States in 100 mile increments. So whoever is driving Trinity from San Francisco
to 100 miles east essentially northeast or southeast, that's okay too. We don't have to go in a
straight line. You know, there's an agreement with someone else down the line who preferably
is a podcast or knows how to podcast or the person who was driving over is a podcast or you know,
so we can kind of hand it off, introduce new people to the concept. And I want to have it in video.
Audio is great too. I love to, I mean, I'd love to have an audio and a video version.
We could really, really keep this going. And then I thought to myself, well,
maybe if we pimped her out just a little bit with some, with some help from some friends
of the show, I'm looking at you, Nokia. What if we put some kind of device, right, if we
put some form of mobile device that was bolted on to her, you know, the could not be removed,
you know, always had power, even if she, if the battery were dead, there was still, you know,
like have a solar cell or some kind of backup, you know, a real geeky piece of hardware,
something just go, you know, something that you'll, you'll put on make dot com later on,
you know, because it's so fucking cool. And of course, it has GPS capability, it has
GPS or 3G, whatever, connectivity through cell connectivity. You see where I'm going with Nokia,
right? And it has a camera. And so it's basically report back to base at some, you know,
predetermined frequency with their location, which we display on a frapper map. So we can track
Trinity's progress. And we can, of course, plot out where she's going to go next. And then when you roll
over, you know, you can listen to the podcast, see the video podcast that was uploaded. You see where I'm going.
So I would really want to, you know, I would love for, for Pod Show to step up to this. It's a big
project if we want to do it right. But if we can get a couple of, uh, a couple of developers to, you know,
to put together some thoughts. And it's fun. The reason why I come up with Nokia is because
you've been talking about them a lot. And I like this new N800. The N800 might actually with a
little bit of love from some developers might actually be a perfect device to do this with in
in conjunction with some kind of, you know, cell phone for connectivity. But, you know, it's based
on Linux. So it's pretty much bullet proof as a, as a mobile platform. You know, it has great battery
life. It has a built in camera. There's, you know, it's a shitty, there's no application that
really does pictures properly yet. It has just like a three megapixel camera. And it looks like
crap when you, with the application that comes with it. So, you know, let's fix that. Doesn't seem
like it should be too hard. And we'll get Nokia to, you know, pay for, uh, for Pod Show, uh, to
put some full-time people on it. You know, it's called, uh, doing something cool and making someone
else pay for it. And if not, then we'll do it in our own way. And we'll get as much done as we can.
But of course, my job would be to find some kind of sponsor like that. Now, the real point here
would be to show that we do care. Now, come on, Trinity stands for something. Trinity is a symbol
of, um, independence from big oil. And obviously, she's going to be driving coast to coast
back and forth. It just could go on for years. There's nothing to say. You know, and if she breaks
down, we've got to work together. We got to, you know, figure out what we have to do. Right now,
I've already started. I mean, she was a tote off today, uh, getting a complete overhaul,
getting ready for the trip to wherever she goes. And totally, it's got to be saved the world
win valuable prizes. Free Trinity.com. I love that so much. And Doug, I'm, I'm, I'm not completely
sold on any idea yet. I'm just trying to get something going. We can get some people who really want
to work on this. I'm game. I really am, because it could be incredibly cool. But, you know, if, if I,
if I tried internally to say, okay, let's build this device, you know, it would take forever,
you know, it says, we're busy. We go through a whole bunch of process.
Man, those engineers we have are so unbelievable. Again, so much shit done. So much. And I got, like,
a million fucking ideas. Anyway. So, so there's no way I could, uh, I could do this internally in
pod show. There's no way. But I think a couple of guys, I can get either box. That's, that's no problem.
But look at the benefit for Nokia. Nokia towards a greener future in America.
Nokia and Trinity for a greener America. I, in a world. Yeah.
All right, so if you want to participate, I'm game. I'll definitely get someone, you know,
helping me out to coordinate all the shit. And we'll make a real, we'll make something cool out of it.
I swear, I had another email. Let me see if I can find that one last second.
Oh, man, I hope I saved that. Oh, crap. Oh, I'm, I'm sorry about this. It's just so much that
that came in, but there was this one. Oh, why can't I find it?
All right. Well, I'm sorry. I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, it was so well set up.
Anyway, believe me, people are ready to do this. There are companies that want to jump on board,
the one sponsor, and besides all that, the pure sheer energy of Trinity has brought the Jeff Smith
back to the daily source code. Yes, Jeff's okay as predictor. He's just been really, really busy.
With his dueling pianos and his podcasting business.
Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, free Trinity, save the world, win valuable prizes.
Jeff, I love your man, fantastic. Look, we got a theme song. So, you know, when you got a theme song,
you're practically there. You're on your way. Stuff is already happening.
All right. I got to compose myself, Sandra Huxbergon. He sent stuff in before that he's created
home. He's got a new company called podcast studio podcaststudio.nl. And he will produce podcasts for you.
He'll put stuff together. He'll come out with creative concepts. He's starting a business.
And he's sending us, I guess, his wears to show what he can do.
Anyone's in suck off my podcast anytime. Oh, that'll make a nice outtake for someone somewhere.
Grab him. Took a candle's lid. I got a little incest's got incense.
I'm frustrated. He won't pay me 20 bucks. I said that I did for free.
Well, as long as he kissed the ring of your bitch.
I need my laptop in the bathroom and I'm listening to something. I'll take it a shower.
I need a couch. I need a kitchen. I need to be able to watch the morning bed, you know.
I need bandwidth coming through. I can't be restricted to one spot. This is the sucks. Oh, baby.
I'm doing my probing. I'm probing around. I gotta tell you, I really thoroughly enjoyed myself.
It was, it's working for the girls. I'm a kind of knock-in-eat.
We're there. We're not as candlestick. They creative juices are just flowing and anyone can suck
off my podcast anytime. And by the way, what happened to humanity? No one's leaving their
wife eyes open anymore. Oh, that's so sad. I said that I do for free. As long as he kissed the ring of the
your bitch bitch, it has a crisp, cool, cool kind of feeling. I need bandwidth coming through.
I can't be restricted to one spot. This is the sucks. I grabbed my laptop. I plugged the laptop in
and I'm telling you, I had like super fast internet. These are the nights that I really love.
It's a honder. I should have prefaced that this was under the title. Should the daily source
code be explicit or not? I was so into that whole thing about Trinity, I totally forgot about
the serious satellite stars. One, two listeners. And I don't even know where it caught off. So
Peter, I was going to hate me. Although he loves me, I know he loves me just a little bit more these days
because when he gets up at six o'clock in the morning and he already has a show that he can put
into the line up. I know he loves that. All right, one last song. I know something about, well,
you know, it's the whole candle and night time vibe means urban out or something like that
at least it's a pod safe, if not unpronounceable. I want to be with Angelina Jolie, I want to be
would be happy together forever. I go to bed and I wake up with a dream in my head. I pass you the
cream and some bread as we're having breakfast together. With Peter singing birds flying together
I'm carrying you on my wings first storms and that weather. We share our dreams while sleeping together.
We share the same thoughts without speaking, never a word.
I want to be with Angelina Jolie, I want to be a word that touches her lips and music
divine that sounds in her mind. With Peter singing birds flying together
I'm carrying you on my wings through storms and that weather.
We share our dreams while sleeping together. We share the same thoughts without speaking
never a word. I want to be with Angelina Jolie, I want to be. We'd be happy together forever.
Yeah, I realize the song is total cheese, you know, but it reminded me so much of what the
French would call a chanson. I may be a chanson de Fremage. I want to be with Angelina Jolie.
Cool. All right, buddy, I'm going to go to bed after I do some serious satellite radio crap and
I'll talk to you tomorrow. Join me here if you don't mind. A lot of you are showing up free
Trinity. Adam at podshow.com DailySourceco.com. Take care now.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.