Check out some of the world's best music video,
animation at short films from the Manchester International Festival
and brought to you by Sony PlayStation at m-i-f-dot-potcho-dot-com.
Delta's year at Charlie.
Six, five, two.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need not sticking crazy.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
The podcasting is now curry.
I don't think I'm flying into this jerk.
I don't think.
The secrets of the slumber, I will kill you
The signs of time will blow away, this is the rain
No one but you and I
I need that moon that's gone, tell me about
You're the place that I know
On the beach
Let down on the beach
On the river, my dream, my heart will wait
On the moon that's gone, tell me about
The secrets of the slumber, I will wait
On the water that's gone, tell me about
You're the place that I know
On the beach
Chris Rhea kind of puts you into the same vibe. Of course played courtesy of the
organization to the preservation to the soundtrack of our lives which enables
you to hear this as an educational part of your journey through life because once
you hear this song you'll never ever be able to forget this moment in time
that we share together. I have to big song and answer say it's illegal that I'm
playing it technically but if you go to iTunes go ahead and buy it because you
like it. Chris Rhea thinks the best of album. And let me tell you stuff that
gets played here on the Charlie cells. Got a note from Blake Morgan through a
marky ocean motor and end cough that yesterday they timed it and looked at
everything you know his album came out. Blake member yesterday played maybe
MMA's the fantastic Paul McCartney cover at Blake Morgan did from engine
company records that went to number one on the iTunes chart for a little
while on Tuesday I'm sorry it was Tuesday show didn't do a show yesterday as
we were traveling. Awesome so and if you look at the reviews it even says
people say hey I heard this on the daily source code so I got into work
hopped and over to iTunes and bought not just the track some people bought the
entire album so the pod save music revolution proving once again that it
really does work. How do you like the ambient noise there of the beach at
the ocean we are on the ocean here on fire island which is right off of I
guess it's technically a part of Long Island New York listen to that man of
course I have a little ambient help there let me just see I can turn the beach
down I can turn the beach up and down it's fantastic so we had a nice flight
from from the UK actually there was a it was a little messed up because
there was I don't know if you've been following the news but there are
protesters at Heathrow who are causing a bit of commotion and slowing
stuff down because well two things I believe one part of the group I
doesn't want the third runway open at Heathrow good luck on stopping that
in the other group wants to stop aviation in general because it affects
climate change and so that did make our early early morning commute to the
airport a little bit slower than normal of course the tickets had screwed up
Patricia still has her maiden name in her passport so it was interesting trying
to prove that she was indeed a curry that was fun and then as we were going
through the fast track it was like someone didn't have their weedies that
morning and they said excuse me excuse me sir come here your bag looks like it won't
fit in this rack I'm like oh but who cares I've been with this bag through
the fast track 20 times since I bought this particular roller bag we don't
care Santa plenty and of course the wheels I mean they show me this ridiculously
small rack you know that nothing could really fit into and it didn't fit and I
said but you know what differences it make it's virgins decision you know what
is the danger in my bag being like three centimeters too large well that
of course was not the right thing to say so I wound up having to check that
bag very interesting sir this is British airports this is not virgin airlines
that's suck my my wanker I've really got to learn to relax a little bit
more while while we were in the air phone calls kept coming in
so I don't it's only pod show if you've broken come access my site the
gaming show dot pod show dot com just giving seven not found it's all broken
again I don't know let's help pod show suck less there you go yeah it's all
broken now what's going on and this has actually been a source I think of some
complications over the past two weeks we have optimized our entire site I
believe it's now worldwide and essentially we're still in some form of a proof
of concept phase but you can't really test any other way than just turning it
on and seeing if it works because the choices literally between doing this
optimization or building data centers around the world or replicating data
around the world and so far I think the the speed has really really been good
it seems like there is a significant improvement in accessing it from the UK
in fact here for actually sent me a little a little note the other day let's see
here's what they've been doing they migrated a whole bunch of blogs including
mine to a new server integrated akami caching to speed up the BT pod show site
for the UK started ultra DNS for BT pod show to increase UK speed finalized
penetration testing oh man how come never never calls me for the penetration
testing and they're applying fixes to secure all properties preparing secure
storing of database crap to turn the Twitter module for show we're going to
get a Twitter module for show private profiles interesting and a lot more okay
so awesome that the guys are all doing that and that's part of the problems
you're seeing I think it's also part of some of the password issues that we've
seen where web stuff isn't being replicated in a timely fashion so apologies
people really are working around the clock to get this right so I'm glad
I don't have to really deal with it although I'm technically I'm on vacation
I certainly am on a lot of email and going through a lot of stuff so we got
to the let's see ride the JFK that I went smoothly nice flight by the way
saw blades of glory on the airplane laughed out loud several times luckily
it wasn't a night a night flight I'm sure I would have woken people up and then
we took well the virgin limo then took us to I love that the virgin limo took us to
saveil New York which is out in Long Island I think it's quite right off the
Montag Highway but an hour and ten minutes from the airport and then we got on
the fire island ferry and boy is that a ferry boat let me tell you if you don't
know anything about fire island in a long island then you need to Google
that I'll see if I can find some links it has a very interesting history back
from the wailing days in the 1600s and well quite honestly it's really a
a hideaway spot that I just don't know if a lot of people know about it there's
something like 640 homes here many of them really majorly massively
expensive and beautiful and and somewhere on the base side somewhere on the
ocean side we've got a house actually the belongs to New York state judge who's
renting it out to us for for the period that we're here it's right on the beach
it's four bedrooms I mean it's a it's a real beach house in fact it
reminds me a lot of kind of like what a Malibu beach house experiences
it's a different in architecture across the board but it's really nice in the
this morning if you as maybe you saw the pictures on curie dot com
a family of three deer walked right up onto the dunes I'm sure they're you know
they're on this island and they're quite tame and they used to being fed but still
it was quite spectacular to just have them walk up to the to the deck and just say
hi and we gave them an apple or two and I know the girls were feeding them bread and
shit like stop man you might I want to do that and they might when
come back and rehab it I got to get the I got to get the back story on that but fire
island is um it's an incredible place it is so laid back there is no you know no
formal dress code anywhere on the island for any restaurants or anywhere you go it's uh
it's nice man it's just uh it's come yeah it's it's really nice people say hi to each other
when you're walking on the boardwalk and it's relaxed it really is so uh I'm sure that
the lady Patricia will join me for a show either maybe tomorrow but certainly next week
and we'll talk more about our experiences here but do you have a couple of things
I need to catch up on so we'll do some phone calls right after this
I this is Michelle from whisper pearls do you like it when a girl talks dirty in your air
do you wish that I would do that more well here's your chance I'm starting my very first
erotic audiobook called the Golden Path of Love available very soon at goldenpath.podshow.com
guaranteed one orgasm every chapter at least now that's a tagline if I've ever heard one
yeah these audio novels are really working well it's an awesome awesome model and I
like that Michelle guaranteed one orgasm every chapter boy will I be looking forward to that every single
week hey Adam it's been in California actually specifically I live out in the desert in California
and I've been listening to the DSC uh 651 you made a comment about the horizontal rain flying
pasture window and you're asking like man where's the heat none where's the heat and I'm kind
of asking the same question I'm living out here in the desert for the past I don't know almost the
18 years we've had three of the mildest summers that I can remember um this is August and uh we
haven't hit 120 yet in fact the last two or three years we've only hit maybe one or two days at 120
it may sound hot to you guys but see anything under a hundred and fifteen is great out here yeah I
got to tell you um almost like close your ears let me just see if I can turn up the volume there I'm
still figuring out all the uh I'm figuring it out everything I can do here to crank up uh maximum
volume for these calls yeah it's uh it's not nice today I mean the weather is completely acceptable
because it's uh well it's like 75 degrees but it's been overcast all day there is no sun you know
I could use a little bit of global warming right now so I can understand where you know
having only a hundred degrees instead of 120 you must be really upset. The only big change that I
seen as far as the global warming thing goes is uh yeah we've caused something to change it you've got
150 eight all courses in the excel of LA right now with probably 30 in planning in an
under construction and uh it's a little humid I mean when you're spraying that much water into
the air in a smaller area yeah you're gonna change the way the whole climate uh feels and everything
and it's doing it but uh the global warming and that's so much well I'll keep unfolding and I'll
talk to you later thanks uh I'm in thank you you know it's interesting when I was and again thanks
the chef Mark for hooking me up he definitely was the direct connection to us getting this place so when
I spoke to the the agent uh responsible for for renting it out I said you know um real deal breaker is
internet and and preferably Wi-Fi I mean if you don't have Wi-Fi let me know now if it's not if it's a
wired connection I'll bring uh you know wireless hub along and they said no no don't worry there will
be internet in the house and there is uh by the way uh and it's pretty good it's connected to uh they
they really only have I think one or I don't know how they don't have a lot of connections
on this island I think probably the cable company is providing it but what's really cool is there's
this outfit called I think it's barrier reef I think is what it's called hold on a second I have it here
uh barrier free I'm sorry barrier free and they have uh blanket coverage all over the island
and I was doing a little bit of research on them um because uh excuse me uh back to school
kmart dot com back to school dot patcho dot com so I'm doing a little bit of research looking at
what kind of offering they have and it turns out they've got a meshed Wi-Fi network across the
island and you can see all of the little access points on these different homes it's really incredible
these guys have a mesh network that is actually working now it does have its flaws because uh you
know depending on who's downloading porn at any given moment it will affect the rest of the network
but you still get a good like you know I'd say 700 kilobit per second uh on the on the download side
and sometimes it burst up to two or three megabits per second uh but it's just awesome to see that
this community um has gone ahead and done that so now you can get a homeowner's pass you can get a
daily pass weekly pass or a monthly pass and anywhere you go on the island um you essentially can
log right in and which of course is great for the iPhone and the people that are here let me tell you
they got lots of beautiful cell phones okay Steve it's time for your podcast this week if you
looked over the script you expect me to say this man oh well what else would you do with it
if I had a match I could put it out of its misery oh trust me Steve this is a great little podcast
and what if I refuse to do it what if I get a new host and what if you would not just get right
down to it and do this little beauty yeah go ahead thought yeah forgive me Adam Curry wherever you are
the Muppet cast hosted by Steve Swanson a weekly look into the news music and may him
of the muppets and the gem hints and company hmm found in iTunes and at muppetcast.com all right
awful I hated it worthless grandma I was just a new old guys you know what I mean
um hey let's see we got I was waiting for this phone call to come in I was grinning from ear to ear
when Sam called me to follow up on the exploding Nokia cell phones hey Adam it's Sam here from London
I'm just listening to the DSC 65 one and how do you play my comment again I forget my
that my son's Nokia phone with the exploding battery um I saw the news release on the big
website about Nokia's press release and about the battery recall of a red troll of that and
it was the the BL5C battery that was in my friend's phone blew up I knew I should have the Nokia 62
5 which uses that battery yeah you see that was it I knew it this was the
Nokia said that it was possible the battery could quote dislodge in this case you might want to go back to
650 was it 651 and you could hear that it was more than a little dislodging it actually exploded
out popped across the room and burned a hole in the carpet yeah I think well it's great stuff
I'm really pleased that the DSC possibly had play in getting batteries recall I am a little
pissed that Nokia have relied in this statement saying that there was no reports of personal
injury or property damage because my friend's property was damaged by the battery it's at five
of the carpet but you know battery recalls a good thing hopefully this will stop it happening again so
good skills keep up the good work have fun in fire I'm and I saw a catchy thing yeah it is nice
alright Sam thank you and I have to say I did get an email back from a Nokia apparently your
friend never did send the phone and the battery off to to Nokia so they officially don't really know
that it was you know the that type of battery etc maybe they did send it off I don't know but that's
the word I got back and I have to say as as recalls go and as you know basically as quickly as
this all went just going back to me I think Nokia did a very commendable job of of setting up that
recall and I guess that when you're doing crisis management like that and you're recalling 46 million
batteries you know you you're bound to to just make the information as complete as possible and
just move on with it and not dwell too much on you know stuff that's exploding and burning holes
in carpets because that is not what what you want to hear and that you know because if that gets
out to the news media oh man can you just imagine that he just imagine if if that story about these
exploding batteries you know was out there and you know NBC or whatever had grabbed it oh man
it would be so horrible it really would I'm you know we have there is a television here and it
is hooked up to actually hooked up to what is a direct TV that's what it is and I got to tell you
American TV even after not having seen it for two months since I've been back in at the cottage
it's just it's it's pretty boring shit I got to remember to bring some kind of plop filter
when I'm on the road all right let me see what else do I have here stuff that came in
Sinclair sent oh yeah there's some news about the BBC eye player and people sending me this
note that ISPs in the UK are threatening to to do some bandwidth shaping which means essentially
breaking connections and lowering the throughput on the use of the eye player and so people are saying hey you
know net neutrality you still think it's not an issue look at this bullshit and I'm saying no no no no no
because you know this is basically a rogue a rogue application that is that is running on these ISPs
networks you know unless I misunderstand how it works it is peer to peer so it's not coming directly
from the BBC it's basically the BBC have launched a you could you could technically call it a virus
that is eating up resources of the network outside of control of the network so the BBC is basically
not paying anything and I think the networks have every right to to throttle what what's happening
because it ruins the experience for their other users I'm a typical person who does not use bit
torrent and I just don't use any peer to peer in fact I have fired up juice a couple of times
but that typically it'll work one day it won't work the next day maybe that's bandwidth shaping
maybe it's not but you know the stuff that's coming end to end it's being paid for for instance
stuff that's coming from pod show that's coming through just fine because I think you have to kind of
play by the rules and this you know peer to peer is essentially a hack to get out of paying for
huge bandwidth fees and hosting fees nothing wrong with it I love it as a hack but you know
let's not pretend that this has anything to do with net neutrality if ISPs are going to
going to shape that traffic away or down or whatever actually I do know one of the guys
who's responsible for this and if you read over at slash dot the actually you know they have
a couple of stories there about people protesting there's a lot of things about this about this
I player from the BBC a lot of people feel that the BBC is sold out to Microsoft and that they
already pay for this and it should be made freely available and of course it's a travesty that
it's only available through windows and not through any other browser but to internet
explorer and and won't work on other platforms like macron linux I happen to agree with all of that
and you know and then from the ISP perspective you know I understand but I'm going to hook up with
my buddy Eric and I'll get all the load down and we'll see what's going on so that'll be in a
couple weeks when we get back let's see what are we doing time wise hmm I better move this along
Oh
Hi Adam it's Matt from Gamesweasel just a cheeky note to let you know what's on the show this week
we've got the role playing game and blue dragon exclusively for the Xbox 360
I have a go at singing with sing star 90's collection Peter Mollonio and the team at
Lionhead Studios tell us more about fable too and we've got some tickets to give away to the
Omega sector gaming centre in Birmingham check it out of course Gamesweasel dot beaty pod joke dot
Here's something I haven't done for a while I should be giving you the phone numbers to dial in if you're in the UK
We've got a number just for you this charge with plus four four
What do you say should we do the US one yeah wine us
six three five seven
one two one six two five six three five seven quick shout out to Ola to thank him for today's
artwork he's always so on the ball man they're just a there's some people who I love so much who
just always will contribute something to the show in the form of uh well of course
uh pity love does openings for the show and I get artwork all the time and I really love and so the
the New York license plates were uh we're hacked up by Ola and I really love and do the fantastic
and of course uh even though I don't always play the worst med jingles the calls do keep a
common hey Adam it's Paul hey yeah you know I just heard that and Wilson thing and buddy my wish
was playing that for me the day and I thought wow that's really cool I sort of
thinking about Anne Wilson and I thought about Patricia and I thought wow wouldn't that be
up an Anne Wilson and Patricia yeah yeah some sort of song together some sort of duet
some sort of collaboration I think that would be just hot anyway uh thanks for doing what you do
and uh I'm clear all right oh clear oh then what are you you either a TV person
or you're a pilot one of the two but you're clear that's for sure interesting very interesting thought
there's a lot of things going on with the pod safe music now working and just the pod safe music
platform in general uh stuff has happened and big names coming in lots of cool stuff I told
you earlier in the show about Blake Morgan going to number one on iTunes there is shit happening
it's not just on the pod safe music now work of course it's it's independent productions and
and then media in general hey man what are you doing I'm sorry for the minute dude what are you doing
nothing much just hanging out yeah yeah I wish I could find some cool music oh I knew you have
there anyway as well hey I got it why don't you surf on over to indie radio Chetany and check
out what they got all of them dude I've heard those guys with the cool and they have a lot of
artists coming up to do it yeah it seems to be kind of a weekly yeah a weekly interview of the
different bands around the uh Chetany airy you know while also heard it's not just Chetany airy either
heard it's all over the room for your Texas and Florida and Wisconsin well you know just all of
the United States and even even like a couple of weeks ago I heard they played some French
also out here they have a uh forum you can go to yeah I heard I heard something about that too man
uh uh www.ciradio.net you can go and talk about different shows and see if you can hook up
the bands play shows and different areas yeah dude I'm on there right now it's cool if you're a band
you're going to be heard on the other they just knew media check out indie radio Chetany good
dot com cinnamon email and they will hook you up all right there you have it it's happening
all over the place and everywhere so the big curry family reunion is coming up you know I have a
feeling that I'm missing somehow I feel that I'm missing a couple of uh calls that came in
earlier today because I know that there was one let me just check I'm looking in my uh my conversions
box now I just really weird I had an idea that there was they had more phone calls oh I really need
this rest anyway we do have uh the big curry family reunion coming up and uh wait a minute it
might be this one let me just check hold on a second hi Adam this was cute from Dallas
no no that's a different one I'm going to play that one tomorrow um so it's not technically
upstate New York it's in Westchester County um and uh it which is uh is an armank and people are
coming from far and wide and it's uh it really starts tomorrow uh late in the day when people will
be arriving lots of folks are staying uh in motels and hotels nearby uh we're going to get an early
start Saturday morning because they still want to rent a car and get all kinds of stuff going
et cetera and uh we'll spend the all day Saturday at the reunion um then we'll um there's a
actually there's some kind of rave or something happening on the island Saturday night so there's a
midnight ferry that goes back which is perfect so uh we'll be able to get back at midnight and then
I was planning on going back Sunday uh Sunday late afternoon of late morning and uh getting the uh
the much discussed conversation slash interview with my uncle Don who is uh if you don't know
already is president of the Korea Society very heavily involved in the uh in the current negotiations
with North Korea and South Korea for that matter um but was also uh pretty high ranking in the
CIA um and was uh I think personal advisor to uh president Bush senior when he was uh vice president so
you can imagine I've got some uh interesting things uh well he has some interesting things to talk
about I've got lots of questions you know what why don't you send me your questions for Uncle Don
please preface them in the subject of the email to atamerpodshow.com and uh just say question
for Uncle Don that way I can uh can find them easily and I'll be happy to ask him all of your questions.
I had um uh my name's dig and I'm calling from Houston Techers and I've been at the city listener
since probably the one ten's one twenty something like that uh I'm a live television director
and a video editor and you've had a thread in the last couple of shows about uh the fallacies
of the BBC documentary and uh in uh six fifty-one you mentioned man versus wild you know as a
video editor we manipulate everything picture sound even audio levels and color treatments what
happier just to bring about so there's nothing really true or real it seems cynical but it's true
and everyone's trying to put their message about the way they want to and color it the way they
need to but it kind of hit an all-time well again tonight on the nightly news with Brian Williams
on NBC then he pointed out that a shot in the story about claiming the North Pole had a shot of
the sudden Russian submarine planting a flag on the bottom of the sea claiming territory in the North
Pole and a thirteen year old kid and then recognized the shot as being from the movie Titanic
so even uh routers news services distributing false images and all the news media outlets
picking up and running with it and uh there you go there's your red bill red pill blue pill moment
so help you enjoy your vacation and keep up the great work thanks no dude thank you so much for
calling this in um yeah that doesn't surprise me I gotta tell you if I wasn't on vacation right
now I would probably dive into that I did uh Google it and look for a couple of links and somewhere
so it apparently is true that well we know that the Russians are trying to plant a flag
up near the North Pole so that they can claim that that's actually part of their continental
what you call a plateau or whatever and so all the oil there is theirs and then you go of course
nightly news shows a shot of uh of Russians planting a flag on it and it turns out it's actually
a scene from the movie Titanic and of course it's because we all want to be
Cecil B. Demil we all want to be Steven Spielberg we all want to fill it up we have to put the
pretty pictures to the words we use anything that we can get anything we can get our hands on I say
this as a broadcast professional it's what we do you know and we don't even think about what the
what the implications are my fox does this all the time fox news they'll be doing a story about
anything anything they'll have continuous footage running there used to be a lot I don't know if
they still do it there used to be a law where you literally had to have file footage in the
lower right hand corner and and a lot of times I'll see fox talking about the war and so they have
a conversation there's probably the they switch off between the host and the and a person who's
being interviewed on a left-hand side of the screen or maybe in the corner you'll have just
continuous battles raging on it's all file footage you know and it really it really gives you
quite a in a way a false perspective of of what's going on here's another example I was watching
a great show by the way what's it the power of 10 drew carry hosts that show and it's very much like
a kind of like who wants to be a millionaire meets I don't know it's like yeah you got to guess
percentages based upon a telephonic survey poll and so what was really interesting and of course
let's just presume that they have a really good sample size and they're calling people from all
over the U.S. and so these questions have some real validity to the percentages and answers that
so the question I think yesterday was by the way posed to a candidate who was just stunningly
beautiful from Alabama and I saw them bell the question was what percentage of Americans have
skipped a mortgage payment now if you've been following the news you've probably read a lot
about this huge collapse of of the mortgages the hedge funds that own all these all these mortgages
that are pretty much worthless and now it's a real serious problem let me just not put that aside
okay and if you look at the dollar versus the euro I mean shit man it's like the dollar is
almost toilet paper at this point I can't even blame Patricia for scrunching her money because
you might as well wipe your butt with it it's really really a major problem however from the news
media you'd think that the whole country is defaulting on their mortgages the actual percentage of
people who have according to this poll and by the way the contestants also went very high like between
40 and 170 percent you know like this is oh this is such a huge problem the actual number turned out to be
6 percent which is obviously still incredibly high but it's nowhere near the hype that the new story
has kind of embedded into our minds so just remember take your red pills in the morning my friends
because they had all that bad or is it we do what we need we do what we can you mean not all is a
great with the plan we try to walk straight we try to stay true jog it all up to faith if you have to
whatever you say if it works for you have it your way if it pulls you through
have a nice day have a nice day have a nice day and I'll have a nice day too
you do what you like you love what you do whatever excites you kill us the blues
just do what you choose and as you have a good time keep on your toes stay off of mine
whatever you say if it works for you have it your way if it pulls you through
have a nice day have a nice day have a nice day and I'll have a nice day too
got to tell you I'm really happy with the pod save music I've got on my hard drive because we only
pick up a couple of stations out here it's kind of crap it's a repetitive shit going on
on it's just boring all right everybody that's it for who and the sun just came out just as the last
last few notes of Tim Foley whatever you say popped up there thanks to you sir jersey Todd
for recommending that of course we'll hear from sir jersey Todd tomorrow on the Fubar Friday
edition the beast the beast the beast the beastly beach festival as we come to you once again from
the curry coast so Adam at podshow.com if you care to send me a note and it's daily sourceco.com for
all of the show notes let's just end this one up today without the typical you know podshow podcast
they let's just wind it up listening to the beach together for a couple more minutes and I'll talk
to you tomorrow on the Fubar Friday bye-bye
the best in the brightest sub.daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering podshow and limelight
that.