You're Adam, it's Tony, I'm Josie.
Hey, if you need a savant for loafing around, I'm your man.
I can sit around the couch for two days straight and not lift the muscle.
I can pee in a cup.
I can watch TV for days on end.
So if you need a savant for just loafing around, you can't get me to Tony, Josie.
I'm in the old neighborhood, look me up.
Enjoy the DSC, $5.93.
You're...
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
There ain't no reason things in this way.
It's how they always been in the needs in this day.
I can't explain why we live this way.
We do it every day.
Breaches on the podium, speaking of saying,
It's proper, so on the sidewalk, big for chains.
Old ladies laugh, but from the fire escape, cursing my name.
I got a basket full of lemons in their arms, tastes the same.
We know in a pigeon with a broken leg.
You can spend your whole life working for something.
Just to have it taken away.
People walk around, pushing back their desks.
We're in pay tax, like necklace, and bracelets.
Talking about nothing, I'm thinking about that.
Every little heart beat, every little brown.
People walk a tight road on a razor's edge.
Carry in their hurt and hatred and weapons.
It could be a bomb on a bullet or a pen or a thought or a word or a sentence.
They know we just think of this way.
It's how they always been in the needs in this day.
I don't know why.
I say the things I say, but I say them anyway.
But love will come to set me free.
Love will come to set me free.
I do believe.
I know it will.
Love will come to set me free.
Yes.
Prison walls still standing tall.
Some things never change at all.
Keep on building prisons going to fill them all.
Keep on building bombs going to drop them all.
Working your fingers better to the bone, breaking it back.
Make yourself yourself like alone.
It's filled with cold, so the cadence flow.
The wind blows wild and I may move.
But politicians lie and I am not full.
You don't need no reason or three pieces to argue the truth.
The air on my skin and the world and the my toes.
Slavery stitch and the fabric on my clothes.
Chaos and commotion wherever I go.
Love I try to follow.
Love will come to set me free.
I do believe.
I know it will.
Love will come to set me free.
Yes.
They know reason things are this way.
They always been in the instant of the state.
I can't explain why we live this way.
We do it every day.
Brett Dennan.
Ain't no reason kicking off the daily source code episode number five hundred and ninety three coming to you from the curry manner.
In the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Guilford now.
The reason I play that song, I'm quite proud of this.
Of course, it's from the pot safe music network.
Brett Dennan had his song Ain't no reason as the conclusion to the main first episode of house on Fox TV.
So that was last night.
John Glasscock, learning me to this.
And, of course, I know a D.I. Don't watch house on what it's about.
I can't get it here, but it's cool no matter what.
Hey, have a body.
Let me tell you it's a another beautiful day.
I mean really, really stunning weather up there in the 20 degrees.
centigrade once again, the wind is kind of what it was yesterday, although not really
gusting to any high high degree. So about 15 knots, so 17, 18 miles per hour, give or take.
Why do I mention all this? Well, of course, because I did it again. I'm so proud of myself.
I went flying this morning. So drop Christina off and continue right on to to the airfield
ferrocs. And, uh, oh, man, it's, uh, I'm, I'm like, I'm, it's so, uh, invigorating. I'm completely
tripping because I've, yeah, of course, I've flown solo and it's no problem. And I know how to do it,
but still, now I'm really starting to feel comfortable. And this is after, I don't know, I have,
if I count it up on my hours. I'm sure I'm somewhere between 1500 and 2000 hours of, of
flying time total, but in all different countries and different airfields and different rules. And of
course, I started with helicopters. So fixed wing, much less experience, but, uh, yeah, it's, uh,
getting exciting. Of course, I came back after the flight only to find out that, uh, the pipe
is down. We've got no more pipe. I guess. I don't know, uh, it's, you know, I, I'm not using, uh,
BT internet, but of course, uh, I am using the, you know, you have to have the BT landline in order
to get DSL service. And, uh, it's pretty interesting because I actually got a message from BT when
trying to connect and it says that the master circuit to my ISP is down or something like that.
But it's still kind of cool that then the modem connects to something else and then gives you that message.
Oh, quite impressed with that. Um, but right now, on the, uh, on the vote of phone, uh, USB
dongle thingy, which still gives me about to, it gets up to close to two, uh, a megabit per second,
uh, every now and then. So it's, uh, doable. I was able to download songs from, uh,
pots of music now, working somehow, uh, able to upload this entire show. Of course, back to the
flying, uh, let me just tell you what I did. Um, instead of, you know, touching ghost flying around the
airport, I went down south. I went to midhurst past Goodwood, which is a famous chichister, uh,
Goodwood airfield. They have a horse racing there, as well as car racing and a, a wonderful airfield.
I didn't land. I passed by went out, uh, coasted out over the ocean, uh, essentially turned, uh,
well, turned right, but eastwards. And just followed the coast for a little bit, uh, went past
shore, um, and then, uh, turned around and flew back up about an hours worth of flying, and it was just
really, it was so wonderful. Uh, uh, you know, and you get up to like 4,000 feet and when air was nice
and calm and I'm just like, whooping, you know, like, whoa, man, yeah, I was flying. I don't know
how to, uh, when they're morning, it's huge and fair, it's not at fair to the moment. We'll see
yesterday, uh, saw the aircraft out and thought, well, my one of Adam's showing up or they're just
putting it out into the sun because it, uh, it's been indoors for so long. Uh, anyway, um,
rub it in. Uh, what else are you gonna say? Uh, cover, okay, ceiling and visibility, okay, come on Adam,
you know, uh, ceiling and visibility, okay, otherwise in excess of, was it 10 kilometers horizontal
and no clouds? Um, yep. Sorry, I missed you. I'm usually there. So, um, drop by, have a coffee
and uh, see some of the, um, interesting toys I've got sometime. See you again sometime, bye.
You know, I don't usually go, uh, in on invitations from guys who want me to show you their,
me their interesting toys, Hugh. Uh, uh, I did have my holiday, I didn't see you anywhere. Yes,
they are today. I must say. And yes, thank you. Thank you. I know, I don't know what I was thinking.
Yes, today I talked about the weather report as they're reported for aviation and Kavoke as
it whenever you see Kavoke, that means we're going flying no matter what, uh, and yes, uh,
many people called in and, uh, and told me something of course I knew, but should have said
correct with the first time. Hello, Adam. It's a mic turning here from Bristol and the UK also known
as a German, the so-to-in that other world. Um, Kavoke, C-A-V-O-K, feeling and visibility, okay, that's what it's
done for because you didn't know that, right? You didn't know that at all with tailwinds and the Delta
Sierra. Also, I hope to see you on the annual opening pod show Ireland on the Saturday afternoon there.
That's Adam Newman. You have gone office and they asked the wrong man. I think you're on
you're actually a man yourself. You know you've been seeing the place and you've even got your
right office there. Take care, and we'll hope to see you on Saturday on the pod bus here at home.
I've gone in. Cheers, man. Cheers. Yeah, I really should go check out my office and see if I have
a mayor's chain to wear a key to the city. Yeah, maybe I'll pop by Saturday. Sunday, I'm going to go
pick up an action. I'm going to go to the show in the Netherlands. I hope I can talk about this
pretty soon. I'll see you because there's some cool shit happening around it. Excuse me. You know what
that means? It means this program is brought to you by Tyler and all p.m. I still haven't tried it
out myself, but I'm informed from very reliable sources. It really does work and Angie B will tell you
more about it on her show on wine on wine.podshow.com, which of course is sponsored by Tyler and all
p.m. I watched the Liverpool Chelsea last night. I'm not a, you know, I'm not a big sports fan,
not a big football fan. But when it comes to something like the Champions League, when it comes
to Liverpool playing basically a home game and these guys at the fans are very, very famous. Liverpool
is such an incredibly strong team. And of course we have Chelsea, which is a, uh, a lot of people
don't like Chelsea because, you know, we've got a foreign owner and, you know, it's like, hey,
you know, we don't really need a culture in our club. We'll just, you know, pull together all kinds
of foreigners to, which everyone kind of does. But I don't know, it just has a very negative
connotation in many cases. Now, please Chelsea fans don't get all upset that I'm saying this. I'm
just, you know, observing kind of from the outside. And it was a good game. Liverpool won. It was
interesting because, uh, multiple Dutch guys had to shoot penalty kicks. And if you know anything
about football and this much, I do know the Dutch when it comes to to sudden death. Oh, that was
the studio door. Sorry about that. When it comes to sudden death and, um, and penalty kicks,
the Holland socks. And so first there was, uh, Zenden, uh, he actually, he scored and he had a great
match, uh, all round. But then for Chelsea, they had, uh, Aryan Robin, he had these guys choke. The Dutch
always choke. And he choked. And then, of course, the winning penalty kick was made by, um,
caught another fine Dutchman. I'm telling you, these Dutch guys, they're taking care of business
over here. Now, really sad news though this morning. And they were talking about it at the airfield,
um, a businessman flying back from, uh, from the match, died when his helicopter crashed 10 miles
from his home. This is on an honorary vice president of Chelsea, Philip Carter himself and, uh,
two of his friends along with pilot Steven Holdich, um, perished. They're, uh, 10, a twin squirrel
helicopter. This is, I can't wait to find out what happened because this is very uncommon for a twin
engine helicopter to go down. Uh, and of course, the weather was fine, uh, last night as well.
Um, after the match, it should not have been a problem. Um, you see, where was it found? It was
found on its side virtually intact at Wandsford, near Peterborough. So they must have had a really
something weird must have gone down there. That's sad when that happens. So, uh, that was kind of the
bummer. Did read something on, uh, actually I saved this, um, from, uh, from Google reader. I think
I, where did I read this? Maybe, uh, maybe I read this, uh, while I was on vacation, but I went through
my start items, if you know how that works with all the Google products, it kind of works well.
No, this is from April 24th. Um, check this out. Cryptonite found in Serbian mine.
Min, when Minerologist Dr. Chris Stanley of London's Natural History Museum to
a web search on the chemical formula of a recently discovered unusual mineral he was shocked to find out
that the rock is Cryptonite. The mineral found in a Serbian mine by the company Rio Tinto consists of the
same count chemicals as fictional Cryptonite as described in the film Superman returns.
So, the BBC wrote about it. Uh, the new mineral does not contain fluorine, which it does in the
film, and is white rather than green, but in all other respects, the chemistry matches that rock
containing Cryptonite. I don't know what to think about this, but uh, if you're into geology,
if you know anything about minerals and stuff like that, and or if you're Superman, you know
about Cryptonite. I'd love to hear from you. The perfect Savand moment. We got another one for you today,
as well, um, which I think will you will enjoy almost a second, and just kind of new
voice mail message. Let me see what it is. Hey, Dad, um, it's me. I'm standing outside of the Odean,
you know, cinema, and I thought you were taking me out of the oven. Um, you probably have
a lot of water or something, so I'm going back and you're done, okay? She knows me so well,
you're probably on the line with Ron. Other interesting things coming into the voice mail today?
Hi, my name is Nick Reynolds, I'm Tom and I contact Adam Curry. I'm putting together a session
for this year's radio festival, and I want to do some of the interesting and participating.
It's about the impact of Pock Pock's blogs and everything else on radio.
Hmm. If he's interested, could he please give me a ring on this number? Oh, sir.
No, yeah, I won't give him the number. Well, I think that's uh,
man, man, man. Thank you. Good bye. I think that's the BBC. The impact of blogs,
pods, and whatever on radio, hmmm. So many requests, so little things to do. Oh, man,
hold on a second. I can't believe I had something set up because it's been a while since
since I've heard from him hold on. Let me see, maybe if I'm lucky. Yeah, I think this will work.
Savorite with the nylon, spreading the news with the smile on where the roller rite.
Ringo polite. Let's listen, vote a while to the nylon. He's back, everybody, the nylon.
Hey Adam, Mr. nylon, um, to new format, interesting. I think every
product needs to evolve, so I commend you for evolving. However, I'm concerned, I don't want you
to become the Larry King of the podcast world. Larry King, everybody. It's not like the little
edge ahead. I kind of like the fine cell nature of the old cool mat, which is your show is about
nothing and anything on any given day. So let's not sell the baby out with the bath water.
This will example. Yeah, you haven't said, um, talk to you to a guest and probably about a month.
Oh, oh, allow me. Fuck you. By the way, nylon, please. I want to talk to you. I have
questions about the world bank. You are a true savant. You must give me a number to call.
It would be great if we could do that tonight. Please, you're perfect. You hate me and you and you
have knowledge. So let's get on with it. What's happening here? Kind of gentler side of you. So yeah,
I love that. That's the story of the savant thing every now and then, you know, the Larry King thing.
But, you know, keep the fine-filled and you know, lose your temper a bit. A little bit too
mellow for me. I think you're such a little peaman. You're taking it.
That's it. I'm not alone. No, no, I love you, man. Yeah, it's a Tylenol PM I'm taking. It keeps
me nice and mellow. Nice to see, though, that a lot of UK folks call it in. So we
mind as well. Make sure the US people know there's a phone number for you to call as well.
Where are you? I called you 20 minutes ago and you never called me back. You told me I
did that you were going to pick me up at 11 and if I know you're going to play, I would have made
other plans. This is like the third time recently that you promised to do something for me, Dad.
I'm completely flaked out on me. I understand you have to work in your busy, but I'm your daughter.
When you promise me something, something that's simpler, coming to pick me up, when you say you're
going to pick me up, then you do it. I'm so not fucking standing here in the middle of the night,
on the sidewalk, like some crazy homeless person. I'm really getting sick of this shit, Dad.
You keep making all these promises that I can't tell you more than you are the weed topic.
You're trying to run a little stone or pot head. And now I'm going to have to fucking take
a taxi all my home. And when I get there, you and I didn't have a little talk about responsibility.
And when I told you better be standing out the day, there's enough money to pay for this cab.
You fucking better be wearing men's clothing. She's little actress, isn't she?
Take that out of all the wood. Hello. I'm Chris Layton. And I'm Nick Cooper. And hang on, hang on.
Is this thing even on? Hello. Hello. Mr. Curry. Mr. Curry, can you hear us?
Oh, God, it's just going to turn into a method technical blunders and a series of cock-ups, isn't it?
Not necessarily. We're professionals.
Fessional to my ass. Mr. Curry. Can you hear us, Mr. Curry?
You know, I just give up before you. Who is this, Mr. Curry anyway?
Who's Mr. Curry? Who's Mr. Curry? Mr. Curry?
Mr. Curry only happens to be the bad father.
Oh, I understand now. You do?
Yeah, it's a pseudonym for Dave Terrell.
No, not Dave Terrell. Adam Curry, the poor father. God, you know, the big boss.
Oh, him, that guy who picked us off of a use station and gave us this nice,
cushy mammoth task. I'm presenting the disaster that is the pod zone.
Don't say that. Everything's fine here, Mr. Curry. Just ignore Nick.
The pod zone is a marvelous thing. Almost. Thank you, Bill English. Join you.
And the other fantastic talent on BT Pod Show.
Suck up. Anyway, to the point, Mr. Curry, we would just like to say a few words.
If that's all right with you. Bloody well, should be.
We just like to invite all DSC listeners to check out the pod zone's podcast at podzone.btpodshow.com.
Yeah, it's really good. We host a great show with the best pod save music on the planet.
And all the great features that your listeners haven't learned to know and put up with.
Such as the Crucial 3, Tech News, the misconceptions for his own thingy,
and Nick's STDs. So that's the pod zone. Podzone.btpodshow.com.
Thanks again, Mr. Curry.
Mr. Curry, I remember now the guy who likes naked pictures of podpasses.
Hey, seems to curry would fancy one of mine.
Oh, um, I'm not too sure. Either way, Mr. Curry, we love you.
Oh, and I'm one more thing with grunches.
Yeah, you think I didn't know that?
That's why you guys are on the network. We needed to balance it out a little bit.
We needed some more scrunchers.
Well, seriously, it's welcome. Good to have you guys aboard.
Hey, let me see.
Coming up in just minutes. Another savant from who joins us in the circle of the
Cirque de Stavant. Oh, there you go. There's anyone.
Let's seek this savant or de Stavant.
Seek de Savant. Yeah. Yeah, that kind of works, doesn't it?
Like Cirque de Sly, only different.
Once in a while, people will call in and when they've had a brush with greatness.
And today is no exception.
Hey, Adam, our green sea from New York, and I'm out here in San Francisco tonight.
Went off to a blogger dinner with Scoville and you and some other people.
You never guessed who I met. I found one of the famous savants.
Say hello. If you did put it for them, then you can't find it.
That's a real surprise.
Wait a minute.
I love it prolific program when he gets flustered, man. You can't understand him.
Here you go. Listen, it's him. It's him.
Wait, wait, wait. I don't understand.
I don't understand. I don't understand. I don't understand.
What are you saying, man?
Savant. Say hello.
If you did put it for them, then you can't understand.
I met the prolific programer.
I'm excited. Man, it was great. The intro grammar was here. It was a whole thing.
So, sorry can be here, man. You're up in London, junior thing.
But we'll catch up with you soon. Cheers.
Yeah, buddy. Yeah, I'm sorry, too.
I'm just waiting for the right moment to get the superior savant prolific programer on the show.
Because I know he's got a lot of good stuff to say. I just don't have a reason yet.
But when I'm ready, I know that he'll be there and he'll be ready for me.
The savant specials.
Okay, it's time for our savant from our series of the circle of savants.
Buying the salt and the salt savants.
So long.
I think I'm going to be able to get at least once a month in episode.
There's a fast forward button on there for a reason.
And I hope to be able to talk to savant every single day.
So long.
And by the way, I want you to know that this format change.
Doesn't mean that I don't want to make it pictures, make it pictures.
I'm the salt and the sense of on savants.
Joining us now is a guy who I've had some email contact with over the past several weeks.
I think we probably had contact a long time ago as well.
I don't know. My brain is so fried.
And he sent me feedback. He sent me voice mail.
And honestly, you know, the stuff that he sent me has been so long.
I'm like, I just didn't know where to put it.
So I did finally get around to playing one of his, one of his pieces of feedback recently.
And he joins us now as our official nuk savant.
His savant name is a atomic rod.
Rod Adams, welcome to the Daily Source Code.
Hello, I don't know how are you.
I'm good, man.
Well, now you are a home on a second.
I got this from your website.
An atomic entrepreneur.
It's right.
And you've been professing.
And this is what really interested me and want me to get in touch with you and talk about it.
The concept of a backyard nuclear reactor.
You bet.
And an actor safe enough to be surrounded by people.
Okay, so the first of all, are you actually making anything?
Because I looked around your site and it seems like you've been interested in this for a long time.
Are you actually physically creating a reactor?
Or are you just making a plans and following policy and politics, et cetera?
We have invented the metal yet.
We're doing a lot of design work.
And an awful lot of the background work and the foundational work.
Necessary policy regulations that kind of stuff.
It takes a long time to get a permit to do what we want to do.
Well, yeah.
When you're handling uranium and stuff like that.
Well, there's nothing wrong with uranium.
Well, we're going to talk about uranium in a second.
But first my uranium.
Okay, so Rod, what you're talking about here is building a...
Or I guess the concept of every home having their own nuclear reactor.
And that being an alternative for fossil-based fuel and energy that we currently use.
Correct?
Well, we want to eventually get to homes.
But initially we're going to start more in the mini reactor as the micro reactor.
It's going to be more like large buildings and stopping malls and industrial parks and ships and that kind of stuff.
Significantly smaller than the current reactors.
But not quite to the personal reactor mode.
Sort of like the computers.
You know, one from mainframes down to many computers.
And eventually we had Jonathan and his boys to invoke to then develop the micro computers.
But it took a while.
So on the atomic insights site that I guess is yours.
There's a couple of interesting things here.
And we kind of jails with what you just said.
Atomic power is safe enough to float to power floating cities with more than 5,000 people living within 1,000 feet of the plant.
And that's what we call nuclear powered aircraft carriers.
It's clean enough to operate inside sealed submarines.
True, they're nuclear submarines.
Cheap enough to provide overnight power for about 1.5 cents per kilowatt hour.
I have no idea it sounds like a real bargain.
And compared it enough to make suppliers of all other energy sources very nervous.
Okay, let's start with that one first.
You know, nuclear power, you still need to mind stuff.
You still need the equivalent of a refinery, which is just like the oil business, I guess.
Why would they be very nervous about it?
Well, it's the matter of scale.
A pound of uranium has as much energy as 2 million pounds of oil.
But that in perspective, you can hold the pound of uranium in the palm of your hand.
It's about the size of three hundred marbles.
Two million pounds of oil requires 30 tanker trucks to carry it.
Okay.
So, but it'll end the pound of uranium right now, even after a seven years worth of price run out, cost about $100.
And really, that's all about after all the refining and the enriching that you go through it,
it's surely the value must be much higher after that process.
Well, even after all of the refining and rich and commercial nuclear fuel costs about 1.20,
as much as oil does on a per unit heat basis.
So, you can get that 1.5 cents right now.
If you produce electricity with oil, it'll cost you over 8 cents to get it all out.
Okay.
Now, Rod, you're talking, I've got to bring it back to some really understandable concepts.
First of all, you talk about uranium.
I mean, this is the yellow cake that Iraq supposedly had,
and all the technology that people or other kind of evil acts as evil countries are supposedly developing and using.
And here you are talking about uranium, like you could go down to the drugstore and grab a couple marbles worth a minute.
Is this, is this incredibly hard to produce, then, or enrich to make viable for nuclear energy?
Well, actually, you don't have to enrich it.
There are reactors operating today in Canada that use natural uranium as their fuel source.
It doesn't require enrichment, if you design a reactor problem.
Now, if you enrich it, it does make it a little better, it's sort of like the difference between running crude oil in your car and running gasoline in your car.
Gasoline burns a lot better than crude oil does, so you do some refining to it.
That's what we enrich your engine, just to make it work a little better and smaller reactor.
Okay, and build a reactor with natural uranium.
And this uranium, it's a natural element that comes out of the earth.
I mean, is this just an endless supply?
Is it only found in certain locations?
I'm really trying to figure out how viable this is as an alternative to other energy sources.
Where do we get the uranium from?
Is it in my backyard already?
Cause I made some of your backyard.
I wanted to be my neighbor's backyard.
I don't want uranium in my backyard.
Well, it's pretty common.
It's pretty widely distributed to the earth.
It's about as common as 10.
There are some places in the world that have very nice supplies of uranium.
Particularly the major sources of uranium in the world are Australia, which has about a third of the world's known supplies.
And Canada, which has about 25% of the world's known supplies.
The US has a lot.
And there's deposits in Kazakhstan and a bunch of other places that are very economical to mind.
But worldwide, there's really no limit to where you can mind uranium.
It's pretty widely distributed.
Right, but that's what we thought about oil initially as well.
It can run out, I presume.
Well, we've been looking seriously for oil and using a lot of it for 150 years.
Now, uranium is far more energy dense.
Like I said, one pound of uranium is worth 2,000,000 pounds of oil.
Right.
It's widely distributed.
And we've only really used it for a very short period of time.
You know, we haven't used it for energy until that 1957 was the first commercial power plant.
And not only that, we found as much as we needed in about the first 10 years of looking
and really haven't looked much in the last 30 years.
And the reason to stop looking was the price got so low that it was economical to develop it.
Look at, abandoned mines in the US that are still full of uranium.
We just stopped producing it because the price was too low.
Okay.
So, and that, by the way, can also be a significant problem.
Because someone's less to go in and mind this stuff.
Right.
The price is now almost 10 times, but it was 7 years ago.
So it's back to an economical mineral demand.
Okay.
So how much will a backyard nuke reactor cost me to power my home?
Just, you know, taking into account that we are down the line somewhere.
We've gone past the main frame where the PC version of the nuclear reactor.
What's it going to cost me, Rod?
That's how I get to the PC version.
We'll probably be looking at $50,000 to power your home.
But that'll last you for about 30 years without any new fuel.
That's pretty cool.
Yeah.
But it was at all depends on a bigger house.
Your house may be more developed.
Yeah.
But still, 50,000.
And after 30 years, you can fill her back up.
I mean, do you have to get rid of the whole reactor?
I mean, what's the idea here?
And of course, the obvious questions.
What do we do with the waste and how about the dangers?
Yeah.
Well, the waste is very small.
I used to be an engineer on the submarine.
And I'm way back in a previous life.
On a nuclear submarine, might I chance?
Oh, yeah.
We'll see on account we have a new way.
We don't really.
We don't have like old fashioned coal submarines or beans or something like that.
I mean, you don't have steam engine submarines.
Well, we do have steam engines submarines.
But they are heated with nuclear energy.
Okay.
Right.
I'm sorry.
We got rid of our last diesel sub probably can.
Well, actually, we had one diesel sub that we just beat commission,
but it was a very specialized deep diving submarine.
But other than that, let me just tell you what's the sub in the Navy in 10 years.
That's going to tell you, man.
There's two things I love.
I love flying and I love submarines.
I cannot tell you.
I am so enchanted by, you know, run silent, run deep.
Ice station zebra.
I've seen all the movies with all the submarines.
I love that shit.
Yeah.
Me too.
It was fun.
All right.
So now to the waste.
Okay.
So arguably, there's very little waste.
So just to give you an idea of how little waste,
the reactor on board my submarine.
If you took all the.
If you just looked at the fuel and you put it in a nice container,
it'd be a container, maybe.
Oh, five feet in diameter and 10 feet high.
And that lasted 15 years.
Now we're a 9,000.
Some of them are okay.
But if that.
If that stuff ever gets out of its container,
it could potentially contaminate surrounding.
What do you think it is green?
Who's or something?
I don't know.
What is it?
It's solid.
Ceramic.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I told you, bro, you don't get my face, man.
I'm not like an anti-nube guy.
I'm just trying to figure it out.
No, it's.
It.
It's a material that they can't leak because it's.
It's solid.
It.
It's like.
Very.
Uh.
Pretty shiny metal.
It was sitting in a.
In a.
Battle of hot water for a long time.
It's just that.
That's a hot water.
And you put it in a nice.
Really infilled container.
And it's.
It's.
Doesn't.
I did not know that.
I mean, people totally.
I mean, yeah, you think about waste.
You know, if what we see in your mind, of course, is these, you know, excess oil drums that
have big, you know, atomic energy warning signs all over it and radiation signs.
And of course, you're thinking it's green ooze that comes out.
I mean, that's that's totally what I think.
Sure.
Well, you told me that.
I would.
Oh, well, okay, conspiracy.
You know, just put my tin foil back.
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
Three.
Like the portrait, or the compositions.
Certainly.
Okay, and this.
We can get into that.
But, you, I'm already learning some amazing things here.
So it's.
In theory.
And the theory is that whatever, in cases the shiny beautiful object that is known as
Luke, it ne a waste in theory.
Um, that can be safe guarded in perpetuity.
Sure.
Okay.
Now, sorry.
Put it in the container.
and you can watch it.
And some people want to somehow
postulate a society where nobody will be around
to watch it anymore.
And then, of course, I don't understand quite how they
expect somebody to be hurt if nobody's around to watch it.
But that's beyond, I don't understand how people are going
to be hurt.
No one in the world has ever been hurt by exposure
to the used nuclear fuel.
OK, gotcha, now we can move into the final frontier
of questioning when it comes to nuclear energy.
We've all, we all know the history of Chernobyl.
We know three mile island.
What are the risks involved in meltdown?
Or, and of course, this is something of the most,
the past seven years, what if there's a terrorist attack
on a nuclear reactor?
What are the dangers?
Not to, that's a complicated question.
Let me see if I can give you a simple answer
from my point of view.
The technology that we want to develop
is called the space dumps on a called a pebble bed reactor.
And it uses a fuel that was developed,
not in the first generation of nuclear plants.
It was developed after a lot of thought
and consideration.
And basically, it is a fuel that cannot melt.
And it's surrounded by materials that are very high
in the country, the capacity of materials.
And those pebble bed reactors can operate
in a situation where no matter what happens
to the cooling system, the reactor cannot get hot enough
to melt.
And we like that design a lot
because it makes it easy to design
very safe reactors.
So in other words, the reactor that cannot have a meltdown.
Correct.
Especially when it's designed to be a fairly small reactor.
And you can build a pretty good size pebble bed reactor
and still prove that it can withstand any postulated
accident and not melt.
There's a video on the web that
Chinese have one of these operatives pebble bed reactors.
And they actually do the test instead of just doing
the equations and saying it won't melt.
They actually say, OK, watch.
And they turn off all the cooling and watch what it does
and it was a Australian Broadcasting Channel, ABC,
to paddle this program.
I think it was called.
Damn those Chinese.
Well, actually they copy it out the Germans.
The German pebble bed reactor was developed in Germany.
Called the ABR.
And they built the ABR operative for about 25 years.
They also built a follow-on called the Thorium
Hyperion after THTR.
And so that was also done.
And by the way, you got to say damn those Americans
because it was an American named Ferington Daniels,
who actually developed the idea that they peed 47.
But he didn't have the materials that now is necessary
to make it work.
All right, Rod.
So, so, anyway.
So, it's a South African's work on it too.
So, and if there was an explosion, because I'm just going
based on the fears that it's embedded in people's minds,
if there was some form of explosion unrelated to the core,
but can radiation be released into the atmosphere?
Can we get a Chernobyl repeat or these pebble,
be tree actors?
Are they safe guard against that as well?
It is safe guardians.
Well, they're actually in a full containment.
At least I want to build a full prototype containment.
It's a pretty significant vault with lots of steel
on concrete.
I just can't see it failing and releasing any radio activity
to the environment.
So, Rod, we're going to work to actually build some
that we can prove that to people by actual person.
So, it appears to me that the only hurdle
would you have two hurdles, and maybe I could help you.
I don't know. I'm interested.
I think you got a very compelling story.
And of course, I need to read up and get some background
on this, but the first one would be the PR.
The whole PR aspect, and this goes into politics,
there's just a horrible, horrible meme of nuclear energy.
Everyone's going to be glowing in the dark.
We're going to kill our babies of the future with the waste.
Is there anyone who is trying to work on that problem,
which I think would be almost insurmountable?
Well, actually there are a lot of people,
but a couple of very prominent people.
There's a guy named Patrick Moore who was a Greenpeace founder
and has come to the clean side and then become a pro nuclear activist.
He's been talking around all around the U.S.
The woman named Christine Pat Wooden, Todd Whitman.
And after who's Jersey a director?
She was from New Jersey, didn't she get kicked out of office in New Jersey?
Well, I don't know about that, but yeah, a administrator.
No, she had some kind of, she was a sex scandal.
She had a sex scandal or something like that.
Oh, maybe that was just a fantasy.
That was another New Jersey.
That's right.
No, it was just my fantasy.
I was fantasy people.
First he taught Whitman.
I was like, yeah, baby.
I know what I do to you.
Right.
The other thing, obviously, is money.
I mean, if you were to get into business,
how much money would it take to get a functioning,
mall powering, completely terrorist proof, shiny, waste,
pooping reactor together based on pebbles?
The first one will probably cost us about 300 grand.
$300 million, sorry, $300 million for the first one.
But that's a lot of it's the initial cost of any new machine.
We believe that we're going to be able to build 10
major lot units for on the order of $20 million of fees.
See, that kind of money doesn't scare me,
because I know it's out there.
And well, it doesn't scare me any energy business.
It's an expensive business.
So do you have plans?
Do you have, like, what do you have, like,
blueprints?
Do you sit over that at night with your nuclear buddies?
And you draw this up?
Or are you, do you have engineers?
I mean, how far are you with this project?
Well, right now we've got some engineers working.
Mostly at night on their own computers,
but the good thing about today is we have computers
for a more powerful order that some
were used to design an odd list.
And we have a bunch of business planners,
a couple of MBAs from Duke and an entrepreneur
who's been in business for a number of years
and some good advisors and we've got a pretty solid business
plan going on.
All right, man, listen, atomic rods.
That's serious stuff.
Here's what you do.
You get your MBA boys together.
You get them to put together the presentation
or some kind of something that I can send off to someone
like Bill Joy or John Doer or Ray Lane.
I'll send it to a man.
And they'll take a look at it and these are those kind of,
you know, these are the guys who can make that kind of money
happen.
Yep, well, it's a public promise, man.
It's a what?
I said, I think you just made a public promise.
We've got that stuff almost ready to go now.
Or with it about two days.
Yeah, yeah.
Of course, you're right, listen to this show.
It'll be all over me.
It's like, hey, man, fuck, why do you mention on the show
or because we want to get in first?
We went, I went and talked to some Google engineers
about two weeks ago at Google headquarters
and talked about this.
And we've been doing a lot of talking.
But there's a lot going on besides talking.
Right on, oops, hold on, that's my, yeah.
No problem.
Hold on one second, I think that's my wife, don't go away.
All right, that's what we call a natural edit.
Yeah, I have to break my wife.
You know, she calling me 11.30 at night.
She's calling to bed.
She's oversees him to Holland this week.
She'll do it her start, Dan, who was the star?
Yeah, man, she's like, I can't, I shouldn't be talking about it.
But she's got an amazing, I'm going to go over it
because I'm also partially, I'm not going to actually be on the show,
but a whole bunch of friends of mine are on the show.
And it's going to be pretty cool.
So she's rehearsing and doing press.
And I don't know, she's having a good time.
And leaving it very proud has been, oh, absolutely.
It's just, I got to get help, man.
I need like a full-time person because I got to take care
of the kid.
I got it to you.
I got the animals.
Of course, the cats.
It's 11.30.
They're still outside running around.
I don't know where they are.
They don't want to come in.
You know, I'm doing everything wrong.
You know, it's typical Mr. Mom shit.
All right, dude.
For those days.
Yeah, my baby is graduating from college.
So it's not been too long ago.
I don't remember those days.
All right.
Well, now I feel old.
Thank you.
Atomic Rod, we're going to check in with you from time to time.
Have your MBA boys and that stuff over.
And if you've got any nuclear news, just give me a shout.
You got it.
What's my every move?
And sticking out on notice?
Do you want to be?
Everything that I want to be?
But for all the wrong reasons.
You'll never see.
Without a creative point in your body.
You're forced to imitate.
You try to walk online.
They find out your fate.
Counting out the wig of it.
That's the day I know.
You're right.
You're the world.
You're the new hurrayer of art.
And then you're cast out to see
Finding yourself all alone with the most powerful force in the world
Instead of the blue and slowly drift away
Counting all our wind coming
That's it everybody
I'm different, I'm different
I'm done, I'm done, I'm done
I'm done, I'm done end my heart
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I learned that there are now reactors that cannot experience meltdown, hmm, getting pretty
interesting.
Alright tomorrow we'll probably have another sabondon if I can schedule some of them and
get someone willing to come on and talk about some ship and Friday of course, the maximum
music football Friday I am getting ready for a doozy, it bought it.
DailySourceCode.com is where you can find all the show notes, links to everything discussed
in the show and play it on the show.
And of course, I'm in email anytime at patshow.com, take care everybody, bye now.