Ladies and gentlemen, I present Padshal's poet laureate Melvin P. LeBeth.
Broses are ready. My sweater is beige. For your domain name needs, you should go to this page. GoDaddy.com.
Hello, this is Governor Arnold. I am here to talk to you with the great people of this state of California.
This is a message that stealing cable and internet is wrong. It is against the law. If you are caught, you will be terminated.
There are only two reasons you should be stealing cable or internet access. If for some reason you cannot get quality movies like Terminator, come and do.
Twins, Kindergarten Cup, all of those are acceptable reasons to steal cable TV.
And if you are producing the daily source code, then you can steal someone's internet access. But only long enough to release the daily source code 530.
An atom, I'll be back.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm flying into the future.
Don't wait for me, I'll tell you here
Show me anything
Fire away with the Lord in God
Lacken out of our fire, all fire
Even the rain won't move me out
I'll shout for courage and courage to feed
You everything to desire, all fire, all fire
Do you even tell me anything
Show me anything
I'll tell you here I'll tell you here
I'll tell you here
D-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A
A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-B-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-B-A-A-A-A-A-B-A-A-NAAA-AA-A-NAA-A-A-A-AA-A-A-A-AA-A-AA-A-A-A-A-NAAA-A-
30. But I had the juice once again. I really liked the way the show yesterday turned out,
so I figured I'd give it another shot. I'm a little bit more tired today because it was a very
hectic day. And I think I have a bit of a sniffles. All of that just came on like at the very
end of the day. God, I hope I didn't pick something up. That's the last thing I want. But it was yeah,
a day wrought with hectic back and forth to be quite honest, preparing for the shoot of
new show that we're doing tomorrow, we're shooting with Natalie Delcante. At the office, we were
setting that up. I had to come back to the condo between one and three. I had to be here to meet the
calm cast guy to take a look at the at the connectivity. And you know what it's like, right? I mean,
this is my nightmare. I had shades of the sky installation guy again. I'm running out the door 10 minutes
to one, which I should be able to make the condo no problem in 10 minutes. And I'm on a conference call.
I literally walked by the conference room where a meeting was taking place and I was on the conference
phone. And I walked out and so I'm on this call and then I got a call waiting. I see it's an
unidentified number. And I don't even think about it. Because you know, I just normally don't answer
what is it? A block number is that we call it in the states. I don't answer that.
And another three minutes, I'm like, oh crap. Oh, you know that was that was like the guy
calling to see if I was home. Because they said you have to be home between you at the hour specified.
But if you missed the call 10 minutes before when they call you and they don't get an answer,
oh, then they just might go to their next job. And sometimes you can wind up with a cancel job number,
whatever it is, job ticket. And indeed, it was him calling. So, you know, I'm running to the condo.
I'm standing downstairs. I'm calling. I'm trying to get him on a line. And yeah, so I took another
30 minutes, but he finally got there. He came up, couldn't find it. Working on it for two and a
half hour straight. And I was like taking meetings here. We got Greg Milk from the weakest beat
talking about his video show, doing that here with Moody. And this guy's just rummaging around.
You know, the couches are all astrue. And he could not figure it out. I told him, I said,
look, man, somewhere there's something's misconnected disconnected. Ah, the longer that, well,
the longer the shorter it is, he didn't fix it. He walks out the door. Literally. And of course,
you know, I'd cleaned everything up. I'd cleaned up the Wi-Fi router and everything in the hallway with my
multi, uh, my multi Wi-Fi relay station, which involve the eye Mac and the linksis.
And he walks out. And all of a sudden, I see the T, I had put the TV on one of the channels that it
wouldn't receive. And all of a sudden, flips on. And all of a sudden, the modem light comes on.
I'm like, oh, no. And of course, the guy's gone. I can't get into the closet anymore.
So, I'm now using another link system. It seems, I'm just going to knock on wood. It seems like it
fixed itself. But anyway, he's coming back tomorrow. It's at 730. And uh, and hopefully it'll still be
running by then. And maybe he just jiggered something the right way. It seems wrong that it's something
that it happens that way. But lots of comments from you guys, lots of explanations about this
tinfoil hat moment that I had to including this. Adam Mike from Baker-Sfield, California.
I think the items that you were describing in the telco closet, it's called a 66 block.
So we call that harness. Still interested standard. There you go. 66 blocks. Take care.
Hey, ladies. He doesn't even sound like like a hot telco guy. You know, he was just the
right kind of butt crack. Listen to this voice. Adam Mike from Baker-Sfield, tell him Mike. I'm
a, I think the, uh, I'm a telephone repairman. Adam's that you were describing in the telco closet,
yeah, called a 66 block. Okay, man. 66 block. No, what I'm saying.
That's what we call that harness. Mm-hmm. That's what we call that harness.
Hey, baby. I got a 66 block over here. My harness. And it's just standard. Mm-hmm. There you go.
66 blocks. Take care. I love it when I have more time to prep the show. When I can actually
listen to the comments before I play. And so I can set that up. Um, you know, I had all that,
I was doing all that weird routing and stuff. And of course, you can expect the one and only
prolific programmer to call in with some suggestions about the routing tables. Hi, Adam.
Well, because I'm right here from San Francisco. I just came home the other day. But, uh,
I went to a Muslim DSC. Five two nine. That's about 21 meets and three seconds on the clock.
Um, once we're at, you know, about your DNS, you don't need to actually configure a DNS.
If you have all your clients have their own DNS clashing, then they can just come off the roots of
either way, whatever you I speak in. I've done that. And therefore, everyone comes here. Doesn't need to,
I don't need to convince you. I don't know if you can get a deep on social host. That's all.
You know, DNS talk has always turned me on prolific programmer. So I appreciate you calling in.
And I just spent a second on it. The problem is the thing, you know, I was getting, I was sharing
the internet from the airport on the ethernet of the iMac. And I didn't really have an ethernet
network to connect to the only way I could do it was by, um, faking kind of, you know, making the,
the linksis think it was just a router. But actually routing between the, uh, it's ethernet
channels, I guess, what you call it, and, and it's wireless channels. Um, and, and so you can't actually get,
you can get DHCP assigned, but then you're not on the same network as it was, I can explain.
Anyway, I wound up with one network was 192.168.1.4. And the wireless side of the linksis was
198.192.1186.2.4. And so I had to make a static IP on the .1.4 network in order for it all to fit.
And so that meant it wasn't serving up IP addresses through DHCP. And therefore, I used a,
a separate domain name server.
By the way, before I forget, I really want to thank Marcus Couch again. I, there was something
more I wanted to say. Marcus has a new episode out of a podshow music rewind episode 52 hosted by
Jack from Get Jack. And he says it's kicking ass lately. The show's been doing great. 40 music podcasters
contributing. And he's got some other stuff in the works. He's, I love him, man. And his wife,
they're awesome. Excuse me. Uh, since Theo, I was speaking of which, uh, email from
Karen Schmidt, hi at him. Chest cold and funky voice prevented me from calling. I ordered
mocha flavored splender from Amazon and got the shipment this week. Immediately, I fired up
the sense, say, oh, met a cup of coffee. I put milk in it and put in a packet of splender. It was
like drinking a foamy hot chocolate. Mm, totally awesome. Good luck with the move. I love forward
listening to the charity for a long time to come. Karen in Virginia. He asks folder. Mm,
calling Karen when you feel better. Please. The voicemail, the volume has been so incredibly low.
You know, it's since all the best of Charlie's, I guess, everyone kind of got out of the funk.
Let me play you the, the number. So it's embedded in your brain.
I'm sorry. I'm sick of that. Oh, man, believe me, that hurt me just as much as it hurt you.
I'm so sorry about that. Let's try it again.
One, two, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven, one, two, one, six, three, five, seven,
last one, two, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven. Yeah, all right, sorry.
Let's see what else happened. We did some, so we got the Natalie shoot ready.
Oh, it worked on our channels for Tvo. I think we're coming out with five channels on Tvo.
It's going to be a lot of fun because the producers that we work with and we'll be able to pump a lot of
shows through this. I think it's in a way, analogous to what we're doing with serious.
So I'm pretty excited about that. The reach is reason, I don't, I think it's the number of boxes
that have this capability, I was like close to half a million, I think. So it's definitely an
interesting channel, distribution channel. And we have to physically deliver a different type of
file to them. I'm thinking it's MP2, I'm not sure. So it's going to be a lot of work involved.
I mean, it's the same thing with serious. We take it from MP3 and then it goes to,
that I think they have an MP2 special kind of code deck and they compress the crap out of it.
If you're listening to this show on serious right now, in that satellite technology great with
the AM sound, that's how they get all those channels on. Okay, so what was I going to say?
I don't know, oh yeah, the Tvo thing, right? And I got a lot of feedback about Trinity. A lot of
offers to, you know, hey, I'll take Trinity right off your hands, no problem. I really want to give
her away. I'm thinking I want to do a combination of, first of all, I'm going to get it fixed.
I think the way we'll do it is, I would love if, I mean, it's not really a fair promotion
because it would only work for the states, you know, I could provide a ticket fee to fly out
and then pick the car up and drive it back or something like that. I wanted to be a real prize
and the car will work presumably. Yeah, I don't know, so I got to come up with the right
from most. Let's work on that. Let's come up with a great giveaway. Something just for just
for daily source code listeners, not a network wide thing, just for people who have been stuck
with the Trinity concept for as long as it would physically last. Let me know, Adam at podshow.com.
Hi, Adam, it's Rowley from the Dark Compass podcast. Just let you know that I've just started my
third year on podcasting and I have been dragged by my hair into BT Podshow by your talent
scouts and I'm loving every second of it. So thanks for letting me join your illustrious teams
and hope to talk to you soon. Bye.
Music coming from the UK and around the world, splattered with some new tunes from the Podshow
music network and something to laugh about in my own inevitable style.
Hi, this is Chris Jugginson and you're listening to me right here on Dark Compass.
Hi, this is Jade Leary and you're listening to England's Voice of Reason.
But we're bringing role parents, something like a 12 inch mix. What is a week without role?
Dark Compass.com. Our talent scouts dragged you by the hair, right?
Well, I have another show that joined BT Podshow.com. This is great. It's really exciting to witness
almost exactly the same process that we witnessed in the States when we started,
as we're witnessing now with BT Podshow. And it's the same excitement. I'm really jazzed about it.
Particularly when you hear this next. Let me just play this for you. It's unbelievable.
Hi, my name is Karen and I'm your chai-rise queen at chai-rise.btpocho.com.
I wanted to talk dirty and what could be dirtier than numbers. How many people listen to you show?
When I started, my audience grew from one to thirty over eighty shows.
Then I moved over to Podshow. And in the first month, the audience jumped to six hundred plus.
And in the second, to over eleven hundred. And the numbers continue to swell.
Where else can you get hit? Like that? BT Podshow. Are you coming?
I love it. Oh my goodness. I gotta get that show. I gotta get it on my tablet.
Which is turning out to be a really great iPod, the way many of us have envisioned a mobile
podcasting device. Check this out. The home screen of this device has widgets and you can
configure them. You can say I want the clock and I want the clock here. It's very much like widgets on
your Mac or what was the Windows version that was not the Windows version. Can you remember?
Confibrillator. That's it. Confibrillator widgets. It was confibrillator for Windows 2, I think.
After a while. So it's very much like that. Not as pretty of course. That's typical. But that's,
that's not far off, I guess, if we have enough people involved. So there's what else is there.
I'd like status bars and things. And there's an RSS reader that comes with a device.
And I've subscribed to my channel from my collection on PodShow Plus. So I have an on the
go channel. And in this channel, I've got New York Times, some CNN podcast. New York Times from
page that is, I've got a couple of my favorite PodShow podcast. I'm Pacifico's the hell way
is in there. You know, stuff that when I'm either walking to the office, I can listen to some
shorter ones or if I'm riding to the UK office on the train, then a PCH is perfect for that.
And in this feed reader, it has a widget on the home page. And when you, you can see the
story show up and you click on it, then it opens up the full blown interface, which is still pretty
small on the N800. But it had, it even displays the little icon, the little PodShow headphone
head. And so what I've discovered is, and this thing updates every 30 minutes, it does it
through a known Wi-Fi connection. So that's either here at the office or other places where
I've, you know, it's set up a, where I've accessed the Wi-Fi before or through my cell phones.
So it's always getting the most, you know, the most recent version of the feed. And what I find
myself doing is, you know, just before I leave, I look at it and say, oh, let me see, okay, here's
two shows I want and I just click on them and it's a save and you save it. And if you're on the Wi-Fi,
it's put, you know, that goes pretty quick. At least it does, it does now. And then you can take
them on your walk. So it really is pretty much that dream device almost, you know, wherever I'm
near Wi-Fi spot, it's like my iPod filling station. Very cool. And, you know, and it's kind of like an
oversized iPod. There you go. Okay, I wanted to talk just briefly at this point about the
controversy going on in the United Kingdom. And I'm really kind of bummed that I'm not there
right now that I wasn't able to see the past week of big brother, celebrity big brother,
because this sparked off a huge, huge media frenzy in the UK. And I totally saw this coming and
just wish I was there. Let me give you a little bit of background for those of you who are
not familiar. Well, you're probably familiar with big brother and the concept of celebrity big brother.
The celebrities in the house, Leo Sayer, a dirt Benedict based from 18, Germaine Jackson,
Julio, I forgot her last name, Milf, Shoot, who else is in there. How a mannequin, remember.
Okay, Shilpa Shetty, she's a Bollywood starlet. Actually quite a quite a successful actress,
at least according to Wikipedia. She's been in the business for 14 years. I think kind of a personal
challenge for her this as well. She's always been in exactly the right movies.
At least that's what I read. And a winner of the regular big brother show from two years ago,
I think, two and a half, three years ago, Jade Goodie. And Jade, and in the UK, it's fantastic
how these things can happen. It's very easy. It's not very easy, but there are a number of
people just famous for being famous without any real entertainment related talent. And Jade was
exactly that. I think very aspirational because she became a star. And then you write a book.
And then the UK, you sell them million copies pretty easy of a book. She had a perfume and it
works. And I think she was kind of a hero of a very large group of women, most likely.
But, I don't think there's any way you can be delicate about a conversation like this.
But I think in the US would be considered trash, trailer trash. And in fact, in the UK,
maybe they would call her chavey. No, I don't know. But there's still a lot of class differences
that are quite clear in the United Kingdom. And that's just historical. And that's not really
what the issue is here. So, oh yeah, there was also a girlfriend of a soccer player,
what they would call in the UK a wag, as in wives and girlfriends. So, kind of like, you know,
someone you might expect, posh byst to hang out with. But of course, she actually has hung out
with Jade Goody. I didn't mind even going through all this. She hung out with Jade Goody for about a
year, because, you know, they're of the same ill, I guess. So, anyway, so there's always a lot going on.
And what's happening now with with with big brother is we're seeing some things. It's become
such human nature to be on the in in these types of situations, even for people who,
you know, even for people who have never been in that situation to do a reality show. I mean,
our culture is changing around us. This is just happening. And we're also interpreting this data
when we watch it on television, in a very different way. And we're also forgetting things,
namely that it's on television. And lots of things that are said in a 24 hour situation with
cameras on a full time are not said with the knowledge of, hey, this is actually something I'm
saying to a rather large audience. Interestingly enough, the audience numbers were somewhat
down around the three millions. And I think the best, the best big brother episodes or series
have all been between the six and the eight million, which is a pretty decent size audience for
the UK. So, there's numbers happen to be down. And there was some some fireworks and some stuff
going on. And if you're listening to this on serious stars 102, I'm so sorry. You can have to
download the podcast at dailysourceco.com to hear the rest. So,
I shouldn't try to be slick, because then I lose my train of thought.
Okay, so there's, there's some misunderstandings in the house.
Shilpa Shetty is Indian. And she speaks impeccable English with, I would say, a pretty typical
Indian accent. And she's been the one that's cooking and she's been making stuff that she
that she wanted to eat, which is more than likely culturally different and different in many ways
than from what Jade and Danielle, the wag. Oh, that. What they're used to eating.
And anyway, so what happens is that they get into bickering fights. I've been in this house for like,
15 days. And they're going nuts. There's just a lot of shit going on. And these two girls
Jade Goodie and, and also Joe from, what does she, what's she from S club seven or so? I mean,
just three peas in a pot, I would say. You know, they're talking trash and they're talking
behind her back and they're saying nasty things and they're making fun of the way she talks. And,
and, you know, I can't even, I don't even want to paraphrase, let alone try and get the exact
quotes. It doesn't matter. It's the way people often talk when they're not being viewed by millions
and millions across Britain. And so, of course, this catches fire, you know, slow newsweek,
right? Of course, there's no one dying in Iraq anywhere. There's no bombs going off. So,
you know, let's make a big deal out of this. But it got all the way up to,
was it Gordon Brown, I think, made comments. He said, you know,
I mean, so here's the debate. People were saying, oh, the show should be taken off the air.
She should be evicted. Well, it boiled to a point where Jade Goodie, so this is the world who
came from nowhere, became a superstar thanks to Big Brother. Now, with an overwhelming 86% of the
vote has been evicted from the Big Brother house. And she, her life is as good as destroyed by
Big Brother, of course, which I guess, in a way, is all of us. And she's gone and I've talked
to Patricia, so I only know this second hand, but she's going on every chat show that she can.
And this tears are flowing. And she says, oh, now that I see the tapes, it's so horrible,
I'm exactly the, I was behaved exactly like the kind of person I love. And so that, so I had to give
you that background otherwise it makes no sense. Because it is an important point that I want to
make with, with what's happening with the way media is injected into our lives and how we view it.
And what we think is real and not real. And what I heard on Big Brother, I hear all the time
in the UK, all the time. And I wouldn't say, I wouldn't go so far to say, I hear racism all the time,
but well, here's what I hear most commonly. Oh, I don't mind foreigners, but I wish they could
speak English. If only they would speak English, boy, they can't speak English. What are they doing here?
And that, of course, is a very dangerous route of something, but there's no denying it. And Patricia,
I have noticed this for the past two and a half years. We hear this a lot and we're pretty amazed.
You know, you come into a country fresh and also you start to pick up a little bit of things,
you know, and everyone hates Tony Blair. I mean, everybody I talked to hates him. I mean, really
angry with him. And I hear this a lot about foreigners. Now, don't forget, if you look at the
history of the United Kingdom, and they have paranoid about rabies for a thousand years,
and it is an island, you know, and for some reason, well, for lots of reasons, I guess, there's a
culture of maybe we should call it protectionism or nationalism, but it's not really racism.
And then some of the words may be inappropriate. You know, when you make fun of someone's accent,
and I got to admit, I find myself doing it, too. You know, we'll be sitting there watching
big brother. And the show, a show by Shetty, she's stunningly beautiful. She's incredibly smart,
very well-spoken, just beautiful. But you can't just help yourself, you know, when we're sitting
on the couch and we'll be like, oh, I can't even do it. I feel so bad. I can't even do it.
I feel horrible. But you know, you do it. And I don't get offended. It's funny, because I don't
get offended when Brits do an American accent. You know, and it's the same thing, totally taking
the piss out of everything that, you know, is Yankee Doodle, Dandy Impression, you know, and
we do the same thing about Brits, particularly about the way people, so you talk funny, it's funny.
That's why they call it talking funny. But what I'm a little worried about is that this conversation
is not going to be held, that Pete, you know, that, oh, you know what, we're just going to vote
Jade Goodie off. We're going to, you know, destroy her, and she was a really, you know, channel all of
our bad, bad thoughts, and our guilt onto this girl. I'm no fan of her. I told you that,
I do not like no talents on television thinking that they got talent, you know, and maybe it's
my own, maybe it's a fatherly instinct. Like, get away, you're going to get hurt, you know, one day
you're going to wake up and you know, you're going to realize you have no talent for this job,
and it's going to really, really, really suck. And so she's meeting that, you know, she literally
met her maker, but I feel bad because the debate, the discussion can be over. There is
this culture in Britain, and it's all, you know, and it's in different countries for different
reasons. I saw this in the Netherlands throughout the years, first it was the Italians, and then it
was, and I had it myself in 1972, you know, I looked funny, I talked funny, I come from the America,
the dollar was worth five gilders, you know, was an extremely powerful rich country,
yeah, man, the kids would beat me up. You crazy American, that's what they would always say.
You know, it was a weird time people didn't like Americans there, and but it wasn't racism,
it was just, you know, fucking kids, you know, when you talk funny, you look funny, and I'm going
to go beat your ass. I'm not trying to say that, you know, any of that's right, but let's have the
conversation about what we really think and what we really feel and guess what, we could have a
really intelligent conversation with everyone around the table, because, you know, unlike other
countries in the continent, there actually is quite an amazing amount of integration that's gone
on and Britain, certainly the hub around London is multicultural, and I think a damn good multicultural
society. I'm not living there for no reason. It's expensive. How, but of course, expensive keeps the
riff raf out. You know, we don't want any of the poor near us. Anyway, so, um, I don't know,
I wish I was in the UK, so I could follow it a little bit more closely, but I heard the BBC this
morning. I, uh, that's another one on my on my go channel, uh, the BBC a breakfast, um, which is video,
and it's highlights from the, from the morning news. Oh, I love it. This podcasting shit. It's really
good. Anyway, in line with all that, I want to play a song. This is what I talked about the other
day. The song from, uh, that I picked up off of the weekend edition of I Love The Company,
David Epilito. I think it's the lovely Lisa. I mean, you could check out his site. She's got pictures
of his co-host. I think she's his girlfriend now. I LTC.podshow.com. So, he played a song by, uh, I'm sorry.
I'm totally spacing Schwartz. It's it. What's the first name? Uh, uh,
Schwartz. Okay. I'll look it up while I'm playing the song. I'm sorry. It's a little late for me.
And this is the same guy that did, uh, Clinton got a blowjob, which I also played on, uh, on the show.
So, this is not on the podcast music network, but it's so incredible. And go out and buy it.
If it's on iTunes, I looked all over his site. I couldn't find it. It's kind of long. It fits well
with this whole discussion. Oh, I'm doing it.
Oh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh uh, uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh
af uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh維
to the station. You're pointing with the broomstick as a standard operation and thought
you'd hide your violence. Behind that big blue wall of silence but and now you're
rumored with some of the bitches you've been rumored. I applaud the situation but I wouldn't
take a bow. Just tell me officer, a houda bitch now, whoa yeah I won't you tell me
officer, a houda bitch now, a say cheese, houda bitch now,
Eric Schwartz of course, Eric Schwartz.com I'll put a link in the show notes at
dailysourcecode.com. Thanks to David, Aprilito, pulled that straight out of a show episode
197 the weekend edition. I also placed the wet spots and that show awesome. I love them.
I love all the guys he hangs out with. I don't buddy so tomorrow. What are we doing tomorrow?
Oh yeah, so doing a shoot tomorrow got like a demo thing for Intel playing around. I'm gonna
show them some cast blaster video. That's what it was. I lost this stuff. So dailysourcecode.com
is where you can find the show notes. Atomitpodshow.com for all your warm goodness. Wait a
minute. Let me do this differently. Here we go. You know Brian knows the nose own. He writes
these awesome things. Let me see where is it. I'm not as well just do this. Okay, I'll try
this way. So Atomitpodshow.com is the email address to let go of all your doubt and self-loathing.
And you can find abundant life and a great deal on a classic automobile at dailysourcecode.com.
Take care everybody. I'll talk to you tomorrow. Bye bye.
That's crap.
You