Hey home fries, it's CC Chapman from accident hash, encouraging you to check out
BODOD.tv slash battle.
It's one of the coolest battle events out there, and you can only find it at BODOD.tv.
Hmm, 644, volunteer gliding school, Northern Ireland.
I don't have to check that out for Adam.
Let's see, it's at the R-A-F-Sireston Newark Nautspace.
Let's see, about how far is that going to be for Adam.
Let's see, that's not too bad, that's only 375 miles.
That's like a hop skip and a jump in the Delta Sierra Charlie.
Oh, by the way, this is Delta Sierra Charlie 644.
You got the DSC 643, and you said that you want more?
Well, who could it be?
But my man AC with the Charlie 644.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying, just enjoy it.
On casting, it's not a hurry.
Waste to know this time when it shouldn't have been all.
Trying to drive the runway for runway streets.
You bring me all just like I was a feather.
When you put it all together your heart to be.
If I knew then what I know now.
I'd cheat suit your plans.
Then I found out.
Okay.
And maybe I was born a loser.
And maybe you don't want me.
But all I ever tried to do is make it happy.
And now I'm going to lose you.
But that's okay for me.
So I have a wanted to do.
Just make it happy.
Baby watch out to beat so wicked.
Telling all these lies trying to suit.
So excuse me, if that's much ain't unravel.
Or wait you just to come with someone like me.
If I knew then what I know now.
I'd tell I know your plans.
It's time to round you again.
And maybe I was born a loser.
And maybe you don't want me.
But all I ever tried to do is make it happy.
And now I'm going to lose you.
But that's okay for me.
So I have a wanted to do.
Just make it happy.
You know you's crying for you.
Your build is great.
And maybe you don't want me.
But all I ever tried to do was make it happy.
And now I'm going to lose you.
But that's okay for me.
So I have a wanted to do.
Just make it happy.
And now I'm going to lose you.
But that's okay for me.
So I have a wanted to do.
Just make it happy.
Oh.
Hi.
And maybe I was born a loser.
And maybe you don't want me.
But all I ever tried to do is make it happy.
And now I'm going to lose you.
That's okay for me.
So I have a wanted to do.
Just make it happy.
Oh.
You can always leave it up.
Here's the time to make us all happy.
Excellent.
Sir talk.
Jericho.
California.
I just want to be happy.
She comes from Los Angeles.
I'm just reading from the pod safe.
Music network liner notes here.
I'll send just California her own edge to pop rocks.
She's just released the five song EP and iTunes.
We'll also be releasing a full length album in the fall.
Really only a matter of time before we see Jericho in the mainstream of things.
I got to tell you.
I see you're in a lot of things already.
Mm-hmm.
If you want to see it go to dailysourcecode.com.
Check out the link.
You'll see what I'm talking about.
Hey, everybody.
It is episode number 644.
It's late here in the UK.
Not really that late for the hours I've been keeping recently.
But it's a quarter past 10 in the evening.
And I'm doing one for you.
We're still going to squeak out for today.
Although tomorrow's football will also be a late night show.
So kind of adjusted for the mood and for the mood.
I had promised Patricia and myself really today.
We're going to do something different because it's,
Oh, man, we've been almost going stir crazy in the house in the manner, of course.
I mean, it doesn't suck that bad.
But, you know, the weather has been, been rotten.
Her parents have been here for a little over a week now and still have,
well, just under a week to go.
And Patricia had a few things she wanted to do in Holland.
So, so now you know what?
Weather permitting.
I'll fly over and I'll pick up on Saturday.
So we did that.
And as you know, the good lady Patricia, although she loves to fly alone with me,
has a bad vibe about just the two of us crossing the channel.
So I took Captain Daniel along for the ride.
It was beautiful today.
It was what a fabulous, right?
In fact, it was so smooth.
It was almost boring.
Really.
There was not one speck of turbulence at all.
You know, it was take off at Farrow.
So I think we were airborne about,
what is it about?
About 10 a.m. this morning.
And, uh, flipped on the autopilot and a couple of adjustments.
And it was nice.
I mean, there was no one in the sky.
The controllers were all really friendly.
They were happy with some nice weather for a change.
We got all kinds of clearances, you know,
to fly overhead, Rotterdam.
We actually went up to Hilversum.
So that's where, you know, it's really close to end.
In fact, it's easier to go into Hilversum.
Not to mention less complex, less hassle and certainly cheaper when it comes to landing fees.
It's like, I think Amsterdam is 250 euros these days.
Just to land and the Hilversum is almost like a contribution.
In fact, that much rather fill up the gas tanks there,
because they're, they're like a club, you know,
and they can use every single penny.
And it's literally pennies that they make on fuel.
So dropped right there.
Had a nice lunch outside.
It was good to see taxi Eric, good old T to the E.
I reencame over.
She's, uh, yet another beautiful bankman,
beautiful blonde bank manager.
Well, it's not actually completely blonde.
So there we were, hanging out.
We were in a good time.
There was some glider activity going on.
So goodbye to my lovely wife and Dan and I hop back in the Delta share
and flew back.
And it was, as I said, it was, you know,
like completely uneventful.
We kind of came in.
It was starting to rain here and there.
And to see, we wheels down at like a 330 quarter four.
And since then, I've been on the phone.
And of course, now the in-laws are here.
It's just the in-laws and myself.
Oh, man, I love him dearly.
But wow, they got lots of questions.
And they ask him, uh, the same question a lot.
And now the dishwasher's broken.
And it's like, yeah, it's like, oh, man.
You know how it is within laws.
They're really sweet, though.
So a little more mellow show.
I would say, uh, then then you're normally used to just because.
Oh, frankly, I'm tired.
And tomorrow morning, I'm out the door at 10, man.
It's, uh, got all kinds of stuff going on in the city.
It's, it's, it's just going to be that way for a while longer.
Certainly until the 15th when the ladies and I head off, uh,
to upstate New York for the big curry reunion.
Adam, this is Chris Christensen from the Amateur Traveler podcast.
In light of the recent podcast award nomination,
it seemed a good time to remember to be thankful to you and to
Pod Show for the help that you've gotten for the sport of the show,
which I'm sure helped get the numbers that led to the nominations.
Thanks for that.
Rather than just call and pimped the show,
I have an outtake from the show that will never play on the Amateur Traveler.
That just for some reason, and I don't know why.
I thought perhaps you and your listeners might enjoy this.
This is an outtake from the show on Kingston, Ontario.
And it's talking about the number of prisons they have in Kingston.
Including what was previously Canada's only prison for women.
Also called P4W.
Until it was shut down, and now there's a nice penal museum there.
Do you know what's going on here at Kingston?
Sorry, that just kind of sounded bad.
Penal museum, uh, I should probably rephrase that.
There goes, there goes the clean deck.
I, you know, I should do more penis jokes.
That'll get me nominated.
Awards of funny things.
You know, there's the British Telecom, digital musical awards that are coming up in,
I think it's September or October.
And we actually did a live stream from them last year.
We didn't have a lot of setup time, not a lot of promo time.
So, you know, actually I thought the streams were great,
but we made some fundamental production mistakes.
And really weren't able to bake anything out of the material that we had recorded.
And so, you know, really couldn't have any extra shelf life with it.
So you either saw the stream or you kind of missed it all.
So we're doing that differently this year.
Now, they have a podcast award, which they also had last year.
We had like zero influence over, you know, how the mechanics work of the award.
And just actually had a really great call this evening with some folks over B.T.
And I said, look, you know, if we really want to make this a real award,
we got to do some real things with it and make sure that it's like, you know, independent.
And you know, let's not have mainstream shows nominated.
You know, this is kind of like the independent thing you, you know,
you are beyond that independent tip of the vibe.
I'll convince them somehow.
They want to do all the right stuff.
So it would be great to have a really cool award that that is on, you know,
it's televised and it gets a lot of press.
And it would be great to have someone who's really making a show out there.
You know, beating the street, doing whatever they have to do and, you know,
just full of passion would be great to have someone like that win that award.
And, you know, I come up on stage and accept the award.
You know, like cool stuff.
Because it's certainly a big to do, a big shabang.
Hey, I got this one from a number of people.
Elton John, this is, I don't understand this.
This kind of sounds like he was maybe misquoted.
You know, one of these things that's just going to get around.
Now, the article is from the Sun, which is, you know, it's like the largest tabloid
newspaper in all of the United Kingdom.
But, you know, this is something that all the gossip blogs and
and everyone reads all over the world.
And so this will be copied and this will be watered down and made even worse.
But essentially, the headline is,
the pop legends are Elton John wants the internet closed down.
He claims it is destroying good music by saying and I quote from the Sun.
The internet has stopped people from going out and being with each other, creating stuff.
Instead, they sit at home and make their own records, which is sometimes okay,
but it doesn't vote well for long term artistic vision.
It's just a means to an end.
Remember we were talking about old people.
You know, and then Elton John's not that much older than I am.
But this this reeks of like, you know, just old stupid old man stuff.
If you really said it.
And I find it a hard time thinking that he really was that, you know, shallow about it.
But he says, I'm such a lullite when it comes to making music all I can do is write it to piano.
And then, of course, the Sun is quick to point out sales of Elton's last album,
the Captain, the kid.
We're disappointing.
It barely shifted 100,000 copies.
And in the past, Sir Elton has opposed illegal downloading of his music from the net.
Yeah, whatever.
It's not about downloading.
It's just about, I don't think him understanding.
And I, of course, agree in disagree.
I disagree.
I think, you know, what we're doing online is amazing.
We're touching, you know, each other deep into hearts and souls.
And the more often than you realize and exposing beautiful and ugly emotions all the time,
which, of course, completely feeds creativity.
But yeah, you know, there's a lot of signal to signal to noise ratio is out of whack.
And there's a lot of craps here.
I think I've always said it's got to get a whole lot worse before it gets better.
And maybe Sir Elton just can't see past the, the period of a whole lot worse.
Because yeah, we have, it's going to be worse.
There's a lot, a lot more fun stuff to come.
Hi.
And this is my world, one of your Italian guys.
I was listening to your 640, the SC, and I see that you're getting busy with your chat
or a congratulation, I'm glad to find it.
I'm calling you as well from my iPhone, which I love as well.
And I remember something that you mentioned something about loving to receive book
from advisors.
And I have a good one because I was a reading one for my clients.
And I know that this is going to be a little bit on the line of what you do in your business.
This is called the balance scorecard from Robert Chaplin and David Norton.
This is what talks all about metrics of how to get to busy and get things going,
especially for your chatters, maybe it's going to be a good point.
But you have a problem with your business because you're very successful.
I'm glad to hear and I love your shows.
Listen to all of what you do.
But I know that I'm sure that you will be loving to read this book.
Anyway, congratulations and thanks.
Oh man, don't know.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I've heard of the book and I'll definitely, I'll order it through Amazon and get a copy.
And as of, I have my cheat sheet here.
I'll send me this.
Prendi la pilorosa.
There you go.
Which means take the red pill, by the way.
Let me see.
There were a couple of new stories that were relatively interesting.
When I'm out and about, I still have time to check the Google reader, the mobile version.
Let me see.
We did the performers royalties, right?
Did that yesterday.
A lot of, a lot of press coming out about, what is this?
How, I think this, this is like a Hollywood story.
It's talking about how consumers, I love it how they talk about consumers.
How about just fucking audience?
How about people, dude?
Consumers want professionally produced video.
Okay.
I think there may be some fatigue of YouTube stuff.
But, you know, the bottle rocket shootin' out of the ass, I'm sorry.
It just gets me every single time.
I should try that myself one day.
Don't hate the hell, hate the racer actor.
Come on.
Hey there, you trap on studs and studs.
This is Brett.
And this is Emily.
From this in and out of the trap on podcast.
And we're here to remind you to vote for us in the helping fitness category at podcastawards.com.
That's right.
You can vote now to August 11th and you can vote once a day, every day.
I don't know, baby.
I think we're going to have a lot of trouble winning this time.
Why that?
Because there's another podcast in the same category for sex and the title.
What?
We maybe we should rename our podcast to sex and the art of the channel.
Yeah, or sin in the art of sex at the end.
We'll just remember to go vote for sin in the art of triathlon at podcastawards.com.
Vote for us.
Oh, man.
Throwing you with iPods, trapped each knee.
Throwing your kid in.
That's just wrong.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Do you really mean us?
Let's get an iPods, grab these knee.
This is so not good.
I think we got to stop this.
This whole pimping for votes.
It just makes no sense.
It's just, what was that listing?
A Pacifico's hell away.
Someone registered with a go daddy domain podcast circle jerk.com
and pointed it towards the podcast awards.
Oh, yay.
Let's see.
This, you know, I was waiting for this type of comment to come in or this type of question.
I thought it took quite a long time and I've been, you know, kind of quiet about this
because I've just been watching in the sidelines.
But it's good that someone asked the question.
I didn't visit as a command work.
I was just going in for something.
I saw last week.
Apparently Michael Arlington's off the crunch was doubting on the blog.
Whether I thought tech.net was actually a viable business any longer.
And got in a whole hoopla with the boat, the CEO and Robert Skobel.
And I was wondering what your take was on the whole matter.
And how does a pot tech compare to a pot show of course.
All right, man.
Take care and talk you later.
Bye.
Well, you know, I've been following that a little bit.
I think it's kind of died down by now.
But, you know, this is, it's a, I feel kind of bad because
I know what it likes to be on.
What it's like to be on the receiving end of, you know, some, some controversy.
And, you know, it's like all companies,
uh, fuck stuff up, make mistakes, you know.
And, and there's this little circle of, of blogginess and, and,
uh, it's like, you know, it's kind of like the tech news industry.
It feels like it's resonating around itself and kind of whirling in,
in the same continuous circle.
And the same people are all kind of talking to each other or
whatever, you know, whatever.
But this stuff does get picked up by, by other people,
um, you know, considering, you know, it's in the way it's presented.
You know, now we have, uh, was it valley wag?
Um, so we have our own little, I don't know, kind of gossipy,
news, circuit type thing.
And, you know, at the same time, there's like real employees working at companies
and, uh, and, you know, and you can only,
uh, obviously that everyone works really hard and whatever they believe in,
whatever they're trying to do and all this stuff is kind of distracting.
And it's, it kind of feels a little bit like armchair quarterbacking
in a way.
Uh, but that, that's also kind of the entertainment value of it.
It's just, I, I wonder, you know, how big is the audience is really
entertained and entertained by these controversies.
I don't think it's very big.
I don't think a lot of people really care all that much.
Um, I certainly watched lots of podcast programming.
Because they seem to talk about me a lot.
So that's fun.
Um, but, uh, you know, it's like, if we're going to build an industry,
we're going to need a lot of different players and players with all kinds of different
expertise.
So, um, it seems to me like, uh,
podcast has a reasonable, uh, business model.
Um, it's not the same as, as pod shows.
Um, and, uh, and I enjoy the programming.
Uh, not always the production values, but I certainly enjoy a lot of what's being
said.
And I'm a geek like that.
So, you know, I kind of belong in the geek circle.
And, and if that's the audience, then that's great.
You know, that may be a very, very valuable audience.
I just think it's a little small.
So that, yeah, that's really it, you know.
Uh, but, you know, this is just a lot of a lot of noise
spinning around.
And I think people trying to, you know, get stuff to catch fire and
uh, I don't know.
It's all a part of, uh, what media is becoming.
You know, we like to dissect things.
Take things apart.
You know, and doesn't really matter whether it's Brittany Spears or
John Furrier.
Oh, my god.
What kind of comparisons am I making?
Hey, Adam.
It's Bernie.
And you asked in DSC 643, if I would take on the task of putting
together a widget for you to play channels and windows.
Unfortunately, they don't make a tinfoil hat in my size.
I'm really more of a content guy, not that much of a gear head.
But I am getting ready to set up some channels.
Now, it might take me a little while.
So I encourage you while you're waiting for me to get it all together.
Smoke them if you got them.
Thanks for thinking of me.
Can't wait to see that channel, Bernie.
No, man, thanks.
You know, that's cool.
I got a couple other people who are, you know, working on some stuff.
And it's not all that, uh, it's not trivial to do this in in
Windows with iTunes.
But, uh, you know, if someone out there is going to be able to
figure it out, you know, I'm sure they're going to let me know about it.
And look forward to your channels.
In fact, you know, this thing has been stable.
It seems to be working.
I got to tell you, uh, it's really saved my life when it comes to staying
current on episodes.
Um, you know, there's much less to wade through.
I can, you know, just pull up the, the XML of the, you know, the feed.
I can pull it up on my iPhone that works perfectly.
I have been religiously sinking with iTunes so far, so
good.
Probably because the channels are now limited.
You know, you don't have tons of episodes coming through.
So it really, yeah, it is kind of working for me.
So I hope it's working for for anyone else who's put a channel
together.
Um, I think we're going to put the get channel functionality in
sometime next week.
I think we're ready for it.
Everything else seems to be working.
So, uh, and now that, of course, is one stuff gets to get,
it starts to get really exciting.
Um, one of the play this year, yesterday, but after the whole
young, polite thing, uh, didn't really feel up to it.
But there's a new band on the podcast music network.
And, uh, my good friend, uh,
Petty Love is going to tell you all about it.
Hey, Adam Petty Love from Lovehouse Radio.
For the past two years, I've been
according to band Carbon Leaf to post music on the PMN
and share it with the podcasting world.
You might recognize Carbon Leaf.
They hold the distinction as being the first
unsigned band to win an American Music Award
and perform in the AMAs.
Aside from that honor, they have created
some great music and developed quite a following in the
States.
Well, and from a personal note, I just happened to have
gone to college with several of the band members.
Anyway, in my attempts to get them on the PMN,
I started making some headway
and explaining what podcasting and pot safe music
were and kind of leave the whole concept around it.
A couple of months ago, they said they would
reach out to the record company, Vanguard records
to see if there were any objections.
Well, in order to strike when the iron was hot,
I put together a show dedicated to their music
based on some previous permissions they gave me
to play their music on Lovehouse Radio.
With that, I created a contest
based on listener sending emails
to the band, urging them to make some of their music
pod safe.
Well, finally it worked.
With just one email to Terry in the band,
he responded and said that they
cleared everything with their record label
and had posted several songs in the pod safe
music network.
So to celebrate this task, this feat,
I asked that you obliged me by playing
the song they performed on the American Music Awards.
The song is called The Boxer,
and it's a good representation of what
Carbon Leaf has to offer.
A lot of musical talent, a lot of vocal talent,
and just a lot of variety.
So Adam, if you could have obliged me,
I would have appreciated it,
and I'm sure the band would have appreciated it
if we had a chance to share with your listeners
a little carbon leaf.
So here's The Boxer.
We could have asked for a better day
to buy two to the ring to the right.
I'd up here, we'd retreat to the corner
that's the fine tie you to the ring to the right.
The point of the ring,
the point of the ring,
The passion left to burn
The boxers go with me
Their eyesight breaks
Now we remain
Sheels the boxers she knows
When and where to strike
He is the boxer he knows
No peaceful sleep to night
While twilight on the front smoke
He will box a standing tall
Here in through binding
No one around the fight
What to do to the ring to the right
Point of view
Long we remain
Sheels the boxers she knows
When and where to strike
Heels the boxer he knows
No peaceful sleep to night
Long we remain
and Twitter posts. We've been trying to reach him since we were alerted, but so far
I've had no luck. We've been in contact with the highway patrol down there and are anxious
to hear of his whereabouts. This is a very, very serious situation. And I've been totally
disgusted by the heartless comments and the terrible treatment Nick has received from some
of those in the podcast in community. Why must some people have to tick? Why must some people
have to tear others down to the point of total destruction before they realize that they
behave you could have deadly repercussions? Does it make you feel good hurting other people?
Are you truly that pathetic? We hope that Nick is safe and offer whatever help he needs to
get to a better place. I just pray it isn't too late. Man, this is a serious shit going on here.
Okay, so I don't know the backstory to this, but I guess some elements within the quote podcast
in community have been really mean to the guy. Now, if you read the Twitter posts, this is like,
this is pretty scary. So, you know, it's like, it's all from the last 24 hours and he's talking
about, I'm a fat mess. No wonder I haven't been on dating for years. I'm pretty drunk. Now,
consider anything from here on out, a drunk Twitter post and then a little bit further on
finally made it to my coffee shop. busy day was in the newspaper and cop talked to me last night
about being homeless. There's a nice high skyway bridge nearby. I've heard of plenty of people
jumping from it. Maybe I should give it a try tonight. And then, you know, you move up a like two hours.
All right, I'm out Twitter. Time to catch a few more drinks and debate jumping from a bridge tonight.
Sunshine skyway bridge here I come. The next one, just paid the toll for the skyway bridge.
Should I stop at the top? What should I do with my car? I guess I leave it there.
Then the next one, has there ever been a Twitter suicide before? I wonder what I would write as I'm
falling to my death? And then the last post, the last Twitter tweet or whatever the frickie
call it. All right, this is it. Part my car. I wish everyone who was ever nice to me well.
See you in the next life. Posted 20 hours ago. And then that's messed up.
This needs further investigation. Now, I'm going to call Don and Drew and find out what's going on.
And I'll update you tomorrow. It may be a very food bard Friday. I certainly hope Nick is okay.
That's messed up. All right, DaddySourceco.com. You can find the link to all that stuff over there.
And Adam at podshow.com. If you have anything else for me, I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Everybody take care. Be safe.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.
The best and the brightest.
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering podshow and limelight.