Hey, this is Michael Butler from the Rock and Roll Geek Show.
Check out one of my favorite TV shows this summer,
Bow Dog Music Battle of the Band.
It's a competition with Johnny Rotten as one of the judges,
and that is quality television, my friends.
Find out more at bowdog.tv slash battle.
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
It's Adam here from the Curry Condo in San Francisco.
No cow.
It's going to be a short show today.
This is episode number six, five,
nineer of the Daily Source Code.
And it's going to be a short show because,
well, this morning I went to the office right in early,
really energized and completely ready to just dive headfirst
into the thick of things, and it was a real good vibe around the office,
and it was really nice people were congratulating me on my birthday.
I got a nice gift from the company and some flowers.
Went out to lunch with Ron,
and I got a text message from Christina.
And what that message said really took the wind out of me,
quite honestly, which is, well, right now it's,
what is it, it's seven, 15 and the evening on Tuesday,
and you know, so I finished out the day and came back home
and just figured just about the only thing I could do,
we've been through so much together on this show,
if you think about it,
it's shared with you because that's,
it's a way for me to get it off my chest.
One of our cats, Cindy,
and you've seen pictures of them on,
and it's Cindy with an S, by the way,
for Sinbad, I guess, or whatever, but Cindy is his name.
I was hit by a car and killed this evening.
And for those of you who have pets,
you know, we've had Cindy with us for 14 years,
13 or 14 years.
I actually found him in New Jersey,
in a bath, in a gas station, men's room.
In a box, he was maybe two or three weeks old,
completely infected eye,
and he was really being eaten up by infection,
you know, pretty much close to death, and of course,
way too young to be without a mom.
And we took him in,
and Patricia and I and Christina,
who was very young at the time.
We basically nursed him to health,
and he became just an incredible animal,
and a real friend,
and just so strong,
and he's been through so many different moves with us,
you know, from America to Amsterdam,
he's lived in so many crazy,
and in a way, dangerous places,
and I guess this was just
a wrong time, wrong place.
And of course,
you know, really distressing for Christina and for Patricia,
and I hate it.
I really can't tell you how
emotional I am that I'm not there.
And, you know,
it's all these little things you think about,
and this is like a kid, man.
He's like part of our family.
And, you know,
so animals, particularly after many years,
you know, you start to,
I guess when the no longer there is when you really think about it,
but you start to notice that they do all kinds of fun things,
you know,
and Cindy loved to drink water out of the tap.
You always hop up on Patricia's sink in evening,
and you have to turn the water on,
just the right stream,
so that he can stick his head under there,
and drink from it.
God knows why.
You know,
if Christina was upstairs with a boyfriend,
he would always sit right in between the middle of them,
you know, kind of keeping out of watchful eye,
it really is just just a really great,
great cat,
great pet,
great,
we have friend really.
And that's,
and that's really the thing with all animals,
you know,
all they want to really do is,
just feed them,
please,
and they just want to be your buddy.
They just want to,
you know,
love it,
and it's all very simple,
and honest,
and you know,
that's something that you can always count on from a pet.
So,
I really, really miss him.
This is,
and I'm going to miss him.
And,
I really just sucks.
So,
I'm going to play a song for Cindy,
and for all of us to share
in his memory.
Thank you for being a friend.
Traveled down a road
and back again,
your heart is true,
you're a pal,
and a confidence.
I'm not ashamed to say,
I hope it always will stay this way.
My heart is all full,
just stand up and take a bow.
And if you're through a party,
invite it everyone,
you know,
we,
you won't see the biggest difference between me,
and the card attached,
we'll say,
thank you for being a friend.
Thank you for being a friend.
If it's a car you lack,
I truly buy you a car lack,
whatever you need,
and a time of the day and night.
I'm not ashamed to say,
I hope it always will stay this way.
My heart is all full,
just stand up and take a bow.
And if you're through a party,
you know,
we won't see the biggest difference between me,
and the card attached,
we'll say,
thank you for being a friend.
Thank you for being a friend.
I want to thank you for being a friend.
I want to thank you.
Let me tell you about it.
Thank you for being a friend.
I want to thank you.
Thank you for being a friends.
I'm delivering,
in tonight.
From the beginning you will be gone, as we are, I'm so so sad, that once again, thank you for being here.
I want to thank you, thank you for being here, I want to thank you, thank you for being here, I want to thank you, thank you for being here, I want to thank you.
Thank you for being here, I want to thank you, thank you for being here, I want to thank you, thank you for being here, I want to thank you, thank you for being here, I want to thank you, thank you for being here, I want to thank you, thank you for being here, I want to thank you for being here, I want to thank you for being here, I want to thank you for being here, I want to thank you for being here, I want to thank you for being here, I want to thank you for being here, I want to thank you for being here, I want to thank you for being here, I want to thank you for being here, I want to thank you for being here, I want to thank you for being here, I want to thank you for being here, I want to thank you for being here, I want to thank you for being here, I want to thank you for being here, I want to thank you.
Thank you again, I want to thank you, thank you for being here, I've become friends.
Thank you Cindy for being a friend.
And you guys, in the audience, are always great about sending in notes.
I would appreciate it if you would, if you would, if you're going to, if you were thinking
of sending anything send a send an email to Patricia, that's you really needs it and
I can't be there for her in person and it would be highly appreciated Patricia at curie.com.
Okay, tomorrow we'll look at life in a whole new way and we'll start another day of the
rest of our lives.
Thanks.
Bye.
This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds and content delivery
Pajo in my life.