Check out some of the world's best music video animation that short films from the
mainjuts in the national festival and brought to you by Soviet police station at m-i-f-d-o-d-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o
o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-h-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-tcast
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
When I lived here, I was dreaming, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah,yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Above that hardcore dance that is got to be a little bit high control of the school
Damn it, but what about the food? The food's the food's the land
Give me a sauce on a mix, and if it ain't food, then don't try to fix it
And think of the summer's on the path, adjust the face and let the album out
Bob, it might be a deal, and let me write my name on it, put your phone on
To the way back, it's just summer time
Give me a sauce on a mix, and let me write my name on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your
put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on and it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, write your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on it, put your phone on
It's a magic, oh my something's all
You know, there's nothing quite like the summer sounds that the brothers John's in
Strawberry letter 23 and we'll smith summer time mashed up to kick off the daily source
coach for brand new week everybody how you doing coming to you from the Curry Coast it is
the daily source code episode number 653 it's going to be a rather short show today
for a number of reasons one of which is let me see oh yeah I'm on vacation that's
right thanks to Alex from the lowlands for sending that mash up off to me
so the weather is atrocious as was not expected but unfortunately yesterday
wasn't a brilliant day today being Monday what are we at the 20th of September
not a sorry August not that great it said the temperature is nice but it's
overcast and just a windy and I kind of sucks for a number of reasons because
you know of course perfect weather to sit inside and do a show and chill out
even crank up the fireplace however something with this island is quite disappointing
that would be all connectivity blows chunks I have the feeling and I've put
in a couple of calls to to the ISP here on the island barrier free and they
kind of confirm that it seems like well first of all everybody is probably inside
everybody's now you can hear an airplane going over everybody's check in
their email and surfing and download and stuff and oh yeah there's lots of
people have peer-to-peer programs running and when you're dealing with a
mesh network and pretty much everyone goes through one or two very thin tubes
to the mainland I guess what there's absolutely no connectivity I mean I can
literally sit here and watch the packets drop off I can I have a ping ping
timer set up and it's just timing out it's horrible and the most frustrating
thing is you know there's lots of stuff that works perfectly well for
instance Yahoo works well but Gmail forget about it completely crap I've tried
well the the Ajax version you can sit and wait for hours it'll never come
through the HTML version and once in a while part of it'll come through and I try
the mobile version let me see I actually just oh here we go yeah it finally
pop through a little bit I'm I can you believe it I'm actually surfing the
mobile version of Gmail however whenever I fire up iTunes it goes to download
the podcast I wait a minute now it seems that stuff is starting to pop in
for a second let me see I had a show ID for 653 for today it's you know maybe
there's one K per second coming through right now it's it's maddening but
whenever I fire up iTunes now it goes in and accesses media files directly no
problem it brings them in like three three megabits per second sometimes and
then I'll just break off and I is frustrating what kind of tell you so it'll be
a reasonably short show today because I couldn't get to the voicemail
comments I could you know obviously I could barely get through to to Gmail at
all to access any of the stuff that people have been sending in so oh yeah
and did I mention my sister is here now with her two kids age seven or
nine and that's fun for kids when it's a shitty outside in it no so I'm gonna
take them all we're gonna go to the mainland we're gonna take the ferry
across and we're going to hit them all which is what you do on a on a cloudy
rainy day and I'm bringing my laptop with me because I'm sure I'll be able
to find a Starbucks somewhere just so I can access my email just whip through
it downloads some stuff so at least I have enough for the next day or two
here's one that was small enough to come through the tubes hey Adam it's Chef
Mark and Jennifer and forget the overhead noise here but we are on American
Airlines back from Guadalajada we heard your podcast from Fira on your first
one and I just have to say immediately stay away from the deer yeah we
stayed away from the ice cubes and the water in Mexico and it wasn't for that but
there were ticks on those deer yeah and they're really lovely and they're
beautiful and you can't feed them from a distance but just don't get up close
and if you do make sure you check yourself for ticks afterwards but other than
that you're gonna have a great time in the minds and by the way I wanted to
thank you for giving your cooking part to me because I'm coming home for Mexico
with the perfect Margarita recipe mmm good later man I guess Chef Mark Jennifer
Yonola on the plane doing business off in Guadalajada Guadamala oh man please
Jennifer uh send smokesignals tell me how to make the Margaritas I need a couple
as soon as possible hey we had a great family reunion um actually here's the
thing I was looking for on Friday day from New York uh sent this in
hey yeah Adam it's Dave from New York how you doing bro I've been catching up on my
DSC's and I eat your comments in New York for the curry family reunion that's
great happy to have you but before you hop on that plane I think I need to
straighten you out on something you know I mean I have two tingles like the nylon but I
do know what I'm talking about most of the time okay you see you're gonna visit
Guadamala upstate in Almonds New York that's not quite right
Almonds just around the corner from me even west just the county about 30 miles
north from New York City so it's in the New York metropolitan area it's not
upstate remember New York is huge it's bigger than England the term upstate is
commonly used to refer to the majority of the state that isn't in the
New York metro area so we usually figure on it's at least a couple hours
drive out of the city before you're upstate anyway we're glad to have you
visit us here in Downstate New York let me know if you need to borrow another
Piaf 40 and a Mike Mixer for your Uncle Dawn interview I'm looking forward to
that to at least I could do for all the Charlie's to give in us all right
see ya love ya and uh bed pill no asparagus p and scruncher
Dave fantastic man yeah it was great it was great seeing all of my cousins
particularly now that we're all older you know we have a lot more
I don't know for some reason it seemed like we could relate a lot more to each other
and what I'm gonna do is maybe tomorrow the day after Petrish Niles sit down and
maybe I'll bring Willow in who's as I said she's here with her kids
and we'll talk about the reunion we'll reminisce just a little bit
uh because it really was fun it came believe that we actually wound up square dancing
you should have seen Petrish do a doze I know it was very very funny
so Uncle Dawn yes had some long conversations with him and uh came up with a little
different strategy than then just an interview and the main reason for it was he's also
thinking Uncle Dawn is now almost 80 years old of course he's extremely active he's still
the CEO of the Korea Society and as I've told you many times he is directly quite
responsible for calming down the situation in North Korea so just a note on that
when I acquired him on it he said you know North Korea the the political scene is actually
quite stable he says he thinks it's very stable you know more stable than than many regimes
but but in general the region is in in trouble you know they they have issues feeding their
people they have all kinds of horrible uh torrential rain problems that are
uprooting uh the landscape nothing sticking peep stuff is sliding people are dying so
it says not a fantastic scene but he does say the regime he feels is very very stable
and he's been thinking about writing a book now as you can understand and actually
I have it here he served in the CIA from 1951 to 1982 when he retired he received the CIA's
highest decoration directly from the director at the time William Casey so there's a lot of
things a lot of stories a lot of stuff that that he can talk about and there's a lot of things
that he can't talk about and as you know I said well look you know we'll just talk and then
I'll record everything and anything that you feel is inappropriate you know we'll destroy it we'll
get rid of it and he said you know he really feels like he wants to he because he's a master story
teller he wants to tell some stories but then he also feels like he maybe he wants to write a book
and I told him about what we're doing with pod show press and he was very interested
in basically creating an audio novel first and then publishing a book of the audio novel
which is the model that we've created with pod show press and I think we can get him to do that
but something that I'll do for you I got I wish I had my whole set up here because I really
would like to do a great recording of this he wrote a what he calls a commentary it's not really
review but a commentary on a book which you may have seen if not I recommend you go out and you
buy it because it'll be a great set up for what we're going to do with Uncle Don it's Tim Winer's
legacy of ashes and it's essentially it's a it's a book about the early days of the CIA
and it's about two and a half maybe three thousand words so it's something that he feels he
probably can't you know because he's he's been published in in all kinds of uh newspapers you know
he's often been quoted in uh washed and posed New York Times he sent in letters to the editor he
said you know this is really too long for a letter to the editor but he wouldn't mind if this
got out uh on the internet so I'm going to record the audio version of this and we'll kind of
call that a primer for what's coming let me just give you uh uh here we go let me just give you this
uh I'm going to read the first two paragraphs to you uh because that'll kind of set it up and you'll see
how exciting this is going to be so he says for someone who spent 31 years as a CIA operations officer
Tim Winer's legacy of ashes is a painful sometimes ugly read my wife that would be on Meg asked me
how it made me feel to read such a litany of failure about an organization that had taken us to
Sipan, Japan, Burma, Vietnam and Korea the most honest answer I can give to that question is
that winers meticulously researched book did not take me by surprise and that I cannot
quarrel with his basic conclusions my discomfort and shagrid come from the realization that things
were often far worse than I suspected them to be I joined the army 1945 at the age of 17 it was
trained as a cryptanalyst this led NSA to approach me in my senior year at Williams College to see
if I would like to resume that career I was interviewed in Washington by an NSA recruiter who quickly saw
that I had no interest in returning to the increasingly technical field of cryptography he advised
me to apply to the CIA an organization I had hardly heard of what's the CIA I asked his reply was
oh they a jump out of airplanes and are going to save the world I immediately applied to the CIA
and reported for duties two days for duty two days after my last final examination of college
in June of 1951 I'm just going to skip ahead twelve weeks at the infantry school at
Fort Benning came as a vast improvement we felt we were being taught by experts and relish the
experience we were all put under alias and this caused considerable amusement amongst our army
instructors as under the stress of parachute training we frequently forgot what name we were
supposed to be so you know you can only imagine this is just an awesome awesome read and there's
lots of stuff about jumping out of airplanes and doing all kinds of crazy shit that he obviously
feels that he can divulge and share with us so I'm going to record this entire commentary on that
book and again if you have a chance go out and get the legacy of ashes so you can be prepped for it
and with a little bit of perseverance I think we'll be able to get him to open up and start telling
stories that he'll eventually turn into a book and I think it's going to be just fascinating this guy
and give an example I one of the one of the cousins excuse me one of the cousins asked him
you know Uncle Don have you ever met George W. Bush because he was the personal security advisor
to 41 as we call him in the family that would be a George Bush senior and here's the and really
it's so much better when he tells the story but just to give you an idea of the kinds of stories he has
he says well yes I did meet George W. Bush says we were scheduled to play tennis against him and his
father so was Bush senior and Bush junior I don't know what year this was and that's Uncle Don said
that he even went to bed really early you know and I wanted to be rested and he said he had never
played so poorly in his life before and after the match George W came up to him and said
did you really think that you could beat us kind of frightening isn't it and he had that smirk on his
face anyway so that's the update on Uncle Don more to come and I'm very excited about it as I said
I'll try this week if I can find a nice quiet time and even a quiet spot I'll read this commentary
on the legacy of Ash's book so a couple more days here at the beach before we go back to the
UK hopefully we'll get some sunshine I'm looking at the windows right now and I can see that the
overcast skies are going to clear up just a little bit but it's not going to be really nice today
so hoping for better weather tomorrow however I do want to brighten up the podcast
podcasting with Adam for you ready to be stumps time that's he's the contest with young
hey Adam this is hit test number 83 we're going to start right away this is in drone number one
ah yes only kind of been practicing it on the guitar recently that's a hotel
California by the Eagles no doubt about it and number two do that one again
the police don't stand so close to me is my guess what about yours and this week's final intro number
three oh let's hear it for the boy the news Williams something something from the foot
loose soundtrack I think come on y'all hand me those answers and time's up and these are the answers
answer number one from 1977 these are the Eagles and hotel California boom boom
nice the Eagles has answered number one and this is answer number two from 1980 the police
and don't stand so close to me
two stars don't teach you the subject of school go fantasy
just like the police is answer number two and this is answer number
they're 87 Whitney used oh
I said the movie
We'd be used then. I want to then with some body is answer number three and that concludes
hit test number 83. Again, three tracks from way back 77, 1980 and 1987. Three great ones.
I hope you like the metham and you had them all. The links to the iTunes store and the answers
to this hit test can be found at hittest.potshow.com. Next week I'll be back for hit test number
84 so until then, take care and bye-bye. Excellent, John. Thank you so much. Nice to hear
those. Of course, brought to you by the organization to the preservation for the soundtrack of
our lives, which is selling more back catalog than any other show on the interwebs. And it's
sponsored by Kmartz, back to school, check them out at Kmartz.com or back to school.potshow.com.
So what I'll have to do is take the show with me to the mainland so that I can upload it from the
Starbucks. So I have no idea what time you're going to get this show, but sometime on Monday, if you're
in the United States and maybe Tuesday by the time you get this over in Europe. And I'm going to
wrap it up with one more song. This is something Jersey Todd sent me. Again, I was the only
song I was able to kind of eak down through the tubes off of the pod tape music network. Jersey
Todd just sent me like stop the presses. You've got to check this guy out type of message. I can't even
get to his bio page, but I'm going to play it for you because I got the song. It's Ethan Stone.
Title of this track is Warwick. Well, they left me off the roster.
From the time this year, now I feel like such has been known once my spirit here is still
I've met with those boosters. Freaks smiles and handshakes full of fear. They've left me in a place
my own trail. I leave them face down in your beer. And when the demons tear you so
make you wish you'd never try.
There's a foggy hill top pasture. Where the cows up nobody lies. On my way to Warwick,
it's crazy to lift me to the sky. To breathe the air clears my conscience and gives my
armies the world to fly.
When they close the road, Warwick
From the time you see, Because they said they can't afford it, I felt my soul made disappear
I'm going to see her way together, And I just close my eyes and smile
Let the freshest wings by me to rest my soul in the wild
On my way to Warwick, This grace roofing to the sky
To breathe the air, Clear as my conscience
And gives my wings the world of flight
From my way to Warwick, This grace roofing to the sky
To breathe the air, Clear as my conscience
With the dull drops far, I mean, If my wings the world of flight
From my wings the world of flight
From my soul of flight
I've totally got to agree with you, Jersey Todd, Awesome
It's kind of like a spring scene vibe as well
Like in the Ethan Stone's Warwick, From the pot save music that work
Once they get to the mainland, I'll put the link in the show notes
DailySourceco.com
Alright, wait, there was one more thing. Oh yeah, thank you
Also, much for participating in the mystery caster from Fire Island picture contest
No prize other than the honor, of course
PW Fenton sent me the picture of him on Fire Island on the beach from 1972
Boy, what a stunning looking young man at the time, huh?
If you haven't seen it, check out Curried.com
And you'll see what I mean. You see all the interesting guesses as well
As people who thought they knew who that mystery pod caster was
Award-winning, I might add
Okay, we're off. The show will be up sometime later
Of course, by the time you're hearing this, the show has already been put up
But that's the time shifting element
So dailySourceco.com, Adam at podshow.com
If you have any ideas on what I can do to improve my throughput and connectivity
Here on the island, and we'll definitely talk again tomorrow
So take care everybody, bye-bye
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
This podcast is brought to you by podshow and GoDaddy
The show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com
Got something to say?
Walk it with your frequent log from GoDaddy
The best and the brightest served up daily
By the sharpest minds in content delivery, podshow and line weight