Hello everyone, this is Karen, you joy-rise queen, wanting to wish you all a very relaxed Christmas.
Stay tuned with joy-rise.btpacha.com.
And with this angel from above, there's nothing that they both can't do.
A make you wild as dreams come true.
To grab your earbuds and jam a man.
And let the fabulous show begin.
It's Adam and Patricia.
Yes, Adam and Patricia.
Adam and Lady Patricia.
Are you doing everybody?
It's Marcus Couch.
Welcome to the best of the daily source code.
Please, to be your host today.
I'm the regular host of Pod Show Music Rewind.
And also, the scenes scene, you can find out more at
MarcusCouch.podshow.com.
But right now, I'd like to bring in my better half.
My wife Barbara, how are you doing Barbara?
I think you are you.
I'm good. I'm sitting right next to you here.
I'm so excited.
Yes, you should be. It's a great honor to be hosting the best of the daily source code.
Let's explain the music underneath us, shall we?
This is Zorba. What is this? Zorba's dance?
What is this?
Absolutely. Let's dance, Zorba.
My Greek wife.
Any of you guys seen my big fat Greek wedding?
Zorba.
That is the life of me to a team.
Everything is all Greek all the time.
It's like a cultural radio station that just never leaves your earbuds.
Fantastic.
You know, Patricia is also, I think, at least half Greek, according to Adam.
Correct?
Yes, she is.
Dekani's breakfast is here. He's the Kalao.
Oh, bye.
I'm going to call up some man.
Exactly. That's what I said.
Only more pointy.
You know, it's special.
So, we're going to be featuring clips of Adam and Patricia from the daily source code.
Hope and everybody's having a great new year out there.
How was New Year's Eve for you? Really good?
Oh, it was so much fun. So much fun.
I cannot help it. Let's dance.
Yeah, right. Let's do it.
So, O6 was a banner year in the Kouch Household.
We moved to California. We had a really great time.
Man, it's time to get to work, though. It's O7.
What do you say? Should we get to work?
Let's get to work now. I'm breaking the dishes right now.
No, don't break the day. I said no.
No, you can't do that. We got to break the show.
That's our dishes.
Oh, there goes my award. There's a trophy.
Oh, stop.
No, no, no, no.
You better put that down. Put that down.
No.
There. Stop.
Wait, what are we going to eat off of?
We just got here to California.
We're not going to have anything to eat with.
Hey.
Here's the show.
Hey, baby, how you doing? It's Friday.
Yeah, it's Friday, finally.
It is. I was so tired a whole week.
Yeah, well, we went to bed every night at 130.
What do you expect?
What's the matter with your curves? You don't want to go to bed.
You don't seem to understand.
You never hear me complain about being tired.
Even though I'm tired.
You're young. You're still young.
Well, thank you.
But I was your age.
I wasn't tired.
I know, but why don't you just go to bed?
You don't have to wait up.
Just go to bed all right.
No, I have to because I'm afraid that you guys
leave the candles burning.
No, honey.
I have an entire condo in San Francisco,
which is still as far as I know,
has not burned down yet.
Yeah, but.
And I've got candles.
I do lock the doors.
It has a door.
Excuse me.
I don't have a reason why you stay up because you're afraid
that we're going to leave the candles burning.
I do not.
I do not leave the door.
The refrigerator open.
I don't.
That's your daughter.
Stop it.
Oh, you really get me riled up when you do this shit.
Don't.
Don't be blaming me for like the fridge door of that crappy ass.
How can you even call it a fridge?
That's true.
Yeah.
It's not even a fridge.
It's like a cupboard.
Okay.
So, did you hear me laugh?
Start laughing when you get angry.
Start laughing.
You know, laughing.
Honey, girlfriend, you have not seen me angry.
You have not seen the devil come out of me because the devil in me is wearing
Prada.
Okay.
So, I'll avoid you establish.
I don't leave the refrigerator door open.
But, okay.
So, I leave the.
So, the refrigerator door.
I'm not really open, but you have to close.
Close it.
Okay.
Look, give me a checklist.
I'm good at checklist.
I have to do this before I go flying.
Give me a checklist.
And then then you'll know.
And then I'll even check it off on the piece of paper.
So, and in the morning, you can get up and you can see that I did the checklist.
Okay.
So, it's the refrigerator door.
No candles.
Lock all doors.
That's the garden door.
Three things.
Three.
Do it.
I want you to have the rest you need as an older woman.
So, okay.
What else?
Now, you know.
That's it.
Exactly.
And just to know that you guys are still walking around through the house.
And, you know, you need somebody to just say, okay, guys.
Oh, okay.
All right.
So, it is something totally different.
Yeah.
And I can't sleep when I know other people are still awake.
But the other people are your husband and daughter.
You know, we're fine.
The other people's in that.
But we're fine.
It's so unfair for you to blame us that you are tired.
You can go to bed whenever you want.
I don't think it's that.
It's just getting up.
Did you bring your tea?
No.
Where's my tea?
I've made it for you downstairs.
Put it on the counter.
What's the matter with you?
Because you were late.
And you're pretending like, oh, whatever.
Do a show.
Because you were late.
And I made tea for you.
Okay.
Of all the things we discussed Wednesday on the show.
I already told you this.
What was the number one thing everyone caught on to and called in about.
Oh, the folder in the folder or scruncher.
You will not believe the things people are interested in.
Yeah.
And think it's important.
Check it out.
Hi, Adam.
This is Jen from bucket at bucketpotcast.com.
I was just listening to Charlie and listening to your conversation about
punching versus folding.
And I have to say, I was not the burning question about toilet paper.
Was whether you put the roll on so that it feeds from over or from under.
There's an argument in my house at least.
And I don't know which is a different between men and women.
The over and under thing.
Or maybe a fat regional whatever.
I'm totally over by the way.
And I'm a scruncher.
Hi.
Yeah, I'd need to see.
I'm a scruncher.
Yeah.
I need to be over.
You know.
I totally agree.
It has to be over the roll on there.
Yeah.
Otherwise, it could, it's own, it's own through gravity.
It's own weight could unroll the entire roll.
I've seen that.
Yeah.
I agree.
And hotels always do it like that.
So there must be a rule for it.
I like it over with little point in it.
And I think that ladies are more folders because of the scruncher.
Yes.
But most of them are, I think, folders because we're more sensitive there.
Dude, I'm a folder.
But you're sensitive.
Oh, yeah.
You're so sensitive.
Yeah.
It's, you know, there's something else that, you know, that always seems to be a point of discussion is men don't put the toilet seat down.
And I think I'm a very simple solution to this controversy.
Why don't, why doesn't everybody agree that when you're done with the toilet, you put the lid down.
Yeah.
I think women should also put the lid down.
I think there's nothing on this go.
And the, and the, the real lid.
That's what I mean.
Just everything.
So that way everybody does some work.
So it's not like women don't have to do anything.
But I see lots of women who complain about,
not men not putting the seat back down.
Yeah.
I hate it too.
It's just like a big, like, you're here.
Did you hear that?
Ready for you.
Did you read about,
there's a McDonald's that opened up in Holland.
And of course, McDonald's is a franchise with the American company comes and checks it out.
And he had two of those urinals, the ones that,
the modern art urinals that look like a big, big mouth with big red lips.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And the American said you can't have that yet to take it out.
Well, I mean, it is kind of like putting your dick in a mouth.
I mean, let's begin with that.
That's joke.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, but that's no human.
No, there's no humor in the McDonald's corporation when it comes to that.
But the the only thing they have on their mind in an, in America.
Correct.
How come they didn't like it?
Uh-huh.
See?
So we have scrunchers and we have folders and we have another category.
Oh, yes.
Oh.
Hey, Adam.
It's a function to start with all the podcast.
And I, uh, we're just going to like to weigh in on the scrunching versus folding.
And I'm the roller.
Uh, let's figure that one out.
A roller.
But the hell?
You say night change
Yeah.
Night change
I feel the same as before
I thank your scared
Yeah, that's it.
Would you cast more
Student matters
Stop, sis.
You are the stars
That's it.
See there.
All you would ever give me.
Pull around and then we'll ever.
You'll never give away.
Can't dance.
Late night.
It's time to fall.
It's in the sky.
It's back.
It's the day.
Let's time with you.
Let us be there.
Only you know what I'm saying.
I don't believe it's like someone else.
Maybe you're before.
All around and then we'll ever.
You'll never give away.
Let's go.
You saved me by change, I feel the same as before, I think you're scared, and that this isn't what you meant for.
Only when I sheltered, I feel like someone else made it before.
All around the field and the love, all of them get on and go, all around the field and the love.
They all make it on and go.
That's holding Mercury, lead singer and guitarist Matt Hopper, and Matt's from Chicago.
He was also one of the finalists in Rockstar Supernova.
He might have heard that on Rock and Roll Geat Show with Michael Butler, but Barbara, you and I've actually met Matt Hopper before.
He's a kind gentleman.
Yes, he's a kind Chicago boy, and it sucks that he didn't get to be the lead singer of Supernova,
but I'm sure Matt's going to go on to better and brighter things, and I know he's also good pals with Grainian,
from the Pod Safe Music Network.
You also met Grainian, didn't you, Barbara?
Yes, I did, Grainian is wonderful guy, happy and compassionate.
Yes, we've met several members of his family, really great people, and it's a really great thing that they're putting
herself on the Pod Safe Music Network, so to all you artists listening out there, happy new year to you,
much success and prosperity in 2007.
All right, we're going to get back to the clips here. This is the best of Charlie, Adam and Patricia.
So you know little Britain.
Yeah.
And lots of people who listen to the show, probably watch it in America as well.
Great enough.
So what is one of your favorite female characters on Little Britain?
I'm just, there could be a couple of, maybe, or maybe one of them, or one, okay.
I'm a lady, that one and...
No, no, that's...
I'm a lady, you see, no, no.
Okay, listen to this, no listen to this.
Graham Wilson sent this in, listen to it.
Hi Peter, it's Linda.
I have a presenter with me once to know if he can miss the satellite window.
It's Adam Curry.
Oh, you know Adam, long blonde hair, slightly vacant look.
Long legs.
Like to have sex with pies.
Virtual penis.
Never actually met in if his friends.
What all of Bon Jovis old haircuts at a charity location?
That's right, the big head fag.
Okay, I'll tell him.
Peter upset that you can miss the satellite window, but he'll have to do that Florida cop thing.
And beat you to death with a baton.
I'm good as that man.
Hello, it's Linda.
So there's Linda character, she's an administrator at a school.
And people, you know, kids keep walking in that are all different ethnicities and visual.
And they're asking features.
Right, she always calls and then insults them.
She's on the phone and exactly that man.
They crack me up.
I love that.
Thank you, dude.
I have so-and-so in front of me.
And then she starts.
All right, Marcus Couch and Barbra Couch.
The lovely Barbra Couch joining us here on the best of Charlie, Adam and Patricia Edition.
So how you hold that so far?
This is pretty much the longest podcast you've ever been on, huh?
Yes, they can.
But I love it.
Right here.
You're already tired of it.
No.
We're holding a microphone.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
Hey, what's up everybody on the serious window.
You can check me out on the weekend rocking you out on the scenes scene.
Thanks for the segue, dear.
And if you like to find out more about my show, you can go to the scenes scene.com.
And also, we've got Pot Show Music Rewind, which is at rewind.potshow.com.
And rewind is my baby.
That's something that I really enjoy producing.
It's where we take about five or six music podcaster clips that they submit to me.
And we kind of mix and match them all up.
And it's a show that I never know how it's going to sound.
You know what I'm putting it together.
And it always comes out with a really special plan.
Much like Greek baccala.
Uh-huh.
I don't forget Aily's first or the time.
They're listening to the daily source code.
He doesn't need a blog.
It's Adam.
Well, we've got something coming up here that Adam read a letter that I wrote to him to Patricia.
And it's really a great story.
And it's just something that came through for us.
Podcasting actually got us from the dreary depths of Chicago, Illinois, to the sunny shores of Orange County, California.
And I'm still doing backflips.
I totally appreciate everything that everybody had Pot Show's doing.
Not just Adam and Ron and everybody else, but you know the developers, all the guys who were testing the stuff.
You know, C.C. Chapman, the guy who let me in the door, to Christopher Shears, the guy who's doing the pot safe music network.
Man, you guys all rock.
And I got to thank you for everything that you've done and made possible for me and my lovely bride here.
Thank you so much.
Yes.
And well, my thanks continues here as Adam reads a letter that I wrote him.
I think it was June and when he read it, I hadn't quit my job yet.
So I was a little taken up back by hearing it on the source code, but nonetheless, we can all look back at it now and enjoy it for what it was.
Yeah.
Yes.
Thank you Adam.
So I thought it would be particularly nice in conjunction with this email message that I got from Marcus Couch from this scenes scene.
He does is a and the pod, pod set music rewind.
So he's a pod show network podcast.
Yeah.
And so he sent the private email to me.
I'm just going to read a little piece because it really touched me.
I really like it.
Thanks again for the video cast plug.
I received great positive feedback.
I'm quitting my day job of six years and moving to Orange County, California on July 31st.
The compensation I've received from Pod show has enabled the opportunity for my wife and I to make the move.
Her son and nephew are there and the move will bring us all together again.
We really appreciate everything you and Pod show provided us and I can't thank you enough.
Ah.
Isn't that beautiful?
That's beautiful.
And it's not like we, I mean, this is just based upon his own creativity and performance.
Yeah.
And anyone who signs up because, you know, we're about to unleash if anyone knows you know.
So that anyone can do this.
And here's a guy who actually made it happen.
I mean, I just love it.
That's what you want to do.
Exactly.
And I'm just like, I read and there's more.
There's a whole bunch more to it.
But remember, you told that that story on TV in Holland and everybody laughed.
Oh, that I said, everyone will have their own brought in the transmitter.
Yes.
Oh, yeah, they all laughed.
They all laughed.
And then through he said it.
Ha ha ha.
Who's got the last laugh now?
And that's going to wrap it up for this past of Charlie Adam and Patricia Edition.
My name is Marcus Couch and Barbara Couch.
Thanks for listening.
Take care, everybody.
Bye.
So I searched for my place in this world.
I know I've got limited time to be heard.
People keep telling me, I've got to do this while I'm young.
This when I get older all my energy will be gone.
It's so a try to keep my head clear.
I still fuck up sometimes when you're not here.
I smoke so much that I forget my goals.
And now I know what it feels like when time takes its toll.
I'm so have a dream for too long.
Should I move along?
I'll keep on pushing on when you can never dream for too long.
Just keep your focus on reaching the stars, oh yeah.
So I said I'm not right about life.
And what I'd be like if you were my wife.
I'm so lost on real true way to go.
And so I disappear and let you think control.
I'm so have a dream for too long.
Should I move along?
I'll keep on pushing on when you can never dream for too long.
Just keep your focus on reaching the stars, oh yeah.
So now that I've thought this all out, I'm much more confident but still have my dad.
I'll lift my head back up to the sky.
I'll hold on to where I die.
So I have a dream for too long.
Should I move along?
I'll keep on pushing on when you can never dream for too long.
But still keep your focus on reaching the stars, oh yeah.
So now that I've thought this all out, I'm much more confident but still have my dad.
Pot show.
If it doesn't say Pot show, it's made by somebody else.
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT Pot Show Media Network.
Howard by Pot Show and Limelight Network.
Control your part in the show at btpotshow.com.