Potion needs you to help us suck the less.
Yeah, I'm getting sick of it too.
I have this sprint with Potion Radio.
The bottom line is this.
As soon as this shows over, go over to suckless.potion.com.
Get in, get out, and for God's sake, get out with your life.
Because if you don't...
Help us suck less help us suck less potion.
Eat you to help us suck less.
Hello, out of this is Frank Electrolox.
You know, in my industry, you'll want to suck as much as you can.
So I really don't give my hands around this suck less thing.
I keep hearing it everywhere.
suck less suck less.
I don't get it.
More suction is a very good thing.
You need to understand the basics.
And you're confusing the kids.
They need to understand that it's okay to suck.
But no, you've got this big promotion suck glass.
And now everybody's singing the songs.
And doing all kinds of things.
All they're doing is talking about suck glass.
What do they like it or not?
So in the DSC 614, can you shed some light on this whole suck less thing for me?
Frank Electrolox.
Thank you, dad.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
But in the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic, it's Adam Curry.
I can feel your heartbeat.
I know you're lonely.
I can tell you by the way you hide you right.
I can feel your heartbeat.
I know you're searching for something to read me into your life.
Just another night in your city.
Face is on the ground.
We have a blue.
Everyone is searching for somebody.
But nobody has a clue.
Just another night in your city.
All along the dark night.
We have a blue.
Just another band was chasing music.
And it all stopped.
When I saw you.
I can feel your heartbeat.
In the night our eyes meet.
And it seems like we were always meant to be.
I can feel your body shaking.
We touch you in the embrace.
And love works for you.
They tell you by the way.
Just another night in your city.
Face is on the ground.
We have a blue.
Everyone is searching for somebody.
But nobody has a clue.
Just another night in your city.
All along the dark night.
We have a blue.
Just another band was chasing music.
And it all stopped.
When I saw you.
Just another night.
We have a blue.
Face is on the ground.
Everybody searching for somebody.
But nobody has a clue.
Just another night.
Just another day.
And just another night.
Just another night.
Trisha there with her star sisters and just another night in New York City soon to be
Podsafe available on iTunes.
Yeah, and she's binding to a big time into the Podsafe Music Revolution.
So here we are once again in the big Apple and well, what a day it's been so far.
Got up at the crack of dawn.
In fact, Dawn actually had already cracked.
No, Miss Selly, not talking about you.
Dawn cracked. It was a 530.
Got picked up at 630 off to the airport.
Man, I was just completely wrecked.
And of course, it's because of a lot of activity over the weekend.
A lot of intense flying that went on.
So, you know, it does take a lot out of you.
Let me tell you, it's no picnic.
Next time you're flying and you walk by that cockpit and the pilot standing there with a flight
attend this thing.
Because it doesn't matter if you got auto pilots and, you know, it's just it's intense work.
It really is work.
But it's a lot of fun.
As you can tell, I've got the, got the mobile set up all installed here in my hotel room,
which is not the first thing I did getting off the plane.
By the way, completely uneventful flight as usual.
It wasn't the regular version Atlantic 747.
It was an airbus, which is the what the 320 or 340.
I get confused with the airbus numbers.
Why is my mic so soft?
Oh, ow.
Did you hear that?
Sorry about that.
Yeah, so you have a little less room and the configuration is,
isn't quite as cozy.
I quite sure what it is.
It's not the same as the big massive manly 747.
I didn't look at any of the movies, although there were a couple of ones.
I want to actually want to see music and lyrics, but I know Patricia wants to see that,
so I'm not going to watch it and we'll get it on DVD and we'll watch it together.
There really wasn't anything that I needed to see per se.
So, what a couple of magazines, you know, started some trashy novel book,
which was good for a couple hours of entertainment.
I arrived in the hotel.
Now, I got here around 1230 and my first meeting was at 2 o'clock.
This is the way we roll a man's like boom.
When we get out, I just discovered, I mean, a big mistake here.
I've positioned the computer on the left hand side of the microphone
and the mixer on the right hand side.
Usually I'd have it exactly the other way around where I control the volume with my left hand.
And I operate the computer with my right.
It's not that hard to operate the mixer with the right hand,
but the computer and the trackpad was left.
That's like, I took an idiot pill.
Okay, well, we'll get through it.
Upon arrival, all of a sudden,
messages started going off the email, my phone started ringing,
and those of you who follow curry.com,
or I put a Twitter tweet thing out.
I think I might as well get the word out ASAP.
Someone hacked into one of our servers.
And was able to send out at least one message to a number.
A lot, not all, but a large number of members of podshow.com.
And there's just been hours and hours of work on this.
And everything is okay now.
In fact, when we think it's a guy,
but someone who spills his name as monkey backwards,
probably came in from Germany.
But that's just the first stop we got.
He's used all kinds of proxies and spoofs and stuff.
But the minute he was in and started doing stuff,
which he did very quickly,
we were immediately able to isolate the server that he was on.
And basically, watch him while he was doing things,
which were no longer on a live server.
And that's, I'm kind of paraphrasing it.
And obviously there's a lot of information I have that I just,
I'm not going to tell you on the show,
because I'm just presuming it's a he.
Why do we always presume that malicious hackers are he's?
How malicious was he?
You know, it's okay.
So he sent out an email, big joke.
I think he tried a second one,
but that didn't get very far because but then we had,
we blocked the mail server.
The mail server, it's always the mail server.
I'm telling you, my experience.
That's, you know,
and I don't, you know,
we have some special kind of mail set up because
if you send out a lot of emails,
and we don't really send out a lot of emails,
but for verification we do.
Every day there's,
hundreds of not thousands of verification emails going out.
And you can be deemed a spammer pretty quickly by,
you know, AOL or hot mail, etc.
So you basically have to pay a company like strong mail.
A lot of money.
I mean, I shit load a money.
It must be at least $100,000 a year.
It's probably more than that.
So that, you know,
they ensure that you're on the whitelist of all of these,
of all of these different big mass email providers
where people have accounts.
So, you know,
it's a custom configuration and, you know,
and it's just vulnerable.
Send mail is,
we've always had,
and I know,
please geeks and nerds don't email me telling me that,
you know,
it's all about how good you are.
Because of course,
And there's exploits everywhere and everything.
But it seems that just about everything,
everything was contained.
I don't think we had any downtime on the site.
There was some funky DNS stuff for a little while
where you might type in daily source code.com
and output pop geek brief for something completely different.
But, you know,
congratulations to the ops and the tech team for,
for, you know,
identifying isolating,
tracking because of course,
that's the fun thing is when you,
you know,
when someone's on your system
and you're able to isolate him or her
and watch what they're doing without them,
knowing that you're doing it,
which I think we did for quite a while.
So,
we learned a lot about our system today.
So I appreciate everyone,
everyone being,
being to call about it.
I don't know,
it's something,
it's something car lolling,
cumbre.
You probably going to be aware of this,
but I've just had about six emails
telling me that pod shell has been hacked
by something called
eeknome or something.
So,
you've started,
you know,
the email address is,
email address he's using his hacked.by.e
nom.podshow.com
and the body of the email is podshow.com.
Got hacked.
So maybe you could tell us what's going on.
I'm sure the show's in the network is safe,
but just want to tell you
a two soon out or by the way,
I am a folding screen.
Goodbye.
I like the way you put that man.
I'm sure the network is safe.
Yes, the network is safe.
We're okay.
Oh my goodness.
So that was the fire drill.
Do you or is that the typical New York hotel room
with the air conditioner blast in a way?
It is warm in New York.
It's actually quite nice.
I'm sure it's leaves today.
Going from meeting to meeting.
Of course, this is the quarterly visit to New York.
We work with the big brands directly a lot.
But once a quarter we go to New York.
And in fact, this time we're calling it the doors.
We are the doors.
It's the digital online opportunity road show.
And we do a little show.
And show people what's going on with the independently produced media.
Also known as podcasting.
And some of the campaigns that have been very successful,
not just for the audience who have had a lot of fun with the products and services
and participating.
And there's been a couple of them think of Earth Lincoln.
And I dog but also Splenda.
You know, Tyler and all PMs.
There's a lot of big brands that we work with directly.
Have great case studies.
People are in the advertising community are looking for.
You know, this engagement.
It is still the word here on the street.
We're looking for engagement.
And actually, I was thinking about it today in a conversation we're having.
Where, you know, you guys, audience out there.
You love being a part of the shows you listen to.
That's essentially, I call that an audience.
A responsive audience that is a part of the show.
Advertisers and marketers and Madison Avenue.
They collectively talk about consumer or customer.
I think it's consumer engagement is what they talk about the most.
Well, so there you go.
That's an audience.
You want to be engaged.
You want to be a part of the show.
A part of everything that I talk about or whatever.
Your favorite shows are about.
And it's the same thing that drives people.
I believe, you know, to unmasse.
Start texting to vote for, you know, shows like American Idol and similar formats.
It's a way of participating in the show.
It's a very crude way I'll have to say.
You know, it's all you get to do is basically vote for one person.
But you know that your voice.
And that's even questionable with these, you know, SMS scams.
If you've been following what's going on in the UK,
it's.
Man, your vote doesn't always get counted apparently.
Or your vote doesn't count because the contest is already closed.
But thank you for your dollar fifty.
But that's a form of participating, participating in a show.
And kind of a mini community, a little solar system that you're a part of.
So it's really, you know, that is showing what people want.
You're a control of your, your own entertainment.
You're a control of your iPod.
So controlling is just one part of what we love to do.
Being part of it and contributing.
I love doing that.
I love messing around with, you know, getting on other people's shows and
and talking shit and making stuff happen.
It's maybe it's just a human DNA thing that we like to do that.
So let me do it right now.
Let me participate in something Dawn and Drew put together.
Now, you know the story where I popped this song like two or three days early
was a big muck up.
I'll totally take the blame for that.
I wasn't, I wasn't paying attention.
And they shouldn't have happened.
But it don't matter because all's well that ends well.
Ziggy Marley has put into the groove.
Track from his second solar album up on the pod safe music network.
So that any any podcast or where they're doing a video podcast,
audio podcast if you're streaming.
Anyway, you want to use this.
It's all falls under the pod safe music license.
All you have to do is of course report back to the network when you played it.
And if you want to hear more from the man himself from Ziggy Marley,
who I met briefly on one of my many trips at Jamaica,
one of which was a documentary I was at Hope Road.
And then later at the HQ at Marley HQ,
I think that's where Rita lives.
And you just met him briefly in passing.
It's a very cool guy.
Great interview.
Dawn is like so far up his shrink.
It's not funny anymore.
But of course the guy's writing songs for her.
So you know, might as well do something like that.
Check it out now.
Ziggy Marley.
Funny how it's also a title of Madonna song.
I think I like this one a little bit better.
So I think that's where Rita lives.
To the floor, where love grows, do you have eyes?
Yeah, to the floor, where the sun disappears, but a light's in shine.
To the floor, surrounded by the waters of desire.
To the floor, where love grows, do you have eyes?
Can't you wait?
You need to sleep.
If you mind sleeping to your mind, there's nothing you can't change this time.
Can't you wait?
You need to sleep.
If you mind sleeping to your mind, there's nothing you can't change this time.
To the floor, where love grows, do you have eyes?
Oh, I want to go back to Jamaica and all of a sudden.
Oh, my favorite vacation destination.
Ziggy Marley, into the groove, you'll find him on the pod safe music network.
Do you guys, we just hold on a second.
I'm going to check something here.
There you go, that's better.
One, two, one, two, one, two, one, two.
Okay, just messing around with the set up here.
Hey, okay, let me see.
The seat now, all of a sudden, I forgot what I was going to talk about.
I'm sorry, I'm a little bit jet-like.
What's the time right now?
It's 10.30 pm.
It is still Tuesday.
So that's about 3.30 in the morning, body time.
You know me, it doesn't really matter.
Wherever I lay my hat, I just don't know if I'm hungry or not.
That's what I can't.
Maybe I'll have some like macadamia nuts or something.
You know, they feed you pretty well on the virgin flight.
It's just, yeah, it just gets all messed up.
You know, so we're in New York and we're promoting some things.
And this isn't official.
This is an NDA.
This is not a damn announcement.
But it's just something that I've been working on in San Francisco.
And I'm really proud of what it's turning out to be.
It's, you know, just have a listen to this.
If you've got a game, we've got the channel for you.
Pod Show Sports.
Join Legendary Sports and Command.
Run bar on the newest and hottest all sports entertainment network.
As he brings the games to the fans.
Jim, you're in Chicago.
I was so mad.
I almost threw my TV out the window.
From golf.
This game is going to drive me nuts to the grid.
I can't believe it's going to play better than we did.
From the ring.
Frank and California.
Thanks for climbing through the ropes.
Long time no talk.
Yeah, Ray Ben.
To baseball.
Go ahead, John.
Listening on the internet in LA.
I hate the giant.
And fans.
It's just a youth thing.
And a music.
Yeah, right.
From body building.
Body doing things.
Governor Arnold Schwarzenegger.
You're seven times.
Mr Olympia.
We thank you very much.
Then Bob.
Thank you.
You're pro wrestling.
I gotta give you one more thing.
What's your gonna do, brother?
I'm gonna be a broke while on you.
You'll go there and back with Pod Show Sports.
With entertaining special programming on virtually every sport.
And audiences that love to join the show.
Pod Show Sports makes it real.
At an 18 of legendary athletes.
Coaches and movers and shakers.
And you've got a channel that can't be beat.
Pod Show Sports reaches all markets through the internet.
It extends its distributions.
So it's affiliate network of over 150 radio stations.
Sirius and XM satellite radio.
And worldwide on the American Forces network.
God, I love the smell of sweat.
And that found a crazy podcast.
So sports.
Bring the game to the fans.
John, you're in Dallas.
Like a rock.
Bring them on.
They're going down.
Hell yeah.
I'm no sports guy.
Okay.
I don't know anything about sports.
I watch like the world series.
I'll watch the playoffs.
I'll watch.
What is the basketball championship?
I'll watch all that.
I don't know anything about sports.
But this, this gives me.
A little podcast or wood.
And now.
I'm currently in daily source code, listener.
For something completely different.
So what was going on?
I didn't know what was happening.
The Gary Hoggander from the ultimate podcast.
Ah, we're on sports, right?
The new episode that I just uploaded actually is an exclusive that I was given from one of
a five, one of the finest of the, you also find championship name, Stephen Monner.
Stephen was basically kind of convicted of using steroids.
I guess the positive for steroids used during his last fight.
And it was a false positive.
And basically there was a huge, huge black ball thing going on with him.
And a lot of people really dog in the mountain, given him bad name.
Seven kills to come on my show.
Just straighten that out.
And if you listen to the new episode of the ultimate podcast, you'll hear this guy.
Telling his story to anyone who'll listen.
But also letting us know that the major marketing, how list that we have.
You know, as we all know here, for the podcast in the world,
are really not doing us, are not, you know, in my case, fighters.
But are news, the people who are making it, you're not doing us justice.
You know, they're feeding us what they want, what they want to hear.
And they just proves the point that independent podcasting is really the best source of any type of,
of entertainment and news that you can get.
This guy is actually able to tell his story with his words and his mouth.
And not having to deal with, you know, people riding down something that doesn't work.
So I hope you guys check that out.
The ultimate podcast.
The new episode is up now.
You can check it out at the ultimate.podshow.com.
Yo, yo.
I'm going to agree and disagree with you there.
You know, first of all, look in the newspaper.
Find an article that you actually know something about, that you really know something about.
The best example, of course, is in your case, ultimate fighting.
But really, it's podcasting.
When you read other people's truth.
And I don't believe in the whole, you know, mainstream media is out to get us thing,
or, you know, or there's mass manipulation going on.
It's, everyone has their own version of what they think happened.
And man, I've seen this for 20 years.
You know, I'll, uh, someone will write something about me or a situation that I,
that I was either in or I know about.
And like, that's not how went down.
That's, that's not what, you know, whether it's good or bad, doesn't matter.
It's not, you know, it's not all negativity.
It's just like, no, that's just not what happened.
Remember I read that MTV book?
Uh, yeah, there's a big ass book, big ass writer.
I got it from a big ass person as in, as in stature in the business community.
And it said the Adam Curry from Australia, you know?
It's like, yeah, it's the way it is.
It's just the way it is.
And how many times have I said not to say something on this show?
Well, I was convinced that, you know, I knew what I was talking about.
And I get corrected by you guys.
It happens all the time.
Something interesting at Pod Show HQ in San Francisco.
We have, and there must be a scientific name for this.
But we have doubles.
We have at least four people named Chris.
We have multiple people named Brian.
Multiple people named Kevin.
We have, I mean, seriously, multiple people.
Let's see, we had, well, Pod Pimp is gone.
So we had multiple errands.
And now we have, oh yes, it's a typical Pod Show thing.
We have multiple atoms.
In this case, we got a new guy on the scene, Pod Show HQ.
A to the B, his name is Adam.
And he's, I think his official title is,
Manager of campaigns.
Savant do compying you.
And the first campaign he got to manage right off the bat.
And he kind of fell right into the middle of it was,
the sockless campaign.
Go AC, what's up, man?
It's A to the B.
Hey, I just wanted to give you a quick,
sockless update after my first week in Pod Show.
So far, the feedback has been fantastic.
The survey results, the traffic patterns,
all the qualitative feedback and the logosphere.
It's been phenomenal.
So just wanted to say, hey, we really appreciate the listener taking that.
That's what it was.
Now, thank you.
I'm just going to back that up.
A to the B.
It was quantitative feedback from the blogger sphere.
I'd like that.
Let me do that again.
That was fantastic.
Hold on.
Here we go.
The qualitative feedback quality.
It's been phenomenal.
So just wanted to say, hey, we really appreciate the listener taking part in this and participating.
Also, a quick public service announcement.
We've got a Godzilla, golden retriever near the Pot Show HQ.
Bring a plastic bag with you when you take your dog out for a walk in the morning
because I almost hit this gigantic steamer left in the middle of the sidewalk.
Like a landmine.
All right.
Appreciate it.
And the background track is Cersei,
a soul sucker.
And it's from the O.S.
Music Network.
Take it easy, AC.
Talk to you soon.
Now, I think every Pot Show employee should be doing feedback comments like this.
Sounds like you were using.
Well, maybe it wasn't using cast blaster.
Sounds like a Mac program.
I can almost feel it.
Hey, man.
Thanks.
Welcome to the show.
A to the B.
Yeah.
By the way, there is another name for the suck less zone.
We also have the same URL is a superpanel.podshow.com,
which is really a better descriptor of what we're trying to accomplish by creating
a huge panel of listeners and podcasts.
There's a like who wants to participate in multiple surveys that are about podcasting in general independent productions.
There will be a lot about advertising.
You'll be asked to look and listen to multiple versions of advertising.
I mean, I'm enjoying.
Well, the first survey was, you know, it was like a, I've taken surveys like that before.
But of course, it was about podcasting.
So that was kind of fun to go through everything.
I am very much looking forward to the advertising, to the advertising parts, which I think we're going to do one a month or something like that.
So join the superpanel.
Superpanel.
That podshow.com.
Hi.
I made a script today.
I just wanted to say I love the new hit tests.
It's great.
And I tell you, I'm going to keep up the good work.
Also, as it's Monday morning, second traffic.
I'm going to make some, to make some more confidently exercise.
All right.
Cheers.
Bye.
As we need.
Car friendly.
Asor size.
Amy, do we need car friendly?
How do I do it?
I certainly hope she hears it.
I could use some of that myself because that laying on the ground and chairs and
jumping up to the ceiling.
I'm right there with you.
All right.
Where we at 30 minutes.
Good.
I'm going to play another song for you tomorrow.
Just tons more meetings, obviously.
So you probably won't get a show from me until tomorrow night.
Your results may vary due to road weather conditions.
And of course, the time zone in which you reside from mashuptown.com.
This is like two of my favorite songs mixed together.
And two guys who used to be in a band together called,
What was that?
Genesis.
Sledgehammer in the air is still common to be the Gabriel.
Mashed up.
If you don't stay on your tracks, you could have me playing.
If you're free, don't subscribe.
I know it's coming.
I've been in a pain in me.
Do you have a pain difference?
We've got a lot more on this.
Do you think I'm on the wrong path?
There's a mirror that's never in me.
I'll be back on the wrong path.
And in the air tonight, I'm only missing one thing in this matchup, I'm going to hear it again.
So in the air tonight has this fantastic one of the most famous drum riffs, where Phil Collins goes,
I know if you know this song, you know what I'm talking about, and that's not in the mashup.
That's the only thing I really missed, otherwise fantastic from Ben Double M, mashuptown.com.
All right, tomorrow I'll be right here, deadly source code dot com, out of at podshow.com.
Thank you for listening to my babbling.
Another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest, served up daily by the sharpest minds and content delivery podshow in limite.