This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
The show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
Got it.
T.S.C.590.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm testing this out of Korea.
On the moment he's so bad.
Everybody seems to be mad.
Come and choose it, I feel better.
Even my own man looks good.
When they just don't go, let me go too slow.
I will run in my mind.
Gonna have one in my city.
If you're like it, she's so pretty.
She looks fine tonight.
She's always fine to me.
I've been my friend tonight.
I've been calling for her tonight.
I've got to get to know her.
But yeah, I've had money on my man.
Who looked at this light once before?
Who looked at the melted world?
Who had working for the rich man?
They outchanged that suit of me.
Today I'm a man.
To all of you, man.
Can I love me or not, man?
I'm gonna have one in my city.
If you're like it, she's so pretty.
She looks fine tonight.
She's always fine to me.
I've been my friend tonight.
I've been calling for her tonight.
I've got to get to know her.
I've been my friend tonight.
Gonna have one in my city.
If you're like it, she's so pretty.
Easy, mate.
I've got Friday on my mind.
Boy, do I ever,
it is daily source code episode number 590 coming to you from San Francisco.
The Curry Condo, Maximum Music, and completely fully footballer to everybody.
You know the rules.
Whether it's morning or evening for you.
Football.
I'm here to make sure that my message gets through.
I'm wondering if you're really all as dumb as you look.
All rights money up to level who's in my book.
I have to keep what I stand at the knowledge I'm putting.
Put me in the position of a God of a King.
Cause I'm blessed with a gift of the magic touch.
And I'm worth it saying that I'm asking for too much.
All you have to do is get that on your knees on point.
And I promise you the remedy is on it's way.
But you've never been on me so don't waste your time.
Cause I'm waiting so free my position is going to lie.
What's wrong with me itself is this?
It's the price and it's gonna be your second best.
I got the gift and I know I don't waste.
And I gotta get it on my chest.
What do you think is the best?
Better than the best.
And what do you think is the best?
What do you think is the best?
Better than the best.
I'm not afraid of competition.
Cause I know that I'm the best.
And you've ever got a chance to even pass my little test.
Even if you wanted to, you could've paid up.
Why is it the right?
No proof of losers in my perfect power and dice.
Could you write this up with me?
The problem rate of your success.
So I'll make sure that I get the monster not there.
If I want myself and everyone who love me too.
And there's nothing you can do for me that I can do.
What do you think is the best?
Better than the best.
So please kids do not try this at home.
You might find yourself locked up in the big house, if you know what I'm saying.
While the wall music on the full bar friday on the Charlie,
my boys from the lowlands, lepe i ba, Orlando, the Netherlands,
very handy boys golden hearing.
Got some radar love for you baby.
There's a voice on my head that drives my heat.
Very!
What you been doing on my mat?
I've been driving on my hands when on the wheel.
There's a voice on my head that drives my heat.
Maybe coming sign here yeah
Let's have a have a sport I'm shifting here
When she has lonely mistakes you're longing me as much.
She sets her condition from above
When she bends her occasionally
We're gonna wave in the air
We're gonna love
There's my goddamn count going on here
Videos being some forgotten song
Randomly coming on song
The road has got me every time
And I'm just waiting to do a new sunrise
When I get lonely and I'm sure I've had enough
She's a sense of comfort coming in from above
We don't need to let it all
We're gonna wave in the air
We're gonna love
Just realize that song is 34 years old
It's moving into its 35th year
And still sounds like it was produced yesterday
Unbelievable
We moved our Friday when he worked up beyond all
We've hear girls here in three and a half
And nobody was anything sleepin' without
We're facilitron
You know, what's up, I'm Jersey Todd, the official musicologist of the Chacha.
Hey man, I love your discussion the other day regarding internet radio and all the crap
that they're trying to pull up and trying to put these people really out of business.
And I thought that it would be important, none of whom are Friday to bring some more
voices into the discussion.
I'd like to bring you a promo that was put up on the Ponce of Music Network
by the Trucky Brothers.
Check this out.
They're out of San Diego.
Folks, this is the Trucky Brothers.
Hey.
We want to talk to you about internet radio.
Yeah man.
Internet radio has been a way for us to get our music to you.
That's right.
It gives us a chance to be heard.
Yeah.
A recent decision by the copyright royalty board is threatening to silence independent artists like us.
Those bastards.
And significantly limit what you get to hear.
But change starts with people like you out there.
Yeah.
You're not the greedy mofoes out there.
But you call or write your congressman today.
You spell check.
And let them know that you don't want internet radio silenced.
And make sure you don't have a caller ID and stuff like that so they can know what number you are.
Because they'll find you man.
I know.
They'll find you.
And then after you take care of that, you can also visit SaveNetRadio.org.
For more information on how to help.
You may never know how important internet radio is until you can't hear it any longer.
You hear that?
I hear a playing.
That's internet radio gone.
Sounds like a playing.
It's without internet radio.
See, that's the truck you brothers.
But they're not going to get away that easy.
They're not just going to get away with doing a promo.
No, no, no, no.
Check out this song, Adam.
Because it is that good.
Check this out.
It's the truck you brothers with Formula O.
Formula O.
I can't get in the head.
Sing to me a little bit.
Every choice that I made just another little way.
All right.
I won't be able to live.
I'll hunt the feet on the face.
Especially in cash of mine.
Laces place less.
My trace is trace less.
Never give it down.
Get back.
There are lots of advice.
If I give them right cool thingers.
Not play a merry, win a waltz with my ship going down in the desert.
I'm in the night of mine.
Laces place less.
My trace is trace less.
Never give it down. Get back.
My...
Laces place less.
My trace is trace less.
Never give it down. Get back.
My...
Laces place less.
My trace is trace less.
Never give it down. Get back.
My...
Laces place less.
Laces trace less.
Never give it down. Get back.
Musicianscooler.com Adam it's your favorite scruncher Dave Jackson from the Musicianscooler.
Hey I just this whole Tokyo Dan thing I want to make sure everyone's aware of this go to
promoting with podcasting.com it's a 15 page free report for musicians.
So if you are a music podcaster or if you're a musician go over to promoting with podcasting.com.
It's working people are reaching global audiences and the proof is right there on that
page along with the free report check it out and yeah can the pod safe music network
be tweaked?
Sure I'd like to see the top 10 list and things like that maybe be monthly and things like
that so I'm making my list to help pod show suck less.
Where do I send it buddy?
Anyway I hope you're yours feeling better and yes as I said before I am still a dirty
filthy, stinking scruncher man see you later musicianscooler.com
I gotta tell you ever since I started playing this jingle I've been getting just tons of
email of people saying hey that's pretty cool you guys don't want to be the best you just
want to suck less I appreciate it here's a list and it is very cool I appreciate it I'm
getting all kinds of cool lists and a lot of the things are pretty similar stuff that we
of course obviously know that needs to be worked on but we are gonna do it with you my friends
we are going to totally suck less and you know what you're gonna help us and with it you're
gonna be able to win stuff.
I'm sorry about that minor part of it is the football friday we've fucked up
beyond his over pair and of course you can't just be playing the tunes you got to be doing it all
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah you
You're dead, he put them there for Adam and he
So they'd be hungry for the apple that the snake
Was always our friend and yeah
Yeah, God knows great, yeah
Yeah, God knows good, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, why did God's home, can I bust?
Do you suppose he had a bust?
When he made the mettle bust, when he created a farphone
Does he like the girl jam or the stone?
Do you think he rolls his own
I'm there in heaven on the floor
What do you think?
And when the Saints go marching home
Does he not?
Maybe he sits in so much trouble
I gotta tell you, I haven't had this much fun in ages
This is awesome, you know, I don't have to think no soliloquies, no monologues, no discussions, no conversations, no savants
Just a couple of promos, just some music stuff from my first gen iPod
Which, of course, is also coming up and obviously everything you hear on the show today
Will be linked to in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
This is liberating man, this really feels good
Hi, this is Jim Farley, co-host of the music world
And what's up with that podcast?
And I'm wanting to make you and your listeners aware of a very special event that's coming up on Saturday, May 19
On court theater company, in conjunction with Gregory's piano bar in Dayton, Ohio
And the musical world podcast is presenting Matthew Ebo live
One night only on Saturday, May 19, 2007
This is going to take place at Gregory's piano bar on Main Street in downtown Dayton
Matthew will be performing all of your favorite songs in this intimate setting
How can you love me when you don't know who I am?
Seating is limited and tickets are only $15
You should secure your seat early because these are going to go fast
I know is I was blind to get you a blinding friend
I've been on one level for a whole year
For tickets, call 937-773-0115
Or email me, Jim Farley, at barleyjc at gmail.com
That's F-A-R-L-E-Y-J-C at gmail.com
We need your support so that we can continue to bring in independent recording artists
Like Matthew Ebo, so please, make your reservation soon
Come to Gregory's piano bar in downtown Dayton on May 19
To listen to and meet Matthew Ebo, it's going to be a blast
We're looking forward to seeing you there
How can you love me when you don't know who I am?
These pictures got a lot more feeling from a bloodstained dirty hand
And all I know is I was blind to get you a blinding friend
I've been on one level for a whole year old
For a whole year old, for a whole year old, for a whole year old
For a whole year old, for a whole year old
I've been accused of a crime, a death from this
My baby loves me, gives me everything I need
She'll make a crown out of our plight
And I'm happy just to bleed
She knows that I've been trying hard to take my leave
She likes guns, she makes love like a lightning
But it's like poison in a sun, as dreaming
I'm wasting my time again again
Oh yeah
I've been accused of a crime, but it's hard in this film
No one ever told me they would only like to move down
With the pins and needles that stand in a way
With the wires, everybody told me I'll be just fine
But it's my time to bring that bitter white
Nobody loves you, but I ask you get it back
I won't keep wasting my time again again
But a better day than I've found out
I can't so use that as crime, but it wears kind of fear
I won't keep wasting my time again again
I've been accused of a crime, but it's hard in this film
I won't keep wasting my time again again again
Oh yeah
I'll keep living like a different guy
Definitely a friend of the Charlie Matthew Ebel's wasted my time
I keep it on my skin
I'm a man, this guy extra blogger episode is the shit man
There was a greatest moment in podcasting history ever
You gotta get that guy on the show on a weekly basis
To have the back and forth between you two
Man, he was an expert from anybody
I just want to let you know that that was great
I can't imagine anybody wanting to fast forward that stuff
It was hilarious, he put up man
Hello?
Hey baby, it's me
I feel like you're not to call me
I know baby, but I've got this idea and see
I thank you much
To make a bone on your feet
Pound on your feet
Cause I think you're ugly
Everybody wants to look like they look at a bone on your knees
Everybody wants to smile at this moment
Pound on your knees
Nobody wants to cry, no cries in the corner of me
Nobody wants to die, no one dies in the corner of me
Pound on your feet
Baby, just you and me
You'll be the star of your show, yeah
In the corner of me
Everybody wants to talk like they talk in the corner of me
Everybody wants to walk like they walk in the corner of me
Nobody needs a show, there's no shame in the corner of me
Nobody needs to plan, there's no blame in the corner of me
Pound on your feet
Baby, just you and me
You'll be the star of your show, yeah
In the corner of me
You can say what you won't go you won't be wrong
And I swear I won't tell you that you take too long
You don't want to wear that dress
You don't have to lie
Cause I'll seem happy to see you cry
You want to think I didn't come out to you
You can say I didn't know what to do
You'll be the star of your show, yeah
In the corner of me
I think you'll be the star of your show, yeah
You won't be the star of your show, yeah
You're unbelievable
I think you and me should be in a poor-no movie
You will find that track on the Podsafe music network
Nice little mellow moment there
Which of course reminds me
To tell you that we have a sponsor on this program
Tyler and all PM who also are sponsoring
Angie Bees
Relaxing show called unwind
Find it at unwind.podshow.com
You know what's so nice about what we're doing with podcasting
And the tools that we all have available at our fingertips
When I was in broadcast radio come on
I'm a mone here, let grandpa Curry tell you a little story
You would have request lines
You know how on the radio it sounds like
Of course people are saying hi
Hi, it's Kelly
Well, you're calling from Kelly
I'm calling from Trinity
Kelly and Trinity, what do you want to hear?
I want to hear J-Loam
And of course J-Loam is playing
Now it's not like we're sitting around as this jockey's on the radio
Waiting for you to request the songs
We've got to play these songs in the water
The list that they were sent in
They were programmed by
Whatever programs that stuff
And what we do is you just wait until someone calls
And request the next song on the list
Not so in podcasting my friends
Not only are you sending me the songs
But you're providing your own intros
I love it
Hi, AC
This is Brent from podshowradio.com
And heaven and hell podcast.com
Now today is Fubar Friday
So how about a boss to the wall song
They're off the pod safe
Music network
The band's called amp sex
The song is called crazy bitch
And I have to tell you
These guys are really really pissed off
Check them out
Music
That's right
Same guys
Sometimes it's crazy bitch in my life
That I hate
Sometimes it's crazy bitch
Even the fingers from my dinner
They hate it on the inner state
Music
Sometimes it's crazy bitch
Walk along my shoes a star
Like that standing at the bar
Sometimes that crazy bitch
It's a shit just a little too far
Sometimes it's crazy bitch
They did in the trunk of my car
Sometimes those creeps
Bitch, do we kill for me at the beginning
I know because I asked my mom about you
She can't believe me
I know how you wake me up
A heart that hurts me
I'm just trying to understand
Why do you need me this way
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Sometimes it's crazy bitch
And I have to tell you
Crazy bitch
Sometimes it's crazy bitch
That's when she's gonna kill her
Sometimes those creeps
Bitch, do we kill for me at the end
Sometimes it's crazy bitch
They did in the slayer mosh pit
Sometimes the crazy bitch
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Sometimes it's crazy bitch
If the club I'd like to pay
I don't know.
Sometimes it's crazy bitch
Tough enough but it's true
Sometimes it's crazy to my bed with the three feet
Sometimes it's a breeze, it's like a dead energy stream
What's playin' on me?
I'm the very eve of the release of the iPhone, which of course will be the device that is supposed to replace
All of your iPods in your cell phone simultaneously in accordance with John C. The Vorac will be the demise of the company known as Apple
It's time to check out my first generation iPod now, you know what it's like if things have become so ubiquitous and cheap you get tons of them
I got a video iPod
This is the original one of those fat fuckers
So of course this is the part of the show where I can run into a lot of trouble because we never know what's going to come off of Adam Curry's first generation iPod
All right, let me just plug in the wires here
I'm putting it on random, I'm going to forward through just hit first for the next song a couple times
So we know that we're not going to get the same ones we got last time and see what happens here
I'm hearing anything
Well, of course, why wouldn't it be food bar?
How was this?
Is my iPod busted now? My first gen iPod?
Oh crap
Oh no
This is totally harsh in my mellow
This is
Oh, oh, here we go
Oh, yes, and then a cherry
Cool
Let's introduce
You may dance
Right now
If you feel like
It's a buffalo stand
They all came running, they were making noise
Man, hallowing toys
That's a girl from the box with a neck
They could wear padded bras
I can be a fool, I can be a fool
I can down the floor
But if you get to us
I'm on top
No money man
We're not love
It's sweet next day
I'll think you know
We always hang in a bottle stand
We do the diving now
Staying out
I keep you love baby, not romance
I make a moon up to love
James and Don't you get the pressure with me
I can't so keep you
Yes, and me
Tell me
I'm on top
James and Don't you get the pressure with me
Tell me
Don't you get fresh in your eyes?
even 1980, 1981, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops,
that's not supposed to happen.
You know what?
Let's see, how many minutes have we been doing this?
Whew, I've literally been dancing around the condo.
I gotta tell you, it's just been really, really cool.
And liberating and just letting off steam.
I hope you're gonna have a fantastic weekend.
Monday, I'll be back at the manner.
Of course, Lady Patricia on her way to the Netherlands
for some show business stuff.
But I'm looking forward to being back home.
Even if I'm just gonna see her for one day,
it's gonna be good to be.
You know what, here's what I'm gonna do.
Let's break this, break in the law.
Let's go breaking the law.
Do you have a playlist on your iPod
that you've titled something like Happy Songs
or Happy Music or Good Moot or something like that?
I think everyone has something like that.
What is your playlist called?
The one that you have all the Happy Songs in?
Because what I'm gonna do now is I'm gonna roll
us out towards the weekend.
In fact, I'm gonna say goodbye now.
Let me, let me, I can't say goodbye without, of course.
Doing that.
Let you know that all the songs played on today's program
will be in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Of course, you can send anything you want to meet at atpodshow.com.
There's also some voice mail lines.
Go to the to the site to get the numbers.
What I'm gonna do is I'm gonna play at random,
a song from my happy list.
So I know that regardless of what the song is,
and of course, this is a total crap shoot.
I know that it's gonna really take us into a really,
really good, happy vibe for the weekend.
Okay?
So, thanks for hanging out with me for this past week
and have yourself a fantastic weekend.
Let's see what we get from the, oh yes.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Oh man, I'll see you everybody.
Hey, baby, how are you?
I can let you go, I'll tell my world around you.
I need you so, baby, save my soul.
You don't need me, you don't need me.
Baby, I'm all around you.
I can let you go, I'll tell my world around you.
I need you so, baby, you don't need me.
You don't need me.
Baby, baby, save us, be mad.
I know that I'm just home on my own.
I wanna tell you, dude.
You don't need me, you don't need me.
Darling, I just can't thank you, baby.
I know that I'm all around you.
I can let you go, I'll tell my world around you.
I need you so, baby, save my soul.
You don't need me, you don't need me.
Baby, baby, I know that I'm all around you.
I can let you go, I'll tell my world around you.
I need you so, baby, save us, be mad.
You don't need me, you don't need me.
I know that I'm just home on my own.
I can't let you.
I can't let you, baby.
I know that I'm all around you.
I can let you go, I'll tell my world around you.
I need you so, baby, you don't need me.
You don't need me, you don't need me.
I know that I'm all around you.
I can let you go, I'll tell my world around you.
Another pod show pod cast, stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery
pod show in line light.