You better be careful out there on next couple of weeks you hear me?
Let's close the room.
No.
Two sides.
Some more later.
You better be with us.
I can be with the nearest one family.
All the places you've got to come to my place.
I'm done with you!
Walking Phoenix, Mark Wahlberg,
on October 12th.
Get down!
Two brothers collide.
Maybe you could be killed.
Right?
We all the night rated her.
Well, to you, O earth and sea.
For the hot father sent his cast with a gleam.
Because he knows that I'm short.
Let him who had understanding reckoned the number of the cast.
For it is a human number.
Its number is 666.
Well, to you, O earth and sea.
For the devil sends the beast with wrath.
Because he knows that I'm short.
Let him who had understanding reckoned the number of the beast.
For it is a human number.
Its number is 666.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm testing his battle theory.
I left alone.
My mind was blank.
I needed time to think to get the men with front my mind.
What did I see here?
Could I believe?
That what I saw that night was real and not just fantasy.
Just what I saw in my old dreams.
What the reflection saw from how I walked my staring back at me.
Because I left dreams.
It's always up.
They've a place that's way slow.
And it brings me to this world.
Yeah.
What I thought back was not what so big back,
But that just had to sink.
In the midst of that fingers moment weeping.
What's on this far wheel?
What's just a play in the middle?
6, 6, 6,
The no-one on the beast
Hell and fall
With thought to be released
Tons as praise
Don't sacred hands for free
As they stop to cry
As they're told to start
In the night
The fight of the army
The ritual has begun
Satan's world has gone
6, 6, 6,
The no-one on the beast
Hell and fall
With thought to be released
The no-one on the beast
The no-one on this beast
And I've always had a boy, I've always had sex
And I've always had sex
And I've always had sex, and I've always had sex
And I have always had sex
And I've always had sex
I've always had sex
point to a radio station that still plays that will you? Thank you very much. And by the way,
I think, no, I'm quite sure that the actual hearing in my right ear has been diminished since my
first maiden concert. So I don't feel bad about breaking a couple of rules playing that on the
the chat chat. Number six, six. Hey, everybody. How you doing? Coming to you today from the curry
manner. It is a beautiful day. Oh my goodness. We were up at seven o'clock. It's crisp. It's cold.
The sky is blue. The sun is shining. Oh, I almost want to get back in the Delta's
era and fly. Which I did a little bit of over the past couple of days. I was in Germany. Very briefly,
flew over Sunday, Sunday night to Frankfurt. Had a meeting Monday morning and then came back. It was
for those of you who were paying attention to the weather yesterday in the Europe. There was a massive
cold front, which stretched from the south of France all the way up to Scandinavia.
And it was, it came in from the sea past over the UK. Actually caused a, a mini little tornado in
Farneboro. Farneboro is, well, I can almost spit to Farneboro from, from Pharaohs where I have the
Delta's era. So we saw this coming our way as, as I was preparing to fly back and I knew
well, here here here are the choices. Go over this huge front. Believe me, that's a non-starter.
These fronts can go up to 40, even 50,000 feet. You do not want to be in this type of cloud and storm
weather system. Going around it is possible if I wanted to fly home via Stockholm, hitting it and
then returning back. That's always a possibility. And I said, you know, I think just looking at
what's going on, I can go under it. Now, by the way, I was with Captain Yos. He accompanied me
from Rotterdam. So I took the Delta's share over Sunday to, to Rotterdam picked him up and then
yeah, he accompanied me to Aglesbach Airport, which is just the most beautiful, beautiful airfield,
fantastic for, for a general aviation airfield. That's one of the best I've been to.
So that was, that was rather exciting. I have to say, before I forget, on the, so I dropped
Yosuf at, at Rotterdam on the way back. Now, we'd already, you know, passed this, this huge
squall line, which made life exciting to say the least. You know, it's kind of fun when you fly
into the bottom of a cloud layer. It's raining like shit. And all of a sudden, you start, you know,
going up at 800 feet per minute, even though the stick is fully forward, which means you should be
going down. Oh, yeah, yeah, it gets the blood pumping. So I've met Rotterdam. I call up Rotterdam
ground. You have to request start up. And the controller says, now, okay, number 277 Delta's
share, you're going to click for start up, is this the guy from the podcast? And I'm like,
that's right, everybody. I'm here on the radio. So I shot out to Renee at Rotterdam.
I presume he's not just on ground, that it's on control tower as well, but it's very cool that
he was listening. And maybe feel like, you know, I'm sitting in the cockpit going, yeah, I'm proud.
Now, lots of talk about it being a very special episode. Some of you have sent in some stuff.
Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip.
Oh, motherfucker, you're listening now to Adam Carey's DSC 666 podcast. And don't
be stupid. Don't listen to the devil. Master of hell. The blogger who is slendering God
and stop taking drugs now. I said, now, drugs are part of a problem. Not part of a solution.
You. Hmm. Not quite sure what you're coming from DSC. I'd say alcohol is part of the problem
before any drugs are. Anyway, so the big football Friday show, the red pill that I shared with
y'all, of course, invoked quite a lot of response. Here's what I've noticed. First of all,
those of you sending in emails is great, but I can't be reading your emails on the air. So if you
got something to say that we can share with the class, please send it in audio comment or call
the voicemail number or whatever it is. Participate in some way that I can reuse it, please.
Particularly those of you who are saying, who are really pissed off and call me all kinds of
names. Please, please record your anger and send that to me. It's important. Also, you know,
even though I really try to stress this, I have not trying to delve into some kind of conspiracy
theory. And I'm much less interested in how the Twin Towers were demolished as to why. You know,
so, well, everyone's, and I'm sure that if there was a conspiracy, what a great thing to have
the masses focus on, you know, how the Towers collapsed instead of why. You know, why did these planes
fly into it? Why? Why is all this taking place? And it's really amazing. For some reason,
and I'm sure television has a lot to do with it. A lot of people basically think that, you know,
that this has never happened in history, that the powerful people who basically owned the money,
that they're not manipulating, that only happened in the past. You know, that happened,
well, the last time that happened was was basically, you know, the Nazis and Germany. That's kind
of the last time that that stuff happened. And media was manipulated. Yeah, I think it's pretty well
documented that, that, that, uh, would, what was at the gobbles? Was that, uh, was that Hitler's PR guy?
I think it's pretty much been proven that there was a lot of mass media deception going on. But of course,
that was the lie. It never happened after that. Not for a single minute hasn't happened after that.
It's Ed Loss from Postmouth here with a bit of feedback about episode six, six, five,
and the idea of having a chip implanted and only being able to use money if you have this chip.
Okay, let me just preface this for those of you that didn't hear episode six, six, five.
This is zeitgeistmovie.com, which I really enjoyed watching. The premise of this is saying,
actually, they had a, uh, some quote proof, a friend of one of the Rockefellers said that this
is what Rockefeller told him that the ultimate goal of, uh, of starting wars and, uh, and taking
way freedoms was to ultimately have all money flow through embedded RFID chips. So instead of having
a bank card, which is pretty damn close to an RFID chip, by the way. Instead of having a bank card,
you'd have a chip and you just, you know, use this to scan every single science fiction,
futuristic movie portrays this, by the way, which means it's inevitable or it'll never happen.
I think there's a distinct possibility. You know, Mike, my animals are all chipped.
You know, the defra, as they call it here, Department of,
Ecaf, Ecaf, Ecaf something in agriculture. Uh, it's, uh, ecology, food, recreation,
agriculture. Don't remember what it's done for. They can scan my animals. They can scan almost
every single animal. That's just a, just a, you know, it's only like 50 centimeters higher,
and then they can inject more of those in me, you know. Uh, so the point is if, uh, all money would also
be, um, communicated through your embedded chip, and if you acted up and didn't play along with
the game plan, what we just turned off your money. So that's what this comment is about.
Oh, this is episode 666, and obviously people have been sending you a lot of, uh, comments and
things about the number, and it all comes from Revelation, chapter 13, verse 16 to 18. And he
calls of all, both small and great, rich and poor, free and bond, to receive a mark in their
right hand or in their foreheads, and that no man might buy or sell, save that he had the mark,
or the name of the beast, or the number of his name, and here is wisdom. Let him that have
understanding count the number of the beast, for it is the number of a man, and his number is
603 score and six. So that's where it comes from. It's funny that you were talking about all this, um,
pit chip in the arm, idea for episode 665, don't know whether you actually did that to the
divinity, but there you go. 666 is there, the idea of having a chip, or a mark implanted into you,
and you'd not have to buy or sell without it, maybe there's something to that Revelation.
Oh, I like that one. That's a good one. That could start a whole conspiracy theory by itself.
Yeah, as it just coincidents, I started talking about this stuff from an episode 666 or
is there something else going on? You've got to read the book, clearly.
Yeah, all kinds of deception has been happening. That's a read legacy of astials. You'll see
the CIA, and this is from the government. The government has declassified all this paperwork,
you know, this is stuff from the 60s, and before that, even is now out in public domain,
the Freedom of Information Act has provided all this great information. You'll see that the U.S.
certainly has funded terrorists and guerilla movements and tried to start up rising,
and wars, and tried to have dictators killed, and we're not murderers, little bunch.
But of course, all of that ended. We don't do that anymore, do we? Ah, please.
So the only thing I will say is that while lots of people are sending me links to proof to
to counter what zeitgeist the movie is saying, why is it that people who are
trying to prove evil and conspiracies have all this great video footage of public and
commercial broadcasters that they're able to edit together yet, when someone goes into dispeel all
of this, you have to go buy a book like popular mechanics, by the way, part of the herst corporation.
So, you know, a couple people have pointed me to popular mechanics and their study, and
they've got lots of big red words to say fact. But you know, I'm looking for like the video evidence.
I love the video evidence. We live in the video age if you can't show me the video,
or if you're competing against the video, trying to prove a point, you're just going to lose.
Is that simple? But again, I'm not into conspiracy. I'm just saying let's follow the money. Let's
keep our eye on stuff. Uh, it's another book I need to read, uh, head CS sales. We still
crystal me. I need to read the Roth child, uh, which of course is one of the big families, which
uh, could possibly maybe maybe be out to expand their empire and influence. Yeah, never, no, do
you. A couple of people sent in comments about the TSA, the, uh, transport safety administration.
I think it's a administration agency. Agency, I believe, part of Homeland Security.
Yeah, I thought I had it bad by having to go, uh, go through a kind of a minor, not so, or not so
pleasant experience. Think about people who do this shit professionally.
Hey, Adam is a Robin. Yes, I'm on my way back to the airport for no trip. Well, I can say
about the TSA. Welcome to my world, over and over and over, sometimes more than once a day.
The last thing I got jacked up on was the MM50. I take that with me on trips, and uh,
they didn't like seeing that in the X-ray machine. So anyway, I feel for you, but I'm living it tailings.
Robin is a, uh, is a captain on a major major US airline. So we have to go through that
crap every single day. Yeah, I can understand, welcome to your world indeed. But still,
you get to sit in that cockpit, man, and fly. I have to tell you, I'm dreaming about it again.
I really, really am. I, you know, I feel so good now in the aircraft. I've really gotten to a
point where I'm, uh, I'm just, I'm feeling, I'm not overconfident, but I'm feeling confident. I still
have great respect for particularly mother nature. Yesterday showed me that again. But I just, yeah,
just, I'm, I'm wearing my plane, which is kind of, I guess the way it should feel. Oh,
that new thing I bought that, uh, the, uh, what is it, uh, portable collision avoidance system?
It works pretty well. Um, I didn't even expect it to pick up military aircraft, but, uh, indeed,
um, see it was flying just over the last bit of Germany before hitting the Netherlands and, uh,
a Tomahawk launched. Was it Tomahawk? I think it, not a cruise missile. I think it was a
Tomahawk anyway. Some kind of jet fighter. And, uh, so he was launching right underneath me.
And, uh, and I could pick him up. So he, I didn't realize that those guys had some kind of
squawk as well. So I could follow him for about, uh, 3.2 seconds before it's like blasted out.
And, uh, pretty amazing. Yeah, I guess my problem with, uh, with TSA is, you know, I don't mind
airport security. Of course I don't. But when it's stupidity, you know, so here's Robin,
he gets nailed for an MM50, which is one of the first, was one of the first advertisers we had
on the pod show network two years ago. It's a docking station from a Logitech that you, uh, that you
could put an iPod into. Uh, and it's just a metal docking station. You know, and meanwhile,
I'm passing through, you know, they're pulling out my hair gel. Well, I've got transmitters,
transceivers. I mean, I could actually jam the radio communications of any flight that I'm on,
because I carry so much shit in my bag. You know, I, and I'm licensed to carry it. I'm a licensed pilot.
I'm licensed to carry my transceiver, you know, and I, I carry along for a number of different
reasons, uh, mainly come too lazy to unpack my entire bag. So, you know, think about that. I could,
I could jam the entire communication system of the plane. Uh, yeah, that's okay. And by the way,
and please take your lighter as well. But, whoa, as me, if you try to take some hair gel.
Hi, this is Sam from San Francisco Bay Area again. Uh, I got cut off. But I was just saying,
you know, when the TSA started, um, they were smart about a few things. They got rid of the stupid
security questions, which never made any sense. It never really accomplished anything. But then,
this stupid liquid thing is the dumbest thing. And I've lost all respect for the TSA with this
liquid crap. There's no way that someone is going to blow up a plane carrying a diet,
cober juice box on a plane. And it's completely eliminate my ability to go to go somewhere with
only carry on bags. Oh, you know, that is so true. That, that's the biggest problem I'd have to
say. Think about the time that we're wasting, not just by these, and, you know, long, uh, security lines,
which actually are move, I haven't been, okay. So that experience I had from New York to San Francisco,
Suck, then I almost missed my flight. But in general, I have not missed the flight, and I don't
give a shit. I'm, you know, I'm just in zombie mode anyway. But you, you literally, you can't travel
with just hand luggage anymore. You know, so that does take more time. It just takes time to load
stuff up. And of course, there are people that have to then have stuff loaded at the gate. And,
uh, it's debilitating. It really is. And it's okay if we're going to keep to some certain rules.
But be consistent. I opened my bag in, uh, in Frankfurt. And there was a, at the bottom of the bag.
They must have missed this. There was a huge canister of hair, a canister of hair spray. So I don't
mind, you know, them putting in their rules and everything. But be fucking consistent and do your job.
So now you're just not doing your job, okay? You suck. Um, and it's just,
to most annoying thing possible on airline. So I don't think the TSA has any scientific or any kind of,
any good reason why this could ban makes any sense. And I don't think anyone could blow up a plane
with a stupid 10-ounce bottle of anything. So as far as I'm concerned, the TSA is full of crap.
So of course it actually never even happened. You know, it was a, it was a threat that was thwarted.
I'm willing to believe that. Uh, but there was no actual, uh, explosion created by mixing of liquids
on an aircraft. Ah, let me get off of this. I don't care. I'm flying myself.
You know, it doesn't bother me anymore. I take all my liquids on board, my own plane. I love it.
Had a really good time in Germany. Um, I didn't stay in Darmstadt this time. Stayed, uh,
in Frankfort at the, oh, great hotel. The Villa Kennedy, which is on the, uh, the Kennedy Hala.
Um, beautiful, beautiful. But man, I tell you, first of all, you fly over Germany. It is just
absolutely stunningly beautiful. And the sun, the, the couple times have been that the sun is always shining.
But, um, gosh, they, they really know how to, uh, it's something about the German culture.
They really, they are perfectionists. And, uh, the people that we've been, uh, been working with
rattle from will, um, you know, these are just great guys, you know, and then they really want to get
shit done and, and do it right. And I have to say, feels very, um, the work ethic, uh, and dedication
feels, um, uh, it's, uh, exemplary. I'd have to say. So it looks like, um,
Podshow Germany will launch in Berlin first. Now, we, we have a couple of options. There's, uh,
and I, and I have learned even though I'd like to get a really cool funky office like we
have in the in London. Man, it's really difficult to get infrastructure if you need phones and
good connectivity. I'm not talking about a DSL line, but something, you know, that we can really
use for, for big-ass media files. It's tough. It takes a long time, um, even in the UK, even our
part of here British telecom couldn't, couldn't help us, you know, move things along any faster
because, you know, the roads had to open up and shit. So that's not, uh, that's not really something
that we're going to go for. So there's a couple of business, um, housing opportunities. The Berlin
one, there's actually a Twin Towers in Berlin, which I'd find to be just too static and, yeah,
however, a Pulse dump, which is just to the west kind of south west of Berlin. Now, that's a pretty
funky place. And there's some awesome, uh, independent labels, new media companies. There's a lot of
stuff going on over there. So, uh, that's probably where we're going to wind up starting the office.
And I'd say, um, in the new year, we'll probably be, uh, be ready to go. So, uh, very, very excited about
this. And, uh, in the next few weeks, now, we'll be, uh, I'll come up in, uh, in Germany. I guess,
we'll, we'll kind of centralize the meetings to Berlin, kind of what we did here in the UK with
our draft and darts. Um, we'll, uh, do a, uh, be on Broadway. And let's talk about some podcast.
Hey, Adam, what's good, man? This is Major and Jay Mack and Fro, man, the staff over here at
hoodhive.com. Just want to say what's up to you, man. Uh, thanks for all the support you've been
showing us. And uh, we just want to let you know to, or we'll have to, uh, listeners know that they
can go to hoodhive.com slash vote and get in the vote for us over for the VH1 hip hop honors award.
We're nominated for best underground website, underground hip hop website. And really,
I mean, this is a big thing for us is big for podcasting in general. We're the only podcast
up there, too, by the way. Yeah, we're, everybody else is just doing the typical, you know, hip
hop website thing. We got a podcast and we're proud of that trying to take the podcast movement
even further. So any hope, any help you could give us, and that regard with the folks.
Hope and hope you help. Yeah, definitely, man. So, thank you. Thank you. Yeah, I'm going to keep
plugging these guys because I really want them to win. Uh, you know, take that into consideration
that this is, uh, the best underground website. Um, and it's got to be hoodhive without a doubt
for the VH1 honors gover to hoodhive.com and find out how you can vote for them. I guess the
voting's done online. So, uh, whereas I typically hate these types of things. If it's a VH1 thing,
come on. Let's go spam those guys. Let's make hoodhive win so that they can mention me in their
acceptance speech. You know, everyone, uh, how, you know, at these award shows, I want to thank
God, you know, as long as you just slip my name in, that'll be good. Uh, let's see, uh, of course,
now that we're turning up the heat, uh, on a German friends, cross the border there, questions
are coming in. Edmhy, this is Michael, listener from Germany. I have a technical question about
pot-safe music. Um, here in Germany, there are a free radio, so we call free radio's and also
free television, um, broadcasters. They're funded by the state, basically, or they get federal money,
or whatever. Usually, they use gamma license, music, because they have a general gamma license,
or maybe. Yeah, that's, uh, that's a German version of the ASCAP BMI. Uh, so I do have a little
bit of knowledge of this. Let's see what the question where it leads. If would. Now, those free
radios and free TV broadcasters want to go online, and they want to use podcasts for some of their
content. My question is, let me back up a little bit. Um, they asked Gamma if, um, they could use
gamma music on their, or yeah, gamma music on material on their podcast. Gamma says, on streams,
yes, on podcast, no. Yeah. In other words, they cannot use gamma music, gamma license music on
their podcast. So my question is, is it possible for these broadcasters, both television and free
radio to use pot-safe music and under which conditions? Is it the general CC license, do they have to,
uh, say, okay, this is the artist that we play from and link to him. Is that all it takes or is there
other any additional things that needs to be taken into account? Yeah, thank you very much. Yeah,
and uh, I'll listen to the show like that. Thank you. I guess you will. Yeah, so there's of course,
uh, I'm not a lawyer and there's all kinds of opinions and uh, and there's no jurisprudence,
there's no precedence and it's very complicated. So in general, of course, that is the entire
point of the pot-safe music network is every person who uploads their music there has the rights
in one form another to actually do that and uh, gives you, um, producers and podcasters
who are associated with the network who have uh, signed up to the pot-safe music license,
gives you the right to do just that, uh, to uh, to use that work in all kinds of derivatives,
which would include a podcast. Now, um, in uh, many European countries and I believe it's still
the same in Germany, um, the the Gemma, the Golf Echo Mike Alpha, which is their Ask God BMI,
has almost a God-given right. Once you uh, sign up with them and and let them handle the
performance royalties for your work, uh, no one else can be assigned that right, which is kind of
twisted, um, now in the US and in other countries around the world, you can always write out a separate
license for your music. So I don't know if it really would be enforceable if it went to court.
I do know that right now, there's a huge con-con-troversy, uh, going on in the Netherlands,
where yet another rights organization, the Saina Sierra Echo November Alpha, which interestingly
enough, uh, goes after rights of the artists who perform the work. Yeah, it gets crazier.
Uh, they've sent bills to the public broadcasters who've been putting out their radio shows as
podcasts and I'm in significant bills like totally up to maybe 100,000 euros, which as you know,
these days is about eight million dollars. So, um, you know, this has led all the public broadcasters
to stop putting their shows out as podcasts, which of course sucks. And the reason why they will
allow it, uh, streaming, which, of course, again in the States now costs a significant amount of money,
or at least that's what the latest word was. It's all still very, very confusing.
Um, you know, it's because they think that you can't copy it, or that people, it's too much
hassle for people to go copy stuff off of streams. When it comes right down to, of course,
don't get a shit about copying your crappy music, but that regulation does allow us to do some
very, very interesting things ourselves at Pod Show. Hey, I'm direct, you know, how been like
you since, I mean, way back to some use even the cards. But anyway, so, you know, I've been
paying attention that I gotta say I didn't do this one coming. Um, some of you pop it around on the
internet and if I hit bookmarks and I go to curie.com and, and I hit your link and it takes me to
what is it? Plus TV, is up plus TV.com? Dude, I think you got something here.
And see this one coming. I meant to it. Yeah, blue pill. Okay, keep on the blue pill then. Yeah,
this is, so this is, this hasn't even officially launched and I just kind of mapped to go
daddy domain name to it. Oh, by the way, if you're looking for a great deal on a go on a domain name,
just go to godaddy.com and use my checkout code, DSC3 for 10% discount across the board and whatever
you buy. So I mapped the plus TV.com to our test, which we'll really start ramping up the first
of October as we will be broadcasting live from backstage at the digital music awards at the
roundhouse in London. Those of you who are listening, well, no, we did this last year. This year,
it's a little bit different. So we've built this system, which I'm very proud of. L to the A,
Lisa has really set this up all by herself under my direction, but God, she's been working on it
for six, that will maybe eight or nine months. So we, we have this entire scheduling system,
which is very familiar to me, because it works very similar to that of a, of a radio station.
And we've automated a whole bunch of video that can run through this thing and, and it's on 24,
and it's, uh, it's great video music videos. It's a wacky crazy single clip videos. It shows,
all of it has been cleared and run through the pods, the pod show network. So it's all above board.
And of course, because it is streaming, we're actually going to be able to roll out some of the
videos of the, the artists who are nominated for the digital music award. So October 1st, you're
going to see us ramping this up, then October 2nd when the awards take place, we'll be coming to
live backstage, uh, truly is your backstage pass to the digital music awards. How do I know it's
going to be the best backstage pass? Well, because we have a free bar, uh, inside the venue, where
our kind of our areas, our stage, our set. And I know one thing for sure, when you want to get musicians
on camera to interview, all you have to do is say, uh, the bar is over here. And that, of course,
is where we have most of the cameras set up. So that'll be fun. Uh, so that kicks off 4 p.m.
UK time, uh, which would be about 8 a.m. San Francisco time. Uh, the whole, the shabang lasts about
eight hours. So around midnight, UK time or 1 a.m. We're going to start, we're going to repeat
everything that took place. So those of you, uh, just waking up in the states will be able to, uh,
to witness it. And we'll keep going all the way through, uh, the day after the DMAs, uh, with the,
you know, red carpet. We've got everyone's going to be their Dr. Cockney, OJ, uh,
Nadda.Contin's coming over. Uh, I might even do stuff on camera. But it's, it's going to be fun.
And it's going to be something different. Uh, so this is, you know, someone, someone picked it
up the other day and said, yeah, that, you know, the plus TV dot com, it's kind of, it's kind of like
what, you know, MTV might have been today if they hadn't gone to all the, the long-form programming.
I'm like, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
Adam, it's being on desert, um, just listening to the DSE and your playing that could, from, uh,
network. And uh, it's kind of reminds me of something different. Ninth, uh, always getting around
about it's, uh, little factoid, uh, yeah, that we kind of made up. Basically, it's 1% of the population
thinks, 2% of the population think that they think. The other 97% of the population would rather die
than think. Think about it. Thanks, bye. Hmm. That's a good one. I might have to write that down.
Let me think about it.
Hi Adam, it's Matt from Gamesweasel. On this week's show, we get plumbing with superpaper mario on the
Wii, but he's very thin this time. We've also got a review of his rivals game, Sonic Rush adventure
on the DS. We've got part two of our Star Wars, the Force Unleashed feature, and you can win
copies of Juice 2 for the Xbox 360. That's all on Gamesweasel. To be found at gamesweasel.beteepotshow.com.
Soon to be in video version, uh, right now it's audio. Matt Cuddle, the award nominated
for uh, was a GMA, a games media award, awesome dude. Congratulations again. I hope we'll be
awesome if you want it. It's up against some big mainstream properties. It doesn't you live
in the UK, uh, ratios about 20% to 80 from the U.S. So step up the Colin will you let's
didn't expect to get any more comments about my, uh, my iPhone that dropped down the
throat of the porcelain beast, but yep, it is. Hey Adam, I have a question about your iPhone.
After it landed in the toilet, did it sink? So I had to think about this question for
second because I'm like, what does he mean? Did it sink? Of course it sank. It sank to the bottom of
the toilet, but more interesting, um, after I dried it out and stuck it in kitty litter, which is
really true, by the way, people who thought that it might not have actually happened.
It did come back to life. It does sink if that's the kind of sinking you were talking about,
uh, but the touchscreen is forever host. Uh, but I'll say it again. I'm not missing it.
I missed the pinch technique, but all things, all things remaining the same, the combination from
me of the N800, um, and the E61I. Yes, it's two devices. Yes.
Yeah, there's, there's that kind of drawback. Yes, the kind of, um, industrial feeling. Boy,
you can toss those fuckers around. I've dropped these things so many times, uh, and they just
work and they've got everything. Almost everything that I could wish for is working on these two
devices combined. So, uh, I guess I'm, uh, I'm kind of red pilling for, uh, for Nokia there.
Let's do one more comment about, uh, about the evilness of the world and then we'll play another
awesome song. Okay, what do you say? Hey Adam, uh, this is JT. Uh, I had to say it bad. You're starting
to sound like a really paranoid Democrat, which, uh, stop a really paranoid Democrat. The
fuck you, first of all. You know, I'm, I'm not a Republican or Democrat. I probably lean more
towards Republican than Democrat if you really thought about it, um, but why, why would a Democrat,
why does that have to be a Democrat's thoughts at all? You know, the Democrat right now
can suck my dick. You know, it's, big talk, big, big talk, but where's all your power? Where
are you changing things? You can't, you know, you should, there's a lot, you know, please, please, please.
I'm so disappointed in government in general. Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, they're all sucking on the same
straws. Trust me. Okay. So, you know, that, that type of name calling, I just will not accept.
It's just ridiculous. I'm an American. I'm a world citizen. Uh, I, I'm concerned and I think
and we can have a discussion, but the call me a, a paranoid Democrat screw you. Uh, I know you have
Republican tendencies. So, uh, don't mean that as an insult, just that you're just getting all
back down there. Um, I understand and believe that there is a, uh, definitely, uh, a, a lot of
blue pill in the media. And yes, we have been told what they want to know and write down to the reality
TV shows or whatever you want to call them. And uh, the news and all that I can understand and
believe that. Right. Okay. Well, it's not the entire point. And, and, and by the way,
it's just the way the media is made. It's, you know, the whole, the whole point of television is to trick you.
You know, what's, what's Zoom? What's a jump cut? What's a, what's a, what's a fade? It's all,
effects, effects by definition are things that can't happen in reality. Uh, I do not believe
that the media is, you know, encouraged with the government. If they were, they wouldn't be
trying to put people out of Iraq. I don't, I, you know, I really don't think that I said that,
you know, the government and the media are in codes. I, you know, um, but is it a fact, a historical
fact that the US government has been in Kahoots with certain influential journalists? Absolutely.
And that happens in the commercial sector, too. Look at the, uh, look at the correlation
between Apple and the Wall Street Journal, Steve Jobs and Wald Mossberg. Come on, you know,
you can't tell me that there's no relationship there. Yeah. Of course, Wald has his integrity,
but you know, there's, there's ways to massage these guys. I, I try it all the time.
If you're journalists and you'd like to be massage by the pod father, just give me a jangle.
Find a sabotage the troops that are over there. 12 of the, uh, the one government, uh, one
world government. I say that's a good thing as long as it's consensual. Now, it's by Conquest. Yeah,
that's not a good thing. I don't believe that they're, and I think it's a conspiracy, but, um,
I definitely don't believe that there is a, uh, uh, that, that it's bankers and, um,
you know, all of the rich families that are pulling strings and trying to get us into Iraq
and Iran and all of that. Okay. So this, this, I think really is the point that I have to
disagree with you because historically, throughout mankind's history, the rich, the powerful,
have always, always tried to protect our own, our own backs, our own families.
You know, when you got a lot of money, you got a lot more to lose, I guess. And, you know, it's all
relatives, but come on. This has been going on. What do you think that the royal family here in the
UK, they're so influential that they can sit on on UK taxpayers' pounds and have all these
castles and not do anything. And it'll do anything. You know, I think they're important for
Britishness and for the culture, but they don't actually do anything. I don't even know how much they
own, but you can't tell me that that's not because they have some form of influence. And, you know,
if it, come on. So we have our own version of that in the US. We have our own royalty.
And we all know that we worship the dollar. We've even combined the dollar with the Lord in God
we trust. It's on our money. So I totally believe that bankers are in charge. This, by the way,
would be a good reason to look into Hillary Rodham Clinton's campaign from what I understand
I have not done the research myself, but I appreciate anyone who did from what I understand,
she is taking a lot of money from hedge funds, i.e. bankers. And these guys, they just don't
invest in stuff for no good reason. They invest to get it back. That's the whole way our system works.
You know, if you have enough money, you can buy enough TV commercials. You can get elected.
It's that give me $300 million. I'll be president tomorrow. And I just feel like
people are on edge about all of this and they are just paranoid. Yeah, okay. So we're allowed to be paranoid.
It's just, I understand that there are things that are not in our control and there are things that, you know,
I wish the government would be more secret about things because the nerve tells the public
the more it gets cut around, the more things we get, and the more it sabotages our efforts. There
is a terrorism issue. There is an Islamic, you know, radical Islamic uprising against the rest of the world.
And it's not going to go away. I don't think. We have to put that into
a situation where we can control it. I don't want to be in control of the word, but I do want to
control our state. And so that's something that we need to be aware of. And you cannot control your
fate, my friend. Look at Katrina. You cannot control fate. Now all I know is the most logical
reason for the United States and coalition. It's not just the United States that went in,
although they seem to be the only one staying as the world's policemen. The reason they went into
Iraq, thank you very much, Alan Greenspan for telling us now after you've left the federal reserve,
Cox Sucker, that it, oh, Iraq was all about oil. It does after everyone deflected that and
denied it. Here's a guy who's been on the inside circle for a long time.
Conscience catch up to you there, Alan. Of course it was about oil, but not about stealing oil.
It's about protecting the interests, our own interests, controlling our destiny.
And I believe the entire point was to provide stability in the region.
But I think the war machine got the better of us and the profits are soaring and
that God knows what I think the dollar is in many ways being kept artificially low, but that's just me.
So that was a complete control of your destiny move, but we were lied to.
And, you know, it's one thing to say, hey, look, we got to go into the Middle East because we got
to protect our interests and the world needs that oil and we need that oil and this is why we're
going in. That's one thing, but to lie about it and use the oldest tricks in the book. That's
fucking lame. And now to be to be standing there and watching a civil war take place.
That's there's something real wrong with that. That's finishes up.
I am definitely not a going back clone, but if you want to get a little there,
what I consider more reality, I think you're going back. That may say something about me,
but I, I didn't hear what you said. I got to do what?
I am definitely not a going back clone, but if you want to get a little there,
what I consider more reality, I think you're going back. That may say something about me,
but I, I, I, I, I believe. Anyway, I really wish I, I really wish I understood.
I, I, I don't, I don't know what you're saying there at the end, so I don't know what I'm supposed to
look at, but I'll gladly look at anything. And please send me some video montage as of stuff that
the, the dispels all of this and that, you know, we got to look at, is it all religion? Is that what
it comes down to? It's all about religion. There's nothing else. No one else has pissed anybody off.
There's been no back and forth. There's no huge financial gains or losses for any party anywhere in the
world. There could piss someone off. I, I really, I really, I really respectfully have to disagree with that.
Before I forget Julian Smith sent me a note for you to check out the alive and Baghdad video
podcast, which he says is probably the best political, political one around right now. Apparently
seriously short on funds. So they're taking donations alive in Baghdad.org. And if you don't
know how to spell Baghdad by now, well, then you can just go to the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
to find out how you spell that. Help to help the brother out there. He's doing some very interesting
stuff. I'm going to play one more song from the pod safe music network. Do,
I'll be back with a final thought before I get out of here and I've got to go to London once again
today and Chicago tomorrow. So it's a cha cha in movement.
And I vow right now to last time I get in. So to commemorate, I go out and tie one on.
I guess I'll quit drinking when you're gone. If I put off jail tomorrow, what I want to get
today? I'll just sit here till the future. Come and slap me in the face. If it don't change my
direction and I'll blow it out here in space then you can't say that I've ever lost my way.
Do, do, do, do, do, do. At least I thought that's what I told myself I'd do. Do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
Then in a cloud of smoke, my car moved to LA. My girlfriend got pulled away.
But if I put off jail tomorrow, what I want to get today? Come on, I'll just sit here till the future.
Come and slap me in the face. If it don't change my direction and I'll blow it out here in space then you can't say that I've ever lost my way.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do
do, do, do, do, do do, do, do, do, do, do, don, do, do, do, do, do,
But don't change my directions, and I've blown out here in space, and then you can't say that I've ever lost my way.
Nashville's favorite song, and you can't say that I've ever lost my way.
Matthew Ebel's back, we lost my way, brand new on the pot, say anything that worked, you can find a link to that in the show,
no, it's a daily source code dot com.
Hey, I'm coming to Nashville around mid-October.
I'm hoping that I'll have some time to hang out.
So far, these business trips have been pretty unlucky for hooking up with people.
So, of course, Berlin is going to be a big one in a couple weeks, and then that'll probably be just before Nashville.
You see, see what my life has become.
I'm like a fucking travel in gypsy.
Now, since I have to go to Chicago tomorrow, I have a speech on Thursday.
Here's what I was thinking.
I was thinking, why don't I hop a plane?
I already have way there.
Why don't I hop a plane over to California and then head on up to the portable media expo, which I didn't go to last year?
And really, I just like to hook up with people.
As all these people who I've known for a couple of years now, some of them I've never met.
I'd love to be meeting them, new people.
I think we've got a couple of party suites going on.
Quite sure Richard Brewer Hay is setting everything up this year.
I hope that we'll also be demoing some of the new Pod Show site, which is not really slated to be released until I'd say end of November, beginning of December.
That's when we can start doing some data stuff.
It's very, very different.
So, as we move more towards, actually, I have a description for you.
You're going to like this.
It seems for the internet meets LinkedIn for media.
That's all I'm saying.
So, maybe we'll hook up with the portable media expo if you happen to be in California.
Ah, who am I kidding?
The only reason I'm going is to hug Angie B.
Another Pod Show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoDaddy.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds and content delivery Pod Show in my life.