You better be careful out there on next couple of weeks you hear me?
Let's close the room.
No.
Two sides.
Some more later.
You better be with us.
I can be with the nearest one family.
All the places you've got to come to my place.
I'm done with you!
Walking Phoenix, Mark Wahlberg,
on October 12th.
Get down!
Two brothers collide.
Maybe you could be killed.
Right?
We own the night rated R.
4 out of 5 Dennis recommend the DSC-664 for their patients who chew gum.
And the fifth one is choking on the blue pill.
Scruncher.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Do the next generation radio content in my ears.
We own the night rated R.
I like to think I'm flying into this journey.
Fantastic.
It's Adam Curry.
I don't need no foreign car.
Movie star moon guitar.
But you box in a funky bar and one more night with you.
I don't need no green charm.
Dad is far falls along.
Ain't no pink and you be home as long as you are true.
I don't need no motorheads.
I don't need no Biggie Rain.
Bought a fade.
More pink.
Love the band that loves to swing.
Let the girls ride.
Let's go get us out of town.
Doll down and say round.
Hold on knees to rock and sound, And what one ride did.
Let's go get us out of town.
Baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby
Baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, everybody, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby
I just need my big old friend
She's little things to do
I don't need no foreign call
Movie star
New guitar
She's watching the fucking bar
And one more night with you
Now
Line up my voice
Ryan Setsor brings his orchestra to the pod save music network
One more night with you
I was previewing that track
Earlier on the speakers
And Patricia came up and she said
That band, that band that's playing right now
Was it?
Yeah, no kidding
When we all love a band like that
Everybody how you doing is
Daily source code episode number
664 coming to you from the curry
Manor in G-town west side
Representing beautiful day today
I can see the controls of the jets flying overhead
And actually I'm tracking
Well not the not the jets overhead
I'm tracking the general aviation traffic today
I've got a new little gadget
From the pilot geek
Nerdazoid winky
Blinky shop known as trans air
I bought a traffic collision
Avoid and system
Which is
Essentially what it does is it tracks aircraft
In the general vicinity
You can set it to certain distances and levels
And the
I guess the concept is
When you're flying around
It'll tell you where other traffic is located
And it will produce a
I have not heard it yet
It will produce a loud audible warning
If some things within
Dangerous limits
So a new gadget for the Delta Sierra
Which I plan on flying this weekend
Because it looks like
Another trip to Germany is
Order
Oh yeah, we're getting very close
My friends
My Deutsche of Hoinde
We're a common boys
It's going to be fun
So I think we may be in Berlin
Over the weekend
Possibly Berlin
Certainly a trip to Frankfurt
To meet some people
Lots of stuff happening
Very excited about that
And of course
Even though I've got a full week here in the UK
In the London crash pad
I have some time today to bring you
A data show
A data source code show
Last night
It was a
Patricia and I were in the city
We went to a
Let me see it was the name of the company
There was a reception
Slash party for
The radio taxis group
I don't know if you've ever heard of them
I'll all be in the UK
You probably have
I guess they're one of these private car companies
And they've just started a
Carbon neutral program
So they have these huge
It's pretty funny
They've got these huge
Extender penis limos
That run on bio diesel and biofuels
That was very cool
And they had a party
Which was put on by a
Super Agent Keith
And Alan the Killer Kingston
And so Patricia and I were invited
It was pretty cool
There were lots of people there
There that we knew
Race Antili from the Alien Autopsy
Video series
And you've been working with him
On some stuff
The Elvis Lost Diaries
As an example
Which he says
There's lots of cool updates
So we'll be meeting hopefully
For lunch later this week
I'll tell you what's going on with that
The barefoot doctor was there
We're good to see him
Of course we're working on a show
With the good doctor
And this is the guy that is completely
Solved my
My numbed index finger
Just by
Jabbing his fingers into my vertebrae
A couple of actors
From saw one from East Enders
There was a Patricia point out a few people
From Coronation Street
Don't watch Cory
So I wouldn't know
Some West Ham united players
And their wives and or girlfriends
Also known as the Wags
It was good
It was fun to be out
And the Queen's hairdresser
Or maybe he was a queen hairdresser
I didn't quite catch it
But either one would have applied
We'd have a good time
Very hungry though
Because they had like snacks
And we were hungry
Which we'd be eating the city
And decided to come on home
That rattling in the background
Is the fan by the way
The temperatures actually heated up a little bit
In the attic
And I hope the weather stays this way
For the next couple days
Aw wouldn't that be nice to fly with this weather
Ah look it forward to it
Other cool stuff to mention
For the city PD
New episode
The second season
Episode 4 has dropped
Things are heating up
I'm not going to tell
Well, I'm not going to tell you what happens
You must check out this episode
Damn the production has gotten so incredibly
Ow
Sorry
Production has gotten so incredibly good on this show
I'm really really digging it
I'll put the episode 4 in the daily source code channel
If you haven't subscribed to that already
Go to Adam.podshow.com
And look for the DSC channel
I'll also put that in the show
And you're going to put that standard in the show
No it's now
So you can subscribe to it if you haven't yet
Hey Adam, this is Chris Thompson
And so I'll see you
I'm calling to say hi
And also
I want you to discuss possibly
The iTunes
Music store, wireless music store
Or whatever they're calling it
And they're integration with Starbucks
I know you were talking about doing a thing
With the Kass 18
And the UK
I'll skip the name
But Apple is doing it with Starbucks
I think pod show should be doing it with
Whatever the company is
Not that you're competition or anything
But still
It's just like
You know
It shows that it doesn't market there
So what do you think about that
In your time speed
So you're talking about caffeine
Euro
And so I'm going to pick up the
Conversations again
Over the next couple of weeks
About integrating pod save
Music into the caffeine
Euro experience
And indeed
So first of all
I think that's a pretty interesting
Pretty interesting deal Apple put together
There with Starbucks
Interesting technological connection
Actually
Not quite sure how they're going to do it
Across all the stores
But I guess they've got it figured out
They have to drop some kind of hardware
And with some kind of smart software
To figure out what's playing now
And how you can buy that off of
The iTunes Music store
So a couple things
One
I understood
And I, you know, Natalie Delcante
From texture.pot show.com
You know, she is the expert on all this stuff
And she went to the unveiling of the new iPods
And she said that there was indeed
A capability to access podcasts
Wirelessly
But I don't know if that only works
If you're at Starbucks
I'm not too sure this seems to be a lot of
You know, just a lot of questions
Up in the air about about how that's going to work
I had personally
I think there's other ways
It doesn't all have to be about the sales
Just the exposure I think is the exciting part
And quite honestly
I don't know, man
I'm a little down now on the whole the iPod thing
Apparently there's a new version of iTunes
Out which now encrypts the way it talks to the iPod
So people who are using Linux
Can no longer talk to the new iPod
Even though apparently this new iPod
What is it?
The nano video or whatever it is
That seems to be flying off of the shells
But yeah, it seems like
The cooler the boxes are trying to get
The more locked in and locked down
They get which is a little bit disappointing
Hello, I'm Mr. David from my Southeast Texas
I'm Friday I got touch
I went to the Apple store
And got me a 16 gigabyte iPod touch
And box parts
Wait a minute, they're out already
I didn't know they were out
That's interesting
Oh, that was faster than I thought
I thought it would be another week or so before they came out
Okay, I don't know if they're in the UK yet
I'll have to check
Most fun, I've thought I've ever used
I know you ditched your iPhone
Try to turn it into a hubo
Yeah, it's been worked out too good
Check out the touch, it's pretty cool
Got some weird things
I think we need a hammer apple for
And that is
You can enter a contact
Which can enter a calendar information
Which frankly things kind of stupid
Man, no kidding
Oh man, that doesn't make any sense
So it's a read-only device then
Damn, why do they pull all the cool shit out, man?
I thought it would let you enter neither of those before
So why just one now and not the other
Maybe Steve needs to give us a hundred bucks for that
And
And outside of that, I guess the memory
And some of the videos play that kind of dark
But maybe they'll fix that when the software update
And you know, see you
Bye
And I went to the Apple Store online
And so now they're promoting it
Something feels wrong
It feels like this was an afterthought
Not really planned
Apparently, even though they did show pictures of these devices
Having Bluetooth built in
Apparently it's not
Which I think is a huge mistake
Because man, how cool would it be if you could use it
You know, in conjunction with your phone
I mean, this Bluetooth protocol
It's very very smart
You know, you can access your SIM card by remote
You could basically turn any external device into a phone
Just by using the Bluetooth protocol
And sticking it actually
And I now have a secondary phone
Which I just stick in my bag and I use that with the Nokia
And 800, which I'm loving more and more
Now that I've kind of had the iPhone slash iPod touch experience
I got to tell you, I got this new beautiful leather at case
That kind of locks in place with magnets
I don't know if it's available yet
I have Candyman Luke hooked me up with it
And I saw there was a...
Hold on, where was this?
There was a note
Let me just check for a second
It looks like they're about to upgrade
There we go, Mimo 4.0, the Shenuk version
Let me see
There's something new
They're coming out with a whole new tool kit for the windows
I'm not quite sure what's happening
But I have a feeling that they're going to do a significant upgrade
On the next round, on the next release
Could be very, very interesting
And I just have to say it's a little bit...
Well, it's definitely bigger than the iPhone
But, you know, carrying these two devices
It does kind of get me where I need to be
It's got all the stuff that I need in there
Particularly the audio
Although, of course, you know, still having trouble with quick time
But it now at least will eat a lot of different MP4s
And of course MP3s it does
And it understands flash
Not super, but it does it
You know, regular flash, not a problem
When you're looking at flash video
It does about a frame a second
I think flash has just
Has so much overhead the processors can't handle it
But I'm liking it, I really am
So I'm kind of back in Nokia world
I have to say
And, you know, I've got the iPhone sitting here
And yes, I do miss that lovely browsing methodology
But, you know, now that I'm using the new
The new opera browsers
Yeah, you know
It's typical
Apple always has the nice finesse
And things feel good
And it has always, you know, always has some beautiful
User interface
You know, features
But it's always missing shit
There's always stuff that they have to do differently
So I think from mobile I'm going to stick with the Nokia
However, seeing that leopard is coming out
The new leopard, that's the new OS 10 operating system
From Apple
I am pretty much convinced I'm going to be switching back to Apple
From my general laptop use
When that comes out
Of course, I'm expecting that there will be new MacBook Pros
To go with it
And that's what I'm going to make the switch
So I'll keep you updated
I mean, once again, I looked at all the
All the leopard stuff
That operating system looks really, really cool
I'm just salivating
Comic strip
Yeah
The comment
What is it?
The comment to
There was a ratio I thought up for comic strip
Blogger comic strip bloggers
Comment to something ratio
Fuck
Well, it's been pretty low
He comments on almost every single episode in the show notes
But hasn't been sending a lot of stuff until I started complaining about it
And of course, here he is
Joel
Oh, I don't carry
Yeah, but the fact is the mission statement
But so ink
The mission statement is pissed off
Comic strip blogger
Well, I actually don't give a shit
And then more about it
But so
Because you thought that
Have you got my advice
Ah, CSB
Just because you're not seeing something live yet doesn't mean that I'm ignoring your comments
But mobility
The message about
I was a way of immobility
Yeah, well, I'm ignoring mobility
Yeah, the comments
Yeah, RSS feeds for comments, yeah ignoring that
Every fucking thing
Ah, the fucking thing
However
I would like to be your EU correspondent
Again
Okay
Yes
CSB, of course you can be my EU correspondent
And be careful what you wish for you
Just might get it, you know?
By the way, dude, what's up with the microphone
Sounds like you're talking into your laptop
So here's my first story from you
Switzerland
Even so it's just not in EU
Since July 2007 is Halloween
Citizens of European Union
To immigrate
To migrate to Switzerland
And work permits without any residence permits
freely moved to Switzerland
And EU citizens can now
Previously everybody had to arrange
Work permit or the residence permit before coming to Switzerland
Now EU citizens don't have to do it since July
Ah
Cool
Alright, so I presume
Yeah, I presume that's a good thing
Even though they're not in the EU
You are now allowed to go live and work in Switzerland
Nice one, dude
Comic strip
As I said, I hooked up with race until the last night
And he said there was some exciting news about the Lost Elvis Diaries
Which is coming out to being published by Harper Collins
Early next year and of course you will be able to get the entire Lost Elvis Diaries
Exclusively before the book comes out
We'll start rolling out the the episodic audio novel
Which is going to be a lot of fun
We of course since it encompasses Elvis's entire life
Now we have
We have some older Elvis
And we're looking for younger Elvis
Hello Mr. Curry
This is Elvis
Presley
I heard your call for
He interested parties in reading my early Diaries
I think it would be
I'm coming to view to have me read them for you
As they are my own words
If you'd like me to read them on your show
I'd be very happy to
My number is
I don't want you to read now your number man
Don't do that
Yeah, all that missed there was just a mom
That everyone who sends in
You know audio thinking that they can be the next Elvis
To read the Lost Elvis Diaries
The always go to Mama Mama Mama past away
Which is like almost a sure fire bat
The same now that guy's not going to cut it
Everyone doing it at night
Hope you feel it all right
Ladies, I hope you enjoy this stuff
We got a special guest in the internet
It's the break-on prize
And your break-on
That was amazing
You know that girl over there she lived in real world
Yeah, man
I don't know
I think she would talk to her man
I'm a mella kind of fella
L-a-a
I got something to say
L-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a
A-gul-ree-y-ye-h-fye-e-a-ch-a-e-sy--hi-y-E-h-e-ah- bag-kg-u-m-e- הס-h-s-f Exodus- Fu-ch-eee-
One of her hot things
Cook, cook, press, shut up and dress
She stumbles to the bar to hang with Paris
Three, relax, pop and add a bit
To take me back to a night naps and dance
Lock me three girls, one bed, enough set
This is why I'm the spot
Drug me this photo of you
You're using a bag of clothes
All the girls in the dance box
This is the biggest deal
You're using a bag of clothes
And you're just making yourself with a little pop
Pop, pop, pop, pop
Lookin' nice, actually
Eyes keep this glasses
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all
all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right
all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all left, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all, all right, all left, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right,
Lings, of course, the DailySourceCode.com in the show notes for today's episode, Nice, man.
He's got a good groove there.
What does he call himself?
Here we go, from the bio here, with the Rockstar Poor LP, Raco morphs into a persona
he describes best as the anti-just in Timber Lake, Nice, anything anti-like that is good
with me, my friends.
My mom and dad named me Kristen Roli.
My friends call me the nine.
I'm going to give you a couple of reasons why you should think of me as the American
SmartS.
I support Pork, the other weapon of mass destruction.
Is everything Nealcon with you?
Hey, you know what Nealcon got me, you know where I am today.
Which is where?
We're tired.
My only girlfriend is Satan.
I like the way that sounds Sean Hannick, who's a real moron, as far as I'm concerned.
I've never met a more unpleasant man than Sean Hannick.
We're going to be hand-attized.
I desperately need to be protected.
I need to be sanitized and immunized from your Hannickization.
The American SmartS available at iTunes, Pod Show, our own website, smartass.hellocignetwork.com
or you can subscribe to our feed, feeds.feedburner.com forward slash the American SmartS.
Shortcut TAS, the American SmartS, of course I look at TAS and think true air speed,
but that's just me.
Yeah, I gotta tell you ever since September 11th, the most recent September 11th, you know,
talked a little bit about some of the conspiracy theories that are out there and about
demolition of the towers and there's so much going on and last night I was talking to Patricia
about as we were in bed and I'm like, you know, do you believe in all these conspiracy theories?
And she's real intuitive about stuff.
She says, now this whole thing, this is like a bitch slap fest between Bin Laden and Bush.
It's a personal thing.
It's between families.
And so I kept taking her down the road and said, okay, why?
And she said, well, it's about money, it's about oil.
So why did we go to Iraq?
Well, you know, and before you know, you're stuck in a couple of conspiracies.
And I think we need to explore this a little bit more, but not, not in the way that everybody's
doing it.
I've seen at probably most of the videos.
I've been reading tons and tons of books and I have to say now that I'm almost done with
legacy of ashes, the history of the CIA, it's pretty clear that throughout, you know,
the past 100 years, the United States government or the clandestine agencies that are contained
within it, which I would have to say, RCA and FEMA, actually, I consider those guys to be
pretty much black box, a black box agency.
It's clear they're willing to do a lot to stir up shit in other countries for sure.
And there's, you know, there's pretty much proof of plans that have been out there to
cause crap on the American soil.
And I'm really looking for, for some insight.
I'm not looking for rehashed videos.
I'm, you know, I'm looking for just for some, some conversation about, I'm not quite
sure how to approach it because before you know, you wind up in the whole conspiracy theory.
And then there's the Aluminati in the new world order and all this stuff, man, I mean,
it really be true.
And I'll be really hypnotized by the Montauk project, you know, I don't feel hypnotized.
Maybe that's why they, uh, why they ban marijuana because people who smoke it probably
you have too much clarity.
Hi, Adam, it's Gary Alexander from Las Vegas, I'm the ultimate podcast.
That was a new video, podcast that I'm doing the combat zone.
Oh man, you got to see his latest episode of the combat zone, he's got a hot fighter on
there.
I'm coming on the search, uh, the new site right this is the new search at podshow.com
searching shows.
Yeah.
Application that you guys have in the minute, yes, I'm also having trouble with this huge
space between the results and the top of the page.
And that seems to be when I, when I use Safari as my browser, I think it'd be honest
with you.
I've always had issues, different issues, but I always had issues when I used Safari
on the site.
When I pull up Safari and view a page in podshow, it is very awkward compared to whenever
I pull up Firefox and view the same page much, much different experience there.
So, you know, I don't know if that's something that you guys are very familiar with and
just kind of accept and want us to accept.
Well, you know, that's a good point.
So what I did is I fired up Safari, uh, the Windows version of Safari, I guess that's
3.0.
And you're right.
Maybe the problem.
I see the banner shows up first before the search results.
That's wrong.
I'm pretty sure that I thought that we were also checking and doing QA on Safari.
This is the problem.
You know, this is exactly the shit that we dropped into with all these different browsers.
You know, I thought the browser wars were over, but oh no, they all implement things
just a little bit differently, which means you got to have a whole cycle, you know,
God forbid, uh, the opera browser gains some traction, which I think it actually might be
certainly on mobile devices, same problem, you know, you've got to have a whole cycle of
a team that that looks for compatibility with, uh, with the, with the Safari browser
and then ultimately I'm sure with the, uh, with the opera browser and that has to be QAed
and it's, uh, it takes an incredible amount of resources to do this, particularly when you're
using a lot of Ajax stuff, so sucks, sucks, I'll talk to the team about it, though,
for sure.
But that's just something I did want to point out.
I also learned to point out, uh, big episode on my, on my video show, become as um,
with Gina Carano.
She just called on Showtime here in the state session, she was, she called on Hawaii,
I won by submission, or at a way for a girl to win, right, by submission, for your naked
joke, is that?
And, um, you should check that out, I'll set you a link to it, and one, everybody, if
you want to see a hot, hot female fighter who can kick your ass, check out Gina Carano
on the combat zone, all right, all right, well, yeah, mom, yeah, of course.
I'm starting to believe this red pill blue pill stuff, let me tell you, I really am.
I don't, I think that I'm still in, like, a purple stage, I don't think I've completely
chumped down the whole red pill, and you're not, I'm seeing all these huge conspiracies
and we're living under, you know, we're being oppressed.
And the world is about to be taken over by a small group of families and the Council of
300.
We are in deep shit, deep deep shit.
Well, I'll just keep it real.
We got, we got bigger problems than new world order.
We've got iTunes problems.
Hey, Adam, Jesse and your hamster, you're saying here, I was thinking you might
be able to answer a question I have, every, it's pretty regular now that the podcast
that I'm so subscribed to will, and I use iTunes as a pod catcher, and I haven't set
up so that once I play a podcast, it disappears and goes away, and next time my iPod
thinks it's no longer on the iPod, but all the time, all of a sudden, I'll think one day,
like 30, 20, 10, all that episode of a show, we'll show back up, just happened for your
show.
It's happened for other independent as well as sort of math produced podcast, and it's
a hassle to go back and delete those 30 podcasts, especially when it's happened all the
time.
So I wonder, is that an iTunes problem?
Was that a problem with the person that puts out the podcast or is that my problem?
You like you could set on that, it would be great.
Yeah.
Well, this is, that's kind of hard to say, whether it's an iTunes problem or some other
kind of problem.
It's really all about the implementation of RSS and the GUID, the global unique identifier,
I think, is what that stands for.
Makes it very complicated to get it right all the time, you know, and what will happen
is sometimes you'll have a system refresh, a new upgrade.
I've seen this happen, it's certainly happened to Pod Show.
I think I've seen it happen with the feed burner as well, and, you know, what happens
is it looks like there's a new feed or a new published date or somehow, I mean, it can
be a very small change that can affect the way your pod catcher in this case, so iTunes,
the way it reacts and what it thinks it's supposed to do and what it thinks it's seeing.
Of course, you know, all these systems are dumb systems, right?
They're just looking for rule-based stuff.
And if something changes that hits the rule set, then it's going to go and redown load.
It's an incredible waste of resources.
I hate it when it happens to us, and I think it happened certainly in the past two or
three months, I've seen it happen.
We're all of a sudden, a whole bunch of older episodes start showing up, and yeah, we try
to be very careful about that, but sometimes shit just happens.
I think that's really it.
Shit happens, you know, this is a relatively new technology.
It can be implemented in a number of ways, of course, typically when people implement
the lazy way, which is the way I would program stuff, being a shitty software engineer,
then stuff, it's breakage, essentially.
It's something, you know, the new Nokia, the N800 video center, I think there's a video
center for N95, but for N800, here's something I discovered, it's really stupid and
it's broken, it's just an implementation, and by the way, you know, the Nokia guys,
and the guys who work on this stuff, in conjunction with Nokia, you know, they're smart,
they're smart developers, so guess what happens?
If you're subscribed to, so I have a couple channels set up, then it actually comes pre-installed
with pod show channels, with specially encoded videos that really perform well on the
N800, if you have a show in two separate channels, or if you're subscribed to these
show to the show twice, well, that's a bad example, regardless, it downloads stuff,
you can play it on the fly, but also download stuff, if the same show in same episode
is in a different feed, it will download the episode again, so you literally will have
the same episode twice, which is broken, I mean, it should say, wait a minute, this is the same
episode, and it should not be downloading that a second time, so I think it was day one
or that said, we make shitty software, so I guess we all do, so just trying to make it better.
Hopefully, just talking about it, will help our brethren who are the software engineers,
look man, they're just trying to figure it out themselves, you know, you can't figure
out every single use case or scenario that someone's going to use this stuff, it's
hard, it's hard, hard work.
All right, last song, this one just added to the Podsafe Music Network, as far as I can
recall, this song was originally written by Howard Jones, and of course, is on the PMN,
he also has his own podcast, and I pick this link up from Nigel Pace, who, as you know,
has become kind of the independent promoter of awesome Podsafe Music, I focus a lot
on the UK stuff, but basically worldwide, he's kicking ass, and I love getting
promoted by him, essentially, I have no idea how his business model works other than
he's an independent promoter for podcasters and independent producers and is really working.
This is Katrina Carlson with the classic Howard Jones song, and I just got to believe
that Howard produced it, and I think I hear him in the background somewhere, have a listen.
Here you can look at the menu, but you just can't eat, you can feel the cushions, but
you can't have a seat, you can dip your foot in the pool, but you can't have a swim, you can
feel the punishment, but you can't commit a sin, and you want her, and she wants you,
and she wants you, and she wants you, and no one, no one, no one ever is to blame, is to blame
you can be the mansion, but you just can't live in it, you're the fastest runner, but
she's not allowed to win some break the rules, they live to kill the cost, the insecurities,
the thing that won't get lost and you want her, and she wants you, we want everyone,
and she wants you, and no one, no one, no one ever is to blame, we want every chance,
you can't have an opportunity, you can't have a chance, is to blame, you can see the summit that
you can't reach it, it's the last piece of the puzzle, but you just can't make it fit, doctor says you're
cured, but you still feel the pain, aspirations in the clouds, but your thoughts go down between
and you want her, and she wants you, we want everyone, and she wants you, no one, no one, no one ever is to blame,
no one ever is to blame, is to blame,
in that pretty great song remains a great song Katrina Carlson no one is to blame you can
find a link to that the pot set music network from the show notes a daily source code.com
just reading through the the upgrade notes here for the new I guess it's the new the new version
of the the any hundred operating system here it is I want to read this to you because
you developers out there might like this the main reasons in Shenukh that's the code name
for the new and our external alignment with the genome and Linux baseline is a top priority this is
why here we go memo is moving to GTK which I think stands for the genome toolkit
two dot one zero and g lib c I don't know that's libraries I don't know exactly how it works I guess
they're integrating the Hilden project so I think what this means is that we're going to have
some great looking applications try true and tested so excited about that actually yeah that's I must
say every single new release of that thing has been more excited about and and I just love the industrial
ness of it I've dropped this thing so many times it's still just plugging away doing its job
all right everybody I got a pack up it's almost 11 o'clock I get to get my ass out to
out to London town let's see what's on what's on deck for today I'm meeting about the
uh oh no I'm gonna go to my uh my g cow here meeting uh see about the uh digital musical words
got a couple of meetings with producers man we are busy we are busy and of course prepping the trip
to Germany more about that later in the week I hope to talk to you guys tomorrow I'm gonna do my
utmost you know Adam of pod show dot com daddy source code dot com uh thanks for listening to
another pod show podcast stick it in your ear
this podcast is brought to you by pod show and go daddy the show will give you a special code to get
great discounts at godaddy.com got something to say log it with your frequent log from godaddy
the best in the brightest served up daily by the shop is mines in content delivery pod show and
lineland