This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts on GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Block it with your free quick blog from GoDaddy.
Hey, Adam, you ever play that game where you pass a phrase from person to person
and then you see what it comes back as after it's going through several people?
Well, try to do that at the podcast music live through a combination of Skype and second life
and people that were there at the performance, a personal and a Matthew evil.
Can you announce the DSC 550?
And well, this is what it came back as.
Thank you for tuning in to the daily source code number 1242.
How did I turn Scottish?
I don't know.
Oh, well, so much for the accuracy of modern technology.
Here's the DSC 550.
In a world where TV networks, movie studios and record labels
still think they can govern what you see in here.
One man has the power to return control of entertainment to the masses
and make big media corporations wet their tiny little pants.
From Pod Show, home of the world's most dangerous new content
comes the Daily Source Code with Adam Curry.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I just can't see it's about a curry.
Just leave part of the safe to move back in the podcast.
The DSC 550.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
And make big media corporations wet their tiny little pants.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Oh yeah.
And combination with that diet coat.
It's actually keeping me up.
The young pumps.
Apparently making some noise in British.
Hey everybody how you doing coming to you from the curry condo. It is the Daily
Source code episode number 550 Delta Shira Charlie is once again in Northern
California for a second time on the new time schedule for the year so it's
going to be about a week of course as you know delayed so I'll be leaving
and I was at Thursday. I got to get back because Saturday evening at the
Lady Patricia and I'm not this coming Saturday but next Saturday we have a
dinner a dinner at Dawson. A dinner date with one of the head honchos of
BT at his house. Oh man speaking of posh people which we'll talk about later
of course. The young punk's by the way and not coincidental that I played
that I got an email from Nigel from podcastlive.co.uk who of course was
instrumental in getting Howard Jones onto the pod save music network. He says
he broke the young punk's to the podcast community on Sunday. Today he got a
message from their management. The young punk's are on news night tonight and
we're on all local BBC radio this morning which went out to 10 and a half
million people coverage in the mirror in the Daily Record as well. Hey hey hey
getting some shit done with that pod save music fantastic. Oh man I'm thankful
that as plenty of stuff that came in while I was traveling I am tired. I really am.
This is like a mid week thing you know when I was kind of prepared to go
on Sunday it's very different and I didn't watch any movies on the flight.
Right about half of a book I'll get it in a second for you and I'll tell you what
book it is. Oh it's how the world was taken over by mumbo jumbo or something
like that. Pretty interesting book. And I don't know what happened though but I
am. My back really really hurts left side lower like lower back which is
very close to the area where I had which I heard when my motorcycle accident
three years ago. So I get I'm old. It's just acting up. Oh what can I do? Oh yes of
course there's always Amy Mac to save the day and make my ass nice and firm in
the process.
Adam it's Amy Mac. Hey baby how you doing? I'm glad to hear you feeling and
sounding better. Yeah. Although it seems that every time you get sick I end up
with it a week later. For two people with a sea each other it's a little
strange. Anyway today we're doing an airplane with it. We've had and switched
mics. Good. I only have one with me so I have to use this.
Start standing with a part. I'm standing though that's good. Okay
shoulder your arms up to the side. Arms out to the side. Even with my shoulders
hip. Now bend forward until your chest is facing the floor. Okay. Now take the right
leg and lift it behind you. From the side you should look like a capital T or an
airplane on a stick. Or an asshole. Great. Now bring everything back to the
starting position. I could feel it though. I could see it. Which legs I've been
bend over and lift the left leg at the same time. Go as far as you can without
tipping over. Really want to lift that leg and squeeze the butt. Good. Now
I'll make and do seven on each side. Okay. I'm doing real quick. Okay. Remember to
breathe through the whole thing. You make it sound so easy. Make sure that standing
knee is slightly bent. Yeah. Yeah. It's the left one that really hurts
Amy. Squeeze the butt and the abs to prevent falling over. With the back
hurts it's not just the butt. Really try to lift that leg and keep your back
straight. Oh, this is great job. No. I mean, I can not plan for us to save the
world. The ass reciting. This all holds until I get the hang of the whole video
thing. There's so much to do for a little show. I'm not surprised but it's
definitely not routine yet. Okay. Well, I hope you have a good visit at HQ. Thank you
Amy. Amy. Let me tell you something. And by the way, Amy is doing a couple of
shows. She's got video going on. Of course, she's got fitness attack where
they me Mac. I'm all out of breath from the exercise. Amy, I guarantee you
if if you are going to do a video version of exercise, it'll be a ratings
Bonanza. What an awesome idea. How can I assist you in getting this done
even sooner? All right. Let's check the voicemail. See who called while I was in
the hour in the air for 10 hours. Adam, hello. It's Colin Grant here from BBC World
Service Radio. It's a digital planet. I'm wanting to get you on the program.
I'm not going to. I'm not going to.
Number. Five.
That's a four. Jesus Christ.
Friday about Citizen Generalism. And I'm going to get you one. Okay, bye.
Friday about Citizen Journalism. Oh, Colin. This is not very hand. Why do you
guys always call so late? You know, for all the money, all the money that you guys
get, you should be able to schedule this a little bit more advanced. You know, now
I got a, I got, I don't know, I don't know, Colin. I don't know. I don't know if I can
do it. Well, I was reading something else by the BBC that the, uh, that's
some like advisory board at the governors or whatever they call it, uh, a very upset
that, uh, BBC, uh, the websites that are viewable outside of the UK are going to or
will or are carrying advertising. And the advertising is filtered out in the UK. It's
kind of weird. Although I'm not against it. I mean, I pay my 190 pounds a year for my, for
my TV license. And I'm very happy with the results. What I get for it, I think it's a damn
good deal. Um, and, uh, if you get me even better programming by exploiting and they sell
so much stuff already. It may, it's not like the BBC is not, uh, it does not have commercial
departments. They more and certainly have lots of commercial. It, look, a BBC's on serious
sidelight radio now. You think they give them that way for free? I don't think so. Let's
see what the next message is. Hi, I don't have a guy in his ex in the shakes. Hey,
I'm going to give you a bounce. I, uh, be listening. And thanks a plan. I'll stop. And, um,
yes, like, it's easy. Thanks for the support with Jason. Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Thank you
guys for being on who's on it. And, uh, for going to podcast, con, UK and for performing.
And you guys are smart. Cause, you know, it's like a total guilt trip. Is like, how, how
can I not, you know, play that? And then, of course, not rip out with the shakes on the daily
source code. I want to bet a line. I want to bet a line. More than these four
worlds. I might have been why if I want to bet a line. I want to be your man. I want to be
your man. Cause you're pretty cool. And you've got to tell me what to be your man. I want to
be your man. I want to be your man. I want to be your man. I want to be your man. I want to be
your man. I want to be your man. I want to be your man. I want to be your man. I want to be your man.
Cause you're pretty cool. And you've got to tell me what to be your man. I want to be your man.
I want to bet a line. I want to bet a line. I want to bet a line. I want to be your man.
Just like the one day before, only fast in the world
What's happening here?
And I want to run the show
Look down from on high, it's your grand-run battle
I want to run the show
And I want to run the show
Look up from on high, it's your grand-run battle
You want to run the show
Oh, this is it, this is it, this is it, this is it, this is it.
The shakes, you can find them on the Podsafe Music Network and of course, Podsho Plus,
Podsho.com slash music, just go to DavySourceco.com and get the direct link to the shakes.
I want a better life.
It's okay.
So I got some aspirin while I was doing that.
It's something really weird going on in the condo.
Everything was still connected when I came back, you know, the TV work and the internet
was up.
I did have to reboot the the wireless router, what I have a a D-Link 624, I think it
is.
And it's really strange, if you're very close to the unit, even it won't even see it.
So you can't even connect to it.
So you have to physically move away and there are some spots which are in a direct line
with the unit.
I can see it from where I'm standing and just like maybe ten, six, seven, maybe ten feet
away and and and and then you can see it then you can connect.
But if you veer like three foot, three feet to the left then it'll still stay connected.
But then, you know, there's no actual throughput of data, it's like I have all these dead spots
all of a sudden.
I have to admit, you know, being on the 24th floor here with the tower of death across
the street, which is now cranky, this thing is grown another seven stories it looks
like, God, that thing is ugly.
Hey, you're gonna take it away in my view.
There are so many Wi-Fi connections, this must be because there's just so much going on.
There, I mean, I think I can count 15 sometimes 25 different Wi-Fi points up here and
they come and go, you know, it's almost like when the wind blows.
But you would think that, and I have tried some different channels, I haven't done anything
this trip yet, so I'm not going to troubleshoot anything yet until you guys tell me what
I should try out, you know, is there some kind of, kind of the Mac, I know on the, I have
the eye Mac here, you can turn on interface robustness, which really makes me feel good
when I turn it on, whatever it means, but apparently that does help it seek out certain
signals better.
But you think the thing is sitting right here, you know, I should have a great connection,
but right now even the laptop that I'm using on the Baker's rack with cast blaster, you
know, to get a proper connection, I actually have to turn the laptop a little bit.
So somehow something is, something's freaky, that's what it is, email from Karen Hardy,
just listen to daily source code 549, you said the Bowie song was from 1975, the year
of my birth and it was 22 years ago, although I often wish I was 22, I am in fact 31 until
September 2nd.
Hey, I'm my birthday, September 3rd.
Karen, I'm an idiot, I'm an idiot, and I can't count, sorry about the, it's something
we have, it's unbelievable, hey Adam, Chef Mark here, and you got me so excited talking
about David Bowie, you know, I am one of the all-time figures, David Bowie fans of all,
and in fact, what you're hearing underneath here is the first live performance of sound
and vision, and your statement got me to thinking about the release date of 75, and I'm
looking back on his whole dysagraphy, and actually, unfortunately, no, that's not true.
Sounded vision was released as a single with a B-side, a new career in a new town in January
477, and the album low came out January 14th, 1977, and you might be thinking of some
of the stuff from David Live, which was released in 75.
Hold on a second, hold on a second, Chef Mark, you are surprising me, did you hear that?
It's like this is the Chef Mark who's always sending in recipes and a little dainty stuff
to impress chicks with, and he's like totally in a bowie, and he's like rattling
off all this information.
All right, you're incorrect, it was an undies, and you know, I was thinking about maybe
I was incorrect, perhaps it was the Detroit Spinner's rubber band man, which was the
other single I had as my first 245, maybe that was from 75, but I really, really, really
think it was possible that maybe it was 75 in Europe, is that possible, and that you're
looking at a US release, Chef Mark.
He did a lot of sort of life things, it was a mix of a lot of the old stuff from Diamond
Dogs and some of the new stuff he was working on, you're going into the Young American
Space.
In any case, you know, this album low was really a groundbreaking album, Brian Eno and
Robert Fripp were instrumental on this album, and I got an interesting little clip to
read to you from about the story of the song Sound Envision.
A reggae style whack on a choke symbol, offsets the little team beat the characterizes
the hit theme from this unnervingly unpredictable sequence of songs.
His bowies concessioned two words, after several bars of Alomar guitar riffing, interspersed
by that old familiar detuned bowie's sax.
So that part where he just sang, is probably he's probably thinking about the sign that
flashes on and off in BBC TV studios, or at least did in the days of Muffin the Mule,
early gig, and what's my line.
Interestingly enough, in 1977 this was picked up by the BBC and used as background music
during announcements for a while, probably at the behest of Alan, Crack to actor Yentong,
he's the guy who he wrote that song about.
What this song says is simple, you don't need to write a triple concept album about mutant
graphs or pploids to maintain a life in pop.
You can mutter a few words, sing along to a silly tune that could be a nursery rhyme, and
still get a hefty advance.
Blue, blue electric blue, that's a color of my room where I will live Sims Bowie,
peeping out from behind the net curtains, and making himself a nice cup of tea.
You know, joins in on the vocals here, together with Mary Visconti, better known to pop
pickers as Mary Hopkins.
There are still no signs of the much-funted, oblique strategies at work, only a bow
in the direction of 50s duo, tune-wise, that is.
This was a big hit that everyone was looking for, and that description comes from the book
we could be heroes, the stories behind every David Bowie song.
This David Bowie moment brought to you by the culinary podcast network with Chef Mark.
Hey, surprise me dude, really, totally blown away by that.
Nice.
Now we have some more things in common.
I actually hook an up with Chef Mark in two weeks in New York, Ron and I are going
to do a New York trip, so looking forward to that.
I was, I don't know what the hell I was going to talk about now.
Hold on, what's this?
I'm just looking at my Google node pad.
That's some biodiesel style.
I'm going to save all that for tomorrow.
And by the way, the developer and 800 for the Trinity developers, and I have received
a couple of requests for SSH access, which means some geeks want to enter my ports, and I'm
going to open them.
I'm going to open my ports.
Why, for you, boys?
Is the couple devices and the navkits and the world license, and I don't know all
this stuff?
Of course, was immediately sent from Finland, and is being held up in Texas at customs.
Of course.
So it may be another day or two.
I think another set is being sent from New York.
And you know, you guys don't mess around, man, when they commit to something, they're
really commit to something.
Hey, Adam, it's Mark.
Just goofing around my guitar here on my lunch break.
And I got another solo for you.
This one sent in by Chip from the top of the pod saves podcast.
Now did you know that the very first guitar solo came on July 2nd, 1863, on the eve
after the first day of fighting at the Battle of Gettysburg, when Corporal Leonard Spanky
McPatterson, noodleed around on his sixth drink for about 20 minutes when he couldn't
remember the 2nd verse to O Susanna.
And an art form was born.
Unfortunately, Spanky took a musket ball to the head the next day, and really didn't
develop it much.
But that, of course, did not stop Chip from top of the pod saves podcast from sending
his solo.
Let's check it out.
Pretty cool, Chip, and for those of you keeping Scott home, Chip says that he was using
his smash-o-blaster, piece of shit, Red Strat Squire that he modified with some cool pick-up,
see more dug-in live wire pick-ups, a Wilkinson Whammy bar, and a graphite nut.
And for those of you who've never had a graphite nut before, let me just dial you.
You have no idea what you're missing.
So there you go, Adam.
There's your guitar solo of the week, thanks to Chip from the top of the pod saves
podcast.
Right on.
And if you're a sixth drink slinger, a shredder, a jazz head, whatever, you play the guitar,
show us your chops.
We want to hear your guitar solo, because the guitar solo is a dying art form.
And let's pump some life into it, okay?
So send your guitar solo to House of Tone, all one word, House of Tone at gmail.com.
Catch you later, Adam.
You nutty bastard you.
Don't change a thing.
Yeah.
Except maybe you're underwear.
Yeah, okay.
Catch you later.
Okay.
Oh, no, this has happened a while.
Sometimes the universe comes together, and the timing is just perfect.
Hey, the other sad life repair man's coming after you.
Sad life repair man, what's he gonna do?
He'll fix your misconceptions and answer questions too.
There's nothing in the universe, and he can't do for you.
Sad life repair man.
I have body, I'm serious.
SM, I guess we'll call SM radio now.
What is up with that merger?
Ah, well, we're New York, rest assured.
I'm gonna go talk to the brass.
He was going on.
Haven't received any other memos.
Other than you will be rich beyond your wildest dreams for sure.
I remember all of a sudden what I was going to tell you,
House of Tupid was on during the shakes.
I went and got that book that I've been reading on the plane.
I picked it up at the airport.
It's my Francis Wien.
Wien.
Whiskey hotel echo echo November.
How mumbo jumbo conquered the world?
And I have to say, this is my kind of book.
I'll just read the the back here.
Uh, because this is kind of what the book is about.
What colonized the space recently vacated by notions of history,
progress, and reason?
Cults, quackery, gurus, irrational panics, new age,
mysticism, moral confusion, and an epidemic of mumbo jumbo.
Francis Wien evokes the key personalities of the post-political era,
including Princess Diana and Deepak Chopra,
of Solomon Bin Laden and Nancy Reagan's astrologer,
while charting the extraordinary rise in superstition,
voodoo economics, and emotional hysteria over the past quarter of a century.
And it is my kind of book.
He gives a lot of history about the whole rise of motivational speakers
and self-help books.
And I'm only halfway through the book.
I'm not quite sure if I want to endorse the book yet.
If you should go buy it, I'm only about halfway through.
And I've to admit the chapter I'm on,
which is the demolition merchants of reality,
is a tough one.
Oh, my head was bobbing in the plane and like,
ah, let's maybe I should watch some mighty boos instead.
Hello, Adam Duke in Portland, Oregon,
home to your friend, Kenster Jay.
Oh, yes.
Portland, Oregon, haven't been there in a while.
And I really must go visit Kenster Jay.
In fact, as my mind is starting to warp around
the free Trinity project.
I'm thinking maybe, maybe,
I drive her up north first.
Portland,
I think I need to go to Seattle.
I would be great to roll up into Kenster Jay's driveway.
Anyway, back to the audio comment.
And I have two comments for you on two different segments.
The first one for your posh of people's segment.
Okay.
I think you can expand this a little bit.
I don't think posh people are just only potty pigs,
but as an airline employee,
I noticed that they're also packing pigs.
They seem to have the biggest bags
that I've ever seen in my life.
Well, you know, of course,
because Mark Jacobs says so,
you have to have the big bag.
You know better than to ask that.
You know, if I was the cherries for a while,
but screw that through the cherries out.
You're absolutely right.
Posh people have,
you know,
and not just,
are they packing pigs,
but there's tremendous synergy.
So no, a symbol,
no, they have matching luggage.
You know, you just can't cut it these days,
unless you've got to matching Louis Vuitton luggage.
I agree.
So,
they're taking up space.
These posh people by overpacking.
And they're potty pigs.
Mh.
Death to them all, I say.
Possibly be packing this amount of these posh destinations,
but they're going to.
It's unbelievable.
One bag, you know,
70 pounds of stuff,
knows.
The second segment is for free kind of these.
Hopefully,
Trinity can make it a beautiful portland organ.
We have a number of fabulous biodiesel facilities,
and hopefully come to find out,
home to a biodiesel processing facility
that can be a river.
So maybe Trinity can make a trip up to Portland,
and we can take her around the town.
Hope that would work out,
and hopefully enough folder and scruncher,
and being an airline employee,
hope retail wins,
or it's not being appropriate for me.
We'll talk to you later.
No, of course not.
It's completely appropriate for you.
Absolutely.
Tail wins to you, my friend.
Yeah, I heard that somewhere
of North,
I was reading it earlier.
I don't have the link handy,
that a biodiesel company got
to $214 million in venture capital,
I think,
to start producing more.
It's fantastic.
Yeah, I'm going to try and do that definitely.
And let us know what airlines you fly for.
And are you flight attendant?
Are you a cabin crew?
No.
Are you cabin crew?
Do you put the yellow door selectors to automatic?
Or are you on the flight deck?
And querying minds need to know my friend.
Hi, Adam.
This is Norman again,
from the German normcast and pod parade podcast.
Hey,
I couldn't talk.
We get it.
A few months ago,
you played the audio feedback that I did together.
Oh,
Wachter, I'm Mal.
I,
I've been in,
sits in Pinkler.
With you,
from the German podcast cafe,
in your daily source code episode number 452.
We were explaining the problem that podcasters
outside the USA might have.
If they play songs from well-known artists
listed in the PMN in their shows,
because these artists are often signed
to the different versions of BMIS cap
in other countries,
like,
for example,
Gamma,
Stemera,
Swisa,
and so on.
The result of this audio feedback being played
in your show was a discussion
in several forums here in Germany,
so it had a positive effect.
But unfortunately,
no problem has been solved since then.
The authorities and organizations
such as the Gamma are moving very slowly
if they move at all.
They sometimes remind me of a big old dinosaur.
In one of your last episodes,
you mentioned the possibility that the PMN
might come to Germany as well.
Hold on a second.
First of all,
let me just summarize what the issue was here.
Unlike the United States with ASCAP BMI,
you can hand out a special license
to anyone you damn will please
to let them play your music.
You could hand away this right
to play a song on a podcast.
And there's another right associated with it
for the download.
But just when it comes to performing rights
organizations,
which is what he's talking about here.
And in many other countries,
and in Germany as well,
once you sign up with an organization
that represents your performance rights,
you do not have that right
to give another special license to anyone else.
So it's very confusing.
And although I think you probably be okay,
and I think you guys have figured it out.
The conversation is good.
And eventually the D.J.M.A.
and Stemrah,
and all those guys, the Lemrah,
the Nimrod,
they should definitely adjust their laws or bylaws.
Now, this is interesting for us
because you and myself and other podcasts
are playing a huge amount of
hopefully pot-safe music
in our shows,
and we have made nice contacts
to several artists and bands so far.
This is just one more thing.
I didn't say the PMN
was coming to Germany,
Germany,
but Podshow,
Podshow may be coming to Germany.
We want to go on with it.
Now, we have got a new phenomenon coming up,
which reminded me a little bit of the Arctic monkeys.
They became famous overnight,
and weren't pot-safe anymore.
I don't think they really were,
and they've never on the pot-safe music network.
I believe they exploded through my space.
I think you're a lot of conflicting information about that.
By the way, your English dude is fantastic.
Absolutely impeccable.
Podparate.de,
the Pot-safe music charts here in Germany,
there was a song that went out of the charts
with the last episode.
It had to,
because every song can only be positioned
for another eight times after its new entry.
We do this because we want to keep the charts fresh
in a way.
A young band from the USA called Rock Kills Kit
did a great song called Parallelized,
and by the way,
the whole album,
which is called IU nervous,
is brilliant.
This song,
which sounds a bit like the early U2,
has been our number one for several times,
and it is the most successful record in the pot-parate so far.
For me personally,
it's the best song of the year 2006.
And now,
the band has appeared in the Gima database,
and they have a contract with Warner Music.
The CD is announced,
for example,
at Amazon DE,
as brand new,
which it isn't,
and it will be re-released
with the beginning of March 2007.
The song is played on some normal radio stations,
now,
and there it is always announced as brand new.
No,
no,
I've played it in my own show
for the first time in August 2006.
The problem now is that many people
who have played that song also in their podcast shows,
are now wondering if they have to take these particular episodes
of their own shows from the internet
in order not to eventually violate some laws.
We,
who are doing the pot-parate,
will not do so,
because we think that these episodes
were legal and correct when they were recorded.
Because you're really mad at that song,
that's what I realized.
So,
this is another thing that has to be looked after in the near future,
I think.
Thanks for the attention, Adam,
regards to all your listeners,
and keep up the good work,
including playing the Beatles in your show.
It was really great.
And the next time,
you come to Germany,
hopefully there'll be a chance for us to meet you.
Bye for now.
I thank you.
Choose.
I would very much like that.
Absolutely.
And I think,
you know,
maybe you shouldn't overanalyze it all that much.
I'm sure it's okay.
I really am.
And I'm sure that the law,
it's just a text time to change laws.
I don't know if anyone who's gotten into trouble
for playing something that has showed up in a gamma database,
all of a sudden.
And I think you're right to just continue to play Rock Hills kid.
In fact,
if anything,
you know,
Rock Hills kid should go to bat for you.
They should be kissing your archlock for helping him out.
You know what I'm saying?
Let's see what it's all about.
No way.
In that gamma database.
Rock Hills kid.
the breakout hit, it's amazing. Rock kills kid, paralyzed. On the rise, pod safe. Link in the
show notes at deadlysourcecode.com. Amazing, it's 38 minutes. I didn't think I was going to do
it like close to the normal 40 today. And I just tried to get my Gmail going again. I don't know
what's wrong with this Wi-Fi crap. I gotta look at that. Anyway, have yourselves a great day,
Thursday and just about every single part of the world, unless you're down under and you'd
maybe a little bit later. And maybe tomorrow. And some other, somewhere else, maybe yesterday.
I'll be back tomorrow for sure. And oh, it'll be, uh, thank God, it's Friday.
Oh, man, fantastic. Food barred. That's what I am. Can't wait for the weekend. Take care
yourself, everybody. DailySourcecode.com. Adam at podshow.com. Talk to you tomorrow.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery,
podshow and linelight.