Yo, what's Tony Costa telling you to check out this Christmas podcast.com.
It's the official podcast for the new Sony film, this Christmas,
starring Chris Brown for Genie King, Columbus Short, and an all-star cast.
The site includes a special holiday podcast from yours truly,
exclusive interviews from the stars in the film,
and a special red carpet coverage from the premiere.
You can exchange gifts, but you can't exchange family.
This Christmas is truly the next holiday classy.
See it in theaters on November 21st, and check us out at thisChristmaspodcast.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie, 6-8-4, when two tracks go to war.
1-2-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1
-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-
-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-2-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-2-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-
And we'll show it
I'll show it
I'll show it all
This is the worst scene
I think you're making fun of me
I listen to the worst scene
I'll know where you...
Let's pretend that they are now
Say what you can do
I'll show it all
We got to Georgia, my life's
Oh man, it's hard to soundtrack to my life for the past 25 years.
Frankie goes to Hollywood to tribes.
On Delta, Sierra Charlie's 684 coming to you from the Curry Manor.
We're back in Blighty.
Hey everybody how you doing?
I actually had that song lined up to play for the Fubar Friday.
In fact I had pretty much a whole Fubar Friday lined up.
At the time I was home Friday and my partner in crime on the No Agenda show.
John C. DuBourke had been waiting for probably about two hours for me to hook up with Skype
and do our No Agenda show, which is a lot easier for me because I can just sit there
and just listen to him and talk some shit back and forth.
I was spent.
I had nothing left.
I had no more energy.
I'm so sorry.
So I'll keep a lot of that stuff.
I just could not hold back on playing this because even though it was written and performed
over 25 years ago, it still holds true today.
If you listen to the lyrics and feel the vibe.
Nice guys, by the way, Frankie goes to Hollywood.
I hung out with Holly Johnson quite a bit in Amsterdam.
I think they recorded the follow-up album I believe to this.
They recorded in the vis-a-lored studios in Hilversum.
And the bass player is kind of weird.
But Holly is a real nice guy.
And I know he's around somewhere in the UK.
This is one of the worst things ever.
At one point, there was a news report that he had died in an airplane crash.
I can't remember which one it was.
Some big horrific crash.
And he was supposed to be on it.
But he wasn't.
And I think a lot of people still think he is dead.
But he's not.
Anywho.
My goodness.
It's been quite a trip.
Saturday morning.
Got up.
I did my usual routine.
Of course, I was going to leave for the airport early afternoon to fly back.
I just got to tell you a bit about this.
First of all, I'm writing all this stuff and I'm online on the MacBook Pro, which
Oh, man.
I love this thing so much.
I got a happy MacBook Pro story to tell you.
So I'm writing away.
And then, you know how if you unplug your Mac, then the screen dims just slightly.
But it can also happen if the light, if the ambient light changed a bit, your screen
will change in brightness.
Which is to adjust, of course, for whatever situation you're in.
Did realize that happened from moment and then I say, hey, wait a minute.
My Mac is disconnected from from the wireless networks.
I'm hunting around that I can't find the wireless network.
And I don't understand it.
In fact, I don't see any wireless networks.
And then it hit me.
I was, of course, doing my laundry, which, you know, this guys, if you ever have the opportunity
to come home from a long trip with your laundry freshly done, guaranteed blow job time.
I'm telling you.
So I'm doing my laundry.
And I said, wait a minute, I don't hear the dryer anymore.
Well, the power had gone off in the building.
Yeah.
So I'm like, I'll just write for a little bit longer.
I was writing in, uh, in Gmail.
So, um, you know, I did all probably already auto saved half of my email.
And I'll just continue.
So I wrote for about another half hour, 12 to 12 30.
And I still know power, right?
Because that, of course, is what happened is the power went off.
And the same is disconnected my power cord.
And I'm like, well, yeah, I'm going to find out what's going on.
Because I do want to post this message.
I was actually a message to a number of pod show producers.
And so I do, I do the select all Apple key all.
I select the text I've been writing just in case, right?
Because it hadn't, it hadn't been able to auto saves since I had no net connection.
Posted it into a text, uh, was it simple text or text edit document.
It used to be simple text, teach text.
Now I think it's just text edit.
And I just leave it there on the screen.
I call the downstairs to the concierge.
Oh, man, no, the whole block's out.
They expected to be out for a couple hours.
And indeed, by the time I left a 23245,
it still did not come on, which was a real bummer
because I wanted to set up the I Mac there with back to my Mac.
But of course, I should have done that one before before the day of departure.
Um, and then I'm like, well, you know what?
I still, so between 12 30 and 230, I still had some time.
Like, you know, let me show you if I can figure if I can hook it up
to my cell phone.
So I'm mucking around, right?
And, and of course, I did something wrong.
This configured.
I didn't have the right information for the, for the, uh, for the cell phone provider.
And somehow the Mac locked up.
Now this is not such a big deal.
It does happen, particularly when doing Bluetooth shit.
I mean, this happens.
It happens with all PCs that it just gets confused.
I don't know what it's doing.
It'll lock everything up.
And then I realized that that text document that I had posted this, you know,
like an hour and a half worth of writing work into.
I hadn't saved it.
It was still sitting there as untitled.
But I couldn't save it.
I couldn't do anything to get out of it.
And I'm like, fuck.
You know, so just fuck it restart the fucking thing.
So I'm pissed.
I'm like, ah, shit.
By the way, I, at that point, I was sitting at the window.
I found, uh, some kind of wireless network.
Since the building was out, it was pretty easy to get some further signals
and connect.
And like, okay, I'll just start all over again.
Let me see how much Gmail has saved.
And of course, it had saved about half of it.
And check this out.
I fire up, text edit.
Am I document fucking reappears?
If reappears on the screen.
I'm like, fuck you Steve Jobs.
You make some awesome shit.
I'm really, really digging it.
Hello Adam.
This is Ranger Craig from the lock.
Normally, but unfortunately, for the past five days,
I've been working with our instant command team,
dealing with the oil spill here in the Bay Area.
So for those of you who hadn't heard about it,
oil tanker hit the bridge in San Francisco and started to leak oil.
Of course, Ranger Craig was the first one to welcome
me back to San Francisco at the beginning of last week.
And he's the, the first one to, well,
welcome me back home with this horrible message.
So please pay attention because Ranger Craig does need some help.
As does the city of San Francisco.
I'm calling you.
I know you have a lot of listeners in the San Francisco Bay Area.
And if you could let them know,
we need help.
It's starting to come together here in terms of using volunteers.
Folks that live in San Francisco,
called for you on one to find out more information about volunteering,
helping with the stillking up and bird rescues.
Other folks can visit the website for alcatraz,
or the Golden Gate National Recreation Area.
That's nps.gov slash alcatraz,
or nps.gov slash GEOGA.
And they can probably link to get more information.
It's really important that people don't try to deal with the oil,
touch it, or come into contact with it.
It is really, really toxic stuff.
I mean stuff.
So let them know that they should get some training
and get a little orientation for going out there to help.
And that's the way they can help.
Again, go to the Park Service website for Golden Gate,
or alcatraz, called for you on one of the living San Francisco.
And help us try to clean up this basket for the take years.
To recover from this, they've already cancelled,
or are talking about canceling crab season this year.
It was a bad spell, but not as bad as it could be,
but we can go and help with it and get it.
And I thought you might be one of the people
that can help get that word out.
So hopefully I'll be back from the rock in the near future.
And the meantime is along from San Francisco Bay.
All right, Ranger Craig.
Thank you very much, my friend.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't be there to help myself.
I'd love to have done anything I can.
So of course, if you're in San Francisco,
you want to help call 3101 or go to the website.
Ranger Craig mentioned to see if you can contribute.
Yeah, I actually looked at some of the new sites,
looking for some more information on this.
I mean, it's a bad accident.
It's a nasty ecological issue that is taking place.
And what is the new show me?
Britney Spears runs red light with kids in the car.
Fuck you, journalist.
You all suck ass.
Hey, Adam.
This is Scott from Dallas.
The booth next to your show yesterday.
And you were talking about, and I can't remember which DSCA was,
but you were talking about how some people are telling you to lighten it up.
And I know comic strip blogger said something about that as well.
But I wanted you to know that I had fallen off listening
on a regular basis for the last few months.
And just again, and I have just blown away by the value
that you spot taxes delivery now.
So I appreciate you being political.
And I appreciate you bringing some new insight to the things
that are going on all around this.
And I just want to say, from Dallas, you fuck you, Adam.
Yeah.
And that's okay.
And this is what I say to lots of people.
It's okay.
You don't have to listen to every single episode.
You can pick it up somewhere, really.
And you may not understand some of the little things
that are popping throughout the conversation.
But you'll pick up on it.
Sometimes people say, you're doing, you're not doing this.
You don't do this anymore.
You show us become this.
You show us become that.
You become this.
I'm unsubscribing.
It's like, go ahead.
It's okay.
You're allowed to drop out.
There's nothing that says, you know,
just because, you know, you started that you have to come back
every single day.
It's really believed me.
It's totally okay.
Not a big problem.
During that call, I got a call from super super chief head sales
Weasel, Chris Jacob.
He's in things in Berlin today and we're meeting on Wednesday.
I'm pretty excited about this.
We're meeting in Helsinki.
I'm going up to Finland.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
We have a meeting with the Nokia folks, which I'm pretty excited about.
So looking forward to that.
I don't think I've ever been to Helsinki.
No, in fact, I'm positive I've never been to Helsinki.
And if it wasn't such short notice,
I'd consider taking the Delta Sierra up.
Although it's just looking at the weather report.
It's like snow minus four for Wednesday,
minus seven or minus eight degrees expected on Thursday.
I don't even know if the Delta Sierra's heater can handle that.
So that'll be fun.
Let me see.
We got lots of stuff to do today.
Since since I missed Thursday and Friday,
got some cool feedback from you guys.
And of course, I have to catch up myself a little bit
on the Fubar Friday.
That means time for the hit test.
I'm growing casting with Adam Curry.
I Adam, who are you ready to be stumped?
Oh, yeah.
Because he used the hit test with young problem.
Hey, Adam.
This is hit test number 95.
Yes.
And here we go with intro number one.
Bring it on, man.
That's something my intelligence here.
Instead of course, as my old piano Miss Diana Ross,
you can't slip that one by me.
Easy, easy.
Number two.
Oh, another fit young.
This isn't hard.
This is fantastic.
Go over Washington, Junior.
I'm just a two of us.
Oh, man.
I'm going to get three out of three again.
Bring on number three, young.
And number three.
And it's like something from those SOS Band days.
I don't know.
I'm going to give it up on three.
And time's up in these ID answers.
Answer number one is from 1980.
This is Diana Ross.
Oh, yeah.
My old piano.
My baby is 10.
We'll live on my party.
But still be 10.
And I'll be 10.
No, be as cold.
My old piano.
It's 80 in case my.
And this is answer number two from 1981.
Bill Witterson.
Grow for Washington.
I see the crystal rain drops fall.
And the beauty of it all is when the sun comes shining.
All right, sing along now.
Just the two of us.
We can make it if we try.
And the beauty of it all is when the sun comes shining.
All right, sing along now.
Just the two of us.
We can make it if we try.
Building castles in the sky.
Just the two of us.
Bill Witterson.
You and I.
Thank you for watching.
Just the two of us.
Answer number two.
What's the third one?
And this is answer number three from 1987 ABC.
Offer on an early age.
A look of what?
No.
To me.
It's cold.
Oh, it's cold.
Moonlight.
Love died.
There we go.
I got it.
On the night.
Moonlight.
Earthlight.
It's cold.
Outside.
Moonlight.
Love died.
On the night.
You.
The ABC and the night you murdered love.
There's answer number three.
It says number nine.
Not even close.
Try to three.
So Adam, how did you do?
I had two out of three.
It's been better.
It's not too bad.
The answer said to this hit test.
And also the iTunes link.
So you can buy these tricks online.
Can be found at hittest.pharchio.com.
Next week, I'll be back for hittest number 96.
So until then, take care.
And bye-bye.
To be back.
Hittest.
And she will.com.
info.
Y'all.com.
J.N.B.O.L.D.P.
D.S.
Ah.
The infamous Y'all.
So we'll have another one on Friday.
If I get to the football Friday.
Which should work out?
Because it'll be back Thursday from Finland.
And we can do a regular Friday show.
Thank you very much.
I'm working towards episode number 100.
Not bad.
Mom.
Ah.
I told you.
I had chief sales with Chris Jacob in Germany.
And Berlin.
Here's a.
I think a voice mail comment from Germany.
Hello.
Adam.
Sales guy.
You from Germany.
Ah, of course.
Sales guy.
You.
Adam.
I was selling something today.
And I was just thinking.
How do you.
How does sports show make money?
Could you explain the thing?
Is that just.
Do you just make money?
Based on advertisements?
Or do you also develop applications that you sell to companies?
I'm just curious to find out.
You know how.
How sports show can be used.
So you can afford your luxurious lifestyle.
Yeah.
Would be great if it gives me some insight.
Think deep.
All right.
Sales guy.
You.
Well, first of all, I actually pay for most of my own luxurious lifestyle.
I hate to say it.
Because I've worked pretty hard for the past couple of decades.
So most of that I take care of myself.
Yeah.
We have three ways of making money.
Might as well tell you right now.
And I'm not ashamed of it.
Very proud of it.
In fact, we syndicate.
Our platform our content.
So that's one way to make money is by our deal as an example in the United Kingdom with.
I British telecom.
That's just one way.
Really.
It's advertising.
It's going to be a large chunk of our business model.
And we're getting better at it every single day.
There's another.
There's another category of making money, which we do.
Which actually does quite well for us.
And I think we're going to do a lot.
No, I know we're going to do a lot more of it in 2008.
We're just loosely calling it seller payment.
And the best example of it right now is go daddy.
And in fact, I got a nudge from the guys from from the guys at HQ that I haven't been
keeping up my go daddy quota.
The way this works is, and this has this I have to tell you that seller payment.
I eat the idea of me promoting products or services in my show.
However, I feel fit.
And then essentially, well, I don't get paid.
But anyone else on the pod show network who participates does get paid.
My money goes straight back into the pod.
So that's another way pod show makes money.
Is by signing up customers for products and services.
So go daddy.
Which, by the way, if you're going to get a domain name, which eventually,
I think, almost everybody does.
And go daddy is all kinds of extra products like a quick blog.
You know, they've got free email.
There'll be associated with your domain names.
You could register Adams going to healthsynki.com.
And I could have a blog with it within seconds.
I could have a special email address for it.
And what the deal is is if you use my codes and actually on curry.com,
and I'll post a link in the for now.
And I really should post a link in the show notes as well.
If you use a checkout code DSC1, DSC2 or DSC3,
you can get all kinds of different fantastic deals at go daddy.
Which you just can't get cheaper anywhere else,
but through the pod show network.
And the shows associated with the pod show network.
There are people making significant amounts of money with this,
which means of course that pod shows also making significant amounts of money.
And the way it works is we go out and we find fantastic products.
And we negotiate a bounty for each new customer.
We sign up or someone on our network signs up.
And we also negotiate a really good discount,
which of course you can't get anywhere else.
It's kind of like a QVC needs MTV if you will.
So those are the three ways we make money.
And then of course we steal it wherever we can.
So out of Jeff for Michigan.
Just wanted to say on a lighter note.
I was, I remembered what you said at the beginning,
actually the end of last year,
your kind of thought of the year or at least prediction for the year
that the music industry would be in a major meltdown by the end of it.
I think that's starting to occur.
My small little red film moment at that time.
This is recently I just read in a couple of blogs and some news articles
that radio had and Trent Resner of nine inch nails,
I believe, where the two that are going to give their music away for free.
And the whole thing being is that since the bands make their money,
they're going to get the music out there as they're advertising
and get people into the concerts.
Which makes a lot of sense.
And that's the way a lot of people like to support their bands as being there.
So anyway, I thought I'd pass that along.
It's kind of break up some of the other red film moment.
I'm a little lighter.
Hey, take it easy man.
All right, dude.
Thank you so much.
And thank you for reminding me of that.
Because we often forget to go back and look at our predictions.
And while you were talking there, I pulled it up.
This was posted on January 1st, 2007.
There's a lot here.
I'm not going to read it all.
But my predictions for 2007 in media entertainment.
The music sales industry will suffer a total meltdown.
As several established artists, without a current record deal,
will crack the online social media networks.
Although sales will not be significant, mainstream media will build a case against
the big three labels, touting their demise.
Shareholders will become nervous,
resulting in a stock tail spin and an exodus of management.
I think all of these things are pretty much happened.
The lawyers left running the joints won't be able to maintain sufficient levels of creativity
to keep business viable.
The artist responsible for the upheaval.
Manage their online customer base to their own online presence.
Utilizing a myriad of APIs available to them for sales, messaging,
and media distribution through channels such as PMN and CD Baby.
There you go.
Isn't that exactly what happened with the radio ahead?
The music publishing business will flourish as new players innovate on licensing terms
and become talent development agencies.
In some cases, this will be the indie record labels.
I think that's exactly what's happening.
Madonna has now signed a new form of record deal where the label is essentially getting
a lot of money from her performances, her concerts.
Let me see, then I say there will be a open source cross platform iTunes replacement
that will open the floodgates and new content.
I don't know if that's really happened.
Mobile playing options drive time audiences will search for audio podcasts.
I think that's definitely happening.
As you go back and read it, but some of the things,
I guess it was pretty easy to predict these things.
Maybe I'm not that smart and they feel it's just simple to predict.
Hi Adam, this is Charles.
Hey, Charles, the drunken Londoner.
Oh, sober Londoner.
I'll just walk down our golf street.
Yeah, you know, half as funny when you sober Charles.
Yeah, I was looking to yesterday, which is what I'm trying to make.
Just approaching kind of a street.
There's just two, this wonderful city.
No, well, no, well, I'm talking about.
Yeah, yeah.
All right.
All right, Charles, what's up?
So I was looking to yesterday, which is what's the day today?
It's the, what's that?
The eight.
Uh, 683.
November.
So it was a seven.
You're talking about the dollar dropping.
I have to say, you know, rats and thinking ships seem so bit unfair,
but when people like to sell,
whose sister, let's call her Mrs. Bunchin.
Oh, you're talking about Gisela Bunchin, the supermodel.
Um, brokers, her deals and it's a manager.
She, um, from what I read, has just, um, just, uh,
demanded payments or requested payments for her latest job.
One of our latest job in euros.
Yeah.
You know, that's kind of telling.
Isn't it?
It seems just shame.
It seems like, um, you have to, you ask those down.
They're going to take a lot of us with them.
Well, you know, I think you're making a good point here.
Um, and honestly, uh, I'd be happy to get paid anything in euros right now.
Uh, for the very same reason, it's, it's just much more stable.
So yeah, if it's happening on a micro level like that with Gisela Bunchin,
who, by the way, uh, I could think of any other ways to pay her for her services.
Uh, you can now only imagine how other countries must be feeling.
Yeah, I should, man.
You know, why don't we, um, why don't we consider getting paid in euros?
Or trading that oil in euros?
Yes, it truly is an issue.
Hey, Adam, this is Matt Collin, you're from West Michigan, right along the beautiful
shoreline of Lake Michigan.
You know, it's one of those Americans that I add definitely not happy with the direction
that this country is going to, I think we've just totally lost track of where we should be,
you know, heading to and doing, you know, in the world, everything.
I kind of have this little theory that I think kicking around.
You know, when it comes down to it, really the United States, the actual government itself,
what we're, we're like 230 years old, kind of a thing.
We're still babies when you look at the rest of the government throughout the world,
especially, you know, like anywhere in Europe, Great Britain, France, Spain, whatever.
Even the Middle East, we're even much younger than that.
Yeah, I'll just stop you there for a second.
Yes, and many would say that there's been no empire that has lasted more than 200 years.
So we're probably living on some borrowed time.
Of course, all of these other empires have reinvented themselves.
So yeah, I'm following you there.
If a father of a pre-teen daughter or a pre-teen in general, you know,
she's looking older, she's starting to act older, but at the same time,
you know, she needs to be reminded once in a while that she's not.
And that's, I kind of see the fact that, you know,
to me, it looks like the United States of America is kind of having this,
we're getting bigger, we're getting stronger.
We think we know everything in fact is, we don't need to remind it once in a while that.
We don't know everything.
And so for those older established governments who have already gone through this,
and now maybe, I don't know, maybe they're in their 30s.
Now if you want to look at that way, they've been there, they've done this.
And maybe that's what our problem is right now.
We just need to be reminded that, hey, we're one part of a larger world community.
And it's kind of maybe figure out what's going on with ourselves before we can do anything else.
I don't understand, making sense.
Anyways, though.
Yeah.
I'll see, scruncher, red pill, and, oh, yeah, fuck you out of the way.
Yeah, thank you.
Yeah, I have to agree.
You know, I have my own moronic teenage you hear at home as well.
And yeah, they, you know, absolutely.
It's adolescents, perhaps.
But we do have to kind of work on it.
And we got to work on it kind of quickly because you only have a short amount of time
when the teenage you start to act like an idiot that you've got to bring them back down to earth.
We'll be participating in that as much as I can.
Ah, one thing we can do while she Yankee doodles.
Oh, wait a minute, this was done in Norway.
Oh, it doesn't count, I guess.
We can mash up.
You'll love this one, check it out.
Oh, wait.
That's the way it should be.
Say you, say me.
Say it together.
You need me.
But you know I'm in.
You need me, say me.
You need me.
I have to agree.
I have to offer me.
Oh, it doesn't count, I guess.
You need me.
That's the way it should be.
Say you, say me.
Say it together.
You need me.
How you want me?
lean in here.
That's the way it should be.
May I come before me to talk to you?
You can't pretend it's just an ugly thing
It doesn't matter what I say
I'm flowers I see, fresh
And make you feel like a pain
It's been a treat for best with friends
You didn't get all the tears
You saw me, I'll show you the world
I mean when you are right now
But I made it through your heart
I'll tell you a different story
We lost it, I'm open, don't you?
You see, tomorrow he will be me
Thank you
Hey there, this is Rich Pab
And my 10 year old son
Tony
And almost every day we bring you the Japanese podcast
And in this podcast we teach you how to say things that you will never ever use in Japanese
Like for example, you should never say to your mother and law
And you should never use or stress
Take that line
And you should never say this on the train
If you're interested in learning Japanese, you will never ever ever ever ever use
Come to the japplishpodcast at www.japplishpodcast.com
Almost done
Yes, same to you
You know he got his 10 year old kid to say fuck you Adam Curry and Japanese
That's a very cute show, by the way, I like it very much
Hey speaking of foreign languages
Here's a savank we haven't heard from in a while in the Charlie
Hey Adam, this is, I don't know
The lazy friends fuck out, yes
And I'm calling you
You know, nice, nicely done with Ron Paul
Even though, you know, libertarians are not exactly my cup of tea
But at least the guy sticks to his convictions
So, you know, good for him
And I like the fact that he's the only Republican who has been very clear about
You know, condemning waterboarding and qualifying it as torture
And by the way, did we actually confirm an attorney general who did not condemn waterboarding
As torture?
Is that actually, did that actually happen while I wasn't looking?
That's unbelievable
I asked for your little problem with the TSA
What were you thinking?
You know, you said over and over
During your, you know, in the DSC
You said over and over that you were going to
Bring something along, just to prove that security doesn't work
Well, that's what you played and you lost
No way, hold on a second, hold on a second
First of all, lots of misconceptions about this
I'm not on any no fly list, okay
The lazy French fucker has it, has it by the right end
I'm getting opened up upon arrival by custom
So that's a little bit different than most people are thinking
Yeah, it's possible
So that would mean that the echelon project is working
Either a, the echelon project works so well
They could decode the daily source code
And here those horrible comments I made
Or it means that someone in the audience called them up
And told them to be on the lookout for what I'm bringing in
Which I think is probably more likely
I mean, no sympathy there then
You, you, you know, you played around with them
And because you're wrong, it proves you that, you know
They can put some people on the watch list
And, you know, it works to some extent
No, I'm not, I'm no big fan of that, you say
I hate, you know, those stupid restrictions about liquids
And things like that, I think it's stupid
But, you know, you know, the one who said you were going to play with them
And, well, you know, they, they figured you were going to try something
So now you're blessed with it, hey, sorry dude
But you should have, if you don't get it on the download or something
Anyway, um, well, I hope you see you around
Then, uh, can just go sometimes soon
You take care, bye-bye
Yeah, I was actually getting something
Because you, you're called there, I know reminded me of something
Uh, when I went to the airport at San Francisco
I had not seen this before and maybe I just missed it
Or maybe it is brand new, I think it's new
There was a booth near the check-in counters
Uh, the international check-in counters
And, uh, right near the door
And it had this, like, eerie kind of blue neon high-tech glow
And there's this sign, this square sign that said clear
And, uh, the TSA, TSA guy who, it's the same guy by the way
Who checks your passport before you check-in
It's, it's crazy
Uh, so they checks my passport before I check-in
You know, ask me the three important questions, you know, did you pack your bags yourself
You have anything sharp?
Um, and he said, hey, you should really check it out as a good deal
Now listen to this, my friends
Uh, I have the brochure here
Fly through airport security sign up today at flyclear.com
Avoid the hassle of airport security
I'm like, well, that's pretty interesting
What is it?
Well, first of all, why clear?
And just think of this name
Just think of how smart this name is
Hey man, don't worry, you can go through security
Because you're clear
Does that sound science fiction or what?
Why clear fast?
Get through airport security faster with less hassle
Don't worry about unpredictably long lines
It's convenient
Access a designated security line with special benefits
Enjoy help from our attendance as you go through the clear lane
Use your clear card at all participating airports at no additional cost
It's secure
Your identity is verified using your fingerprint and iris images
The department of Homeland Security will administer continuous security review of members
This is it, this is the national ID card
This is how they're going to track your ass into oblivion
So just imagine, right?
So I'm looking at this in this belief
But they've created a product called clear
So essentially, you know, now they can track your ass anywhere
And all it is is you just get a different security line
You still have to go through the metal detector
You still have to go through x-ray stuff
But I love this line, I just really loved it
The department of Homeland Security will administer continuous security reviews of all members
So this is like please, would you please like track my ass everywhere I go
Again to you, this will become mandatory within the next three to five years
If we don't get a guy like Ron Paul in the White House
We're fucked, my friends
$99.95 for the first year, what a bargain to be tracked by the American government
And upon arrival in the UK, oh yes, iris, the faster way to clear immigration
It's the exact same thing
So every country now wants you to have an ID card with a little chip on it
That's so that they can track you
I don't think so, I really don't think so
And if you think that that's cool and it's no hassle, think again
Do not, I repeat, do not sign up for any fingerprint or iris scanner
Any recognition systems, it is the beginning of the end
I'd love for the Buckeye Drive Time podcast and the tone ranger
Fuck you
Fuck you, I don't care
There's a word into the Blackwater type of companies.
And you're right, I didn't even bother to realize
or think about the fact that there are thousands
of these companies out there.
But one very important factor that I think a lot of people
probably don't realize about these private companies.
As you know, currently the US publicly states,
the number of US soldiers killed,
and has that number come down.
It looks good for Bush, blah, blah, blah.
But what a lot of people don't realize
that these private security and these private firms
when they incur guests, because they are a private company.
They are not reported.
So for every US soldier that is no longer killed
in the war overseas, they have a private firm
is loses a person.
Not counted.
So on behalf of the US,
the US people never actually really know about it,
which I think is something that is very,
very important that they still look
and be loved into.
Cheers, give a good shot.
Good work, man.
Thank you.
And actually, that brings up another thing I just want.
And this is something, I guess, on Friday,
John C. Duvorak and I will bring up again.
On no agenda, there was this story that was sent to me
about a Dutch couple.
Between 25 or 30 years old, who were caught caught,
I would say, it's not illegal.
Hitchhiking in Texas on the way to Mexico
is they were backpacking throughout the US.
They wanted to go all the way down to South America
and then over to Australia.
And they were picked up by Border Patrol
and thrown in jail for six weeks
without an opportunity to speak to an attorney,
without an opportunity to phone home to the Netherlands.
I had no one to call in the US.
Now this story, I think it's kind of popped
to the top of the stack again in Holland
because this couple are now saying they're going to sue
the United States, which is probably why they got
some attention, but it all happened at the end of 2006.
And it appeared on a television show in Holland,
in February of 2007, I think.
The program is called Nova.
And this television program pretends
to be a very journalistic, a deep journalistic program,
which is bullshit because I've been on the program
and they don't do any work at all,
as far as I can tell, any journalistic work.
And so I took a look at this and I'm like,
oh, this is pretty interesting story,
so I really wanted to get the first hand information.
And at one point, the woman of this couple says,
after a month, after four weeks in jail
in this jail in Texas, they were allowed to finally write
a letter, so they were writing letters to each other
in the same jail, of course, she was in the women's ward
and he was in the men's ward.
And I freeze framed the video because they showed an envelope
and from that I got the jail in,
it was at, oh boy, hold on a second.
Now I got to go and find it.
I didn't write this down, anyway.
So I discovered the name of the jail
and I googled it and it was very hard to find anything.
In fact, it's homepage had been removed,
which I found interesting.
It was not just the 404, but a server not found,
so it was completely gone.
It turns out it's a commercial jail
and it's run by an outfit called management,
the management training company.
Interestingly enough, a former executive
of the managing the management training company
was the consultant to the cleanup of jails in Iraq,
in particular the Abu Graib Hotel.
Ha ha ha ha, prison.
Does that mean anything to you?
And when you read, and I'm not gonna post any links about this,
I wanna keep this discussion kind of on the Noah gender,
so we'll do that on Friday,
but I think we really should go deep into this investigation,
because clearly it's one of these commercial jails,
which are incentivized, as they say,
to keep people out, but of course they're not,
because every person they get into jail,
they get paid for and there's money rolling around
and clearly they're shit and they're horrible
and unconstitutional behavior going on on these jails.
Just it blew me away in two regards, one,
how easy it was to track this down
and these journalists of serious newspapers,
the Al-Hameen Dochblot in Holland and of Nova,
had not even gone that far to even Google the name of the jail,
they could have found out so much
that there's a real story here, a real story.
Hundreds of millions of dollars in contracts
have been a war probably no bid contracts
have been awarded to this company.
And it's, the shit just keeps on getting deeper, my friends.
Oh, wait a minute, I gotta pop a red pill haul.
Okay, yeah, I feel much better.
Hey, it's already 45 minutes.
I wanna play one more song for you
and this voice mail attached to it.
Hey Adam, this is Laura Adams.
I have to show, called the MBA Working Girl Podcast,
and I just wanted to share some random thoughts with you.
Number one, I love using the PMN for my show.
I just found a funny, funky song
that you might wanna play called Super Hot Lady Cup.
Also, thanks for recommending the Constitution classes.
I watched all of them and am now studying
more about the Constitution on my own.
If you haven't seen a video called The Money Master's,
how international bankers being control of America,
a highly, highly recommended.
It's about three hours and 35 minutes,
but it's just jam-packed with excellent information.
And you're really responsible for opening my mind
that to Ron Paul.
He is now my name.
So thanks so much for what you do to that the great work, bye-bye.
Yeah, all right, right on.
Well, first of all, let me just check the latest Tally.
Ron Paul, now over $8 million,
we have just under two months to get the remaining 4 million
for the 12 million quota that we're looking for.
It's necessary in order to have enough money
to advertise before the primaries,
which have actually been moved up
with some mysterious reason.
So yeah, I'm still definitely right behind Ron Paul.
If we get this guy elected, boy, would that change our lives?
It certainly would be a way to bring this
moronic teenager of a country that we have back in the line.
It's completely necessary.
So far, I see no other candidate who has even
a semblance of the right idea.
Second point to your comment there.
Yeah, I know, Bohall, I have played this song in the past
probably two years ago when we were still at the cottage.
Happy to play it again, super hot lady cup.
It is Bohall.
Super hot lady cup.
I want to go to the coma, but I ain't got the time.
But this lady cup is driving me, driving me out of my mind.
Won't you stop writing that ticket?
Walt is 100.
He helped you change your mind.
What to do with them now?
Hands cut, you're pretty like that,
I felt that you and me could reach a top of five.
Super hot lady cup.
You're so kind, lady cup.
You can't speak ever in time.
So you got my license, and I read your phrase, sure
So you got me going close to 69
That might be illegal and for to sell a saint
But I can't help myself, not my y'all, don't buy high
Super hot lady cop, mama y'all, don't buy high lady cop
Wow super hot lady cop, you can't smell your tie
So I'm baby cocked
She had a nice set of guns, 38 to least, and as we talked, I got into trouble when I tried to steal my piece.
See how I was sticking to myself if I played my card right.
I hope it gets wrong by the end of the night.
I worked my way out of this situation, and now I'm thinking I should have paid the fine.
As a step to the van, I heard a teller partner, if the party wagons rocking, don't come and knock it out.
I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot.
I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot.
I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot.
I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot.
I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself.
I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and I can't help myself, maybe I'm super hot, and
except through the pod show network, and I was just thinking, it was kind of travelling back in time over the past
15 minutes or so, thinking about the show, and I say I was so weird, so surreal to be walking
through San Francisco International Airport, hearing on the  system, if you've been an
SFO or any other airport you've heard this.
The current Homeland Security Alert is at state orange, and I was thinking, all we're missing
there is the current homeland security alert is at orange.
Avoid the hassles of homeland security with your new clear card.
I mean, is that something straight from an Arnold Schwarzenegger movie or what?
Be careful. Be careful. Don't sign up for that shit.
All right, Adam at podshow.com. DailySourceco.com is where you can find all the
show notes or everything discussed and played on the show.
And I'll be back tomorrow. I hope you'll join me. Take care, bye.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.
Yo, what's up? Is your man Tony Costa from Cossus World?
Telling you to go check out the new Sony Pictures release.
This Christmas is Star's Chris Brown.
But Kai Fife for Regina King. Lauren Lundin. Columbus Short.
And it... It just has an all-star cast.
Yeah, I mean, you can exchange gifts.
You can exchange the socks. You can exchange fruit cake.
But you cannot exchange family.
So make sure you check out this Christmas when it hits theaters.
November 21st, 2007. And I'm out.