Hey buddy, hey buddy. Over here. Look, I got the genuine DSC 569 Dirt Cheap. No, no, it's
a real thing. Look, it's got the lighter clicks. It's got the all scruncher, a folder. It's
got the Trinity開lights. It's got it all. Dirt Cheap, only $500. This left for this
stuff will cost you $3,000 in the market. Come on, what do you say? The DSC 569 Dirt Cheap.
Eh? Eh? Eh, you're not a cop, are you? Because if you are, you know, carry me,
me do this. Yeah, you add them. Carry, see you tomorrow.
The DSC 569 Dirt Cheap. No, no, no, no. I can see them, bring them down my neck. So many cameras.
I don't want to feel this way anymore. I can't remember how I felt before.
Dirt Cheap. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I'll lose my life for you, I'll keep having you. I'll leave it, I'll do, I'll ending this game of action, no, night and shoot a
When I saw the rain, I'm crazy and so
Breathe down my neck, suffocate me
Breathe in my heart, you'll be the jack of me
Deep down my stomach, you'll be the jack of me
I'm crazy and so deep, you'll be the jack of me
Breathe in my heart, you'll be the jack of me
As more of California's solace
I'm sorry Mishra that Carlinah
but North Carlinah no less
Most excellent classic case, in into nightmare I want to think
Latino fella for suggesting that to start off the daily source code.
Hey, everybody.
It's a daily source code.
What is it?
Five, six, nine are already.
Today is beautiful in the UK.
I'm a little bit bummed out because I could have had the Delta
Sierra, my aircraft delivered to me after its annual inspection over
the weekend on Saturday, exactly.
And the week commander called me up and said,
yeah, he didn't bring it over and Captain Dan was unavailable.
And he said, well, you can always fly yourself across the channel.
And I looked at the weather reports and I looked like it was going to be
about a thousand foot cloud ceiling.
And my minimum is 1500.
For pilot experience is Captain Dan a thousand feet would be okay.
So I said, fuck, I'm not going to do it.
And now, of course, here's a beautiful day.
And it's supposed to be really nice all this week.
It may get a little bit rainy around Wednesday in the UK.
I've been thinking about providing weather reports to the UK.
I'm getting pretty good at this stuff.
And now that I have understand how to decipher and decode and aggregate all
the meteorological data.
So instead, in lieu of that, I had a configuration weekend.
Oh, yeah, I decided to tackle a couple of things that I had on my list for a while.
The first was to fix the internet here.
So I called up my provider and said, look, connection sucks.
I think it's this router.
And it took me a while to understand, for her to understand me and for me to
understand her, that they don't actually sell routers.
They send you one when you get the service.
But if you want to buy an additional one, you go to any store and you buy one, which kind
of makes sense.
And it's really it's an ADSL mode of slash router, slash access point or whatever.
I don't need the access point, portion of it, because I'm quite happy with my Apple airport
network, which is running on WDS.
I know it slows down traffic a little bit, but still, it's fine.
So she said, you know, we support was an action tech and linksis, I think, which I
have neither, of course, except for the, I think broken one, or I thought at the time broken
one.
And so I'm like, let me see if these airports are compatible and apparently they're
not because you need a PPP over A and they only have PPP over E except after C.
And, yeah, so I, so I was just noodling around in the airport to configuration.
And I noticed something rather interesting.
And it kind of took me back to what I'd tried to set up in the condo, because essentially
I just took my existing airport networks, I just plugged them into the router for the service.
And it was just kind of working, although I must say a lot of the computers seem to disconnect
and reconnect to the network a lot.
And it dawned on me that what I had done inadvertently is I, so the original, the action
tech modem that the ISP sent me is plugged into the ADSL of the phone jack.
And it provides IP addresses in the 192.168.1.xxx range.
And I just plugged the, the airports into one of its ethernet ports.
And they start providing their own address space in the 192.168.0.xxx range.
And I remember that something with the subnet's, if they're set to 255.255.255.0 is an
example that that kind of crosses over and can create conflicts.
And so I went about resetting the, the Apple airports so that they just passed through
as a bridge and we're not providing IP addresses.
And voila, duh, oh man, I can't believe I've been using that crappy messed up packet collision
configuration for so long when I could have fixed it, the fix was at my fingertips for,
for what?
Two months now.
So that's pretty much fixed.
That more, I still think I need to get a new router, just a better router because
it seems like it's, it has its quirks.
And you know, maybe like, so you have to flush out memory or something.
So the next step, of course, was going to be to upgrade the firmware.
I skipped that step over the weekend, figuring out, I'm happy that the shit is just working
now.
Let me have that settled down.
And now that I had a good connection, I went about to reflash my portable devices.
Have you ever done this?
Have you ever reflashed your Nokia phone?
In other words, putting the new, the new system upgrade onto it, the new firmware.
It actually started with me reflashing my Nokia N800 Internet tablet, which was an okay
experience.
It's certainly not a consumer experience because you have to manually reinstall applications
that don't come baked in standard.
Didn't really like that.
Oh, I have to say, I kind of did like it because it becomes such a development box for
me that there's a whole bunch of mess running, you know, stuff running that probably shouldn't
have been running and may have been affecting different parts of the system.
I must say, though, that I think I've noticed that the battery has changed its behavior.
I'm not getting much more than about, well, I don't know, maybe my usage has changed,
but certainly the battery indicator, that has changed or it isn't right yet because I'll
be using thing for a couple hours and I pretty have a usage and it'll show a full battery
and then I can stop using it for like 15 minutes, click the screen and then I'll see
the battery indicator has dropped down to half.
So it's not really giving me, it may be lasting as long as it did under the circumstances
of usage, but the indicator certainly isn't making me time my work very well.
All of a sudden, well, we're getting low now and then you literally have like 30 minutes or
something.
There's the coolest thing.
I upgraded the symbion software on my Nokia, was the E61, which has Wi-Fi built right
into the cell phone and I always knew that it had the capability to set it up with the
CIP protocol as an internet phone and that it actually integrates completely with your
address book, but I was never able to load anything onto it or to get the configuration
just right.
And after flashing the device, I went to gizmoproject.com and I got the, it's like the N80 series
I think, but it's for Symbian, I installed it and presto all of a sudden now I have
a void phone and a cell phone in one device and it has a lot of really smart features.
When it sees a network that you've used before, it will automatically connect and be ready
to receive incoming calls and make outgoing calls, it, it, it, it knows to automatically
connect when it sees any type of network in general.
I mean, it's all kinds of cool things, so that it actually, hello and behold, just
might work as a, well, like a really cheap phone, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip,
comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, well
something else happened over the weekend, which almost passed me by unnoticed, luckily,
he's here, our European correspondent.
Hello, I'm Gary.
Here's your European Union correspondent, a guy who is the link at www.comicstripbloc.com.
So yesterday, European Union, it means you, it was celebrating 50 birthday, well, I wanted
to say, happy birthday, you, and fuck you, yes, still, several EU countries are racist and
are blocking freedom of movement of workers, and like them, French, Feroque, iters, and Dutch
podcasts.
And generally, Europe is an ancient civilization, an museum, museum that is slowly dying,
over-taking by East Asia and USA, on generally by Asia.
And peace in Europe, in late 62 years, was due to USA and NATO, not due to EU itself, but
of course, bastards take care of it for everything.
So Adam, maybe, tell me, what do you think?
You'll survive next 50 years, so that 100 anniversary of you will be once celebrated.
You, coming straight blogger, yes indeed, the European Union celebrated its 50th birthday
on, was that Sunday yesterday, and of course, this 50 years after the treaty of Rome,
I believe, in which the member states formed the union.
And if you recall what do you call it, not the proposal, God, I'm spacing on it anyway.
The ratification, there you go, the ratification of the constitution, the European Union
constitution, did not take place as the Netherlands and France both said no to the ratification.
So now things are kind of spinning up, we've got a new president coming in.
As the presidency is handed over, there's a possibility of trying to get the ratification
of the constitution done in 2008 or 2009, I think.
First of all, whoever's doing PR for the European Union sucks ass.
First birthday, kind of, crept up on me, it was there, you know, where was all the pre-promotion?
Where were all the, excuse me, sir, a perfect time to mention that I just love the new
Folgers flavor brands, again, if you combine the width of splendor, with that flavored splendor,
you've got a yummy treat, yeah, where were all the, where was all the setup for it?
All of a sudden, there was like, you know, I saw classical concert and then some concert
somewhere else and Ron and Chris and Marta and they were all in Berlin just recently and they
didn't mention anything to me, I don't know, it just sounds kind of weird that all of a sudden
whoops, there we are, we're 50.
I think in general, it's a really good idea to have a European Union, the only way you can
look at the Netherlands as an example, very, very, very small country.
Now about 16, 17 million inhabitants, a closed off language, they speak Dutch, of course,
just by everyone speaks fluent English, which is a very important part of their survival
and a very, very strong financial infrastructure that provides a lot of financial infrastructure
to the rest of the world in tax shelters, tax shelters is really the best thing that I can
say, a tax shelter, and of course, a very powerful bank, A.B. and Amro, which seems to
be coming less powerful every day, without that, they would have been overrun, I think
a long time ago and really, you can see the makeup of the population, I saw a change
in a span of about eight years when we lived there a couple of years ago and I hadn't
been there for eight years, you could really see the change up in the population composition
if you will. And that's happening all over Europe, and I truly believe that there only
if you can, well, really, I think the UK doesn't feel like they're part of, like they're
part of Europe, it doesn't feel that way, and of course, it's all about the monetary
position. The UK itself has a very strong financial position in the global marketplace,
but by not using the euro, they're kind of excluding themselves. So if you do look at the
United States, which is more or less to say, it's kind of the model on what the EU, I guess
is based on, except the this whole thing about the constitution is very weird. There's a
lot of stuff on the constitution, which just doesn't make sense as a constitutional document,
if you compare it to the declaration of independent to the own US constitution. So there's
some things that need to be fixed there, but the idea of using of having interstate commerce,
if you will, and arranging a lot of things to make it flow easily, and still being able to have
independent state laws, look at the difference in laws, in the marijuana drug laws, in California,
very different than they are in, say, New York. So, you know, it is possible to live in harmony
as member states in the union with some very significant differences at a local level. So it's
important, and if you want to be able to not be overrun, indeed, by the West or the East,
and become either Asian or American, then you have to join together. So it makes a lot of sense,
and historically Europe has been able to do that. So yeah, I'm actually all for it, but indeed,
you know, everyone does have to kind of join in, and I think the most important thing
is this crossing the borders to work in different states. That is very important.
Now, I don't know if Hawaii, as an example, has any different regulations than the Continental
US, because that would be kind of a way to compare it, because in Ireland, there's only so many
people that can fit on an island. And in a state, it's a little different, because if you run out of
state, you just fill out, you know, you spill out into the other states. So, but yeah, I'm following this.
It's very interesting to me. And sometimes I read the, I read a newspaper every single day,
the Financial Times, and you know, just look at this. I'm going to like, wow, man,
sometimes it looks so archaic, and so almost medieval in the way things are discussed and
and the approach that's taken, but yeah, change often takes a long time.
On April 2nd, the cell cancer of ANGB will present a special one-hour feature on Karma Koda,
the award-winning independent electronic adeo, a redcrocker, and had their peers.
I'll never forget one of our first shows. There were some Japanese tourists who had actually heard
the music on mp3.com and showed up at one of our shows, and they somehow got their self-decephensisco
and, you know, science CDs, and we kind of knew that we were on to something special.
I'm seeing Swan as the opening credits for the film Neverland was just like, it just confirmed
everything that we were thinking. You know, it's a whole revolution. The last 10 years, you know,
everything is different in business, and it's completely made Karma Koda, Karma Koda.
It'll be previewing a brand new album illuminate, as well as the other three CDs,
and this in-depth look at one of the most successful indie bands online on the chill cast.
Check it out at ANGB.com.
That's B with a W.
Mark Yoshimode Namcoff sent me the final tally since what came in over the weekend,
in our bum rush, the charts campaign. I'm very impressed, particularly with the international
participation. I'm very, very interesting. Of course, you'd expect the actual iTunes market
place to be smaller, therefore, um, shit. I don't know. Maybe it's more active audiences.
That's also very possible. I don't know how to interpret the data, but
looking at the iTunes music chart across the board, our bum rush, the charts, a campaign that lasted
for one day, the result, and I'm sure it's spilled over into a couple more, resulted in the song
mine again from Black Lab, reaching the U.S. Rock charted iTunes position number 11 in Canada,
number 10. In the USA, we did break the top 100. Overall, that means across all genres coming
in at 99. So, made the new move, as I said on Friday, 53 in Canada, that's the overall chart.
That's half, you know, almost halfway up the chart in the Netherlands. Rock chart number two,
Sweden, number seven, Germany, number 12. Wow. Great job, mine of Hoina. Number 73 overall in
Germany in Holland, number 15 on the top 100 overall chart. That means the, with all genres,
Norway, 55, 10 on the rock chart in Norway, 42 in Switzerland on the rock chart, Sweden, 95 in the
top 100 of all genres, Portugal, 31 on the rock chart, Australia, 35 on the rock chart, UK,
71 on the rock, Italy, number 30, Finland, 42 on the rock chart, Denmark, number 40, Ireland,
54, New Zealand, 54, Austria, number 15 on the rock chart. That's unbelievable. There were over 16,
clicks on the buy now page at bumrush. The charts dot com. So, of course, our tally doesn't
include the people who bought the songs directly from iTunes or put their own links on,
but one thing's for sure. Some kids going to go to college because of this. That's the cool
part. I've been I'm so impressed. I, it's unbelievable. Of course, you know, I've seen some
articles over the weekend saying, oh, well, they didn't make it to number. What cares if we made
it to number one? Look what we did in one day. And as I said, the international participation
was just outstanding. And I must say somewhat unexpected. Hey, Adam, this is Alexander calling
from Stockholm. I bumrushed all over the place yesterday. And I am wondering where to send my
receipt. I think to remember that you last week said that we were supposed to send you emailed
the receipt to you. And there would be a contest. We would win valuable prizes. And was it
saved the world? Bye. Folder. Yo. Folder? Yeah, actually, it wasn't my contest, but I was involved
in the contest. So you send the receipt to Adam at podshow.com and I'll forward them off and
make sure that that that gets tied up. I didn't want to provide any personal incentive. But it did
happen. So I can't remember exactly who said that. I'm sorry. I'm spacing for a second. But I'll
forward it to him. So then we can, uh, can wind that one up from Stockholm down under.
I heard I'm David from Perth calling you. And you're doing, mate, just putting you know,
do the bumrushed the charts thing, purchase black labs. So, um, I have to say I grew
at WFN. It's not really biting, but I know what the hell it's for a good cause. So, one,
can you take us up David this time? How we all went on that? Thanks, mate. How did you been
telling me? Well, we'll talk to you soon. See you, mate. Folder? Yeah, you really should
congratulate yourselves as, uh, as an, as an audience that made its voice heard. Believe me,
that this was watched. And particularly these rock charts, statistics are very, very interesting.
If you know how much money it takes to get a song onto the charts, it's, it's incredibly
difficult. This shows that, you know, right now, if we put all of our collective audiences together
in the same boat, we're making some big difference. But it won't be too long before one show can
have this type of power to move the needle on almost, well, almost anything. And of course,
the, the perfect place to start is with the Podsake music network. Hey Adam, this is the
path man from the Rockout Lab podcast down under in Australia. In a bit of a follow-up to
bun rush the charts and the promotional power that Pod casting can have, I've got a quick story
for you. You're recently played a band called One Day Remains from South Africa,
on Fubar Friday, episode 5-6-8. I actually discovered this band almost a week ago through
my space bought and I emailed the band to get permission to use one of their songs on our own
podcast, Rockout Loud, which the band responded to quite positively and sent us a track the very
next day. We then featured their song in episode 9, which really leased on the 15th of March.
But since then, some more interesting developments have happened.
Oh, hold on, I'm going to stop you there for one second because I've got to say goodbye to the
serious satellite radio listeners. You're going to continue throughout our block of the Pod Show on
and if anyone else is interested to look at those shows that are on the serious network,
look at serious S-I-R-I-U-S dot Pod Show dot com. The hearing themselves on our podcast,
one day Remains got back to us very excited and said, guys, how do we get our band promoted more
through this thing called Pod casting? And my response to them was, well, you've got to get
you music on the PMN because that's okay. Now listen independent artists, listen mainstream
record labels, listen to what he's saying, listen to how this works. I got the song from
Sir Jersey Todd, who of course is my official musicologist on the Charlie. And he sent it to me
pre-package, you know, and I take his advice, hands down, no questions asked, whatever Jersey
Todd sends me, I will play, at least on Fridays. If he starts sending me stuff every single day of
the week, I'm going to start making choices. But on Fridays, it's his slot. He fills it up.
I trust him to do the right thing and get the right tracks in there. And even if I don't agree
with it sometimes, I still trust him because I think he's got that knack. I have to say, I don't
think there's been a single time that I didn't like the track that he sent. So you see how this,
this is a whole backstory. I didn't even know about this. That's fascinating. Well, not only
we can play a music, but other podcasts as World Wide will have access to your music and be
able to play and promote your band. So they did just that. They uploaded four tracks to the PMN.
So really, I mean, the power of podcasting and also the PMN, I just really want to push the
value of that and we go out to gigs all the time and we're just talking to bands and trying to,
I guess almost educate them about this whole new media and digital world that they can access and
promote their music through. But this is just one example of how a band and under a week has
gone to an Australian podcast has then been found by Jersey Todd in America, which here's then
40 to you in the UK and London. So around the world in a week. So I think that's pretty cool.
Anyway, so I just thought I'd drop you a quick line and let you know what was happening.
Thanks for that, Adam. Catch you later. All right, man. Folder. Yeah. Thank you.
Absolutely. So you didn't know that it's got to Jersey,
turned that Jersey Jersey, turned. Sorry, man. Jersey Todd. Mark sent me an email.
Four words, subject line. The bum rush idle podcast, which is actually five words, you idiot.
There is, there is some type of competition type thing we can put in here that would be fun.
I think the key to it is probably using the iTunes chart as some kind of metric. Interesting.
I've got to think about that. But that could be very, it wouldn't be interesting if you voted
by buying the song. Gee, what a concept. It's like the reverse idle almost. You know, with
American idle or any of the idle formats around the world, you got to sing your ass off,
doing covers. And then you'll get a record contract because of votes. And this would be,
I'm just ideating here. And this would be buying the song translating into votes.
Of course, it's got to be enough to make a difference. But hey, I know we could do. We could ask,
yeah, I got an idea. Ah, see, I got an idea. I got all excited. I started moving around,
banging into the furniture. What if we asked iTunes to put a chart together for us?
Of some specific songs? I could be fun. And we'd have to make it open ended so that anything,
oh, yeah, I'm liking it now. If we made it open ended so that any song could make it in, any song
could be nominated by purchases, not by votes, with by purchases. In effect, we could create
anyone could create their own bum rush. Oh, fuck it. Okay, I'm going to talk to the apple guys.
Oh, so that sounds like a really good idea. Oh, I'm an exciting idea.
And the only people who make out are the artists. Yeah, awesome. Well, I'm sorry.
I think it, um, okay, so we should probably, all right, I got to think about this. You already
here. I'm getting diarrhea of the mouth. More about, um, I've told you about this guy, Nigel,
who keeps bringing fantastic artists onto the network. And I said last week, I don't know if this
guy is a, um, a record promoter or what he does. If he, if he, these artists that he's promoting
are actually on his label, but just like the story you heard about, you know, how was song travel
around the world in six days? You know, it's very simple, very simple. Hello,
independent record promoters who are now out of business or on their way to jail. Here is a
way to make the same thing happen. Hi, Adam. It's Nigel here from MattBounceyDogs.com,
but you probably know me better as Nigel from podcast live. I heard you're using me as an example
of an independent promoter and just to set the record straight, I'm really not Thomas Dobby's
record company or actually any artist's record company for that matter. But I do promote music to
podcasters and not just any music. I turned down about three or four artists a week who sent me
rehearsals and tapes, you know, they, they, the sort of thing that they're record on their mobile
phones, however, they're not all that bad. Some of the artists that got through are the young
punks. Leave what you're in.
Sarah Macbatch. I say I don't care and have just to get my back from clear.
And the hits just keep on coming.
Nigel's new Nigel's hit collection.
And of course Howard Jones.
You know, all I do is send out a mail when I put a new truck from the PMN to anybody who wants to receive it.
And I know you already on the list, so there's no point in me telling you that all you've got to do is
stop me online at Nigel and MattBounceDogs.com. And I'll add you to it.
Oh, by the way, I've got some really great stuff coming out in the next game month. I used to watch out for my mail.
You tease. See you. Hold her. I think.
So that's Nigel. Doesn't it sound like he has got his own little hit collection going on there.
I think about the involvement that he has with with this with this it is it. I have to say it's
a movement. I keep reminding myself how incredibly freaking cool. Oh, hold on a second.
Tom's hooting just sent me a Skype DSC cover art. I'll let's take a look, shall we? Hold on.
I'll just download it. It'll open up the Skype channel so you can hear it when it's done because it
gives that nice little Skype from from from. Oh, my, here it comes. It's nice and fast now on my yeah.
There we go. Okay, open it up. Let me see. Oh, cool, man. Awesome. I'll put it in today's
a today's art. There we go. Sorry about that. Yeah. So that's Nigel.
And as I was saying, I sometimes I just forget how incredibly cool the positive music network is.
I mean, it truly is a social media network and it really does work as you can tell.
And I received an email. When did this come in 14 hours ago? So that was last night sometime. Hi Adam.
This is from Sandy Shaw. Now, I played the song. The puppets got a brand new string, which of course
is the new version of puppet on a string. As she owns all of her own material. She is a pod
safe artist, almost by definition. Hi Adam. Someone sent me a copy of your last show and I was on it.
How amazing. I'm really happy to join the media revolution. I'm so tired of the marketing and
promotion mechanics that is nowadays called the music industry. I started to sing in the 60s
because I wanted to be a musician. I wanted to see and change the world, not be a performing
The reason I'm jumping back on board now is that I can do it without corporate interference.
I can relate to my audience directly. I feel comfortable with this. It's so 60s, so Smith,
so Sandy. I feel I really feel part of a changing society. Cool is a state of mind. Love,
Sandy Shaw, XXX. Oh. This is awesome. I grew up listening to Sandy Shaw. Now she's joining the
revolution by her own words. P.S. You do know that bum rush in the UK has slightly
naughty implications. Now that's that's awesome, Sandy. I'd like you to let's hook up and maybe
you can explain it to me. Although I have some ideas. Oh man, I love it. I love it. This is
and by the way, says someone sent me a copy. I presume that's that's Nigel.
So hopefully we'll be hearing more from Sandy Shaw. And more artists like her, young old,
back catalog, new catalog, who cares. It's right there. It's yours for the taking. It works.
And let me work on this this bum rush thing. This bum rush idol. We can't use the word idol.
I've got to think of a different one. But it has to be apparent. And it won't be a reality show.
It'll be the reality of real time what people really think about songs and how they really get
behind it. To the question that was raised last week, who does the Pacho tags in the UK?
It's Philip E Collins. I'll put a link in the show notes. We got her from voiceovers.co.uk,
which is just the place where people put up auditions for their voice. And I like that system.
Philip E Collins, who does it? Thanks Brian. No for jumping in on that thread.
And the guy who always does a fantastic opening for the Charlie. At least he's been doing it for the
past. I don't know. 30 episodes. It seems like his PD love. And it's always nice when he sends
in something that is for his own benefit. Hey Adam, you were talking about milestones the other
day. And you were talking about whether or not to show 100 is really still a milestone. And so forth.
And just kind of debating that. Well in my mind, a milestone or at least something that elevates
your podcast to the next level is an official Jeff Smith jingle. Well what of my shows,
the daddy cast, has now risen to that level. Take a listen.
Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good
Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good.
And that would be a part of the package that you get when joining. And I think it'll be a pretty cool idea. If you want to contact Jeff directly, it's TheJefSmith.com and Jeff is spelled G-E-O-F-F. Where the heck did that come from? By the way, who made that shit up? I guess it's from Jeffery. Yeah, shit. Okay. Makes sense.
Hey, Adam. How are you? It's Pablo from Ecuador again. Hey, Pablo. I'm calling you because I just hear your podcast where you work on people, how to use their cell phones. Just to give you a little bit about how it works on phrases.
Okay. Now, this is really important. You pay attention because I'm going to explain something to Pablo. That pertains to everyone using a mobile phone because it really does work, even though he gets a little bit confused.
Check it out. I found that crap because I used my cell phone. And in order to dial to your phone number, I used first the country code in this case it's 01.
Okay. Stop right there, Pablo. That's the point. The O-O. That is not the country code. One is the country code. So for the UK, it's 04. So instead of typing the O-O, which by the way, in the United States,
you have to dial 011 and then the country code. That's really the only reason for the plus because these days,
O-O works in just about every single country except for the United States.
So the plus sign does not work for some of us. You have to dial first the country code. That's it. So, how do you later? Bye.
Pablo, thank you, man. Yeah, okay. So we already gave out the US number. So either it's 0044 or it's plus 44 for this number.
I just got a couple more voice mail messages that I want to play for you. This one is about the cost of receiving SMSes.
Hey Adam, it's CJ for a user. I just want to give you one little feedback on the GSM. You'd never pay for receiving an SMS while roaming.
Apart from, of course, the paying SMS services where you send one to pay.
Okay. Now I got a fundamentally disagree with this. When you are roaming in a different country and SMS text message, you pay for when it comes in.
In some cases, it can be as high as, you know, a dollar per message. The same with phone calls, by the way, where you may pay nothing for incoming phone calls in your particular region.
When you travel outside of that region, you better believe your pain and ex amount per minute.
And then you get like 20 back at 50 cents each. But apart from that, you only might have to pay a surplus when you're roaming and sending.
So that's all the GSM part. And let me know how you get on with your GSM project and your avoid stuff.
And by the way, can you do me a favor? It looks and see if you can get me an N.800 as a previous sample for a site.
Yeah, right. Oh, not really kidding. Actually, but you better know. All right, have a good weekend fight.
Yeah, I do find it very fascinating. All these different ways of connecting and creating voice calls. And it's really the device is, and I have to say, I think Nokia is,
God, I got to get those people to pay me money for saying some of this.
That's it. We should this should be a way to like reverse advertising. Wouldn't that be a great way to do advertising?
Just talk about the shit you like and then afterwards, you know, you go to the advertising and say, no, pay me.
Yeah, they've got their shit together though. When it comes to this E61, I think it's really, really, really smart. You know I'm going to use it.
And it's not about the money per say it's more about like fuck you. I don't need you. I can do this with my own connection here.
I pay for connections at work. I pay for connections at home. I have Wi-Fi connections all over London.
So I'm going to, you know, I'm going to be my own phone service. I'm going to turn my own prices. And it's not quite as convenient yet.
But I don't usually, when I find myself out on the road and not in the proximity of a Wi-Fi hotspot.
Yeah, okay. I'm, I'm happy to use the cellular network. Nothing wrong with it.
But otherwise, I can do all this stuff myself. And I like it that it's on one device. That's what really makes a lot of sense.
Hey Adam, this is full from Memphis, Tennessee.
Um, originally Nigerian. So that's okay. From Nigeria. Well, I think I received several emails from you.
That explains the actions. I got two things. The first thing you've probably heard before is, uh,
Do you think it's a coincidence that the name Adam or the father of all mankind?
And then, uh, you Adam are the, uh, fathers, uh, podcasting.
Um, uh, kind of strange coincidence.
Well, I think, uh, I don't, I'm not the father of podcasting, but, um,
Uh, I think we're all put on this earth to do something to achieve something.
And maybe, uh, my role is to change media, or at least contribute to it.
The second thing is, um, how come you only take phone calls from the people that are, uh,
regular, uh, regular calls of the show? That's not true.
It's the regular callers of the ones who actually send in phone calls that are useful.
That's why a lot of phone calls are so long and so boring and just, you know,
And I'm not, I'm not going to edit phone calls or the topic is just not interesting or, or the,
or the topic is pretty much over and close. Um, so you find out that the, the people who get on the air
come regular is because they're sending in comments in a format that I find usable as no other reason for that.
Um, I think you should take, uh, phone calls from other people, you know,
Yeah, yeah, I think you play other people like mine who,
Another thing that bugs me is phone calls that start off with, hey, I'm so and so from the so and so podcast,
I'm really more interested in listeners.
So more, you know, just gives us a why the audience to listen to.
All right, Adam.
All right, I have a podcast also.
It's called people wearing O show F O L A R I N and O separately.
Show.
All right.
Now you wonder why I don't play all the boys' meal comments.
One more song for today before I get out.
Uh, Ed Ovet sent me this amazing.
This is a fantastic song.
Hey, Adam, it's a late Saturday afternoon.
I'm surfing around the March 24th new podcast music network uploads.
And lo and behold, look who I found none other than the boss himself Bruce Springsteen,
harmonizing on vocals on the following track.
I think you'll like it.
Jesse Malen, broken radio.
I was thinking about another time still in my mind.
Well, I used to know a little girl how this world.
You wave out loves you more than you know.
Breezed on rivalry and rock and roll.
No one's ever more to sit there so she lets go on a radio.
Well, we never had a lot of cash, but we love those kids.
So I'm saying that she missed the book.
She just blew the bridge.
The angels of him are the new known.
Breezed on rivalry and rock and roll.
No one's ever more to sit there so she takes on a radio.
Still making it so dead.
In books we never left.
Love all the soul and Sunday.
We might read again.
She used to talk about astrology.
She was morning June.
She dance with strangers and celebrities and distorting the full moon.
I was thinking about the universe from what it's worth.
All the one on that the Phoenix bird, the tide and return.
The angels of him are the new known.
Breezed on rivalry and rock and roll.
No one's ever more to sit there so she takes on a radio.
Sometimes I see him a place when there's no more place to go.
I'm a radio.
That was right.
It's busted.
It's crap.
It's broken radio.
Jessie Manland with guest vocals from Bruce Springsteen.
You can find him with the pod safe music network.
The album is called Glitter in the gutter and he's from New York.
Awesome.
All right.
Everybody a little bit longer than I intended.
But of course it's Monday.
You know, got to catch up on all the stuff that happened over the weekend.
So we back tomorrow with another daily source code.
From the affluent suburb of Surrey.
You know, it's Gilford, G-town, Westside, represent.
How sad is that when a middle-aged white man talks like that.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.