Hello, it's Chris Lane here from the Pods Zone. I could play the way, but that's not why I'm here.
Although he's not here at the moment, Nick Cooper and myself would like to wish you, yes,
you, the one with the ear buds, looking befuddled at this audio bombardment of your programming.
A very very Merry Christmas. If you don't celebrate Christmas, then have a fantastic time anyway.
Well, I guess I'll be able to be off then, until next time. Bye.
Brothers and sisters are reading from the book of Adam, and so it came to pass in the fourth year
of the Daily Source Code that the podfather did find the numbers that were secret. And the numbers
that were secret were 600 and 4 score and 7 and 600 and 4 score and 8. And the podfather declared
that the numbers 687 and 688 shall be secret numbers and shall not be in the counting of the
Daily Source Code. And the congregation was confused and such that the counting becomes 700,
but yet it was not 700 for the numbers of 687 and 688 had been skipped. And yet it was not so.
For we did celebrate the 700th episode of the DSC. And low, we give thanks for the Charlie
that the podfather has given on to us. Let us rejoice now for the DSC 700.
It is, come on Friday, everybody get ready to sing along. If the anthem that we all know
and put it in the song, right? Send them my names to tell me that you love me. I'll send it
in your face and then I'll do. I love to hear you horror lies when I'm between your eyes.
You blow your way to my face and let my lips embrace you. I'll send them a face and then I'll
do. I'll send them a face and then I'll do. I'll send them a face and then I'll do.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass. Then the next generation radio
content in my ears. I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I pull it up with a million trucks. Look at the smell and the feeling like a million bucks.
Pass the bottle, the heat is on. We're in a hot-a-loss, looking at cheats and sound. What's wrong?
The club in the movies floor. And I'm looking for a thick young lady to pull. One suicide.
We can't get a matter to pay and take notes to the brand new days.
I need an opportunity to stop. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home.
We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home.
We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home.
We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We're not home. We
We're not home.
It's like that, it's like that, it's the perfect match of our round number, like 700 DJs
on us to do.
It's like a hurricane.
It's the first by a massive town bus cop, new to print, sports, warrants, and winger.
Yeah, everybody, how you doing?
It is the data source code.
I'm back in the curry manner and the affluent suburb of Surinone is Gilford.
We're on the west side.
Major delays coming in from New York, actually from Liberty Airport.
As you know, Newark Airport has been renamed to Liberty Airport, Liberty Airfield.
I think field sounds better.
Hey, no problems getting out of the country.
That's for sure.
Except, of course, for the massive snowstorm that hit the northeast and did give us some snow and some freezing rain and some ice in the New York Metro area.
Actually, that wouldn't have delayed me that much.
We're not that the Virgin Atlantic air crew.
They did something really dumb.
They had the lost power while we were at the stand.
The external power unit failed.
And so they had to restart it.
Now, there's one thing that you learn as an airman when you train to be a pilot.
When you're going to start anything, anything at all it has to do with electricity.
So whether it's the engine that's going to be sourcing electricity or if you're connecting an external power source,
you turn off all of the cockpit electronics.
It's just a rule.
Because you have a good shot of blowing out your radios or some other piece of equipment.
And I could see them trying to start it.
The plane was literally, it was like they were turning the key.
And the lights would come on.
Everything would go off and then it would go dead again.
And the captain came on and said he was trying to restart it.
I'm like, man, I hope you turned off your shit.
They got the power running.
Oh, well, we have some malfunctions here in the cockpit.
So now we have to have ground engineering come aboard.
So they actually had to replace some bits and bobs.
And we finally got off three hours late almost.
And of course, because we were late, there was an hour waiting on the tarmac at Heathrow.
In order for us to get a stand, which was, I guess, a lift ons are some other company taking over.
It doesn't matter because I don't remember anything of the flight except for sleeping.
And I did wake up briefly when we all had to put our seat belts on because of severe turbulence.
It was kind of fun.
The roller coaster type turbulence where you would drop.
And you'd feel a little bit of weightlessness come in.
And you could literally hear people go, woo, woo.
Like we're on a roller coaster ride.
Anyway, it was fun being New York.
I do miss her.
I'm going.
Adam Curry.
See one hundred.
He's your New York.
This man.
We all miss you.
Oh, man.
I wish I knew who you were.
Yaman.
Good times.
I miss New York myself.
And I left too early because the annual concert.
How could I?
How could I have scheduled my life not around this?
Hi, Adam.
This is Jan from theonswell.com.
And many other places on the next.
I just wanted to say it.
You're still in town on the 17th, which is upcoming Monday.
You should try to go and see if you have it if you want to go and concentrate.
He's having a concert.
Check it out.
Look at it.
It's at the time of that comment on that.
All right.
Take care.
I love you.
And I'll see you at the concert.
Yeah.
Bye.
Grab.
Oh, man.
That completely slipped my mind.
Second year in a row that I have not made the infamous David
Epilito Christmas slash New Year's concert.
Very bummed about that.
But on the other hand, I am happy to be home with my girls.
Finally, I think I'm going to be here at home.
Through Christmas.
Maybe even through New Year's if we can think it.
I've got a lot of response about my, my being on the Homeland Security, TSA, Customs, Border
Protection Agency.
Look out list.
Which means for the next 40 years, 4-0.
Unless we change something in government, I basically will be, well, I can't really
call it harassed.
Because they're not harassing me.
These guys are just doing their job.
It's the computer system that's all fucked up.
The fact that that exists.
There's an automatic targeting system that gives you a score based upon everything from
Department of Motor Vehicles to the IRS.
And if you hit that score, well, then they've just got to interrogate you.
Lots of comments about that.
Hi, Adam.
This is Jonathan New York.
Hey, David.
I just started listening to DSC699.
And you were just driving your deal.
You went through at New York Airport.
And you said you were disappointed.
Disappointed.
I mean, what you've described must be illegal.
I know we have to worry about Homeland Security.
But this still is the United States.
And your man of means.
And so you should, so I'd like to see the government.
I mean, the ACLU, I think, would love to take your case.
It's so obviously a gross trust test on your rights as an American.
And so I, you know, I just, it's not just annoying or disappointing.
It sounds to me, it's totally illegal.
And so it sounds to me also like with the great test case.
I mean, we've seen over the last several years an erosion of our rights.
Slowly, more and more in the name of security.
And I think we have to put a stop to it.
And it's been done to you as so illegal that it would make a great test case.
Anyway, hope you do that.
Thanks to the daily source code, Adam.
I love you, Adam.
Oh, bye.
Oh, baby, I love you too.
Send naked pictures.
And I don't want to be a test case of anything.
I'm sick and tired of being tired.
I've spent so much of my own money on fighting laws.
The most recent one was, of course, the,
the attempt and the successful attempt I might add to uphold creative comments as a valid copyright.
It cost me a lot of money.
You know, lawyers and fees and all that shit.
Even though I won, I didn't get any damages.
So I'm tired of doing that.
I'm tired of it.
I'd rather use this show, which for me is pretty much free.
ACLU, by the way, the American Civil Liberties Union is all over this.
Reading from a post on there on their site, which I'll link to in the, in the show notes at daily source code.com.
It appears that the Department of Homeland Security has violated not only congress's ban on risk
assessments, but also the private, the privacy acts notification requirements said Steinhardt of ACLU.
At the very least, DHS has violated the spirit of the law and the ethical obligation to vet a program like this through congress
and through full public and democratic debate and control.
So the ACLU has filed official comments calling on the Department of Homeland Security not to implement the program, which, of course, they did.
So they're all over this.
They're working on it.
And, you know, again, it's, to me, it's not a problem that, that I show up on a score somewhere and they want to question me.
What is a problem is that this happens continuously.
There's no way for them to put into the system.
Guys, okay.
All right.
You can kind of trust this guy.
Kinda.
Because of course, no one really trusts me.
Just take one look at me.
So that's the real, that's the privacy here is, is that you can't get off this list.
In fact, it's not really a list.
It is, it's a query.
It's a query across hundreds of databases from many different federal, state and even tribal databases.
Whatever the hell those might look like.
And the ATS, the automatic targeting system.
It's almost like a Google page rank.
You know, hey, I got a high page rank today on the automatic targeting system.
So once again, time to fuck with Adam at the border.
Yeah, it's pretty ridiculous.
And of course, there should be a way to contest the information that is in these databases.
That would be a request under the Privacy Act.
That appears not to be possible.
The only thing you can do is file a freedom of information act.
And of course, under the, I'm sure under the Patriot Act or some other fucked up law,
you're not allowed to actually get that information and contest it.
So I'll just have to live with that.
But that will give me lots of material for the show for the next 40 years.
Yeah, I'm so Jerry Alexander and Ross Vegas.
I wanted to talk to him just listening to 699 from the daily source code.
And, you know, you just got actually a positive.
You just got done talking about the Homeland Security issues that you had.
First of all, I have, I want to apologize about that.
I think that that must have really sucked.
You know, you, you are American citizen.
And you have to spend a lot of time getting, you know,
you know, we all know you're not threat the Homeland Security.
But at the same time, I do have some other points that I would like to just kind of throw out there.
And obviously not meaning to piss you off, but this kind of sparse some interest in myself, you know.
Okay, well, hold on. First of all, you know, need to apologize, dude.
You know, I'm a young cadudal band, you just like you.
So we're both in this boat together.
So you don't have to apologize on behalf of the American people or anything like that.
You don't live here. You are, you are American citizen.
Let me just say one very important thing.
I pay income taxes in the United States.
I am, I have, worldwide, I have to file my income taxes.
Any money I make and I do make money in the United States.
I pay taxes over in the United States.
Income tax, capital gains tax.
It's all paid in the United States.
It's all above board. It's all there.
So whether I live there or not, I am certainly contributing to society.
And of course, I'm paying for some fucking bullets in the desert.
You do not live in the States.
First of all, that's a little different, I think.
And I want to.
It's funny because, you know, Steve leads my buddy from the old MTV days.
And now works at serious satellite radio.
And we were on the same flight.
He said, oh, well, you know, it's your travel patterns that set it off.
Bullshit. Bullshit.
Has nothing to do with travel patterns.
Well, because you travel a lot, you get this treatment.
That's nothing to do with that.
I mean, I should be fucking rewarded for what I'm doing.
We have over 100 people in our company that we employ.
They're all working in paying taxes in the United States.
As you get a fucking metal for that part.
You sort of are different.
And you travel back and forth a lot.
I think those two things alone are interesting enough.
And with, you know, for someone who doesn't know you from Tom Dick or Harry.
It would have happened to your huddle masses coming in through through New York, through the island.
Elis Island.
What, what have happened to that?
Where we welcome you with open arms.
Please.
You know, Steve, they would think, okay, with that sort of weird.
You don't have a business card on you.
I remember that.
That was the first time I had a business card with me every single time after that.
In fact, this time, they asked me for a business card and said,
Yeah, go ahead.
You already have five.
I mean, it's like, these guys aren't doing anything.
And actually, you know, I've replayed this movie several times in my head.
These guys, they don't, they're just asking.
They're just trying to assess if I'm a threat.
Something pops up.
Some kind of flag.
They don't, they just ask and stuff.
They just look in it at all kinds of documentation, you know,
to see if something's out of order.
That's all that it is.
They're not actually doing anything with it.
They're writing stuff down on pieces of paper,
scrap paper with a ballpoint pen.
Eh?
Hello.
You can tell I'm home.
So they're writing stuff down on pieces of paper.
There's no filing system.
They're just doing it just to see if I slip up or say something that they don't like.
That's all that's going on here.
I mean, I know you know, you see, you're not threat to all that security.
You might get threat to the, you know, to what the agenda of some of the other,
you know, politicians, which is a great thing.
Ah, yes.
Now I think you've hit something.
Isn't it coincidental that ever since I really became a
staunch supporter of Ron Paul that this has started happening?
Is that just coincidence?
I don't know.
You might have to read the book.
I think that there are reasons, obviously, that you are getting
chosen to be on this list.
And unfortunately, that's a pretty negative situation for you.
But what if the guy next to you is on the list and, you know, he is a threat?
No, that's okay.
Of course, I'm not against, you know, security and checking people.
I am against the fact that I've been checked four times now in a row.
The so-called random checks.
Yeah, I'm against that.
Yes, I am.
And it makes me feel very unwell-comb.
So, you know, you have to be able to be approved at some point.
It just, that capability has to be in there.
I think that you have to have, maybe not exactly what's going on.
It's obviously not a refined program.
It needs, you know, the bugs, bugs work out of it.
But I got to tell you, man, I, at least are doing something.
And, you know, we're in a pretty pretty fucked up situation here in the
Ivy State, not just with a presidency.
A lot of policies and things of that nature.
I'm glad you're not doing a political show.
But, at the same time, education for, for everyone here is very important,
especially for people in other countries that think we're a bunch of assholes here in the
States.
We're not, you know, I mean, there are assholes here, but, you know, there's assholes in France
and everywhere else around the world.
Not just to pick on France, no French, you don't love you.
Anyways, sorry about that, dude.
I know that I've got a suck in knowing that you're going to get that every single
time you come into the States that blows.
So, hopefully, you can get that fixed.
Post some strange, man.
Call, uh, Julie Brown, downtown Julie Brown, maybe she can fix it for you.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, that'll help.
Um, look, you know, this is kind of the propagation of the, of the war on
Terri, you know, that there are people who hate us.
That's not really true in my experience.
People don't hate us, you know.
There's, uh, God knows how this came about.
And whatever we've been doing was fine for the past five years.
And now in the six year, we've got to put this new automatic targeting system in.
Why?
Now, and there is no absolute security.
Maybe a good idea would be not to fucking other people's countries.
Get the fuck out of there.
Maybe that would be an idea.
Maybe then people wouldn't be so pissed off at us.
Just a thought.
Oh, you remember, um, remember the, uh,
girl slash woman who called in about, uh, her husband having some kind of weird virus
where Amy max voice appeared, uh, or not didn't appear.
Started playing or it was, was audible on his computer.
And, and she didn't know she thought I was a virus or a bug or something.
And, and I, of course, immediately drew the conclusion that her husband was searching for porn
to come across Amy Mac, uh, she's called in now with a response.
Um, this is Eric Teflon, Iowa again.
I'm the one who had the husband that had Amy Mac's voice mysteriously showing up on his computer.
And so it's a great technique so long.
I've been so far behind on my podcast because I just had my computer shut off.
I was doing so many other things with the holidays season.
But, um, I have a few different facts on how this happened.
Okay.
He actually didn't have the internet of all.
So no, he was in search of the porn.
Mm-hmm.
Um, he was playing like a video game or something.
Like one of the simulation games or something.
Stimulation games?
Um, that's all he had open.
And, um, you know, I did the virus checking on his computer.
I had like 40 some viruses.
So I don't know what's one of those, but he didn't even have the internet open.
Um, and I know we've got-
I love these type of bug reports.
Uh, he didn't have the internet open.
Uh, what you mean is he was not using a web browser probably or internet explorer.
Uh, but I'm pretty sure that his computer was connected to the internet.
Because these days, that's pretty typical.
If you have a DSL or a cable motor, you're not dialed up.
So you are connected and the internet is actually communicating with your computer.
And any program running on your computer can communicate with the internet.
So it's not just the web browser.
And it's not that I expect you to know this stuff.
But it's, uh, it just always amazes me.
Uh, how people think this stuff actually works.
Which is fine because you don't need to know how it works.
What we need to, what we need to do is figure out how to get rid of this, uh, so-
Called virus or bug or whatever.
And are you sure your husband wasn't searching for porn?
You don't even seem to know what game he was playing.
So, um, the wireless in our house.
So it's always on wireless.
There you go.
I don't- I don't know what's tell you.
Since you're really weird and that's really all I have to say.
Um, but since I have been catching up, um,
you did have a caller who called me from New Hampshire.
And I just want to thank you for your shit because Iowa, where I live,
is actually the first, um, of the caucuses.
Um, so, um-
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
All right.
Finish up.
Really, Iowa is probably the most important, um, state-to-end, um,
as far as presidential election goes.
But, you know, maybe even a little partial.
Anyway, Adam, um, have a good day.
And, uh, I love you.
I love it when you say it like that.
I did watch the, uh, a piece of the Iowa debate, which is kind of fun,
because it was, uh, like a PBS, uh,
hold on a second.
Let me see what that is.
One second.
Okay.
I can't take that now.
No time whatsoever.
Okay.
So I think I figured this out with the Amy Mac thing.
Um, so first of all, uh, here's what I want you to do.
Now go to the computer that your husband had the problems with.
You might want to pause this for a second, uh, while you walk over.
You at home can do this as well.
It does, I have figured out how this kind of virus thing he works.
Uh, so open, uh, you have to open.
It doesn't work with Firefox.
Open up Internet Explorer, uh, a way for just a second.
Again, you can pause this.
So if it takes a bit longer for it to open up on your computer now,
I want you to close it, but not by selecting, uh, file exit, uh, whatever it is.
I want you to click on the closed button on the, uh, in XP, and I think in VISTA,
it's the big red, uh, red X button.
Okay. So you've done that now, right?
Now go to your, um, volume control.
There should be a speaker icon in, uh, in your, what they call the task bar.
Uh, down at the bottom of your screen.
There should be a little speaker, uh, icon there.
You want to click on that. You want to, uh, I think right click.
So it brings, uh, no, just click on it. Oh, shit. I'm sorry.
Just click on it. So you get the volume control.
The volume slider. Okay.
Now you want to, uh, bring the volume down about halfway.
Okay. Now push it up all the way to the top again.
And now click on the desktop.
If you can, as close to the middle as possible, click on it three times.
Ready? One, two, three.
Oh, it worked.
I hear Amy Mack.
It's a bug.
Hey, Amy.
Hey, Adam, it's Amy Mack.
Today we're going to be standing.
So go ahead and get yourself situated.
Oh, crap.
I just feel like you're going to be doing a type of jumping jack.
So bring your right leg forward and your left leg back.
Okay.
And then switch.
You're also going to swing your arms as well.
But with the opposite arm going forward.
So right leg forward and left arm forward.
And then switch.
Okay. Great.
Now 10 quick ones.
Ready, go.
Now you should be lunging just enough to fill your butt squeeze with every jump.
Yeah, I feel squeezed.
Squeeze.
Breathe.
And relax.
Great job.
Well, until next time.
Amy Mack.
She's not a bug.
She's a feature just one of my favorite women.
Hey, Adam.
This is the divas from TheDivaCast.com.
Wishing you a Merry Christmas.
Happy holiday.
Happy Hanukkah.
Amy, know what the hell?
Happy best of us from the rest of us down here in George Adam.
I don't know if that was sexual or not.
But I'd like the way you guys laughed about it.
Thank you.
DivaCast.
Hey, it's episode number 700 of the daily source code, which means we're celebrating.
Nothing, you know, I don't have any like, you know,
I didn't bring any brownies or cookies or anything for you all.
But I did bring something very special that comes from our friend in Holland.
Because it also is another...
Jesus Christ.
Shut up.
Go away.
It is also another special occasion.
Today marks the 100th episode of Young Pullet's Hit Test.
Play along.
Adam Curry.
I Adam.
Who are you ready to be stumped?
Because he used a good test with Young Pullet.
Hit Test.
Number one.
One, one.
One hundred.
Hey, Adam.
This is the anniversary episode of the Hit Test.
Sure is.
It's number 100 and it all started almost three years ago on January 22, 2005.
And those three years many things have happened.
If you talk about me producing and recording the Hit Test,
then I've done that from three different studios in three different homes.
I've done it from our location.
I've done it from a train and I've done it in a plane.
If you look at the people I've done it with, then I've done it with match.
I've done it with Peter.
I've done it with Adam.
Me feel an Alexander from Curry and the crew.
I've done it with Kevin, the announcer guy.
I've also done it with Dave, the voice of the Hit Test.
Quite a list there, Young.
And there's also a lot of stuff themed.
There's been a lot of themed hit tests.
I've done it with 70s, 80s, a few artists, a lot of stuff.
And, well, of course, this one is themed as well.
I hope you figure it out.
We're going to start with intro number one.
Ross out.
Here we go.
Test number one.
One.
Off.
Oh yeah.
Know it well.
That would be a 50 pound.
Me and Mrs. Jones.
I wonder what the theme is, Young.
Number two.
That's a hard one.
Crap.
I have to give up.
And number three.
Oh, easy.
Boom.
That's Andy Gold.
Never let a slip away.
Talk to my baby on the television.
What is it?
Mub songs.
And I know you have them all at them.
You should have at least.
Kind of.
What was number two?
Well, this one, like I said, is themed.
There's one person behind these three songs.
And that is Lady Patricia.
It's a favorite song.
You're wife.
She selected these three songs.
That's right.
And the first one.
The first answer is from when it all began between the two of you.
Oh, just.
Number one.
One.
You're talking to my wife behind my back.
Billy Paul, one of those guys.
And it was still very secretive.
Me and Mrs. Jones.
Yeah, that's right.
These are our songs.
Mrs. Jones.
We got a thing.
Go in on.
The song from 1973, me and Mrs. Jones.
Billy Paul.
I mean, you played it song for her.
Yeah, I'm ready.
You've got a thing going on.
What was the second one?
And this is answer number two.
Oh, Roger Stewart.
Ten more in the first one.
Watch to it.
I don't know what day it was when you walked to the room.
You're in my heart.
You're in my soul.
You're in my best friend.
It was just kind of hard to get in the intro.
First of all.
That's right.
Got it.
Watch the words.
You're in my heart.
That's cool.
The final acclaim.
And this is the final answer.
There's another one.
Classroom number 138.
Some from 1978.
And the gold never let us slip away.
The song you both like.
Yes, right man.
Very much.
I'm told.
That's true.
And the gold from 1978.
And the gold from 1988.
And the gold from 1998.
The gold from 1998.
Gold from 1978's and never let her slip away and whenever you hit a song
Patricia told me we got in your day cannot go wrong anymore and that's it for
this anniversary episode number 100s I know you had them all at them at least I
really hope so because these songs were really special for you and your wife
so already that's it the answer to this hit test and also the iTunes
link so you can buy these tracks online are available at hittest.bacho.com
while I don't let me tell you that I really loved creating these hit tests and I
really loved to create 100 more of them so next week I'll be back for the next one hit
this number 101 hopefully with the statistics but that all depends on how much time I have
because right now I'm still on vacation so if I don't have enough time they'll be available in
hittest 103 because 102 is kind of special as well and I'm thank you for playing everyone
else thank you for listening have a great week and until next week bye bye
one one one one hundred cut-tast at gmail.com
hi yon that was fantastic dude thank you so much um and I really like that you went behind my back
and let me see on on crap hold on let's see if we can call her
I got to get the I got to get the details on this what are what a great collection of songs
and you're right those are those it's our songs that's that we have a couple more but those are
definitely the ones along with the dialer in by a Skype so that means that I can't just rely on
an address book entry let me see how do I come on Skype how do I do this um so it's let me just do
plus oh fuck sorry uh you know Skype is so different on the Mac versus um here we go
no I don't understand I'm isn't there a place I'm into the phone number there we go
plus four four okay I'm not going to read the number to you obviously
uh let's see if we can get the lady pee on the phone this will be kind of funny
let's see come on ring
hon how come here for a sec I was just calling you did you uh did you talk to young
polette you didn't talk to young polette about the hit test about our favorite songs you
you you I can see you're lying I can see you're lying I can see it in your face come over here for
second I can't hear you because uh he just I just did a hit test and I was like uh me and Mrs. Jones
Rod Stewart uh you're in my heart and uh Andrew Gold yeah you didn't know anything about that
a little bit hold on set how come you're so soft there we go I don't hear myself no you got to put
the head front well what do you do do you send you an email what happened do you call you
I haven't failed with you that's what I that's exactly what I said I said he's gone behind my
my back and hanging out with my bitch that's no good yeah we don't ever hear the whole
oh I'm sorry so I had to subject myself to um to anal probing by the Department of Homeland
so I can bring home the bacon to you and meanwhile you're here doing stuff behind my back with
young polette with young and now it's nice on thank you very much it was called Merry Christmas
Merry Christmas to you and he he was like there was a theme and I couldn't I didn't get
Rod Stewart because it was the intro to Rod Stewart was so short as like I didn't know what it was
but then when I heard Andrew Gold I'm like I kept saying these were love songs these are I know these songs
these are are songs and but the theme was of course there there are songs that's it that's it all right
baby okay well did you enjoy it yeah it was great I love that did you hear me singing along
would you think I was I thought you were in pain yeah yeah the hell out of here thank you very much
did you uh would there was enough gas in the car yeah yeah yeah yeah I love supposed to be
bags but you're busy well if you give me 10 minutes then I'll come downstairs yeah okay well I'm sorry
not really yeah hi Adam this is even Crawford from reaching for the city pod Jeff
and I just wanted to drop a line let you know that this Sunday December 16th I've been invited
to pod test a wrong call support party in Durham North Carolina called or the wrong call T party
also signifying the date of the Boston Tea Party now a wrong call of course will not be there
but it's going to be a supporters around all there's going to be some speeches going on and there
is going to be music miles part rich uh the pod safe entertainer will be doing a acoustic set
as well as a full set with his new band hip slacks is going to be some entertainment there as
well if anybody is in the rally Durham area and wants to attend this party they can go to reaching
for the city dot net and there I'll have a link to instructions on how to get to the party and what's
going on at the party and things like that it should be fun and a lot of support for doctor
Ron now I had a little bit of a downer with this as well and after I was asked to protest this event
my mother called and of course I was not always a downer so I told her and I could almost steal
for eyes glazing over which he said Ron Paul who's that that's supposed to mean something to me
oh no and at that point it hit me that we have a long road ahead of us in getting Ron Paul
even to the nomination my mom represents for better or worse a large portion of the voters out there
that really can only tell you the the front runners that they hear on the news i'll tell me
can probably tell you about Hillary or Obama or Romney and look at how close if she even knows who
hook it is I don't know I did try to educate her a little bit and at that point she told me well
you know I really have to go to Walmart so I didn't get very far obviously but anyway we got
a long road ahead of us but the money the support we're seeing it grows so got to got to
stretching along there got to keep going forward with that but anyway yeah if anybody
that listens to the DSC is in the Raleigh Durham area on Sunday December 16th please come out there
show your support for Ron Paul it'll be fun music food and hey I'm gonna be there so it's a winwin
situation and remember reaching for the city dot net I had to link there to the information
the party so with that Adam Curry keep up the good faith and I'll talk to you later man
alright man thank you so much and thank you for for participating in in the drive for Ron Paul
that's right this this coming Sunday the 16th of December it is the anniversary of the Boston
Tea Party so we've got a Tea Party going on on our own we're gonna we're gonna show him what
was boss you know I'm saying Tea Party of seven dot com or you can find it from Ron Paul
2008 dot com and we want to drop another money bomb we only really need about two two and a
half million dollars more of course we'll be fine to make the twelve million dollar milestone
for this quarter which should be more than enough to just blast out I mean I think that what hasn't
happened yet is they haven't started really using the money on advertising so they're they're
getting ready to do that I would believe I got an email from a Jonathan the finance director
with the campaign so I got to call him I'll see if I can reach him today and find out how things
are going and of course you'll see me posting all the way up until and through Sunday to remind
people this is the perfect opportunity to support Ron Paul and I know exactly what you're saying
because I did have the TV on the hotel room while I was in New York and even in the in the opening
graphic montages and what we call a leader in the bills you're the leaders when they're talking
about you know the debate or anything about the the presidential race essentially and they'll show
you know some candidates and you're right Ron Paul has even show up in those and notice how could
be by the way I'm telling you everything in my body every bone says they're setting that guy
up for a humongous fall I'm not quite sure why I feel that but it just feels like it
so and also isn't the Ron Paul blimp how we do on that did they did they get enough mud yes
here you go we're flying 923 a.m. Friday December 14th this is fantastic
and let's see thanks everyone for your support in reaching our first goal of $200,000 the
blimp will fly for the tea party as the next step we need to receive 400,000 total sponsors
by December 21st to keep the blimp in the air through the New Hampshire primaries. Wow this is great
this is going to get a lot of news and and it looks beautiful I'm not quite sure how big it is let me
see are they they're not broadcasting yet not yet they have what is it just in TV set up on this page
Ron Paul blimp.com what a fantastic idea this will definitely make some noise and get some exposure
and you know it's it's going to be very interesting to see these elections remember
it just posting about this stuff just sending in money it's not enough you actually have to
get up off your ass and you have to go and vote so if you're not registered as a Republican
or if you need to change your party affiliation there's deadlines for that stuff you can find
that information quite easily the Ron Paul's website but that is what it actually takes and I
have to believe that you know the amount of people that actually vote the percentage is so small
anyway that we actually might be able to pull something very interesting off and boy wouldn't that
wouldn't that really surprise the mainstream media wouldn't that wouldn't that turn some heads
I think it's I think it's absolutely of course I think anything is possible
but I do I do believe it is possible that we get this guy elected so hey I'll put a link in the
show notes to to all those things as well before I forget if you're looking for a fantastic
set of headphones you've probably heard the the spot in front of the daily source code it's
big recommendation from the network to check out the new Sony headphones it's Tony dot com slash
headphones they've got wireless headphones they've got noise reduction headphones and people
really seem to be liking them I'm getting a lot of calls about it so check that out for sure
and let's play this comment first hey Adam it's Kevin Crossman the proud scruncher from
pack podcast.com man with a bummer coming back into the country again I do appreciate you continuing
to keep this issue alive it's seriously fucked up just like you said I have a couple ideas
first of all obviously need to follow that paperwork and we want to know what's happening with that
maybe we need to you know credit new domain name free Adam Curry dot com yeah now you're talking
I'll perhaps have a new tagline podcasting is not a crime or how about don't send me to get
mo don't send Adam to get mo dot com and of course if you are gonna register a domain like that I
highly recommend you use my promo code dsc3 and you'll get that domain for $6.95
all right one more comment before we roll out the last song for this food bar Friday
hey Adam this is Dave and Colorado this is in regards to bringing back control of the masses
I think that's a real good idea a couple months ago my wife was talking to me and
sure before you continue let me just remind everybody this is basically the idea of slowing down
the most powerful force in the American economy which of course is us the consumers just by slowing
it down and letting the government know that we're slowing it down because we are actually in control
and we will keep control and it's not that hard it doesn't mean you have to stop buying stuff all
together maybe if you stop buying 90% of stuff stuff that you probably don't need anyway so okay
so you and your wife were talking about what happened if we didn't do or if we didn't buy Christmas
oh man and that's hard it was kind of thinking I don't know how good that would go over with the kids
so we decided to do it and we brought it up to the kids and say we're all for it you know
they have everything that they need or they don't have everything they want but everything that
they need and that's really good man shit I don't have everything that I want
not by a long shot and if you have everything you want and there's nothing left to wish for
and of course I have more than anything I need so that's a good good point right there not
and wow big up to you my friend for talking to your kids about that
we're talking about the kids not having medical care or food in other parts of the world so
we're going to take all the money that we spend on Christmas not only for our kids and our family
members but all our guests together and we're going to help build a church in India
there's other places that you can spend your money you can do like half our international
which is farm animals for family in Africa you can drill wells for people who don't have
clean drinking water or so on and I was just thinking that you can stick it to the man and
you can help out your community whether it be here by where you live in the same country or around
the world and my kids are all for it and I just think it's a good idea we can stick it to the
man and say you know we're not going to fight your stuff and in a matter of fact we're going to
help out our brothers and sisters throughout the world and that's all I was thinking but anyways with
all with all love and respect go fuck yourself out now thank you you know as you were talking
there I was thinking of myself okay so it's clearly possible and it seems like we're all willing
to participate in slowing down our spending for a number of good reasons or at least not spending
them on stuff that we don't need so spending it on like you just said you know helping out
your local community or or other countries that's fine too just to make it easy I'd say let's
work on the United States for the time being but it doesn't work it's you know all you get then
if we if we really are successful at propagating that idea all you really get is that you know consumer
spending will go down and that will be bad for the economy or that's a bad indicator for the
of the American economy and of course if no one knows why that's happening then we fail so we need
some kind of you know some kind of campaign and as you were talking I was saying why don't we
write a declaration of independence a declaration of independence from the United States government
and instead of saying we the people we would start off with we the consumers and then we could
essentially because that's where the declaration of independence was it was a letter to King George
of England saying we the people over here in the new land you know we're distancing ourselves
from you so now we don't of course you know we can never distance ourselves from our own government
but we can send a very strong message equally as strong as the declaration of independence
and starting off by we the consumers would anyone mind taking a stab at that you know go look
at the existing declaration of independence the existing one you know that one and let's do a modern
day version of it trans trans mortified if you modified if you will to this campaign that we the
consumers of the United States of America have decided that we need to separate ourselves from the
way you are running the economy something like that I'm a little too fine to think about it right now
but please think about that register domain name for that it this could be a pretty good idea
I have so many ideas just not enough hours in the day to actually execute and thanks to Jersey
Todd for sending me this track man Alice Smith she's on the pod save music network she's beautiful
inside and out this is woodstock not works safe which makes me like even more
really stop dreaming I just let it slip away thinking about all the bills I've got to pay
I think I have my Trinity my back on with a date 10 days and it won't stop taking anything
so please excuse me because I'm feeling quite dead and imagine it was 10 days and it won't stop
taking anything fill them out like a cello going in and what the season say how stupid it's
for me
why man what a sunny day I can't wait to get out and play walk down those city streets
laughing at our old city creeps say I got a lot to organize I have a lot of thinking to do
another day is gonna be out another day is how it will be
10 days and it won't stop taking anything so what the season skills me
because I'm feeling quite dead and imagine it was 10 days and it won't stop taking anything
fill them out like a cello going in and what the season say how stupid it's for me
is that
It's been 10 days and it's time to take it any day
So what do you think this gives me?
Because I'm feeling quite sad and I'm happy again
It's been 10 days and it's time to take it any day
I'm feeling a little like a cello
Go in and pull out the sleeves
Just say how it's gonna fit this
It's been 10 days and it's time to take it any day
I'm feeling a little like a cello
Where's this girl being all my life?
How do I can that sound?
Alice Smith from the pod tape music network woodstock
She got another track of their called dreams
Nice!
Like the sound, it's like the vibe, it's a different, awesome.
I was just looking at the flight plan for the Ron Paul Blimp
in the Rally North Carolina, I guess, just about now.
Greensboro, later this afternoon, Charlotte,
and then landing at 6.30 at Chester Airport.
And then Saturday all day flying from Chester Airport
to Greensville, North Carolina to Columbia, South Carolina
back to Chester, and then, of course, the Tea Party of seven
in the Columbia area on Sunday.
And I guess we've got to get those guys more money.
This thing is cool.
It's a serious blimp, you know, with like, guys,
like pilots flying it.
You know, there's, you know, one of those little cabins
underneath.
This is a great, this should get some news.
This really should, let's pay attention.
I mean, there's no reason why it shouldn't get news.
And maybe now people will understand who Ron Paul is.
All right, my peeps, don't forget your last chance of dance
for this quarter for Ron Paul, Ron Paul 2008,
please donate money.
Let's get this guy elected.
Can't be much worse than we have right now.
And I endorse him, and, and I'm just a disc jocky.
Links in the show notes of dailysourcecode.com.
And, of course, you can email me at him at podshow.com.
It looks like I'll be here all the next week.
Of course, I'll be in an out of the city,
doing crap just before the holiday is really kicking
to full gear.
Please enjoy your freedom.
I'll live your life with passion.
And I'll see you guys in my day, bye.
Another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear.
The best and the brightest.
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering podshow and limelight.