Make a statement with Saudi stereo ear buds, sleek metal housings that reduce vibration
delivering killer sound from a tiny package, by yours at Sony.com-slashheadphones, Sony
ear buds with style meets sound.
In a world where women wear comfortable shoes and technology has changed the way you get
your entertainment.
This is the pod show network, no big media, no excuses, no BS.
Delta share a Charlie 690 file, $16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass, and the next
generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I like to think I'm flying into the future, I like to think I'm flying into the future,
I like to think I'm flying into the future,
do you usually watch or do you ever watch or really watch ahead,
one minute,
Give me the 9th club, the George Benz, the 9th of the set, he's going off, daily source code 695 and guess what?
I'm still in San Francisco. That's right, coming to you from Recondo. It's Monday evening, so Tuesday and Australia, just picking up the show.
And the reason I'm here is it's actually all good reasons I told you it was going to be crazy until the end of the year.
And I was right, so we got some lots of stuff that I'm still going to do this week.
Here at Pod Show HQ, there's a lot of other things that are not good in my friends. First of all, I have been as sick as a freaking dog for the past 48 hours.
I mean, like, I have not been this sick for five or six years, at least 2000, let me see 2002 probably. Oh, yeah, it's I mean, and I waited so I didn't do a show yesterday, which would have arrived in your on your computer or on your iPod or whatever Monday.
Because I was basically just trying to stay alive. It sucks when you're sick and, you know, and you have no family around you, your wife's not there to make that great chicken soup with ginger, not that I could use any chicken soup at the moment right now.
And, you know, so I waited probably about 48 hours and I got to do a show. I got so much to talk about and lo and behold, the cramping starts. It's like I'm having contractions, man. This is horrible. Anyway, we'll talk about that later. I'm sure you weren't about it all in depth.
But the, but there was a real full bar, a real full bar or we call it element to to this past Friday. I was actually supposed to fly back to Europe and there was a reunion.
Well, I wasn't really the reunion, but the the pirate radio station that I worked at in the early 80s, decibel radio and Amsterdam.
They had, well, so there was a new, they were kind of like relaunching decibel radio.
As a couple of guys had just gotten a commercial license to start a station in north and south of Holland.
So basically Amsterdam, and then I think Rotterdam is where you can hear this station.
And it's called decibel radio and they were using you. The whole vibe, the whole jingle is the assets.
And so this whole relaunch and all the old jocks from 25, 30 years ago when it come together, everyone who worked at the station.
And of course, I really wanted to be there. But you know, having had to pull the trigger on making a decision to stay here.
I couldn't make that.
However, good friend of the Charlie Ray, who does send me these montages from time to time.
I haven't had a chance to use this previous one, which is really intended for me in the Lady Patricia.
He sent me one regarding this very reunion. And I thought, I'll let you take take a listen to that.
It's about four minutes. And I'll just grab a little visit to the little boys room.
I'll be right back.
Hi Adam. It's a new ray on the Charlie.
Although you've deleted number four, I'm not that kind of guy who gives up very easily.
So this is number five. How are you doing?
As you know, there will be a big party in Amsterdam this Saturday in the escape.
And I've just received the VIP invitation for the kickoff party from the legend who will return this Friday at $1,600.
It's the future radio station in the Netherlands.
Descible radio started in 1977 as an illegal radio station on an attic in Amsterdam.
It was the biggest radio station in Amsterdam.
It was D.B. Radio, who invited Mr. Adam Curry to develop his vocal maturity and become one of the best disc jarkies in Holland.
My country was just too little for the part father.
This weekend there will be a restart of Descible Radio and Adam will host a kickoff on Friday.
So I talked to the big bus and next week I hope to become one of the newest generation disc jarkies in Descible Radio.
The station that probably tickles you at him with a lot of memories.
So your biggest fan from Holland has got three quick questions to share with all your Charlie friends around the world.
Question number one.
What was the most important thing why Descible Radio became so popular in the 80s?
Without a doubt the music too.
How are you preparing yourself for this exciting weekend?
I'm cute. I just realized that probably the biggest part of your Charlie friends never heard it to you in the early 80s.
True.
So here's another thing.
Let's all take a trip down memory lane.
Right now it's going to be fun.
But we'll dad embarrass you Adam.
A little bit probably.
Come on, hump on board.
Let's go back to Amsterdam.
1883.
Adam was 19 years old.
Um, excuse me.
Thanks. Once more.
Um, could everybody do this?
Yeah, there you go.
Everybody can come down in the studio.
This studio can only, you know, you put four people in here.
It's full.
I mean, like, so, uh, because somebody called to get us a book of records, please.
Here's the news.
Can you hear that?
I think this was, uh,
I think this was a New Year's Eve celebration.
It's almost time.
I'm going to pop the cork on the champagne.
By the way, my alice was John Holden.
Oh, my lady.
Oh, lady.
I want to first kiss.
I don't know.
You can have the first kiss.
But we need a countdown here.
Wait a minute.
Yeah, it's easy.
Go how much you grew to there, Linda?
Yeah, I want to do my creatures to try and shoot
Keep her from the law for cleaning.
The biggest greatest in the oldest rocker roll star.
The little prince.
Where do we go from here?
Oh my god.
What the hell?
Why do you have to be a hard-greater?
Four teams has the hour, four teams has nine.
Eight teams with, uh, what's the mind?
Oh yeah, that's october, right?
Yeah.
Still a little bit sleepy.
If you're working to be in your car.
Good morning to you.
No, we can radio.
One, ninety six point two.
Culture club.
The culture club room.
The album kissing to be clever.
On version records and tape.
We have a fabulous morning and about 12 minutes here.
You can do it one, eight, four, one, six, eight.
But of course you've been dialed that same number right now.
And we're back.
We've got a thousand seven.
We had a big party coming up this Saturday for both of us.
So, the final third quick question for you, Adam.
Can I buy you a drink?
Alright, thank you very much.
That was quite embarrassing.
What a voice, huh?
Boy.
I don't even think I was nineteen.
I think I was seventeen or eighteen at the time, honestly.
Yeah, so the guys that have, uh, had a live stream.
So it was very surreal to sit here Saturday.
And it, whether it was pretty shitty.
So I went out, did some grocery shopping.
I wasn't feeling that hot, but I wasn't really sick yet.
Um, you know, then I listened to, uh, a basic listen to the stream.
They also had a studio cam.
So I could see all these guys and of course, uh,
everyone was much fatter than they used to be in a lot balder.
I even went out, uh,
doing some grocery shopping.
And, uh, I hooked up the Nokia N-810.
Uh, through Bluetooth to my E-61I.
I used that basically as a data modem.
And I listened to the stream while walking down the street here in San Francisco.
That was a pretty cool cyber experience.
You know, thinking the 25, 30 years.
After I used that literally climb on top of the building to adjust the antenna.
But now, uh, you know, 5,000 miles away.
I'm actually receiving this wirelessly through the air.
And I was a head trip.
And it was a little bit, um,
how can I say?
It was emotional.
It was very weird.
They're also really, really sucked.
Anyway, what can you say?
And, uh,
So then you're kind of,
uh, Saturday night,
I didn't sleep a wink at, uh,
and like two o'clock in the morning.
Uh, my daughter texted me.
She needed something.
You know, the cat had gone missing.
And Patricia was, because I was supposed to be with Patricia in Amsterdam.
Patricia had a different engagement.
She was going to, uh,
some show that they've asked her perhaps to perform in, uh,
in the new year.
And so she was going to, you know,
take a look at this show.
And, um,
you know, and then she, uh,
she called me at 7 a.m.
You know, it's always funny,
because, you know,
when I went back home in the UK,
and uh,
someone from the San Francisco office calls it like 10 o'clock or something like that, you know,
so the girls would say,
well, don't they ever,
don't they ever think about the time difference?
I had low and behold.
No one does a really good job at it, I guess.
Um, before I get into Sunday,
let's listen to this.
This is one of my favorite promos.
Happens every year.
Happy to do it.
Great show.
Ah, Christmas.
Christmas.
Hi, I'm Steve Wad.
Seems like a lot of people are trying to replace the word Christmas with the word,
holiday.
Yeah.
Well, I'm here to say that I'm happy to celebrate Christmas,
and I invite you to as well.
Join in the fun as my co-host,
James Cooper from yChristmas.com.
And I take a look at Christmas
and some of the customs,
traditions,
and reasons for Christmas,
on the Lifespring Why Christmas Show.
Want to be part of the fun?
We would love to have you on the show.
If you have the favorite Christmas memory,
record an MP3 and send it to me at
LifespringYChristmasatGmail.com.
Make it about two minutes long,
make it family safe,
and it just might end up on the show.
You can be a part of the Christmas tradition.
Come check out the show at LifespringWhyChristmas.com.
It is a very Christmas.
Yeah.
What is it now, Steve?
Three years we've been doing this?
I love them, man.
It is a very good show.
You're this Christmas show of Lifespring.
It really puts me into the spirit.
Merry Christmas to you, my friend.
So it's hard to pinpoint exactly
when I started feeling so ill.
And it wasn't...
I'm pretty sure it's really one of these
flu bugs that's been floating around,
that I've just been lucky,
not to get it, and it's been a very tiring week.
I haven't slept well.
And so, you know, some germs roam around,
go on.
I look at this motherfucker.
I like to jump on him.
And they got to me.
But it was kind of coincidentally.
It happened while I was watching a movie.
It's a...
A dramatized documentary about Abbey Hoffman.
Abbey Hoffman was a radical protester,
actually a professional demonstration organizer
in the 70s, 60s and 70s.
And I'm very familiar with Abbey Hoffman
because when I was...
Gosh, I'm gonna say maybe 9 or 10.
And this was without a doubt,
a part of my...
this... this formed a part of my...
of me.
My overall DNA.
We were just living in the Netherlands.
Had been there for maybe two years.
And there was the Americans' Women's Club.
My mom was a member of the American Women's Club.
And it was a pretty senseless organization, probably.
But, you know, it was a way for...
There was probably a hundred American families
over in Holland at the time.
A lot of them from Texas instruments.
Another company's like this.
It was just starting to go into these new open European markets.
Ah, excuse me.
And... did you just think Sensei or like I did?
I can't help it.
And they had a library.
You know, their own library.
Essentially, the women would bring in all the books
that they had already read,
or that they had laying around the house and wanted to clean up.
And so they created their own library, which was nice.
I used to go with my mom to the American Women's Club.
And I'd walk around the library and there was this book.
And this book said steal this book.
And I'm like, holy crap, this is great.
And it was really kind of a guide,
a guide to gorilla warfare, if you will.
You know, and how to organize demonstrations
and how to, you know, really have an effect
with doing something to change the country, the world, etc.
And I didn't know much about Adby Hoffman,
but this book was fantastic.
It told you how to, you know, how to survive on no money.
If you're like a fugitive, which, you know, watching this documentary,
this drama, I should say,
it's a Jeanine Garofflo place as girlfriend in it.
So it's really well done.
I actually have found it on,
I don't know how I came up with looking for it for it.
But I know I did a Google search and there was a Google video.
I'll see if I can put a link to it in the show notes
at dailysourcecode.com.
And so I watched it about two hours,
an hour and a half hour and 45 minutes.
And it was really fascinating.
This guide actually, I think, did effect.
You know, did stops, did stop the war in Vietnam.
Or it certainly had an effect on the thinking of the country.
And, you know, it was the hippies.
It was the summer of love.
And it really delves into, and this is kind of one generation
before me or half a generation before me.
Yet a little bit younger than my parents.
And it was, it was fascinating to watch.
And I just, you know, and I just started thinking,
like, wow, you know, we really do something like that.
You know, something else I remember from this book,
was to coordinate a simultaneous toilet flush.
You know, if you end the theory there is,
I don't know if that still holds true with today's,
supposedly upgraded infrastructure,
but the theory is that if you get an entire city to flush,
they're totally at the same time at a given moment
that there would literally be shit roaming through the streets
because the, you know,
the infrastructure of the sewer system wouldn't be able to handle it.
It was that kind of stuff.
Yeah, it was really, I enjoyed it very much.
And it really awakened part of the revolutionary in me.
If you can get a hand, your hands on it.
I'll see, maybe Amazon hasn't.
I'll see if they have a copy of it,
no link to it.
I'll be Hoffman's steal this book.
And so I started thinking, you know,
and thinking about Ron Paul, thinking about,
and also, you know, just because I was home
and I wasn't feeling well, I had the television on.
And kind of just say one thing,
if you want to help your country at all,
if you want to do anything,
the first thing I do was turn off your frickin' TV.
This is bad.
What's going on with American television today is,
it's just atrocious.
And it's meant to distract your attention
from anything remotely possible.
And we could go into how that works,
but another time, maybe,
because having worked in American media,
I know that there's no grand scheme,
there's no master plan.
It's just how it is.
There's influence.
And you follow that influence,
because that's what you do.
And it's all based upon greed,
greed, or should we call it,
maybe greed is not the right word.
A vanity, maybe that's better.
You know, in the media business,
everyone wants to be on top.
Everyone wants to be the man, everyone wants to be the superstar.
How do you get there?
Well, either you really, really go for it,
like Madonna did,
and you're bitch all the way to the top,
which is a very tiring way to do it,
or like most people.
You know, you kind of go with the flow.
And so that's how stuff doesn't get on the air
and things that aren't important,
for instance, finding out that,
guess what, turned out Iran isn't actually
making nuclear weapons.
But of course, this is already being spun
into, well, you know,
they could have the capability by 2012, 2015,
so we still got to do something about that.
This is bad news.
So, of course,
I'm basically laying down on the couch,
and I'm like,
I don't want to get up,
and I'll feel too good.
Let me Google around.
And what is really the root of all of our problems?
You know, me, I like to follow the money.
I believe that the only way we can get anyone
elected in this country is if we have enough money,
and that's actually going quite well
with Ron Paul's campaign.
Of course, we'll hit the $12 million easily.
I think we'll go over it.
December 16th, the Boston Tea Party Tea Party 07.com.
So, we're going to do another money bomb for Ron Paul.
So, Senator, there'll be plenty of opportunity to advertise,
which is the way we'd like presidents
in these United States is through commercials.
Another reason why I don't want you watching television.
So, when else might have better commercials.
And, you know,
just letting my thoughts go free and thinking about stuff,
and I eventually came up with a phrase
that I've heard mentioned a lot.
And I think it was probably,
while I was on the Abbey Hoffman page
on the Google video that I saw in your related videos.
And it was a video of President Eisenhower,
his exit speech in 1961.
So, he'd been president for eight years.
It was time for him to leave.
And he addressed the nation in a televised speech.
And this was where the phrase,
the military industrial complex was coined.
And I just want to play that for you
just so you can listen to it
because I want to talk about it.
This is...
Ladies and gentlemen, the president of the United States.
As I said from now on.
Good evening.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we now stand ten years past the midpoint of a century
that has witnessed four major wars among great nations.
Until the latest of our world conflicts,
the United States had no armaments industry.
American makers of Plouch Airs could
with time and as required, make swords as well.
But we can no longer risk emergency improvisation of national defense.
We have been compelled to create a permanent armaments industry
of vast proportions.
I did do this.
Three and a half million men and women are directly engaged in the defense established.
Now this conjunction of an immense military establishment
and a large arms industry is new in the American experience.
The total influence, economic, political, even spiritual
is felt in every city, every state house,
every office of the federal government.
We recognize the imperative need for this development.
Yet we must not fail to comprehend its grave implications.
Our toil, resources, and livelihood are all involved.
So is the very structure of our society.
In the councils of government,
we must guard against the acquisition of unwarranted influence,
whether sought or unsought by the military industrial complex.
The potential for the disastrous rise of misplaced power exists
and will persist.
We must never let the weight of this combination in danger or liberties
or democratic processes.
We should take nothing for granted.
Only an alert and knowledgeable citizen can compel
the proper meshing of the huge industrial and military machinery of defense
with our peaceful, methods and goals.
So that security and liberty may prosper together.
Sounds a bit like a science fiction flick, doesn't it?
Well, it's not.
It's real.
It was a real president.
The president that, as far as I can tell,
everyone really loved and thought was good.
And he came from the military.
He was generalized an hour.
He knew what was going on.
And this is exactly what has happened.
What he won for has now taken place because
and this is from my own experiences.
So I do have some firsthand knowledge of this.
First of all, Dick Cheney, part of the military industrial complex
is vice president, right?
And the way Washington works as I'm learning now
and as I delve into a deeper and I have, you know,
of course you, uh,
and it'll be bumping the Alex Jones's info wars.com.
And there's all kinds of, you know, stuff out there.
But just for my own,
distilled, rationalized perspective.
This has happened.
The military industrial complex has taken over so much money
is being made on any war.
And of course, there's a couple of them going on
that were involved in one way or the other.
For, you know,
not just making war weaponry.
But this is kind of the hidden, you know,
the hidden fact of this war of the Iraq war
is that there are so many companies
involved in the servicing of what's taking place.
I mean, no longer do we have soldiers who are on KP duty.
You know, there's no one who has to
peel potatoes.
No, it's catered.
When I was in Bosra in 2003,
I couldn't believe my eyes.
When I saw the base 5,000
troops in this one base in Bosra
and they had a burger king,
they had a pizza hut, they had a full on
diner with a great salad bar.
I might point out.
You know, these,
our troops have now become high-tech troops.
You know, there's like, they're like athletes almost.
This is really disgusting to think about it.
But also very science fictiony.
You know, they, you know,
everything is done for them.
They're serviced in every single way.
And of course, there's more private soldiers.
They're all not for a second.
In Iraq than there are,
in listed men and women.
And this is costing us billions and billions of dollars.
And every corporation is intended to make profit and prosper.
So, you know, and then eventually get taken over
or take over.
What are the two?
So it's in the DNA of companies to find war.
Now, if those companies are represented in our government,
which, of course, is almost exactly like show business.
You know, where people come in
and they don't want to ruffle too many feathers.
They want to climb up the ladder.
And you've got these lobbyists.
And you've got money flowing in.
And everyone is controlled one way or the other.
And it's a slave of the system.
And so, I conclude from that that it actually
doesn't matter who our president is anymore.
It does not matter unless
unless the people step up to the plate as well.
So, what you're seeing right now on television
and why do you still have this thing on?
I told you to turn it off.
What you see is a show.
It's a show just to keep us occupied
because it doesn't matter.
Whether a Democrat or a Republican,
whoever becomes president,
everything in this whole system is set up
to continuously create revenue
for the military industrial complex.
Now, that doesn't mean that I'm giving up on the presidential elections,
but I do have some thoughts about it.
Now, as you know, I'm endorsing Ron Paul
and Scott sent in the following comment.
Hello, Adam.
It's a scotch.
It's a scotch of the uncommon sense podcast on Podgeau.
I like yourself, would like to see Ron Paul
get a chance to turn this country around.
I was thinking out loud on my podcast
recently here about the whole way
that our elective system works.
You know, we've got computer modeling programs
that they're using now,
that are just getting incredibly
deadly accurate at predicting
how a change in position
will change the number of people voting for you.
Yeah, you know what this is?
It's the same software we use in television.
The same software and same,
maybe not exactly the same software,
but it's the same algorithms we used to determine
how will movie ends?
You know, even though the director and the writer
might have intended it one way,
we can get a bigger box office
if we change that.
That's the same software.
It's the same algorithms.
It's been used since the 50s since television began.
Absolutely right.
It's just like weather or forecasting or modeling.
They know the demographics in the country.
They know how many gays.
They can basically divide up the entire population.
Yeah, they know who went to college
and everything.
Absolutely.
And a lot of people have these databases.
We have access to it too, in theory.
You know, the pie into the demographics.
And they know that within any demographic,
you can get a certain number of votes
if you can sway them.
For instance, if you wanted to get the
the gay demographic, you might say
that you are very in favor of gay marriage.
If you wanted to get a demographic of elderly people,
you might say how in favor you were
of improving the social security system and so forth.
And you can literally get predictable
bumps in your popularity or bumps up or down,
depending on which direction you want to go.
It's pretty sad.
Also, the whole way that our elective system works,
you've got to have the cute little sound
if you are complaining about the advertisements
and the way they sound compared to what we have here
on the internet and such.
And it's so true.
But the problem is that with our system,
we've got now, how can you compete
when they know things this precisely
and they know exactly what you need to change things
in a certain way.
It's kind of frustrating, isn't it?
To have Ron Paul go with a different sort
of advertising and campaign
would probably put him at a disadvantage.
And I was thinking about all of that
and about the idea that candidate
that I've liked in the past
have not made it so good here in New Hampshire.
We get the first shot in the first
in the nation presidential primary.
And I voted for a number of Ron Paul's in the past
that I really believed in.
They were not the mainstream candidate,
but they would have made
darn good presidents, I think.
And they never went very far.
And I thought how frustrating that was.
And it got me to thinking about Abraham Lincoln.
I mean, how do you think Abraham Lincoln
would be perceived if he would run
for president today?
I mean, the guy
didn't look good on TV.
In fact, from when I understand,
he would have been butt ugly,
especially in high-deaf.
Didn't someone tell me that he was gay?
Well, there was some rumor about him being gay?
Uh, I doubt he was very good at a sound bite
and God knows what they could have
dug up from his past.
So it's kind of sad, doesn't it?
That, you know, I would really like
to think that possibly Ron Paul
could be like Abraham Lincoln.
A man that has some real sound
values down to earth,
honest, all that sort of thing.
And yet our political system may very well
make minced meat out of him.
And what a pity, do you, huh?
Anymore, anyway, thanks for listening to me
and interesting in your comments on this.
And, um,
take care.
Yeah, so, you know,
it's all a part of it.
Right now, Huckabee is, uh,
shooting up in all the polls, all the,
all the data, all the stats.
I think it's a setup.
I think they're just setting them up
and they're gonna make them look like an incredible fool.
You watch.
Um,
I don't believe any of it.
I really don't.
I really don't believe anything
anyone's telling us.
Um, just don't believe it.
So, um,
okay, so anyway, so
we, we cannot
just elect a president.
We cannot just go after
getting our guy in there who's going to work
the system from the inside.
The system is big.
The system is vast.
We, we, we need some
civilian action to actually change this.
You're going back to the military industrial complex.
You know, when, uh,
when you think about troops coming in or going
out of Iraq,
I mean, what's the visual you have there?
The visual is, you know,
big C 130's transport planes,
uh,
landing in deserts.
Yeah, dude.
I'm sorry.
It's American Airlines who's been contracted
to transport our troops.
It may not be American, but it could be united.
But I think it's American Airlines.
Hundred to millions of dollars worth of contracts.
I mean, this is, this is what's happening.
Who makes that money?
Then I'm doing it for free.
They really aren't.
They're doing it for profit.
And this is what's keeping our entire system rolling.
Uh, I got to tell you.
I think we should stop it.
I think we have the power to stop it.
I think it's not even that hard to stop it.
And I'm still formulating my ideas.
So this is homework for you guys.
But it seems to me that if we need to do,
it has to be a two-step process.
We have to demand that Ron Paul become president
because he holds the ideals of the constitution.
He pledged his career to the constitution.
And I think we need to stop the military industrial complex.
It seems like a big job, right?
Well, it isn't because we still today,
we still have enough freedoms.
But it's dwindling by the second.
We still have the power to do exactly what the writers
and Los Angeles are doing for show business.
Remember politics and show business kind of the same thing.
People climb the ladder the same way.
In fact, I'd say politics is show business for ugly people.
I think we can strike.
I think that now I need some data on this.
But obviously people who work at plants where they make weapons strike.
And there's many ways to strike.
You can you can call in sick.
You can there's a million different things we can do.
Of course it would be much better if we basically said,
I'm striking until Ron Paul is president.
That's one way.
You know, so how about Burger King?
Pizza Hut.
You know, what if all the employees said,
Hey, you know what?
I'm sick and tired of this war.
I'm not going to support it.
I'm not going to work anymore until you guys get your ass out of Iraq.
And stop making money off of it.
Stop making money off the war.
Now we can do this with tons of different companies.
Entire industries.
So I want you to think about it because in the next,
in the coming few weeks, I'm going to be coming back to this topic.
Because I really believe we can make this different.
This is where it all comes together, right?
My Abby Hoffman revisiting Abby Hoffman experience.
I'm a realization that show business.
And media is just like politics.
And that we cannot just think that we're going to elect a guy who represents our ideas and ideals.
And that it's all going to be okay.
We have to take action.
I'm, you know, this is I'm really too old for this.
I'm sick too.
I don't feel up to it.
And I don't work for the right people.
I work for myself.
But there's got to be a way that we can, we can affect this.
You'll see that the writers are going,
and the writers are having an effect on the media business.
We can have the same effect within weeks,
within weeks on the military industrial complex.
So let's think about this.
And I'd love to hear from you.
Obviously the common lines are wide open as well as email
Adam at podshow.com.
Oh, yeah.
I don't know.
It's Amy Mack.
I baby.
I need some yellow.
I don't know.
I apologize to the ones that I love.
The left cheek and the right cheek.
I'm sorry that I let you get all sudden flabby.
Although I have to say that every squeeze in and earlier today
they are still quite nice.
Oh yeah, baby.
It was never my intention to leave you all alone for weeks on end.
So from now on,
I promise I'll leave you a priority when I meet.
So Adam.
Yes.
Please take me back.
Oh, Amy.
Are you kidding me?
I go to I'll wait another year for MP3 love
for my exercise.
And I'm glad that you didn't actually make me do an exercise today
because I don't think I would have been able to handle it.
Hey, Adam. It's Chris Wayne here.
You're willing to do that one over the weekend.
Yeah.
About him.
It's Chris Wayne here.
Your illegitimate pods on from the UK.
You know, I must just say I haven't listened to it.
Yes, 48.
And the latest DSC, which we're all on.
Oh, the Chris Rio one, right?
Daily source code, episode 694.
Um, head over to the iTunes Media tool.
And did buy a Chris Rio's voice in your photo.
Excellent.
It's one second for that.
And yeah.
Keep going on with it.
Obviously shows that playing music on your show sales.
Thanks.
See you soon.
Of course it does.
This is the secret.
I got some meetings like Universal Music Group
and Warner Music Group.
They now want to talk about licensed music on podcast,
which is probably going to be a really short meeting.
Like, okay.
You know, look, pod safe or not.
Is that simple?
Either you put it up on the network.
Let people play it or not.
It's that fucking simple.
That's going to be the meeting.
But it works.
It's proof right here.
You've been playing a 10 second snippet.
Sales, songs.
How hard can that be?
How many Chris Rio CDs?
Do you guys still sell?
Huh?
Of course Matthew Snodgrass has the real answers to why.
Music sells when featured in the hit test.
Hi.
I'm Casey Casey.
Do you remember those classic hits of the 80s?
Me too.
But you've never heard them quite like this in the newest of the KTL series.
Adam Curry.
Desacraced the hits of the 80s.
No cover on the night.
That's right.
You can come to hate those timeless tracks of history year in a whole new way.
When Adam Curry put you some worse than a blind man with a cleaver.
Listen, as he performs this classic duet with Sir Evan John.
And it's not just the vocals Adam murders.
He takes that finger nails across a chalkboard styling to the tune itself.
Some one call the police.
Or this holiday to the 1984 ad of two ad of Dutch.
The Zumpens telling me Brian Adams is running right back to Canada.
Oh my dear Lord, call in the dark.
I don't know what love is.
Frankly, I echo Noah to make of this.
I think I just give up.
Check the website.
Thank you.
KTK's now.
You know Patricia always says it.
And she's right now that I'm listening to it.
It sounds like I'm in pain when I'm singing absolutely.
Adam.
Here's some Portland here.
Listen, you know, I don't like the fuck Adam Curry thing.
Fuck you Adam Curry at the end of the message.
I, I think it should stop.
I have enough.
I love you Adam Curry.
You know, that's it.
That's so nice.
I think we should start changing that I agree.
From now on, please end your comments with I love you Adam Curry.
And say it like you mean it damn.
And say I love you Adam Curry.
It's that time of year.
Time for the big Pacho Radio Christmas special.
If you love Christmas as much as I do,
join Brent Bradley as he puts you in the holiday spirit with some incredible Christmas music.
Greetings from some of your favorite podcasts and potsafe artists.
A Christmas story that the entire family will enjoy.
And your chance to win a Christmas package full of lots of cool surprises.
So make sure to mark your calendar for December 1st.
That's the day that all the fun begins.
Hope to see you there.
Where you ask?
Oh, that's easy.
PachoRadio.com.
So I've been away from home for quite a while.
It's going to be at least for the rest of the week.
I'm pretty sure.
I'm not feeling well.
I'm feeling a little bit lonely.
A little bit melancholy.
So, well, what can you do?
I think the best thing.
I think that I've got somewhere else to be.
I'll be leaving here at 6 a.m.
To stay in the sea, my family.
All my sweaters, they've been packed.
A bit of cold won't make me crack.
Once I get there, I don't know.
I don't care how I'm coming back.
Cause I would walk a thousand miles.
I would walk a thousand miles.
With a snow rain or better cold to be back on for Christmas.
I've been gone too long to say,
But I'm coming anyway.
I can't leave this town and get back on today.
Let the snow fall through the air.
I got eight long hours to spare.
I'll be waiting at the airport bar for three, but I don't care.
Cause I would walk a thousand miles.
I would walk a thousand miles.
There was a snow rain or better cold to be back on for Christmas.
But this long flight, don't bother me.
Three men and shepherds came to see.
The baby born this morning,
Lows away from their locality.
An angel singing, clear padded Lucia.
The Christ is coming here with no plan.
We're no strangers to where that's still.
The time and to find me.
You know we found me.
So I would walk a thousand miles.
I would walk a thousand miles.
Through the snow rain or check out lines,
A traffic change and I would walk a thousand miles.
I would walk a thousand miles.
Through the snow rain or winter storms
To be back on for Christmas.
I would walk a thousand miles.
Through the snow rain or better cold to be back on for Christmas.
Matthew Ebel recorded live in 2004.
I'll be home for Christmas.
Little melancholy there just to touch at the end.
Alright, so let's get all over the show.
We've got to stop the military industrial complex.
We need to elect Ron Paul.
It's just a minor agenda.
People, I'm sure we can take care of this.
TatiSourceco.com, Adam at podshow.com.
I'll be back talking to you more about this later in the week.
Bye-bye.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Imagine headphones without wires.
Now their Sony's Bluetooth wireless headset.
A rechargeable listening experience with 11 hours of music playback.
So you and your music are free to move.
Pick up yours at Sony.com slash headphones.
Sony wireless headphones.
Your music on plug.