Make a statement with Sony stereo ear buds, sleek metal housings that reduce vibration
delivering killer sound from a tiny package.
Buy yours at Sony.com-slashheadphones, Sony ear buds were style-meat sound.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation
radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this genre.
Sometimes an atom's all alone.
He meets his love right there on the microphone.
So here she is, yes, the Lady Patricia.
The say-to-heads are better than one.
And with this angel from above, there's nothing that they both can't do.
They got to have a wonderful journey.
Time's filled with all the clinging glitter.
Butterflies of happiness.
His voice sounds even better.
When the Lady arrives on the Delta Cherichardly, oh I see.
A good split, the feeling of her love penetrates his head.
The meaning of life, it feels so matching when she's around.
My God, she looked great to get the shell on the road.
An open vest, the Passegdabla.
She smiles and pray for you in bed.
My dear Charlie Friends, dear Pat Father, Elife Patricia.
One giant stack for AC is a giant stack for the Queen.
Ladies and gentlemen, just and only here on the DSC.
Join Adam and the lovely Lady Patricia.
Summer journeys to Niagara, and to World of Places,
I believe all our kids.
We'll save our fears.
I've a cozy little flat in what is known as old man hadn't we'll settle down.
Right here in town, we'll have man hadn't.
The Bronx and Staten Island too.
It's lovely going through the zoo.
It's very fancy.
I know the lancest street you know.
The some way charms are so.
When Bobby breezes blow to and fro.
And tell me what street compares with much street into life.
Sweet push cards gently glide.
The great big cities of wonder store.
Just make for a girl and boy.
We'll turn that hat into an island of joy.
We'll go to yankers where true love conquers in the wild.
And start together dear in child.
We'll go to Coney and eat baloney on a road.
In central park we'll stroll where our first kiss we stole.
So do so.
And my fair lady is a terrific show they say.
We both may see it close.
Someday the city's glamour can never spoil.
The dreams of a boy and go.
We'll turn man hat into an island of joy.
Hey everybody it's dream of a boy and go.
A boy and go.
Daily source code episode number 701 coming to you from the curry manner.
And we welcome the lady Patricia.
Hey baby how you doing?
Yeah doing fine.
It's so nice to hear that song.
You can see New York.
If you hear this song you see New York.
That's why I chose it specifically for you baby.
I can see myself walking in the central park.
Yes.
It's so beautiful.
Chestnuts roasting on an open fire.
Especially when it's winter.
I remember that I remember the smell.
Jack Frost nipping at my nuts.
Yep.
And you could feed the little squirrels there.
But it was very cold in the winter.
So that's why I played it for you because I knew we would give you that New York vibe.
And you were talking about New York the other day.
I know.
I've got New York on my mind.
Really?
I don't know why.
It's totally.
I can feel the atmosphere and everything.
The whole thing.
Really?
How long has it been since you've been there?
Not so long.
I think it was to use it.
In a year ago.
Wasn't it a year?
Longer than that.
I remember what it was.
John for Cartveg was there too.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Walking.
Maybe that was more than a year now.
At the end of the year.
I think it was.
I think it's two years ago.
Time is going by so fast.
I know.
Ladies and gentlemen, the lady Patricia is wearing a nice.
What is that you have on?
It is.
She's dressed in black.
Rubimanto.
Yes.
Nice boots by the way.
Oh, yes, and.
Oh, wow.
I'm not taking them off anymore.
No, I've noticed that.
And did you notice it last night in bed?
I was wearing them too.
No.
You didn't.
It wasn't necessary.
I didn't need the boots to get all excited.
I know.
Say, please just tell them.
Just tell them.
It's good for my ego.
Holy.
So you don't need that hunt.
Yeah, I do.
Everybody knows you got a big ego.
Yeah, big ego.
Yeah.
So been home for the holidays, which was nice.
Nice to be.
Nice to be home.
Wow.
Pretty much not stop talking.
Since I came home.
But you were always so many times.
Yeah.
It was the first it was like you were home and gone again.
It was the home and gone again.
10 or 11 days in San Francisco that I come back.
Then I went to Helsinki.
You went to New York.
No, no.
First the first I went to San Francisco came back.
Went to Helsinki.
He was thinking.
It's not true.
It doesn't stink.
I never did food.
No, I had some good food.
I had reindeer.
You had good food.
Yeah, I like it.
We remember all the stinky fish every time.
Well, I hung out with the candy man.
You know, he knows where to take a stinky fish.
A stinky fish.
They had stinky fish there, too.
I know.
They do have some kind of stinky stuff.
So Helsinki then came back here.
Then went to San Francisco again.
And I'm supposed to stay for a week and stay for two weeks.
Yeah.
Then came back.
Then went to New York.
New York.
For four days or whatever.
Normally I would have gone with you.
To New York.
Yeah.
That was not possible because you didn't have any time to do something fun.
I know.
And it wasn't fun because it was wet.
It was wet and it snowed.
Everybody had a cold hair.
Why don't I had a cold in New York, too?
No.
Which we've kind of scared.
I mean, I haven't.
I had my, my sick time this year.
Mm-hmm.
That's it.
How about you?
Yeah.
Christina hasn't been really sick.
Well, she brings the sniffles.
Right.
But what she does is she fights it real quickly.
It's gone.
And then we have it.
And I can get rid of it because I'm an old fart, of course.
Of course.
Yep.
So this will more than likely be the last show that you're on.
Uh, of 2007.
That's right.
Can you?
I was thinking about it.
I couldn't believe it.
You know?
But I was young.
Imagine.
I mean, I come from the 60s.
Yes.
And then you come from before the 60s.
I know.
But in the 60s, start to think.
Wow.
It's 60s.
You know?
Uh-huh.
Well, you live through it.
You really live through the 60s.
I think they're writing down.
1961.
If you turn it around, he was 1961.
Oh, power.
Yeah.
Oh, that was such.
That was cool.
But then I, and you thought about, you know, wow.
What is it?
2000.
What if it's 2008?
My god.
That's so spacey.
Yeah.
Well, but we're living in space.
We are.
But if I look at all the equipment, all the gadgets and the connections and the email and mobile phone.
You would have told me that.
Then I would have thought.
My man.
If we walk around the street with little earpieces talking to other people.
Yeah.
It's amazing.
What's possible, you know?
Uh, I don't think it's on necessarily good.
I don't know.
Because we're becoming pretty enslaved to all the stuff and all the stuff.
All the stuff and all the connections.
We have to get out once in a while.
You're good at that balance.
You know, balance.
I know.
I'm always asking you to balance everything.
Bye.
Cool for your baby.
I love balance a little bit.
But if I, if I walk the street here in the streets in, um, your regular street.
My street.
In a gulf.
When you walk your street.
I see these people.
Everybody has a phone on any.
I noticed that the other day when we were shopping in the high street.
Nobody is noticing anything anymore.
Absolutely.
You know, you know, some, I think when we didn't have those those things at our ears,
we were looking at each other.
You know, you had, you were, you saw connection or you, you, you looked at each other or you,
you, you know,
Good point.
Yeah.
Or you, or you saw that somebody was actually very handsome.
Or what?
You know, I'm very good to, could, to dress her.
Well, how to be honest.
I still look at people.
And I observed that stuff.
Yeah.
Look at you anymore.
No.
You're absolutely right.
I was, I was looking at that.
I was actually thinking two things at the time.
Yeah.
You know, the high street is, um, it's almost like a 35 degree decline.
So you stand at the top of the high street.
You can kind of look all the way down.
Yeah.
And you just saw scores of people on their phone either texting or talking.
Everybody is in his own world.
Yeah.
In their own little cone of size.
And, and that just kind of, um,
walking around, you know,
just almost aimlessly.
Yeah.
You're right.
And I was also thinking, fuck those guys must be making a lot of money.
Yeah.
I mean, you noticed, because we were in Guildford in, uh, in town.
Mm-hmm.
There's afternoon.
I like to talk to the people.
Mm-hmm.
I just start to talk to anybody.
Oh, but surprisingly, when you speak to them.
Walking next to me.
Yeah.
When you speak to someone, they actually enjoy it.
If it's something nice.
Yeah.
Because it was a mother walking beautiful, beautiful red hair, uh, red hair daughter.
So, is she for sale?
She was gorgeous hair.
I'd like to find her for my husband.
Flame of shut up.
The, the color just flamed in the beautiful.
That was nice color hair.
Um, the sun was going down a little bit of winter sun.
You could see the beautiful red hair.
She was probably 17 years.
Oh, really?
And I said to the mother.
Oh, my god.
Is there her own color?
It's beautiful.
She said, yeah, I got three daughters.
They all have red hair.
I said, it's amazing.
Yeah.
And, you know, I like that.
I like it.
Yeah.
We were standing there next to, you know, just one of the traffic lights.
Mm-hmm.
We're on red.
So, are you standing next to a stranger?
And we're all my thing on crazy.
Wherever you are right now, whatever you're doing, I want you to pause this show.
Just go ahead and put it on pause.
And I want you to make eye contact with someone in your direct vicinity.
So, if you're on the bus on the train, if you're in the car.
Yeah.
Just pause this right now and make direct eye contact with someone and smile.
Look at them.
Okay.
Very good.
Make sure you feel good.
It does make you feel good.
Yeah, it does make you feel good.
Yeah.
Because otherwise, you feel so lonely.
You know?
Ah, yes.
All right.
So, are we in here, it's right?
Yeah.
So, wrapping up 2007, good year for you?
Um, yes and no.
No.
Especially because I still miss my little cat.
And thanks for everybody who sent me beautiful condoluses and beautiful little stories.
There are lots of really beautiful stories that people even made.
Yeah.
I had so much mail.
Thank you.
Because it really helps.
Yeah.
Because you always feel lonely when you're, you know, sad.
We still miss our pussy cat.
You miss us.
And you think nobody knows how I feel.
But people do know how you feel.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
You know, they had the same experience.
And I was, I'm still, I still miss them so, so much.
Yeah.
You know, and I noticed that my cat, and I told you that before, it took months and months.
For ginger, the red one.
Yeah.
He's best friend to get over this.
I think that the cat's more and so much.
Oh, no kidding.
And his old face just.
It's gone.
Yeah.
You know, it was not his face anymore.
So it's hard to, to have a little grin.
You know, it's coming back.
Right.
It's coming back.
But so ginger and I were very sad.
Yeah.
Well, we're all very sad.
So.
Okay.
That was amazing.
That people just, you know.
So that was bad.
So it was bad and good at the same thing.
Thinking about you is good.
That's nice.
So that was it.
And for the rest.
You know, I think the dancing was was wonderful.
Good experience.
Yeah.
I hope that when the weather is getting better, I would like to go out again and have a nice
walks and dance again because I'm actually waiting for my dance teacher.
Are you waiting for the dance school to move back to the neighborhood?
It's too to the neighborhood.
It's such a lazy person.
It's too far.
It's too far to go for a half an hour and hour dance.
Okay.
I wish I could dance with you.
But that's just never going to happen.
And especially the English people, you know, we just had a strictly condensing here.
Just finished.
Yeah.
And we had dancing with the stars for the Americans listening.
Like the American.
And it was 9 million.
That's a lot for it.
But it was 13.9 almost 14 million for the Christmas East Enders episode.
But I have to say, we were like, you know, we sat down.
We were glued to the set.
We watched it.
Yeah.
It was fantastic.
I've got to say, it's just great acting.
I really enjoy the acting.
The stories.
That's hard.
You know, it's not as bad as American soap operas.
Well, what I like about East Enders and the acting is that the people who acted are so,
they look so real.
You know, they're not too beautiful.
Like the American soap operas.
The people are so perfect.
And so beautiful.
Yeah.
And so glamorous.
You know, their faces are lifted.
They're so gorgeous.
True.
And they never get old.
But here they're real faces.
Real people.
Some people, some actors don't even have makeup on their faces.
Really?
No.
Oh, no.
Nothing.
That's why you can have to see their red cheeks.
That's right.
When they get slapped.
Yeah.
Exactly.
I like that.
It's a special sort of acting.
Yeah.
You know, theatre.
It was a pretty good Christmas meeting.
Theatre.
Theatre in East Enders.
Yeah.
I like that.
It was a good media Christmas.
I would have to say.
Yeah.
So what I wanted to say is wrapping up 2007.
Wrap it up.
That means that.
You watch the dancing.
Everybody's, oh, I'm going to do this.
But nobody does it.
Right.
But actually, you should.
Because I noticed that it is so cool.
It's fun and it's good for your body.
You feel much better.
And you lose a lot of weight.
Hey, why don't we do a dancing show with you?
Huh?
Ha ha ha ha.
I'm going to step back for your enthusiasm.
Ha ha.
Yeah.
I want to.
Let's go.
I don't want to do a dancing show.
Yeah.
Where?
What do you mean?
Something cool.
I mean, if, uh, I don't know.
That's very hard.
Why is it hard?
I don't know.
I promise you'll get you one of the steady cams that goes around you in the opposite direction
of your twirling.
Well, you know what?
Maybe we could promise people if I go dancing again.
Maybe I should bring a camera.
Hmm.
Okay.
That's a good one.
Yeah.
You can see his dance in just normal.
Just the time for me.
Yeah.
Just show normal people dancing.
It could be fun.
Yeah.
And I wish you could dance with me.
But you're to touch.
It's the wrong length.
I wouldn't mind learning how to dance.
I know.
I'm anxious to do a drive.
Anxious.
Yeah.
No.
Are there cute tall chicks at these dancing schools?
Uh.
Because then I'll take it over.
No.
Well, who am I going to dance with then?
Is there anyone in mind?
You should dance with me.
Because when, when.
Yeah.
In our dance, we have those couples.
We have only one who is by myself.
Oh, by myself.
I have no partner.
You're looking at my belly button.
That's what I said.
I explained that to my teachers.
That I can dance with my husband.
So you have no dancing.
The only thing we can do is laying down.
And how does that work for you?
Fantastic.
God.
I want to play the hit test.
You want to play the hit test?
Okay.
This will be the last hit test of 2007.
So you remember it goes real fast, right?
No.
I'm not good at that.
Okay.
You know, young actually does a video.
You want to see the video version of it?
I may actually be funnier.
Oh, is that?
Yeah.
Let me see if I can get to it.
Does he do video version?
Yeah.
It's fucking crazy.
With him.
Yes.
He got a seat.
Oh, don't even know how he looks.
In the studio.
You want to see?
He's all right.
You know, he's not my type.
Hold on.
Let me see.
I don't know if it'll play right away.
If I have the download of that.
I'll kind of suck.
Let me see.
Hold on.
Let me turn.
I can turn the monitor.
So you can see it.
So it's 102 video.
Oh, man.
Is it MP4?
Does that mean they'll take for fucking everybody to download?
Oh, we'll see.
Well, let me see.
Let me see.
There we go.
It might work.
Okay.
It's not moving, huh?
Really?
You noticed.
All right.
We'll wait for that to start up.
Well, anyway.
Okay.
Sorry about that.
Yeah.
All right.
Go ahead.
Say something.
Well, what I wanted to say is I noticed because I have a lot of information in my head, you know, throughout the years.
All the things that I know, all the names that I know, all the music, the songs, the singers, the groups.
I know so much.
And until we played the trivia spot the intro game.
That's what I wanted to say.
They didn't know shit.
I didn't know.
Well, I couldn't come up with it.
A fast enough.
And that's because you're not using those names anymore.
You don't hear the music anymore.
It was all the way in the back of my head.
So let me just explain.
I bought this game called Spot the intro.
And it's like a musical trivia game.
Yeah.
And it's all right.
You know, the five different categories.
You go around a board with your little dude.
And you know, East time you land on a spot.
You could five questions every question.
You answer right you move ahead one.
And that's a really, you know, they said it was from 14 ages 14 and up.
But it was.
We played with Christina.
But I have to see.
She knows a lot.
Yeah.
She absolutely does.
She does.
I was amazed.
I was amazed to see her.
I fucked this one.
Yeah.
I'll show it to you next time.
I'm counting casting with Adam Curry.
Hey, Adam.
You ready to be stumped.
Hell.
Good.
He used that.
Fantastic.
With young pull back.
Hey, Adam.
This is, he tests number 102.
And we're going to start right away with intro number one.
Yeah.
Bam.
I have the tiger.
You should know that one.
No.
Number 2.
Bam.
ξhrrn back-to-time.
And the final onage.
Bam.
Damn.
Bam!
Bam.
Hey,有, problem.
Now we've shot it.
And so number one from 1982, Eye of the Tiger, Survivor.
I have the Tiger Survivor, answer number one, and this is answer number two.
From 1988, Jenny H. Jazz, turn back to clock.
I want to say her hospital.
And I still can't smoke, I wish that I could turn back the clock.
One, there you go.
Did you mention, if you want to be with me, that's fine.
I'll tell you.
Yeah, of course.
And to number two, Jenny H. Jazz, and this is answer number three.
From 1990, this is Phil Collins, something happened on the way to heaven.
Wow, this is good.
Yeah, but you recognize Phil Collins sound.
I smell the jazz.
You can run, and you can run, but you're living.
Answer number three, Phil Collins, in hit us number 102.
So Adam, how did you do?
I wanted to have.
The answers to this hit us, and also the links to iTunes.
So you can buy these tricks online.
Can be found at hittest.partshow.com.
And by the way, you can also follow me through Twitter.
And you have to look at twitter.com slash young polettes.
Alrighty, Adam, thank you for playing.
Everyone else, thank you for listening.
And next week, I'll be back for number 103.
So until then, take care, and bye-bye.
So much fun.
I do recognize him, but I don't know what.
Like, oh yeah, I know that.
I know that.
Well, it's interesting because, of course, I told the story about Simone.
So that's why he put, I knew that.
And I was thinking, is that Johnny is just, I didn't know for sure.
I was like, turn back the time.
I recognize him.
And I actually have queued up as the,
Yeah, you were pointing out.
And I had queued up, I want to play you the pod safe version of Shadow Dreams.
Oh, good.
Because he put it up.
Simone and Clark put up.
Shadow Dreams.
It's a whole different version.
So I want you to hear that.
And we'll play it in a couple minutes.
So yeah, I thought it was, I knew it was full content.
I didn't know.
Somebody should actually do that again.
That's all.
That's a great song.
Which one?
Turn back the clock.
Really?
Yeah, yeah.
Somebody should cover that.
Well, maybe Clark will do it himself in a different version.
I don't think that works, because
You don't think it works?
Did he did Shadow Dreams?
I know.
But he's old enough.
And if you see them on TV, you think.
You know.
You're brushing young group.
But if he's doing that, but he's doing a whole different version.
So it would be, I agree with you.
Yeah.
That if he did kind of like a new uptemperal solution.
For example.
A girl's allowed me to random.
Yes, something like that.
With a sprinkle of pojo.
They do, they do all those covers.
They always covers.
Yeah, but everybody's covering old stuff from the 80s.
They do.
From the early early 80s.
Yeah, that's true.
Okay, but we'll play it later.
And then you tell me what you think.
I think it turned out it's good.
Yeah.
I like it.
What's that?
You?
Well, I was thinking about that.
I had a visual of that picture that you showed me with all the hair.
Yeah.
Clark.
He looks like he looks like a hippie.
He does a little bit.
Oh, not bad.
No, he's a good looking guy.
Good looking guy.
Yeah.
Hey, don't get too enthusiastic.
No.
Oh, you're not jealous.
Never.
What are we going to do in 2008, darling?
What are your dreams?
What are your wishes?
What are your desires?
I'll wave my magic wand and make them all come true.
Well, the main thing is I would like to feel great.
You know, good.
No pains.
No nothing.
No.
Because the last six months has been a little bit.
A little painful.
Yeah.
I don't want that because it's a bit too.
Nothing serious.
It's just.
No, but it's too early to get to have pains to get older and have pain.
So I really have to work at that because as long as you move and move and move,
that's the best thing you can do.
Yeah.
So I promise that to myself.
Okay.
So keep on moving.
All right.
So healthy.
Health.
Health on top.
If you don't have your health, what do you do?
I mean, you know, people don't realize that until you're sick.
Oh, I got a fuck man.
I can't do shit.
Yeah, really.
Remember when you have the flu.
No, imagine you're doing something else.
I had a couple of folds.
You know, I'm a bit of wild.
My problem.
You're too wild for the fragility of your frame.
I know.
Maybe some other people who are listening right now have the same problem as I have.
I, in my head, I don't accept that my body is a little bit older.
You know, and I do everything too fast and too wild and too.
And I'm running around and I'm running on this, you know, dude, I even have that.
What are you talking about?
And I think I'm, what am I doing?
This is not good.
So what happened a couple of times.
I was in the kitchen and the floor was wet.
And then I, you know, go around to corner.
And I fall so hard on my back.
Now normally when you're younger, you jump up and you think I'm shit.
Boiling.
No problem.
I'm probably jumping your bones up and you go, you know.
But it's not possible.
I'm broken up with the fuck.
I don't know.
Yeah.
So I probably, I don't know what happened.
But it's like, I damaged something in my backyard and anything.
But I didn't want to notice it.
I didn't want to pay any attention to it.
So that's my problem.
I think other people have their two.
I'm too young in my head.
But my, I forget about my body, you know.
The bones, especially the bones.
So in 2008, we're going to see lots of things change.
Oh, at the end of 2008, we'll have a new president in the White House.
Yeah.
What are things going to happen?
There's a lot of stuff going on in the world right now that I,
So he's, I never, well, sometimes we talk about it again.
So he's, I don't like him.
You don't like him.
I don't like his face.
Who?
For Bush.
Well, don't worry.
He has no chance of winning.
So I don't like, for you.
He's not getting in the race.
I try to like him.
I really tried.
But I can't.
Yeah, but I can't.
I have no law for him.
Yeah, but it really doesn't matter.
What has to happen now is actually something you said earlier.
And I'm not talking about the things he's doing.
I'm not talking about war.
I'm not talking.
I'm talking about his personality.
I'm talking about the person.
His aura.
Right.
From the beginning, I really tried.
I thought maybe he's going to do something or maybe he's going to, you know,
I have to say, did you see the Ellen?
Did you notice?
Yeah, where his, uh, one of his daughters was on Ellen and then called.
Oh, I didn't.
Was that good?
I have to say it was, um, fun.
It has nothing.
It really has nothing to do with it.
I'll tell you.
I want to look it up on YouTube.
But that's not her father.
What do you mean?
No.
What?
You said his daughter.
Yeah.
George Bush's daughter.
I don't know whoever it was.
It's not George.
What?
No, no.
But she, thank you.
Yeah.
Okay.
Good point.
Yeah.
She called.
She had fun story.
That's funny.
No, no.
She called him.
Okay.
Yeah.
Let me show you.
Check this out.
You got your glasses on?
Yeah.
Okay.
Watch this.
You'll see.
It was actually quite endearing.
Take a look at what happened yesterday during a taping of the Ellen DeGeneres show.
Thank you, Matt.
Could you just pick up the phone like right now and call him?
Sure.
Okay.
You're going to kill me, though.
Maybe.
Oh, did you say hi?
You think I'm allowed to do this?
Why not?
You're his daughter.
You're going to get in trouble?
At this point, Ellen is thinking, holy crap.
This is going to be so fucking cool.
This is going to be on YouTube in a minute.
I'm going to get George Bush on the phone.
Yeah.
Just hit the see if you have a downtown hit nine.
She had it all set up.
She had the phone there.
Number anything.
No, no, no.
I'm covering that.
Nobody's even looking.
I'm not even looking.
I don't want to get in trouble.
I couldn't really.
No.
I just want to say hi.
Okay.
I'm calling.
I'll call you.
Okay.
I'm going to get anything.
This way.
Give me a kill.
I'm going to be in so much trouble.
Why wouldn't they want to say hi to everybody and say hi to everybody and say hi to everybody
because it's more mean.
It's pretty funny.
Hey, Hannah.
Hi, Mom.
Hey, I'm not watching you because you're just taping right.
Yes, but what are you doing then?
I'm getting sitting here with Daddy.
Oh, hey.
I said.
I want to say hi to Daddy.
Okay.
Check it out.
Hello, President Bush.
How are you?
This is Ellen Degeneresho.
Ellen's great.
Ellen's got my little girl, too.
Oh, she's great.
She's scared.
She was going to get in trouble because I just said is it easy to just pick up the phone and call
you dad any time.
She said yes.
And I said, okay.
Well, then let's call him and she goes, oh.
And now she's scared.
She's not going to get any Christmas presents.
Dad?
Yes, baby.
Are you mad?
No, not at all.
Okay, good.
See?
Oh.
And it's okay, Ellen.
All right, look, they were showing a picture of you holding their daughters when
they were just born.
That's beautiful.
The best day of your life.
Remember, Dad?
She is so cute.
So the ending is not here.
But at the end, he says, I love you, darling.
Merry Christmas.
I have to say.
Yeah, but you know what he's saying.
Yeah.
Why are you taking off your head for me?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah, it was a little bit less.
Okay, stop.
Stop.
That was the most unprofessional thing you've ever known on the show.
I know.
Oh.
Take off your pants.
Okay.
Show it.
Hey.
But do you see how she's a bit scared of him?
Oh, yeah.
I afraid I'm not going to get any Christmas presents.
The first came out of the mouth.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, good acting then.
I would have to say.
What does Matt Lauer say?
He's scared.
Yeah.
You know, that's a good point.
She was absolutely terrified.
She thought I think it's fun, but I'm maybe my dad doesn't think it's fun.
Let's see what Matt says.
Let me see.
I didn't want her right after that.
Exactly.
Okay.
Good point.
That's a good point.
Matt said, he probably like hammered her right after that.
Yeah.
All right.
Okay.
But still.
You know.
So.
Yeah.
I mean, what I was going to say is what I agree with what you said earlier
is that we need to.
Oh, it sounds so sought off.
What?
You need to stop and smell the flowers.
You know, people got a, you got to balance yourself.
We're, as a society, we're fucked up.
We're in a, in a very.
There is a fucked up spiral.
We can't actually see what's going on around us.
I mean, you're really perceptive.
You look at that and I'm thinking, you know, how cute.
You can say, yeah, but look how terrified she was.
But we can't even see that stuff anymore.
Yeah.
Because we're so inundated with happiness and the way it's supposed to be.
So hunting success.
And you know, this is the way my parents used to talk on it when I was young.
And we just sound that old like old fox.
Really?
Did they?
Well, they didn't enjoy life.
No, but you know how old people say back in the day when I was young.
It was also different.
Isn't that exactly what we're doing?
And I know you hate that when people do that.
Yeah, it's not exactly what we're doing.
But this because you cannot think back.
There is nothing there.
You don't get it.
You don't understand anything.
I do.
What are they talking about?
You know, I do.
Yeah.
You mean.
You know.
I think anyone over the age of 30 should pretty much understand what the fuck we're talking about.
Yeah.
I should do something about it.
Because it's not going to get any better.
We have to go back to old fashion.
Enjoy.
Or geez.
Back to the, let's go back to the 60s.
Yeah.
Make love.
Let's make love.
It's not worth it.
Yeah.
I can't.
I didn't.
It doesn't work.
No.
It doesn't.
What I wanted to say is, yeah, just, you know, notice each other a little bit more.
Yeah.
You know.
Bye.
All right.
You hear it already?
It's the new version.
And it's now a pod save.
Clock Dutchless shatter dreams.
So much for your promises.
They died the day you let me go.
Cut up and wherever lies.
But it was just to lay down alone.
I thought it was you.
You said they died.
For me.
And just see you giving me.
Give them me.
Nothing but shatter dreams.
Shatter dreams.
Feel like I could run away.
Run away.
From this empty heart.
Welcome to reality.
Unfound the future.
Not so bright.
I dreamt the impossible.
The name is made.
It's good for a cow bright.
I thought it was you.
You said they died.
For me.
And just see you giving me.
Give them me.
Nothing but shatter dreams.
Shatter dreams.
Feel like I could run away.
Run away.
From this empty heart.
You know you give them me.
Nothing but shatter dreams.
Shatter dreams.
Feel like I could run away.
Run away.
From this empty heart.
I thought it was you.
Who said they died.
For me.
And just see you giving me.
Give them me.
Nothing but shatter dreams.
Shatter dreams.
Feel like I could run away.
Run away.
From this empty heart.
You know you give them me.
Give them me.
Nothing but shatter dreams.
Shatter dreams.
Feel like I could run away.
Run away.
From this empty heart.
I thought it was you.
Who said they died.
For me.
From this empty heart.
You know you give them me.
I dream the impossible.
Come on, let's dream the impossible.
Who you give them me.
Dream the impossible.
Let's dream the impossible.
I like this version.
But it was nothing wrong with the old version.
Yeah there was.
It's owned by his former record label.
Of course there's something wrong with it.
So you can't just put that on his new album without paying them.
Probably bastards.
It's still incredible so it's beautiful.
I love the woke up to reality and saw the future wasn't so bright.
It's one of a kind.
It certainly is.
I could have had some some soulful girls in the background there.
Yeah.
Just a little bit.
I know this is his sound but.
Foistills sounds.
Sound yeah it's good.
Yeah it's good.
He probably played all of most of the instruments.
We did the production or whatever.
Yeah.
It's so easy to do.
Very good.
Good.
Great song.
Clark Dashwell.
It does.
Clark Dashwell has a CD out.
What's it called?
Let's take a look at it for a second.
Clark Dashwell.
No no it's called tomorrow tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
Yes.
But that song is not on it.
No.
It was a different tomorrow on it.
But he all the lyrics.
I was reading a little bit.
He's very earthy.
Yeah definitely.
Yeah.
He wants to save the world.
That's why I like about him.
Yeah.
In his own way.
It's not going for the money.
Just great music.
Yeah.
I think I think you're right.
The record business is fucked up.
But the music business is still is pretty good.
There's a lot going on.
There's a lot of shit happening.
Yeah.
So you can buy a CD.
I think off their site.
So.
All right, baby.
So 2008.
We've gotten health.
Anything else?
Creativity.
Oh yes.
Yeah.
You need that.
Because of how everybody feels at the moment.
I think that a lot of people are very creative at the moment.
Really?
I think so.
Interesting.
Yeah.
Because of creative stuff.
Really?
Yeah.
But it's from the revolutionaries, right?
It's from the people who are rising to the top.
We're breaking through the matrix of insanity.
I think it's because of the internet.
You can feel and hear more things going on.
And people with.
Yeah.
You know, does their talents more?
Yeah, but you also got to make sure that you get out and walk the fucking
Street or do something.
I know.
That's pretty important.
No, but especially even if you just walk in.
Because this is normal here in Guilford.
We have this high street.
And there are a lot of musicians are playing there.
Yeah, that's right.
And I'm standing there.
And my mouth is open.
I mean, I'm listening to them.
And they're so gifted.
And they're so.
The great musicians.
I can't wait to take you to a central park.
I haven't seen it myself.
But David Epolito.
The guitar man from Central Park.
Oh yeah.
I'm not in the winter.
But he does a concert every Sunday.
Same thing.
Oh yeah.
Thousands of people show up.
Yeah.
He actually makes some kind of a little bit of that.
Sorry.
There's so many talented people.
And where do they go?
Yeah.
Well, that's exactly what's happening.
I mean, you don't need to have millions and millions and millions of people
going to your shows or buying records or your t-shirts or being a general fan.
You need that anymore.
Because there's no record company that's going to take away 95% of that.
97%.
No.
After recouping all the costs.
So.
I'm not going to invest in you anymore.
Well, they're not.
No.
No, they're not.
I noticed that.
Did you just burp?
Yeah.
Well, you know, I was thinking.
Let it go.
Well, you know, I burp because I was thinking about my own record balls.
This is Patricia.
You have to know that I can say things.
I can say just a word to her.
And she or a name or a name of a person.
And I start to burp.
And she will start to burp.
It comes up.
I'm throwing up in my mouth.
Arco.
I'm trying to get, I'm trying to get you to burp.
No.
Did you just say you threw up in your mouth?
It's true.
I was thinking about my own record company balls.
And I thought, oh.
It's no business there, baby.
Where there's no business.
There's nothing happening.
It's over.
And I know ideas.
And then he doesn't answer.
And then some of you comes with his ideas.
Who are not that good.
You know, anything that doesn't cost any money.
Yeah, but you know, you're on the internet all fucking day.
I mean, that's not entirely true.
But you're really good at finding stuff.
You're surfing around.
You're looking at medical information.
You're finding shit on YouTube.
You know, in fact, you're doing everything except going to podshow.com.
Your sister actually, you know, checks out shows from the world.
What did you check out?
Well, I'm listening to big bands.
You know, I was.
I know emailed you that file.
You didn't.
Stop.
Anyway, doesn't matter.
You know, these people are out there.
How many tons of people have sent you ideas and want to work with you?
But you don't, you can't.
Or you don't want to connect with them to do so.
I mean, it could be done now.
It's just not the way you're used to doing stuff.
No.
It can be done in across the world.
You don't have to be in the same spaces as a person to create to something.
You know, certainly you like making music.
No, you.
Yeah.
But I think what I like the most is working with the producer.
It's working with the producer.
Performing.
I'm not somebody that's going to sit behind my desk with a mic.
And then seeing and feels so good at the end of the day.
That's not enough for me.
I thought you really like making records.
So you like making the hoarding in the studio.
According to the studio.
But what I noticed is that I do miss some creativity on stage or something or doing something
and getting a reaction.
Panto.
You could do panto.
Nobody asked me.
You would be great for fucking panto.
I know.
We got to go.
It's too late now.
Next year, let's go watch a panto.
You would be great in a panto.
No, they're a couple here in town.
That would be perfect for you.
No.
You would be a big bit.
Look at bigans.
For those of you in America.
You have no idea what the hell we're talking about.
Yeah.
Panto is like this tradition.
And of the best actors.
It does a matter.
Well, but it's a panto mind.
Is that what they call it?
No, it's not.
But it comes from panto mind.
But it's actually there.
It's singing and speaking and.
The stories.
What is the story?
And what's the deal with the Lobsters?
Yeah.
I don't know.
We don't know.
Because we never been to one.
But they say fairy tales.
Yeah.
And it's Christmas.
And they bring sort of fairy tales.
In theatres.
Certain.
And everybody's going.
Everybody's going.
Yeah.
It doesn't matter how big you are.
And how famous they do a panto.
Yeah.
And even the guys from.
And they're coming from America.
Doing a panto.
Yeah.
Who was here?
Come on.
What's his name?
Henry Winkler.
We're doing panto and woking.
Yeah.
Woking.
I'm woking.
And it was somebody else.
Some deals.
I was doing a panto.
Woking's like.
New work.
Not a sattro.
But there are a couple of Americans.
Right.
So you can do a panto.
There's all kinds of stuff you can do.
You just got to do it.
They're going to do something creative this year.
You're going to you're going to wait for some show in Holland.
I promise to do something.
I'm thinking I have a couple of plans in my head.
And I hope to.
To do.
Just tell me what you'd really like to do.
So we've narrowed it down to performing.
So you'd like to perform.
What do you want to do?
You want to have a big band.
I think it's on the cabaret kind of a thing.
Cabaret with with jokes.
No, no.
What do you mean cabaret?
Very.
Means a band singing.
Right.
It's sort of a movie kind of Hollywood kind of atmosphere.
I'm thinking about it.
I got it.
What?
I know exactly.
I know how to fucking do this.
Next door.
Hi.
Michelle Harper.
Next door.
Who's that?
The guy who owns Harper's?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He has a nightclub.
He can take 2,000 people.
It's unbelievable.
I've never even been inside.
He had a, he gave us his car to drive home one night from the Christmas party, actually.
But think about it.
Yeah.
What an amazing show you could put on there.
And he has the dough to do it.
Maybe at the.
You could find answers.
Yeah, but halfway the year.
He maybe really make money.
Starting to have maybe a sort of a thing together.
And we could come to England or in Guildford and try it out here.
Why don't we also.
Because the arrangements you need anyway.
So you're getting your arrangements.
Why don't we, why don't we take a look at there must be a big man here in the neighborhood.
This got to be.
We got a fucking music academy here.
Are you kidding me?
This, this, what a perfect set of.
Well, if I have the arrangement, we can do it anywhere.
Yeah.
With any.
I'm going to talk.
I'm going to talk to Super Agent Keith.
No, I'm going to talk to Keith.
I'm going to talk to Keith to talk to Harper about it.
He's asking me our agent that's Agent asking me.
But if you want something, is there something.
What would you like to wish for?
Look, we'll have.
That's what Harper will pay for it.
Keith will set it up.
We'll make do a limited, a limited run.
You know, you do a couple nights with a with a great band.
You know, we'll have him get the arrangements together.
And do a great show in a real night club right next fucking door.
I mean, literally, I can drive you, drop you off,
come on, uh, uh, buy, I'll pick you up later.
You don't give us, you don't need to make money.
I didn't give a shit about that.
You just want to do it, right?
He'll make money.
It'll be fantastic.
I pay him.
No, shh.
Don't give him any ideas.
That's not good.
Cool.
And then, and Pod Show will video it.
Yeah.
And, uh, now listen to me.
This is a great idea.
So we'll, you know, we'll, we'll shoot it.
We'll do a multi-camera shoot.
And then, uh, we'll, fuck, we'll release a DVD if it's that good.
Or release put it online.
Yep.
How about that?
Great.
Are you serious?
I'm sorry.
I'm telling you he'll love it.
Yep.
He'll love it.
Okay.
Well, we have a project already.
Gosh, dang it.
Well, they, we got a project to work on.
I'm doing it.
I just got excited all of sudden.
See how easy it is folks?
That's how easy it is.
Just go, make it happen.
And you don't know what, I don't need anything.
My, my instrument is in here.
Yes.
And I will examine your instrument a little bit later.
Stop it.
Open up and say, ah, so I can look at your instrument.
Yes.
Oh, look my instrument fits in your instrument.
Stop it now.
All right, Debbie.
Thank you very much for closing out the year on the, on the, on the,
this source code.
I had fun.
It's awesome.
Yes, I am.
You're still naughty.
Yes, I try.
After all these.
Oh, shit, that's all I got left.
That, that are my enormous knob.
So combined, it's pretty good.
All the rest is just filler, all the stuff in between.
It's just dropping me up.
You know what I noticed when I was doing it.
And we're just babbling a little bit.
Yeah.
You're so much more, you're so funny.
I know you can be so funny.
And the listeners don't know that.
But in the house and you, you were thus, you know, in the family.
I don't know if I'm going to like this story.
You, you are so funny.
Without the mic.
You are so, you have it now.
When you're sitting with me, it's coming out of the mouth.
Oh, it's so, what you, I'm just talking about.
Oh, you're all by yourself.
You're always so, so serious.
And I'm listening here, you know.
Listen, you know, you know, I, you know,
that fucking door.
I don't think, what the,
I don't think it's something.
It's always so boring.
It's really, really, thank you.
That, you know, that really, that's all thanks, baby.
I just feel great now.
I'm sitting, you're asking for naked pictures.
I'm, you know, I'm not always serious.
Oh, I didn't hear that.
Why never get any.
Otherwise, you would have known about it.
No one ever sends me any fucking naked.
In fact, it's only guys calling me lightly.
It's a little concerning.
Oh, yeah, it is.
Thanks.
There's no women calling it.
I don't know if any women are listening to this show.
You're perfect.
Just middle age, guys.
Make it picture.
So, what, so, maybe I should just no longer do a show
on myself.
You can be very funny.
If I don't, if I'm not by myself,
if I have someone else, I'm always looking
to do when you have an interview with somebody.
And you always say, you're, why are not funny?
You're not trying to be funny.
Trying to ask someone's fucking questions
and get some answers.
Still, you know, just in between put some funny things,
you're so funny.
What do you, give me an example of where I was not funny?
Oh, thank you.
Well, sometimes when I see you doing interviews,
and I think, when did you see me doing interview recently?
Thank you.
Well, it was the last time.
Did you, that was the last time?
When I'm being interviewed, or when I'm interviewing.
No, no, it was a written interview.
And I thought, God, you're so serious.
Are you?
Ah, but I'm being in well.
Don't get angry now.
I'm not, I'm crushed.
Oh.
No, it's good.
It's in a compliment.
Back to the show for a second.
Fuck all the interview stuff.
I don't care about that.
I don't do interviews.
No, yeah, no, you hate it.
Yes, I do.
So, you think my show was boring?
No, I said, did I say that?
You said you said no, in fact, you said, you're so boring.
I mean, you're so serious.
You said boring.
God.
But it's serious stuff that I'm talking about.
It is, we're, who's going to say, I remember even when, when we, in the beginning,
you said, don't laugh when we have sex.
Do you remember though?
No.
Yeah, you said that.
I don't like it.
I don't like it when you're gay.
Bullshit.
I did not.
I remember.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, you're confused.
No.
No, absolutely, no.
Why would I say that?
That's not true.
No, you have to have to have everything.
You were giggling last night when I was pounding you.
Did I say stop doing that?
Did I say stop?
Did I say anything?
No.
But you can't stop me.
Right.
But I think I don't, I don't know about that.
I, that must be one of your other boys.
Sometimes it's very serious.
You know.
Yeah.
No, no.
So we're sponsored.
No, it's not the responsibility.
It's a, I want the world to continue in harmony.
Let's laugh more.
That's what I'm saying.
I'm more fun.
Have more fun.
Next year.
Send me naked pictures.
No, no, no, no.
Because it's not nothing funny about that.
No, what do you mean?
It's, how it's a nice porn.
Can people just email me porn?
It's not funny.
It is, well, that's not funny.
What other people's porn is not funny?
That's not for funny.
That's sad.
That's not for me.
Oh, okay.
I mean sad.
Whatever.
But let's, let's.
We didn't know.
Now porn is sad.
Simple.
That's very simple.
That's all it takes for guys.
I'm a bit disappointed now.
Okay.
There's more in you than that.
Yeah.
I need to, I need someone to bounce off of.
All my good shows are when someone else is on.
Yeah.
Is that so?
But, you know, there's no one around to do that.
Yeah.
Because don't I always say you're not a likable person?
Why yes, dear.
You said that many times.
Yeah.
People think that you're an asshole.
You are not.
You are very lovable, very sweet, good person.
And people should know.
I don't care if people think I'm an asshole.
Well, I do.
Because not fair.
Yeah.
It's all right.
Those who get to know me will be delighted.
You're very misunderstood.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's for sure.
You are.
Okay.
Right.
So let's change that.
Next one.
Change one.
Everything different.
New chances.
Right.
Okay.
I'm crushed.
I'm very confused now.
Stop it.
Well, now I'm insecure about my show.
Not easy.
Who am I?
I'm not judging you.
Of course not.
Except for the boring part.
Well, you know, one of the things that you've been to.
Well, you'll have to.
Then maybe don't get with you.
Okay.
Then you're going to have to come on the show more often.
To keep me funny and keep me likable.
Yeah.
Okay.
Because I'm going to make you.
That's our new goal is make.
Makeup.com.
Come on.
All right, baby.
Shall we have some dinner?
Yeah.
All right.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Another pot show pot guest.
Stick it in your ear.
Dramatically reduced ambient noise by up to 85%.
With Sony's noise canceling headphones at work.
Home or travel.
Shut out the noise and really enjoy your tracks.
Get yours at Sony.com slash headphones.
Sony headphones.
Your music never sounded so good.