This podcast is brought to you by Paancho and GoGay.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Log it with your fruit-whip log from GoDaddy.
Tells his share Charlie, five, seven, five.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this genre.
Fantastic, it's Adam Curry.
Hello!
Adam!
Baby, baby, baby, baby, baby.
I don't know who this is.
I won't hold on to your under
I never thought of you the guy in fear
Me, the guy in fear
With lover to the ashes
I don't know all the eyes
I don't know the eyes
But about the past, about the head
But maybe the light comes shining down on me
Just shining out of you
I'm not of you to make near us know
A roar of all the knowledge comes in the earth
A roar of all the things in the earth
And my life, I run so far away
I just run, I run all my life
Couldn't get away
I run so far away
We've got a hand touch your face
And there's only this and there
And from my the earth
And there's come my the earth
We've got a hand to try again
I'm holding it in a theme of life with the earth
We know life with the earth
And I run, I run so far away
I run so far away
I just run, I run all my life
And I run, I run so far away
You know that song is 25 years old?
Yeah, I believe it
Block off sea goals, I run
Picking off today is Charlie for obvious reasons
If you follow in the news at all about the UK service men and woman
Being held in Iran
But of course they meant I ran, I ran so far away
And why is it that for some reason I think
Steve Case from AOL was in flock of sea goals
I know it's just maybe it's fatigue
Hey everybody, how you doing coming to you from a very crisp northern California from the Curry condo
It is now just about 11 o'clock Monday night
So Tuesday everywhere else in the world more or less
And Thursday I think in Australia
Welcome everyone down under the tower of death
As I looked, I'm sorry
Don't have anything quite, quite adjusted the way I wanted to be
Hold on let me just, there we go
We reset some of the levels here
Sounds like we're breaking up
The tower of death to my left here that would be for you listeners to your right
It seems like another eight stories have been added since one was that last year
Two weeks ago it's unbelievable
One rink and hill tower of extravaganza
And they're still at it 11 p.m.
Still working on it, never stops
Never never ceases
Ah, so had a pretty uneventful flight on virgin upper class
As per usual
Actually slept about five hours of the ten in transit
I was pretty tired
Had to get up right in early this morning
And of course, I was busy late last night
In the attic with the lady Patricia
And then I had my serious sad light stuff to do
And I had just all kinds of stuff
Production work, you know
So I was tired, went to bed late
It was funny though on the way to the airport in the car
I had radio well the driver had put on the radio
I said put on radio four so I could just listen to people talking
And apparently when we see I have a new story about it here
I put it in my Google notebook
Here we go
I want to read a verbatim
I don't want to get it wrong
I was unbelievable
It was like I was in the virgin car service
On my way for a virgin flight
And on the BBC
Comes a report that an airline pilot has been arrested
On suspicion of being above the alcohol limit
On board a plane due to flight to New York
Ah
He was a virgin Atlantic pilot
Okay, okay, that may be feel really good there
Anyway, so a good flight as I expected
And I did have one meeting today
At four on the afternoon at the office
So is in the condo around three went to the office
I'll tell you more about the meeting that I had and why I had it
And of course I'm pretty tired as you can imagine
Even though I'd asleep a couple hours
And I want to go to bed desperately
And I didn't have a lot of things to say
Because you know what I'm going to tell you
I've been on an airplane for 10 hours
Luckily you guys have come through with all kinds of wacky shit you've sent me
Hey Adam, how's it going?
This is uh
Well, I'm not going to tell you who this is
Oh, yeah, no, no, no, no, here I-
This is a Charlie listener
That's right, I'm a DSE listener
I'm actually a podcaster
But I'm not going to disclose my name or my podcast
Only because I know you've been talking about how you would
I'd rather would listen to
Listeners rather than podcasters
Even though I got to tell you I've just reached episode
Number 20 in my own episode
And I was so excited that I wasn't going to give you a call to let you know
That thanks to you
I did my 20th episode
Yes, I saved thanks to you because I started to listen to you for a set
For a while now, a couple of years, maybe a year, a couple of months
And when I first started listening to you, you were promoting
Hey, if you got something to say, you should do your own podcast
And guess what I did
And now that seems like
You've not taken
Uh, liking too much for other podcasts
But anyways, I still continue to be a
Listener
So anyways, I just wanted to chime in
Say hello, hey, you know what?
I want to contribute on a regular basis
So I'll probably be sending you some more of these
MP3 files so that you can play on your show
But for now, I will just go back to recording my show
For my one listener
Me
Yeah, I guess I'm just practicing social masturbation
Yes
All right
I'll talk to you later, Adam, bye
I truly am the Sultan of the Savans
Okay, I've got a new one, the anonymous podcast listener
Welcome to the family, my friend
Uh, got a nice press release here, Richard Brewer, hey, from
Podjo, it's Hugh, sent this to me. Scott Sigler's ancestor
Sky Rockets, the top 10 of Amazon's bestseller list
On first day of release
This was Scott's personal bum rush
The charts, he's been bum rush
Well, he on April 1st, he bum rush the Amazon book charts
Podjo presents the world's most popular podcast
novel as it opens at number one on Amazon's horror
And sci-fi lists, cool
Oh, man
Check this out, I didn't know this
Uh, Sigler
Sigler's fans have now downloaded more than 3.2 million episodes
Of his podcast novels, landing him a print publishing deal
With Dragon Moon Press
Awesome
Congratulations Scott, that's very cool, dude
I mean, it's like, it's almost like
We knew it was gonna happen
And what did he, he was, let me see what the numbers are
Top the charts, Amazon's number one in sci-fi horror
And genre fiction lists
The genre fiction lists
And sister held the number set number seven spot
And Amazon's bestseller list
Number seven, I'm fucking believable
Following only Harry Potter
And the deadly hallows in fiction
That's fantastic
Oh man, so cool
Let me just see what else
I've got, I've got all kinds of, all kinds of stuff
This is a really nice one that I read just before I left
This morning
From Thomas Hoffman
Hey Adam, just want to thank you
Thank you for saving my sanity
I'm an American expat teaching in China
In a city that has virtually no English-speaking community
Except for college students who dabble in the language
Oh
What city is it, man?
I discovered the DSC when I loaded up my iPod
For the ridiculously long international flight to get here
I love your style
You save me from the watered down
Politically correct English TV station here in China
Yes, there's only one English TV station for the entire country
Dude
No satellite, can't you get anything on satellite there?
Must must be able to
And if you got broadband
There's always juiced
I don't hear much about juiced anymore
I grabbed the DSC every day
Listen to it religiously to remind myself
That whitty English sounds like
Your entertaining is hell
He both the great work Thomas
Thanks, dude
I'd love to know more about what you're doing over there
It sounds fascinating
And of course, big news today
Hey Adam, how are you doing
I'm from SLV podcast
Just so I would give you a good bell
Because I've just seen on the on the TV
All of the news that I've probably seen
So if anybody else has probably seen this
But yeah, my doing a deal with Apple
To get rid of the DRM on some of their tracks
It's not all of their tracks
I'm telling you now, mate
The revolution
I want the revolution has stopped
Bring it on
Note to self
When saying something prolific like
The revolution has started
Note to self not to stumble over words
Yeah, this is very cool
I'm actually I'm not sure how much difference
It's going to make for EMI
I mean you'll see
Mark my words
We've been yelling and screaming about DRM
And get it off
And I don't think it's going to make any difference
In their sales
They still only have so many artists they can promote
And it's much better for us
I love it, you know
By something I can easily put it on any device
I want that's obviously fantastic
And of course we're getting higher resolution
It's about time
And I really mean that
So what's it going to be
325 kilobit sample rate I believe
Of course it'll be in the AAC format
Which although an open format I guess you still have to
Transcoded to MP3 if you really wanted to go on all devices
So I think most devices these days will play AACs
But just not the enhanced version
Or maybe some of them will do the enhanced version
Sorry
So a buck 29 is that what it is
For a high grade version high grade copy
Or high resolution if they're calling it
And so the 99 sense stuff will be just crab
And it'll be low resolution
Which it's always been 128 kilobit sample rate I think
So that is pretty it is
I mean you have no idea how much we're missing really
And the entire generation of kids growing up listening to
Inferior sound quality
Yeah
So we'll see what that goes
Keep my eye on for sure
Oh my goodness
Yes
Yes it made a appearance quite a while
Heat up everybody
For satellite repair man coming after you
For satellite repair man
What's he gonna do?
He'll fix your misconceptions and answer questions too
Nothing in the universe
And he can't do for you
For satellite repair man
Yeah
I want to
Hey Adam PW
And with all due respect to the originator of this expression
You
I apologize for being among the silent on the issue of how to solve the kitchen TV problem
What I would have recommended was exactly what you did
But hey you're a folder
It was interesting to hear you talk about the delay though
I have a similar situation here in my home
The fancy digital HD home theater setup is very close to the master bedroom
I just need to set some of this up
Heat up is referring to the sling box that I hooked up for Patricia
So she can watch the television in the kitchen
On her iMac
Therefore removing
When negating the need for the television that was next to the iMac
Which of course
Makes sense to only have one monitor in there
By the way, I tried to access my sling box
I guess I thought I had it all set up probably
I guess the NAT or whatever the firewall and the router is blocking it
So I can't watch it unfortunately
Anyway, so that's what Peter was going to suggest trying the sling box as well
And I guess he has the story of his own
And the TV in the bedroom is just an analog connection
And the result is about a four second delay between the bedroom and the HD setup
But the real result is that whenever Ros goes to bed before me she demands
That I switched from my beautiful HD signal to the low Res analog version
Because she kids they're hearing the delayed audio coming from the other room
That's where she talks
You're going to get your ass kicked if she hears that
I know man, all wives sound like that at one point or another
Hey, if you had a collar on Friday that claimed not to like the Folger's coffees he sampled,
the members of the Fenton Household are coffee freaks. We grind our own beans and we make our coffee
strong. We love coffee. So when I ordered my free coffee sample from Folger's, I picked out the
Colombian blend that I figured would be the closest to my favorite style of coffee.
When it came in the mail, I stuck it in the cabinet so I could try it at some other time without forcing
Roz to try it at the same time. When I went to look for it one day, it wasn't there.
So later in the evening, I said to Roz, do you know what happened to that coffee sample I got in the
mail? And she says, yeah, we drank at this morning. So I guess I liked it every bit as much as my
more expensive whole beans. You mean, you went, we drank it this morning. So I may have to switch from being
a grinder to being a Folger. Sorry, I couldn't resist. Later Adam and oh, Tricia, please do more
shows. I'd get into it deeper, but you are after all the boss's wife. You'll
well, Pida one things for sure. She will not hear your plea. I think that's pretty clear.
Yeah, I got a couple of responses. I love this when when people push back on the sponsors,
the show, and of course, Folger has been sponsoring a large part of the network for a while.
I think actually their sponsorship ended. It doesn't matter because the conversation is interesting.
So I got an email saying, the guy hated the coffee. He couldn't even finish one cup, and that
did elicit some response. Hi, Adam. This is Tim Stanton from Stanton Coffee and Indianapolis.
We are coffee roasters. I'd like to comment to regard why your caller David Peterson
probably did not enjoy his Folger's sample of coffee. Part of the education behind it is coffee
technically goes stale after about 14 days of roasting it. So anything that is pre-grounded in a
sample pack is most likely stale. Part of the reason that he enjoys the experience of grinding,
releasing that aroma, probably no matter what type of coffee it whether it's a regular roaster
or french roast as he alluded to. He's going to have a much better experience.
What we have done ourselves is to educate the people in the independent coffee industry because of
the influence of corporate coffee like Starbucks and other chains. We try to help them on a daily basis
make their coffee taste better. And we'd like to say thank you, Adam, once again, for actually
helping us develop the independent coffee.org website. And as part of that, you know, like I said,
all part of you and Pods show. We have started producing podcasts. So thank you again, Adam,
keep up the great work. Love your show. Oh, you confused me there for a second. I was like,
I don't did a help out with that website. I can't remember that. But you're podcasting too. Okay,
and that's cool. I'll go check that out. More response to Folger. Yeah, it's Bard and Oklahoma
City. How's it going? Just want to say a quick thank you because yesterday I received in the mail
free of charge my Folger's gourmet selection. And Folger's hooked me up with a little package called
lively Colombian medium roast. So I thought I'd check it out together with you here. Hold on.
Oh, it's a sound seeing tour. Oh, this is quite nice, guys. This is this is pretty good.
lively Colombian medium roast. It's probably fantastic also because it has a little bit of
splendid in it. Yeah, it's great. Thanks, Adam. Thank you, Folger's. Thank you, Splenda.
It's a double shot. I love it. Thank you. Let me let me see one of the, uh, I think it just ended
their sponsorship. They, uh, they, they up to twice, I think. Uh, let me see. Yeah,
oh, here we go. A message from Matt at Pods show HQ. I appreciate all of your hard work during
the Folger's campaign. Just want to send a reminder. Campaign, uh, end date is 331. When you have
the opportunity, please send along your fun reporting for the campaign. Oh, okay. I, it doesn't matter.
I still like the coffee. And if you do, let me know. It's a really cool, you, and Splenda's
ended as well. Holy crap. Okay, Tylenol PM still sponsoring to show excellent and more to come.
You know, Sandy Shaw wrote about me. Do you remember Sandy Shaw? She's the, uh,
how are the original, um, Brit chicks from the 60s? And she had a huge hit with puppet on a string
and turns out she's always really controlled her entire career and just went pod safe with the
new version of puppet on a string. Pop, it's got a brand new string, which I think is very funny.
And so she wrote about, uh, about me playing her song on, uh, on the Charlie and, uh, about pod casting.
And, um, I guess I didn't read the entire site, but, uh, she wrote about some other things that are
very cool to me. I had a list of very advanced licks from the after-and-sovers of, sorry,
known as Rodgey. Um, I was supposed to link to the Sandy Shaw website and we're, uh,
asking me through the details of the biography. I'm pretty sure that you haven't spotted this,
or I'm sure you can mention it. It says in 2003, how has been so many past this climate attack?
And they bought us the first plane of Rodgey's, uh, when he allowed for Lima Lima,
Yankietta, um, they bought it to fly around the UK. And it says in 2005, uh,
certainly buys a second plane of Trinidad and the next part to fly around Europe.
Anyway, I thought you'd appreciate the show recently, like, flag noise. I was, uh, given the
she's a grandmother, would that make her a gill? Anyone, hold on.
Considering she's a grandmother, does that make her a gill? I don't, that's sick, man.
Nah, I put her squarely in the milk category still. Gill.
It is cool. They have a Trinidad. That's a serious airplane. I don't know if it's the 10 or the 20.
But that's like a 235 knots, a 25,000 feet. That's a, that's a nice aircraft. Wow.
We'll have to find out what the, um, what the call sign is and find out where she, where she keeps it.
I can, we can do a flying with Sandy Shaw.
Hey, it's taken, uh, I don't know about, uh, a year to get the show on the air. But finally,
it's going to happen. No, it, it's, it's already dropped. Uh, it's already started.
Our first game show.
You know, I was thinking, I'm pretty good at trivia. Oh, yes, as who says me?
I know I can book your asshole, man. Yeah, maybe if I don't take my meds.
You think you could take me on? I think those cold northeast winters of frozen your brain.
If you think it can beat me. All right, Grandpa, you're on.
But it's grandpa now. When I'm done with you, it'll give a whole new meaning to the term Boston
Massacre. Oh, yeah. There's only one way to settle this.
Bone.podshow.com. See you there, April 1st, and you better bring a hand key to life away your
tears. You better bring a diaper, baby. I should have saved an extra diaper.
Oh, yeah.
Bone.podshow.com. Yeah, we've been working on this show.
It's swear to God. It feels like a year almost. Maybe it's been half a year. At least six months.
And all kinds of reasons why we didn't, we didn't get it on the air. And, uh, you know, we did a number
of pilots and, uh, internal didn't even publish them. Uh, we're happy with some.
hated some others. And, uh, I think we've got, uh, we think we've got a pretty interesting formula.
And, uh, there are actual prizes to be won. And so the first SmackDown is between the
Uber podcasters, CC Chapman and P.W. Fenton. Better known as the Satellite Repairman.
Yo, Adam. Yo. Trucker Tom here. I was listening to your latest podcast and, uh, you said
something about a 24 hour a day, seven day week, uh, podshow video channel, which I think is actually
quite an excellent idea. Uh, I've got a suggestion that would go right along with it. Uh, why not
set it up so that people can chat about what's playing, uh, in the, in the, in the, in the channel,
what's playing, what's happening, what's happening and streaming right now in the channel.
I think that would be, uh, sort of an added attraction to get people to come to the website.
So that's my suggestion, uh, hope your family's doing great. You can find me, of course,
at Trucker Tom podcast.com. Catch you later. No, Trucker Tom, you're going to be a part of it, my
friend for sure. Yeah, sometimes, at some point last year, I came up with a very simple idea and I,
I wrote up a business plan and, uh, kind of a concept for something called the plus.
And the plus, uh, really was a throwback to, um, or is a throwback to my radio days and my
knowledge of programming a radio station and an MTV as well. My television work. What I really
wanted is I, I want to have, um, a nonstop 24 hour a day video channel. So let's just call that a
stream, which, uh, well, I mean, we're starting out really, really small, uh, just one stream, but,
something that I wouldn't intend to go to multiple time zone streams later on just because it
makes so much more sense because I really want to program videos. Um, and these can be music videos,
but there's also an entire universe of single shot hilarious, uh, awesome, amazing viral videos.
And, um, and so part of the plan was, uh, a methodology, uh, to acquire these videos. So they
basically, um, acquiring the rights to put them into rotation, which just about everybody wants to do
because they, everyone just wants to grow an audience. Um, but the hardest part really is automating
this because I know how MTV, um, used to put their signal together, if you will, they had guys
literally sitting 24 hours a day at something called the NOC, which was the network operations center,
the uplink and Babylon, New York. Of course, we know what an NOC is today, but it has a different
type of meaning. And they would literally play one clip after another and then insert the promos,
the, um, you know, all the wacky little animations, um, top of the hours, the commercials, the
VJ segments, all on a schedule. And, uh, that's one part that's hard, but imagine actually programming
that. See, with most television, it's like, okay, so we're going to have it's our prime time
hour. So from 8 to 830, we'll have, um, I don't know, CSI. Oh, that's actually from 8 to 9 and then from 9 to 930,
we'll have everybody loves Raymond. You know, it's not all that hard when you're dealing with
half hours and only a very limited amount of time that we're really counts. If you want to do 24 hours
a day and you want to have, see, I think, um, and some of our samples, we've done 71 elements
individual elements in one hour. Um, and this has to remain fresh. So stuff has to rotate. Well,
there, you know, there's a methodology for doing that in radio. Um, and they're software,
but there was really no one has ever put all those pieces together for television and specifically
for the web. Uh, so we've been doing that. And Vincent is team of, uh, been putting together
the technology. That's why that was the meeting I had today at four o'clock to see this thing. It was
absolutely amazing where, you know, we just a couple of mouse clicks and it put together a full hour
of programming and, uh, the minute we put it together, it was streaming it out, uh, transitions,
titles, everything. It's, it's amazing. Um, I'm just, it was like, wow, this is kind of what I
dreamed of. It's not perfect yet. There's, you know, there's all kinds of stuff yet to be done with,
with the transitions, et cetera. Um, but I think within a couple of weeks, um, I'll take about
a week to fix some of the, the bugs that we identified today. So let's call that two weeks then.
Yeah, maybe two, three weeks and we'll have it up and running. Oh, man. It's going to be so incredibly
exciting. Let's see what we have 29 minutes. Uh, I got a little more juice left in me.
You know, I mean, SOS, Sultan of the Savans.
Programmer here again from San Francisco. Well, thank you for playing me comment on DSC 573 on
Puber Friday. Had some thoughts on the SMS controversy on the DSC at the moment. Oh, yes. Oh,
yes, prolific programmer. Those words are flowing out and it's controversy. Thank you very much.
It varies by provider. How much is charged when you receive or send? And I had a provider called
SOSCOM before. And they depend on pre-paid or when you're in contract.
My, um, this WISCOM service I had was called not-tell easy pre-paid. It was a pre-paid service.
Wait a minute, man. I got to write all this down. You give me so much information, prolific
programmer. I'm still trying to figure out that you were all you sent me at the other day.
Uh, that just really should be a recurring thing. I lied for a worldwide roaming. No call. No
cost receiving either calls or text messages. Um, it was great. Unfortunately, it was this continued
a few years ago. Since then, I've been getting local sims wherever I go and because for the
reasons you've stated, I know I couldn't really have a Spanish sim, a UK sim. Hey, uh, what
is talking about is a sim card. Um, and yeah, but that's not really the solution. I want people to
just have one number to reach me on. Uh, and, and, and you just can't do it. There is no global
global plan that is just within any reason. You know, if, if you're not paying for your incoming
calls and your text messages, then you're paying, uh, it was a pound per gig, no per megabyte of
data transfers. It's just ripped off. I mean, I don't know. I'm sure it's in settlement somewhere.
You know, if I'm using vote of phone in the UK, they're probably ripping off singular here in the
US. I mean, it just gets passed along to me. Uh, Argentine sim, wherever I go, I get them because I
ain't saying touch because as you noted, the call calling calling from a broad and receiving calls
abroad is very expensive. There is a solution I, I sort of discovered by accident. I have a service
called bonded at home, and you can essentially take your modem, you see, voice over IP service.
You can take your modem along with you when you travel. And thereby, you can receive calls from
people, say, if someone's a call you, Patricia or Christina, they can call you on a UK number
and get you wherever you are. That's all kids. Yeah, I know that. You know what? Actually,
I set the girls up with Jaja. I've talked about them before, I think.
J, A, H, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J,
except they pronounce a Jaja, but at home, we say, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, J, and they have a very
interesting system where on a web page, which, of course, is convenient, as you know, the lady
Patricia has her eye mac and the kitchen and little phone book, it's all all our calls or
all our favorite numbers are all filled out. And she just clicks on whoever she wants to call
and then either her mobile or cell phone or the, the home phone will ring, it will display the
number that she's calling. So the caller ID is actually passed through, you pick up and then it says
one moment, Jaja is connecting you. Excuse me, I don't know. And then you hear it ringing and then the
other party sees your number up here, the caller ID works there as well. They pick up, you connect
and you're paying virtually the same rates as Skype or Gizmo or any of these other.
In fact, they sometimes can even get a better rate because I guess they have some kind of
switching technotechnology and they can get the cheapest minutes for you and it works. I mean,
I load this thing up for Patricia, Patricia calls her mom and her sister every single day.
Many, many times a day. And I think our phone bill when we first moved to the UK was
easily 900 pounds in a month. And that's when I got really interested in voice over IP, believe
me. That's just, that's just obscene. That's 1800 bucks. And now it's like I loaded up 50 bucks.
I don't hear, I don't hear anything from them for two, three months. It's just amazing.
Hello, I was TJ for a user. I had to just stop listening and call. I was listening to a
horrific program, but shouting out is URL. We should make them an item for a very fixed program
or a scripting web pages. Anyway, I didn't know if you saw the comments on your blog post,
but even I got myself an NH under thanks to you. So we do definitely get yourself a no-check on
All right, that's it. I'm a traffic on Brussels, so just going to be sure very good. We can't
cheers, bye. No, man. I don't need a contract for everything. I just like their shit.
That's for sure. Hey, let me see. Oh, man, did I forget to load that one up? No, I didn't
luckily. Well, let's have a word with the nylon spread and the news with the smile on where
the wrong old right window for light. Let's listen world around to the nylon. Hey Adam, it's the
New Yorker in London for nylon. Wow, the 15 soldiers. Let me first say, you know, I, I wish
their families, all my prayers. And I hope we get these guys and lady back. I think the US should
be blockcating Iranian ports disrupting the oil supply. Of course, that was shooted up to $100
a barrel and they're come to the bio diesel industry. So I am not condoning this at all, but there
is one question that I think has the BS, which I think is being asked in the US, not here. Why
didn't those guys defend themselves? Now, before someone jumps in me, that quote is from Lieutenant
Commander Horner, who is the executive officer of the USS Underwood, which is the American
frigate that works at the HNS Cornwall. Why did the Cornwall command to send two boats out
with no backup in highly contestant waters? But if they did get in trouble, there was no way to
support them. Why didn't they provoke a hold off? Stand off waiting for American air planes to arrive,
surround them, create some sort of standoff but stop them from being taken hostage. So I think
the loser engagement has to be questioned. I think the Commander on the Cornwall really has
to answer as to why he sent two boats out, people lightly on and ribs, rapid inflatable boats,
and no backup possible is something that go pear-shaped as they say here. Nothing about 15
sailors, but I think the US implies, you know, the macho thing, that they would not have been taking
hostage. But I think there is a question to be asked about was there no way to
at least a Volca standoff and why they were sent to board about with no possibility of being
backed up. Finally, I'll let you know. I'm a closet scruncher with folder tendencies.
Cheers. Yeah, it doesn't surprise me. The nylon ladies and gentlemen,
as part of our stable of savants, nylon, I'm a little disappointed by your take on all this.
First of all, I believe I think I heard a snippet of news somewhere that
was there an apology, which is really what Iran is asking for it? I'm disappointed in nylon,
is that you didn't cite the history between the UK and Iran, or actually it's a Persia,
because the brits have been in that region since 1902 or 1903, I think in 1908,
and they've been displacing governments and shas and putting people in place because of BP,
of course, British petroleum, which may at one point have even been British Persian petroleum.
I can't quite remember where the name came from. Maybe it was always just British petroleum,
but they had a Persian partner and then at one point the government wanted, or the shy,
I think wanted to nationalize all of it, all of Iran's oil, and then whoops, he was gone,
then all of a sudden his son was put in his place. So there's definitely been a bad
vibe between the United Kingdom, or Britain, I should say, and Iran. So this shit has been going on
for a long time, and it's like, what were they doing? Well, we all know what they were doing.
You know, they're spying, checking stuff out, showing that they're there, of course.
So, uh, wouldn't mind hearing your thoughts on that there, uh, nylon.
Alright, I gotta go to bed, so I'm gonna play one more song for you. I can't remember who recommended
this to me, but I do like it. Cocony, and it's, uh, well, where are we?
There we go. Get your light up.
It's overrated, scholarship, you've earned it. That's the way, yeah, that's the way.
What is when you got it and gone and made it? You're for a certain amount of troubles and
stay in the deal for that you try to send it. That's the way, yeah, that's the way, yeah.
What is going on in the right way? You're for a certain amount of troubles and stay in the
deal for that you try to send it. That's the way, yeah, that's the way.
You're for a certain amount of troubles and stay in the deal for that you try to send it.
I also ignore, yeah, whether I, I'll smash it and you break it. That's the way, that's the way.
What is going on in the right way? You're for a certain amount of troubles and stay in the
deal for that you try to send it. You're for a certain amount of troubles and stay in the deal for that you try to send it.
You're for a certain amount of troubles and stay in the deal for that you try to send it. That's the way, yeah, that's the way.
What is going on in the right way? You're for a certain amount of troubles and stay in the deal for that you try to send it.
If you're a geek, you'll appreciate this.
I recommend that to me. I went into my Google notebook where I keep all of my show prep for the show.
Just entered Kokoni and it popped up with an entry and a link to an email which of course is in Gmail. Open it up and there it is from Aaron Cooper.
Subject not your official musicologist. Dude, here's the deal from the United Kingdom with influence, such as any Lennox to rhythmic Cindy Lauper.
Lannos Morris, Seth Savage, Garden, Chili Pepper, Seal, Bonnie, Rate, Chris Isaac, Sarah McLaughlin, Tracy Chapman, Amy Grant, Foren on Blons, Peggy Lee and Nancy Sinatra.
How about about about about about about about? He actually recommended it for a football Friday.
Interesting. I kind of like that one. Kokoni gets your light up.
Wrap it up daily source code for today.
So as always, it's dailysourcecode.com, Adam at podshow.com, and it'll be an interesting week.
I'm going to be here all week. I'll be here all week, everybody.
And I believe Monday and Tuesday and Los Angeles. So I hope you stick around for the ride. Take care.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds and content delivery podshow in Lennox.