You know, Adam, you may say that the DSC 600 is no big milestone, it's just another
hundred shows, just another show.
But something about the double zeroes on the end of the show number has to at least make
you a little reflective about all the great quality times on the show.
Pump that, that's like that bad boy up and down.
You pump it, you pump it, you pump it, you pump it, and then all of a sudden it becomes
frothy or the openness that the show gives.
That's so sad.
Anyone can suck off my pipe any time or just the fine production that can inspire us all.
Yeah, I was wondering if you can always understand, because sometimes it sounds a little
rough, but anyway, as far as I know, I'm in pocket, we're going to finalize plans.
I think I just might go, I don't know if I should go next week because next week is kind
of like, you know, I'm just not sure, I have half of mine, I have no idea why I said
that.
I'm spacing out a little bit today and all of a sudden that sounds like a really good
idea.
I'm an exciting idea.
And the only people who make out are the artists, awesome, I'm sorry.
I think it, um, okay, so we should probably, all right, I got to think about this.
You already here, I'm getting diarrhea of the mouth.
Well, Adam, keep up the diarrhea of the mouth for another thousand episodes, but congrats
on DSC 600.
Oh, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby
baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby. baby, baby baby, baby, baby baby, baby baby, baby, baby baby, baby baby, baby baby, baby baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby baby baby, baby baby baby,
I know, I know you miss all the sun
Wherever it is, what will you remember?
You should fall short of your shine
Remember life holds me one guarantee
You always have made
And if you should miss my love
One of these old days
If you should never miss the arms
And if the whole is so close
All the lens that used to touch your so tender
Just remember
What I told you the day I set you free
Keep me, keep me from you
That's right baby
Ain't no mountain high enough
Ain't no river wide enough
Ain't no bandwidth in enough
To keep me from you
Daily source code episode number 600
I didn't want to make any big deal out of it
But you guys have sent in an array of stuff that I feel obliged to play
And kick it off today with a mashup from DJBC
Ain't no misty mountain
That's a mashup of diner awesome
Ain't no mountain high enough
Ain't no thank you from Led Zeppelin
I've been following the whole mashup culture for several years now
And I've been looking at all the jurisprudence
Et cetera
And I just got to say you can't sell them
You can't put them on the pod save music now
But damn I love the mashups
I think they've just got to be okay for the Charlie
So just a little way of celebrating today
Dad, did you want some introduction for the Daily source code?
Yes, I did
Did you do number 400?
These things
I don't know
Well, what you do?
Number 600
I don't know, let's find out
Don't just hear away
Charlie
This is the Daily source code
Number 600
Wow, that sounded good
Yeah, I liked it
Our green thing from New York
Thank you so much, my friend
Hey, whether it's shitty today
And it's been crapped throughout the entire weekend
Which is a major bummer
Because this weekend
And I was tired, man
We had a long week, a lot of stuff
And London, a lot of moving back
And forth amongst the masses
You know, commuting can make your tired
Of course, it did give me a fantastic opportunity
to catch up on a couple shows
I just hadn't had time to listen to yet
But my big plan this weekend
And now that I've done that
Severe wind shear channel crossing
It's like I want to go
Cross the channel, go to Antwerp, go see the wind commander
I also borrowed one of his heads
Can you believe that I have this
You know, we use these Dave Clark headsets in aviation
In general, of course, there's lots of
You know, there's bows
And you know, all the major manufacturers have a headset
But you know, it's the Dave Clark
You got to have the green headset
You know, that's what proper airmen we use
And I had one that was only, I don't know
Year and a half old
And I thought that there was something wrong with the avionics
After the annual inspection that they had
Tweeted knob, left or right the wrong way
It sounded over modulated, sounded like crap
And I was actually having a little tough time
Hearing the ATC controllers
Turns out my headphone had been blown up
I don't know that happened
I know I'd like to keep him loud
But it burst so I borrowed the wind commander's headset
And of course he wants it back
So I figured, what better excuse
Than to go flying than to bring the headset back
So it was crap crap, crap weather
I would have not been fun at the end of the day
Of course, doable, but we would have had the same similar situation
To the severe wind cheer from past week
So I wasn't really looking forward to it
And so what does every pilot do
On a day when the weather shitty
You can't fly, you are all ready to go
Of course, we go visit the pilot shop
Let me tell you, I bought some goodies
I treated myself
Kind of an advance of episode number 600
I got a life raft
I've always wanted one
And I finally saw one that only weighs 12 kilos
The problem of course with these things is
They take up room and weight
And normally they're twice the weight
So this is great for the lady Patricia
Because I know last more than a minute and a half
If we have to ditch in the North Sea
So we'll have a nice little four person buoyancy raft
I bought a new life jacket for myself
A really spiffy one with it's really thin
And it's not yellow on the outside
Only when you deploy it so it doesn't look like a dick walking around in it
And it's just much less in the way of the flying
I got myself a transceiver
With VOR navigation capability
I know I needed one of those
Because if you have an electrical failure, you can't communicate with the ground
And by the way
It's really small, it's in the north of the icon
I'm considering
Being really bad
And taking this with me on my next flight
To the states
Kind of put it in my bag
I got a lot of electronic shit in my bag anyway
So I could probably get it through the
Get it through the scanner
And then I have an adapter so I can plug my headphones into it
I could just follow the entire flight
Follow the whole cockpit
If I get on frequency at the right time in the beginning
Of course you got to get on the ground frequency
To hear all the frequencies there being relay
To your flight otherwise you lose it
And then you can't
To track the frequency that they're supposed to be on
I was thinking of doing that
Also but the coolest thing I got
It's relatively new
You have electronic knee pads in aviation
So instead of carrying
Well you're still going to carry your maps
But your maps, your approach plates
Your frequency listings
It's all inside this nice moving map
It's got to be 20 centimeters on length
I think 18 centimeters probably
You strap it to your knee
It can even you can even tie it into the auto pilot
It has a approach mode
I mean just a fantastic, fantastic navigational aid
Which you could also see is
The fucking toy
At a good time with it
Inside the fucking view
Hey Adam, this is Tom from the fog view podcast
And last Friday when I introduced the carry cutting him song
I must have been having a football Friday because I messed up
And I attributed this theme song to the great Greg Smith
When you know I meant the great Jeff Smith
I'm sorry Jeff
But you can check his workout at
TheJefSmith.com
That's the GEOFFSmith.com
Also Adam, congratulations on show number 600
Thank you my friend.
Take care. Thanks.
Yeah, I caught that actually, but for some reason
I guess it was a whole song after it
And I just forgot to go back and correct you on that
Because that was kind of weird.
You got a jingle by the famous Jeff Smith
And still I deed him as the famous Greg Smith
Something different to sure
You got all Jeff's back.
You upload another song to the pop safe music network
I can identify
If this geek rule the world
Attitude last night
I was the king in second life
I was the master of as far as I could see
And as I looked around the place
I saw the look on my own face
Staring through my 24-inch screen
I thought I'd like to run the whole world
From my desktop
Be the head of time show and quit my major job
If this geek rule the world
Attitude last night
I thought I'd like to run the whole world
I thought I'd like to run
Attitude last night
It's been a year, like 24,000 friends
Oh my space, probably gonna never get
Lookin' my face to another crazy little thing
You thought I'd never do it
Keep messaging to do the bit but you're full
You wanna follow my Twitter, oh no
Got in my P.I.S. but no, I know
You'll be answer for head, miss what I said
Could true up to leak your dead
Sneak it through the back, no
I'm gonna get more ram on the man
Had it like I'm on the floor, snap
Took a video video, put it up on YouTube, dig it over
Put a P.H.P.S, forget it, go, little time bomb
Mother, what a school, nothing coming up
Push up, pull, hey, let's party
Bad hard guys, pull
The more I think about being king of the castle
The more it sounds dumb
Had a whole lot of hassle
I'd drop me and make a mess
And watch it all go down
Another bubble purse before it hits the ground
If this key cruel the world
I get my instant message hurt
By everyone who shot the bird
And call me crazy
This key cruel the world
I finally get myself a girl
And get a life and move out of my brother's basement
Oh no, if this key cruel the world
I'd screw it up and later
Don't need to know
I never do it, not again
This key cruel the world
You think I ever get a girl
Get a life and move right back
In my brother's basement
Oh no, if I'm on the ground
Oh no
Taking it on this afternoon
Just about to board a flight to Kuwait
Just wanted to wish you congratulations on
So 600 and so what you want to get back
So I'm going to call you on and take care
Cheers, bye bye
Need to unwind?
Will then come check out my weekly podcast
Unwind
Fan GB
Featuring pot-sake music network artists
And a mellow mix of sweet pop
A acoustic rock
And smooth jazz
That's guaranteed to melt away
The stress of your day
More chill than the chill cast
I present the very best and latest
Easiness name tracks
With a variety of male and female vocalists
As well as instrumentals
To keep your ears perked up
Even as you're winding down
Plus, I bring to you special artists
Spotlights
Interviewing independent artists
Such as Matthew Ebel
And Rebecca Haveland
Giving you a behind-the-scenes look
At the folks who make them music
Take some time to unwind
With Angie B
Every Tuesday at unwind.pot-show.com
Unwind from Angie B
Sponsored by Tylenol PM
Also sponsor of this fine program
The Daily Source
Go to episode number 600
I got to tell you I do subscribe to unwind
And it's on those train rides
To shortage
And back when I listen to shows
Like that
And sometimes listen to it on the plane
And I'm just like
I just fall asleep
But it's great
Listening to the solstery
Dulse at Tones of Angie B
And let me see
Coming up this week
Now Saturday
I'm going to be traveling to New York
Sunday traveling to Austin
For the big eye media conference
Which is basically a conference of
Advertisers and particularly buyers of advertising
So you can understand the importance of that
Some things never change
Let me tell you when it comes to sales
You still got to do the hand job
And I have no problem with that
So before that
Now we do have some advanced lined up for this week
I also intend to find a day
It's probably going to be Thursday
Perhaps even Friday
When I will do the Antwerp trip
According to that one
Both to Antwerp and back
And of course I'll cut that down to size
And we'll have a trip together
I'll just talk about what the fuck I'm doing
Hopefully
Just like if I were flying with someone else
It'll be you
And me
And a couple hundred thousand of our best friends
And I also have a feeling that we'll be talking to
Some other savants in the area of mobile phones
After you hear this comment
Hi Adam
It's Sam here from London
You tell me
I usually only phone you to men
I'm stoned to breaks like them
I'll receive right here
Okay
I had no idea what you just said
But you're calling, I appreciate it
Hey
I won't be advised to do any of your servants
I'm offended mine
Finally last week
On early on Thursday morning
To recount a bit of a horrifying story
She was working at 23 am
When you're seeing your bang
And a bedroom which sort of the concrete smoke
So the first thing she wanted to do was call the fire brigade
So she went to pick up her phone
But her phone was in two bits
And the battery was missing
So she panicked
She thought someone was in her house
So ran for the nearest phone box
Fortunately when she got there
There were police about on the street at night
So she grabbed one of the police officers
And said, look, there might be someone in my house
The house might be on fire
And stuff for ringing your help
The police went back to the house
Fortunately the fire hadn't gone
The smoke could clear
And you confirmed that there was nobody in our house
But on investigation
They found the mobile phone battery
And it's not here mobile phone battery
It had shot
From her mobile phone across the side of the room
And underneath the wardrobe
And said itself on fire
Well, well, well, well, well
I've heard of this happening with laptop batteries
I've heard of it
Happening with some cell phones in the US
I thought mainly
I thought it was only motor rollers
But you're telling me it's shot across the room
And said itself on fire
This is
Those Nokia guys man
They think of everything don't they?
There's a pretty much just a molten lamp
A metal underneath the wardrobe
And it sets fire to the car
And also it's a stuff that fortunately
The fire didn't spread any further
Now my friend had only gone to bed
I'd want to clock in the morning
And put the phone on charge
Just before she went to sleep
And so whatever it happened
The thing that seems to have happened
was that the somehow
The mobile phone
Or the battery exploded
Left to shaft at the phone
And shot across the side of the room
Now it's something that's probably traveled about
7 foot and then set fire to itself
Now this is pretty dangerous
It's Nokia phones can do this
If you just leave them on charge on their own
I mean it was an original Nokia phone
With an original charge on an original battery
Now hi, okay
Hmm
Original phone
Of course, I presume
Original charge or original battery
And this is not just a threat to everyone's home
I mean I can imagine that happening upstairs
In the attic which is the complete wood floor
Would burn like an MF
But it's also a matter of national security
How can we take these dangerous cell phones on airplanes with us?
This has to stop what is going on
Right
Now she's wondering what to do
She's called Nokia and they'd say
Let me guess
Why don't you send it to us?
Send her the phone
Yeah
I'm just wondering if your answer wants to go inside of the device
I mean you know
She'd go and get compensation for the damage it caused to our house
But it could have been so much nasty
I mean people could have died
No, a homeless I can hold on
So first of all the compensation to our house
She should be insured for that
And I don't necessarily want to
I hate lawsuits
I hate it
So don't do that
I'm sure that Nokia has a reasonable explanation
And if not I'm sure that just like any other company that's had these issues
They'll dive into it immediately because of course no one wants that
I don't think the way to go is to contact Nokia
Well, no I take that back
Yes, you should send the damage product to them
Only after you write up the story and take numerous pictures
And you show the situation of the bedroom and how far it's shot
And all that and then give that to someone like a gadget or something
Because if there truly is a problem that will put pressure on all cell phone manufacturers
To revisit the issue because it will come from a wider sharing of audience
And we'll all be thinking about this
But again, I'm not into
Let's go kill the corporate beast because they're making dangerous shit
I mean this needs to be investigated
In fact, you might even want to send it to
The gizmodo or in gadget guys to have them take a look at it
Maybe they can make some sense out of it before you send it to Nokia
But it does have to go to Nokia because without these important data points that your friend has
About what happened, you know, they'll never be able to improve anything
Or start any type of investigation themselves
Result of this
So I'm just wondering if CSB or anyone like that's got any advice on how she should approach Nokia with this
And I don't know if this is the kind of thing that you want to go public with
But I still do it was an interesting story and it makes me personally amazing before I put my Nokia phone on charge
So that's about it for now
I'm a folder, I love the show, keep it up, it's great
I love all the advanced stuff, it's fantastic
So yeah, and then you guys got some advice and it's compacting me on it
That'd be great, cheers
All right, buddy, cheers
Yeah, well, the savants that come to mind are of course comic strip blogger
I'm sure he'll be sending in something
And depending on how happy
And if you can speak for the company, I'll ask Candyman Luke if he can give his view on it
Very interesting
And as a lover of the Nokia devices, I'm also a tad bit concerned
Frank Jonas at me in email, I'm seeing this more and more podcast
Let artists pay them money via sonic bids
So they get played on their shows
Here's an example of how I'll show with unproven audience
One several artists over by charging them for plays
If anything, these shows should be ashamed of themselves
That's like charging for show content
This is beyond wrong and puts podcasting in a really bad light
Let me just take a look at the link that you provided here, sonic bids
What pops up here?
Area 67 plays music from unsigned and undiscovered artists
Looking for exposure and all genres are accepted and played
They will have guests on the show to discuss the music and also to review what is playing
Guess what also talk about new equipment out as well as discuss music business
Topics, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah
Okay
Congratulations to the following sonic bids artist that we're selected
And how does this work? I don't see anywhere
I don't see oh
I don't get it
So how do you, how do you buy airplay?
Let me see
I don't understand how this works.
Okay, so I'm just going to presume that what you're saying is true.
Let me tell you about the Podsafe music license.
Ron and I thought about this for a very long time.
And the idea of payola, which, of course, is illegal in the United States, is a horrible thing,
because there is only money that can buy preference in a limited resource.
And a limited resource would be public airways.
And so anything that is limited, so that would include satellite.
But when it comes to the internet, I don't see a problem.
I really don't.
If a show wants to charge artists for being played, so be it.
That could be their business model if they have enough audience.
But audience is not stupid.
Especially if they're posting it on Sonic Bids.
Yeah, that seems pretty obvious what they're doing.
But the same token, you know, the could be a show that will promote an artist's entire album.
If they want to take cash for it, that's fine, because it's not a limited resource.
You don't need money to get podplay.
You just don't.
You can create your own show and create podplay.
So I disagree with what you're saying there.
And we thought about this for quite a while that that should be totally an option.
You don't want to be able to charge whatever they want for whatever they want in their show.
I don't think we should put the traditional restrictions on it because let me say it's not traditional media.
And it definitely is not a limited resource.
I'm sure I'm going to get some feedback on that.
Hey Adam Curry, this is Carmen Tyler from the Carmen cast.
So, 600th episode, huh?
That is amazing.
You know, I know that call you be podfather, which you are.
But on 600 podcasts, I think that makes you the pod king.
So, your majesty, congratulations on your 600 podcast of the daily source code.
Oh, yes.
Carmen, I shall make you my queen.
She lives in Los Angeles now.
Next time I'm in town for more than three hours.
I'm going to look her up.
Ah, Carmen.
But don't call me the king.
Just call me the Sultan of the Savans.
Hi there Adam.
It's Kevin Crossman from fratac.cast.com.
Just wanted to give you some feedback that I thought you did a great job trying to hang in there
in your interview with Tom extra blogger.
I mean, what the fuck was the matter with Tom extra blogger?
I mean, interrupt you every goddamn minute.
Did you even answer questions?
Just kept interrupting.
So, what I want to do here is play a little knock-knock joke on comic strip blogger.
So, okay, you're with me, right?
Knock-knock?
Who's there?
Interrupting cow.
Interrupted.
Talk to you later, Adam.
I didn't mind.
I liked it.
I thought it was pretty cool.
And did you notice I kept my sunglasses on throughout the entire video interview?
But it's nice.
I liked comic strip blogger has a really good point.
He tries to piss you off to get you angry because only then are you truthful?
At least that's his hypothesis.
I was truthful throughout the entire meeting.
So, and the audio stuff is pretty good.
I thought it was pretty in-depth questions, but just funny.
And it's good because there's a guy you can talk to the same way he talks to me.
You can talk back to him that way, so that kind of works.
Let's see, coming up this week, I believe we'll be kicking off our suck less promotion.
I think you'll like that.
It's going to last for quite a while, but it's a way for listeners to participate, get free stuff,
and most importantly, help us suck less.
And also, maybe by the end of the week or the beginning of next week, we will be announcing
very interesting new addition to the Pod Show podcast network.
We have a well-known personality coming on to the network.
He'll be building several channels.
And he's already started work.
I just don't want to announce it yet because, well, there's no damage announcements, of course.
But he also requested me to hold off on it a little bit, but I'm so excited.
I think you're going to be-
Well, I think a lot of the blogging world will be surprised when you find out who's coming in.
I don't know, Jim, right, there's a comment.
Yeah, 10 minutes to work, and it's dinner right.
Okay, a whole lot.
If you in the States and you can't understand what James is saying,
the final thought of the week on Friday was to do something different to challenge yourself.
Even if it's a turning left when you go to work, instead of turning right to go to work,
because it challenges your brain and literally changes something in the chemical,
make-up, and distribution of neurons and crap.
So it's good.
It'll make you feel wonderful.
So this is his response to that.
He's getting a different turn off the intersection, as you would see.
He has a good idea for your listeners.
Anybody got stuck, not over there.
10, 10, 10 miles from here.
There, when you're too is your route, too short of the route.
And I guarantee you, if you've got any distance to go, anything will be 20 miles,
or 30 kilometers or over a European, you want to be hungry.
I guarantee you, it'll take you through some interesting minutes.
There you go.
Our James.
Bit.
Oh, man.
Don't call me from the car.
James, I can barely hear you.
A good point, though, if you travel to work and you have a satellite navigation system,
and once you start it to avoid highways or motorways,
and take the inside route, I guarantee you, it's going to work.
And while you're doing, record something, will you?
Yeah.
Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen, the drunk Londoner is back.
Oh, obviously, it's right.
Bob, I'm not drunk.
I'll say, like, give me your cold.
That would happen.
What happened to Charles the drunk in Londoner is his, his bag was stolen.
His laptop is cell phone and his iPod.
So he hasn't been able to listen for the fast couple of weeks.
I think he's found a worthy substitute though.
He's made a very kind of it.
I happened to just kill.
I was on some random randomly strange coincidence.
I happened to, I sent him my computer.
The one I have at home.
Not my laptop.
They were neat.
I sent my iPhone on camera.
Oh, I made it.
I was just nasty.
Anyway.
And I just click on when he puts his downloading.
And he made a real kind of a mate.
Yeah, no idea.
That's just me.
So much to me.
Okay.
Maybe not.
I just sent out your way.
Think on your phone.
But that's all good.
Well, let me explain.
I said on the show.
I said, you know, this guy's been calling in for a long time.
Big fan of the show.
He's got ripped off.
I said, I got one of these red iPod.
The virgin Atlantic sent me.
I'll send that to you.
So he just received your address.
By the way, Charles.
So the iPod is on the way.
As soon as I can rip it off of the lady Patricia.
He used it for rehearsals.
When she was in the Netherlands last week.
So there's probably a couple of star sisters songs on it.
But you don't mind, really.
I'm really, really going to tell you off on it.
And then when I'm done with that nice red iPod,
I'm going to alternate charity or something.
And I'll put your name over it.
That's okay.
If not, you let me know.
I'm never going to hear this message.
Because I'm not able to listen right now.
But I'm leaving this message.
So that maybe you can hear something.
I'm waiting for him to go.
I love you, man.
I love you.
Yeah.
On the same podcast.
Right.
You know, maybe if I'm a fool.
And I was dipping in a great point of the street.
It's over there.
What do you do?
I'm going to land on this.
I'll be here.
We need to be messed up for you.
Show them.
What the fuck are we going to do?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Right.
You were told.
Next time, you know, those commercials on television.
And if you in the UK, they have them now.
Where girl goes to a party.
And then she sees herself at the party.
Getting drunk and dropping stuff and falling on the floor and puking in the toilet.
You know, this is, this is, this is your, this is your James Charles, your brain.
This is you on drink.
Can, about the green room guy and the dreams stuff.
I don't want to be in a stream.
All thought I'd listen to that dream podcast.
And then you make an online offer.
Yeah, but I had a dream where.
Oh.
Please.
I don't know if I want to hear this.
He's talking about the dream I had about there.
I'm totally spacing out.
Eric Bergen and his girlfriend.
It was a sexual dream.
I was hanging on your whole play.
And you flew to Switzerland.
And you were really pissed off.
I didn't hang it on the outside of the play.
But you really pissed off.
But you said, yeah, what doesn't matter?
And you've always loved it.
And it was nice.
I know that can I probably reflect upon you.
I'm making these messages.
It was like, oh, yeah.
It's all good.
Cool.
It's good.
So, fuck.
I'm going to regret this.
Oh, yeah.
Cool.
This is Charles.
George, I'm Londoner.
I'm having a lovely time in London.
I like it here.
It's nice.
Come visit.
And I can be your guide.
It needs our calm help.
And take you out on the town.
I'll give you a nice place to stay for a nice place to go.
Thank you.
Bye.
Charles, the drunken Londoner.
Please promise me you tell me exactly what you drank to reach this state of an
ebryation because there's the perfect spot.
You can replicate that.
You got yourself a regular spot on the show, my friend.
Arthur, you're real.
I picked it up from the title.
It will become a parent throughout the lyrics.
Perfect.
For a 600 episode of Charlie.
So pretty.
So much for saying that.
I love you so much for saying that.
Arthur.
And some crystal news
I say
Thank you so much for watching this video and I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next
video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see
you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video
Part of the Yoria comes to us from Texas and is on the Pod St. Music Network, where the whole Heath showed us. And that one's titled current job, as I said, there was the title to conserve my eye, hey, that's it, for Daily Source, go to episode 6, I'm going to thank you so much for those of you on that video, from here there we were, Rei II, a woman, who knows even all of them, us of them has been quite wide, so far and let me tell you, it's not hard, all we've got to do is do it every day and what else am I going to do? I've got none. Better to do?
But you guys sending in comments, editing bits, making music, you're really the ones that keep me going every single day, so the thanks is to you.
DailySourceco.com, www.podshow.com. Hey, we got an interesting week. I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.
The best and the brightest.
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering podshow and limelight.