Hey, home fries and CC Chapman from accident hash encouraging you to check out
BODOD.tv slash battle.
It's one of the coolest battle events out there and you can only find it at BODOD.tv.
It's Adam Curry and the DSC 646 in stereophonic sound.
stereophonic sound, stereophonic sound, stereophonic sound, stereophonic sound.
60 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no stinking drinks, I like to be touched like a huge jerk.
Autistic is that a curry?
The time comes baby, don't worry that I say it no, no, no, no.
Yes, I've eaten black, but we have come back.
No, no, no.
It's the two reasons that did before told you how used to be.
What you call it someone like me?
No, no, no, no.
If in a story were for word, had a lot of history.
What you call it someone like me?
No, no, no, no.
I did before and had my share.
It didn't lead nowhere.
I would've loved someone like you.
Because I don't want you to be you, I hope.
Wait for secret on and see this night through.
I'll make them care about the young people.
Talk about the answer.
Talk about the old side.
I'll make them care about the young people.
Yes, I've eaten black, but we have come back.
No, no, no, no.
I can tell there's something going on.
Everyone is leaving, I'm still with you.
Because we had a walk with you, but we have come back.
We can see what I want to see this night through.
I'll make them care about the old side.