And the beginning there was A.M. radio, families everywhere would gather around the living room,
listening to their favorite programs, and all was good.
Who knows what evil looks in the hearts of men, the shadow knows.
Then came the advent of F.M. radio.
Now broadcast could be heard in stereo, and teenagers found this, especially in tweaking,
as rock and roll music to be heard with great clarity.
However, parents became concerned as to what this music was doing to their kids.
Now it's the 21st century, and satellite radio is all the rage, or is it?
In a world where TV networks, movie studios, and record labels still think they can govern what you see in here.
One man has the power to return control of entertainment to the masses and make big media corporations wet their tiny little pants.
From Pod Show, home of the world's most dangerous new content comes the Daily Source Code with Adam Curry.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Delta Sharon Charlie 568, it is from our Friday.
If you know the lyrics, please feel free to sing along because we're fucked up beyond our pain.
And let me let you love me.
I'm sitting in your face and tell you I love you too.
I love to hear you more allies when I'm between your eyes.
You blow me away.
To my face and let my lips embrace you.
I'll sit in your face and let love you truly.
Life can be fine if we both six to nine.
If we sit in a face as adults as a place as a play.
Till we're blown away.
You're so explicit, you're show.
I never miss it though.
I think you and me should kick it.
Come with you to screen I want to get it.
Come on.
Now try to pump you up or inflate your ego.
No.
Now this is just place.
Don't you know.
I tune in week after week.
I want to be a host of love and internet geek.
Like the way you move over here.
Like the way you're out here.
Thank you, soccer, football, making my nays.
I come home to you in and I turn out the lies.
I'm your number one fan.
You don't know.
I'm here.
I'll do everything you want.
Because I want you so bad.
You're good.
I can't tell you're free.
We see you.
I passed a little secret.
Yeah.
Day time library.
Night time on the free show.
Yeah.
You're good.
Like the way you move over here.
Like the way you're out here.
Thank you, soccer, football, making my nays.
I come home to you in and I turn out the lies.
I'm your number one fan.
You don't know.
I am.
I'll do everything you want.
Because I want you so bad.
I can't tell you're free.
I want you so bad.
Why is the score for you?
I've run for you.
I've been keeping that touch short.
I'll give you a new hope.
I'll resign.
I need to short.
I wanna score.
Like the way you move.
Yeah.
Yeah, like the way it's done.
Yeah!
Thank you, soccer girl for making my nights.
I come home to you in an eternal life.
I'm your number one fan that you don't know.
I'm gayer.
I've been waiting for you.
I've got to want you so fair.
What a way to kick off a football Friday.
A brand new bro low soccer girl from his new album.
Somehow a little birdy leaked that song to me and boys.
It's perfect for a football.
Hey, everybody.
How you doing?
Daily source code episode 568 coming to you from an overcast.
And somewhat damp.
Uh, affluent suburb of Surrey known as Gilford.
G. Town West side represent.
It's the curry manner.
The Lord of the Manor at your service.
Hey.
Uh, what a way to wrap up a couple of really busy weeks.
Yesterday with bum rush the charts.
Wow.
We made the needle move.
I couldn't.
I could really.
I was blown away.
How fast it actually happened.
Now has the song.
Black labs.
Mine again.
Reach number one.
No.
I didn't expect to see much.
Let me tell you just in.
The events as they unfolded yesterday.
Of course, I recorded the show relatively early and was busy.
In the city and London for most of the day with meetings and stuff.
So only could, you know, catch some casual updates as they came in.
And the first thing I got which I thought was I learned so much from this exercise.
You know, even as I was doing the show yesterday, I'm thinking, wow.
You know, it's already the 24th of the 27th in Australia.
You know, how at least times of global campaigns are not very easy.
And also in the full knowledge that a lot of people would listen to my show at the end of yesterday.
Or perhaps even today or tomorrow or next week.
And I'm thinking, wow, you know, this is really something like this.
It doesn't really work on a one day, one day shot only.
Yeah, we moved the needle in day one, which is great.
But I think that if we were to continue this, which I don't believe we're going to do.
It doesn't really make sense because to me, the proof is already here.
Let me just tell you what some of the things that learned yesterday.
First of all, the Washington Post had a great article about bum rush the charts.
And I wasn't able to read that before I did yesterday's show, but I got it sent to me.
And there was one piece that I thought was really interesting.
They took the effort, which I really appreciate Mike Musgrove of the Washington Post,
to contact Apple and got through to Derek Mainz, a spokesman for Apple,
who declined to comment on the campaign itself, but said the best seller list that would be the iTunes top 100
is compiled using proprietary methods that the company doesn't disclose.
It's much more complicated than taking a snapshot of the previous 24 hours worth of sales.
So that means you probably would have to have a sustained campaign to really make something move up the charts.
But just to enter the charts and here's what I really learned.
The individual country top 100 charts.
Wow, that's what we really saw a lot of action.
The United States, I don't even know if it's cracked into the actual top 100 yet.
It's done a lot on the individual charts such as the rock chart.
Hold on a second, I have where is it?
Here we go.
Now this was yesterday afternoon, and so I don't have an update.
On the rock singles charts, that is, so it's a subdivision.
In the US, the last time I was able to check it was number 67,
it reminds you the only independent pod save song on the entire top 100 for the rock chart.
In the UK 71 Canada 22 Australia at 35 Austria 35 Denmark, number 40 Finland 42 Germany 13 Ireland 54 Italy 30 the Netherlands.
Number five New Zealand 56 Norway 23 Sweden 9 Switzerland 42 overall the top 100 songs chart.
We entered the Canadian top 196, the German at 98, the Netherlands at 38 Norway 100 Sweden at 98.
That's as of 9 p.m. Pacific Standard Time yesterday.
So I do expect some spill over and depending on how the proprietary magic sauce.
Can you imagine that what a weird industry we live in where the way a chart is compiled is secret.
It doesn't make a lot of sense to me, but it's okay because I'm so proud of what took place.
I saw as I was really busy scanning technology most of the time.
I found that to be the most compelling to see that yes sure podcasters were in this.
And we were telling our audiences what we'd like them to do to see if we could make the needle move.
But it was really the audience.
I saw post things on web logs and on podshow plus pages just everywhere.
And of course, you know, we had a great logo.
And it was an audience participation move of anything.
And I was just blown away by by the results so far.
Was it sent me this.
I got it.
I forgot who sent me this.
But it was kind of funny yesterday.
This report came out US sales of music CDs plunged 20 percent in the first three months of the year.
According to the figures released by Nielsen sounds can 89 million CDs were sold from the start of the year through March 18th.
It's compared to 112 million CDs sold during the same period in 2006.
Wow.
Oh, by the way, we do actually know how many people clicked on the link.
So that'll be some knowledge once everything's compiled.
Now at last count, I heard it was around 15,000 who had clicked on the by link.
To actually purchase the song.
So I'm sure Chris Penn will have an update for us on that.
He actually posted quite a long story about this.
And he really, I think he approached it more as a as a promotion.
And you know, how we could make a promotion like that work differently in the future with more success.
To me, it wasn't really about a promotion.
It was just about seeing if there's enough audience to make something move that is actually visible in the big,
mainstream world.
Do you realize how many tens, if not hundreds of thousands of dollars are spent on on on on individual tracks and albums to get them into a chart?
You know, to chart.
That's the beginning when when a song charts in the mainstream world, even if it just bobs into the top 100,
even if it's not at number 100, that's where the record company is jumping up and down.
Everybody's freaking out.
They start trying to book interviews with the artist.
You know, it would really only be the beginning of an entire campaign.
So I never expected the song to go anywhere.
Certainly.
I'm just amazed it entered the top 100 anywhere on the first day.
That's really fucking fantastic.
And of course, there's plenty of comments about this.
Hi, Adam.
It's been downing.
I listen from Melbourne, Australia.
First of all, let me apologize for the abrupt ending on the prime.
I've tried yesterday.
I'm certainly not a professional podcaster and have, in fact, never been involved in any
aspect of digital audio production.
However, I'm just a chance for something I believe passionately in to the fact where
I didn't actually get to bed this morning till half past one local time.
Just because I was up late monitoring how things were going.
I'd just like to say big thanks to all the Aussies who got out there and pushed
mine again our chosen songs to number 35 on the rock charts on the Australian
and I changed music.
So why took out a guy's?
We're showing that we have an active podcast audience here down under.
Now, Adam, when are you going to get your butt down here?
So we can have some cold frothy bass.
Have a good one, Mike.
Fold our scruncher.
Valmed, I'll tell you.
I'm going to come down.
I don't, I just don't think I'm able to get my girls to go with me.
Which may be better because what happens in Australia stays in Australia, I hear.
Have the green from business we grow to bum russ the charts.
She calls it a grassroots effort that's using social media, including dig YouTube, blogs,
podcasts to try to get podsake music in the iTunes top 100.
It's interesting in light of the meltdown of traditional CD sales.
She points to the same data that supporters of indie music are trying to push sales
of the music.
They treasure.
I understand the idea that by pushing the music.
I understand the idea.
By pushing the music, they feel it will send the message to the RIA that suing folks won't
get them to buy that the music industry needs a to promote a broader group of music
and through a broader group of channels I might add.
So then Heather, almost typical.
I don't blame her for thinking this way.
It says goes on to say, but at the same time, it makes me think whether it will
matter what music you put in the iTunes top 100 sales don't seem to matter because people are
copying each other.
Each other CDs and letting each other copy their hard drives.
In the future of music is band supporting themselves through touring and other kids money
making efforts then wouldn't go into shows be a better way to point to the future.
So there you kind of miss the point, Heather.
The point is that people are so passionate about music and I think it's just as much a call
out to the big four labels to allow really to drop a lot of all the negating factors
of how we can consume music, listen to music, how others play music for us.
That was just as much a shout because here's a song that I'm sure a lot of people didn't even care
about.
They just wanted to participate, which is really the point.
The point is not, I was like Eric Bergen said yesterday.
I was like, well, this is not because people like the song because you told them to go
by it and I can think that's really my point is that I know that within the daily source
code audience, you guys will do a lot of stuff.
I mean, you do it every single day.
The show was filled up with stuff that you're doing for me and for the audience, for yourself.
Really, it's a master-betteria exercise.
You know, and we do all kinds of nutty shit.
We tell people where folders are scrunchers.
I think it's just proving the bond between a podcaster or any producer of independent media
who does really its episodic content.
These are shows people call them what you want, but they're shows.
We have audiences and they're growing in every single MP3 player or a computer that is sold
that enables video or audio.
That's another opportunity for us to grow the audience and it's very hard to prove.
You know, the only people who really know the power of audience are advertisers.
That's really the ones who understand it the most.
And so maybe now that we've started to move the needle, maybe maybe we'll see some things change.
Really the only thing I'd like from the music industry in this regard is just to,
you know, to treat independent producers of programming with some respect.
And you utilize any of the licenses that are available out there.
You could certainly use the pod save music license.
If you own the masters, all you have to do is convince the artist or the singer-songwriter who wrote the tracking
question you want to put up to convince them to sign the pod save music license to waver their ASCAP BMI fee.
Or, or, yeah, to supersede that license, I guess there's to say technically.
And you're good, you know, and I'm sure we'll play your stuff as well as just as much chance.
Actually, you might find out that we hate your shit and we're not going to play it.
And that would be a pretty interesting message for you as well considering it's your business.
Ah boy, when I started this morning, I was like, I barely open my eyes.
I'm just so full-barred, but I'm into it now folks.
Hello?
I had them.
It's Edward's when pots of here again.
Oh, yes.
I'm not talking about from this time, so don't worry.
Just saw this article from the 75 March 2007 on the BBC News website.
Had line actors in landmark podcast, too.
No, I'm going to do.
I'm going to play that next.
I want to hold on a second.
Because there's something much, much better.
Thank God.
And I was so happy Eric Bergen provided pushback.
Yes, they thank God.
Not everyone appreciates bomb rush the charts.
Because I love when we have a contrarian view.
Let me say this quick Adam.
This is the New Yorker in London.
You're nylon.
Really bothered by this bomb in the rest thing.
Let me take up to a macro level.
You can play that the big record companies run their machine and people buy records.
You're running the machine and the other podcasts.
People are running the machine and saying, buy black labs.
It'll produce a result.
It's manipulating the system.
You both manipulate the system.
And you both assume, respectfully, that you have a dumb consumer.
If we tell them what to do, they will do it.
And that's our power.
Our power is we can drive people into desired results.
Okay.
Hold on a second.
Oh, I love this.
So first of all, I think I even said this yesterday.
Yes, we're showing that we have a machine that is equally as powerful.
But there's a a slight difference here.
The machine that is the mainstream media is based upon limited access to shelf space.
There's only so many channels.
Only so much ether that can be used up.
So the people that have called control over it or that determine what content goes through it.
They're only giving you an offering that they determine.
And they determine it by a whole bunch of factors, which I think at the end of the day is based upon,
you know, what kind of return can they get on putting something through.
The difference here is we just pick something willy-nilly.
You're right.
It would not have mattered.
It would not have mattered what we chose.
We could have taken any song.
Could have been a classical piece.
The whole point was to show that that power is there.
And that short now we did it with an aggregation of audiences.
But it's not going to be too long before one individual shows audience will be able to move the needle like that.
So yes, of course, that's what we're showing.
And please don't be confused by thinking that we're trying to prove that the music industry,
charts and stuff works better in an independent world.
Not at all.
This is about showing that we have a machine.
So that what you shouldn't take offense to that.
This is, you know, if you want to show someone that your dick is bigger, you got to show your dick.
Like that because it assumes both of you manipulate and both of you have consumers.
Okay.
And by the way, you got to be real careful calling at least my audience dumb.
I don't know something at all.
And they certainly wouldn't have done.
What am I fucking hypnotist?
Let me do my eye.
Look into my eyes.
You show by this.
Oh, it was, we did this together.
And I'm sorry you didn't participate clearly.
That is not making their own choices.
You're driving them and narrowing down their choices.
Okay.
So again, again, I'm not narrowing down the choice.
Simply proving that we can make any choice.
Regardless of what we want to show or what we want to buy or what we want to buy.
Well, this is, you know, this was the original idea behind priceline.com.
Of course, in quite pan out that way, but we'll see this.
You know, the consumers decided to support this.
Yeah.
What I call an audience.
The people who make me want to do this shit every single day.
So it wasn't forcing anything.
It was like just to show that our dick is big too.
So two, this whole thing about not being directly involved.
You are.
And you're next to on a funding on your PowerPoint slide.
We bummed the charts.
Look at our power.
And you will gain some of this.
Last thing.
Really.
Okay.
So.
Dude.
The whole point of not sanctioning this as an official pod show thing.
Was so that everybody can take credit for it.
Anybody who's doing anything in podcasting or independent media will be able to say.
Look at what happened.
Okay.
Will we have it on our PowerPoint?
Yes.
For our next funding round.
I don't know if we're going to need another funding round dude.
But will we have this on our presentations towards clients and advertisers?
You better fucking believe it.
Of course.
All the more reason to have not been the official whatever of this.
God.
That was really clear, wasn't it?
No.
You got it wrong.
This is so everyone can take credit for it.
Everybody who who participated can take 100% credit.
That's exactly the point.
Okay.
What's your final point?
Is this record companies?
Why are you dragging the two record companies to come to you to help you manipulate their
artists?
It's the new way for them.
Okay.
Well, first of all.
I think you mean not manipulate their artists, but manipulate the audience.
And let me tell you that there are a couple people out there.
Princess Ty, but people who have a podcast will know these names.
Nigel from the UK.
Well, to an extent to Jersey Todd.
I mean, these are people who get really, really passionate.
I have no idea if they have any financial gain.
I just look at them as promoters, promoters of music.
And they, you know, they hook people up with artists.
And there's lots of people doing this.
And it's not just for independent artists.
It's for mainstream.
How do you think Thomas Dolby got on to the pod save music network?
You know, this is what Nigel did.
I had no idea what Nigel does.
He may be fucking Thomas Dolby's record company.
I don't care.
All he's doing is he's coming in.
He's stepping in.
He's saying, hey, how you doing?
I'm Nigel.
Look, I got Thomas Dolby here.
And he'd love to.
He'd look.
He cut a promo for you.
And here's a song.
And he put on the pod save music network.
He wants to join in.
Someone bringing a new kid into the playground and saying,
OK, he's a little older than the rest of y'all.
But he's been around the blocking.
I was out of build a sandcastle.
You know, can we jump in here and play?
You understand?
It's about the promotion.
It's how it works.
It's not manipulation.
Many people can only really take place when there's a monopoly on the resources.
I don't have a monopoly on audience.
No one has a monopoly on audience on the internet.
It's just, it just don't.
You know, and if you just keep doing whatever you want to do,
you'll persevere.
Your audience gets stronger.
Your audience has connections.
People have, you know, stuff starts to happen.
People want to join the party.
So it's not about, uh, I really don't like,
do you saying that?
That's kind of offensive.
New Alan Creek.
Oh, on the new Alan Freed, dude,
I did not take money.
That's, you know, that fuck you.
You know, it just fuck me.
Fuck me with a chainsaw.
You ask.
I, that's, that's very nice.
You calling me a criminal.
But you, we get a new, uh,
milkin dick.
Don't brag about a record company that wants you to manipulate the system for your audience for desired results.
No, dude.
The whole point is to expose,
not brag to expose
that these record companies really see the power in what we can do.
I can't manipulate my audience.
Yeah.
And hey, by the way, part of it's about to drop away by serious.
Sorry.
Short goodbye.
I can't manipulate the audience.
The audience is free to do whatever they want.
And, and people don't like it.
They'll go away.
They'll find something else.
I can't manipulate them because there's no way for me to
determine that it's only one choice and that there's nothing else out there.
You can do a bummer to charge tomorrow.
Today.
You don't even have podcasts.
You can do it through my space.
I'm sure you can.
It's just when it's podcasting.
I think the message is a little bit more powerful.
And I think the bond between a host and the audience is much, much stronger.
And there's a relationship there.
And I could tell anyone.
I could have told anyone.
Like we had dinner last night.
Anyone at the place I could have said,
Hey, would you do me a favor?
Just because we're buds.
You know, would you buy this song just so we can prove a point?
And you do it.
So that shows a real trusting relationship and a strong bond of anything.
It's not about bragging.
Dude, you are so stuck in the mainstream world.
It's not funny.
Take your head out of it and see the light on the other side.
Nothing to brag about.
No big impression of my part there.
But you're really listening a bit there by thinking that's a plus.
I'm team up with the media to manipulate the audience.
So that's that.
Last thing, the scholarship points.
Go to the site.
I don't see what they skip scholarships.
You sign up.
Do surveys.
You do points.
And you get money at the end.
So I'm even dubious there.
And I like the fact that black labs don't get in 50% of their earnings to the college fund.
All in all, it's everyone making money in a new medium sort of way.
And it assumes that you can manipulate just as well as EMI or Sony can manipulate.
Not moved at all.
And that's all next time in New York and the W Union Square.
Thank you.
You're challenging me to a duel.
What the hell is that?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
And go reread all the information.
You know, I made no money on this.
I didn't get a dime.
I didn't want to see a dime.
It's too bad that money was involved.
But it's the only way we can officially charge something.
It's the only way people say something's believable if someone pulled their wallet.
It was just about proving a point dude.
That's all it was.
And by moving the needle, we've shown that in a very short time with, I think, still a reasonably small audience.
We were able to make something happen.
So the message here is that these audience host relationships are very, very strong.
People are very motivated.
The audience is happy to go and do some fun shit.
Particularly if we can do something against the man.
And love doing that.
And that individual audiences will, one day, maybe sooner than you think, be large enough to move needles all over the fucking dashboard of mainstream media.
Hi, Adam.
Perfect programmer here from San Francisco.
I need to respond to Mr. Bugwin's comment in DSE 567.
And what he said that the bummer the charts thing is he doesn't understand what's going on with it or something like that.
Mind the sign of it seems to be that you are trying to show the record come is that they are no longer necessary to make an artist successful.
In that they can now just upload the music part, save music network, and have podcasts to play it.
And get away from the record monopoly on the industry.
That's all tears.
Broly think programmer.
At your command it's the Broly think programmer program.
Hey, Adam.
It's Angie B.
By the way, that's B.E.E. like a busy little B.
I'm sorry that I haven't said any audio feedback in a really long time.
I know where did our love go.
But yeah, anyways, I had a story.
Since to me, by one of my chill castlessness this week, that I thought you would like.
All right, so he said he was on a photo shoot with a bunch of lovely female models.
And he didn't have a stereo, so he was just playing episodes of the chill cast all morning.
And he said that everyone's in like a dreamy mood.
And around about episode 24, he said he was on a video conference.
And the person said, hey, look behind you on the couch.
And apparently two of the models were totally making out.
So yeah, that's what chill cast is all about.
And that's that's for.
And yeah, unwind is more about taking a hot bath, popping in your earbuds, getting into your bed with the blank.
It's pulled all the way up to your chin and just letting go and unwinding, falling asleep.
Yes.
And I thought that I would clue in as to why we ladies enjoy Tylenol Pam so much.
As opposed to men, there's a certain pain that we get every single month that makes it hard to sleep.
And you men don't have that, so it's really great for that.
And especially now that they've got the vanilla liquid, what could be better?
Drink a little vanilla liquid.
Ah, there goes the pain.
Sleepen through the night.
So anyways, check out the show at unwind.potshow.com.
See there.
And you know how to make an old man smile.
Yeah.
You know, the chill cast does have that effect on me.
I also want to immediately make out with models.
Hey, I disagree with you, dear.
Men have a certain pain every month as well.
And Tylenol Pam may just be very well suited for it.
It's called, the paying the fucking bills.
Yeah, hi.
My name is Adam Curry.
I'm in the funny situation right now.
I'm trying to open a parachute, which I bought in your store.
And it doesn't seem like it wants to open.
But I would like to do that here.
Yeah, I'm kind of in a hurry here because I'm on my cell phone.
I just add some trouble with my plane.
And I jumped off.
And now it seems like my parachute won't open.
And I want the model quay start to, which I bought in your store.
And I thought maybe you could help me with this.
Okay.
So can you explain one more time?
What are you trying to do?
Okay.
I'm trying to pull that thing with my hand.
You know, I'm trying to pull it so that the parachute will open.
And it will expand.
I think I didn't read the manual right.
Or maybe I didn't read the manual at all.
Yeah, that's a quay start.
Yeah, that would be the quay start too.
Okay.
So what is that?
What does it open?
I don't know.
It seems like like the handle is stuck.
You know, I'm trying to pull right now.
And I don't have a lot of time, you know?
Okay.
So what are you trying to do?
Just for me to have an idea.
Oh, DSC.
5.
6.
7.
Hello?
Make that 8 if you don't mind.
And stop the girvee.
To make a motion.
To practice further around.
Man, there's a engine show.
To turn its roll around.
It's a football front end.
Hey, Adam, how's it going?
It's Jersey Todd, the official musical just of the Cha Cha.
Happy day after bum rushed the charts.
You know, as I record this right now, all the stats aren't in.
And I'm sure by the time that this edition of the Daily Source Code airs.
There's going to be a lot of discussion about the final numbers.
But I got to be honest, I don't care one bit.
Because on March 22, 2007, we did something spectacular.
You see, I've always heard that there wasn't a podcast community.
I've always heard that people were too bogged down in their artificial barriers in their turf to make podcasting anything more than a fad.
That cannot be said anymore.
That is the true benefit of March 22, 2007.
Because on that day, we celebrated the fact that on one day for one band, one song,
we could come together as one giant podcast family.
On March 22, 2007, we celebrated our musical Independence Day.
But what now? What now? What do we do now?
Well, let me propose this, that every day, be bum rushed the charts day.
Because it's not just about one band.
It's about the thousands and thousands of other bands that are out there.
The bands that have been out there on the Ponsate Music Network from day one and the artists that's just about to load their track today.
It's about each and every voice being heard, the podcast or the band, the fan.
And not having a big media tell us what we need to listen to or who to purchase.
I encourage every listener of the Delhi source code, each and every listener of the Delhi source code,
to go out there today and just purchase music from any artist who's going to stand up there and say,
Hey man, my music kicks ass too.
And let me get you a band that check out as the revolution is re-invigorated.
It's South Africa's one-day remains.
They recently uploaded some tracks and I'm just digging them a lot.
They're a little harder than what I normally give you on a football Friday.
But man, oh man, it's good stuff.
So check this out.
It's give it all away by the band one day remains.
Check you later everybody.
All this time.
All this time you've been there.
All this pain.
All this pain you've made you.
Oh, what you could see inside.
What you could be in that dough.
You could see what I can see.
Show me what I can do.
Tell me what you need.
All this time you've been there.
All this pain.
All this pain you've made you.
You could see inside.
What you could be in that dough.
You could see what I can see.
Show me what I can do.
Tell me what you need.
Why don't you tell me that I look at them and they'll go
And I'll try
Show me what I can do to make you see them
Tell me what you need
Why don't you tell me
One day remains
The pod save music network, where the wonderful
Lead in there from Jersey Todd, the official musicologist of the
Chacha, absolutely dude right on
Whatever you want to do with pod casting
Just know that you now have the power
You've got proof, you can show
And disagree a little bit about the community aspect
This to me was not a pod cast community
Exercise, it was an exercise in audience
Once again, has shown that they actually have something to say
And do give a shit and do like some control and are willing to exercise
If they feel it's for the right reason
What's going on here today?
It's Friday
One day Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday
I have a smile on the phone
Wow
So much to talk about as the final thought
There were he actually
I thought maybe I'd talk about something that's coming up
In the next couple of weeks and I want to thank some people in advance
And for the hard work they've been doing
And that really is
The operations and engineering staff at Pod Show
Just let me know
I want to let you know that
As we have grown exponentially
And of course that's not just the US
But we have services in the UK
And hopefully we'll be going to Germany pretty soon
There's a lot of decisions that have to be made about the big iron
About how these sight of this type of scale
Really works with this type of functionality
And really preparing for the future
It takes a shitload of work
We are in fact going to move over to our own
Colo location
Which means we'll have I just called the Data Barn
And the reason why is because I built one of these in the past
In 2001, 2002
It's a huge project
It's very, very complicated
If you're talking about a live application which would be Pod Show
Plus
And our media delivery
And bandwidth and all this stuff all having to come together
Within three months
The Pod Show operations and engineering teams
Have really gotten a Colo set up from scratch
So that includes design architecture
Technology selection
Think of the stores and machines load balancers
Network equipment
Contract negotiations with vendors
Equipment ordering installation
Set-up configuration
And somewhere around mid-April
We're going to switch over from where we are currently
Which was a typical third party outsourced solution
Which I think is pretty much the way everyone starts
But before the proverbial shit hits the fan
We want to make sure that we're ready
And before we really turn on some interesting marketing initiatives
That should bring a lot more audience into the world of independent media
And so
There's going to be downtime obviously
It's going to affect a lot more people than downtime
Would have affected a year ago
And I'm talking like huge when you think about it
And you ask shit
I won't be able to upload
I won't be able to download
Ads won't run
Even people just messing around
Really it bucks with you
So we're going to try and put together a really nice package of programming for you to enjoy
Keep you busy
You know, in my space usually does like a little tick-tack-toe game
Or Tetris game
We're going to try and bring you some cool media
Because it's going to be several hours
I'm not going to bullshit you
And we're also going to be talking about this more in the weeks to come
As we ramp up and get ready for this day
I'm trying
And engineering and operations
I promise me they'll try to make it happen on Friday the 13th
Which is just fabulous
Because if you can't cover it up
You might as well turn it up
That's one of the Podgeos slogans
So I want to thank the engineers
Both in engineering and in operations
For helping podgeo grow
And for putting in all these extra hours
And for all the shit you're going to encounter
Because of course, something's always full barred somewhere
Along with that I'll say that
I fully intend to talk to a couple of the engineers and
And ops folks about how things are going
And we'll put it on
Slip off my chair, I'm sorry
And we'll put it on the source code
And we'll kind of enjoy this journey together
And we'll try to make it not too thin foil hat-tick
If you know what I'm saying
So to those men and women, I salute you
And really, to all the doers of the world
I love it when you get off your ass
And you do something
Even if you just move in your mouth
I'm really going to buy a link for an iTunes song
Have yourselves a great weekend everybody
Bye-bye
Oh yeah, I'll be smoking one for you too
Another Podgeo Podgeos
Stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest
Served up daily by the sharpest minds in content
Delivering Podgeo and limelight