Delta's Yaracharly 69 or 1. It's 4v5d
Mainly 16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped by us
than the next generation radio contenti my years
We don't need no sticky drinks, man.
I like to become silent, you too.
She's trying to kill me.
I'm guessing it's Adam Curry.
Together.
We have you live like this for such a long time.
Do you know that something's a mess, but what you can't find?
I'll do the dirty work.
Hold up my sleeves until it hurts, man.
Leave it to me.
I am the man you need.
Won't you change your head and get your life back?
Let's put our heads together.
I'll do the dirty work.
Hold up my sleeves until it hurts, man.
Leave it to me.
I am the man you need.
Won't you change your head and get your life back?
I'll do the dirty work.
Hold up my sleeves until it hurts, man.
Leave it to me.
I am the man you need.
I'll do the dirty work.
Leave it to me.
I'm the man you need.
Just bring a new monk's dirty work from the pod safe music network.
Hey, everybody.
How you doing?
It's been two full days that we haven't spoken and good reason for it because I'm busy.
What can I tell you?
Oh, man.
Of course, two days if you saw my blog entry at curry.com, two days.
Two blissful days of playing with the brand new Nokia N-810.
Of course, I'll be telling you all about it in this football Friday edition of the Charlie.
I don't know if it's a child's own Londoner.
I'm just listening to it.
I think six, six, six, six, eight, six, eight, I don't know.
You know what?
I had to call him that fucking idiot.
I'm calling you lazy.
Now, I'm not your biggest man.
I'm fucking respect what you do.
And saying that you're making one out of pod.
So he clearly doesn't understand business.
There's no way pod shows making that much money yet.
Certainly I imagine not enough to pay you a wrong yet.
He's going to be playing back into the business building it up.
Sure, you will make a fuckload if and when you sell it.
But that's what it's like at the point.
I call you lazy.
Marba, fucker.
He's just jealous.
You're jealous.
It's a small-minded twat.
You really are.
And if you want one out of go, go round fucking do it.
Jesus Christ.
And get something to money.
Take your daughter to school or something like that.
It's fine back with the force of the state.
Sound like a laugh.
But I bet that's a real pain in the ass.
Running too fucking offices.
I'm sorry.
My friend, you are severely misguided in my opinion.
Like I said, like I'm not Adam's biggest fan.
But I told you respect what he does.
And that's all I have to say about that.
Ooh, got me ruined.
And stop.
I don't want Marba.
So easy to complain.
Don't change.
Never change.
I stand along.
Got to change direction.
Don't change.
I stand along.
You're a fool
Oh, it's all the face I want to dream of now
And you're a fool down
In the strong face, I will be bringing down
And you'll fall down
See the mind, lie down, burning from
But it's hard to escape
Where your flash will walk
With a smile of faith, I will be bringing you down
Because I am my enemy
How for sons, what's the peace?
And I get damn all yours, take that
Really?
I'm not belong, you're all
You're all
There's nothing like a little over-modulated
microphone in a hard rock and tune
I love that, just a just right
Right, right against distortion, fantastic
Hey, hey, hey, I'm going to San Francisco
On Sunday, for a week
Not exactly planned that way, but as you know, we're trying to
Close up a couple of the deals before the end of the year
And you just got to do it, you got to do it
You got to do it somewhere between
Thanksgiving and December 15th
If you want to do it in the US, we're also working
Over here in Germany, so it's
A lot of back and forth because of course
This is the media business that we're in my friends
And that shuts down around mid-December
Just stops, you know, people at agencies
Go on vacation
Listeners, tend to go on vacation
Viewers tend to go on vacation
Everything just kind of winds down very slowly
And then it kicks up again around January 5th
But for business, it just really, really blows
Hey, so I've had two fantastic days
Wednesday, I was scheduled for an interview
And a photo shoot
A part of it was being done here at home
And then we were off to the London office
And actually a day before I expected it
There was the candy man
He arrived with the red and yellow truck in front of the manner
That meant that the Nokia N810 had arrived
Man, I'm so happy this device turned out to be what it is
Because, you know, I want to sell these things
I want to get you guys a great deal
If you're interested in buying it, it is perfect
I mean, nothing is no devices ever perfect
But man, this exceeds even my expectations
Let me see if I can give you a little bit of a description
about it. First of all, they've taken a
I'd say almost a page from the Apple Playbook
The way they're packaging this device
When you open up the box, you know how Apple
When you open up an Apple thing, it's like porn
And it says, you know, made for you
And Cupertino, California
Well, even though it doesn't have any of that
Certainly not a made for you and Cupertino sign
It's just you open the box and there's the device
And, you know, it's nicely presented
Much better than I've ever seen
Any cell phone manufacturer do
By the way, do you know the history of
Nokia, these guys are going to weird company
They used to be in, I think they made paper
And then I think they made rubber products
Like rubber boots, they're manufacturing company
And then at one point they decided to go into
A mobile telephony and cell phones
And man, they have never looked back
It's a funny, funny, funny company
So I'm trying to think best
How to tell you about this device
I could give you the comparisons between the
9800 and the 810
But it's really the closest comparison I can give you
Is between when I had the E61
Which is the
What a lot of people will call it blackberry
But it's not, it's a full-quality keyboard
Phone from Nokia
And then when they came out with the E61I
It's almost that type of an upgrade
The device is thinner
It's smaller, of course
The big
Different, since it has a slide out keyboard
Underneath now
10 does not have a cell phone in it
But that's not what it's for
I see this as a
It's right in the middle of my
Computing triumvirent
If you will, my communications triumvirent
So I have my laptop, which
Thank god, I have the MacBook Pro
Man, I'm loving this thing so much
Oh, it loves me back, believe me
Although I must say, my favorite streaming porn sites
Don't work too well, I'm flip for Mac, that kind of sucks
You know, the native windows on windows media
Play on windows does the streaming porn
Much better if it's windows media
Streaming porn, but that's okay
I can even even with that problem
I still love my MacBook Pro
And she loves me back
Then of course I have my cell phone
Which is really for me
Having used the iPhone, having used the E61I
I just really need something that's going to have a
Long, long battery lifetime
That's not going to last the seven hours
They apparently work in Cupertino
Because that's how long the iPhone battery lasts
Seven hours, that's it
And if you're not a near computer
Or you don't have all the appropriate
You know, wires and dongles and threads
Then it's very difficult to charge and it just sucks
It's just no good
You know, the E61 has the camera
It has the Wi-Fi, it has all that stuff
Now the web browsing experiences of course
Subpar
Compared to the iPhone certainly
Because what the iPhone has with that zoom
One thing and you know, navigate around a web page
No one has even come close to that
And not on the N8010 either
However
And maybe this is the best place to start
With the telling you about this device
It has a Mozilla browser in it
Which is 100%
I have not been able to find any flaw
100% compatible with all of the Google services
So Gmail works on it
Full browser, full view mode
They've actually fixed the zoom
Feature on the A10
So when you zoom in it
It's much faster
It basically just really zooms in the picture
Or the webpage quick
And you still have to, you know, navigate
Which you can do with your finger or you can do with the scroll button
But the cool thing is
All of the keyboard shortcuts work
And this, oh my goodness
To sit there and hit J for the next message
Or hit Y to archive something
Or hit C to compose
And then start typing an email address
And it's actually doing what Gmail does
I'm a computer and it's starting to give me all the possible email addresses
I want to reach
Fucking beautiful
Thank you so much
I was showing Neil Dixon
I was showing it to Neil Dixon on Wednesday at the office
I was poking his eye out with it
Ah man he's so jealous
I love it
Just love seeing him turn green
Kind of what had sales we saw
Chris did to me when he had the zero zero version
And was poking my eye out with it
And then Neil said
Oh, so it doesn't do Google Docs
I hadn't tried yet
So I tried to Docs.google.com
Completely works
100% beautiful fast snappy
Oh
That pretty much
Cleansed the deal for me right there
But there's more
There is more
Hey Adam it's tonight
I will from the UK
I'm sort of reading area
I just posed your podcast
Which I'll be listening to for a while
That's very much appreciate
And you just don't about me
It's the M800 series again
Which I greet as like a stomping device
And I'm holding out for a converged one
All the little things I need
I check out the suggestion
Check it out the
Neil 1973 from FIC
I don't know if you come across this
It's an open source phone
Where it's all of the other
But some pieces thrown in
Because I personally hate carrying out two things
I don't know if I've gone any
Under that I just won't have it with me
So yeah
That's it
Oh yeah
Into the guy who's here to fuck you
To the fuck you Adam Curry site
Just for good now
Say fuck you fuck you
Fuck you Adam Curry man
So yeah
And fuck you Adam Curry
Thanks my friend
Very nice
Most of the applications of the same
Skype isn't working yet
I think it's supposed to be fixed today
That's a known bug
And they're making that work
Of course Skype is another big part of my
Communications infrastructure
This device it really fits right in the middle
You know when I'm sitting downstairs
Or I'm just walking around the house
Or even in the office I just want to
Get something on the web really quickly
Because that's really what I use it for
90% of the time
It does have G-talk in there
And it has a camera built in
So you can do video conferencing
I don't think it'll work with the
With eye chat
Haven't actually tried
It may
If you set it up through whatever
Protocol
It might work
But it really doesn't matter too much for me
The keyboard is obviously
When you have a tactile physical keyboard
It's just going to be easier for typing
Less typos
And of course I have to learn the keyboard
Because it's so it's pretty broad
I must say that the top row of keys
Are a little hard for me to punch in
Because you're basically hitting up against the top of the case
So the top line of keys
Which in this case is the Q-W-E-R-T-Y
And the numbers are accessed through the function key
On those keys
Which I use a lot
Use numbers a lot when typing
It does take a little bit of getting used to
So you're not hitting the key below it
In fact I wouldn't have mind that if it could slide out
Just five millimeters more
It would have been perfect but I'm not really going to complain
Try it on the train
Had my MP3s
I've loaded up the video center
Which I don't think has been officially released yet
Of course that does have a pod show feed in it
Videos look beautiful
Sound is fantastic
The media player
Big improvement
This of course is also the new operating system
It's OS 2008
Honestly I just can't say enough nice things about it
And it's really because
It's a feel
You know when you have a device in your hand
And you know how the software reacts
And how the user interface reacts
And it can feel
Well it's like windows mobile
Which by the way has all of these functionalities
They've got fantastic smartphones
But it just feels
The cheap
I don't know what it is
It doesn't make me feel good
You know because what does this thing cost?
400 bucks
I mean it's not a cheap device
And I'm sure these smartphones aren't entirely cheap
But it doesn't even matter to me
It's just the feeling of robustness
That it's solid
And that I am in control of the device
And I'm not waiting after I issue a command
Or click on something to see if it pops up
It seems almost twice as fast
With some functions
Particularly with the web browser over the N800
I can't say enough nice things about it
Let me give you some downsides
Of course they've gone into miniaturization once again
So the last time they shrunk down a device
Which resulted in the N800
We wound up with a new ant dick power plug
Which I find horrendous
Because if it drops off the nightstand
Then it's charging
And the ant dick can break off very easily
It's a really really thin little poker thing
That you used to charge the device
I wouldn't have mind of being able to charge it
Through USB port
Of course I'd say that for all of the Nokia devices
I don't think any of them actually does that
Maybe it's a special cable for it
But I haven't come across it
They've also miniaturized the USB port
Which I understand why they do it to make things smaller
But of course now I have one specific USB cable
That will work on this and I can't use the 15 other USB cables
I have lying around my life
Whenever I need one I know I can grab one from somewhere
So you have to now carry the special USB cable
That bites
Oh and the so it has an internal memory card
A two gig memory card which is nice
And then you have an external memory card
Which is accessible through the front of the device
And guess what?
They've shrunk that one down as well
So instead of the regular memory card
I think it's now a mini SD
So all of the data had carefully backed up
From the N800 onto my card
I of course could not bring back to life
On the A10 because the memory card wouldn't fit
I hate it when Nokia does that
It's annoying
It's not the upgrade path
I was looking for exactly
And of course the beautiful leather at case that I had
For the 800 no longer fits
And this device is actually physically thinner
And not quite as wide although the screen is at least the same size
Of not bigger
And that's really those are about the only downside
You know I'm figuring out the interface
Again, it does not have the beauty of the iPhone
You know pinch open to zoom
In fact, Nokia is pretty good at licensing
If that was available I'd tell them to go license that
In a heartbeat because that would make it
In fact, I saw sales weasel Chris
Showing me something on his N00 device
You know I'm so cool I have mine before everybody else
And I saw him do a pinch move on
Like dude it's not an iPhone
He's like oh yeah that's right
I gotta use this button over here
They're not far off from it
So as I discover more I'll be telling you more about it
Of course
It's my life from Birmingham in England
I just thought I'd like to let me know
I've got one of those
Nokia 810s on order
For my expenses and I'm looking forward to it
When I do get it and say with it
I'll let you know how I feel about it
I wish I knew you was going to order some
And put it out there
Some sort of offer to like I'm going to stick with it
And get one of the only ones and just go with it
I just like the idea of it and it's better to give this into
You talk about the 810 or your previous versions
So start right, have a play everyone
So go on and pre-order
And hopefully I'll get it soon
I'll get released
Fuck you I don't care
Yo yo
Thank you
And let me know what you think of it
Actually I'm going to go to the
I'll put a link in the show notes
So you can at least buy one
I think through Amazon
Let me just see what their price is
Of the device today
It's probably going to take another three or four weeks
I think before
Before a potchoke
And offered to you at this awesome price
That we've been working on with the folks in Finland
And 99 cents of 450
So 200
About 220 pounds
Hey British people
Oh you guys doing by the way
I haven't heard a lot from you
Of course you got Charles
A drunken Londoner
A couple people calling in
But what's going on with you guys
Have you have you gone silent on me?
Is it because 25 million records of
People receiving child support
Has gone missing
Been stolen from the government
Is that why we're all hiding?
Why we're all being real quiet?
Or is it perhaps because you're waiting for
The hit test?
One girl in casting
With Adam Curry
Hey Adam
Are you ready to be stumped
Because he used that film test
With young pro men
Hey Adam
This is hit test number
97 and we got to start right away with intro
Number Rocker
So I'd uh
That just won
That's in that zoom
Not zoom
But zoom
I can't remember who was by zoom
Number two
Yeah
That's right
It's a rhythm
It's my girl Grace Jones
Hit me with number three
Young
And the final one is number three
That one I don't know
I've got one and a half stars at least
Cause I didn't know who did zoom
And time's up and these are the answers
Answer number one from 1982
Fed Larry's fan
Larry's fan
Alright
Just one look
And we were on the moon
Lion high
Hit a neon sky
Oh
So
Change the name
Oh
What a great song
Fed Larry's fan
Then zoom is answer number one
And this is answer number two from 1985
Grace Jones and slave to the rhythm
On day
To keep the
And this is the third and final order from 1987. Swing out sisters.
Oh, Render.
Sorry, I don't know this one.
Oh, I'm just quiet.
Swing out sister and surrender as answer number three in hit test number 97.
So Adam, how did you do?
I wanted a half star, so yeah.
Anyway, if you want to know how you did in every hit test and what you ever score is,
you have to wait a few weeks because in a few weeks time, I'll have some statistics ready for you.
Oh, that's all I need.
I don't know if you're going to be happy with the end result, but very fair.
That's probably not true.
Alrighty, the answers to this hit test and also the items linked so you can buy these tricks.
Online can be found at hittest.parcio.com.
The next week I'll be back for hit test number 98.
So until then, take care and bye-bye.
We'll be back.
Hit test and she will not come in.
Oh, young bullet.com.
J-N-P-O-L-E-T-S-O.
Hey, y'all, and we're moving up on number 100.
This is fantastic.
As Y'all said, all of these songs can be found at hittest.podshow.com.
And you can click on the iTunes links and go buy them at the iTunes store.
It's a great way to fill up your iPod with the great songs from the soundtrack of your life.
And of course, we're continuing to build our soundtrack to our lives.
We'll do that together.
And it's that time again.
It's the Christmas season.
So it's time for some Christmas songs on the Charlie hand.
Which was a night before Christmas.
My face was a grin.
Because I found free music on the PMN.
A y'all, this is Jeff Smith, from the Podset Music Network.
We should do a Merry Christmas Happy New Year.
That's right.
Hey, buddy.
Send off some nice holiday cheer-art way.
I'm sending it to your family.
Of course, if you know.
What do you do?
One of the things we'll come in.
I was feeling blue.
And the presents for my family and friends.
Now we'll get to give back its December.
As a sad looking in my room.
My side is sweater from the end too.
And the idea made me like a food to the head.
Going get that sweater to my cousin's head.
I'm reaching for the holidays.
I'm packing up all that crap.
I'm adding it back.
I'm giving it to someone new.
I'm reaching for that baby.
I'm packing up all that crap.
I'm adding it back.
I'm giving it to someone new.
Send the bills and some fuzzy dives.
Today I'll be looking at a quarter-old slice.
It's a sandwich maker.
No one in the dark.
You aren't gonna get in there to beat yourself up.
Feel so rich, ray of lads, if I get a boo.
My dark glass around me has struck.
Share my golden CDs.
I'm coming from the misery that we're looking at.
I'm reaching for the holidays.
I'm packing up all that crap.
I'm adding it back.
I'm giving it to someone new.
I'm reaching for that baby.
I'm packing up all that crap.
I'm giving it to someone new.
I'm reaching for that baby.
Nothing like regifting for the holidays.
The Alice project.
You can find them on the podcast.
Music.
Now working, of course, link in the show notes.
It's a daily source code.com.
Speaking of phones, devices.
This is pretty funny.
It's a story about an iPhone.
I've got this in an email from Duke Garin.
I think who works for a major airline.
The link to plainbuzz.com, which of course I'll put in the show notes.
It's a daily source code.com.
This is about passengers with iPhones.
Okay.
Let me see.
My captain did the lecture over the public address system as they had just pushed back.
And the advice of a ground stop in Memphis due to storms in the area.
Then a minute later, the flight attendant dings up to the cockpit and says,
You know, some guy with an iPhone says the weather's good.
And once know what the real reason is for the delay is something wrong with the plane.
So, you know, what a scenario, right?
And of course, these things happen.
You can expect that you're on a flight.
You know, someone has an iPhone in the back.
You're piloting command.
And you say, hey, look, we got to do a ground stop in Memphis for due to weather.
And people are looking up on their iPhone.
Of course, getting unsophisticated non-aviation based weather from like weather.com or something or whatever
The iPhone standard weather widgets are.
And then I guess it may be worried.
So the captain gets on the public address system and says the following.
If the passenger with the iPhone would be kind enough to use it to check the weather at our alternate.
Calculate our fuel burn due to being rerouted around the storms.
Call the dispatcher to arrange our release and make a phone call to the nearest air traffic control center
to arrange our timely departure amongst the other aircraft carrying passengers with iPhones.
They'll be more than happy to depart.
Please just ring your call button to advise the flight attendant and your fellow passengers when you don't when you deem it ready.
And responsible for this multi-million dollar aircraft that is passengers to leave safely.
Ah, yes.
There's nothing like a good use of the public address system in there.
Adam, hey, the motion on to the California air.
Just finished listening to no agenda for and fired up just 690.
Um, what's that, you man?
You and John Vorac came up so perfectly.
I'd like to guys have been talking with each other for the last 20, 30 years as a, as a talk radio team.
We have a local team like that that actually simultaneously has been the area.
Um, a local radio station.
And you guys hit it off easily as well as they do.
I don't know if you've listened to them there.
They're on here in the air and in the area from 6 to 10 a.m.
But, um, just want to tell you, man, no agenda rocks.
And, uh, you need to get a good team for that.
I don't care if you say there's no team.
You need a good team.
But, uh, fuck you.
I'm curry, scruncher, and go home and punch.
That's amazing.
Right on, man.
I was just actually looking, uh, someone did sent, not a, someone didn't,
didn't send me a theme song.
I was sent a, um, I can't find it now.
Crap.
I don't know where it is.
Maybe it's, uh, maybe it's a wave file.
Hold on.
Let me see what I can find it.
Yeah.
I sent a John to Vorac and note.
I can't find it.
What the hell was up with that?
I try this.
Let me try my good old, uh, Google desktop search.
Um, I ping them and said, are we doing a show today?
Because, of course, in the States, it's a holiday, um, both today, uh, both,
yet today and yesterday.
I just see no agenda, no agenda.
Fuck.
I don't know.
Someone sent me.
I know who sent that to me.
I'll find it.
Maybe I'll use that.
If not, you know, I don't know.
It just feels right.
You know, to just start yapping and not have an agenda.
Not have any jingles or anything like that.
And I, uh, I like talking to John.
And that's really all we're doing.
I, I, I must admit, I forget that I'm actually, you know, recording anything.
We're just talking like we do, uh, when, uh, when we're at the office or if we have lunch or something like that.
And, uh, and he's a smart guy.
He's pretty knowledgeable.
About a lot of, a lot of different shit.
He keeps amazing.
He went this stuff.
He knows about.
And that sent me an email.
And it's just pretty weird.
I have not received one of these, but apparently, number of people are getting messages from Skype.
Telling them that their London Skype in number is changing.
Which is fucked up.
Here's an exact sent me a sample of the email.
Hello.
I love the way Skype brought the talks to their customers.
Customer.
We're very sorry to tell you that we have to change your Skype in number.
As some of you may know, apparently, only the smart customers.
We get Skype in numbers from a variety of telecom suppliers.
Unfortunately, we have to return some of the O2O7 Skype numbers to one of our suppliers of London numbers.
This means your number will stop working from December 20th, 2007.
We apologize and realize the inconvenience this will cause you.
Again, we sincerely apologize.
How lame is that?
I don't have a, do I have an O2O7?
Let me see.
What's my number again in the UK?
I can't quite remember.
Let's see if it's O2O7.
Okay.
Crap.
161, 3753, plus 44, 207, 161, 3753.
Well, that sucks.
I guess my number is changing too for the UK.
What does that, it's a Korean new jingles then.
This is an outrage.
Why have I received a message about this?
Skypeers?
Oh, this is not good.
Let me see.
Matt says, I've had the same number for over two years.
And use it for business quite a bit.
Now they give me one month's notice.
Following the recent 2007, no.
Following the recent O2O7 outage, oh, I guess there was a problem.
Some people did call it and say there was a problem with the UK number.
Following the recent O2O7 outage, this company is turning into a joke.
Great for free services, but any paid service is hopeless.
Pretty outrageous, really.
Yeah, I agree, man.
That sucks.
Oh, well, it's all part of what Fubar has become, I guess.
Just looking at some Ron Paul stats.
This is great.
I'd love this one who sent me this.
This is sent to me by Mike Feldabor.
I sent me a Google page count.
People looking X for president.
So X would be one of the names.
And at the top, I see a number three is Hillary Clinton with about 300,000 results.
John Edwards with a little more than Hillary Clinton.
And then Ron Paul with almost a million.
It's a great graph.
I don't know exactly what it means.
But I'm really hoping.
I'm really hoping that what it means is that the mainstream media is just not catching on to what the public is really saying or what they're thinking.
Either that or we have a very small group of people doing this.
All group of people doing a hell of a lot of work.
One of the other will find out soon in the primaries.
Hey, Adam, there's a woman.
I'm in San Francisco and you're not once again.
Fly out here and we always seem to miss each other.
But I get stopped by the officers.
I got to go to both officers and I saw Kevin, Moody, Natalie, Lisa.
I hit a bunch of people there and I say everybody is heads down, working hard.
Hey, Robin, don't be hitting my people over there.
So I just wanted to thank everybody publicly for working so hard to make much so better.
I also want to give a special thanks to Richard who is always a class act.
So once again, this is Robin.
Beautiful day.
Looking at my window here and just from the flying perspective.
I have okay.
You know, yeah.
At least 200 miles there's a building.
I'm looking forward to taking off out of here.
Very soon.
All right.
Tailwinds, my friend.
And we'll talk again soon.
Yeah.
Back at your Robin.
Tailwinds to you.
And there's nothing, an airman likes hearing more than cavo.
Okay.
And it was cavo.
This morning here.
I know I'm leaving Sunday, but I'm really contemplating.
I don't give a shit.
What kind of weather it is tomorrow?
I've got it cranked the engine on the Delta share.
She hasn't flown for like what a month now.
She's got to fly.
You know, I don't think it's good to just leave your aircraft sitting around unflown.
Even though it's inside, it's nice in the hangar.
You know, it's all dry and warm and cozy.
That's not a good idea.
And I'm going to be gone for another week.
Crap.
Here's what I missed.
I don't know if I'd missed it in email or, you know, I'd put it in a folder somewhere
but it was a good piece of feedback from our buddy.
Oh, shit.
You know what?
It's time for his jingle.
Hey, buddy.
We love you.
Coming up with something really important to say.
He is our satellite repairman.
The satellite repairman's coming after you.
The satellite repairman works he can't do.
He'll fix your misconceptions and answer questions too.
There's nothing in the universe and he can't do for you.
The satellite repairman.
Woo!
Here.
Come on in, Peter.
Go, Adam.
Peedub.
On Tuesday, you had this to say about the writer's strike.
Because I don't believe they're going to work this out.
In fact, I think it's very difficult to work out this writer's strike because,
well, quite honestly, you know, it's very,
and complicated to make money online with, with video.
No one's really making any, we're making money.
It's costing a lot still to do it.
But, you know, look at the YouTube.
I don't even see any ads.
Let alone a few.
Just look at, you know, many other sites out there.
The known is really making a lot of money.
Dude, what are you talking about?
What does making money have to do with it?
If the studios aren't making any money off the internet,
then why wouldn't they be willing to agree to pay a few percent of what they make
to the writers?
Isn't three or four percent of nothing?
Nothing?
What's so hard about agreeing to pay nothing?
The only possible answer is that they would have to pay something.
Because, despite what you say, they are, in fact, making something.
Dude, nobody refuses to pay nothing.
Dude, you're talking about profit.
There's one thing we know in Hollywood.
There is never any profit.
And they don't receive a percentage of the sales price of DVDs or the retail price.
They receive a fixed amount per disc that is pressed.
There's an entire infrastructure set up, which, of course, is full of holes and back doors
and stuff the drops off the truck.
And there's all kinds of shan against going on.
But in just because it's the same as the record business in general.
There is a pretty good system of counting how many CDs went out and exactly who deserves
money from each individual CD.
It's not a percentage of the profit of the CD, which, by the way, is the real issue here.
That's where real money is being made.
And, of course, the studios and whoever else is on the other side of the table from the writers
fuck the writers, because they said that they actually would up there, you know, make them whole
or whatever term they used.
But they never did.
So, you know, that is a big problem.
Just add on top of that, that they're lying to the writers by saying,
you know, that online version of the show, the episode we put up there for people to watch,
that's promotional activity.
So, you know, it's like, of course, there's all kinds of bullshit going on.
But it's just not the same thing.
You know, a one single video viewed by one person.
You can't really define the price of that, the revenue because advertising
is a whole different way of making money on a product or on a service.
So, it's not that they don't deserve anything.
It's not that they shouldn't have any piece of the pie.
You know, I understand where they're coming from.
But the whole idea of residuals is going to be problematic moving forward.
It really is because a residual is basically money you're making off of a copy.
There you go.
A copy of a piece of work that is used in, you know, usually a typical
and syndication or a DVD format.
But it's, you know, now we have a whole different revenue model.
I like what Jack Myers is saying at jackmires.com.
He says the advertising agencies who have great benefit from advertising
on online video and audio.
They are the ones that should be putting money aside for the writers
and giving it up, you know, through some understandable key,
I guess, some understandable way of slicing and dicing the money.
But that's even before it hits the studios.
It's, it's really a good way to do it.
I don't think it'll ever happen.
Well, actually, that would be kind of interesting.
Wouldn't it be interesting if the writers just went to work for the advertising companies
directly and cut out the entire studio?
Hmm.
That's something there, I think.
Hey, hey, Adam, this is Miss Angelica Jinks and...
What?
Otherwise known as Naive London Girl.
It's feeling like a red pill sort of morning here.
Now, I know Adam, you listen to our podcast,
but I would love, love, love it.
If something you're regular listeners, check us out as well.
Yeah, I do listen to your show.
And it's dirty.
That's all I can say.
You guys have a dirty ass show.
Naive London Girl dot pod show dot com.
This month, Wanda and I are chatting about sex while you're on vacation.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's hot holiday sex.
Exposing your affair to your lover's wife.
Cocaine and my hot lesbian sex.
I'm telling you, this is a great show.
Sex during menstruation and my very favorite topic.
Kind of linguists.
Hmm.
Now, it's amateur talk, so adults only.
Yeah.
That's Naive London Girl dot pod show dot com.
It's Tim Curry.
No, no, it's Adam Curry.
It's so freaking tall.
He's really tall.
He's so tall.
He's like a foot and a half tall.
He's got longevity and a long willy.
All right, then.
Naive London Girl.
If you really want to hear what women are saying behind closed doors,
you don't even need to open the door.
They talk so loud.
You're like Naive London Girl dot pod show dot com.
Hi, Adam.
It's Matt from Games Weasel.
On this week's show, we've got a review of Call of Duty 4 Modern Warfare.
Also, we're going to the Olympic Games with Mario and Sonic.
I've downloaded some great games on the Wii and the Xbox 360.
We'll let you know how they play.
And you can win copies of A's Combat 6 for the 360.
That's all at gamesweasel.beteepotshow.com.
Yo, thank you very much, Matt.
I gotta give me a Wii, man.
Sounds like too many people are having fun without me on this device.
They would fit perfectly here in the manner.
You know, this is the kind of song that works so well when it's kind of cold
and dark outside.
If you want that kind of warm Jamaica feeling,
10CC doesn't for you.
I was walking down the street.
Concentrating on truck and ride.
I heard a dog push beside of me.
And I looked around in the state of fright.
I saw four places.
One man, a brother from the gutter.
They look me up and down the deck.
They turn to each other.
I say, I don't like wicked stuff.
I don't know.
I love it, don't.
I don't like wicked stuff.
I don't know.
I love it, don't.
I don't know how to love it.
You got to show some respect.
I watch the whole evening.
Well, you look down at my silver chain.
You said, I'll give you one dollar.
I said, you got to give your demand.
It was a present from my mother.
She said, I like it.
I want it.
I'll take it off your hand.
And you'll be sorry.
You cross with.
You better understand it.
I say, I don't like wicked stuff.
I don't know.
I love it, don't.
I don't like wicked stuff.
I don't like this guy.
I don't know how to love it.
I don't like wicked stuff.
I heard it, but I don't know how to love it.
I've been a girl, I don't know how to love it.
I heard it, but I don't like this guy.
I don't like something, how to love it.
She said, I got it.
I want it.
I don't like to make up.
I don't.
I love it.
I don't like to make up.
10cc's dreadlock holiday wrapping up another week as we get closer to the end of 2007
closer to the beginning of 2008
Alright
Yeah, that's actually what's mean a good mood
I think we should just stop the show here
Exactly the kind of song that can take me carry me over this Friday
Into the weekend
DailyStoresCode.com is where you can find all the show notes
From a podshow.com if you want to send me a message
The next program will be coming to you
From the Curry condo in Northern California
I will talk to you guys on Monday
Have a great weekend
Live your life with passion
And enjoy your freedom
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best and the brightest
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content
Delivering podshow and limelight