It's time you've got in the game.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Get a domain name, free-click blog, and complete email.
Get in the game at GoDaddy.com.
Delta, Serator, daily source code, five, seven, seven.
A $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just thinking it's a curry.
If you're pissed off, like old nylon, you might feel better if you get pissed off.
If you're all tanks, like CSB, just relax.
And on zip, on zip with me, you're in trap-ball.
On a new curry, scalded out at this day, you're in trap-ball.
On a new curry, scalded out at this day.
To this house, a bed of goods.
If you shot you in the head, just like John Wiltberg.
So just relax.
And don't stop screaming.
It's about about to start screaming.
You're in trap-ball.
On a new curry, scalded out at this day.
Ah, thank you.
Mark Yoshimura Nympha for the...
You're in trouble, son.
Okay.
Golden shower Thursday, Mark.
Everybody, it's Daily Source Code 577 coming to you from the curry condo in San Francisco, Northern, California.
Hangin' out.
This is disgusting.
It's okay.
Golden showers are fine as long as you're business sitting down.
It's Thursday morning for most of the world.
Of course, California, someone behind the times has always in the weird time zone.
It is early for me right now.
It's 11.15 pm on Wednesday evening.
So I'm kind of moving to Thursday already.
I had another fantastic day here in San Fran after a horrible night.
I don't know.
Of course, you heard yesterday show and you heard my frustrations and shit breaking all over the place.
And then after I finally salvaged the file from Casplaster, which just would not save it properly,
it failed to upload to the podcast, delivery network and I had, well, we have 24 hours.
We have our guys up 24 hours a day now.
So I was able to get a hold of somebody and turned out that something had burped at just the moment.
I was uploading and all this stuff is going on.
And it was not very pretty.
So of course, so the show didn't get uploaded until the morning,
PST.
So it was late.
I'm sorry.
I don't even know when you guys listen to the show.
Because I released it at such a different time.
So maybe you're just to get in your day started.
Maybe you've already had your full day and I hope you had a good one.
I got to tell you this, there's something.
I have a problem, a physical problem that I haven't told you guys about.
There's been building up over the past week.
And I might as well tell you because, well, it'll make me feel better if I talk about it
because I hate it.
And it's, this makes a sound a lot worse than it is.
And I don't like what I have to do to fix it.
You know what tennis elbow is?
I think I've also heard of skateboard ankle, but you know,
if you, if you somehow if you overuse your arm and I guess your elbow and other joints while playing
too much tennis, then you can develop tennis elbow, which is the equivalent.
Well, you know, it's, and it hurts and it can even swell up and it can probably be you from playing.
I have something that I've had twice before in my life in the past seven years.
And, and I'm equating it to tennis elbow because I have headphone earlobe.
Yeah, okay, I'll wait until you pick yourself up off of the floor.
My right earlobe is something.
Whenever I'm using headphones excessively, and of course, I really be doing a lot of production.
How did the headphones on?
Really tight for long periods of time.
Been wearing them. And of course, extremely tight air tight headphones in in the Delta share.
I want to, you know, flying around.
What happens is my earlobe.
It's like there's an infection like an abscess, I guess, inside my right earlobe.
And it grows and it starts to swell up.
And the only thing that that can fix it is I have to go to the doctor.
And they have to cut it open and it basically let all the gunk out.
And then it's over.
And then, you know, then I feel fine. And I wear a bandaid for a day or two.
But it's, you know, it's that build up. I know it's coming.
I know, and it's, you know, starting to like, it feels like my ear is glowing.
And of course, whenever I put headphones on, it's a million times worse.
Anyway, so this afternoon, just this evening before we left,
I asked Rosie find a doctor for me.
You can do this because it's going to get really bad.
And, uh, yes, headphone earlobe.
It exists.
And I have it.
Adam, hey, this is Mark Kelser and Hollywood California right now.
And I'm listening to five, seven, six.
And, uh, I got to tell you, uh, listening to cruise box.
I heard it on a podcast, that podcast song.
It brought back some memories.
You know, I've been listening to podcasts for a long time.
And, uh, and I got to give you a major compliment.
So, call it kiss your ass or whatever.
But, you know, you've done it.
You haven't podcasted it.
Um, you've got the same energy the same drive.
Um, and, uh, my hats off to you.
I, I listen, I kind of listen to you.
And then I come back and I, you know, after a while, and I listen to you again.
And you, you, uh, that energy is just amazing.
So, uh, we've come a long way.
I mean podcasting has come a long way.
And I'm looking at all these people in Hollywood right now on the streets.
And now I want to, you know, be something famous.
And, uh, I wonder how many people really want to do that work once they become famous.
You know, it's hard work.
And, uh, congratulations, dude.
And all the best to you and all those people out there that are getting people like me to listen and watch.
I really appreciate it.
Oh, Mark, thank you.
I was waiting for a folder of scruncher tagline there.
Uh, Mark, thanks for calling it and appreciate that.
That's really nice of you to say.
Yeah, it's consistency.
Uh, it's not hard to do though.
I tell you every single day, no matter what time of day I'm always excited about doing the show because first of all,
every one of my life knows I'm doing the show so that leave me alone.
And it's like, hey, doing a show.
So just let him be.
So it's nice because I get along fine with myself and my friends here on the Charlie.
And, um, and the stuff you guys send in, it makes it really easy to do.
It really does.
And at least for my show, it does.
Yep.
I think, uh, I think we're, we're definitely, uh, we're definitely growing.
Uh, I, in fact, I know we're growing.
We have this, uh, this big, uh, technology move coming up on Friday the 13th.
So not this Friday, but next Friday.
And, uh, this is going to be big.
Um, so we're moving into, uh, into our own location.
Um, you know, there's, we're moving on.
We were, uh, we were still, uh, at Rackspace.
Not with our media hosting, but with all our applications.
And, uh, you know, we've had, um,
we've had, uh, experiences where our application brought down all of Rackspace.
You know, there's just, like, so all of a sudden we'll have a surge of traffic or something happens.
And we really need to, to set ourselves up for us.
You know, not to fail, not to die under success.
So that's happening Friday the 13th and then we've been doing a lot of work, um,
well, of engineering and operations, of course.
I'm doing a shitload of work to, to, to prepare to get this done.
Um, but on the 13th itself, of course,
we, you know, it's always prime time somewhere.
It's always download time somewhere.
So there's no perfect time to pick, you know,
you can say middle of the night, but, you know,
that's next week in Australia.
And, uh, and yesterday in Hawaii, you know,
it's like, you can't choose a good time Friday.
I think is reasonable because, uh,
uh, that is typically when traffic is the lowest across the board of, uh,
uh, and all countries, uh, from, you know,
Friday to Saturday and Friday is reasons.
So, uh, everyone's given up there, uh,
a good chunk of their weekend, I'm sure.
And we'll, we will be down for several hours,
but we're preparing a lot of stuff,
uh, behind the scenes look at, uh,
what's going on, you know,
just a typical pod show style, you know,
and where my space gives you a Tetris game to play.
Uh, we're going to give you content.
So, um, uh, before warned,
and you'll be hearing a lot more about this in the coming week,
as, uh, every single show in the network will be aware
that it's just going to happen.
Of course advertisers, all kinds of people.
And it's very different from a year ago
when we would relaunch or, or change something.
And we also have, you know,
changes to the interface coming.
We're not going to do it all in one go,
but it's going to be, you know, uh,
day upon day, week upon week and, uh,
good shit on the way.
Uh, let me see.
Checking the, uh, the Gmail,
Derek Richardson.
Hey, Adam, hope you're well.
Couldn't believe my ears.
Daily source code 575.
Flock a sea girl's awesome.
Mm-hmm.
And I love that man.
As song was like, uh, 28, 29 almost 30 years old.
You just don't hear that shit on the radio enough.
Speaking of a ran,
Neil Cochran sent me an email.
And, uh,
let's see.
Oh, he has a link here, which is probably,
you know, I'm going to save that.
You know, there's a, this whole thing about the,
the soldiers that have been there.
That have been captured and, uh,
and arrested, I guess.
What do you call that?
Um, well, I know what, uh,
President Bush calls it,
the hostages, um,
you know, and, uh, the relationship
between Britain and, uh,
and Persia or Iran.
A lot of, a lot of you writing in about that.
I, I, I may do something next week when I'm, uh,
when I'm back at the, uh,
at the manner.
And up, you know, we should really delve into that.
Because there's a lot more,
behind, you know, this story.
That's a lot more to it.
I think that's what Neil was pointing out.
Uh, we see was, uh,
weird stand of comedy lecturers on TV last year.
Robert Newman's history of oil.
Uh, Robert Newman's a comedian,
although he's more a political activist,
as you'll see in the clip.
You should give it a look as a couple of
snigger word, snigger.
Snigger word of the parts,
but it really got me,
it's really got me thinking.
Well, you know what?
Let's just have a quick check sewing.
Let me just open up the, uh,
the web browser audio port here.
See if there's any narration.
Robert Newman's history of oil.
I'll definitely put a link to this in the show notes
at dailysourcecode.com.
The terrifying 100 year history of oil.
Okay, I'm bored.
I can hear you are, least.
Anything else in the ran that I want to do today?
Let's see.
James.
15 sailors and marines captured allegedly in Iranian waters.
14 men, one women.
One woman.
Doesn't take a genius to work out who had the map does it.
No.
You're right.
Sex, drugs, and coffee to ho, is a novel.
It's the story of a single week in the summer of 2006.
I'll be reading the 39 chapters as a weekly audio podcast.
A bit like an audio port, right?
But there's more.
A central figure, the heroine, perhaps,
the catalyst certainly is Alice.
Okay.
I told Jack a lot about last summer.
How strange it was, and he talked to many of the others too.
But shit, I never expected him to write a book about it.
Alice's weekly video blog is her way of thinking back to last summer,
making sense of what happened and changed so many lives,
at least the lives of those who survived.
She was there in July in the South of France.
Sex and drugs and coffee to oil tells her story.
You weren't.
Or were you?
Watch her video blog.
It's easy to find on BT Podshow or at www.Alice and Paris 2007.
All is one word.com.
You know, those of you have been listening for a while.
That's Malcolm from Abu Dhabi.
He's been working on this project for quite a while,
and it's very interesting, of course,
only as you would expect Malcolm to do.
If you ever heard Malcolm on the show, he's got this haunting voice,
and he's been in entertainment for a while,
longer than myself, I might say.
I don't want to put any age on him,
but he's done the music video for David Bowie.
One of the early ones.
And so this sex and drugs and coffee to hold.
If I'm pronouncing it correctly,
it's part video blog and it's part audio novel,
and it's really worth checking out.
So I'll put a link to that in the show, no, says well.
Just all kinds of gems today.
I got a couple of people emailing me this story.
About this is amazing.
You have to see the pictures,
because it's going to drive you crazy.
See, this is Andrew Terry sent me this,
who else sent me this.
Sinclair, of course.
Under different subject headings,
one is better run.
They found your old house in Tennessee.
The other one is redefining the term,
hot hole.
You're not going to believe this.
Law enforcement officers in Tennessee,
make the greatest underground discovery
since Tutic Ammon's tomb was unearthed
in the valley of the kings.
Under this ordinary house,
and this picture of indeed a very ordinary house,
a marijuana grow up.
That would be a plantation, I guess.
Unlike any you've ever seen with caves
of middle Tennessee,
growers constructed a complex of offices,
living quarters, restroom facilities,
and the climate controlled forest
of over 1,000 cannabis plants.
You should see this thing.
It's like a nuclear shelter,
only for growing weed,
and it's beautiful.
And of course,
it's everything's been confiscated,
but wow.
I mean, you can see the technology
that have 150 yard tunnel
that leads to a concealed escape hatch,
blow a hydraulic rock,
which opens up kind of like something
from Hogan's heroes.
You can't crawl underneath the fence.
Only it's hydraulic.
It's amazing.
It's just unbelievable.
I love it.
All right.
Make sure you check it.
You're going to love this.
Make sure you check out the link
at dailysourcecode.com.
Hi.
I hope this is Adam Puri.
My name is William I,
and I'm calling
because I have a new picture
on patcho.com.
That I think you would like
and my Uncle John told me
to give you a call,
but you know that I exist.
So basically what I do
is I go through different genres
every week.
Postes a plan and take about
four songs that I really like.
And then in between that,
I have co-hosts,
who are my roommates.
I'm a college student in California.
And we talk about dumb things
that are very funny
like the kids who got
goals, making of the band
on TV,
and we talk about
our roommate,
who's an area
slash a durian and her
funny ways.
And how she loves us
at the animals.
So I mean,
it's plain,
but it's pretty cool.
So if you took it
a look that would be great.
My URL
is William I,
Cecil L,
I,
M, A,
C, E, C,
I, L, L, E.
Quite a minute.
This is the prolific program
or school of URL linkage.
Let's do that again.
Just in case anyone wants
to write it down.
If you took it a look
that would be great.
My URL
is William I, Cecil L,
I, I, A, M, A,
I, C, E, C,
I, L, E.
Partial.com
or
William I, L, I, A, M, A,
and I. Partial.com
And also
I am a school nurse,
not a school nurse.
Thanks so much.
Did your uncle
young tell you to say
that when you called
him?
Hmm.
Okay.
I'll put that link in the show notes as well.
I actually had to listen to that three times to write
the URL.
But it's, it's great.
A nice podcast.
You and your girlfriend, I guess, do that.
I'd like your gallery on your,
on your podshow plus page as well.
I love the one of the two of you
in, in the, in the pool.
Didn't uncle young mention
that sending naked pictures
is very good for your downloads?
So, um, three campaigns
have ended of sponsors of this show.
They'll be renewing the next run,
I guess, um,
as you know, advertisers don't advertise
20, you know, 12 months a year.
They, they, they, they time it with product
releases and all kinds of multi, multi
dimensional, uh, initiatives.
God, that sounded very advertising like
didn't it?
Uh, so Splenda Folgers and what else?
There was another one that ended.
Uh, anyway, so we have a whole slew of new ones
coming up, at least on this show.
Uh, it's different on every show on the network.
But I think we've got, uh,
what do we have?
We have cover girl coming.
We've got, uh, Paramount.
Oh, we got an awesome show
where we're working on with Paramount, uh,
p360.
It'll be from the back lot of Paramount studios.
I'm really looking forward to that.
That's part of what we're going to be doing in Los Angeles.
Um, is, uh, is doing some pre-production on that?
Uh, what else is coming?
Shit, I don't know, man.
I'm fried.
I did get some interesting feedback about, uh,
advertisers on the daily source code, which, uh,
uh, I don't agree with, but hey,
it's a golden shower Thursday.
I had them.
This is Alexander from Stockholm.
Uh, I called you last week about
sending the receipts for the Bumnush,
the chart purchase.
Um, yeah, by the way, uh,
it's time to choose a winner, isn't it?
Uh, uh, I got to ask, uh,
I got to find out exactly how we're going to do that,
but I have a ton of receipts.
Uh, excuse me,
Tylenol TM.
It'll help you sleep.
Good for chicks.
Uh, I can't wait to send this off to Tylenol.
They're going to love it.
Uh, what was I saying?
Yeah, this is from Bumnush, the charts.
Okay.
So I got your receipt.
I've got all of them.
We're going to be doing the drawing.
I guess we'll do that next week when I get everything organized.
I'm in New Yorker in Stockholm, Sweden,
and I guess my BSE handle would be
the new Sweden or something like that.
Anyway, I wanted to say something about
Splendent and Folgers.
Um, I'm a huge fan of your show and of what you're doing.
And, uh,
the production of your show and, um,
and, um, it seems that just about everything in your life
is very high quality.
And, uh,
you enjoy, you know, uh,
virgin upper class and your airplane and, uh,
Patricia seems to, uh, really, uh,
enjoy the finer things in life here.
But, um,
now that you've, uh, ended your contract
apparently with Splendent and Folgers,
I have to say that, uh,
those are both very, uh,
to, uh, to me, um,
poor, uh,
product and poor quality.
Um, now you see,
this is where, uh,
at first I'm like,
okay, it's pretty interesting.
Guy wants a handle.
He's the new sweet.
He's getting into stuff.
He's been listening and,
and he under clearly understands
my level of sophistication in life.
And, uh,
and now he's saying that these are poor products.
Uh,
I can hear coffee drinkers everywhere going.
I completely agree with the coffee roaster
that called in the other day saying that,
you know,
coffee goes stale after
what did he say 14 days?
There's something like that, huh?
And also Splendent.
I mean,
what's going on?
It's, it's like, uh,
it's like,
a chemical that tastes like sugar.
I mean,
technically not correct.
It is actually made from sugar.
If you would really pay attention to the,
uh,
to the conversation about it,
then you would have known that.
It's not just,
it's not a chemical.
Mm-hmm.
It's all bunch of chemicals.
But it's made from sugar,
and it really works and tastes good.
Sugar would be a better thing,
because it's a natural,
you know,
grown product from nature,
but sake sugar,
chemically,
you know,
well,
you know what I'm saying.
Anyway,
Yeah.
I think that a,
um,
a show like yours should choose
if sponsors more carefully,
I think.
Now,
this is,
now I really got interested by this,
because one thing is very clear
to the new sweet,
is that I'm choosing my sponsors.
I'm glad you,
you feel that that is,
I mean,
you don't,
I guess you don't,
didn't even think about it.
You just saying it as if it's fact.
And it is true.
Um,
And I think I've said many times before.
You're going to see advertisers,
probably auditioning to be on,
on certain programs,
on maybe on any program.
For that matter.
Um,
and,
there are,
man,
there's,
there's lots of sponsorships
and advertisements that I turn down for this show.
Um,
I'll give an example.
I won't name exactly which company,
but I will tell you,
a company,
an oil company.
And I turned it down.
I said,
no, thank you.
You know,
and they advertise on the network on other shows,
that we're all,
you know,
all to happy to endorse the product or their initiative,
which actually wasn't,
wasn't bad at all,
but I just like,
I don't feel like I should,
you know,
I'm more about independence.
Um,
So in fact,
there is a form of auditioning happening already.
I'm sorry,
a serious satellite radio listeners.
I'll be back again
for the Fubar Friday festivities Friday night.
You take care now.
I'm a big fan of the live,
blah, blah, blah, blah.
So really,
it's,
it's very close to what you're talking about.
Um,
now advertising,
of course,
for me,
and the type of advertising we do,
which is not,
you know,
ad words or,
Google,
like relevancy track stuff,
you know,
it's only going to work if I think I,
this can appeal to each individual audience.
By the way,
we turned down lots of advertisers,
not interested in because we want brand advertising.
And brand advertising is about awareness and getting you to try something.
So,
um,
even though I was not a Fulger's coffee drinker,
I was more than happy to try it and talk about it
for the run of the campaign.
Same for Splenda.
Now,
I continue to use Fulgers.
Um,
okay,
I'm kind of cheating because I use Fulger's instant coffee,
which,
I don't know,
the taste is good to me.
So,
you know,
it's,
it's enrich my life in that way.
And for lots of people,
and they've talked about it,
and they've sent in comments,
same,
and for some,
it doesn't,
which is okay,
but to call it,
you know,
not upscale or downscale or not at my scale,
that just doesn't make any sense.
That,
your sponsors should be,
you know,
Jaguar,
like your car,
um,
I can't.
No,
they don't have to pay me.
I'll endorse their car for free.
The bird,
what your airplane is.
It's.
That's what they're.
One, eight, two.
The ground here,
airplane.
Oh, again, you know,
I'll fly,
fly and talk about it for free.
No problem.
No,
I would say.
It's not new to me.
You see,
I know that stuff.
So it's not that exciting to me.
And now,
no.
No.
Hey,
you're more of a,
you know,
magnum champagne.
Please.
Uh,
show then, uh,
I'm a dude.
I don't drink.
Please,
produce,
take sugar.
So,
um,
that's what I think.
Choose your sponsors more carefully.
Because they reflect on you,
and pod show,
and everything you do.
Thank you.
Dude,
control your kid,
William.
Now,
I appreciate what you're saying,
but,
uh,
I just have to disagree.
I grew up with folders,
Flavor crystals.
Wouldn't that fall juice?
Wasn't that from 100 years ago?
Oh, man.
I'm a,
I got to tell you.
so,
So,
Yeah, but
Like I'm a man, desolving
What's up?
We don't need you with two sides at the game
That's right
You can let us know which one she's best
Stop
What is it about?
Come on
Stop
charts
ahead, please slow down
baby
Let me see the way that you go down
I talk in the bountleton
fucking me in humans
institutional mess
No kiss in the boy & pass
Jimmy
Love waste and avoidain
have any
I wanted him to Like singing
like a breakthrough
Now
Come on
Give for the wordt walked
I should've went off
And I'm like removing
I'm sorry
Hold you by the waist, put your face up the mouth, put your face at the pillow, hold your waist from my arm
Yeah, that's a plan for the night
If you like it, I'll be your man for the night
Hey, stop, drop, drop, we see the phone
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
Are you a small trampoline now, Jesus CJ this, don't forget I can't go by the face of this bane
Let me kiss you funny first, boy, don't get hangin' here, So it's gone, let's cool, can you move your tail
Make a love on my heart and never forget I'll never, Don't cry
Try, try, what is it about?
Go together, put your weight down.
Hit the beats, do it again
Now come on, you're taking it away!
It's time man, you must send me confused, I won't let them lose, we can let them change you
My dog on bad news, I'm a real flake dude and I'm rich for a wrist look like an ace in the way
A journey so, yeah, bro.
Okay, love making
He's in a world, oh-ho!
If you're wasted, well, certainly, please stop, drop, Daniel's soul now, pot safe from the
pot safe music network.
Alright, prolific programmer, you continue to intrigue my friends, for real.
Alrighty, time to shut this puppy down tomorrow will of course be Fubar Friday looking forward
to it very much.
I'm going to have a nice Saturday as well, just going to chill and sleep in a little
bit.
And then Sunday, off to Los Angeles for two days and then back home, unfortunately, I'm
going to miss the Lady Peas birthday, which is Saturday, but you heard her on the show.
She didn't give a shit anymore.
She wants to start counting backwards.
I get it.
Thank you very much for spending this past half hour with me, DailySourceco.com for tons
of links today that you'll definitely want to go check out.
What I've been podshow.com, if you have anything to send, and of course, you've got the
phone numbers, well, they're on the website as well on the show site.
Talk to you tomorrow, for Fubar Friday, bye-bye.
The best in the brightest, served up daily by the sharpest minds and content delivery,
podshow in my life.