And the beginning there was A.M. radio, families everywhere would gather around the living
room, listening to their favorite programs, and always good.
Who knows what he will look in the hearts of men, the shadow knows.
Then came the advent of F.M. radio.
Now broadcast could be heard in stereo, and teenagers found this, especially in tweaking,
as rock and roll music could be heard with great clarity.
However, parents became concerned as to what this music was doing to their kids.
Now it's the 21st century, and satellite radio is all the rage, or is it?
In a world where TV networks, movie studios, and record labels still think they can govern what you see in here.
One man has the power to return control of entertainment to the masses, and make big media corporations wet their tiny little pants.
From Pod Show, home of the world's most dangerous new content comes the Daily Source Code with Adam Curry.
Delta, share a Charlie 571.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
And I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love
I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it,
Did I love real?
I'm liking it. Almost part safe. It will be part safe for a couple of days. It
comes out officially on April 10th on eyeball records. New Atlantic a name of the band,
the wire and stone, the title of the song from the album, the streets, the sounds, and the
love. Hey everybody, how you doing? And it is daily source code episode 571 coming to you from
the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Gilford on the west side from the curry manner. Ah boy,
despite it being another fantastic day. Actually aviation wise, not a super duper day. I think
there's limited visibility is still a lot of fog pretty high up. Doesn't matter. The November
277 Delta Shiro was not ready anyway to be ferryed over today. So hopefully that'll happen to
tomorrow. And of course it could happen Friday or even over the weekend. But I'm here. And
so I took advantage of a little bit of pre-production stuff I'd done. I thought I was going to take
advantage of it. After dropping Christina off at school this morning, to head on over to my favorite
store. Yeah. It's the PC, where not the PC, where the hell is it? You know, the computer store
essentially. I was so sick and tired of dealing with manky routers and the DSL modems and I was just
sick and tired of it. So I'm like, okay, I'm going to go buy the hottest shit, the best ADSL 2 plus router
or modem built in with wireless router. And I wound up choosing a net gear. I got to tell you,
I have never had as many problems with any products when it comes to wireless. This is, I mean,
it connected to the ADSL fine. But half the computers in the house can't even see the network. And I
have done everything you can imagine. I've reset it to default. I've set it to only talk to B and G,
based routers, not even deal with G plus and Mimo and N and N draft and Nino and all this crap.
Who fucked up Wi-Fi? Jesus Christ. I'm sorry. Didn't mean to take his name in vain. I'm just
excitable when it comes to crap like that. It was so simple. But this stuff supposed to be plug and play.
Because I figured, you know, this is going to be great. I'm going to have one of these routers
that knows how to automatically adjust its six internal antennas. Well, I guess even to have
it work backwards compatible, although it says so right on the box that'll work with G, regular G
access cards, which, of course, I have in all of my machines here. Half of them can't see it. The
max can't see the net gear and network. The Windows machine see it, but can't connect to it.
My Nokia internet tablet, the N800, it sees the net gear network. It won't connect to it.
So, um, and there you go. I went back to setting up the airport as in Bridge mode. And it's working,
although the speed is crap. I think it's, uh, it's really my location in retrospect to the
to the exchange. I'm barely getting a megabit per second right now. And that was on the wired
connection to the DSLR router. Hey, yeah, yeah. At least now when I pop open a video, it doesn't stop
and just keeps on playing. Yeah, even though I can tell that it's barely keeping ahead of the
the download speed is barely keeping ahead of the play speed. It is working. That's all I really
wanted because last night I was showing Patricia stuff on not her computer downstairs. And it was just
it was horrific. You know, and rebooting these things, uh, okay. If you have any idea why this net gear
thing, I mean, yeah, I probably should go get one of those USB plug-in things that will do the end
routing. But I just wanted it to work with everything that I had that was existing here. Yeah.
Uh, let me see. I did, uh, actually on this all comes on the heels of an email I received from
Basile, uh, Basile was telling me how to actually help me set up my airport. Um, and I have just the,
uh, what is it? The airport extreme, not the express, but the extreme. So that's with the silver
apple, uh, like the kind of alien. Yeah, the the the the bling apple logo on on on the housing.
So it's not the new end router or anything like that. Uh, and he helped me set it up so that that would
actually, um, connect directly through the ADSL modem. I know I don't know how to do it with this net gear.
So I put everything back to bridge mode. It seems to be working. Uh, if it'll stay consistent like this,
although I'd much rather be on the on the net gear router because these, uh, these airports,
um, they do have some kind of quirky things. And they do require some resets from time to time.
I just got to figure it out. Maybe a Basile will send me some more information on how to do that.
Some really cool that Jessica released is, um, a double ender. Yeah. Yeah.
Uh, Cali Lewis from a Geek Brief TV and Natalie Del Conti from texture. Did a double ender yesterday.
Mm. You know how I love the double enders. Um, so you can check it out. Geek Brief TV. It's the
most recent episode. Geek Brief dot TV. Geek Brief TV dot podshow dot com. Um, very nice, uh,
little discussion there. It's like, yeah, the network is coming alive. There's, you know, cross
promotion and I didn't have to get involved in any of it. Lovely. Lovely. So with the, um, how, you know,
none of these router issues are more or less getting sorted out, uh, a couple of the things I got
to, I still have to fix my, uh, my Gmail apps account. It's, uh, it's still not resolving
Curry dot com is bouncing email. Uh, it's just time. I just need time to sit down and call my friendly
Google representative to help me help walk me through it. Um, uh, I think what I did is I, I fuck something
up. Uh, I, uh, I configured my Google apps domain, uh, as mail dot curry dot com. And now, whatever I
want to, uh, configure the MX record, uh, I can't do that. I can configure the MX record for
Curry dot com, but not for mail dot curry dot com, or at least I don't know how to do it. So, uh,
help. Uh, uh, Dave Peterson did send me a, uh, a cool link. I'll put this one in the show notes.
Um, it's a nifty tool that helps you manage multiple Gmail addresses. It's a Firefox extension.
And so you can switch back and forth between accounts without having to log in log out or have
different accounts open on different tabs and it really integrates very cool. Dude, I appreciate that.
And, um, uh, we'll most certainly, uh, give that one a try. Uh, let me see. First caller of the day.
Yeah, it's got to be one of our buddies. Yeah, let's just call them a regular show. We got them
changed. Uh, just following up on one of the callers who are hanging about, uh, regular callers who
only being clear on the SC. I sort of consider myself a bit of a regular caller. I've heard my
voice on the podcast. Most things, but just to put them straight on something, I would see a good
50% of the stuff that I send you, you don't put on the podcast. And I'm not bothered. Um, because most
of it's bubbling, shite anyway. Um, so, you know, I'm just a random, no, I'm not sure if you
do. Um, if you ring in and it's interesting, I'm sure he will be cleared. Um, and this may not
get clear. Uh, well, give me a minute. Uh, no, no, James, absolutely. Yeah, it's true. James knows it.
There are lots of people know it. People send stuff in. I don't play it. I don't reply. It's like
a message received. You know, I get a lot of stuff. So, but it's definitely not the regular. There's
no such thing as a regular. The regular, those are people who actually send stuff that I can regularly
and now we're from our sponsor. It's the yanks versus the brits. Ooh, uh, we'll drive each other crazy,
but everybody knows that it's apparent to see that just like you and me, it's the yanks and the brits
to die. The yanks versus the brits. Mind the gap. Haven't done one of these in a long time.
Busco 9 a burks and this one in. And it's not an audio submission. It is purely in tech. So,
I'll have to take a stab at it. An Englishman was having coffee and croissants with butter and jam
in a cafe. When an American tour is chewing gum sat down next to him. The Englishman
politely ignored the American who nevertheless started up a conversation. The American snapped
the gum in his mouth and said, do you English folks eat the whole bread? The Englishman frowned
annoyed at being bothered during his breakfast and replied, yeah, that's of course we do.
The American blew a huge bubble. Well, we don't. In the States, we only eat what's inside.
The crusts, we collect in a container, recycle them, transform them into croissants,
or crescents, and sell them to England. The American had a smirk on his face. The Englishman
listened in silence. The American persisted. Do you eat jam with the bread?
Signing the Englishman replied, yes, cracking the gum between his teeth. The American said,
we don't. In the States, we eat fresh fruit for breakfast. We put all the peel, seeds,
and leftovers, and containers recycle them, transform them into jam, and sell it to England.
The Englishman then asked, do you have sex in the States? The Anxmild and said, yeah, of course we do.
The Englishman leaned closer to him and asked, what do you do with the condoms once you've
used them? We throw them away, of course, replied the American. Now was the Englishman's turn
to smile. We don't. In England, we put them into containers, recycle them, melt them down,
and transform them into chewing gum, and sell them to the States. That's why it's called
Rigly's. Now we're from Archbite here. It's the Yanks. Versus the Brits.
We'll drive each other crazy, but everybody knows that it's apparent to see.
Let's just like you and me, it's the Yanks. And the Brits. The Yanks. Versus the Brits.
Mind the Gat.
I had a prolific program right here again from San Francisco. I wanted to comment regarding
the comic strip bloggers, comment about 13 minutes into episode 569 of the Daily Source Code.
About the European Union, perhaps some history is an order. The European Union was originally
started as a steel community between the French, the Germans, the Italians, the Dutch, the Belgians,
and the Luxembourgians. I think they're called the guys from Luxembourg. As a result, you'll find
that all of the EU institutions are based in either France, Germany, Luxembourg, Belgium, or Italy,
or the Netherlands. Then England, in 1973, Ireland joined the same time.
And in 1992, the Massberg Treaty was signed in Holland, which established the currency union.
I really love this EU talk. It turns me on. This, of course, is all on the heels of comics
or blogger, bringing to our attention that the European economic community, I believe,
turned 50 last Sunday. It's all very confusing and we're trying to suss it out. But we have the
experts clearly on hand. Let's see what happens. What happened next was in 1999, the EU
expand in 1979. In 1970, the EU expanded again in 2010, Eastern European countries.
P.V. In prolific program, what you're doing to me, man? He sends me these
files. I love prolific program. He sends me these audio files. He sends him an AIFF format,
which means like 30 megs for one comment. Then this is what it's built up with. Okay,
let's back to our history lesson of the EU with prolific programmer.
Poland, Czech Republic, Hungary, Slovenia and the Baltic States, which are a lot
we are doing in Estonia. In 2002, at midnight, the euro became a currency, not just the
figment of the ECB's imagination. All right. I gotta go see if he has any more in the history lesson
that pertains. I should preview that. I didn't realize it was two and a half minutes. I'm sorry,
prolific programmer. Yeah, I'll play a jingle, make you feel good.
So prolific programmer is responding to comic strip bloggers comments about the EU and the
EEC. Then this guy from New York, who's a new regular caller to the show, he calls himself
Nylon because he travels piece from New York, lives in London, travels back and forth,
believes in the financial sector. He called in and I really want to play this first bit again for
you about the EU because I got a ton of responses to it. It's just unbelievable amount of responses
in, oh, I'll just give an example. This is from Devon Osterdorf. Adam at the risk of
defending all New Yorkers. The first time I heard Nylon's voice, I knew he was going to be annoying.
I think it's readily apparent that the guy does not get it. Perhaps if he pulled this head out of his
panty hose, he listened to what you say prior to making an asset himself on the show by blatantly
demonstrating his lack of comprehension. I really did not want to write this note as I'd like to keep my
input upbeat and positive, but I'm pleading with you to stop playing his comments. Unless, of course,
the Jeff Smith sends in something too priceless to let Gather dust on the shelf. Well, he didn't
call in today. Even though I did, I pleaded with him to please. I like it when people have
contrary in views. And it wasn't Jeff Smith, although Jeff did ping me, but it was slow.
Our buddy, Slough, who stepped up to the plate.
He's an island, outspoken, expatriate, he's in London, but he's from New York.
Let's listen to a little bit from Nylon. When he called in a couple
days ago. Hey, Adam, it's the Nylon, the New Yorker in London. No, I know you're in a little
budget there. You can't employ a fact-check, fact-checker. So a couple of corrections and then a final
word on bummerous detots. First, the reason why you probably don't know about the E.C. 50th is that
it's actually the European economic community that's somewhere in the 50th birthday. And that
consists of Belgium, France, Italy, Luxembourg, the Netherlands, and West Germany. It wasn't
sort of a master treaty. Dara, so you get it, right? Just him starting up a little bit. You can't
afford a fact-checker. Oh, he's an island, outspoken, expatriate, he's in London, but he's from New York.
Oh, man, I sure hope he calls in again.
It's a jingle extravaganza today.
Comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip,
haia, Adam Kerry. Shouldn't we meet up in London soon or something? Any fucking way.
Let me correct, lay mass corrections of nylon. So, when I was studying at the University in Rome,
in Italy, then I was visiting Musei Capitolini in Piazza de Campidolio, where Roman treaties were
signed that created European economic community that morphed later into European Union.
So nylon is talking out of his ass, claiming that only funding members were celebrating 50th
anniversary of EU. All member countries were celebrating it, including UK as one could see Tondibler,
there too. So nylon, shut the fuck up, a stick to issues that you know from personal experience,
like for example, jetting off in a toilet of virgin Atlantic airplane or something. By the way,
funding members, my ass, the all other worst races, the all, and only day are blocking freedom of
movement of work as the 2011. So it's clear we have to get nylon, comic strip,
blogger, and prolific programmer on one Skype call, one conference call. This would be fantastic.
Can you imagine the tower of Babel that would exist if we had the three of them on the phone
and we tried to figure out what the fuck the year is the European Union is?
Hi, Adam. This is Max from Hampshire in the UK. The nylon seemed to get very hung up about the
idea that there's a difference between us as in podcastes and us as in the audience. When the
thing I found with podcasting is it only takes half an idea and maybe a cheap headset and some
Skype call recording software and audacity and use pod shell will use various other services and
that's it. You switch from being audience to being podcast or even if it's only just your friends
that are listening in, then that's great. Your friends can tell their friends and so on and
difference between a large podcast and a small podcast is the number of people who are listening.
It's not like mainstream media like TV or radio where the big entities like the BBC or
Cleared Channel in the States or whoever have access and have reached a huge number of people
being seen as so wide ranging widely available now that it means anyone can listen to the
nonsense, bypass out the world structure tool. You press out or whatever it's a great big free
full and it's fantastic. Folder? Yes. Now I realize I played two comments out of order. I really
should have played this one because nylon did go on the talk about bombers that charred and how it
was all wrong and it wasn't a, you know, what did it prove and that was on the heels of his
EU comments. Mark was in Brussels at the time. Hey Adam, how's it going? My name is Mark. I'm
calling from London and I was calling in mainly about the European discussion you're having
yesterday about 50 years. Over the weekend I was in Brussels just by complete accident and
kind of an interesting. I had no idea that it was going on whatsoever and I guess in being
surprised I didn't seem to be talking about it that much. The other thing was, I just kind of felt
over there even in Brussels the whole thing kind of felt a bit lame. You know, they had simply red
playing some concert and some other sort of third-rate bands. It's really interesting. Simply red
Mick Hocknell. I think it's celebrated in most parts of the world. In the UK they laugh at it,
man. They call him a, what a ginger minger. I basically ugly red head and that's really strange.
Same with Phil Collins, man. They do not like Phil Collins here in the UK or something about
he had an affair with his nanny and then somehow his wife became the, the scorned woman. Well,
of course, she was the scorned woman. I presume, but he really got railed in the press for a long,
long time and people just don't give a shit about him anymore. That's really weird the way you guys
will just write off some, I think, very talented people. Um, and kind of the rest of the weekend,
I guess I was speaking with people and Brussels about the whole thing. And it kind of seems to me
that the one thing that they have as, maybe in Europe, as well, that there's kind of a lack of
understanding about what it actually feels like to be European, like an identity problem. So
that was my points and my question. I guess is, what does it, what does it mean to be European?
What does it feel like? What is the European way? So if anybody doesn't know about this, then yeah,
call them, let me know. But yeah, I love the show. Thanks a lot, bye.
Yeah, man. Thank you for calling in, appreciate it, Mark. Yeah, that is a very good question.
What does it feel like to be European? I think I have some inkling of an idea.
I feel somewhat European. I also feel, um, pretty American, really. I certainly don't feel
British. I don't know if I ever will be able to. But boy, I do love the culture here.
But that's a good question. Since this is a turning in to be, uh, or turning out to be such a,
a jingle-based show for everyone who's calling in the next call, or I don't have a jingle
for, but I was just looking for one. Hold on a second. This will be funny.
Hold on. I'm going into Napster as we speak.
Because the person is Luke. Now, you know Luke as the guy who delivers all the goods from Nokia,
yeah, we call him a, we call him a little bit something different here. We call him the candy man.
So I don't have a jingle, but I do have this for you, Luke. Hold on. Let's see if I can make it work.
Come on, Napster. Do your stuff. Buffer through that DSL gateway. Come on. You can do it.
Piece of shit. The f- just one song. It takes like six hours to download it. I hate this.
Huh, the podfather. I need connectivity and throughput. Better than this.
Hey, listen, I doubt plus four or four star-dash and I'm going to be more haste to not end it up here.
So that's working as well. Hey, just a quick update about the, you know, the Sahara sent
America and the charity run. So feeling sushi are still running. They are about, let's say, halfway
down the, down the list of contestants. So they're doing pretty well, going at every speed of about
five, five and a half to six kilometers per hour. And it should only eight contestants have dropped out so far.
So it seems to be going pretty well for everybody. Yeah, temperature yesterday was about 45 degrees centigrade,
which is, I think, 1520 on the Richter scale. So yeah, things are going fine.
And I'll call back later in a week when the racetrack over how everything went. Okay, bye.
All right, Luke. Thank you very much. Update from his friends who are doing a marathon every single day
through the Sahara desert for a good cause. Frankly, Luke, I don't care what you talk about because you are the candy man, my friend.
Five, six, three, five, seven, one, two, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven.
Peter was going to kick my ass. I forgot the satellite window closed. Sorry, Peter was probably in some
tirade and rant that I was on. Luke is calling in from Zurich as we were talking about. I did make a mistake
about this plus thing in countries that do not use the GSM mobile protocol. And in the states,
that is quite a few places. You actually have to do the access code. Oh, one, one. It does that
suck or what? Now, I love America, but man, what's this worth 110 volts? What is this with
NTSC? You know, what is this with not using GSM? Like the rest of the bloody world?
Ah, here it's together. Hi Adam, it's Luke from Zurich. I just wanted to call it to say
it's written down an offer about roaming. When you received calls inside Switzerland,
with a pay as you go like you speak, pay things. You got money for giving a call. I mean,
that person who said to call pay decks or something. It's got pricing, much you can repeat.
When you call, I mean, this side of the call is not meant to be it.
By the sense, bye. All right, yeah, it is a rip off man. Whenever you leave the country,
whenever you go to a different country within Europe, you're paying for your inbound calls.
I don't think there's even any plans you can get that give you a blanket pricing for
for all countries and for roaming. And it can be quite high on the pre-pay funds. It's our
rate. It's like a pound fifty three dollars a minute if you can believe it. All right, this one submitted
by David Sweeney from the Catholic Family podcast. Subject with the Gmail was outstanding new song
on the PMN. Well, that will catch my attention won't it? Getting assignments without your skill.
But if things I'm scared to say I'm not, then my mind I know all I can do is kiss you.
But I'm a copy between the curtain and the crowd.
And I don't leave cause I'm free to be alone.
But it doesn't even matter not all gone.
All right, I'll sign up to find you when you look into my eyes, pay me your promise to me.
I'll just get without your skill. I'll just get out of your skill.
There's a picture in my bedroom by the window.
I don't sue kids just outside my closet door.
I don't know if I should run away or tiptoe.
But I feel like I can't be here anymore.
And I don't leave cause I'm free to be alone.
But it doesn't even matter not all gone.
All right, I'll sign up to find you when you look into my eyes, pay me your promise to me.
But I'll just get out of your skill. I'll just get out of your skill.
And make it sound so easy. To make them all so bright.
So when they come to me, they're dead.
And now they're still gone.
I don't leave cause I'm free to be alone.
But it doesn't even matter not all gone.
All right, I'll sign up to find you when you look into my eyes,
pay me your promise to me. I'll just get out of your skill.
Without your skill, I'll just get out of your skill.
Without your skill, without your skill.
That does sense your skills.
It's about to say goodbye when I noticed that one of my channels that updated at PodShow
Plus.
And we got to start talking about channels, just a reminder.
It's the channel that includes my digital flotsome podcast, not mine, but I feel like
it's mine because I've collected it.
It came to me, but it's from PWFentan, PEDA, the satellite repairman.
I alluded to this when I was in New York.
It got some horrible news, early morning, PEDA, let me know that his dad had passed away
quite suddenly.
And I met his dad in New York a year and a half before that.
And that's fucked up, it's like, whoa.
And I haven't said anything about it because obviously that's not my task and I wanted
to make sure that PEDA had his own way of telling everyone about that or not.
But I see now in the feed, it looks like his most recent show was a tribute to his dad.
So I'm going to stop the show now and I'm going to go listen to that.
And I suggest you do as well.
I'll put a link in the show notes, obviously.
And since some good vibes, PEDA was way, first whole family, his wife Rosiness, his
kids and grandkids and illegitimate children.
All right, everybody, dailysourceco.com for the show notes and links to everything we talked
about today.
Adam at podshow.com.
Thank you so much for listening to my crap.
Talk to you again tomorrow.
The other podshow podcast, stick it in your ear.
The best of the brightest, Sav. daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering podshow
and limelight.