Yo, what's Tony Costa telling you to check out this Christmas podcast.com is the official podcast for the new Sony film this Christmas
starring Chris Brown, Virginia King, Columbus Short, and an all-star cast. The site includes a special holiday podcast from yours truly
exclusive interviews from the stars in the film and a special red carpet coverage from the premiere.
You can exchange gifts, but you can't exchange family. This Christmas is truly the next holiday classy.
See it in theaters on November 21st and check us out at thisChristmaspodcast.com.
We're here on the streets of San Francisco trying to hunt down one of America's most wanted
Adam Curry. He's wanted by the TSA, by the FBI, by the CIA, by the ATF, for carrying various forms of
hairspray across the United States, and also by a man in Hoboken New Jersey who went to college
with Mr. Curry, and says he suspects that the man has been listening to too much array game music.
The suspect is approximately 8 feet tall. He has very tall bushy blonde hair and walks around in rose-colored glasses.
If you happen to see Mr. Curry, please help us stop him before he records the DSC 682.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Yes, today I arrive at San Francisco International Airport. Had a nice little chat with the
customs officers.
Let's go. I go through to get my suitcase. Five minutes after I'm standing there, the same
guy had apparently come running from his little cute little there.
How do I have your cross-miss form for a second?
I got to write something on it.
And he writes on it, baggage check, baggage check.
And I say, oh, oh, why is that? Did you just always on the side you wanted to check?
So I'm popped up in the computer.
I'm on the list.
I am on the list.
I am most definitely on the list.
And I'm not quite sure what it is, but it's not a pretty one because I am going to get ripped apart
every single time I come into the states.
Now, there's something really seriously fucked up because what's happening here.
So I'm popped up in the computer.
All of this talk that we've been having about the constitution and a skull
fucked up rotting corpse of the TSA.
I'm on the list.
Oh yes, skull fucked up rotting corpse of the TSA.
I can't leave you fear of what I say.
Enjoy your freedom.
Remember, remember the fifth of November,
the gunpowder creasant and blood.
I know of no reason why the gunpowder creasant should ever be forgotten.
I'm on the list.
I am on the list.
This is the second stoneienia굴點ий
from the World tradition
It's an illusion, a bunch of confusion
The only solution, a new revolution
A new revolution
Corporations making billions selling us their lives
Make a profit even if nobody's left alive
The new world earner is the devil disguise
With the television news set to hypnotize
When the bureaucratic power tips get the grip
Should we see through the grip of sound
Got a stop and lay and got
Oh, our prosecution never made your institutions
Stepping on the Constitution
Let's sign a revolution
Let's sign a revolution freedom
It ain't free
If they take our rights
Then we've got to fight for our democracy
Yeah
Let's have a sitting on the White House lawn
A sitting on the White House lawn
A noer, a sitting on the White House lawn
I'll be out.
Let's have a sitin' on the White House long.
I knew ever seen it on the White House long.
The only solution.
I knew ever you should.
Freedom people, new revolution.
Kicking off episode number 682 of the daily source code.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
Officially still the fifth of November.
Of course you're probably listening to this on November 6th.
What we need right now is a clear message to the people of this country.
This message must be read in every newspaper heard on every radio scene on every television.
This message must presound throughout the entire interlink.
I want this country to realize that we stand on the edge of oblivion.
I want every man, woman, and child to understand how close we are to chaos.
I want everything to remember why they need them.
I got to tell you.
As fried as I am, and of course it's been a very busy couple of days.
Happy to tell you all about it.
I've had a smirk on my face all day.
Starting last night, midnight.
Because the 24-hour period of the Ron Paul Money Bomb, which of course was to coincide
with the fifth of November.
Handily, virally propagated through the V-Vendetta.
I remember remember the fifth of November gunpowder trees and implot.
Of course borrowed from our British friends.
Wow.
Can you believe it?
So I'm looking now.
What time is it here?
It is now a 930pm on the fifth of November.
I'm looking at the scorecard right now.
7,150,312 dollars in the 79 cents.
Raised so far in the quarter for Ron Paul.
Last night.
Before I went to bed.
At midnight, it was 2.3 million.
So I think by midnight, Pacific Standard Time,
$5 million will have been raised for Congressman Dr. Ron Paul.
Just Dr. Ron.
Da.
Thank you all.
Everyone who was participated.
Everyone who put money into the pot.
You're investing in the future of America.
You're investing in your freedom.
Even if this candidate doesn't make it all the way to the White House,
the message is out, the message is very clear.
And you know what?
It's such a relatively small percentage of people that made this happen.
It may be 40, 50,000 people.
Actually, I think Jonathan, the campaign finance director,
will give me some stats.
I think it was pretty busy today.
I did have an email or two back and forth with them.
But I think it will give me some stats on how much money we raised
through DSC.
I'm certainly curious because the number in total was really,
I think, only 40, 50,000 people.
Which means that not only will the candidate get more visibility,
but we can always drop another money bomb whenever we need it.
It's really not all that hard to do.
This is just beautiful.
For me, today was it really showed something special.
And maybe it only works if you're American and you're kind of in the American system.
And you are realized that it's very important for a candidate to be able to raise lots of money
because I said it before, I gotta say it again.
We choose our presidents the same way we choose our washing powder
through repetition of commercials.
It's just an extremely important part of any campaign in this country and this system.
But man, man or man.
And you know what?
No celebrity.
No Oprah was needed.
What are Oprah raised for Obama?
Like one $2 million that she invited everyone to her house.
We didn't need any super celebrity.
No one's the celebrity of this.
Except for the constitution and freedom.
Man, it feels good to say that.
You know what?
Let's loosen up a little bit.
I need some exercise or is it an ass or size?
Come on, Amy.
I need some ferman of the buttocks.
Hey, Amy.
Hey, Adam, remember me?
Yeah.
It's Amy, man.
Amy.
It seems that we are both a little overloaded when it comes to getting the recording thing done.
So I know it's been weeks since we've asked her size.
I'm right.
But I thought some circumstances go, you can use all that space and headroom in your apartment
and we can do something big.
Go ahead and get yourself situated.
Okay, I'm ready.
I'm standing socks only.
We're going to do moving jump squats.
So you're going to squat like you're sitting in a chair and then jump up and forward
while squeezing the stomach and butt.
Okay.
Good.
Another one.
You want to go as high and as far as you can while still keeping your balance.
And of course, don't forget to breathe.
This time, you want to jump up and backwards.
And again.
Good.
Two more front and two more back.
Ready, go.
I don't hear you squeezing.
Breathe.
Okay.
Now, I don't know what the next few weeks hold.
But if you're missing me, you can watch me kick Brandon's ass and the super music video show.
Now, when I see it, I owe you two butt squeezes.
And remember, there's always time to say it with me.
So size.
Okay.
I saw it in me today as I was on my way out the door at a big presentation today.
And she said hi.
No butt squeeze.
No nothing.
So I presume she's listening and was maybe even disappointed.
Sorry.
I forgot to breathe.
Maybe even disappointed that that hadn't done it yet.
Okay.
Amy.
So you owe me two butt squeezes.
Of course, this program emanating from the Curry condo in San Francisco, California.
Man, it's been crazy three days.
So we had this big presentation today.
And it really involved a whole bunch of people in the company.
Really everybody would have to say right down to forbidding anyone to download porn during
our demonstration of our new site because it's running on a sandbox inside the office.
And so, you know, it's all on VPN.
So when you actually play some media coming from outside, the building, it just clogs up the pipes and it complicated.
But everyone refrain from downloading porn this afternoon.
That was great.
But it was a lot of work yesterday.
I've been Sunday Saturday.
It was no weekend, man.
It was just crazy.
But I did get a lot of great comments about, I told you, I felt this won't be one for the archives.
And I also felt quite good.
I actually listened back to the entire show Saturday morning.
Football.
I got to say, I think really added to the soundtrack of my life.
Adam, this is Martin calling from David.
I heard Marilyn listening to the DSC number 681 or Friday.
The food bar Friday.
And that things to play after the hit test, the beetles thing, whatever.
I want to call that thing.
Mashup.
Oh my god.
Every single song.
I'm 40 years old.
I know pretty much all the songs from my youth.
Not having heard them when their first came out.
Every one of those songs.
I'm not even through listening to the thing.
I can't wait till I get home and sit in my car right now.
Can't wait till I get home and start finding all those songs.
Wherever I can find them.
I just forgot how many great.
Sorry.
Dr. Ron.
For president.
That's what I suppose to be.
Dr. Ron for president.
Almost forgot.
Yeah, man.
I put a Lincoln show notes to the full file.
You only heard half of it.
I think continues for like a total of 10 minutes.
That.
I was at the something versus the beetles.
Geez.
Gee, the geez or the breeze.
It's in the show notes for the show.
Almost obscure beetle songs.
There are and.
Dude, that was just fucking awesome.
So whoever sent that in.
Like I said, I haven't looked gotten to the end of it yet.
But I just stopped in the middle to pick up the phone and call you.
And absolutely awesome.
Thanks for putting that together.
Putting that on the air.
Yeah, of course, man.
That's what food bar is all about.
And when I actually have the time, which is all I wish for,
it's just a little more time in the day.
When I have the time, I got to tell you.
I so get into this shit, but that was,
I did that Thursday evening.
That was probably two and a half hours of preparation.
Just to get everything.
Find everything downloaded.
You know, transfer stuff over from computer to computer.
You know, it takes time.
So when I got the time, then.
That's why I'd rather not do a show than just throw something together
and why I skip a day or two.
Hi, Adam.
It's Kevin Crossman, the proud scruncher from Frap Pack podcast.
There you go.
A little commentary on your last football Friday, which was really.
Definitely one for the record books.
Lots of great music.
Although once again, jersey time.
But you down because that song was very generic and boring.
Whereas the rest of your stuff was really inspired and.
Oh, hold on a second.
Easy on the toaster there.
You know, jersey time.
By the way, no easy task for this man because.
You know, he.
I've missed so many football Fridays that he also, you know,
has to like spin up inspiration within seconds when he finds out that I'm doing a show.
I like the choice personally.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have played it.
You know.
Although I do trust jersey Todd's opinion,
Surgery as he taught official music colleges of the Chacha.
That's this program you're listening to.
So not to harsh man on the guy.
All right, please.
Come on, he's family.
You know, maybe just wasn't your liking, but.
You're in the family.
We all kind of cooperate.
It's given take.
Regarding your experience going through security and having to show them.
A business card to get into the country of which you are citizen is incredibly.
Disturbing.
I was thinking about your vibe about, you know, thinking about gadgets again.
And since I'm a new iPhone owner, I thought, well,
couldn't you just show, you know, plot your internet tablet or whatever you're using these days.
Go to the pod show site and surely there would be some information that would show that you are the CEO of a.
Okay.
All right.
No, but a lot of people have suggested that I record it.
So next time that's what I'm going to do, I'm going to wear my wireless mic.
I'm going to put it on.
I want to get off the plane.
I'll put it in my coat pocket or something.
And I'll record my experience because I'm guaranteed to get pulled over again.
Because as you know, I'm on list.
Someone who is on many, many lists.
Some of them shit.
Come extra.
Are you corresponding?
Because there's a lot of shit going on in the world.
Not just in the United States of America.
What's up, Adam?
You're a CSB, your EU co-respondent.
Your EU, my friend.
So Italy is now expelink.
EU citizens who came from Romania.
What the fucking fuck?
What kind of bullshit is this?
Wait a minute.
They're expeling.
I guess what he's trying to say is,
One European country is throwing Europeans out of its country.
And that's not the way the rules are supposed to work.
It's the fucking freedom of movement gone.
So apparently it is legal after all.
If EU citizens are not the motherfuckers, then.
So Adam, better tell your bird Patricia to get fucking British citizenship as a AP.
Because otherwise, she, as EU citizens, can be expeled, for example, from UK.
Cool.
You know what?
That would probably happen just because of me.
Because I'm on some list somewhere.
I think she has to live there for a total of five years before she can get that.
And I doubt that she'd give up her Dutch nationality.
Although, I don't know.
I'll have to ask her.
You know what?
We'll ask her together when I'm back.
Man, I missed doing a show with a lady P.
And Adam?
Yes.
Stop touching yourself in an appropriate way when I'm talking to you.
Respect.
In a world where evil walks the earth, where supervillains are taken over by demonic beings.
They all want one thing and one thing only.
To take over the world.
There's only one man who can stop them.
One man with the powers and abilities to kick some serious demon ass.
In a race against time to stop a portal that opens to hell itself.
One man.
One hero.
One son of a bitch you don't want to mess with.
He's faceless.
He's fearless.
He is black shadow.
Those demons won't know what hit him.
From the mind of David Podio, book off their Steve Sailor.
Comes his story where the super powers beats the supernatural.
Four men more.
At the Steve Sailor.net for more details.
Like shadow.
Comes soon to pod shell.
And a pod catcher.
You know, if you haven't checked out one of these audio books.
You audio novel, I should say.
You really got to check it out, man.
Because it's a great entertainment format.
It really is.
I've been listening to a couple on my international travels.
I stack them up because I don't have a regular daily commute.
So I stack them up and listen to a whole bunch of them.
Another thing I've been actually even buying this off of iTunes.
Recommendation from Head Sales, Weasel, Chris Jacob.
Mad men.
I guess it aired at some point somewhere on television.
But it's on iTunes.
The entire series is about advertising men of the early 60s.
The guys from Madison Avenue and it's just phenomenal.
One of those episodic things.
It's just, that's very cool.
If you have not yet checked out pussy the musical.
Please hurry on over to pussythemusical.podshow.com from the.
Sad and perverted mind of Mark Yoshimo to Nemkoff.
Yet again.
Creating something that is an alter ego to a mainstream hit.
Just when you thought you'd had enough of high school musical to come to pussy the musical.
I think he has 12 or maybe even 14 different songs in this musical performed.
By voices you probably know from the pod show network and beyond.
People creating independent media.
I have done a song called The Snatch.
Myself is a boy band that will be in a upcoming episode of pussythemusical.
And I'd like to play you one from I think it's episode two or episode three.
I'm so happy that this came together.
You know my partner and co-founder of podshow Ron Bloom,
who I've been friends with for all going on 14 years now.
We've done business together.
It's more than just a partnership.
It's a brother ship and a way like a marriage.
No doubt about it.
We certainly see more of each other than our wives.
And you know, Ron's background is music.
You should Google him.
You see the stuff that he's done.
It's pretty extensive.
I kind of baked into what I do for podshow is this program.
I'm involved with a lot of production and just working with creative people,
which I really enjoy.
And it's not like my partner Ron enjoys it any less.
He just has different responsibilities.
For a company within our partnership and he doesn't get to do as much creative stuff
as I'd like him to do.
So I was delighted.
Absolutely delighted when I heard his contribution to pussythemusical.
So I wanted a hot blue jeans and she said,
Come over here, boy.
And give me a dance.
So dance.
I want our letter.
We were back at my place.
She was doing the same dance.
And right on my face and I said,
hey, baby.
Good thing I got no weekend plans.
Cause there's a road and I'm not.
And I ain't gonna put up with fire.
I got a girl on my left to go to my right.
I'm gonna be up all night.
And let us in the place where the money is sweeter.
Swirl my life.
No, my swirls ain't better.
The other thing is going to be so, so tight.
I have to move around and not give me that good job.
That's right.
And that's what I'm talking about.
But if I am.
Go to a room down.
Hold down tonight.
Client.
Ron Bloom from Pussy the Musical, Music and lyrics by Mark Yosemore Nemkov, Vocal Slide Guitar by Ron Bloom.
Awesome.
Let me see, Colts coming in from across the seas, international listeners of the Daily Source Code.
It would love to hear more Presidential candidates on the show.
Yeah, you're not the only one.
That's better from Belgium.
One of your colors mentioned that it's a great platform.
I must concur because your platform's DSC must be, well, it's, I mean, I'm from Belgium.
I'm from Holland, but it's just, I've been following these primaries and the elections for years in the US.
And finally, this is a platform that, you know, it's script from all the over Chiever stuff that's going on.
And it's just, it would be a such a great platform to get these guys on and get them to speak out to you just in a conversation instead of dog fighting each other in a debate or over achieving taking those positions.
And I totally concur with one of the commenters in the last show and get these people on.
It's a really a cry for, for also for the international DSC listeners to get to know the candidates in a different way in a way that is, well, more future bound.
I hope you get them on and, well, I'm, at this point, so, I'm almost blue again.
Scruncher and see this be, I love to meet you man, you're fucking asshole.
Great, love you, fuck you, bye.
I am, man.
Well, you know, and it's, it's really true.
And I got to tell you, I eagerly look forward to new YouTube clips or a more new news articles about Dr. Ron.
And you just don't see anything, I think, that even comes close to the format that we used here on the daily source code.
Just ask the questions and let the guy answer.
I don't have to prove that I know something or nothing about politics doesn't make any difference what I do.
Ask the question, get the answer, wait until the guy's done talking.
Everyone wants to be a fucking superhero in media.
Well, I can be controversial.
And it's funny because I got a lot of people, blue pill takers, no doubt, who said, well, that was a pretty bland interview.
Boy, that was pretty dull.
His message speaks for itself.
But we had now, 7,168, 475, 82 cents.
Yeah, I wonder.
Of course, I'd take any any candidate who's running.
I would love to ask him all questions.
I'd love for this to be a platform so we can listen and learn.
Is it possible, do you think?
I'm Gary Chris from Leviton, Pennsylvania.
I'm listening right now to DSC 680.
And I'm listening to a West Coast caller call about other politicians call him in.
And I'm going to give you a very simple answer if to why you won't get any of those politicians to call in.
I'm not saying the primary Republicans are Democrats.
And he's not, honestly, because if they actually answered the questions, honestly, we wouldn't like the answers.
Because the answers would be, I'm rich.
I'm powerful.
I want to be more powerful.
I want to be more rich.
And I will flee from skinned your lives in order to get richer and more powerful.
And I have to.
That's what we don't want to hear.
And that's what they're not going to tell us.
And we're going to do.
Fuck them all, I'm Gary.
Welcome back everyone towards me here.
We're here in our final round with Carmen and Crystal.
In this last round, you shout out the first thing on your mind after I say a word, which is designed to bring you both to a common answer to our final question.
So here we go.
Are you ready?
Of course.
Yes.
Great.
Okay then.
Our first word is...
Betrayal.
Murder.
I interesting.
The next word is...
Conspiracy.
Hashen bracket.
Okay then.
And our final word is...
Trust.
Desire.
Non-existent.
Now you have your three words.
Using all of those along with your responses,
Tell me the name of the newest audio novel containing all of these attributes.
ASB.
He art of sex and bitchiness.
You are both correct.
Michelle, please tell these low lives what they've won.
Both of you will receive and all expense paid subscription to the audio novel by Terry Woodard.
The art of sex and bitchiness.
This is an erotic murder mystery hosted exclusively on Potshow.
We suggest you retrieve your prize from the seclusion of your own home by going to ASB.potshow.com.
Enjoy a little murder and betrayal, but you won't find them conditional love.
Because we all know everything has a price.
One, two, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven,
One, two, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven.
Yeah.
I appreciate if you call in anything you got to say.
Happy to hear about it.
It's nice to get a different topic started.
Here's something that came in that caught my ear.
Hi Adam.
This is Jennifer from Black Area, Scotland.
I'm an American living in Scotland.
And I'm an avid reader of the time magazine.
I said I'm an avid getter and I read it once a while.
This week, it caught my eye.
I'm a cover.
It says the secrets of the birth order.
And it talks about how the oldest children differ from the youngest.
And being the youngest of four, I was quite interested.
And it's got a very valid point.
How parents treat the children differently.
And I just thought it would be difficult for anybody who is a parent
who should maybe treat their children more equal.
Well, first of all, thank you so much for the tip.
And I will see if I can pick that up somewhere.
You know, this is funny.
I think everyone has this situation.
If you have multiple siblings.
I was the eldest of three.
I've two younger sisters.
Tiffany, two years younger than I am.
I think.
Yeah, we're separated two years.
Each of us.
I felt that I had to break all the ice.
You know, by the time we're all rolled around getting through
a puberty and adolescence.
It was fucking easy sailing.
Yeah, really easy sailing.
So I felt that I got a much harder treatment.
And you know, interesting.
I don't know if it parents should.
I think a lot of the treatment comes with experience.
You know, a lot of it is fear.
You got a kid, man.
It's like the most precious thing you have.
And you don't want to.
Look, why do you think I learned how to fly helicopter?
So I could hover above my daughter to figure out what the hell is going on
and where she's going.
This is, I find the point extremely valid.
And being the youngest of four.
I often feel like I'm the, the warmth of the litter and the one with
the, the least expectations put upon them.
Really?
And also my oldest brother is the golden child.
He is very good.
And he does not walk on water.
But my parents seem to think so.
Oh, my parents.
I don't think they felt I walked on water anymore less than my sisters.
And my husband's quite similar.
He's the youngest of two.
And he sees the article as extremely relevant as well.
So it's just a little hit there.
And there's also a good interview with.
The Hollywood legends about lions and lambs.
It's Robert Redford Tom Cruise.
And you know, there's a couple of street.
And that's extremely good as well.
Okay.
Talk to you later.
Bye bye.
Yeah.
Thanks for calling.
You know, interesting.
You bring up kids.
You're forced.
We have only one child, Christina.
Now 17 years old.
And so, you know, you can't treat her any better or worse than the next one.
Because we only got one.
I must say though, Sunday.
Had a really web 2.0 parenting moment.
And I don't want to get into too much detail.
But let's just put it this way.
Christina was being a shit.
You know, as kids can get teenagers.
And I'm not want to overreact unnecessarily any more five years ago.
I was much more on edge.
But I've milled down significantly.
But she really, I mean, she was not being helpful to her mom.
Let's just put it that way.
It more ways than one.
Now I'm 5,000 miles away.
And separated by, you know, eight hours of time difference.
But it was, it was actually eight hours on Sunday.
And, you know, she just was a, in teenager mode.
But really, you know, I would have had to go and sit her down and talk to her in person.
And in fact, you know, I got her on the phone for like a couple seconds.
And, you know, I had this like Alec Baldwin moment almost.
I'm like, oh, this is not good.
And then she wouldn't talk to me and she wouldn't answer her phone.
And she, you know, but I had to, I had to have a, I had to communicate with her.
You know, it's, I couldn't just let it go.
Because it is something I had to be discussed immediately.
And I had to sit down and, you know, and be a dad, you know, sometimes it's not fun.
And I could not get through to her through any means.
And then I did something very interesting.
She has a Facebook account. I have a Facebook account.
Some of you may have seen this since been deleted.
But I went over to her Facebook wall.
And I wrote on it.
And I said, you know, hey, man, you really got a line.
And then she wrote back on my wall.
And then you have to hit wall to wall to compare, I guess.
And, you know, she had big attitude.
And I came back and, you know,
you know, continued with the writing saying, look, you know,
I think your life ain't so bad.
You might want to ask some of your friends here who many of whom have been over to the house.
Many who seem to be sometimes nicer than you around us.
And then she went off in the writing, and this is all happening on Facebook.
She went off and like, you know, when, what are you doing on Facebook anyway?
You're too old, you know, one of those.
And so I said, look, I'm frustrated.
And I have no other way to, you know, it's my last desperate way of communicating with you.
And a couple hours later, sure enough.
And I hope I really do hope that some of her friends on the Facebook said, hey, dude, you're out of line.
Which she was, as she knows it.
And she was a Brett Full and she was sorry.
And, you know, we broke through the barrier.
But it all happened on Facebook.
I just want that to be very, very bizarre.
An extremely bizarre parenting web 2.0 moments.
Hey, hey, there's something.
I think I hear a jingle coming.
Another web 2.0 parenting moment.
Alright, let's bang out some pod saying music show.
Big bang radio.
I just want to close my eyes to the world.
I need to spend the night with you, girl.
Just give me a reason for some day.
Release the sensation when you play.
Make a link, a link, a link, a go all the way.
Hear it on the radio.
What more say?
Let's see.
I want to hear what's up real wide.
Can't miss something say, trip from my mind.
To hear me in the meantime.
I just want to spend the night back in time.
And bring the sounds to life from my mind.
That's a dream you're reason for today.
Play it up and drive away.
Let it go, let it go, let it go, go all the way.
Hear it on the radio.
What more say?
Let's see.
I want to hear what's up real wide.
Can't miss something say, trip from my mind.
To hear me in the meantime.
I want to hear what's up real wide.
Can't miss something say, trip from my mind.
To hear me in the meantime.
I want to hear what's up real wide.
Can't miss something say, trip from my mind.
To hear me in the meantime.
I want to hear what's up real wide.
Can't miss something say, trip from my mind.
To hear what's up real wide.
To hear me in the meantime.
Can't miss something say, trip from my mind.
To hear what's up real wide.
To hear me in the meantime.
Can't miss something say, trip from my mind.
Can't miss anything say, trip from my mind.
star cast.
You can exchange gifts.
You can exchange to socks.
You can exchange fruit cake.
But you cannot exchange family.
So make sure you check out this Christmas when it hits theaters November 21st, 2007.
And I'm out.