Imagine headphones without wires.
Now their Sony's Bluetooth wireless headset, a rechargeable listening experience with 11 hours
of music playback, so you and your music are free to move.
Pick up yours at Sony.com-headphones.
Sony wireless headphones.
Your music, I'm plugged.
Radio content in my ears.
We don't need nuss.
Dinkin' grins, man.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Fantastic.
It's Adam Curry.
Hey world, we're women, we're comfortable shoes, and technology has changed the way you get your entertainment.
This is the pod show network, no big media, no excuses, no BS.
We don't have to share Charlie's 701.
Got me the strangest woman, believe me this shit's no sense, but I really get her going.
When I take out my big tennis, record of the band that plays the blues, the band that plays the blues.
She just loves my big tennis, record of a favorite blues.
Last night I tried to tease her, I gave her a little pinch, but she said I stopped her driving,
and get out that big tennis, record of the band that plays the blues, where the band
plays the blues.
She just loves my big tennis, record of a favorite blues.
I come her with kisses when we're in a love with stretch, and when she gets on excited,
she picks up my big tennis record of the band that plays the blues, where the band
plays the blues.
She just loves my big tennis, record of a favorite blues.
I got my big tennis record of the band that plays the blues, where the band that plays the blues.
That's the way to kick off the Charlie, huh?
Jackson, my big tennis, I guess those were from the days when they still had 78s,
because they were 10 inches in diameter, of course, the long playing format, and Maxi Cingle
came in the 12 inch, and for extra points, the single, how many inches was that?
It's a really important size.
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
It's a daily source code episode number 700 and one, it's Monday.
I met the man, a nice to wake up in my own bed next to my own wife, as opposed to someone else's wife.
And the cat and the dog on the bed, and it was really nice and sunshiney this morning.
I knew it wouldn't last and indeed now everything has gone gray.
It's really weird whether it almost feels like there might be some snow or definitely some
precipitation coming down, which is pretty much what it was on Saturday.
Those of you who don't listen to Noah Genda, the weekly show I do with John C.
I went out on Saturday for some flying, hadn't fired up the Delta Shiera for two months.
I looked in the logbook, November, sorry, October 15th was the last time I flew her.
And, you know, it's not good to have a piece of hardware sitting around, even though it's indoors
in a hanger and it's more or less dry and toasty warm.
And also, I just needed to fly.
I really did.
So Saturday we had about a 24-hundred-foot ceiling, and of course the weather on the temperature
on the ground being two degrees Celsius, every thousand feet you go up, you drop two degrees
in temperature.
Actually, sorry, it was about three degrees at ground level.
So I kept around two thousand feet under a well beneath the clouds, so even though it was
in freezing temperatures, there was no moisture I was hitting, because if you literally fly
through a cloud and it's freezing, guess what, you'll pick up ice on your wings, on your
prop and your struts and everywhere, and that's, you know, you can only do that so
you can only have a thin layer of ice before you start flying like a brick, but it was great.
And I'd spoken to the wing commander, I said, dude, you know, I haven't started this
thing up in two months, said no problem, just give a two full counterclockwise swings on
the prop.
I'm sorry, clockwise, because the prop actually runs counterclockwise, so clockwise against
the motion that typically turns in, just so you can grease up the cylinders a little bit.
I got in, primed, I turned the key and came to life immediately, God, that is so nice when
that happens.
I mean, you have the same thing with your car, right?
If you haven't started it in two months and all of a sudden, it just comes to life, magical.
So there were very few people flying as you can imagine, but it was great, just to get
up there, fly around, it's like riding a bike, I guess.
I still kind of remembered everything.
I didn't make the best landing in the world, I ballooned a little bit, but got her down
nice and safely and smoothly and very lightly, but with a little more runway use than
I'd expected.
And that was it, I had enough, you know, as you know me, I'm not a guy who just likes
to go fly around, I like to really be going from point A to point B. I might need, I was
actually maybe in considering doing a cross-channel trip this week, if not this week,
maybe right after Christmas, because it is the most, when the sun is shining and there's
no clouds, it's absolutely beautiful.
Okay, by the way, thanks to PG Kelly for suggesting, I opened up the show with my big
10 inch bull moves Jackson, it's not pod safe, but damn, damn funny.
PS says, PG aren't the listeners of pod show, the real boss of pod show, so in order
to please us, I suggest you take the rest of the year off, spend all that time with your
wonderful family, force yourself to spend this time now. We have no idea what we'll be
facing next year, God bless.
Yeah, sure. I don't think I could do that. I have no one to talk to about the crazy shit
I talked to you guys about. And of course not only do I talk to you, but you listen and
you actually talk back to me.
Adam, Kevin, from pod show, I'm a motion of the daily source code, I don't know what number,
I just put it on pause just now. Um, you say you had a pair of tickets or VIP tickets to
let's step on and you didn't go to go to some party. I'm going to talk to you like I would
any of my best friends. You're fucking crazy. You're either crazy or you're lying because there's
no way you would give up or any normal shoe and who likes rock music would give up VIP tickets
to see the biggest concert at the decade. There's no fucking way you do that. And if you did,
I don't know what to say except I know, I know you don't always say this, but you're
talking to Adam Curry and I do love you, but you're crazy.
Yeah, you might say I'm crazy. First of all, I fully believe Led Zeppelin is going on tour
and there's lots of indicators pointing in that direction as well. So I think there'll be ample
opportunity to see them on the road with Jason Bonham, of course, on drums replacing his father.
Second of all, this was not just any old Christmas party. This was the Pod Show London Office Christmas
party. And I only found out two days before the Christmas party that I had this opportunity through
my friends at Virgin Atlantic to go to the concert. And, you know, these are my friends, you know,
these are the people that I work with on a, well, almost daily basis. Of course, when I'm not
in London, it's Skype and an email. But, you know, these are the people that I see every single
day and we're working hard and we're always at it. And it's nice just to hang out with them unwind
and relax. And there's no way I was going to move the party. And of course, there's no way I'm not
going to show up. Arguably, I could have done a combination. But, yeah, I wanted to be there from
beginning to end. I thought that was more important. You know what, if you have your own company,
then you understand what I'm talking about. By the way, thank you very much to Ryan Randall for
making the fantastic logo for the wrong brand for today. You'll see it in the, in the album art
on the episode. If you're playing in the Pod Show, a Mashboard player, you'll see it. It's really nice.
I'm thinking that, well, it says fight planned ops lessons. I don't know if it should be planned or
perceived. Maybe we should make it perceived ops lessons. This is kind of catching, catching on.
And maybe what we should do is we should put these up on a flicker feed and make them,
make them available to anyone who wants to put them on to clothing.
Nah, maybe we need to control that crap. I just don't want any more projects.
I asked Chris McIntyre to make some t-shirts. So maybe he'll use this as a logo or maybe he'll
come up with something himself. Maybe we can use all kinds of different logos. That's even better,
probably. Because you know what? I'm just wearing the wrong t-shirt. That's right. I'm fighting planned
and perceived ops obsolescence and abstinence. Let's see. What do we have here? Oh, yeah, this
came in today. So disgusting. I'm just so tired of this. Well, nobody agrees with me.
Yeah, I could buy another phone at him. Lucky you. You know, I guess you're talking about this show
that I'm just whining about stuff. Is that it? Well, I'll say to you what I'd say to any guy calling
it and fuck you. And if you're going to do that, you know, at least in the naked picture.
This is probably about my complaints about being on the lookout list for the next 40 years.
So I'll have to go through an interesting ordeal coming into the United States.
However, I tried to enter the United States. And I'm Chris from Levittown. I got a question for you
with this. Oh, man, security thing. I'm wondering, I would advise this for nonsense and see if they can
just, you know, take it back to your country, but you're an American citizen. So you have different
rights. What happens if you don't cooperate? You know, don't get massive, you're, you know, mad or
anything like that, but just don't answer the questions you don't figure out of it. As your physical
answer, no. I don't have one on the side of what I want to do with you. When you ask for your
own, say, no, you're business. When you're saying, say, no, you're business. When you're saying, say, no,
you're business. When you're asking why you're here, say, no, you're business. When you're asking
why you're overseas. Say, no, you're business. What happens? What what happened? What would they do
to you? What could they do to you? It'd be interesting. I mean, I think most people follow
along these rules and because they think they have to, you'd mind the Patriotic is not a legal law.
Patriot Act would no-envoy the moment was signed. It's violates the Constitution. According to
the Constitution, it violates the Constitution. It's no-envoyant creation. So it's not even
an out of law. Although it's forced and they have the power to force it. So it might be an
interesting test case if you have the time to deal with it next time you come back to the
military. Don't cooperate. See what happens. Yeah. I'll be calling you from Gidmo is what will
happen. That is, of course, the actual reaction that this type of secondary screening evokes.
Of course, you want to say, like it's not your, in fact, I kind of, I think the second time in San Francisco,
I did say, when he asked me for a business card, I held up my passport and said, isn't this business
card enough? And I think that probably added 30 minutes onto my, my ordeal. So that's not a
very good idea. Besides, it's very misunderstood that you actually have no rights when you are
entering the United States, when you are at that kind of border, no man's land. You do not have
your civil rights. In fact, you actually subject to search and questioning by default. So you might
as well just do it. Again, I'm not against that. I'm not against checking out who's coming into
our country. That's, you know, border border control and protection is good and important for a number
of reasons. But not if you can't take law abiding citizens off the list. Obviously, that's not a good
thing. Hey, Adam, this is John and Dallas. The skull sucked the writing course of the TSA guy.
In the great, he probably walks around. Hey, man, in case you wonder who I am, I'm the skull
fucked the writing course of the TSA guy. Yes, right. You probably hear him in a child. Yeah.
Just listening to 69 and I am really appalled at what you're having to go through there.
I am curious. If you do request the information that got you on the on that list,
I'd really be interested in knowing what it is because recently with some of the things
you've been talking about, supporting Ron Paul, advocating a lot of things, you know,
calling Bush and more on, basically, it was the war and everything. I'm wondering if
it looks like it cut off in the middle there. Yeah. Maybe the only thing I can say about that
is a good start would be to elect Ron Paul. Every single interview or article that I read about
there's always a connotation saying, well, he's never going to get elected anyway. I find that
interesting. You know, with the election so far off with this campaign starting so incredibly early,
with the amount of money that he's raised, what did he do yesterday, by the way? Let's take a look.
Of course, I was posting like a crazy man on curry.com, keeping up with the donations. I know
it was over 18 million. Let's see what it is this more. Actually, right now, it's a 204pm on Monday.
So I'm loading up Ron Paul, 2008.com, 1718, looks like 18 million, 170,000. So probably about
six million dollars raised. And so this all happened yesterday on Sunday. And obviously,
this is fantastic. What a great result. I did get a call from folks at campaign HQ about a
number of things. They're working on Sundays, obviously. One of those about my endorsement video,
which I'm going to shoot tomorrow at the office in London. It's already written and ready to go.
So I'm very excited about that. I was contemplating maybe doing it just with the camera on my
Mac, but I thought, that would look so fucking YouTube. I want to make it kind of look professional.
What does that sound like here? Hold on. What's the, no, that's the heater. Sorry.
I really wanted to have some kind of stately impression. I wanted that to be good. And also,
so we're talking about the money bomb. And he, of course, was very excited about the amount of money. He
said, you know, it looks like we'll hit six or seven million, which he was pretty much on target.
That's thanks to RonPaul Graphs.com. What a fantastic idea. That is where you can actually see
the delta, I guess, between money donated on November 5th and this latest one for the Boston
Tea Party. He said, you know, but it's really, we've got to come up with something new.
And I said, what do you mean? He said, well, we've actually had the whole back on spending,
because we were running out of money. Because that was, of course, my question. I said,
hey, dude, have you guys started spending yet? What do you, and he's like, are you kidding me?
We're spending millions on advertising. Of course, in the primary states, where the, the
primary is, will be held in the, and the caucuses and what have you? He says, we actually had
the whole back because we were waiting for this next money bomb. You know, we need to have a regular cash flow
really as soon as we can. So I'm thinking, well, he mentioned a site to me. Is it RonPaul
Money Bomb? Let me say RonPaul Money Bomb.com. Because really what we need to do is we need to raise
a million dollars a week, I think. Yeah, Ron Paul Money Bomb. Let me see if it, I think we should do
one of these every single week, like every Saturday, you know, and we should just try, or maybe
buy a weekly, but we've really got to up the frequency. It's okay if we don't do, you know,
five or six million dollars every single time, but these guys need to have at least a million
dollars a week to spend. If they're going to put any dent in anything, we really need that. So
I think was just a couple of, you know, a little bit of reconfiguration on one of these sites.
I like the RonPaul Money Bomb. You know, we have to have a weekly tally, and we can do a week
over a week. People like doing that. People like looking at week over week donations. We have to do
something that is more than just, you know, weeks, weeks on end. So maybe January 1st would be another
good one, but really, you know, it should just be continuous stream. Very, very important. And of course,
I'm still waiting for the mainstream media to pick up on RonPaul. Let's see, said he with a, a very
skeptical tone. Oh, what's this? A crap. Looks like the internet crapped out. It's been happening.
Today on on and off, by and large on and off, it's been cropping out. Okay, can't look for that right now.
All right, what do you do when you're in the pinch?
Comics trip. Comics trip. Comics trip. Comics trip. Comics trip. Comics trip.
Comics trip. Comics trip. Come on in my friend. Hiya Adam. Hello.
Oh, have you heard this? Yes. So I'm about to take a big dose of blue pills at this and that's
this is my last audio comment in year 2007. Oh. So the new eutrity was finally signed by all
eulidus last week. It's very, very important and it enables fluid operation of now and large eul.
Also, Ireland still could dump this treaty in a referendum speaking of Ireland. I will reveal
you a secret. I was personally active undercover in campaigning in Ireland for their nice,
niche, sorry, not nice, niche treaty referendum in 2002. This referendum could then stop eul
enlargement. So eul also should go to the grassroots and do campaigning and whatever it's
needed to help your beloved Ron Paul to get them in action from a republican party. So Mary
shopping Christmas and a happy new year 2008 to you Adam. Carrie. That's a totally new year.
Yo. Yo. Well, I don't think European nationals can do much to help. You don't even see
Ron Paul. They don't even know who he is over here. Except maybe the people who listen to this show.
There's, I mean, it's all Clinton Obama, Giuliani. Maybe they've heard, you know, they say that
Hucka dude, Hucka Hucka, Hucka thing. Of course referencing Hucka B. And that's purely because of
the Chuck Norris idea, which by the way was stellar. It really was. So anyway, so I think the Ron Paul
campaign is going to be stepping up. Thank you very much. Comics are blogger for that report.
I got one for you. I got an awesome song that'll sound even better on your brand new
Sony headphones. Check them out at Sony.com slash headphones. They've got wireless headphones.
They've got special noise reduction headphones. If you've got a pair, call in. Let me know how they're
working for you.
Yeah, Adam is so count on calling you again. Again, Mary Christmas and sent you some more twisted
Christmas tunes. I hope you enjoy them. If you do, please feel free to enjoy them with the
masses out there again. These tunes are from Bob Rivers. I think Rodney Carrington,
some stuff. I just found all over the web there. But they are twisted Christmas tunes. Dude,
enjoy. Hope to hear him soon. All right. Talk to you later. All right. All right.
So Cal Tom, everybody. Send them in a nice folder of Christmas tunes.
I'll be sharing with you up until next Tuesday, I guess. 25th. You're like this one. Me and Mrs.
It's not in. But when Santa's gone, we'll lose to the north corner.
We meet every Christmas Eve as Chris Kringleaves, 630. The reindeer teams at the end.
Sex it twice, making all kinds of noise. Not a jack in the box displays.
We've got a thing going on. We've got to be extra careful. We've got those doors to build.
And I'm just on Santa's birthday, I want to sneak on and unwrap you behind the old man's
day. I'm going to send that one to Patricia. You know, Billy Paul, Mrs. Jones,
me and Mrs. Jones, one of our favorite songs.
Oh, this just came over the wire. This kind of sucks. Dan Fulgoberg, singer and songwriter
who's hits leader of the band and same old, same old langsign, helped define the soft rock
era died Sunday at his home in Maine after battling prostate cancer. He was 56. Oh, man, that is too young.
His death was announced Sunday on the singer's website. Dan left us this morning at 6am.
He fought a brave battle with cancer and died peacefully at home in Maine with his wife,
Jean at his side. It read, his strength dignity and grace in the face of the daunting
challenges of this disease when inspiration to all who knew him. Oh, man. Sorry to hear that.
Let's play some of Dan Fulgoberg. Interestingly enough, neither of the two songs that
were mentioned in this article. You probably recognize this one, though.
I've been in love with you. Stronger than any mountain could be. True than any tree ever
grew. Deeper than any forest right here. I love with you. I'll read, I'll read in the winter.
You said showers in the springs. We'll fly through the marvels of us with love on the rain.
Through the years as the fire starts to glow. Burning lines in the book of my life,
through the vine grows. And the pages start to glow. I'll read love with you.
I'll be in love with you.
Longer than every day she's in the ocean. I'll read, I'll read, I'll read, I'll read, I'll read,
I'll read, I'll read, I'll read, I'll read, I'll read, I'll read, I'll read, I'll read, I'll read,pre deinen
in peace, Dan Fogelberg, longer than one-one-six-point-seven-of-a-film-light-of-a-film-of-a-bully.
Great songs that I've made for sure.
Hi, Adam.
Allison Lee here from CrapCast.
Yes.
I just want to say hello.
I've been thinking about you, miss you, I've been listening.
First I want to thank you for being on your pod finder episode number 31, talking about
CrapCast.
Yeah.
Big hug to you.
Thank you.
And second, okay, here's a small world story.
So I'm listening to this past Thursday show, and you start talking about your
flying experience coming out of Newark and being held on the tarmac.
Well, guess what?
What?
I was being held on the tarmac on the plane right next to you.
I was sitting on the continental flight and our pilot came on and was trying to make
us feel better.
And in so doing so said, see, the plane next to us right there, they've been sitting
on the tarmac as well, but they don't have any electricity.
Just right.
Oh, so close yet so far, but then it gets better, and you should have been on my plane.
Cause guess what happened now.
You all got naked?
So, we're sitting there in after five hours.
Yes.
To Ruth comes on and says, due to people calling from their cell phones to the continental
airlines, as well as somebody having someone's private number, we are now going back
to the gate to let these people off.
Oh boy.
Please ring their bell.
She had right.
Head count to figure out the number of people we need to arrange this for.
Oh, busted.
It wasn't me, but I rang my bell anyway because at that point, hello, five and a half
hours sitting on the tarmac with a plane going nowhere.
I know shit.
I have Gordon Bethume's number, his office number at least probably wouldn't have helped
on a Friday evening, but I probably would have called it after five hours.
Well, the bells went off like crazy, and then people started screaming about getting upset
that we'd lose our place in line and the D.I. seeing.
Oh, yeah.
Then all of a sudden, everyone's at fucking aviation expert, right?
I'm on story short at six hours later, we were back at the gate.
Leaving the plane saying bye-bye to going to Florida for a few days, but so be it.
I was very happy that point to get off and get home.
So, but if I had only known, we could have been texting each other back in the
way through the window.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, small world.
That's small world.
So.
Say it.
Have a great holiday.
Love your show.
Say it.
The big hug.
Love you.
Yeah.
We could have had some nasty back and forth texting, baby.
Now the Twitter is broken on T-Mobile.
We could have done it directly.
Hey, Adam and he's stuck in San Diego.
Hey, you are looking forward to a great show about Shalom.
I've just been spending the last week catching up on the last two weeks of DSCs, so I'm
one behind.
I've just listened to most of 69 and I finally have to make a couple of comments.
First about the no shopping thing, very briefly, just over last couple of years of gas
prices have gotten high emails and calls for boycotts.
And they've got some gone around either.
All right.
Let me just interview for a second.
You've talked.
So this is about the wrong brand and about getting people to consume less to show the strength
of us consumers.
So it's not about stopping shopping entirely.
It's maybe about choosing what you shop and showing the strength of what the mighty consumers
of the United States of America can actually do.
Not entirely an organized program just yet.
So you know, not like I'm calling out yet, I'm just trying to figure out if anyone comes
up with a great idea, because clearly I'm stuck as how we can propagate this, then I'll
be happy to get behind it.
But anyway, so you're equating this to, I think what you're about to say here, you've
talked is that people just don't give a shit.
Is that what you're trying to say that when we all were saying, hey, don't buy gas,
people just were filling up their hummers.
Is that what you're saying?
Total gas outs or boycotts of specific gas stations and unfortunately, that sort of thing
just really tends to not work because people make up and offset what they're not buying
on that one day that they don't shop with shopping on other days.
So it would work that way for gas and I think, you know, I love to not go to a mall
or not go shopping for a day, but you know, I know that most people would probably offset
that by going shopping another day.
Let me just say one thing about the oil look in person.
First of all, you can't expect and we're so used to quick fix immediate result culture.
This kind of stuff is just not going to happen.
It's just not going to be, oh, look, look at what we did, you know, I don't think you can
quite do a Ron Paul money bomb on people not buying gasoline.
However, if you look at just what the markets are doing, the free markets, the consumers
have already really made a very clear choice.
So do you think that car companies would be making hybrid and electric cars out of their
own accord?
No, of course they wouldn't have.
They're doing it because consumers want to people want an electric car.
They want to hybrid.
So now everyone's jumping on board and making them.
You know, I think that's a real testament.
And whereas in the past, we know there is tons of evidence.
What was that car?
The EV, I think, electric vehicle that you actually couldn't buy but was given to celebrities
to try out and they took them away.
And there's a whole video out there, probably get it on video.google.com, the death of the
electric car.
I think is what it's called.
Let me Google that.
Well, we're talking.
Well, second, I'll do it right now.
The death, it wasn't the death of the electric car, we'll learn.
So you know, they clearly wanted to stifle that and now look at whatever everyone's doing.
The death of the electric car.
Google with me, everybody, here we go.
Let's see.
Yeah, the death of the electric car.
Three minutes, two minutes, oh gosh, I hope there's a, looks like lots of trailers.
Maybe it's not available in full.
Where did I see it?
I probably saw it on the plane.
Virgin probably had it.
It's like a documentary.
Hunt around if you find a link.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no.
If you find a link send a to me.
I'll add it to the show notes post show.
So that is working.
There is something happening there.
I think that has to be a sustained effort of a longer period of time.
Oh, there we go.
It makes a difference.
Yes.
And then as far as your travel woes, man, oh my god, dido to scull fucking the rotting
quirks of the PSA and Homeland Security.
You are being abused and reemed every single time you travel as these last few times.
It is horrendous, horrifying, terrorizing to hear.
Well, let me just make a clear that I don't think that the people at Homeland Security
are harassing me or abusing me, they're doing their job.
And they're doing it to the best of their ability.
I presume they're just trying to figure out if I pose any kind of threat based upon some
vague warning that is not telling them anything other than check this guy.
So now they're doing their job.
Nothing against that.
By the way, I have a very different feeling about the TSA security screeners who are
at the airport, who are the same people who use to pretend to be screeners back in the
90s when I was traveling a lot.
Throughout the 90s, I was always harping on those guys, like they're really the idiots.
They really are.
And you can hold me up as long as you want, you know, undress me all, feel me up.
I don't care.
I have nothing to hide from you.
But the system of being going through secondary screening and not being able to get off that
list or be cleared as it were.
Well, that's actually interesting.
I wonder if, you know, next time I'm next time I'm at the airport, I'm going to ask those
people who are the, who those people, it's Homeland Security who are selling the clear program.
Say, if I get this ID card and give you my fingerprints and you give me a retinal scan,
will that allow me access into the country?
Without being harassed, I'll ask that.
Let's see what they say to that, okay?
And I had to tell you as, and Israeli citizen, you know, I'm Israeli and, you know,
traveled enough, both into and outside of Israel and around the rest of the world to know what
real, airline and transportation security is.
These Israelis kind of have it down.
And what the TSA is doing, my friend, is not security.
It is theater of the absurd.
It is ridiculous.
So I can always ask them, but as I definitely hope, you can follow up with the Freedom of Information
Act request and maybe get some information about what they're doing to you because that is just
a piece.
So, stop putting in my two shackles and I'm just catching up in Hebrew.
What we used to, what you used to want us to say is, left these day in, at a hurry, go
fuck yourself and then, you know, or fuck you.
And then, of course, the recent thing is, I need to have a car at him.
I love you, Adam Curry.
Ah, left me clear.
I have a great weekend.
All right, you have to.
Thanks for checking in, man.
Oh, yeah, by the way, I totally agree.
Give me some Israeli security and then I'll buy it.
And I'm pretty sure that they can take you off of their list if they know that you're
clean or clear or whatever you want to call it.
All right, let's do one more.
Interesting, this came in today, not meant for a football Friday, but a manic Monday.
No, how's it going, Adam?
It's Jersey Todd, the official musical, just of the Chacha.
Yeah, yeah, I know, it's not my day, but I had to talk it today because I got something
for you that's just absolutely bizarre.
There's a band up on the Ponte music network that they're incredible,
called the mob stories at a Belgium.
They put up a new track in the last couple of weeks.
And I've been listening to it a lot and I love it.
There's something incredibly catchy about this track, but also at the same time this band is
incredibly unique.
They, I've never heard of a band like this.
They actually have two female lead singers.
We've played them before on Fubar Friday, but this track that they posted, it's like,
nothing I've ever heard before.
I mean, I love it.
It's incredibly catchy.
There's a beat to it.
They are overwhelmingly enthusiastic and seeing the song.
The problem is I have no fucking idea what they're talking about.
Check this out, and maybe you can help me out with this.
It's the mob stories with big dick, but it's not a, I have no idea what they're
fucking talking about, check this out.
Sound is about to happen.
There's got to be no longer rule on the track.
Everybody's watching.
You don't know what to do.
Yeah, it's taking some beefy videos.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's taking some beefy videos, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's taking some beefy videos, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's taking some beefy videos, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's taking some beefy videos, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You are living me.
I hide, I'm not like you, you can hardly make this,
I, you hate right for me, you'll never want me down me.
I hide just not done like you,
you can hardly make this, I, you hate right for me.
You'll never want me down me.
Whoa, I got this feeling.
If I'm just bad to help us
There's just been a lack of hope
Much every sight
Everybody's watching
You don't know where to go
Gotta speak
Don't be beaten in sight
Yeah, yeah, yeah
We sleep safe
That we get you
We want you
We love you
We love it's cool
Cause it's curious
Yeah, yeah
Gotta gotta get a lot of no one
We are not bad
But it's what it says
What it says
It's what it says
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah
I'm like you
That's true
Is it?
I'm not like you
You can hardly make me smile
You ain't right for me
You'll never walk me down me
I'm not like you
And hardly make me smile
You ain't right for me
You'll never walk me down
Easy, easy
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, right go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go that's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
They kind of look cute in a nerdy kind of way.
The mob stories from La Bosaica.
So you can find them on the podcast and music.
Network link in the show notes, of course a daily source code.com.
Alright, well, 41 minutes 36 seconds, not bad for a day's work.
Going into the city tomorrow, Wednesday, Thursday, so there will be shows, not quite
sure what time I have to go in yet, but there's plenty of stuff to do before we hit
the holidays, plenty of work to do.
Looking forward to more of your comments through the voicemail feedback phone lines.
Of course, Adam and Pod Show.com if you want to email me at daily sourcecode.com for all
of the links, including promo codes there for cheap-ass domain names.
Now that the quality of the domain names is cheap, but you can get them for cheap-ass prices.
If you just want one for $6.95, you might check out code DSC3 or just go to daily sourcecode.com
when you find all the links there.
Hey, got a pretty cool offer coming up.
I think sometime mid this week, I'll tell you about that later.
Dronatically, reduce ambient noise by up to 85% with Sony's noise canceling headphones
at work, home or travel, shut out the noise and really enjoy your tracks.
Get yours at Sony.com slash headphones, Sony headphones, your music never sounded so good.