Welcome to the Daily Source Codes 630.
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello,
hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, we're
and even if you're a sleepy Christie's fool,
it's a bad of a curry.
Cool.
You guys are beautiful.
Okay, we'll be here.
Yeah.
I saw stars around.
They had a power green steam here from New York, and I wanted it to just thank you for
D.K.S. like or what a lot of us hope it would be like.
Watch it for one slide, the family stone, soundtrack to our live.
Every day people are surely.
Thanks a lot.
Some people go on slow breaks.
How do you do?
How are we?
Nothing's wrong but it's alright.
You know, how about your shoulders that you don't want to be environmentally conscious,
because it's a really tricky thing to do.
I'm just hoping that they can cope with some newer way of fueling things and cleaner ways of doing things.
Because we do the usual things like carbon neutralizing and stuff like that.
You know, all the flights and all the transport.
But I don't think it's enough.
I think there's a lot more we could do.
You know, there's still a lot of waste.
And in both we've been here today's kind of helping and making a point.
And hopefully more people will pay attention and get part of the course.
Thank you very much indeed for coming to join us today.
Enjoy the rest of live Earth.
But here we'll leave Jonathan.
There you go. That was it. It's down there with Damien David.
I'm joined here with the Danish and Germany.
It was for weeks, which I can't possibly explain to you.
But it's lovely to have you both here.
Why not if you win the same hat as Jack Osball?
It's lovely.
I started off.
No, they were good on sale.
Oh, price outside.
So I picked one up.
Let's go to get one.
But he couldn't carry it off.
Why is he selling them outside?
Yeah, I think they made it of hemp.
Which is a natural fabric and fiber we should be using.
I'm going to try it on too.
How you enjoying the concert so far today?
Yeah, it's brilliant.
Yeah, it's great.
It's great.
It's a nice and best music for yourself.
I enjoyed racing life.
I thought there was no photographer or fantastic.
And I'm very much looking forward to saving it.
I think they might be coming up next.
Genesis was great.
Genesis is really good.
Really good.
Well, it was at its last time.
It's like a guilty pleasure sometimes.
It's nice to see they're still alive.
If they find out what that was, it's nice to see it.
I've got some energy as well.
Lots of energy.
It's better than their age.
You're going to say that.
Let me ask you.
Have you turned off all your appliances before coming out today?
Yes.
Absolutely.
Everything.
I left the house and you were on the radio.
When I switched off?
Yes.
You normally do it.
Really.
But it is genuinely, it is wowing.
It is.
You know, what's so weird?
I find out.
I don't know if you're the movie.
We kind of have none about this for quite a long while.
Yeah.
And it's only now that it's getting to a real, almost the crisis point.
We're getting to do anything about it.
Yeah.
We don't speak well in human rights.
It's quite worrying.
We went out to do a marathon in Kenya for the saving planet Earth, which is on Monday,
running wild on BBC.
So that's why you're here.
That's why we're here.
I think we're just free loading.
Yeah.
We've actually done something like that.
We went out and did a marathon between five of us.
John Colchore, Kelly Find Liberty X.
Well, he did the big bit.
He did the eight Mars.
How did three and a half.
You know, the better legs.
Someone hunky.
Yeah.
It made us realise.
You know, I've fed a baby Rhino.
And you realise that this...
Hold on.
You brushed fed a baby Rhino.
No, I can't say that on the series.
I think you love formula milk.
I gave this baby.
Low, low.
And he fed a baby Rhino.
It made it really.
It's got a switch off his point.
Got a switch off my point.
Well, if let's then let's go out and feed a baby Rhino for the future of mankind.
Then why can't we turn off our TV?
It does happen to the two.
That's our table.
And what about your baby Rhino?
There's a baby Rhino that to keep your chance, so he reads his name.
He says that's right and it's all that I've written.
I make quite a good point.
I thought I'd hurt him.
You know, you get...
No, I really don't know what I did.
You know, am I?
Yes.
When you say good-up?
No, you know, am I?
Why can't they give you an oxygen to offset your am I was to plant trees instead of flying more?
Greenmile?
Yeah, is instead of encouraging you to fly more.
The Greenmile was to do with death blow.
What?
It was a curse.
It was a good movie.
Good idea that actually penalize what they instead of animals that take them away from us
Look at him with his saintly glow just because he fed a baby wine out
Right save the rhino, please, happy with the friend the rhino
Did you cladal it?
45 days old, it was quite big
Blimey, did I have a hole yet?
No, it did after he was feeding it
He gave you
He wasn't feeding it, he wasn't feeding it
If you've got a baby wine out of me, please send it into the list and it's he knows how to nurse them
Well, I'm bad you guys got off your backside, so this I feel bad now that I haven't won a
I'm going to turn everything off when I go home and leave it off for as long as possible
But genuinely I'm hoping the message gets across you think of these kind of events can change things
You think people do change their mind?
I just think about it
I think I can enjoy it as well enjoy the entertainment
I think they do, I honestly I have not been the greenest person
I have actually now started switching things up and started recycling
I know it's taken up to this point for me to do it by our machine site
She even can borrow your house
Nice to meet you guys
The total night, but I'm afraid it would probably get worse
We're going to go out now alive because just about to start on the stage
And we've all been looking forward to this
I know one of the best fans around at the moment
I think they're just about to come on right now
It is the fabulous
Cassibian
Thank you
Hello, we're Black nécess
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah. yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
come on, come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, good!
Please....
...冷 up
Stop
There's only one way to Nova
You walk autowash away
One, two, one, two, one, two.
Check one, two, one, two.
Don't bless you.
One, two, one, two, one.
I just want to address the whole world where we want to save your energy.
Because I can't, I try.
One, two, one, two, one.
Come on!
One, two, one, two, one, two, one.
Come on, two, one, two, one.
Come on, two, one, two, one, two, one.
Welcome to the Daily Source Codes 630, where you're here.
All kinds of commentary, stories, savants.
And of course, it's Fubar Friday.
So what better way than to kick it off with some great Friday Fubar music?
One, two, one, two, one, two, one, two, three.
Or something else.
Here's the DSC 630.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic DSC Battle Curry!
What ever low wants?
Love again.
And the man, the low wants you.
Pick up your mind to hand.
Low regrets.
Be glad yourself, enjoy yourself, you're through.
I always get what I aim for.
And your heart, I'm so...
Is what I care for.
But ever low wants.
Don't be bad, don't be weak.
No again.
Don't get wrong.
Some take off your phone.
Don't you know who can do it.
Don't be bad, don't be weak.
It's never more.
You're no exception to the room.
I'm here as it's the better you feel.
I always get what I aim for.
But ever low wants.
You're no person.
Don't you know who can do it.
I'm here as this, never you feel me.
Hmm.
I'll need D.J. Redworm could make a Saturday morning sound just right.
Sarah Vaughn and Nellie Frutato featuring Tim Bolan with the Primiscuous and whatever
Lola wants mashed up into Primiscuous Lola.
What are you doing daily source code?
630.
It's kind of weird show because I missed Fubar Friday, although it's still Friday somewhere
I believe.
And maybe it has crap.
So we're going to try and do a, let's see.
We're going to do a show with the attitude of a Fubar, but with the chilled out
Meloness of, you know, like a Saturday morning kind of.
Beautiful weather outside here outside of the curry manner.
And today is the 7th of July 2007, which means live birthday.
And of course we have a direct satellite connection to that, so we'll see what's going on.
And maximum music.
I saw stars around your feet once.
Little lights like fish you swim in.
Took off your high turn, your chin, and time stood still.
And I said, Mark, space, we walked up in the hills of times.
Like this sometimes, like those we felt that he'd have all yearns.
I feel my head and spill my tears in one time.
In one time, in one time.
In one time, I will see.
I saw time around your feet once.
Little seas that blink and shimmer.
Throwing on more cold hearts.
You need your mark and take your place.
In one time, in one time.
In one time, I will see.
I saw time around your feet once.
Little seas that blink and shimmer.
Throwing on more cold hearts.
In one time, in one time.
In one time.
I think 2004, maybe it is certainly 2005, let me see, where is it, 46-plus?
You can tell what I did is, yeah, July 19, 2005 was added to the podcast music network.
You can tell that I've gone back to my songs played, I have like 28 pages of songs that
I've played that I can review on, the PMman is pretty cool.
So I should probably step back to Thursday night because that's the last time, actually
we spoke just before Christina and I left to go to see the Justin Timberlake show and of
course, thanks to the folks at Virgin Atlantic Marketing and the personal account management
services for hooking us up with the tickets in a sweet no less at the O2 venue, formerly known
as the Millennium Dome.
I'd never been in there, it was great.
Great show, Fergie was on first, Timberlake actually did a set in between two sets of
Timberlake, it was a pretty good show, I got a little tired at the end of basically watching
a music video on stage, but it was good, JT, as we call him.
JT, yeah, he's a real musician, man, and he's got a band, he respects the band, it was actually
really nice at the end, he brought everyone up on stage, all the dancers, they all took
a bow, you know, it wasn't your typical good night and come back for an encore and then
leave and speed off in the limo as much more personal than that and sound was pretty good
for that venue too.
And of course, the most fun was hanging out with Christina, which was really the entire
point Friday.
So a lot of work went into Friday in preparing for a company wide football, where
we were laying out strategy of the company, strategy of some of our products, introducing
each other to what we do because we're now probably about 125 strong, so there's about
100 people in San Francisco and the rest of the company gathered by a web ex, which by the
way, I hadn't used web ex in a while, damn, that's how I'm going to do all my meetings
from now on.
They got phone bridges that tie in, the video was fantastic, they've got chats, sharing
of documents, really, although that part we fucked up, we didn't get the PowerPoint
working.
And I actually created a little video for everybody, you know, because I wanted a little
different impact than just the web ex video and put a link on curry.com, you can find
the football channel that I put together, a lot of the episodes that we watched together.
And so that really started 11 a.m. San Francisco time, at 11, 20, my video file had finally
uploaded, so we'd already started and of course I couldn't get on web ex while I was
doing the upload because I wanted to conserve the bandwidth.
And that took us up to about 10 o'clock and I was fucking wiped, I'm sorry, I had already
had a lot of songs and I just couldn't pull it together, I was so incredibly tired and I
knew Christina was going to have to get up early because there's she's off to a place called
new key, or as I hear him say, new key in Cornwall.
And this apparently is a tradition, at least a recent tradition where after the primary grade
school and all through, you know, up until the sixth form, and now everyone's going off to
different schools as kind of like a final hurrah, the kids all go off to this, it's like a holiday
trailer park camp. And there's no real adult supervision, of course there are rules within the camp,
but it's kind of like, yeah, one parent who I like Simon this guy that rocks his dad,
he said, you know, it's kind of like safety by numbers, you know, you got a couple hundred these
kids and it seems to work itself out. You know, there is, there is someone who can kick some
ass at the, at this holiday camp park, if need be, but apparently things go reasonably well.
So it's, it's weird though, it's hard, it's hard to wave to your daughter and another she's gone
gone for a week. Oh, although I know Patricia now I'm going to have a lot of fun.
Let's see, um, so let me just check our satellite connection here. Yes, okay, the satellite connection
with the BBC is working, live Earth is taking place today, Cassabian that was just on stage.
And I've got to tell you, I have, I'm a little conflicted by this. Now first of all,
obviously, the idea that we can, um, raise awareness for protecting our planet, absolutely.
The whole idea of save the Earth because it's falling apart and going to implode and, you know,
we're killing our, our entire ecosphere, um, maybe true, may not be true. It didn't just start
all of a sudden, you know, so there's a lot of emphasis on saving us because we're going down a
black hole. And when I'm a little conflicted about it, you know, I have read a lot and,
in fact, I posted a link to a different type of documentary, which shows a contrarian view to the
inconvenient truth, Al Gore documentary. But the BBC is just bringing on so-called experts one after
another, you know, and they're just rattling off all these statistics and, you know, 40% of the
world uses glacier or water to survive and the glaciers are disappearing, you know, implying,
of course, that 40% of the world will have no water. It may be true, but, you know, it's a very
one-sided view and- and I'm just trying to figure out, who's doing this? Who's putting this one
out? This show? This is huge. It's a huge show. It costs a tremendous amount of money for the
facilities. It's around the globe, you know, it's- I think it's going to be heavily sponsored in
the U.S. So it'll be interesting to see who's sponsoring it, but I'm just going to predict.
Now, again, I do my bit to- I do what I feel is sufficient to contribute to
conserving energy, conserving energy is the main thing that we do, but this whole idea of buying
carbon credits, I predict this is a bubble market. It's, you know, it's a crazy, crazy financial instrument,
so you can, you know, you can buy credits. So someone is going to- the way I understand it is this,
a company may have X amount of carbon emissions they can emit per year, and if they reduce that,
that reduction can be translated into credits, which now are being traded and bought and sold all
over the world, a lot of it online. And to me, it feels a little- a little weird as a financial
instrument. So I think there's going to be a lot of wealth created. This whole green thing in general,
already the U.S. government, I think, spends $4 billion on green projects. You think we could
solve something with that amount of money. But anyway, it's a great show, and, of course,
people bonding together and feeling good together and having a common goal and mission together,
that's always good. And of course, you know, concerts and stuff like that here in the U.K., that's
culture, particularly during the summer, people love the festival, they love getting out, they love
being together, sharing music together. So it is a good thing, but still very, very surprised that
at all of this information that's being stated as a fact, and just put my question marks around
statements that clearly cannot be completely taken as fact, because they're just so much information,
we know so little.
Yeah, how's it going, Adam? It's Jersey Todd, the official musicologist of the
Chacha, and the hardest work in lawyer and podcast and baby. Hey, you know, I know what you like.
I know you like the ladies. And let me drop a little bit of pimped knowledge on you today,
because I've got something very, very special. I've got, let's just call it a Manajataadi,
because, well, you know, every once in a while I find something really, really good up on the
podcast, music network, and tonight is no exception. Tonight, I've got, well, let's just put it this
way. This is going to be the one time that I'm ever going to be able to tell you that I've got
two, two, very, very funky chicks, and that actually happened to be a good thing. These girls have
the funk, and they're funky all over, and they're the band, the mob stories, and the song that
they're going to play, called epinephrine, just rocked my socks off, and I think you're going to
like it, too. Check this out on your football Friday. Talk to you later.
Singing you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you
you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, don't you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, you cry, that's what's going to get me cold, it's what what is going to get me cold and it's what, it's what is what we happen to do to you for you for you for me for you for me for you for me if it's what, what the one is you for?
I ain't even a lie, but I think of you for a few years
It's been for a bit, guys, you come back, baby
Well, it's been too much, it's been so good
I'm back, now I'm back, so that's the way
Three weeks, I'm gonna use the big amount, girl, we'll stay here
Getting so much fresh, yeah, yeah, yeah
We're ready, I'm a little busy, yeah, yeah
Well, baby, I'm a little busy, yeah
We're ready, I'm a little busy, yeah
See you tomorrow, baby, hey
See you tomorrow, baby
Well, baby, I'm a little busy, yeah
Let's never, I don't wanna be too lazy, let's stop
Let's stop, let's do it, baby
See you, I'm a little busy, let's go
Come, come, come, come down on the ride
And make you lose your life to this
You
Oh, I know everything I do
Just want to be my friend
And grow up with that face and trend
We'll let the head
To the other workers in the band
And no long days to damn about you
Girl
One gives a damn about you
No one gives a damn about you
Girl
Don't you try to try to try
If I didn't try
Try to try
Try
If I didn't try
Well make you lose your life to this
You
Never let me go
Make you lose your life to this
You
Bye-bye!
We're the attitude of a bar Friday.
It kind of reminds me of some funk like from the 80s, you know what I mean?
I was just, well, the song was running a presenter was on stage.
They're trying to get Al Gore to come on, you know, turn on the sound of the background.
They're trying to get, you know, trying to get Al Gore on by a satellite into Wembley Arena.
And she was saying, you know, if we all just turned off our pilot lights,
we would save enough carbon emissions.
Here comes Al Gore.
Enough carbon emissions to fill Wembley Stadium over 400 times.
I'm like, what does that mean?
And award-winning luminary.
Okay.
Why don't we just stay with us for a second.
You may have missed it.
So let's see what he has to say.
Oh, there's a nice picture of our planet, Washington.
Hey, they probably use Google Earth, didn't they?
This is the National Museum of the American Indian where Al Gore speaks to the world.
Thank you so much.
Dr. Mann, Guggie Cook, what beautiful and eloquent words.
Thank you acting director Tim Johnson and the National Museum of the American Indian.
All right.
Al, hello, Wembley, dude.
Hello, Wembley.
Grace, and inviting us here today.
The American Indian people.
Oh, no.
He doesn't know.
I think he doesn't know.
We've been here for years here and around the world.
Have been very eloquent in their warnings about what we're doing to the Earth.
Oh, be going down.
They remind us that solving the climate crisis will require not only new laws and new technologies,
but also a new understanding that we are connected to the natural world.
Some who don't understand what is now at stake.
Oh, I have to catch the highlights on the 11 o'clock news.
I hear someone much more important than Al Gore.
Hey, Adam Howard Greenstein here from New York.
And I wanted to just thank you for DSC 628 on July 4th, which was a really a great way of trying to explain to everybody out there in the world.
What America is about?
And it's really tough to understand if you're not living here and growing up here.
But I think it did a pretty good job.
One thing, though, I think it did miss is that we are here in America most of us, just everyday people.
I mean, whether you're a savant or regular listener to the Charlie,
whether you're nylon, pissing you off or prolific programmer who's sometimes difficult to understand.
You know, we're all out here just being who we are and who we are for the most part is just everyday people.
And so if you're feeling it, if you're feeling the love on Fubar Friday and you want to kick out some really amazing music that tells a lot about what America's like or what a lot of us hope it would be like.
Want you to throw on Sly in the family's stone from the soundtrack to our lives.
And everyday people here on the Charlie.
That's probably the one.
I'm not a bad idea.
I checked it with the organization for the preservation of the soundtrack of our lives.
It said, go ahead, Curry. You can play that.
You've got me.
I've never really paid one again.
There is a lot of fantasy.
There is one lot of fantasy.
There is really a lot of fantasy.
There is a lot of fantasy.
There is always a lot of fantasy.
Oh, I can't believe you long, yeah
But I can't believe you long, yeah
We got to live to hell, yeah
There's a ground where the flowers look black
I'm that pretty, you see the wind, I'm that corner
So I'm the white one, yeah
I'm that lost, and so I'm that so wanted to be
We're Howard New York, sliding the fountain stone, everyday people
On a maximum music, Fubar, strike that Saturday
Let's see how I'll's doing for a second
He's been talking all that time during the song
Does he have the attention of Wimley Stadium yet?
I just present an Abraham Lincoln
Ow, show me some polar bears that are dying, man
That's what gets my attention
Hi Adam, it's Neil Ford
Just being listening to 69
And you're a bit about podcasts and stuff
I'm just out of interest, and we're on YouTube
Can I find videos of people shooting Bucky Rockies?
Yeah, they're out of these
Because I have to say that the idea of that is just
It's my day
So thank you very much for giving me an image of that
And yeah, if you've got the appropriate keywords to search
And I will, I suspect Bucky Rockie and Alice would work
I'd much appreciate it
Actually, you'll keep up the great work
So it's been brought in recently
And yeah, take it
Thank you, thank you so much
Well, I don't know if you actually took the time
Or, you know, all it is is three words put it right into YouTube
Ask Rocket and fireworks
And there's a whole bunch of them
This is my favorite actually
I'll put a link to this in the show notes
So wait, let me just set this up
What did you put it in?
So there's, and there must be at least 10 or 15 videos
Of people shooting, you know, like the small baby finger
Type bottle rockets out of their ass
So you stick the rocket between your butt cheeks
And then someone else lights it and it goes off
And most people are standing and kind of clamming
There is an art to it, okay?
Because there's not a lot of force coming out of the rocket
And if you just place it in the neck of a bottle
There's no friction
So, you know, people clenching it between their butt cheeks
That's friction, so eight times out of ten
The rocket ignites, it doesn't leave the buttocks
And it synges their ass
And it's funny, of course, but this one guy
I'll just rewind this a little bit
This one guy
He, he actually, he gets on his back
And he, and he points his ass
He's not like in a porn position
Points his ass up
And his friends then stick the rocket in
Well, let's listen in
Oh, it's on his head
But if you go get on your back
Look, they put it in
Just keep going with that
They're fighting a bleibt in
Somebody hold his legs back and somebody's like
The guys holding his body's feet
To asshole, don't worry about it
Just your balance is first.
Asked down.
Pulling your sack up first.
Pull your sack up.
But this is really a very adventurous pose
I would have to say.
And guys, like, he is a human rocket launch
and now what happens is, of course.
And if there goes, it's not leaving the buttocks.
He is, he is writhing.
And now it's about to explode while I was still in his ass.
Wonderful.
Ah, the things that get me going on a Saturday morning
I can't fall asleep all when I'm tired.
The only way I'll sleep is if I die.
I need a little luxury with your arms around me.
And the feeling that you're all I need.
We gibi my idv.
Breathing onto your head.
So why do you all want to get me here when Irie?
Oh, stop complaining, you'reams around me.
And the feeling that you're only
I'm the free
that I care
And I'm the free
You know
And the feeling that you're only
I need a little opportunity
But your arms are around me
And I'm the feeling that you're only
Again, from the archives of the Potsay Museum Network
And definitely Golden Oli for Charlie Listeners, the Muffs
And just a little bit of luxury
Hi, this is John from Dallas on the listener
I am currently driving to work and listening to Monday's episode of the BSC
I just wanted to ask you about this nine-line character
Is this guy for real?
It's somebody that's on your payroll
It's getting accurate
What a negative shit
John, I can't stand listening to this guy
I'd rather listen to CSB, he's negative too
But at least he's funny
This guy is just a whiny mother fucker
Language, please
No, he's not on the payroll
He's not, I don't think he's an actor
We still don't really know what he does
Because he won't devolves the information
But he's for real dude, he's totally for real
And now that I've figured out that I've been missing out on voice mail messages
I'm sure I'll be hearing a lot more from him
Hey Adam, listen to Craig here
Wondering where CSB comic strip blogger is
I heard nylon talking
And he's certainly grabbed you
But comic strip blogger is more interesting
That's a survey
The other thing is on your set list
Can you make some of your questions the optional
So people who are a little more privacy concerns
And still be involved
That would be useful
Take care, do a great job, bye
Well that's an interesting question
People who have a little more privacy
Well you have to, I guess you have to let me know
Which ones you'd want to be optional
That's actually the way I think it should be done
You should be able to opt out of any question
Eh, some to look at, I'm sure I will get around to it
Sometime in the coming week
Of course two questions, two statements, two callers
Back to back saying that they're not big fans of the nylon
Who of course will continue to be able to enjoy
The Charlie as his platform
Because he has such contrary views
And both people also asking about CSB
The infamous comic strip blogger
Comic strip
Adam Kerry, you fucking idiot
Your DSC publish on USA Independence Day
2007 was not shitty
You may be ignorant, lazy and shallow asshole
But your sincerity, hands more
You are just too kind, comic strip blogger
Let me clarify one thing
You are fucking wrong about pointing out
UK and Brits as main brothers of USA
Actually, there's only 24 million English Americans
Originating from Britain
But 49 million German Americans
34 million Irish Americans
14 million Italian Americans, 10 million Polish Americans
I'm Polish myself, 8 million French Americans
And only 5 million Scottish Americans
Like yourself
You know CSB, CSB
So maybe you misunderstood me
I was talking about the original settlers who went over
They came from Britain
And I'm talking about in the past two hundred and twenty thirty years
I'm talking about the original, you know, the guys in the 1700s
That's what I meant
And by the way, what are you reading from what's your source?
Many, many, many millions of other known British Americans
And English language, anyway, is just a mixture of German, French, and Italian
So while USA has British and European, your roots
It is much more than the sum of its parts
And if you add them, carry
Blackberry, really, like UK
Then get yourself UK citizenship
And does EU citizenship
And have both USA and UK citizenship
And for facts, they stop whining about these British American things
And concentrate on the future on your pod business
You fucking quanker
You're a comic strip
I feel so much better
Comic strip
I know what to focus on
Comic strip, she spent the rest of my life doing
Thank you so much, strip
I love you man, thank you so much
Hey Adam, it's Father Roderick
You'll never guess where I'm recording this
You know how much I like to travel and to take people with me to
It's Lee, Franz, Ireland, or the United States and my
Sound seeing tours for the Catholic insider podcast
But this is without a doubt the coolest place I've ever been
I am walking around in Middle-earth
You might have heard of this new online role playing game, The Lord of the Rings Online
But it likes second life for elves and hobbits
Now I love this game
It is one of the most beautiful online worlds I've ever visited
And once you're in the game, you can travel to all these fantastic places that you remember from the Lord of the Rings movies and the books
And the great thing about these virtual worlds is
Even though it's cold and rainy here in Holland, in Middle-earth, it's warm and sunny
Hey, I'm thirsty
Here's a hobbit pub, let's go inside
Hello there, how may I help you?
I'd like to have something to drink please
Stay and have some tea
Tea is far too hot for tea, I'd rather have a pint
Don't please to be of service
Let's sit down first there
You know Adam, hundreds of thousands of gamers visit this world every day
But I think that a lot of them might not be aware of the fascinating history of the sights and the people they come across here in Middle-earth
Did you ever wonder why elves are immortal?
And where are these horrid orcs come from?
Just the other day I was in the old forest for a quest
And I met Tom Bombadale
Now did you know that this guy is thousands of years old
And if you leave the Shire and travel north
You'll discover this incredible city on the shores of Lake Evendim
Like Twilight as the elves call it
It's now in ruins and it's a dangerous place
But do you know it was once a royal city founded by one of the ancestors of Aragon
My new podcast series, The Secrets of the Lord of the Rings, is a first podcast ever that is completely recorded within Middle-earth
Every show is a sound seeing tour of a different region
And if you plug in your earbuds and close your eyes
The magic of the theater of the mind will take you
A journey of discovery through this wonderful world created by J.R.R. Tolkien
So if you play the Lord of the Rings online or if you're just a fan of the movies
Where you've read the books head over to www.sqpn.com
And subscribe to the Secrets of the Lord of the Rings
And now it's time for a pint for these hobbits here
Talk to you later Adam
It's time to organize a search party
Father Roderick has has completely lost it
He's gone deep into a second life type world
He may need me
Sounds great though Roderick
Like in that a lot, dude
It's a football Friday Saturday edition
Maximum music
People go on smoke breaks
Others serve the web
Some people get up and grab a coffee
But I'm not one of them
I don't like being a net
All I smoke is grass
I prefer to spend my time sitting on my skinny white ass
I've been some life's all around the room
Just right before I start
Sometimes I'm in there for 30 minutes
And all I do is fart
So if the facts machines on the fritz
And that'll copiers go in berserk
Don't ask me to play Mr. Repair
And when I'm taking a dog at work
Or I'm taking a dog, I'm taking a dog
I'm taking a dog at work
But don't bother me
You can't just see him just taking a dog at work
I go in around 11 o'clock
I go back in after lunch
Every time it comes out right on the dime
And it looks like a nestly crunch
And I'm afraid to you who's the Johnny
And that's all my floor
There'll be a 10-minute layover
Before anyone should open the door
After he's been taking a dog
We're taking a dog, we're taking a dog
We're taking a dog and we're equal
But don't bother me
You can't just see him just taking a dog at work
And if I'm not in my disc
And I'll be on the porcelain throne
I'll waste my day on the crapper
Until this time to go home
I don't talk to me through the storm
And you break my concentration
The last thing that I need right now
Is a case of constipation
And I'm a fan of the courtesy flush
That's yeah
I like my ass tape a three-plot kick
You know I sat on the shit of this afternoon
And read mail bills moving dick
Twice so you can call me Ishmael bitch when I'm taking a dog
But taking a dog
It would be
I don't bother me
You can't just see him just taking a dog at work
I don't care the boss is looking
I don't care if the phone is ringing
I'll be in here dropping the news
And you'll probably hear me singing
That I don't take a dog
But taking a dog
It would be like
I don't bother me
You can't just see him just taking a dog
That would be
I'm proud of him
He's popping his head
And then he's going back
You
Yeah
I'm proud of him
You're as if
So the next time you're in your office
And your stomach starts to jerk
Get outta your chair and drop a shower
And take you and don't badly
Well luckily I work at home
So
Dumping makes a lot more pleasurable
You know what I'm saying
Stock, stuck in my heart
We're taking a dump at work
I don't know, Dan Johnson, Daniel Johnson Jr. from Southwestern Ohio, which is listening
to Daily Source Code 629er from Thursday.
And really, this is a kind of contact content and the real reason why I listened to your
show is to, I'm really excited about the channel concept and some of the stuff that you're
talking about with being able to do, I've been watching the Cheddar videos that you've
been posting over at curie.com.
And pretty excited about that.
And as I mentioned in an earlier audio comment, I've been using channels back since August
or whenever you launched a pod show plus, which is actually, hey, happy birthday to you,
pod show plus, by the way, I guess there's a birthday coming up.
And one of the things that I have noticed though is that I'll receive a message from
a content producer, podcaster or blogger or, you know, a content producer saying that they've
uploaded the news show.
And I'll go and check the feed or I'll go and check the channel and I'll see that it hasn't
shown up there.
And I'm really getting to geeky, geeky, would be helpful to understand how all this
is going to work out with how the feeds are going to get up to it because you're talking
about matching up channels and individual items within a channel and how the feeds get
updated because it seems like there are some days that I won't get anything and then
maybe a couple of days later I'll start getting everything and I'll be catching up with
everything.
I subscribe and choose a former iPod lemon to, a couple of pod show plus feeds, one
of them is my music podcast feed and then one is like everything else.
And I'm just wondering if there's a maximum number of shows you can put into a channel
or if that really even matters, if you could set some light on that, that would be great.
They had jobs to get and come in from to you from a Southwest and Ohio make it a great
day.
Everybody.
Dan, thank you so much, man.
You know what, what you're probably witnessing is something that's very complicated
to do, not to understand.
So you have all these feeds living all around the world because you're using the channels
to basically enjoy shows, content, music, programming, video audio from other places as
well and so we're giving a utility to do that and to organize.
Now a lot of these feeds and this is iTunes has the same problem.
They have to be checked and they have to be checked regularly and of course if you're
talking hundreds of thousands of feeds it becomes quite a chore.
So part of the way you solve it is by more processes doing the same functions.
There are ping servers around the web that unfortunately are not utilized as well as they
could be by by systems that upload and and publish feeds.
I think Podshow actually does that automatically.
I'll have to double check because I know we certainly implemented something a long time
ago.
So checking these feeds there can definitely be a lag.
So we're getting better.
The way people are implementing technology hopefully will get a little bit better too.
And sometimes servers just don't respond.
They're not available and then they have to wait for another pass for another go around
on the merry-go-round.
So absolutely you're definitely seeing those types of issues crop up and it's a continuing
process.
Part of it is due to scale.
Just lots of people collecting stuff and more importantly lots of stuff that people want
to collect from the outside.
So a lot of work.
Absolutely.
You know what I haven't done a long time?
I haven't played anything from my girlfriend and I feel really shitty about that let me
tell you.
And he closes to who this is now.
Come on you know she's got those dulcetones.
Love Spiral's featuring Andrew B walk away.
Blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue purple
blue blue blue blue blue blue red then blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blueShe is
purple blue blue blue pink blue blue blue grey blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue gray blue blue
Gloom Ivory peanut through cloud.
I feel it's easy I don't want to take the fall
I've planned to see the song once
Just want to take it all, yeah
Then walk away, yeah
I've come close to the vibe
Nearly burn my hands
I've been lifted high
To bed up to the sins you
Now I walk away from my own space
I've had a way to save again
How long away from my own space
See I won't go away
Find my own space
Ooh, see I won't go away
Till I feel safe, again
I won't go away
Find my own space
Ooh, see I won't go away
Till I feel safe, again
I won't go away
Love spirals, as you beat, I walk away
Furgies on stage in life are the black eyed peas
She was doing interview with Jonathan Ross
She said, I don't think today is a day for my lady lumps
Looks like a great time that looks like everyone is enjoying themselves
It does seem that we have a green fever catching on
Everyone is going to websites and calculating their carbon usage
Really have no idea what it all means, it just seems like an awful lot
But you know what the result of it are?
Well, really our natural resources, our fossil fuels
We're going to need to stretch that a little bit, I'm pretty confident
So that's not a bad thing at all
Hey, before we cut out here
When ever you send something, I'm always curious
Hi, I'm Dr. Pryle, I'm here from Sydney, Australia, here for vacation
Oh my goodness, the boy does get around, doesn't he?
Why do you comment regarding games?
It's a comment on the July 4th, 2007 episode
Number 628, the daily source code, where he's
Ranting about the American fast level of Uber patriotism
As we call it here
Uber patriotism
Is that what you call it in the UK in Australia?
Where?
I find it really almost disgusting as to how
I know where the U-yanks are about the world
Not you personally, but some of you
Starting with the president going down to the
Well, did the chat by the coffee from every morning?
Um, it's almost odd when I meet someone
I mean, it's saddened at the use as a medical hospital
We just not know where London is for instance
Um, that's all she has
You're disgusted by that
Dude, you gotta give us a little break
You know, we live on a continent like a whole continent in a way
It's, you know, for thousands of years
You guys have been crossing each other's countries
Beating the crap out of each other so you kind of know the way
You know, but it's a different continent
Only a couple hundred years and it's been even shorter than that
That the transatlantic travel has really been possible
I think if you really trace back history, it's, it's pretty logical
Now, that's not to say that I don't think it's disgusting
That the people aren't drilled that in school
And that they at least have some kind of understanding
But that is a whole other issue
We've got to talk about education
I think history should start with
Good morning class
Let's look at today's paper
Let's look at the issues that are being discussed
And let's trace back historical roots to the problem
Now that
That would be a history lesson
Nothing's wrong but it's alright
I lay me down to sleep tonight
Toss and turn, sleep on car
Restless for the sun
The dreamer dream with you in view
Better times and dreams come true
As what open tell me where's the dawn
Restless for the sun
The view from here
Don't darken
It's shout so clear in my mind
Don't break in through darkness
Dreams come true in better times
So hold me close and speak to me
For the dreams we've yet to see
Can't wait to see you when the morning comes
Restless for the sun
So hold me close and speak to me
For the dreams we've yet to see
Can't wait to see you when the morning comes
Restless for the sun
Jimmy Bradshaw, another pot of music favorite
Winding up a food bar Friday
There in walls as Adam
Going against my better judgment
Sending you with three minute feedback file
Which unfortunately I didn't get
But I'll read the email
You're normally gracious enough to play my feedback
Then of course I tend to keep them short
Promotion just gave me so much that I had to tell you
Give it a listen at least
Key points
How many of us should put them be three as a part of this?
The information from the Coca-Cola message
The text message that is sent to the participant is wrong
The code gives you either a 79 pence or a 99 pence
DRM free track
You also get entered into a draw for an 80 gigabod iPod
I finished with a 30 second film
The DSA here we go
This is the part I wanted
The DSC is making existing advertising work better
I thrown away numerous bottles of Coca-Cola with these codes on it
It only listening to the DSC that actually prompted me to use them
Many many thanks
It's from DRM
The guy with the hot sounding wife
Craftman
Would you please just have your wife send the comment for me?
Yeah, that would I would appreciate that
This summer when you buy Coke
Do you get music
You can win an iPod
Or free songs on iTunes
What day is it today?
It's Friday
Saturday
I can't get away without it
Final thought of the week
It's Saturday
And I'm Friday
The jingle don't match up
I don't know
Look at this library thing
Maybe you know I'm a guy who likes to do instead of talk
Well, that's not how I like to talk to
But there are talkers and there are doers
With all this energy that's being
It's positive energy that I'm seeing generated here for libraries
Maybe that's something that all the talkers can do
If you have a weblog or a podcast
Why don't you say something nice
Why don't you know a lot of weblogs is like
You, you, you, you look at what this person's saying
I don't I'd you should agree with him
It's a lot of disagree disagree
Don't see a lot of link love
Just pure out of love these days and seeps
Maybe it's just what's in my world
But the way it feels after that
So why don't you just post a note and say hey
Read this guy's weblog
This is person's podcast
Because I like him there my buddy
And my friend I appreciate what they do
Or just be nice to a fellow human being
Go smile to someone on the street
That type of energy
Now that would be really good for the world
So you can do it you can do it just by sitting there behind
You're a little weasely keyboard in the underwear
And you could do some nice for somebody
And if you actually feel like it
You know call someone out of family member
It's great a little bit of positive energy this weekend
I'm going to do it I hope you'll join in
I hope you'll join in