From the Curie Manor, Gilford, UK, from the Curie condo, San Francisco, more from the Curie
cockpit of the skies above, wherever Adam might be, there's always the Daily Source
Code.
This is episode number 601 with Adam Curie.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next Generation Radio
content in my ears, I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Something in my mind, I've been there taking time to shoot a song for you now.
Taking a song now, the guy not been so wrong to shoot a song for you now.
Taking a song, the guy not been so wrong to shoot a song for you now.
Taking a song, the guy not been so wrong to shoot a song for you.
Kind of interesting.
There we go.
Yeah, you know, I saw it pop up on, on Podger's Music Spotlight, which you could find
at poncho.com slash music and I'm like, yeah, yeah, that's actually pretty cool.
Do need to haircut though, big time.
This is what Spin Magazine said about Pop-Leave-I, and I quote,
equal parts psychedelia and glam, Pop-Leave-I, channel such
formable front men as Robert Plant, Mark Bowlin, and Prince.
Whoa, that coming from Spin.
Not a lot of plays though on the Podger Music Network, yeah, got to get that up a little
bit.
Hey, everybody.
How you doing?
It's the Daily Source Code.
It's episode number 601 still kind of wallowing in the, in the backwash of all the
goodness surrounding episode number 600, it can't really help because it's still a crap
day today.
Again, raining, it's windy, it'll be nice from time to time.
I mean, that means the sun will basically break through a little bit, but it's going
to stay generally overcast.
This is, of course, for the G-Town region, that would be the affluent suburb of
Surrey known as Gilford.
Now even though it's kind of dark and gloomy, it's been this way for what Friday's
Saturday's Sunday.
So it's like four or five days now, there's just been crap weather.
It is even kicked in some natural cycles on the Lady Patricia, because what she does when
the weather is, it's crap and kind of dank and dark and, you know, and particularly
when, well, in the winter, she does all the time, but, you know, when we were having such
beautiful weather now to have this crop up on us, she's resorted to making her famous
soup.
Listeners of the Charlie have been around for a couple of years, we'll know that this
is the soup that cures all.
It has a little bit of ginger in it and all kinds of other goodness.
And what she does is she makes it at night.
I said, this is so old fashioned.
She makes it at night on the aga, of course.
And then when it's all steamed and brewed and there it has to sit overnight and she puts
it near the window where, you know, it can cool down, yet it doesn't get too cold, but
you also don't want the weather all of a sudden, striking into it and ruining it all.
And so the this morning, when I, when I woke up, I could, I could just smell a little
bit of it.
She's just heated it up now for, I guess, what should be lunch?
It's already five to two on behind as usual.
And you can smell it throughout the whole house.
It's really nice chicken vegetables, just that hint of ginger, oh, man, my life is so
good.
All right, uh, notice of on today, I'm working on a couple of leads.
I did talk to a candyman, Luke over at Nokia about yesterday's question about the, uh,
exploding, uh, Nokia battery.
And so I've passed on contact information.
We're going to keep it kind of low key.
But there is a guy, a dedicated guy at Nokia, apparently, who looks at all this shit.
And even there, the belief is like, way, it can't be in a, it can't be in a original
Nokia battery.
It doesn't happen with ours.
So, um, trying to set it up, so we investigate what's going on, because, you know, one
is all it takes.
What's somehow I, I think, I think there may be some bogus parts involved in play here,
not entirely sure, uh, crap hold on, pilot era as usual.
Hey, man, you won't go shoot some pool?
I can't, man.
I gotta go work on my podcast.
You know what?
How's that?
I thought you dropped out of school.
Yeah, I did, but I went to this podcast and they hooked me up with all the fact knowledge.
And Orole, now I can do it.
Wow, that's so really cool, man.
Hey, you think I could do something like that?
Maybe there's another podcast coming up on May 19th.
Go to www.podcampzanandtonio.org and check it out.
Don't let opportunity pass you by.
Learn the secrets of the pros atpodcampzanandtonio, remember that's May 19th, podcastanandtonio.org.
Yeah, I tried to play the Spanish version of the promo for some reason it was gone
or it wouldn't load.
I was like, that would be so cool to have a Spanish podcast promo running, but unfortunately
couldn't make it work.
There's a lot of stuff going on with these podcasts.
It's, uh, it's a very interesting phenomenon.
Of course, we know the podcast camp in New York, familiar with that one.
There was, oh, there was a huge discussion going on in the UK about two different podcasts.
And so there's a podcast, uh, I guess UK.
And then there was, and which is going to be held, and I think, um, either Manchester
or Birmingham.
I don't think that's been short up yet.
And then there was another podcast being organized, I think, uh, in Buckingham
Sure.
So podcast bucks.
And there was this whole discussion about, you know, you shouldn't have two podcasts.
But the, I don't know if they were scheduled for the same time or around the same
time or whatever it was and it was, the whole discussion felt so perpendicular to the
entire idea of a podcast that anyone can set this up and, you know, the rules are pretty
much obvious.
And, uh, you know, it's, uh, it's supposed to be an uncomference, which is very difficult
to organize.
I might point out or very not to organize, but to make run smoothly because you still
want to try and not have the speaker audience, uh, type relationship where basically
the speakers are the audience and the audience are the speakers.
And, and to me, it's, it felt like, wow, you know, so there's two different podcasts.
And, uh, one is basically claiming superiority over the other.
I don't know.
It was just weird.
I had nothing to do with the spirit of podcasts and I can't, we all just get along.
But so anyway, this podcast that's coming up in the UK, uh, the interesting, uh, to see
if it's Birmingham or Manchester, either one is a fine flying destination, I, I might
have, you know.
And maybe maybe Thursday, I'll be flying myself.
We'll cut a Charlie, uh, in the air.
Uh, today would have been possible, but we commend William is, uh, he's flying somewhere
else today tomorrow going into the, uh, in the city.
You've got a couple of sales calls to do with the sales we easled Daniel at the UK Crash
pad office.
And then in the evening dinner with super agent Keith, look him up, super agent Keith
Bishop.
That guy's got something going on, uh, lady Patricia and I will be entertaining him in some
swanky restaurant and so, uh, you know, it's, uh, you remember the hit tests?
I'm sure you do.
Yon Polad who, by the way, uh, did today's opening for the show, appreciate it,
Yon.
Uh, he used to put together the, uh, the hit test.
And I'm, I'm really working around regulations and fair use and all kinds of, you know,
different, uh, different policies because I'd love to be doing the hit test again.
And of course, when I stopped doing the hit test, there were many, many voices saying,
well, why don't you do a, a pot-safe music hit test, which is like ridiculous, because
you need some history, you know, you need to hear a song and have to think, oh, yeah,
that was, uh, the summer of 69 or, you know, the summer of whatever it was that
a really trigger a memory and emotions, not just a recognition factor.
Now with 600 episodes under my belt and several years of doing this, uh, including several
years of the pot-safe music network, how long has that thing been around?
Now two years, two and a half, maybe even longer, three years, perhaps?
Um, I think it's time to do that.
And of course, there's always someone out there who's put something together.
Hey, Adam, this is Maurice's on deck from the Sunday Sundana, and I've got a new contest
for you.
All right.
It's called the pot-safe sack and it's really simple.
Now play just the second three pot-safe songs, okay, and it's up to you to get the name
of the artist and the song.
All right, everyone in the play.
The simple, let's hit test.
Yeah.
Then pot-safe.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Here's clip number one.
Okay.
I know it.
That's brother love, uh, there she goes.
There she goes.
That's the most popular songs of the PMN, yeah.
So that wasn't easy.
It was again.
I figured that one would be in there.
This is what I mean.
How many pot-safe hits do you roll?
All right.
On to the next one.
Okay.
Number two.
Here it comes.
All right.
I know those hooks from a mile away.
I might need a jingle for this one.
So let's listen to this once again.
Uh, not on the radio.
Jeff Smith.
And the last one.
Okay.
Here's clip number three.
Dude, you make this too easy.
Uh, the best pot-safe artist to many of the listeners.
So got any idea?
Yes.
Here it is for the last time.
I think I know it.
Drive away.
Matthew Eagle.
On to the answers.
The first clip was this one.
Ooh.
And of course, it was brother love with goal she village.
Yeah.
The huge hit on the pot-safe music network.
God, that was right.
Yeah.
All right.
clip number two was this one.
What was it?
The King of the King right for the VSC.
Mr. Jeff Smith.
Not on the radio.
The York San Francisco.
The San York in an box.
You become somebody told me.
You got that one right?
Probably.
And the last pot-safe sack was this one.
And of course, Mr. Matthew Eagle with my way.
So thanks Adam.
I hope you liked this first episode of Pot-safe second.
If you do, I might return with another episode soon.
Ladies and gentlemen, he's on that from Pot-safe sack.com signing off.
Bye-bye.
Samaris.
I appreciate it.
It's going to be hard though, man.
It's going to be hard to create.
I mean, look, this was almost no challenge for me.
The whole point is it has to be kind of, you know, difficult.
I can just hear young pull-ups.
It's his butt-crack sweating right now as he's listening to all this going on.
Mash up for the day, DJ Error,
over the confluence of giants.
See if you can detect the hits in this one for a sec.
Yeah, yeah, I love this.
I love this guy.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
I always have to think of this, you know, I just can't help myself.
I do my business on the throne.
I'm a sitter, I'm a standard, I'm a left-right-hander.
It's nice to know I'm not alone.
So besides Steve Miller-Band, David Bowie, the Patentini Group,
but this is not American, Steve Lee Danes do it again,
and all that mashup from DJ Error, Error.
courtesy of mashuptown.com, official supplier of mashup,
to the Chacha, resurrected.
You know, the more I play this folder scruncher song,
the more links I get to a new...
I mean, I know everything about toilet paper dispensers,
colored toilet paper.
I mean, I just know a lot more about the world's bathroom habits
and I really should.
That's still that makes me a much richer man.
All right, so it's taking a long time,
and I think that Friday, we're finally going to launch.
It's just called this an unofficial dam announcement.
We've teamed up with E-Paul, who, of course, accredited
and leader in industry of measurement,
audience measurement, and particularly a surveyed test results.
We're going to be building the biggest,
all I just call it, the super panel of podcast listeners
and creators, starting with the United States.
And it's going to be good, because not only do you have the chance
of getting all kinds of cool stuff, but you help us suck less.
Help us suck less.
www.thevotecast.com.
New episodes, every other Tuesday.
Where people with different people
with different political views can have a conversation
and still walk away friends.
The Votecast.
Nice.
Okay.
Quick update on Afghanistan.
My goodness, what have I gotten myself?
What has my wife gotten me into?
So you recall that because the Royal Dutch Marines
performed where they're on the Dancing with the Stars show
in the Netherlands week ago,
part of the deal was that she would have to bring her show to Afghanistan.
And not just to Afghanistan, but to three camps,
including Condahar, the International Camp,
where I believe the Dutch will just be providing the entertainment
for the entire camp that evening.
I have no idea.
I think there's thousands of people there.
So I'm not quite sure how it works.
I'm getting the information like,
oh, Matt, for God and how much show work that goes into this.
How big is your stage?
Is one question.
That determines how many people we need to bring.
How many people can we bring?
And oh, by the way, you get free transportation.
You get free lodging and meals.
And you get free protection.
Everything else you got to take care of yourself.
So it's kind of hard when you want to bring along cute dancers.
They usually charge money for anything they do.
And rightfully so.
So basically, I'm going to have to sell some kind of TV stuff
to the Dutch market.
And you just to be able to pay for some of the expenses
like now sound system.
We have to bring that ourselves.
A lot that goes into it, but.
And this is another thing I'm investigating.
I do believe they've got all the pipe.
They've got all the telecommunications.
So we can do a lot of fun stuff podcast wise from there.
Talk about some savants.
So I'll keep you updated on that.
And oh, by the way, free Trinity has not gone away.
It has not been sidetracked.
You'll be hearing about that in the next.
I want to say next week, but I just have to be very careful.
Not saying these things.
We're coordinating everything now.
I have a new assistant who is a caller and executive assistant.
Carry who's in the UK office at the crash pad, which is much better for me
because during the waking hours.
And I mean, that's like until six in the afternoon,
even though I do all kinds of crap with San Francisco until 11 at night.
I'm much less sharp.
And I'm probably saying yes to things that I shouldn't.
Because I don't really know what the hell is going on with my schedule.
So she's starting to organize my life.
It's nice.
It really is.
You know, I guess we're chaotic.
I guess we're kind of a professional organization.
He just started up his 16th summer in New York City.
It is the guy from Central Park, that guitar, man.
Your governor, Miss.
David E. Polito.
In a world filled with cruelty and injustice.
Ordinary people feel such strain and strife.
There are just too many rules.
Men for common folk and fools.
Not for those who want to live a simple life.
And there's a woman who has shown the kind of courage.
To be seen when she's not wearing underwear.
And when she's drunk all over town,
She stares the paparazzi down.
So to lock her up, just really isn't fair.
Free Paris.
Oh come on and orange jumpsuit.
Simply will not fit her right.
We can't stand to see her face in such a grand tacky place.
Won't you free our spoiled entitled social eye?
Now on YouTube, I see videos of people who are so angry.
About boring things like politics and poor.
Some place that's called Iraq, but I can't find it on the map.
I think it's somewhere between St. Bart and Darfur.
But Americans like us can still get bothered.
The important things demand we stand and fight.
And I've got something here to say.
Besides my gym is closed today.
And American Idol isn't on tonight.
Free Paris.
When your parents are that wealthy laws are not meant to apply.
And when you have such scant appeal,
driving crunk is no big deal.
Don't make her tell her darling,
take her mouth, go and buy everything.
Free Paris.
Next, I've got a partner.
He didn't even have a TV show.
She's the patron saint, I guess.
A very shallow drunken mess.
So you got to let our Paris built in gold.
One of the true American art forms.
This type of music.
I love it.
David Bollito.
And free Paris.
Free Paris.
Hilton.
He has so many emails.
And he linked to the song.
And of course, it's on the Potset Music Network.
And he said, yeah, it'll probably have a lifespan of only two weeks.
But what the heck?
I'm like, I don't know, man.
She's going to be in the in the break for 45 days.
So we have at least six weeks.
And I think we need to look more of a we are the world vibe to it.
You know, the free Paris.
I think that would get some airplane.
Of course, there's a video to go with it as well.
You can find it.
I think you can get to it from I love the company.
I LTC dot pod.
Sorry.
India, Lima, Tango Charlie dot podshow dot com.
David Bollito.
Yeah.
Crack me up dude.
All right.
Hope you don't feel cheated.
I'm going to cut it short right now because there's a lot going on.
And stuff I want to announce this week.
So I got to get cracking.
And.
This is tomorrow.
Let me think tomorrow is going to be a kind of a crazy busy day.
It's a said lady Patricia not going into town for dinner.
I'm going to be in town earlier probably for a couple of meetings.
I'm not sure if we'll get I'm trying to get a couple of savants that all.
We'll record this evening and use them for tomorrow show.
And of course, suggestions are always welcome and a lot of good ones are coming in.
So daily source code dot com is where you can find links to everything in today's show.
Let's call the show notes and add them at podshow dot com is where you can email me to fill up my box.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best and the brightest.
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering podshow and limelight.