Well, hi everybody, welcome to daily source code episode number 522, still coming to you
from the box laden curry cottage, soon to be the formerly the former kind, I got to come
up with that sentence, soon to be our ex-coated, let's put it that way, it's Sunday
afternoon.
And oh, by the way, I'm calling this episode 522, I realized I made kind of a rookie mistake.
And you changed the nomenclature of your podcast.
So I, instead of doing the episode number and DSE in the date sequence, I was putting
a BOC in the BOC number in there, that really messes up a lot of different players, who
do list shows and alphabetical order.
And so I'm just going to turn it back to the episode numbering that I've been using.
Also, since I am putting original content, even in the best of Charlie's, I guess they
kind of qualify as a regular daily source code.
So part of the advantage of moving house, and as you know, we're in the middle of that,
we have the new house, we're slowly building stuff up.
You, of course, you start with the curtains, I've learned that over the years, after painting
the kitchen, you know, then you kind of start to move over the glassware and you want
to do most of that stuff yourself.
And then by Wednesday, the movers are coming and all the heavy lifting is going to be
done, but they're still going to keep the podcast console here until Thursday.
And when they bring that over, then of course, will officially have been moved into the
new dwelling, the new cottage.
So as I go through draws and draws of stuff, which, of course, is stuff, if it's your
stuff, it's shit.
My shit is my stuff.
Now, looking at gadgets and basically making evaluations, whether I should throw something
out, put together big box of stuff to sell on eBay, or, of course, save it.
And a lot of the stuff, as you can imagine, still winds up in the to be saved pile.
So to my power book, G4, which you know, I, excuse me, I switched over to Windows platform
after my third power book in as many years, bit the dust, and it had to be sent off
to Apple.
Several months for it to be returned, probably almost three months, and it came back
and the battery was to hose, so I had never really got back to using it, but I, I cracked
it open today in my evaluation process and realized that in garage band was the, about
8% complete edit of a podcast I did in interview with Ray Lane and John Doer and Bill
Joy from cleaner Perkins, the world renowned investment firm, Bill Joy, of course, known
for founding, a co-founding son Microsystems, Ray Lane known for a number of backgrounds,
including, of course, the, being president of Oracle Corporation and John Doer, one of the
most famous venture capitalists in the business.
And at the time, and I'm not quite sure of the date, because the date stamps are all over
the place in Garage Band.
I can't really figure out when it was recorded.
It was done via Skype and, and a phone bridge, it was in the summer, because I do
remember recording it and being very hot and actually during the interview, I was taking
off my shirts down there in my wife, Peter, while the conversation was going on, but it
was timed with the release of an announcement by Cliner Perkins that they had made a fund,
which was available for $100 million.
By now, I believe that has been doubled to $200 million, called the green tech fund.
And that means that this money is going to be invested in, quote, green technologies.
Now, of course, I was, at the time, I was very into Trinity, biodiesel, and I wanted to
know a lot more about what these guys who, without a doubt, are gentlemen who can make
the earth move and have done so in the past, their big players, in big money and make
a lot of things happen.
How they were going to approach, filling out this, spending this money essentially,
what they were going to spend it on and what they see as the trends and clearly global warming
and the price of oil and or even the availability of oil are making these initiatives
very, very important.
Now, what you'll learn, as you listen to this interview, which, by the way, I was not paid to
do, it was at my request, it will sound a bit like a commercial for Cliner Perkins,
but not in the way you might expect, if you listen all the way to the end, it's just shy
of 29 minutes, but it really gives an interesting insight into how Cliner Perkins, at least,
is venture capital firm operates and what they're looking in and even how you can approach them.
Of course, I have to disclose that Cliner Perkins is an investor in Pod Show, but as you
listen to it, I think it'll become clear that there's no real benefit to me doing this other than
keeping the relationship going with these guys, which I value immensely, but listen to how they
approach problems, how they approach companies ideas, and how they approach the world, I think
you, I think you'll get a kick out of it. So, oh yeah, I even did the whole corporate intro thing
just to make it sound really cool, like big brewing voice here, ladies and gentlemen,
Ray Lane, John Dore, Bill Joy of Cliner Perkins about the Green Tech Fund on the Charney.
Maybe, I don't know who wants to, you know, who wants to kind of get it going, but
the most logical place to start, I feel, is with the announcement of the the most recent fund,
which is fund number 12, I believe, and then we can, I don't know, John, or Ray, if you want to
pick that up and just explain exactly, you know, what this 100 million Green Tech initiative is,
and then we can kind of take it from there.
Glad you asked, Cliner Perkins, Prof. Bill Dan Buyers, is in the relationship and venture
capital business, which means we're helping entrepreneurs, innovators, scientists, doctors,
those who want to do more than anyone, things possible with less than anything,
less than anyone, things possible, literally to go out and change the world to
realize of dreams and their ambitions. And we've been doing this now since 1972, and so the latest
of our funds, our venture capital funds, Cliner Perkins, Coffield and Buyers number 12,
really the first in which we have earmarked money for a very important and exciting area, namely
that of what we call green technologies, ways to address some of the largest needs and economic
opportunity on the planet. It seems like the venture capital business is, if anything really a business
of timing and understanding of timing. So when I read an announcement like this and certainly a
dollar figure of $100 million, which 100 million of anything is quite impressive,
is it now time has the, have alternative fuels and biotechnology's finally reached the tipping
point where this is really a forge ahead, a leapfrog, if you will?
Well, it's quite clear there's a market need in $60 a barrel oil, it speaks of large and expensive
volumes, but there's also important technological advances and I think Ray Lane, my partners on
this conversation with us, as is Bill Joy, and I think Bill would be particularly good at speaking
to those. Before Bill does that, sorry, Bill, let me just kind of add to what John said about
it before we go into the technology. You know, the venture business is one where its success is
driven by seeing trends, seeing paths before other see them because of technological developments.
And so this focus on green tech is similar to other trends we've seen in the past,
such as the internet or the semiconductor industry or the enterprise software industry and
the development of various trends within it. And this is a major initiative as most of our funds have
been have been focused on major initiatives that we develop a perspective around
developed deep expertise on so that we can make smart investments in. And we think the timing is such
that the technology is at a point, you know, most technological developments over the last several
hundred years have gone through a predictable shape or curve where early adopters, you know,
we can actually see where the cost per unit of output, no matter what it is, whether it is
more law in the computer business or its metcast law or other laws in the networking business,
but various or go back a hundred years and and look at the amount of output and factories
and different core methodologies. But when we can see the shape of that curve before it has been
adopted and we can see the productivity will be an order of magnitude better than its predecessor
technology. And we think that is the right time to focus on it. And we can certainly see that
in the green tech initiative now. Bill, do you want to add to that?
Basically green tech involves consumption and production of resources and whether electricity or
or water or food and this largely involves chemistry, I mean electric chemistry and batteries,
this chemical reaction or making making clean water from dirty water is to separate molecules.
And what's happened is that advanced technology has reached the point now where we can begin to
change and design things at the scales to do better than we could with the kind of crude chemistry
we did in the past. So we can genetically engineer organisms to clean things up or we can
engineer new materials to make resource-oriented processes more efficient. So we suddenly have the
opportunity to make the kind of large factor improvements that will make a real change in the world.
And these industries that have been frozen out of very slow rate of advance are to no rate of
advance for a very long time. The announcement of the investments you want to make came
very close to the to the state of the union with President Bush. I presume it started to hit
hard on his own legacy but really laid in about the U.S.'s addiction to oils, particularly foreign oil.
Is that something that you knew was coming? Is that purely coincidence? Is it all just things
coming together at the right time? Is it for real? Is the government on the same pages as you are?
Well, I think the amount of money that the government is investing in the series
is not up to the challenge and hope that it increases. We certainly come at this from
separate paths but whether you're looking at this glasses half empty or half full, I think you
have to say that until this point in time we've been as a country and as a state as a world in
trouble with respect to energy innovation. And as we look around whether it's with the initiatives
that Governor Schwarzenegger has launched in California or President Bush for the United States,
being green, embracing green, sustainable technologies is without a doubt the most tough-minded
and geostrategic and pro-growth and Tom Friedman would say even patriotic thing that can be done.
It used to be that being green were the things Sissis would do the sort of hugging
liberals, but the government, the frog would disagree with that. And Tom Friedman would disagree,
but all of a sudden to find a way to win the world from $60 a barrel oil that's going to
fuel radical Islamic regimes in the Middle East and is more than a matter of smart economic
it's a matter of worldwide stability and sustainability. All the experts now agree that
there is a serious climate crisis underway in the form of global warming. And so we need real
innovation and incentives for innovations in renewable energy, wind, solar, biofuels,
clean water, clean transportation, increased conservation. And we've seen European nations because
of their higher energy prices take the lead in this regard, but the largest consumer both in
an absolute sense in per capita is the United States of America here in North America. And historically
America has been one of the world's great innovators. So I think the way to look at this green
glass half full is that it's a great area for entrepreneurs and innovators to go make a difference.
And I think the big difference now versus 20 years ago because we're certainly a lot of venture
capital sloshing around 20 years ago and 10 years ago. The difference now is that we can see
a cheaper cleaner, better ways to provide energy. And so we know as I said the beginning of this
podcast, we know the shape of these curves and economic curves. And once we know the shape
and we know that there's going to be an order of magnitude improvement, then that's the time to
push the go button. That's the time to start investing in these entrepreneurs. We're not afraid
of the things that are technically difficult. People come out all the time with business funds. We have
trouble understanding. We look in the encyclopedia. We look in the textbook. They've got some new
science. They've got some new technology. They're doing something in a different way than it's been
done before. It challenges existing order. Sometimes it challenges the limits of our understanding.
We're not afraid of that. It doesn't mean we're not going to vet it. We're going to get experts to
come in. We need to have credibility in the new idea. But the fact that it's hard and the fact that
it hasn't been done before is often the thing that feels the big opportunity to solve these big
problems. And so we thrive on that. Those are the kind of business plans we want to see the big
change the world kind of plans. But I think we're sitting on standstill road for many years and you're
seeing this dot com and that dot com and this semiconductor company. That's the semiconductor company.
And all of a sudden you started to see, I have a new way of cleaning water. I have a new way of
remediating this waste. I have a new way of taking a fuel cell and making energy much more efficiently
and cleanly. And we suddenly start to see, not just one, but a drum beat of these kinds of
innovations coming along. You realize the game's a foot. It's not just because there's a need.
It's because technology is providing an opportunity to do transformative businesses like
Netscape and Amazon and Google and to Nentech and Lotus and Compact. We're in their time
for their problem. This is a new time in a new problem. And these businesses are going to happen
now because the technology end the need are coming together at the same time. We're very fortunate that
that's true. How do you even contemplate doing diligence on all these opportunities?
You know, what kind of resources do you need to bring in to find out what has potential?
Well, we'd like to be involved in a industry at its very beginning. It's always better to back the
number one or number two player than the 10th or 11th. And so the partnership since the beginning
of the biotechnology industry, the distributed affordable, the personal computing industry,
the internet industries, networking industries has drawn on our ability to help entrepreneurs
with really terrific relevant operating and technical experience. As well as a strong and powerful
network of forward thinkers, scientists, consultants, and we're bringing that same network. That's
the same resources to bear in helping today's energy entrepreneurs. You know, innovation and
the energy industry we were marked earlier has been an option more on. There just has not been any
and all of a sudden because of advances in materials, in chemistry, in process. We can borrow from
many different fields, be they, high volume manufacturing, buttering, and depositions to make
possible innovations in energy innovations and transportation in the storage of really electrons
and the transformation of atoms. And we're moving, as I like to say, from a world that merely bits
and bytes to one of atoms and molecules controlled by the bits and bytes and the market for energy
is the largest of all those. We come back to a question you asked about how we actually do this
and what's important. John started out by answering, I think your first question about
those being in the relationship and venture capital business, maintaining a network of experts
to deliver service to these entrepreneurs is our business. And you know, I would say that we
our partnership maintains a balance of technical depth and business skills, business and
economic skills so that we can balance the two of those. What are the right technological
bets, where the right economic bets that will both produce the best outcome in terms of technology
for society and also for a return on our investment. And then below that, you know, throughout
this network that we maintain, we have deep deep technical expertise and entrepreneurs that we
hope are passionate in their falling in love with the technologies that they produce.
We can't afford to totally fall in love with these, we've got to balance them in some way.
But we want to make sure this network delivers deep deep technical expertise and knowledge
about what we're about to invest in. You know, Ray, you mentioned something about 20 years ago
when there was a lot of the money floating around for alternative energy technologies.
In fact, I believe California, particular was probably the leader in solar energy in the
70s, also fueled coincidentally by a fuel crunch. And now the United States probably accounts for
less than 20% of those leading technologies. Where do you see the real pockets of innovation
taking place and maybe more specifically, is it solar, is it wind, is it biofuels, all of the above?
I think it's a lot going on in all of those. Bill may want to take a couple of them and just,
you know, paint a picture of what's going on, what we see is different today than in the past.
But we are seeing innovation in all of those fields. So we have to assess all of them
in parallel and try to make some assessment as to which one, you know, paint a picture of what's
going on, what we see is different today than in the past. But we're invested in battery technology
and more than one type of battery technology. We're invested in solar technology and more than
one type of solar technology. And so, and we try to make choices within each of those fields.
We're announcing this $100 million initiative, but we've come public with it only because
we believe over the last five years, gradually, but in an accelerating pace, we've been both
exposed to ideas from the best entrepreneurs and had the chance to back them in this field.
And as smart entrepreneurs will, they want to keep their ideas quiet or stealth as we put it
and fail they have products ready to offer to the market. And so we've made six significant
investments today. And several of those are now public show the kind of opportunity that there
is for innovation. Public in terms of the public in a sense that they're likely talking about
their efforts, recruiting people, offering products for sale. And then others are on the verge of
offering their services or products for sale. But they show they answer your question, which is
what are the markets like, what is the size of them and what kind of difference are they going
to make in our lives? You asked about solar. We're backing a venture called Mia Sole, which is
making flexible solar panels. They deposit solar material elements on flexible substrate, for
example stainless steel. Instead of putting it on expensive brittle silicon, a crystalline
surface that raises the cost of it. And the solar market sales for these modules, photovoltaic
modules grew 67% last year measured in megawatts. And over the last five years has been growing
over 40%. There's almost an insurmountable market demand right now for innovation in solar energy.
And having said that, so we get a sense of the size of these markets overall. Today solar electricity
generation accounts for less than 1% electricity generation worldwide. Another investment that we've
made is in a brilliant team out of MIT, who this venture is called Lillipcution. And they're making
tiny, but you do know all power, butteen power, the solid oxide fuel cells. And these are basically
rechargeable electrons generators, the size of a battery that you'd put in a laptop or a cell phone.
But instead of running for a few hours on a charge, the run for days on a charge. And when they're
through with that fuel from your cigarette lighter, butteen, you have a squirt more into the cell
and it just keeps on generating electricity. Three others are involved in energy storage to really
disruptive technologies with respect to today's batteries, which are well positioned for improvement.
And another large scale, solid oxide fuel cell project, together with an energy exploration
venture that can more effectively discover and harness bridges from the hydrocarbon economy
we're in today into a renewable economy. All told, renewable energy supplies less than 6%
of the world's consumption of energy. And of that renewables, the vast majority is hydroelectric
power. So there's a very, very large market opportunity that's right for innovation.
Before Bill, before you jump in on this, John may be a question since, as a team you oversee
lots of innovation, many things taking place. How about consumer adoption? Are you also investing
in the evangelism, the prophesizing, and really driving consumer adoption towards alternative
forms of, I will just say, let's call it energy in this case, or do you depend on the individual
companies and points of light take care of themselves in their own business plan?
If you look at the United States, energy and research uses is relatively efficient in the
industrial side. We've done a fairly good job of getting more efficient there, but it's really,
really been poor on the home consumer side. And we would love to find transformative tipping
business plans, technologies that could improve the efficiency and in-residence as throughout the
country. And that's a challenge, because people often look more to purchase costs than
like cycle cost of ownership. And so we have to find new business models in new ways of making
of that more intelligent decision happen. There are three ways to accelerate the adoption
of these technologies into markets. In many cases, they're invisible to consumers. And getting
an advanced battery adopted, for example, by Dell or a compact computers for their laptops,
that's the way the partnership can help by opening doors. The second is to recognize that
most of the markets for energy are regulated. And so there are government and policy
incentives that are today in place and that can be extended or made even stronger, whether they're
in the form of subsidies or clearing out regulatory underbrush that would either slow or hasten the
adoption of these. And we're very active on that front in helping companies get their innovations
and further research funded early markets of subsidized. The third and perhaps most important
is to select the kinds of innovations that are going to naturally appeal to consumers. And those
like the personal computer or like the revolution in podcasting are those that empower individuals.
And so the energy innovations we're involved with are those that are distributed. It's a kind of
personal energy. The same would be true of energy, storage, or of our efforts to find innovations
for clean water. They're not even ideal of enterprise software is going the same direction.
People that are individuals in an enterprise. So these are not mega wide innovations for cities
of 10 million people, except as they can be distributed spread around to villages to your home,
in your garage, into your personal electric vehicle. And I think that's one of the important
breakpoints between what used to be known is clean technology. And about over the last 10 years,
every year year and in year out about 6% of venture capital was invested in so-called clean
tech. That's not the field that excites us. We're excited about green tech, which conveys more of
the sustainability, distributed, personalized, and economically important, and green, think profit.
Excessed, sustainable elements of this new initiative. We think the time has come for this field to
get more than 6% of the worldwide R&D venture capital dollars. And we certainly intend to devote
more than 6% of client-ers funds to these kinds of innovation.
Well, one of the short answer to your question is, whatever it takes, we will invest in getting the word out
on the demand side as well, trying to help manage demand and bridge over to the new energy economies.
And I've heard my partners say many times that success is not enough. It has to be significant
that we have to leave behind something significant for the world. If you look at many of the
cleaner investments over the last 35 years that have been really good economic outcomes,
they've been more importantly significant for the world at large. And we are attempting to
announce new initiatives that will do the same thing over the next 20 years.
Where are the gaps? What are you missing? What are you looking for any types of companies or initiatives
or particular areas of invention? We're specifically looking very, very intensely right now for
areas in the biofuels, initiatives in the biofuels area, whether they're biologically based or
chemically based, free processing, material that would be recyclable. I mean, where the carbon gets
recycled and doing that in a way that's very clean and has good economic and maintainability
parameters. And so it's the whole system design of how such initiatives would get put together.
And we've seen a lot of plants and we're still looking for one that's incredibly transformative
and are very excited to keep looking in this area. And we think there will be a number of great
ventures and hope to invest in several of them. Here's another example, Adam. We spoke about
build it about most of the least efficient uses of energy being in homes. 25% of the electricity
in homes is being used for lighting today. And so we anticipate. We've seen several proposals for real
revolutions that provide more economic lighting, longer-lived lighting, better control lighting,
and significantly lower energy consumption. The field is wide open. We want to see entrepreneurs
or better said teams, great teams that can think through and take technology and apply its
leverage. We know now that in the next 10 years there are great possibilities to apply technology
leverage to deliver an order of magnitude improvement on any of these cost models that we
are driven by today. And the John also has, I think, made the point several times,
imping upon our national security at times. The last thing I would say is, go to our website.
There's instructions there for how to send us, send us, send us your great ideas, come visit.
We want to see the plants. We look at new things every day and we want to see lots of great ideas
in these areas. We know that they're out there. We know they're more than they were seeing.
We want to see more. Bring them bring us your great ideas. I think one thing we didn't touch upon
as well is a lot of the really great ideas come from the great universities around the world.
This country, we have a lot of great universities doing a lot of research. I mean, really great
research and connecting. It is our job, our mission to connect with those research teams and
eventual entrepreneurs for that research that comes out of those universities. And so we want to
continue to network with those great research universities because that's where a lot of the
baseline work is going on that we'll see the results of in the next 10 years in the new
energy economy. Please know that you can come and you can come to us with an idea.
You don't need a business plan. You don't need the management team. You don't need the laser
like focus on an unserved market opportunity. At the beginning of the biotechnology industry,
there were two scientists, Boyer and Cohen in one of our partners Bob Swanson was reading one of
their research papers and took them out for a beer these two of them. And we backed them to the
tune of $10,000 a month to conduct an experiment in their labs and to write a business plan for
what became Genentech, a leader, 120 billion dollar market value. In the worldwide biotechnology
industry, there will be, in our opinion, several, if not many, Genentech's and Google's and
some micro systems and Oracle's really great, big, durable, global companies who can serve
the needs for innovation. In this, perhaps the largest of all our markets, the needs for
clean water, clean power, clean transportation. The largest single trend on this planet over the
next 50 years, everyone agrees is urbanization. We're going to triple the number of people living
in large cities from $2 billion to $6 billion people. Think of that. That's going to be the
equivalent of creating eight cities every year larger than Manhattan. And so the innovation isn't
just happening in the United States, it's happening all over the world. Great innovation in bio
fuels, bio diesel, for example, in Europe, tremendous demands for efficiency and conservation throughout
all of Asia and the markets are also good. So we're open for business and are called to the
world to innovators and entrepreneurs to visit the Cleaner Perkins, a co-field buyers website.
It's www.atpcb.com. Yeah, I'd say go to kpcb.com. Look at the descriptions of our initiatives,
look at the biographies of the partners, pick one of us who matches up with your ideas, send us an
email, describe your idea, tell us your new technology, your new way of doing business, your way of
getting things adopted, and we'll get back to you and let's start a dialogue and see if we can
change the world together. So that's what I'd call quite an invitation. Now if you
made it all the way to the end of this interview, then you'll know what I meant by kind of a
very interesting type of advertisement. There's Bill Joy, a legend in Silicon Valley, inviting
you to change the world together with him. Fantastic. Well, anyway, I hope you enjoyed that.
I plan, that's one of my private promises to myself. I plan on doing a lot more interviews in 2007,
and I will not probably put them on a different feed. I'm just going to make it all part of the daily
source code because it's not what it's all about. Aren't you supposed to build a do whatever you
want to do? So I shall do just that. And a reminder that portions of today's show are brought to you
by Splenda, what's your flavor? Check out Splenda, mix the flavors together, and enjoy. GoDaddy.com,
use checkout code dsc3 for a great deal of domain name, and if you're going to go to the movies,
January 12th, stomped the yard opens up, go to stompedthepodcast.com, stompedthepodcast.com,
and Tony Costas will tell you all about this fantastic new movie, which is going to be a big big hit.
I hope. We want more business from down people. All right, I will be back tomorrow with
probably another best of Charlie, which of course I'll give you an update on the big movie 2007,
and have yourselves a great rest of Sunday afternoon. Or if you're on Australia, tomorrow. Bye.
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT Pod Show Media Network,
powered by Pod Show and Limelight Network. Control your part in the show.