Well, how do everybody? Welcome to the new revamp studio here at the new Gaff. Still haven't
come up with a right name. I still kind of like the Curry Cottage have thought up a number
of different names. Curry quarters, camp curry, the curry crib. Nothing really strikes
my fancy yet, so looking for ideas for that. As you can tell, I've kind of got the equipment
all set up again. Hold on, I'm still rearranging everything. Yesterday, spent a shit
load of time yesterday being Sunday, Monday for those of you in Australia. Here's what
I did. You have to understand I had about 50 boxes, 5-0, 50 boxes up here in this space
that I have on the third floor, which is pretty much the length of the house, and it's
all wood floors. It's completely clean, recessed lighting. It's exactly what you'd want
for an office studio and hang out. The problem is, the stairs up to this third floor, so
narrow, that there's very little I could actually bring upstairs. Now, you know, I got the
big ugly green thing up here because the guys saw it in half for me, but I had no furniture,
so it was impossible for me to literally unpack stuff. So Saturday, Patricia, I had to run
to home base, which is an equivalent of, you know, what channel might be or home depot
in the US. And while we were looking for other generic stuff, which had to do with the
rest of the house, because of course, my portion is very unimportant. I saw a desk, one
of these, you know, IKEA, like, put it together, yourself things, and even though it's
a sit down model, it has exactly the right shell spaces and stacks to put a miniature
version of the studio up and at least get it running. And spent all day yesterday, putting
it together with the included Alan Rensch and Rensch's, I might say, with my screwdriver
and my head off, I followed the directions completely and believe me, this is not something
that I do a lot. Turns out I'm actually pretty good at it. It looks all right, and I also
bought a nice chair to go with it, which I also had to put together. The reason I got all
this stuff, I could literally throw it into the car and put it together and get something
up and running, because I got a lot of stuff to produce before I leave Wednesday morning
is when I leave for San Francisco for about 10 days. Also, I had to record with Christina,
which I was going to do last night. But you know, sometimes when you put equipment back
together, the weirdest crap happens, I'll give you one example. I had the settings,
the all the EQ and the dynamics and the compression and everything that I had at the old
cottage, I had it all set up just perfectly. And I thought I had it saved, but I hadn't.
And I'd said, you know, it's this Yamaha Alpha Whiskey 16 golf digital, who howling, you
can save the scene, essentially all your settings, I neglected to recall that you also
have to save the song data, because that is what it's attached to. And so, of course,
I spent a whole bunch of time figuring out how this fucking mix works again. And then there
was like a hum, and not just a little hum, it was a very noticeable, like a ground loop
hum. These things can be total shit to track down. So I went to like a quarter, 12 midnight
last night, I was tracking the hum. Finally found it. I had a hum or in my monitor. And
I'm not quite sure why, but of course, the first steps to resolve that are to plug the monitor
into a different circuit on the house, which means, of course, I'll have to buy, oh, I don't
know, about 35 feet of extension cord to get to it. Another wall outlet that has another socket.
So needless to say, it's had the usual trials and tribulations of getting everything back together.
This, by the way, is officially a daily source code episode number 526. Sorry, I didn't mention
that right off the bat. I've got a best of Charlie lined up for you, because I still have the
vote of phone bandwidth, which, by the way, I have to say, is quite amazing. Now, of course,
it costs, was it 49 pounds a month, so about a hundred bucks a month. And they do say that there's
unlimited bandwidth with little asterix that means you can only really download about a gig.
So I've been very careful not to not to break the kind of the policy of downloading too much.
Of course, I do have to download best of Charlie's. I have to upload best of Charlie. So that is
definitely is eating into my budget. And Christina, of course, you know, Christina's, I mean,
I told it don't start up lime wire, don't do any of this other stuff, because you'll be out of
bandwidth. It'll be a huge problem, because, you know, of course, the broadband doesn't actually
arrive for another week and a half, at least. And I'm still only hoping that it'll be in by then.
Let's see. So was it Friday that the sky satellite installer was supposed to drop
by I can't remember if I told you the story or not. And so we were waiting, you know, he called
it 10 to 9, said I'll be there sometime between nine o'clock and one o'clock. And then I got a call
which went to voicemail, probably unfortunately, but it wouldn't have made much difference.
You have the driver can't find your house, which, you know, come on. This is the Beverly Hills
of Guilford, my friends. It's very easy to find addresses here. I mean, particularly with,
with UK post codes. And, you know, so anyway, so please call back. So you call back the number.
You go through the whole fucking menu tree. I should have recorded it. It was so ridiculous.
You finally wind up with the if you have an appointment today. And then you press that option.
And then the announcement says, well, you've called it a very busy time. Please call back later.
And then you get disconnected. So I finally wound up going through sales and then got into the
right support, you know, group, which I think they're all in Ireland for sky, at least it sounds
like they're all from Ireland. And, uh, oh, I'm sorry, sir. The installer couldn't find your house.
So we canceled the appointment. We have to set up a new one. You know, like, can you do it Wednesday?
So no, I can't, you know, and what is this fucking sorry excuse for, you know, that you,
he couldn't find the house. You know, are you a satellite company? Yes. Have you ever heard of
satellite navigation? I mean, it'll drop you off right in front of the house. So needless to say,
it didn't matter how much I pitched or moaned. I have an appointment now for the end of the month.
So I had to go out and get some free view boxes. This is this digital video broadcast stuff,
which is very successful, by the way, here in the UK. So at least we have a good clean picture
now on the aerial on the roof. But I was pretty annoyed that, you know, that the television,
we need our TV, we need to see big brother. So I've got that square to away.
Just isn't quite the way I wanted it to happen. Anyway, the vote of phone ban with just to get
back to that is actually pretty good. You know, I can do email quick enough. And I've set up the airport.
I had to do some funky routing because, you know, it's kind of funky to route through the
year power book, a USB network adapter. So there was some actual command line stuff I had to get into,
but I was able to set it up luckily. Now, of course, now I have to go into town and prove that I'm
over 18 years old to the, to the fine folks at vote of phone because they have some kind of,
let me say, I'll actually read it to you. If you try to go to, oh, even if you go to myspace.com.
So I go to myspace.com and then up pops this fine warning, which says content control restricted access.
You are not able to access this service because vote of phone content control is in place.
If you're over 18 years, you can easily remove vote of phone content control. Go to about content
control below for further information and details about how to remove it. And this is the fun
thing. So you click on about content control and then they give you all their policies, but they don't
actually give you a number or any way to remove that. So you wind up calling in, going through
another menu tree and then you have to essentially assign yourself a pin number, then you have to go to the
store with some kind of identification and then they'll take that off. By the way, it's not just my space
that has been blocked. Blip TV and any of the of the video sites, not BTpodshow.com, by the way.
Now that I've mentioned, I'm sure it can't last more than a day before that gets flagged as
completely inappropriate. So it's kind of interesting that they put that in from the outset.
Don't mention it when you order the stuff would have been nice to have known beforehand.
Let me see, before we get into the best of charity today, here's promo.
The soul of the city is playing with corruption. Every day, cops see death. But for the first time,
I felt it. I used to believe in justice. Now, come on the end.
Working with dead cops is a step, isn't it? It's so big.
You're both lucky to still have your bad eyes. I have no more of that bullshit.
That's fun with that important. How do you make it do it? I'm taking charge of the situation.
You're making a big mistake. No, I'm correcting more. I've got a clean shot.
Hold it, I can take it right now.
Sports City PDs, the critically acclaimed police drama, made available exclusively via video podcast
and can be found at one place. The number one new media network podshow is at portcitypedi.podshow.com
to see the show and portcitypedi.com to join the community. Episode 5 launches January 22nd.
If you thought the last show was intense, you ain't seen nothing yet.
Yeah, I was a port citypedi brand new episode out now. You got to check it out.
This was the episode. I think I was supposed to be and unfortunately,
I couldn't make the shoot date, which I really bummed out about because
those guys are doing some amazing shit on an amazing budget. You have to check it out portcitypedi.podshow.com.
Of course, even though I am going to do it, man, I almost don't have to do a best of
Charlie. I've been talking so much so far. I was at 13, 14 minutes.
Everybody's been talking about the new iPhone and amidst all of the the big move of 2007 and
all the boxes. Of course, I think I read, I was in gadgets coverage, their live blog coverage.
I was pretty cool, actually. I think they must have had a two-man team. We just refreshed the page
and then there'd be a timestamp and then whatever Steve had just shown or done or whatever was
happening on stage and then the next time you refreshed those posts would actually have pictures in
them. So that was pretty damn good. And of course, I think you can download the keynote
from Mac world now, from the iTunes music store. Haven't done that just yet because, well,
the whole photo phone thing, right? I have to say, just looking at that phone.
Here's what happened to me. I'm looking at the phone and all of a sudden, and that's not a
drumstick hitting my cowbell, my friends. Now, of course, then the whole controversy everywhere in
the blogosphere about it being a closed box, will it actually work about it not coming out
until June or July? And just look, this phone looks fucking awesome. It has just about everything
in it that you'd want. Although I do want to say a few things about it. And particularly because
on the same day as the iPhone announcement, Nokia or Nokia came out with the the new version of
their internet tablet, the N800. And I was sent one as a gift, I'll say, not to review, but just
as a gift from Nokia. And I did want to report on what I think about this thing because it essentially
has kind of the same dimensions, I think, as the iPhone. Now, it's not a phone. It's an internet tablet,
which means it has it's I guess the idea is to enable all of the functions that you use the
internet for. And mainly, I almost think mainly multimedia applications in conjunction with
either a Wi-Fi network or with through Bluetooth with your phone. So, of course, I have the E61,
which I love very much, which I bought on my own, Nikol. And I've been using this device for
about a week now. No, less than a week. What is it? About half, yeah, four, three, four days.
And this is probably exactly the opposite in what would you call it?
It's an opposite culture that is trying to be built up around around this internet tablet. I presume
at least, because it runs on Linux. And I think it's a Debian is the flavor of Linux that it's
that it's running. So, there is an active developer forum. And this is essentially exactly what
everyone is talking about. If the iPhone is coming out, since it has OS X on it, which is also a
version of Unix, or that's what it's said to be running on, we'll be able to run applications
on it. And the answer came back, because no, absolutely not. It's a close box, and you can't do that.
Whatever. And so, there's a lot of people screaming and yelling. Now, if you look at the
at this internet tablet, it has some amazing things built in that were, I think some of them
developed by Nokia, but all all open source, all based on Debian Linux. I think they're all open
source, at least. You can make, there's a little camera that pops out. You can make internet-based
phone calls, video phone calls. I've actually tried one forks amazingly well with your presence
managed through, see, I have an account on G-talk. So, that's the, the Google chat and
and talk server video service or community, I am service. That's what it is.
It has a very interesting way of knowing when you are using your finger to touch the screen versus
the built-in stylus. I'm not a big fan of stylus. I just want to be able to touch stuff with
my thumbs or my fingers. And so, we'll bring up a larger version of a keyboard. This is the first
observation I have. Typing on any type of touch screen. I don't care if it's on the iPhone or
if it's on an internet tablet. When you actually have a screen that portrays a keyboard,
yeah, it could be even a full-size keyboard. It is definitely not the same thing as using a regular
keyboard or even the tacit response you get from using real keys like on the E61 on the phone that I have.
So, I think a lot of people may be a little bit disappointed just in general about the speed
and the re-learning you have to do to be able to type quickly and efficiently using an on-screen
keyboard because I found it reasonably difficult. Now, what's really nice about the Nokia tablet
is first of all, it works now and it has a full-fledged browser in it, which does JavaScript and they
even have a version of Flash which kind of works Flash 7. So, it doesn't work with every site.
Unfortunately, it doesn't work with all of Pod Show yet, at least not with the MASH board and some
other places where we use Flash 7. I think that they're trying to get Flash 8 licensed into it.
But if you look at the two devices side by side and I'd have to say that I'm very happy with the
phone that I have. I don't necessarily need to have a phone, but I love having a larger screen
something with audio, with video that can do all these things that connects up to, you know,
basically the world. I think that that's something to look at. But if I showed this to Patricia or
Christina, I think they'd probably cast the decide within five minutes of looking at it because
it no way does it reflect that fantastic interface experience that I saw on the iPhone.
So, you know, for all of the the back and forth thing that we're doing, look, either you buy the
iPhone and enjoy it, or if you're such a great developer and you want to create fantastic applications,
take a look at this. This to me seems like exactly the device the community is looking for.
It does Wi-Fi. It does any other, you know, any type of connection. I think it even has
an infrared. It might even have infrared. It's which is seamlessly between Wi-Fi or my 3G phone.
So, I don't even have to think about that. It has a streaming media player. As I said, it has the
full-fledged web browser. It has a personal information management, you know, I map email.
And of course, you can download all kinds of applications. For the geeks, it has an x-term,
yeah, you can drop right down into a command line and you can you're actually in a shell on this
device. You know, let's let's show the world that we actually can do something phenomenal. And let's
port some really fucking cool applications. The number one would be open office. Port open office
to this device and we have a huge fucking winner. It has it already has a PDF reader, but it doesn't
do office documents. So, you know, anyway, I'm kind of going off on a tangent here, but it's
definitely something worth looking at. Because, well, not just, I just love for some of these
people who are yelling so loudly about Apple creating it. Who the fuck cares what Apple does.
Let them do whatever they want to do. Let them sell the candy they want to sell. That's fine.
But everyone's saying, oh, you know, we have to be able to muck around with it bullshit.
Oh, my go find something that's useful that actually is out there and saying, hey, come
muck with me, please. And you can do that with this N800. I was not paid for this endorsement,
but I did receive a free thing. But I really mean it. Let me see, was anything else I wanted to
talk to you about. No, I don't think so. I think that's that's enough for right now. All right,
so I still have this best of Charlie. I'm trying to think what I should do now. If maybe I should
just leave, just leave that until tomorrow, since I've done such a phenomenal update,
yeah, that's what I'll do. I'll just close this down for today. We will call it a full
fledged episode daily source code 526 tomorrow. Then I will bring you, I have two more best of Charlie's
lined up. Of course, it was all scheduled out perfectly to the time with the with the two weeks
that I thought I would be off the air. And as it turns out, well, I could use two more days.
And then Wednesday, of course, is this travel day. So we'll be getting back into the swing of
things very soon. I would love for you to start calling into the voicemail numbers again.
And what I promise I'll do is I'll set up, I'll make some photos of the inside here so you can
follow along. Right on. Okay. Anything else? Yeah. I just found out Trash comes on Tuesdays.
We got a shit load. And everything will be kind of back to normal by midweek after I get into
San Francisco and we back. So get your promos coming in. Oh, I know what I had to say.
Remember what I told you about that movie, Stomp the Yard? It was the number one movie last week
and brought an over $20 million dollars. And if you want to find out more about it,
it's stompthepodcast.com. Costs us World Tony will talk to you all about it. He's got a couple
of episodes there about the movie. And it's exactly what I predicted. I told you was going to be
number one movie and voila. The number one movie of the weekend over 20 million bucks. Fantastic.
Splenda with us for another another quarter of a year. I'd love to hear more about your
flavour experiments. So call that into the voicemail or send me an email at him at podshow.com.
And of course, if you want a great deal on a domain name, check out godaddy.com. Use the checkout
code dsc3 for a really good deal for a year's worth of a domain name. Funness.
I don't know about the sound. I got to work on that. It was kind of pissing me off.
It's, uh, I had it so beautifully tweaked. Anyway, uh, as I said, I'll get some pictures going.
So you can see what it looks like. I'll put those up on the on the on the weblog at curry.com.
And I'll have another update tomorrow. And tomorrow I actually do this the best of Charlie. It's
quite a good one. I have to say, uh, from, uh, let's see who did this, uh, Tino. Tino from the
Netherlands did one. I think you really dig it. He dug up some some old stuff.
Okay, everybody. Uh, hope you don't didn't find this a waste of time since it was really just
about me and about my world and my diminished world and small scope of view of the past two weeks.
I can't wait to get back out into the real world again and get some shit done.
Uh, show notes at dailysourcecode.com. I'll talk to you tomorrow. Everybody. Bye. Bye. Now.
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it. I'm the BT Pot Show Media Network.
Howard by Pot Show and Limelight Network control your part in the show at btpotshow.com
yani.