With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass,
then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic! It's Adam Curry.
From a super secret area of Gitmo, where he gets to wear one of those fashionable orange jump suits,
and then daily visits with Sergeant Ian.
It's Adam Curry in the DSC in 69.
This is what nothing to do got my tail,
but the call I'm going to New York.
We do a planter and watch a tour.
You know my amin' show was fun, but ain't nothing.
They're so pretty, like New York City.
I'm going to Brussels and London too.
What they're fast reminds me of you.
I'm nipples, this steel your heart, and that's a start.
Yeah, I won't be a Boston, not LA.
Sweet home Chicago is too far away.
I got my boots on, walk out the door, and I'm known.
Yeah, I've been to Richmond and Phoenix too.
I've been so many places with nothing to do.
You got my tail, I'm the call, I'm going to New York.
I've been to Atlanta and Washington.
You know my amin' show was fun, but ain't nothing.
They're so pretty, like New York City.
That's right, but I'm here in New York City.
Ain't no city quite as pretty.
I can New York City.
It is that historic code episode number 699er coming to you from Madison Avenue,
in New York City.
That is the Michael E. Thomas Band from the Pods Eye Music Network.
Hey everybody, I'm here in my hotel room, hand held Mikey in today.
Since my stand broke, and the table here is a little too low to pile up a whole bunch of pillows,
and I just want to get the show out, get it done.
So if you hear a little bit of the Whitney Houston tapping of the fingers on the microphone, that's me.
Yeah, that was the kind of vibe that I was in.
You know, whenever Patricia and I see New York City on television, we always really,
we always look at each other and say, man, that really is our home, isn't it?
And it always does.
It feels like home for some reason, even though we only actually lived in the city for two years.
We lived in Jersey for, it was at 10 years.
And I commuted into Manhattan every single day.
So it is.
It's home to me.
It's always felt that way.
More than any other city or any other country that we've lived in, both of us have that feeling.
And some of our happiest times were here.
And I have to say, those happy times are clouded.
I arrived the evening around 6 p.m. at Newark New Jersey's Liberty Airport,
which is the new name for Newark.
It's named Liberty.
I think that happened after 2001.
And I feel anything but free to be quite honest.
Of course, you know what happened, stood in the line there, to talk to the customs agent,
part of the customs border protection agency, a division of the homeland security.
And the first thing the guy said is, hey, you ever have any trouble getting into the country?
I said, yeah, in fact, the last three times of arrived here, the United States, my birthplace.
Yeah, he said, well, why should today be any different come with me?
And he took me along to something which I actually haven't noticed in the three other times I've been checked once in Chicago and twice in San Francisco.
They took me to the secondary room.
Now, the secondary room is, man, nothing like that welcoming feeling you get from the main entrance there at Liberty Airfield.
No, no.
It's kind of like, no, any government agency back room you'd see in Manhattan,
even though this wasn't even Manhattan.
High desks with the whole wall of the customs border protection agents.
And yeah, so my passport was given to one of the agents I was told to sit and wait.
And then till my name was called, and there was a variety of other other people there.
And then by no means was it to all terrorists looking people.
In fact, a couple from the UK sitting next to me looking very, very annoyed.
They clearly have been through this a couple of times before.
And so my name was called and all there come out all the questions again.
Yeah, what are you doing here?
Show me a business card. Oh, you have a phone.
What's that phone number?
You know, I'm happy to give everything they want.
You know, why do you live in the UK?
Kind of question is that.
But I kept my, kept my cool, you know, no problem.
Okay, went through it.
I did ask the officer said, you know, this is the fourth time.
This has happened to me at four times in a row.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Well, it's, you're on the lookout list.
You see this is some new information I learned here.
It's not, it's not the no fly list.
Obviously, because I have no problem getting on to airplanes.
I try to arrive in the United States, you know, the place that I'm from.
I'm on the lookout list.
Okay, could you tell me why I'm on the lookout list?
No, I'm sorry. I'm not a liberty to tell you that.
Okay, dokey.
Is there any way I can find out because clearly I don't belong on the list?
Well, that's not for me to determine, sir.
But here's a piece of paper.
And there's this, this is so embarrassing.
It's an embarrassing country when it comes to this.
Literally zero-oxed, like a fifth generation zero-ox, very, you know,
you can just see this has been copied a couple times.
This is an answer ID number 11.
The date this form was created was January 23, 2003, last updated December 12, 2005.
The question being, I'm always being stopped for questioning an inspection
when clearing immigration and customs. What can I do about that?
Answer.
If you've repeatedly experienced intensive inspections going through
customs and immigration upon entering the United States after foreign travel,
your name or another person's name that is the same or similar to yours,
may be entered into the CBP database.
And parentheses, the Treasury Enforcement Computer System or TECS system.
If you think this may be the case and you'd like to have the situation reviewed,
you can write to US Customs Board of Protection, Freedom of Information Act,
blah, blah, blah.
Basically this is a form that, and they even attach an FOIA form.
Under the Freedom of Information Act guidelines, you may ask to receive a copy of any
information CBP has on file about you.
You may also ask to be told of any actions taken by CBP regarding your request,
which is to be taken off.
I presume if you have already gone through this process and continue to experience
difficulties in which to complain about that, please contact our
Crater Relations Office and then they list a phone number.
So essentially, I did a little bit of research on this TECS.
What is it, Treasury Enforcement Computer System?
Lots of interesting articles.
If you Google that, you'll come up with some fun stuff.
This is a basically part of the automatic targeting system.
All kinds of government agencies tap into this database and provide information and
there's a scoring system, apparently.
And if you have little checks, if you have too many check marks,
next to different divisions, and this could be anything from
motor vehicle to the IRS.
If you have enough check marks against you, and I'm not quite sure how that
calculations done, then your name pops up.
And then you could call it in for secondary screening.
Okay.
So I take my piece of paper, and I still have to get out of the airport.
And so that means that you have to hand that little custom's form to the
custom's officer.
Well, yes, of course, it's time for a second screening, which is basically the
exact same procedure done while they're rummaging through your
luggage.
And I mean, I'm not just talking about rummaging, man.
They're open up mail.
They're looking at correspondence at business cards.
You know, clearly not looking for any contraband, just trying to determine if
I'm a threat to national security.
And I, you know, it actually took the wind out of me a little bit this
time around.
Because I wasn't thinking about it quick turnaround.
You know, I was home for literally two days.
Got home Saturday morning, hung out with the wife and with
with Christina.
And then Sunday, we just hung out some more, went into town.
That is, you know, soaked in some festive holiday spirit, despite a little bit
of rain.
And then, you know, Monday, we had the UK Christmas party for the UK
office.
And you know, I was like, oh, I'll just hop over to New York for a couple
days.
And I didn't even think about the two and a half hour or
deal I would go through.
And it's, it has absolutely taken the wind out of me a bit.
I'm really, I'm really demure about it.
I'm disappointed.
Really disappointed in what's going on.
And as a Washington Post dot com article about this very system.
This is from November 30, 2006.
The federal government disclosed details yesterday of border security program
to screen all people who enter and leave the United States who
create a, to create a terrorism risk profile of each individual
and retain that information for up to 40 years.
So this could be gone for a while for me.
I mean, it doesn't, it's not like the, they're doing everything
essentially, but a body probe.
Yeah, and wouldn't surprise me if they did one of those on me one of
these days either.
We've been doing risk assessment of cargo and passengers coming in
out of the US, the Department of Home, Homeland Security
spokesman Jared, agent said, we have the authority in the
ability to do it for passengers coming by land and sea.
So let's see.
Let's see if there's anything else in here.
Let's just a lot of new, this, here we go.
The parent program, the automatic, the, here we go.
The automated targeting system relies on government databases that
include law enforcement data, shipping manifests,
travel itineraries, airline passenger data such as names
addresses credit card details, phone numbers, the parent program
treasury enforcement communication system houses every,
quote, every possible type of information from a variety of
federal, state and local sources.
It's debilitating and disappointing is what this is.
Okay, but here's, here's the one interesting thing.
You know, this whole under the Freedom of Information Act,
you can request what's on your file.
I don't think so.
According to yesterday's notice, this is from my year ago.
The program is exempt from certain requirements of the privacy
act of 1974 that allow for instance people to access records
to determine if the system contains a record pertaining to a
particular individual and for the purpose of
contesting the content of their record.
So essentially, you can't get that information.
I, you know, I guess I'm going to file a Freedom of Information Act
to see what's on my record and what's, what's up with that.
But I think that I am one of the apparently millions, millions
of United States citizens who are going through this.
And it makes me, it makes me sad, it makes me angry,
obviously, because dude, it's my country.
I was born here.
I defend, I do defend this country.
Tooth and nail, with my life, if I had to, you guys know that.
But the feeling is waning a little bit because this is
seriously fucked up.
And just you fuckers waiting till we get Ron Paul
into the White House.
And we're going to change some shit then, boy, I tell you.
Hey, Adam, this is Dean down here and Houston, Texas.
And I think one thing that's been missing in this whole
Ron Paul debate is nobody's called in who's actually
represented by Ron Paul in Congress.
Well, that would be you.
Yeah.
And I have to say, I've lived here for 15 years and I've
voted against him every time he's come up for election
because while I applaud his stand on the war and think
we ought to be doing something about that, I think
an America that was governed the way Ron Paul's philosophy
describes America would not be in America.
We'd want to live in.
I'm all for the Constitution and supporting the Constitution,
but the Constitution doesn't say anything about food
safety, product safety, the environment, a well-maintained
infrastructure, space exploration, science,
the internet, anything like that.
And what Ron Paul says is if it's not in the Constitution,
I want private enterprise to do it.
Well, I think we see what happens when private enterprise
regulates and maintained itself.
The savings and the whole thing.
Hold on a second.
This is going to get into some stuff that we have to go
point by point.
And I understand what you're saying.
My friend from Texas.
But it's a little over-simplifying things just a little bit.
You can't just say big business is horrible
and regulating itself.
That's just not a fair statement.
By the way, who says we have to deal with big business?
I'll deal with little business if I want to trust the food
that I'm putting into my body.
I certainly don't trust the FDA.
But you're right.
You know what?
I think we should let the country just go exactly the way it is.
Horace Good Citizens.
We're just trying to make a buck.
I employ a hundred fucking people.
A hundred people.
Some schmuck.
You know what?
I just got to say it again.
Skull fuck the rotting corpse of the TSA
and the Department of Homeland Security.
Okay?
Screw you guys.
Catch some real criminals.
That's a real terrorist.
So anyway,
that's okay that you have a different opinion.
I think your misguided though
because Ron Paul is not exactly saying what you are hearing,
which is unfortunate.
We have to go through a transition period.
We have to change the ways of our country and the way we run it.
And it will take a transition period of a decade probably.
I think Ron Paul is only offering to be a transitionary president.
I think that's just fine.
So yeah, of course, you can't just switch everything off.
You can't just turn everything around in a heartbeat,
but you can certainly start.
Food safety.
Toys from China.
You know, I think there's a place for government.
I don't think we need government regulating every instance of our life.
But.
But it's like on that way.
Try the industry.
Keeping track of what goes into my food and saying,
I don't worry about those chemicals.
It'll be fine.
Trust us.
We're just here to make a profit.
I think there's portions of the.
I think the problems are much bigger than that much, much bigger.
They go way beyond that.
You're working for the man.
You're being ruled by the man.
Hi, Adam.
This is Janice from New York.
I'm calling about that Eisenhower quote that you.
Played on.
I think it was DSC 65 and you keep talking about.
You don't seem to have no one seems to have called in yet to tell you that that's part of a movie.
I think it was made.
I think it's a relatively recent movie.
Maybe maybe within the last one or two years.
The movie is called Why We Fight.
And it's all about the military industrial complex.
And it has a video of that.
Clip of Eisenhower is close.
A few other choice.
Video clips of him.
So I think you can enjoy renting that movie.
I think it.
Come out in the last couple of years.
Anyway, one of the thank you for the Bailey.
So let's go then.
I love you, Adam.
Thank you, Janice.
So close by too.
Just drop off some naked pictures.
Yeah.
I saw that movie.
Why we fight.
And that's probably when I got the white picked up on the quote from Eisenhower to be quite
honest.
And then I found it later on on YouTube or I thought about it later.
I can't remember exactly which.
That is indeed a great movie.
And there's another one that I was just given a link to.
It seems to be a really, really long one.
It's up on YouTube and 31 different parts.
It's called Bloodlines of Power.
I'm sure it'll have to do with the illuminati.
And I can get into that kind of stuff, too.
You know, pieces of bits and bobs of it.
But I got to tell you, I'm just a sucker for watching that kind of stuff.
I do like it.
And it's funny.
I was at the Heathrow Airport.
And I wanted to pick up, actually.
I want, you know, I've been looking for a book on Eisenhower.
And I've gotten a couple of different suggestions.
I thought, you know, I'll just hop in the bookstore that had a borders bookstore at Heathrow Airport upon departure.
And I looked in the biography section.
And it's all like celebrities or celebrities, you know, from Big Brother.
And it's unbelievable.
It's TV hosts, all kind, you know, Paris, Hilton, Victoria Beckham.
No fucking Eisenhower.
Not a single series biography at all whatsoever about a real historical figure.
The biography category has just become, you know,
celebrities and their, and their books is pretty crazy.
Anyway, so, you know, I was on my way to the Virgin Clubhouse after trying to score the Eisenhower book.
And behind me, I hear someone go, hey, cut the cup.
Which is, there's only one guy in the world who says that Steve leads from MTV who hired me in 1986 to come to work for MTV.
He, he was walking behind me.
And I knew he was going to be in the UK for the Led Zeppelin concert because he promoted
Led Zeppelin back way back in the day in the Ahmed Erdogan days.
And of course, this was also, I told you this was also Monday.
And I had the special VIP ticket, but I didn't go.
I went, of course, to the Pancho UK London office Christmas party, which was probably more fun.
Although, you know, the importance of a historic event like Led Zeppelin, you know,
you know, just heard a little bit, not being there.
So that was kind of cool to hook up with the leads, my surf course.
He works at a serious satellite radio now, soon to be serious and XM.
He was actually in his own little mini crisis, you know, to get into the,
into the serious building, you have to go through security.
Like almost every single building in New York these days were crazy.
You know, you got these idiots with an X-ray machine.
And you got it, this is, they're really going to catch all my shit, not, you know,
that just rent a security door.
And so he's talking to a Keith Richards manager.
Keith Richards scheduled for, I guess, for an interview or something this week,
up at serious and the manager was like, say, well, you know,
what's the security like in the building?
And yes, he was explaining, well, you know, it's just your typical New York building security.
Yeah, but, you know, Keith always carries a knife with him.
So, you know, and he, and he won't, he won't go anywhere without his knife.
And I know this because it's a bowie knife.
I've seen it before.
And so I was like, oh, man, what happened to the good old days or rock and roll?
They are forever gone, my friends.
No, security is taken away even the right for our friend Keith Richards to bring along his bowie knife.
Comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip.
All right.
From the US, we go check out the European Union, our special correspondent,
commentary blogger standing by what's going on, my friend.
Hello, Adam Kerry.
Here is CSV.
Your eucrass pondered reporting life from the EU.
So, the French president, Sakaze,
wants to create Mediterranean Union between South Europe and North Africa.
And it is pissing off other EU leaders because he wants to use EU money.
EU money on that new union, which we will have capital in Paris.
And you can go down the toilet because of this and die.
In meantime, each French cow gets more money from EU subsidies than could fit at three African villages.
PS.
Galileo will offer high precision to everybody unlike GPS.
That is offering it only to military, but not to civilians this high precision.
And I don't want to fuck you Adam Kerry, but I like you.
Yo.
Yeah, I've been reading about that.
So, cause he's doing some interesting stuff.
He had a doffy over the other day.
Good doffy ordered some planes.
Some airbus planes, I believe, for the Libyan Airlines.
Yeah, the Galileo, I did read up on that as well.
I believe that you can get the ultra super accurate Galileo signal,
but you do have to pay extra money for it.
So, I think they'll still have a kind of an inaccurate signal just for your regular home applications
and for your car navigation, but you do have to pay.
At least you're able to pay more for it.
So, I have to say that's kind of cool.
In the ever existing pursuit of a better mobile setup,
got an interesting comment.
Interesting suggestion.
I don't know if it's going to work though.
You know, I've got the Mac and people keep saying,
I'll try out Uber Caster and I like Uber Caster,
but it doesn't work because on the MacBook Pro,
you don't have a, you've got latency, basically.
No matter what device you use,
unless you use an external mixer,
the one I'm using right now, I lug that along.
And I'm actually using Cas Blaster,
so I lug along a secondary, I lug along the via,
which basically functions as a studio machine now.
But I'd love to just carry one machine.
And here's a suggestion that I hadn't heard before.
Hi Adam, this is Hans.
I was born and raised in the south of the Netherlands.
Sorry to hear that.
In the south of the US,
just listening to the DSC 698,
and you mentioned that you were looking at getting
some different preamps in compression for your on the road.
Like for so nice.
If you have a MacBook,
I thought you might want to check out the Apple GDWAT,
which is a Firewire interface.
Really, really nice conversion.
It's got great, very clean preamps built into it,
and it runs up a bus power, so you don't need it.
Another break to plug into the wall.
Also, since you have a MacBook,
you could also put a expansion slot on the side.
You can actually put in one of those universal audio cards.
They make one that's actually four laptop.
It's called the UAD Expander.
And their plug-ins are phenomenal.
I don't know if you're a software that you're using uses plugins,
but if you can use no standard,
VST, or we'll see other type of the audio unit plugins,
you can't really go wrong with those guys.
You know, you can be on the road
and run a fair child, or 1176 from LA 2A,
and really, really nice gear.
So anyway, check it out.
Enjoy your show.
Go run Paul.
Talk to you soon.
Yo, yo, thanks, man.
So I need some help here.
I need to know, and I like hardware solutions,
but I don't like them when they're USB or Firewire related.
Because I've only seen, I've only heard latency,
and I just can't be talking through a microphone.
And I want to hear the process signal.
I don't want to hear the naked mic.
I've got to hear what you guys are hearing.
What people are going to be hearing in their earbud.
So it's got to be after the compression,
after any processing takes place.
If there's going to be latency,
I'm just not going to buy one of these.
So I really appreciate it.
If you could let me know if there's going to be any latency
with these devices.
Because otherwise, it just absolutely don't cut it for me.
Otherwise, yeah, I like it.
It takes all the boxes there with the running off of bus power,
and not having a lug along another machine.
Boy, I could safely say I would really, really love that.
Yeah, I'm curious.
It's just so calton calm.
You just wanted to wish you a Merry Christmas
and a happy New Year and all that little stuff.
It's just awesome to let you know.
There is a third version of the Hanukkah song.
I actually sent it to you through a website called YouSend it.
Thank you to theamacotchot.com.
So too is, you know what?
I love you Adam Curry.
Yeah.
I already have a good one both.
At least not be done.
Thank you.
Merry Christmas.
And a happy Hanukkah.
I didn't know there was a part three already,
but indeed, I got it through that website.
You call YouSendit.com.
Well, here it is.
Ladies and gentlemen, the deraille dowels.
Thank you.
It's time for my love.
Once again, it's time for my love.
Merry Christmas.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
So incredible to be back here.
Thank you.
Okay.
Hanukkah is the festival of lights.
One day of presents.
How no, we get to eat.
Really nice.
But if you still feel like the only kid in town,
without a Christmas tree,
I guess my first two songs didn't do it for you.
So here comes number three.
Awesome Phoebe from France.
Say the Hanukkah blessing.
Solders, ladies, pal, squeaky, and wheeled graces.
Deborah Messing.
Melissa Gilbert and Michael and it never mixed feet with dairy.
Maybe they should have called that show.
Little kosher house on the prairie.
We got cheer in Louis.
Back still a ranch, jackback.
Tom Arnold converted the Judaism.
But you guys can have him back.
Just get done it.
We've been a getter kiss on the need of this old toe.
But we can't do it on either.
We do something I know.
I'm Jewish.
Dayday.
Never.
Here comes my God.
Look to Evelyn Nelson's band.
You play as harmonica.
Celebrates harmonica.
Tiny Elvis, ladies and gentlemen.
Tyrande!
Schneider, I did not even know you were Jewish.
I'm a Filipino Jew.
In fact, I got around home and like the first pig.
You're going.
Oh, some have been running.
Not a big fan of the Jews.
Well, maybe that's because he lost a figure skating match.
The gold medalist Sarah Hughes, how about my students?
Who did he a David Blaine escaped straight jacket with such precision?
But the one thing they could not get out of, their painful circumcision.
We're in a pouches half Jewish, but a full-time Oscar winner.
Jennifer Conley's half Jewish dude, and I'd like to put some more in her.
There's Louie, favorite pair of men, and more have gold.
She always alone invented quadcopp music, but first game, he rules school.
Hey, Natalie, more conical.
It's not a single way around a group.
I always find getting a half truncum, all this joyful, joyful Oscar.
So get a high colaca, and so you're your long jalanca.
If I've been here really well in a car, have I heard it?
I've heard it, I've heard it, I've heard it.
Happy Holidays!
The incomparable Adam Sandler.
And the Anacosar in part three.
I guess that was from Saturday Night Live.
What I get here there.
Excellent.
What do we know?
Is this the seventh or eighth night?
Yeah.
Man.
More Anacosar in the pod save music that we network crowd people.
We got plenty of Christmas tunes coming in.
More Anacosar.
Why aren't there more Anacosar in Jane?
There's Sandy from Germany again.
Yeah.
I just got back from my evening walk listening to the Charlie.
And I got a little idea.
I saw so many people tonight too.
Wearing their earbuds and listening to something.
And I don't know what they are listening to.
So I wondered, how could I make, how could I make it visible to me and all the others?
What, what these people are listening to?
And here's my simple little idea.
Why don't all of the Charlie listeners make a little not in the cable of the ear,
but the right or left you can decide.
You can decide if your folder is going to hurt or fuck you.
I love you Adam Curry.
So why don't we do this for a week or two?
Just make a little not in your cable.
So we can see each other in the tube on a street and the park.
Wherever we're listening to the Charlie.
And maybe someone can say hi to each other.
And just have a casual nice meeting, a coffee or something.
Change some naked pictures.
Talk about what we think about the stuff that was set by you Adam Curry.
Oh, that's all.
And I love you for saying it every day.
Thank you.
And I sure appreciate it. Have a nice day.
You know, in general not a bad idea.
I don't think the the reach of this show goes far enough for the,
and you do you to be bumping into Charlie heads all over the place.
Yeah, it does happen, but I don't know if it's if the,
the not in the in the earbud cable is going to work.
There is of course the solution, you know,
only have to do or start wearing the wrong brand.
Once those t-shirts come out, you'll be easy to identify Charlie heads.
Hey Adam, this is Craig calling.
I just wanted to say, you know, you are so wrong.
I can't believe you thought of such a wrong idea.
It's just the wrong thing to do at the wrong time with the wrong people,
and it's the wrong clothes.
It is so wrong.
Brilliant.
Love you Adam.
Hi Adam, it's Matt from Games Weasel.
On this week's show, we've got a review of Assassin's Creed on the 360.
Also, we get out of jail with Kane and Lynch dead men on the 360.
We've got copies of Assassin's Creed to give away on the PlayStation 3,
and David Doug from free radical design.
The people behind time splitters and back in the day golden.
I tell us about their brand new first person shooter on the PS3.
That's all at gamesweasel.btpodshow.com.
Yeah, make sure you check out Games Weasel TV.
I think the new site is up Games WeaselTV.btpodshow.com.
It too is a completely awesome, with all the latest clips from all the latest games.
Matt Cuddle bringing you was expertise and insight, as always.
For those of you wondering, you know, what all this stuff is about the wrong brand
and where the wrong clothes, the wrong time with the wrong people.
I'm gearing up to figure out how we can all protest, how we can protest against the government.
In a peaceful protest to bring back control to the masses.
There has to be a way I think I've come up with an interesting solution.
The way to get the government's attention is to stop purchasing, to stop consuming.
We truly are the force in the American economy, not Wall Street, not the oil companies, but the consumers.
We're going to buy hundreds of billions of dollars worth of stuff this Christmas season.
It's already started and we don't stop and we're encouraged to continue to shop.
Just listen to your leaders.
So that's the way towards civil disobedience.
And I'm still working on the, I'm still working on the campaign here, as I sit in my luxurious hotel.
I'm in New York trying to rape Madison Avenue and more money, but we're going to come up with something for sure.
Hi Adam, this is Tracy from San Diego, just listening to, is your baby source code about stopping the consumerism.
And you were wondering, like, oh, any economists out there?
Well, I'm an Austrian economics point of view, which is what Ron Paul supports.
There is something we could do to really throw a monkey wrench in their whole plan.
And that would be, we stopped consuming from a large corporation, started supporting smaller independent entrepreneurs and businesses.
There you go.
Yep.
And see if we hold our dollars in our bank account, or even in cash, the government can still manipulate them by printing more dollars,
which will still the wealth of the dollars that we have.
Which is how they're paying for it, rack. That's why it all is down about 50% since district office.
Yep.
But what we can do is we can convert our certain notes to gold, which they can't really screw it.
And there's actually a very cheap way to do that with gold money dot com.
Yeah, you know, and I looked at that gold money dot com.
And I understand what you're saying, what you're saying is two things.
You can really protest by buying local buying from small independence.
And boy, what an idea there, huh?
Instead of going to the big box supermarket and getting your frozen dinner, go get some fresh produce.
Make something at home.
Spend some time with your family.
Don't watch an hour of television.
Cook.
Come on.
You'll have fun doing it.
Trust me.
So by small by local, I'm down with that.
But then protecting your money by buying gold.
Yeah, that's hard.
There's lots of outfits on the web where basically they hold the gold and you put money in your account.
And then it goes to their account.
You get certified gold bars or whatever.
I don't know, man.
They rated that mint company the other day.
They also took their gold and silver.
I think I don't think we can protect ourselves against that one way or the other.
The government can still come into your home, come into your bank account and take whatever they want to.
So that probably there's no way to safeguard that.
But I still think it's a good idea to protest by no longer buying big by American, by products that are manufactured or grown in the United States.
And don't get it from big chains.
Let's just stop it.
I think we can all do that, can't we?
We're really if we ship it a lot of our consumer purchases to goldmoney.com.
And I had our local businesses use that form of currency.
We would really screw with them a lot because one way would be attacking their money count, which is,
be federal reserve banks.
The big banks, like Walt Kovie Wells Fargo that are members of the federal reserve,
would be attacking medium of exchange, which would be the US dollar.
It would be attacking a store of wealth, which would be the US dollar.
By converting all our cash balances and the gold into the demand for the dollar, which is based further pressure,
which would not allow them to purchase as many goods and bomb as many people over there and interact.
Anyways, that's one of the biggest way to think.
We get throw a month-to-earensional plan that you're talking about by reducing our consumer spending.
Just convert federal reserve notes and gold.
There's an allocated storage either a coin in your hand or something like goldmoney.com.
And then refuse to spend at any of the big companies and just shop with your local entrepreneurs.
And pay them with goldmoney.
Or something to that effect.
And then I would really hit it there monopoly.
Anyways, thanks.
And I love you, Eric.
Yeah, I love you too, man.
I think we need baby steps first.
We probably should come up with one day.
Just one day where we don't shop.
One day where we don't go to the mall.
And we can make a dent.
Well, we certainly should be able to make a PR impression.
Of course, a real easy solution in my mind is to get Ron Paul into the White House.
I vote for him in the primaries.
Donate money to the Ron Paul campaign, Ron Paul 2008.
Do it on December 16th, the Boston Tea Party, a 16th, the Boston Tea Party.
It's TeaPartio7.com.
I've already given my $2300.
That's a maximum amount that I can give.
But I will continue to propagate the message.
Oh, I still have to make my video, too.
Was it four days?
So what is it?
Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday.
So Monday?
No, Sunday is the Boston Tea Party.
So I got to do my endorsement video.
If you have to switch your party affiliation,
you have to do that pretty quick,
depending on which stage you're in.
Otherwise, you can't vote for Ron Paul.
It would really be surprising to me if the amount of votes that Ron Paul received
really were equal to his polling numbers.
Because they're all over the map.
Most of the time, he's not even showing up.
They're totally decimated into the sidelines.
Yet when he's on television, when he does debate,
the poll numbers shoot up the numbers that are done by viewers
during the broadcast.
And he's always at the top of the list.
So I'm just hoping that all that money that we've been collecting
gets put to good use.
He starts flooding the market with advertising.
You know, it's the only way we can get anyone elected in this country
is through money flowing into television and radio advertising.
And I think that will be a solution to a lot of our problems.
And look, I'm a disc jockey, okay?
I don't have a political background.
I've been a business owner, a taxpayer.
I'm an American.
But by no means am I a politician.
I don't claim to understand everything or know everything.
But I do know the difference between a blue pill and a red pill.
And look at the movies that Hollywood has been given us.
A lot of this stuff is coming true.
It's just coming true.
And there's a reason for it.
And yeah, life imitates art, art imitates life.
You choose.
Pretty amazing that these guys showed up on the podcast music now.
We're in fact I got a check and see if this is legit.
If not, then I'll have it removed.
But no one the guys from Durand ran.
They probably did put it up themselves.
The podcast music network, this is falling down on Chuck 699er.
699er.
It's just coming true.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, how should I start like that?
You know, got to tell you, new or old, I just like that band.
Durand, Durand's falling down, you can find it on the Potsay music network.
And I will be doing my diligence on that, but it would not surprise me.
But those guys have been around for a while.
I think they're just as frustrated with the machine as everyone else is.
And they're smart.
I love them for being smart.
All right, that's it for episode 1 from New York.
Wintertime to New York.
Daily source code 699 or 9R.
Adam at podshow.com is where you can email me.
And of course, daily source code.com is where you can find the show notes and links to the
Relevant in today's program.
Beware.
Live free.
Enjoy your freedom.
Live your life with passion.
And score for the running course of the TSA.
Everybody, if I'm not thrown in Gitmo, I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.