It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio
content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Alright, we're back.
Let's get you set up here.
Okay, just just talking to here.
Into this thing right here.
Yeah, because the microphone.
What the...
Hello?
No, no, no.
Grandpa, there's nobody on the other end talking to you.
Oh my god, I thought this was like a ham radio back in the old me.
It's not a ham radio, just say.
The DSC538.
DSC, isn't that my vitamins are for God?
Yes.
Not a vitamin E, DSC just over the charlotte.
And Joel, it's at best, it'll be five bucks!
And what's the Daily Source Code 538?
5 Daily Source Code, what the?
Whatever, just get away.
Welcome to the DSC, 538.
Oh, football Friday, what did you say so?
It's football Friday!
I think I soiled my pants.
Baby me.
Don't you just make a man and slow it down.
There ain't no use in getting all worked up.
It's just a bump in the road.
We gonna work it out.
Yeah, I want you to get out of your eyes.
We could save something special.
I'll let it go.
I'll walk away from what we know is real.
Got to my dear love.
Gonna fight for love.
Pin down and let your shot it down.
There ain't no time all the time.
Baby, don't you just make a man and slow it down.
Yeah, you know I'm all the time.
Don't you just make a man and slow it down.
Baby, don't you just make a man and slow it down.
There ain't no time all the time.
Yeah, you know I'm all the time.
I love you, I love you, I love you
Baby, I love you, I love you
I love you, I love you
Baby, I love you
Oh, fight up
Gotta try, fall up
I love you, I love you, I love you
Baby, I love you, I love you
I love you, I love you
Oh, yeah, baby, that's the way to start off
You are right
I love you, I love you
That's the way we do it, that's the way we do it
That's suggested by Jersey Todd brand new heavies
From the Podset Music Network, all fired up
Kicking off your football Friday
What's the day?
Second of February 2007, coming to you from Curie Manor
It's the master of the manor
The name's Adam, how you doing everybody
Oh boy, technical problems this morning
Incernet was out
I thought it was something
Something in the network
I made a really smart decision
Instead of troubleshooting that
Before I had to do all my recording and productions this morning
I said, I'm going to stick that
Vodafone USB dongle
Into my Vios slot
And it only took me two restart
And it worked
So I was able to get my stuff from the PMN
And do my chip
Crapload of email you guys
It sent me
A lot of Trinity stuff
For free Trinity
And I think that we're going to have to start a
A secondary podcast
Fairly soon
We got the Google group up and running
Lots of people joining
More about that, of course, in today's
Daily Source Code
And of course, you will be hearing more from
Sir Jersey Todd later on
As the official musicologist
Of the Cha Cha
And it may be a little bit of a long show
I don't know
But I got to get out of here on time
Because to a clock
Pickin up the new car
Hi Adam
It's Josephine from Pod Finder UK
Now Adam
If you'd like to know what I'm wearing
All you have to do is check our episode
Two of Pod Finder
And I've got it on, just for you
Josephine
She's only been working with us for
Was this three episodes now?
Already she's totally on to me
You know how to get the promo's play, baby
Pod Finder UK.btpotshow.com
Hey, thanks to a couple of folks
So sending in their comments about
Sky, my, my Sky TV issues
Oh man, big fight with the teenager last night
Because of course, she had the only
Viewing card that worked
Well, you know, if you only have one viewing card
In the whole house, you're going to put that near
The family machine, right?
Holy moly
Anyway, so we were able to watch some television last night
Not like I'm really missing it
But channel 524 on my Sky box
Is wings discovery?
Oh god, I love that channel
That's like porn for me
Watching airplanes
Sydney
Sydney Bowel says
I work for Sky TV's big brother company
Direct TV
Sometimes the agents are asses
But they should not have charged you
If I'd handled the call, I would have sent you the
Shit to you next day air
No charge
Yeah, of course
You know, the UK, of course
Is not known for its customer service per se
Although I have to say, everyone's pretty polite
But I still can't get over the fact that I asked for a supervisor
And I couldn't get one
And it was like they never heard this question before
Which is quite maybe I'm asking for the wrong thing
Yanks, Brits
Yanks versus Brits help me out here
Uh, see, who is this from?
M
Shoot
I don't know who M is
Adam, your Sky problems
Email here
James.Mirdock
at bskib.com
And you will get a call from higher up
The chain and customer services
Sharpish
They will sort out your problems
Especially if you're spending money on HD
Multirume stuff
Yeah, I'll wait
Oh, if I haven't received anything by Monday
Then then there's going to be a lot on the moon
Adam, it's Barbara in Palo Alto
As you know, I am so jazzed about the Free Trinity project
More people are signing up for the Google Group all the time
And I am honored to be playing a part in getting this campaign rolling
Even though we haven't talked about what paths she's going to take across the USA
I have a feeling Trinity is going to be spending some time in Texas
And although I've never actually seen biodiesel fuel
I have seen cooking oil
So how about a song for Fubar Friday that puts it all together?
A song available on the Pod Safe Music Network
Called Sweet Texas Gold
Marby Adam, it's Friday
Happy to meet Trinity
And let's save the world
Come on
I love that
I maybe I just don't come on Friday as anymore
You guys send in the songs in the intro
Thanks Barbara
Perfect fit for Fubar Friday
We live the world
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
WOW!!!
Here you go.
Straight forward, sweet taxes go!
not met yet other than through email, the free Trinity group,
but Google groups, and this comment that you sent in,
I like you already, if this is the kind of music you're into.
You know, I have ego filters set up at a techno-radi,
so if anything, and if anything is posted with Adam Curry
in it, or Pod Show, it shows up.
And from time to time, you'll read someone posting something
about MTV or how MTV used to be.
And in very briefly, there will be a comment about me,
Adam Curry, the fake head-banger ball dude.
And that's not all the time, but if it's ever about head-bangers ball,
they always rag on me, it's like,
I was so, I'm so into that music, and this straightforward,
that is certainly not the heaviest of the hardest
of all the hardest stuff that I like, if you know what I mean.
Hey, Google did something interesting.
They, I got to tell you, man, these guys,
they got their shit together.
I've been using Google notebook to, you know,
kind of as a quasi-outliner to keep track of mainly my show,
which is nice because it's then available anywhere.
Duh!
Not to mention the fact that our entire company seems to have just
devolged on Google Docs, man.
I tell you, there's something there.
It shows that people really use spreadsheets for,
I don't know, lists.
Yeah, the finance department,
user will spreadsheets, but oh, boy.
Anyway, they've revamped the Google notebook,
at least to show it up today.
Now, you can pop it out, pop out a window,
and it resizes neatly.
So now I can have Casplaster open,
I can have a couple other players open if I want to,
and I can literally size my Google notebook
to exactly where I want it to be.
So thank you, Google.
You've made my life even better.
And Google's not the only people I want to thank today.
My friend, Jeff Smith.
Our push people picks by Goli Goshik is a fine question.
Yes, it is.
Our push people picks.
You know, months go by, don't hear from the boy.
And then all of a sudden, he's all over the shit.
I love it, Jeff.
Thank you.
Our push people picks, this seems to be something that
people are very interested in hearing about.
Not from Jen, from Bucket, Adam.
Maybe the new question is,
our potty picks pristine in private.
Yeah, you know, it seems like we're really
onto something strange here that apparently,
people who work in very nice sophisticated workplaces
who have very good jobs,
who, for all intensive purposes,
are indeed proper pristine push people,
they trash toilets at work.
Yeah, Adam, James, Newcastle.
Ed, you know, I don't have you hit a roller.
I'm not you.
There's this topic of tough people being horrible
and nasty and scummy, scummy,
and right to use them, no feast that you made to me.
It's really used not very nice.
And I, it's a bit of my life at work.
We share, building with around 15 sore luts.
And there's a few women, and we've got separate toilets
for females and males.
And the male toilet is just disgusting.
I don't know why men have to make themselves
sort of disgustingly, smelly and dirty,
you know, horrible, but I go in there.
I think it's the toilet myself,
and it's just piss off all over the floor.
If you're a kid, all over the toilet seat,
and this is a workplace we have people invited in
from the public.
We have representatives from all sorts of companies,
and we have representatives from Dell, Microsoft,
every year.
Even in it, they all come in this building
and they use the same leverage we do.
But it's not just that the toilets that people use
and our clubs and bars will pier.
I don't know why they're saying the rest of the company.
Well, actually, I'm lying.
I don't think so, I'll be in with a place.
And it's just as bad.
But men's toilets in the pubs and clubs
or if you need to take a dump in a place like this,
you're out of luck,
because there is no way you would put your ass cheeks on this seat
in some of these places.
They are a bismal.
And I just want to leave a mental picture in some of these minds.
Remember the film train spotting,
and you've got to see that if you haven't.
Okay, so, the time when you and McGregor have to fish
the toilets out of the toilet pool,
Dell, our mental picture in the night,
that was one, not exactly the final spot.
But that was a kind of toilet that I was in two weeks ago
in a pub in Durham, it was fantastic.
Yes, generally speaking, men are pigs
and I'm one and I'm ashamed of it.
I don't think it's possible, I just think it's men.
Just no bite.
James from Newcastle.
Thank you, James.
And maybe it is just men.
Let's explore this.
Women want to hear from you.
What are the women's laboratories look like?
You're a place of work.
I mean, pubs, that's a whole separate conversation,
which I think we can definitely get to.
But, is it just men who are pigs?
I travel a lot and I visit a lot of bathrooms in airports.
Let me tie you.
That's pretty much the train spotting vibe there as well.
I mean, besides all the noises coming out of those places.
But, yeah, what is it?
Is it just men or is it women?
Inquiring minds need to know.
Our posh people pay, spy, godly goshit is a fine question.
Yes, it is.
Our posh people pay.
Well, I wish I could come up with a great quote that would live on forever.
I think I've got one.
People having sex is pornographic.
No, that doesn't sound right.
Well, isn't it just reality what we're seeing?
It doesn't everyone hope they're having sex like a porn star?
That's the last thing I want.
So here was the quote I hope makes it into the history books as being actually out of
curry.
Uh, excuse me, since I was glad I was doing this.
That's a pretty cool quote, isn't it?
Fuck me with a chainsaw, god damn it.
And I think I have a bit of a sniffle.
Do you talk funny?
It's funny.
That's why they call it talking funny.
Reality is funny, Rafi.
Adam and pod showed.com for all you warm goodness.
Wait a minute.
Can we do this differently?
There we go.
OK, I'll try this way.
So Adam and pod showed.com is the email address to let go of all your doubt and self-loathing.
And you can find a pundit life and a great deal on a classic automobile at DailySourceco.com.
Hey, everybody.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Bye, bye.
Oh, crap.
That's a sander from the Netherlands.
Podcast Studio.NL, he's making some cool stuff.
And I'm not quite sure exactly what is Nietzsche's, but if I look at how successful Jeff Smith
has become creating jingles for everybody, then damn.
I think you want to get in touch with sander.
Podcast Studio.
If you're looking for something to be put together, that was his mixture of my quotes
that I want to go down in history as having said.
I really, you know, yesterday and another day, almost a full day with the tablet because
I did so many phone calls.
I emptied out the battery on the E61 around 11.30 last night.
I just did not stop at 8 for 20 minutes.
It was crazy.
And we got a lot of stuff going on.
We have a Nokia proposal do this afternoon in New York for free Trinity.
So I'm very excited about that.
And just I am such a fan of this N800 tablet.
I really am.
And it mainly because the open, you know what, I posted something on curie dot com the other
day.
Let me see if I can bring that up for you.
It was a link to, hold on.
It's just coming up.
You remember I'm on the, I'm still on the voter phone.
So it's a little bit slower.
Here we go.
Starry Hope 10 ways the Nokia 8800 is better than Apple's iPhone.
And it pretty much jived exactly with my feelings.
Let me just run to this real quickly.
First of all, price, Nokia 800 399 Apple iPhone 499 or 599 plus the two year singular
service contract.
Open source is 0.2.
Nokia 800 is a Linux device based on a modified version of Debian GNU Linux, which they call
the internet tablet OS 2007 edition.
The iPhone is far from open, which still not sure what Steve Jobs meant, where he said
the iPhone runs OS X.
I'm just paraphrasing obviously because these are much longer than I'm telling you.
Three third party applications.
Nokia strongly encourages third party developers to make software for their N800.
And that of course is where they have Mimo.org, Mike Alpha Echo, Mike Oscar.org.
Apple has stated they will not allow third party applications on the iPhone.
Or no service contract with singular needed.
Well, with the Nokia 800, you can access internet Wi-Fi via Bluetooth enabled mode, or with
a Bluetooth enabled mobile phone.
This allows you the freedom to use the mobile provider of your choosing.
To get an iPhone, you have to sign up for two year contract with singular.
I don't forget that this N800, it is a VoIP phone.
And sometime in this half of the year, from what I've read, there will be a Skype, a version
of Skype for the N800.
Well, that basically just turned your thing into a phone.
Five removable storage, Nokia 800 has two memory slots that support a range of memory cards,
SD, mini SD, micro SD, MMC, RS, MMC, and LMOP.
This allows you to keep one card in the device for more permanent storage and you still
have one on the front that you can interchange with your camera.
Apple's iPhone has no removable storage, probably design as it helps justify a higher price
model with more memory.
Six, better audio and video codec support.
Yes, I'm down with that.
The N800 supports a wide range of audio and video formats, AAC, AMR, MP2, MP3, RA, Real Audio,
Wave, WMA, 3G, PAVI, H2263, MP1, MP4, Real Video, and Flash Video.
Although it's only Flash 7, now Flash 9 is on the way I understand.
The iPhone, like the iPod, plays only Apple's sanction audio and video formats.
This means you can play content from the item store as well as MP3 audio and MP3 files,
no streaming to the phone or playing competing formats and no flash.
On the browser, no flash either, I guess.
It's not a cell phone.
Now this is a big one because as I just said, it is an internet phone crap, how am I doing
on time?
What do we have?
Shoot.
I'm glad I saw that.
I'll run through this for the serious people.
So it is a VoIP phone is number eight, number nine, webcam for video conferencing, and
number 10, and this is probably the best one.
It's available now, but I really like the open source nature of it.
That's what really does it for me.
Oh, I got an email here from, see, Daniel says, not sure if it'll run in the
Nokia, but I've been using Bash Potter, which works on Linux to automatically
a download podcast and it uses a shell script using WGET.
I'm going to install that.
That's a perfect project for this weekend, depending on the weather, of course, because
Captain Dan does want to do some training exercises with me.
And I'm, of course, I'm talking about flying the aircraft.
Hey, stars people.
I'll see you Monday, folks on the podcast.
I just still with me.
We're going to do some instrument training over the weekend.
Hey, you know, it is, of course, the daily source code Friday, Fubar edition, no Fubar
edition is complete without surgeers, he died.
Hey, what's up, Adam, it's Jersey Todd on your Fubar Friday and you know, when I think
about it on a Fubar Friday, baby, you need to get Fubar beyond all recognition.
And I'm proud to bring to you with, with what I think is her long overdue DSC debut,
Jesse Moss.
Yeah, Jesse's open for Missy Elliott.
She's been recorded with Cypress Hill and she's finally making her way to the daily
source code.
This one's going to get you moving on a Fubar Friday.
It's Jesse Moss with sinking drinking fits.
Check this out.
Gotta find another way to make my day.
Hey, be it so, but it's gotta be more than it.
So enough to stay out the piss, gotta be more as well.
And fish, gotta be more to sink in drinking, fish, I see it.
I've been lucky, but won't count, but as it's too busy countin' empty, sat down the floor
in the ball and I'm far from the feet with everything I got, gotta stop now for a ride.
So I do now away with your best friend and to see it go, like to say, no get bored of myself
feel like everything so, but I ain't a winner, I'm Aussie.
Hey, haven't you remembered just too, to apologize too, and you know, it's lies
when I say I won't do it again, so win.
Dear friend, no weather is good, I should put this bottle down and step that side.
And a minute and I'll just one more sip, one for the road on second floor.
This is working out, I'm Aussie, right here.
I just have one more sip, please hear cheese and cheese and bravery now where we are.
Oh, yep, that's right there, put this bottle down and step that side.
And one sec, there's the teller phone, that's cum to ladder, friend is calling.
Be just brain-run, not to just turn out and soar.
What's next though, yes, that the door we go, I'll just find my shoes, that's somewhere.
Hello, what's this next to my sock?
A tea plane, a lot of Irish thoughts go back to women.
Listen joyously, I, yes, lovely, it's funny.
People say when I was getting a tooth, I'm not sure what to do.
I'll know my skin dark, I will, today's a bedroom, stay in sight.
I was weird, so I'm not still waiting to make a lie.
For recovery, I've been knocked out and can't steal, I'm still waiting to make a lie.
Got the little me, I was weird, so I'm not still waiting to make a lie.
Got the little me, I'm still waiting to make my day.
For recovery, I've been knocked out and can't steal, I'm still waiting to make a lie.
I was weird, so I'm not still waiting to make a lie.
Got the little me, I was weird, so I'm not still waiting to make a lie.
For recovery, I've been knocked out and can't steal, I'm still waiting to make a lie.
Got the little me, I'm still waiting to make a lie.
That's definitely different to Sir Todd.
Jersey Moss, Death Jersey Moss, Jesse Moss.
On the pod save music network, I checked by the way, yesterday about black malicious.
They're on tour right now, and those are their current songs from their live DVD, which they're promoting, so it may total sense.
Before I forget about the Nokia, I just want to say one thing.
What?
Excuse me, Finland, hello.
Let me see if I can do this.
I think I can do this.
Hello, Finland.
Hello, Finland, Finland.
Pay attention, calling out to Finland.
Can't let me get the reverb back there.
What idiot engineer decided that all new Nokia phones have to have these little, itty, little tiny, like little power plugs?
This is the stupidest, design decision I have seen in years.
I have gone through three adapters now, because here's what happens.
You have to see this thing.
If you have a Nokia phone, you have an older model.
You know, there's a plug that goes in the bottom, it's just a straight jack.
What would you call it?
Is that like not an RCA?
It's just like a power, but like on every single adapter in the world.
For some reason, Nokia has decided that all their new phones, at least all the new ones I've seen, have this little, it's like an ant dick.
And this ant dick plug is so fragile that, you know, I love to, I have my phone next to my bed in the condo.
I don't have any phones here at home next to our bed, because I figure, if you're calling the middle of night, I can't help you anyway.
So don't weigh me up.
No matter what's going on, I might as well get a good night's sleep for whatever tragedy is struck.
However, when I'm in San Francisco, I got the girls here.
There's an eight hour time difference.
So I have the phone next to me on the nightstand.
And of course, you know, I reach overnight, you know, getting some water or something, or, you know,
sometimes the phone falls off the nightstand.
It's not a big drop, and it's carpeted, so the phone's fine.
If it falls right on that plug, cushion app, and dick broken, you know, if you, if you pick up the phone and it's still plugged in,
of course, this is what Apple solved with their magnetic power plug.
You know, with the old model, you know, the, the plug would just jerk right out.
With the new model, you break another ant dick, and it's all over the world, our client for this, my friends.
Really, really don't understand that.
For those of you just joining the daily source code, I have an automobile, her name is Trinity.
She's a, egg non-colored, egg non-yellow colored Mercedes station wagon turbo diesel 300 TD from 1984 with five cylinders running on biodiesel.
And we're sending her on the road starting in San Francisco, California.
She's going to go all the way across the United States with a little bit of luxury continue around through Europe.
Excuse me, we haven't talked about this yet, but she could actually go all the way around the world, you know.
She's been fixed up, everything, I think she's been fixed up, I'm still waiting for Rosie to call in.
Rosie, thanks for listening to the show.
And Alexander, members looking for his lyrics for a great Trinity song the other day, he resented to me, ah, you dear boy, thank you.
Let's greet her nipples and fuel her bits, this four-wheeled lady who's full of tricks from the pimps of petrol, set us free.
So let's oil her up and free Trinity, you'll listen to the daily source code.
Dear, thank you.
Exxon mobile, $40 billion in profit. Again, I'm not against those guys making profit because they have to reinvest all those billions for the next 50 years of getting oil out of mother earth.
And it's going to be very difficult, very expensive and look, we can make a difference.
You know, how many how many people can suck oil out of one restaurant? That's probably a good question.
So if I'm just a regular driver commuter and I'm making biodiesel or someone's making it for me and we're getting it from a local restaurant, how much does a restaurant produce?
Ah, these are questions.
The lady love has been sending openings for the daily source code for the past couple of weeks. He sent in two today. The one you heard with grandpa at the top of the show.
Of course, from the lady love from love house radio, the daddy cast and here's another one he sent in.
And if material story about a man named Curry, always smoking dope to, he's never in a hurry.
Said, by these who is the place ought to be, so by twist to faith, he found Trinity, vegetable cooking it.
It's not like french fries. Well, next thing you know, the old cars breaking down, maybe it's because Adam never is around.
We've got our old fix, whatever reason, maybe, and they started a looping call for each entity worldwide.
Joy ride.
So now everybody wants to take your first spin, the biodiesel project has started once again.
To hear more about this realist who's a car, listen to the show because we're going to beef you more.
DSC 538, who are Friday.
Thank you, PD. Fantastic man.
Yep. Let's just roll on a little bit of an update as we get ready for the weekend.
Shall we?
You know, Jeff Smith, man, you are so talented.
I've got to make songs that you just want to sing along to. Can't help it.
Cassandra is trying to find a suitable replacement for Trinity at the condo in San Francisco.
And a lot of people have emailed in about this and there's some threads on the Google group, which you can find a link to in the show.
No, it's a daily source code dot com. But if you're familiar with Google groups, it's groups dot google dot com slash free Trinity.
And I got to kind of parse through the whole Google groups thing. It's a little bit different than Yahoo groups, so working on it.
I'll spend some time this weekend.
You know, people are saying, ah, you should get one of those hybrid jobbies.
Yeah, the Toyota Prius or Prius or however you pronounce it.
Yeah, I'd rather walk quite honestly than drive one of those, although they are extremely popular in eco friendly.
But I don't like that.
Dave from New York, who was kindly offered to pivot Trinity out with the Astro turf, which might be the way to go once she hits New York.
I also sent me some pictures of some mockups of licensed plates, vanity plates.
Trinity, biodiesel, and a photo shop of what Trinity will look like with when she's decked out an Astro turf.
Dave, I think it's good if we can get it to New York, you know?
Let's see.
Ah, my calls have been answered.
Hey Adam, this is Craig Meyer calling. I'm the guy who a couple years ago did that pro code on the map to do the pro
pro potter for you or the cast, catcher or put out a root call that's right on me.
I got your call about wanting a Frapper map interface.
And I have a friend here, a Brit, who just got laid off by her company, who's very interested in doing such an application.
In fact, he already has one done because he's playing the driver across the country in his, the leech to the vet would is.
And, but the same software could be used to track your Trinity trip and he's working on exactly what you want,
which is to have a web interface to have people post in sites of interest so you can plan a trip.
I will send you email so that you get his name and with a little more information that I just wanted to let you know.
Take care Adam. Good job. Bye.
Dude, thanks. Good to have you back in focus and thank you very much.
I've already seen some comments on the the free Trinity Google group about that.
Again, this weekend when I really have time to sit down and have no other crap on my mind.
I'll just go through this and I think we have a community, my friends.
Clearly, we've got something going. There's like 40 people signed up now.
So sick freed from the Netherlands who, amazing sick freed's able to reach me,
but yet this week the gossip rags in the Netherlands are full of stories about how I have,
I'm on the run from creditors.
I didn't see that hard to get a hold of me. Adam just catching up on DSC's.
Love the idea about free Trinity. In my day job, I'm an organic search consultant.
I'm not a podcaster. I really want to help.
In short, I do search engine marketing. Wouldn't be a great idea to set up a total website around free Trinity.
Well, we're going to set that up. It's going to be a profile page on Podshow Plus.
Your help would be greatly appreciated.
The search engine optimization is, that's quite a job, man.
It's like an art. It's not even a science. We got a couple people doing it now.
We're working on our feeds. We've changed some things now, so that you get better search results and iTunes.
But it is truly an art form. You need some specialists for it.
So it would be awesome to have you on board, buddy.
I guess anywhere the biodiesel shows up as a search result.
We want to link to Trinity.
Hey, Adam, Kenny from Northern California, checking in on the Trinity issue.
Do you have $200 for a battery? You got host.
I did. I know I got totally shafted on that one. What can you do?
And it wasn't even broken.
But of course, it went to the Mercedes dealer. What do you expect?
You know, I love Trinity, but Mercedes, blow me.
Hi, Adam. This is Reed and DC with a biodiesel question.
A question is, as people start using other oils, modified oils for cooking.
Let's say oils that don't have trans fats like Burger King is going to do.
Or oils that are actually not oils at all, but other synthetics that are being developed.
They haven't zero calories and so on.
As they start using those, what's going to happen to the use of that oil in the biodiesel industry?
Does zero trans fat oils still have potential to be diesel fuel?
What about some of those synthetic that are not really oils that you can still cook with?
What if getting the waste products from a fast food restaurant is going to turn out to have problems?
Because you can't burn the fuel.
I appreciate it. And the listeners know the answer to the question.
Thanks. Bye-bye.
You know, it's a good question. I think the answer is you can pretty much do anything.
You can poop in our tank and it'll probably work.
At least if it's not less than a quarter full because of the crushed gas tank currently.
The fuel doesn't flow.
Now I think that is very interesting and that might be a good PR angle.
I'll spin up a conversation on the free Trinity Google Group.
Wouldn't it be interesting now that trans fat is in the news so much lately?
I don't see why it wouldn't be able to use trans fat.
Refine it and use it as biodiesel.
I think it'll work perfectly and that is something the press loves.
They love to pick up on something with a new angle.
It's all looking to that but I'm pretty sure the answer is going to be yes.
Hey Adam, it's stuck from Germany. It's been a long time since I called it.
It's stuck from Germany.
It's kind of behind on my chat chat.
It's just listened to 531.
It's just calling it about the...
Sorry, I'm driving.
It's just calling it about the free Trinity and the comment that the gentleman was talking about
with going on a road trip with his son.
I think that's an awesome idea and it actually got me thinking.
Much fodder is retiring in a couple of months and I think we got some work in
going along trip with him somewhere.
It's a driver cross.
Oh no, he's so disrespectful.
Anyway, I thought it was really inspiring and actually we had a loss in the family recently.
It was called the whole family and I've been looking for a good excuse to do something
with my parents and find them with my daughters a great idea.
That's the power podcast we made.
Keep it up and y'all be catching up.
I was looking into an audio book and it was really good.
But bad part is it's like far behind on podcasts.
All right, take care.
Bye.
I'm a thank-ass beautiful.
It really is and I think we'll we'll see more stories like this.
This is Trinity makes her trek around the world starting in San Francisco, California.
I think we'll see people bonding on these trips and I'm very jealous of you because obviously
I can't make a trip like that with my mom anymore.
I don't think my dad and I can quite bond in that way anymore.
I don't know.
But it's a beautiful idea man.
And I hope Trinity makes a stop near you so you could maybe make part of that trip
as a part of the free Trinity project.
All right.
Again, the Google Group is groups.google.com free Trinity.
They're the world wind viable prizes indeed.
Okay, I got one more song for you, a special recording before that.
I just wanted to mention, yes, I was pissed yesterday.
You know, we are without a doubt one of the major forces online for godaddy.com, one of our sponsors.
And we have signed up so many new customers for them.
And we have a really good relationship with them.
And you know, godaddy is pretty famous for it's a very sexy Super Bowl commercials
with the current raining godaddy girl.
Oh, I got a reminder.
Next week to tell you about godaddy girl, UK.
And you know, so, and they're always getting banned or, you know, CBS won't play
I'm during the Super Bowl.
You know, it's like, you know, and there's a couple of them up online.
I think if you go to Bob Parsons.com, he points to to two commercials.
One like a Sharon Stone channel kind of where the godaddy girl sits there and she's being
interrogated and she uncrosses her legs.
It's like very hot.
Definitely something CBS would not air.
But our totally loved it.
It was very, very sexual.
Now, so I did know, partially through the internal grapevine that Paul
Tuddle, senior and junior from Orange County choppers.
We're going to be in the new in the new commercial.
And I knew that it was coming and it was going to be fun and sexy and whatever.
And they go daddy released a like a mini mini portion almost like the beginning of
the commercial.
And you know, you see a door open and it's like, I like a nano second.
You see some chicks dancing in the background.
I'm like, so I talked to the sales we said, dude, can we get like some real footage?
Because that would be cool.
So I asked this last week yesterday.
Some new member who just signed up to pod shows,
sneak peak dot pod show dot com.
That's sneak s n e a k p e e k dot pod show dot com.
Excuse me.
He signed up and has put up a video, which is clearly edited by go daddy.
So it existed within the go daddy organization.
And he's put it up on, I guess it's a he.
You know, is it has put it up on on his on his profile page.
And it's awesome.
If you want to see some of the behind the scenes footage from go daddy,
then you can see it there.
I'm just, I'm just pissed because I want to really roll it out as a big network wide thing.
But it's okay.
So the sneak peak dude is it's clearly on on the tip of getting cool shit from the internet video.
I see you might want to check that out.
Link, of course, in the show notes, a deadly source code dot com.
Hey, Adam, my care from fish ball acoustic.
Just wanted to let you know that the latest episode of the fish ball acoustic podcast is out.
At fishball acoustic dot btpot show dot com.
And this one features a live recording of the shakes doing a totally acoustic set.
Just two acoustic guitars and vocals and a bit of tambourine and and and muracas and so on.
It was a fantastic evening.
The guys played really well.
You will hear on this podcast a versions of the shakes songs that you will never heard before.
Totally stripped back and just really, really good.
Now I'm going to give you a taste of this by sending you a track from the set.
This is an acoustic version of I want a better life, which is their new single.
And it sounds completely different to the single.
But to my mind, it's just as good as I say.
If anybody wants to check this out, go along to fishball acoustic dot btpot show dot com.
And you'll find the whole set there.
And we've got an interview with the lads on there as well.
So some good stuff in there.
Anyway, tailwinds.
Say yeah.
Oh, you're pilot.
I know you're new to the network, but you do realize if you're not a pilot, you can't actually use tailwinds.
You have to use some other salutation.
Yeah, I love those shakes guys.
Liberty Jones, of course, played the crap out of that one.
I want to bet our life is really, really grown on me.
First time I saw them perform it was at the podcast con UK.
And they also are on.
I think the the pre not right now.
Dr. Cockney is on who's on it.
But the previous episode of who's on it with O.J.
O.J. Borge.
Who's on it?
That pod show dot com who's on dot btpot show dot com.
He has the shakes playing on toy instruments.
You got to see it.
But this, of course, is the live acoustic recording that you just heard about.
I think you're going to like it.
Thanks for having us.
Go to the curry house there.
Like the curry house.
Just down the road.
We haven't tried it.
Try it because it's good.
You live it.
So you can probably have it.
Yeah.
What's your problem?
No, no, it's play.
This next song is our next single.
It's coming April.
Yeah, so we're quite excited about it.
And it's the tune called I want to bet our life.
I want to bet our life.
Morgan these four worlds.
I'm my loving wife.
I want to bet our life.
And I want to be your man.
I want to be your man.
Because you pretend you want to be your man.
Oh, does it tell where you want?
Does it tell where you want?
And I want to bet your life.
I want to bet your life.
Just like the one before.
Only faster I want to bet your life.
And I want to run the show.
You're confirm on everyone.
I want to run the show.
Oh, does it tell where you want?
Does it tell where you want?
I want to bet our life.
Oh, does it tell where you want?
Does it tell where you want?
The shakes lie in an unleashed eye-want a better life.
We'd love to hear from y'all.
You know the number but now I hope.
In the UK.
And that'll do it.
I hope you guys have a fantastic weekend.
As I said, I'm going to do a bit of spot of flying if we can.
And just chill out.
Have yourselves a great one.
Don't do anything.
I wouldn't do, which of course leaves the universe wide open.
The source code dot com for the show notes.
Adam at podshow.com.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.