Planting a Jamaican getaway?
Flystone, our stone detendence will see that you arrive with a load.
Stone Airlines to Jamaica fly above the clouds and arrive with a head full of steam when you get there.
And save money with our special economy flights, only 29.95.
John wants you to fly.
In a world where TV networks, movie studios and record labels still think they can govern what you see in here.
One man has the power to return control of entertainment to the masses and make big media corporations wet their tiny little pants.
From Pod Show, comb of the world's most dangerous new content comes the Daily Source Code with Adam Curry.
Delta Sierra Charlie 560.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
I'd like to think I'm flying you to the future.
It's official it's free bar Friday we are fucked up beyond all repair.
This time it's for real my friend stay tuned to your Charlie.
My full bar star.
Is there some way to make this clear?
Because of you I can't sleep anymore since you walked out the door and you left me.
All I do is stare at the wall thinking no thoughts at all.
Simply remember why do you want to drive me insane?
Why do you want to cause me so much pain?
Growing a fire.
I don't think I can make it on my own.
I'm afraid that I might die even on the long way.
So be excited.
Tell me that you're still in love with me.
What you're from in my eye.
I can't feel.
So no darkness from light.
I don't know daytime from night on his face and he isn't real.
Oh well I wake up from this and the midst of your tears and embrace it.
What they tell them I'm supposed to.
I don't think I can make it without you but for me.
I don't think I can make it on my own.
Growing a fire.
I'm afraid that I might die even on the long way.
So be excited.
Tell me that you're still in love with me.
What you're from in my eye.
I don't think I can make it on my own.
Growing a fire.
I'm afraid that I might die even on the long way.
So be excited.
Tell me that you're still in love with me.
What you're from in my eye.
I don't think I can make it on my own.
Definitely a footballer favorite Kevin Reeves throw me a line.
It's exactly what I need today.
I don't know how your fright is going but mine is fucked up beyond all repair.
It's so bad.
Things start off so bad today.
I don't want to harsh your mellow or anything but I almost didn't do a show.
I was like, oh man, I'm not going to have any time now.
Everything's gone exactly wrong.
It's all wrong.
I had it also planned out.
It started last night.
Lady Patricia not feeling well.
Of course you had all the news bleed crap yesterday.
And I was at the day before.
I don't even remember.
So she went to bed early and she has a maybe a little bit of the flu.
It's not like it isn't going around.
And this morning she had an appointment at 10 30 or something or 10 40.
To go back to the doctor so that now that a lot of the nose bleeding had stopped or had subsided
since that huge episode.
Then the doctor could look and see what's going on.
And her nose started bleeding again before she had to go to the appointment.
So of course I'm going to drive her there.
In case we can go to the hospital and get this thing closed up.
It's not a very tough procedure.
Well it turns out that there's not really just one vein on the inside of her nose.
This is such a horrible discussion.
Anyway, they can't do anything about it.
But there may be some infection that is leading her, you know, making her nose be a little bit
susceptible to rawness.
It's crap, right?
So that's crap by itself because I got, I'm on a tight schedule today.
Yesterday I went out and I got myself the new mobile set up.
I promised myself because you know, I've got I've got to set up at the condo.
The bakers rack and San Francisco.
I've got everything set up here in the attic at the curry manner.
And I needed something to take with me to New York because I'm going to be there for a week.
And, you know, I want to have good sound.
I'm sick and tired of, you know, half-assed stuff.
But I wanted something small.
So, man, it's hard to find what we really need as podcasters.
It really is.
I mean, I use cast blaster, which is perfect.
But then I want some processing.
I want signal processing.
So I can, you know, send the whole signal mic and music, etc.
Through one compressor limiter.
And I also need to be able to hear what it sounds like on the other end of the compressor limiter.
So, you know, that's a tall order.
Some beautiful barangir mixers really, really cute.
And I could take two of these barangir mixers.
I use one of the inputs, which would send through to a device, which I'll tell you about in a second.
And then into the second barangir mixer, which would basically just act as a headphone mixer.
Perfect, right?
Get wrong.
Because these portable mixers come with power supplies that will only do 240 volts.
They won't do 110 volts.
And, of course, it's not a big deal because you can get a new power adapter.
Yeah.
But not when you have to have like the funky wacky five-pin barangir power supply plug.
So, that's like a non-starter.
So, I went back to, I went to Anderton.
You know, the place where Roger did is a splash in dash.
And I picked up another one of those compact four.
Let me see.
Hold on a second.
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
I just had to pick it up off of the floor.
The sound craft, four channel, because I know how this one works.
And it's bigger than I wanted.
But probably if you took the two small barangir side by side,
it's probably about the same weight and same size.
And, of course, now I only need one power supply.
And I will have to get a different one, but this has a standard jack.
And I got this, something that was really popular apparently about a year or two ago.
It's a half rack module, which means it's not a huge like 19 inch rack mounted thing that you want to stick in your luggage.
It's a blue max smart compressor, really sweet stereo, half rack size works on 220 or 120 second.
Oh, please.
Yeah.
12240 volt AC.
That's interesting.
It says on the bottom, though, factory configured for 220 volts AC.
Does that mean that I have to change something on the inside somehow?
Oh, please don't tell me that's true.
What a pain in the ass, that'll be.
Oh, if it says 12240.
Well, crap.
Anyway, so pick those two items up on up.
And test it out and so everything's working.
I've got all the, you know, bought new cables, especially.
So anyway, that was to make up time for today because I want to do a proper food bar Friday.
I also wanted to pay a couple bills before I left, you know, like the car company and stuff like that.
It's the only real bills that are, everything else is automatic, I guess.
But for some reason, I can't transfer money electronically to the car company.
And so I'm, so after I get back with Patricia Martin hour behind, I get picked up at 245 today.
It is now one o'clock.
And you know, stuff to pack my suitcase and do all kinds of crap.
And so I, I'm, I'm a Gmail, do my show prep is usual.
You know, downloading stuff and also looking at some other email.
And I go to reply to someone.
And I get the, unfortunately, rather familiar message, you know, unable to send mail.
This is in Gmail, unable to send mail because you've exceeded your quota.
By the way, I should say that Patricia's going to be okay.
It's just kind of tinkering with, with medication.
I should be all right.
It's not a life-threatening situation.
So, you know, I go to save the message as a draft.
Now, this is new because it wouldn't let me save it as a draft either because I'd exceeded my quota.
And just before this happened, you know, Gmail, Farts and Burps once in a while and you get to like, oops, something happened.
Error numbers.
So, and so, please try again in a couple of minutes.
So, that had happened just before this started to happen.
So, I was already a little suspicious looking around.
Really, interestingly, because obviously, my mail quota was exceeded.
You know, I'm always skating around the 98 to 99% of my Gmail.
I was using a lot of my folders with Splendid.
And now, I have that special four gig.
A lot meant that I got through one of our board members.
It was also on the board of Google.
And I said, you know, two gigs just saying, actually, I need much more than four gigs.
But two gigs definitely wasn't cutting it for me.
So, I needed more.
I got four gigs, which was cool.
And it lasted certainly about six months, the additional two gigs.
And ever since then, I've been skating along the 98-99% saturation of the account.
And I noticed that indicator that's at the bottom of every Gmail page, it says, you know,
it's normally it's green if you're okay.
And then it may go red if you get to 99% and then a certain point you're at 100%
and then you have to actually go in and delete something and delete it forever from the trash.
And it's gone.
That indicator has gone.
And I see, it's like they did a refresh.
They, something was refreshed.
The interface made some very, very subtle differences.
Really more in where words and stuff were placed.
But it didn't seem like a big deal, but, you know,
no matter what page I went to, I couldn't find my quota anywhere.
So then, you know, then I went into the trash and lo and behold,
you're not going to believe what happened.
All of a sudden, I'm a 141% of my allotment.
And it even says, oh, I copied this for you.
As I emptied out the trash, no conversations in the trash.
Who needs to delete when you have over two gigs of storage, unlike two gigs?
Wait a minute.
And then I realized what's happened.
When they did some kind of refresh at Google for Gmail,
my account got rejiggered back to a norm.
I mean, it's a regular free account, right?
Only instead of two gigs I had four gigs.
Well, that just went away.
And now I have two gigs instead of four gigs.
The good news is it's got all my mail there.
So it hasn't deleted anything, but it, you know,
it says I have 3,999 megabytes, 141% of my two gigallotment.
Oh, no.
And I've never had it, of course, I've been at a hundred percent,
made even a hundred, 102 percent,
but I've never been at a hundred and 41 percent.
And to my knowledge, when your, when your Gmail box is that full,
email still comes in.
Well, that doesn't happen when it's at a hundred and 41 percent.
I tested from a Yahoo account I have,
and it got returned as recipient has exceeded quota permanent failure.
Oh, no.
And this is bad, and because this Gmail account,
everything comes to the Gmail account.
So immediately, I think, okay, what can I do?
Because, you know, I've got no time.
I've got, I've got to fix this problem.
So, all right, so why don't I afford all incoming mail to my Yahoo mailbox,
which was empty because I had to reactivate that because I hadn't used it for so long.
And, well, that doesn't work because it's just bouncing email messages back.
So it's not forwarding anything.
That's how I came up.
That's how I figured out that with the 141% of your Gmail account,
you know, you're no longer allowed to receive anything.
It's not keeping it for your Google is turning it away at the door.
So I'm like, I got to solve this.
So I opened up another Gmail account.
Thinking, well, what was I thinking?
I was thinking like, well, I could probably pop it over.
I'm like, no, wait a minute, I got the Google apps domain stuff.
I just haven't gotten into it because I wanted to spend some time,
take my time.
Because, you know, you're dealing with DNS stuff,
and MX records, and all kinds of crap like this.
And I'm just not prepared for it because, you know,
I have family members and people who depend on email working,
and I have to set it up just right and make sure that if they're using pop mail,
because I know a couple of the accounts are actually accessing
mail.curry.com or whatever it is.
You know, to pop the mail out of an account there.
Now, to add on top of that, I know this is really geeky,
but I know some of you do enjoy these trials and tribulations.
My email is being hosted by a company called Runbox.
And I thought Runbox was going to be a really good idea.
You know, relatively small company.
Good, good personal customer service and support,
offering plenty of space to, you know,
to manage all email coming into like thecurry.com domain.
Separate accounts, rules for, you know,
for stuff that goes to non-existent accounts.
So it's a really nice setup, right?
And anything that comes into, because I don't pop my mail from there.
Anything that comes into Adam at curry.com is redirected,
redirected to my Gmail account.
Or maybe even to podshow.com first.
I don't know, maybe directly to my Gmail account.
And they have a quota system too,
because you're allowed to receive as much email as you can through their system.
But actually the sending of email,
the reporting or the redirecting I'm doing,
because it does save a copy for a period of time in that runbox email system.
That's limited to, I don't know, like 5,000 messages a day.
So the spam that's not being filtered out by runbox,
which is significant, Gmail does a great job of filtering out all that crap.
But of course, it has to be because, you know,
you got to be careful when you are the main,
you know, the mail master, if you will,
master of the mail, you got to be careful about just throwing shit out.
And so a lot of, you know,
definitely more than 5,000 messages a day are forwarded to my Gmail account,
and then they eventually wind up in the junk folder,
and then spam folder.
So yeah, that's where the curry.com problem comes from.
Is this making any sense?
So, you know, I know that I have to change my MX records,
which means all mail gets routed from the runbox over to my Google apps.
My premier edition domain stuff.
And I just wanted to take some time to do it,
but now I have to go into acceleration mode.
So I'm like, right, okay, on this premier edition,
I've got 10 gigs of space per email account.
So that's more than enough to take care of this problem.
Of course, you have to verify that you are the true holder of the domain name
before you can actually use that 10 gig account.
So, you know, you can either change your MX records,
which is exactly what I didn't want to do,
because I don't want to do that in a rush.
Now, they have something else where you can verify by adding a C name.
So I did that, of course, you know, network solution says,
oh, that's fine.
That's the only domain I still have in network solutions.
Everything else has been migrated over to GoDaddy.
And boy, I'm really hurt and I wish I had this one over at GoDaddy,
but I was just so afraid of it fucking up during the transfer
and network solution sucks so much ass with transfers
that I just want to leave it until, you know,
a day when I was going to figure all the shit out,
which is now, of course, coming upon me very quickly.
Anyway, so I get the MX, the C name record added,
I'm allowed to use the 10 gig email account.
So I quickly, I set up pop.
So now, as we speak,
and it's a really slow process, as we speak,
I don't know how many emails I have in my Gmail account,
but, you know, four gigs worth, no doubt about it.
I had about 26, 27,000 marked as new,
or unread, which doesn't really mean it haven't,
not read them, but, you know, I probably read them
and marked them as unread to come back to one day
and then it scrolls off and you lose that email forever.
So I'm now popping over four gigs worth of data.
Yippee-kai-yay.
So don't send me email.
It's not going to go anywhere, it's not going to happen,
it's just not going to work.
Oh, man.
Ah, okay.
So how's your fucking football going, eh?
I want to say congratulations to the jersey tads,
the tads and jersey.
Yesterday, Robin Bella was born.
I actually have an email here from Todd.
Guys, I'm like on his blackberry sending me updates
from, it was a Robin Bella was being delivered
by C-section, so they knew exactly timing and everything.
8.1 pounds, 19.5 inches.
Mom and baby are great, dad needs a nap.
That's what jersey Todd sent to me.
You got dude.
You need a nap.
But your wife, man.
She got just cut open.
I really want to hear if you saw it,
because I remember when Christina was born
through C-section as well as an awesome experience.
But please, man.
Don't pretend like, like, you know,
it was a lot of work for you.
30 seconds tops.
Comic strip.
Knock, knock.
Adam, carry.
Are you there?
I'm here.
Stop fiddling with this fucking knock.
You're tablet for a fact's sake.
Here is your European Union correspondent.
I just wanted to say that there is only two things
I hate in this world.
People who are intolerant of other people's cultures.
And the Dutch.
Adam.
Can you imagine that while majority of European Union has already opened
their labor markets, the fucking Dutch despite promises,
have not opened theirs on January the 1st, 2007,
so it will not happen on March the 1st, 2007,
as the latest promise was saying.
So let me tell it again.
Fuck you, Netherlands.
I, and 80 million European citizens who are affected
will remember this Dutch disgrace, Dutch disgrace,
for fucking ever.
Oh, those Dutch bastards.
They killed Kenny.
They killed who?
I was like, did he say they killed Kennedy?
I didn't hear that.
For fucking ever.
Those Dutch bastards.
They killed Kenny.
Yo.
I have no idea who they killed.
There is some weird shit going on in Holland.
I have to say they, they finally now have a cabinet.
There were some problems putting a coalition together after the most recent elections.
And what's interesting is that two cabinet members have dual citizenship.
And the opposing party parties, I should say,
are saying, hey, you know, there's a real issue here because who's loyalty
to who are these two cabinet members who have dual citizenship?
I think one is from Turkey, one is from Morocco.
So they have Dutch passports and one is a Turkish,
one is a Moroccan passport.
By the way, Islamic countries, it to some degree.
So their loyalty was being questioned.
And it's interesting because this really did spark off a lot of media attention
about this particular question of loyalty based upon your dual citizenship.
And I got asked by a pretty serious publication.
How do you feel about this?
And I said, well, look, everyone thinks I'm Dutch,
but I was born American.
I've always had an American passport.
I have never requested the Dutch nationality.
Nor do I desire to give up my U.S. nationality for any reason whatsoever.
And, you know, and I said, but, you know, when I was there,
I was loyal to the country, when I was there.
So yeah, there's a lot of weird shit going on with them.
That's for sure.
And you know something's really interesting with podcasting
when the people who call in are engineers and they all have their own jingles.
So I think program at your command is the prolific program program.
I had them prove that program is here.
I just landed in, you know, and therefore I won't be back in San Francisco tonight.
I'm Friday.
I was just about to ask you at that point over the weekend.
And probably just call you in the comments and say,
hey, good job prolific programmer.
I could actually understand you.
And you didn't stutter and stammer.
That was great.
Too bad you're leaving New York because I'm about to go to New York.
Where I will visit the serious satellite studios in New York.
That's what you're listening to if you're on the satellite right now.
Okay.
So that I have no no time to get into all the stuff I'd planned today.
There was one thing.
I want to set it up because I want to get back to this on Monday.
It's not often that I know that I'm going to talk about this on a different day.
Last night on Channel 4, which had been advertised.
I'd seen it the promo is on TV for at least a week.
There was an awesome, awesome documentary called The Great Global Warming Swindle.
Of course, you know, that really caught my eye.
Being a child of the 70s, the great rock and roll swindle from the sex pistols, of course, fabulous.
So the great global warming swindle.
It's rather long, but it's really important that you try and see this if you can.
I have no idea if it's going to be aired in the United States or any other countries.
If I had the time, I'm telling you, I would get a copy and put this up on YouTube.
I think it's that important, not necessarily because I'm saying that it's right,
but because I had never heard the supposing view of global warming.
And so they do have a website, which I will put in the show notes.
And actually, there's a, here, let's do this.
Before I read pieces of the website, they have a trailer.
So let me see if I can do this and be fire this up.
Of course, this will take a few seconds because their trailer is an embedded windows media file.
And I don't know about you, but in Firefox, at least.
Whenever I use a windows media player embedded video, it kind of like freezes everything up.
I told you yesterday that I don't like what windows media player does.
When it has to think about something, particular talking to the network, it gets all funky.
Okay, we're probably going to hear an ad first.
Let me see. This is from Channel4.com.
Some say that the time for debate is over, that mankind must face up to its responsibility for climate change.
Now meet the experts who believe science tells a very different story.
And people say we don't believe in global warming. I say, no, I don't believe in global warming.
I don't believe that humans, you know, who is pausing that warming.
You can't say that CO2 will drive climate. It's certainly never did in the past.
If you are skeptical about the litany around climate change, you're suddenly like you're a Holocaust denier.
The global warming is dressed up as science, but it's not science.
The most controversial and thought-provoking science film you'll see this year,
examines the role nature is playing in global warming.
They're just being told lies.
The Great Global Warming Swindle, Thursday 9 on 4.
Now if you saw, by the way, we didn't get the ad. That was kind of cool.
Because when I watched it, when I previewed it before the show, I did get the ad.
So, that was smart. Thanks, guys.
If you have seen El Gore's movie, an inconvenient truth, then you have to see this movie to balance out your opinion.
Let me just read from the site, and then I'll try and editorialize to make it a little more clear.
The Great Global Warming Swindle, the film brings together the arguments of leading scientists
who disagree with the prevailing consensus that carbon dioxide released by human industrial activity
is the cause of rising global temperatures today.
That's a catchy one, isn't it?
That Earth's climate is changing and always has is not disputed by anyone.
That is, that it is warming now is also not disputed by anyone.
But some people think that the warming is our fault whilst others believe we have nothing to do with it.
That really is true. This is what this film is about.
It's the difference, and there's some very, very compelling evidence that does not say or that refutes the claim
that CO2 emissions created by man are creating global warming.
In fact, quite the opposite according to the proof is that global warming, although it does take place over thousands of years
and they have some interesting graphs to look at.
It has been much, much colder and much, much warmer in the past 10,000 years than now.
So when the Earth warms up CO2 actually follows and they have some theories about that,
or not just theories, but I guess all sciences in a way theory.
Look, I'm not a scientist, but I was compelled by this movie.
The film argues that rises in atmospheric carbon dioxide have nothing to do with climate change.
Further, the present single-minded focus on reducing carbon emissions may have the unintended consequence of
stifling development in the third world, prolonging endemic poverty and disease.
Recent research presented in this film apparently shows that the effect of cosmic radiation
and solar activity may explain fluctuations in global temperatures more precisely than the carbon dioxide theory.
And when you see this, and you will be blown away, not just by the evidence presented,
and of course, it's all in interpretation of numbers and data, but it's fascinating.
So again, literally, the core difference here is that in this film, the theory is explained.
And it's shown in data that carbon dioxide levels increase following the warming of the Earth.
It's not that carbon dioxide increases and then the Earth starts to warm up.
And they have historical data going back quite a long time, almost as far back as I am old.
And what's interesting about it is they go into the political aspects of it.
I'm already really talking about this, but it's really on my mind.
This is what the shit I wanted to talk about today.
In the 70s, and they're blaming it on Margaret Thatcher, which is a fun thing to do.
You can always blame everything on Margaret Thatcher.
Of course, we had an energy crisis with the OPEC countries in the 70s.
So Margaret Thatcher, of course, hated foreign oil.
She hated the coal miners because they were a big pain in her ass, at least, at the time.
So she didn't want carbon emission based fuel, whatever.
And she was a big proponent of nuclear.
And through the campaigning that Margaret Thatcher did, more or less a meme was built that carbon dioxide is bad.
And by the way, we're all made of carbon dioxide.
I'm like 98% carbon dioxide, which includes water.
It's not like a bad thing.
It's not like a poison.
Carbon dioxide is what makes things grow.
But that kind of got turned around and twisted into this idea that carbon dioxide is essentially causing global warming.
And they take it once a further.
The founder of Greenpeace, who was left Greenpeace since, he had a lot of interesting things to say.
He said, look, it's not even about the global climate anymore.
It's being used as an excuse for anti-globalization and anti-capitalism, in fact.
And that no politician today could have any type of platform without including greenness.
And when you look at the data that's presented in this film, particularly that of all carbon dioxide in the atmosphere and the troposphere,
the whole carbon dioxide, only about 1% is man-made.
1%.
So, you know, there's so much new data in here that my head is just spinning.
So I'll put the link in the show notes prominently so you can find it because there's a lot of information on the site.
I don't think, I mean, are they going to, let's see if they're going to replay it now.
Oh, that's too bad. Oh, what's this? Play, what is this?
Oh, that's play fantasy football. Why don't they just, this is a great, they should put this on YouTube.
That's so, it's so good to see this.
So, of course, you know, you take that a little bit further and then, you know, it's very unpopular.
You know, you can't just stand up. It's like when I say, hey, hold on a second with your net neutrality.
You know, there's a lot going on in networks. It's kind of the same thing.
You know, people stand up and say, well, you know, this global warming thing is full of shit.
And the zeitgeist is already so embedded in our minds that we're, you know, we immediately assume that someone who stands up and says that is a part of, you know, big oil or, I'm sorry.
Yeah, big oil or or different industries or the man or whatever.
And really, there's enough evidence that, you know, you just might want to reconsider your opinion. It's really, really, really fascinating.
And I'm going to study as much as I can about this about this theory and I'm really happy the channel for air that it just blew me away.
It's too bad Patricia couldn't see because she was already in bed.
Okay, and so then at the end of the day, what the documentary, it's a film, but I think it was more documentary.
What it, you know, what they hypothesize or what they go against that out to prove is that because there are such a movement that Africa is now being told, hey, you shouldn't be using your oil or your coal or other resources.
You should be looking at, you know, if you want to develop, you should be looking at solar and wind energy and add like the African guys are like the fucking I'm going to do with the solar panel.
He'd up a transistor radio. I need to, you know, I need to be bacon steel here. We're not going to do that with solar panels.
And look, please, if it's, if you can find this anywhere or if anyone knows where there's a copy available uploaded to Podshow, go ahead, put it, you can do it as an embeddable.
If we get to take down notice, we'll, we'll take it down, but you really have to see that it's that important. It really, really is.
Whew, okay. So flying to New York today, but of course, we can't really have a complete full foobar without at least some word from the garden state, from the Jersey.
Hey, how are you doing? Okay, I guess you have to be from Jersey to sound right saying that, right?
I'm Brian from audio attitude, not in Jersey, but in Michigan's UP, as it happened just a few miles from Jeremy Roe.
When you hear Jeremy Roe play that, Fubar, Friday, Jersey Todd theme, Jersey Todd, the official musicologist of the Charlie plays a song from a great pod save artist.
But not today, Adam, as you know, Jersey Todd is a bit too fubard to join us today, but he did send a quick update.
Hey, it's time we're welcoming into the world, Robin, and Bella. He pounds one ounce, nineteen and a half inches, she's very pink and very mellow and very calm.
I'll talk to you later. Bye bye.
So I've been on some kind of a pod sabbatical thing, and Todd, the other day told me to get busy and do something useful.
I said, why not fill in for Fubar Friday? Make sure you play something, Adam's going to like.
Okay. Well, you got it, JT. Adam, today we're going to welcome a brand new very special talent to the PMM.
There's a good chance that everybody listening has heard his work. He's a music producer, songwriter composer, recording engineer, music performer, and even a Grammy nominee.
He's also from Jersey, and back in the Jersey days, he's now in Vegas. He had a studio in Mercerville, the cater declines like Bruce Foster, Skip Scarborough, instant funk, springsteens band, the smithereens, Bon Jovi Gettars, Richie Simbora and Billy Joel, Paul Shea for Richard Marx.
I mean, the list goes on, but when he was just starting out, this was like roughly 79. He had a little bit of time on his hands in between the sessions.
And so Tommy Merolda began making his own music, one analog track at a time, vocals drums guitar. He called this one man band The Tom's.
Now, Billbora Magazine called the independent album that he released back in 1979, the best power pop album of the decade, and it's a hot collector's item today.
Now, while he's put out a lot more music by the times, as well as his other band, the horizontal ladies club, kind of that name.
Most of his time has been spent producing performing songwriting with musicians, like 50 albums worth.
You know, share, both of Richie Simbora's LPs, but it was his Grammy nomination for best album of original score written for a motion picture for his work on the movie Stan alive,
that brought his music talent to a lot of movies, like, oh, days of thunder, carmen, once in the life, and this most recent Rocky Belboa picture, also the upcoming Evan Almidey, the sequel to Bruce Almidey.
So, okay, so you're thinking, okay great, the guy's talented, he's got lots of talent, he's done stuff, okay, what's the big deal?
Because he totally gets the independent artist.
He's part of this new media revolution where independent artists are starting to blossom all over the place, and he's focused on Las Vegas because that's where he's located now,
and he's mentoring a lot of independent artists.
Like, for example, Junior Anthie, Sex League, Fletch, AMV, randomized, and he brought music by Las Vegas rapper D John and the killers in on the Rocky Belboa picture and featured their music.
So, you're going to hear a lot more of him and probably a lot more indie music coming out of that Vegas area, because it's heating up.
And he also has somehow figured out time to put together a new Tom's album, and that's coming out shortly.
He wants the lettuce, have a taste of it, and so that's what we're playing today.
Thank you, Jersey Todd.
Thank you, Adam.
Have a safe trip to New York.
Happy food bar Friday, everybody.
Here's Tommy Marolda.
The Tom's with adventurous kind.
Hey.
Just wanna get some, tell me when we did better,
made in China tell me, come and watch it now, tell me damn it,
but you never know the answer.
I am the adventurous kind, never know what I might find.
I am the adventurous kind, and I have no will, I have no mind.
Just wanna get some, tell me when we did better,
and got a lot of attention, come and watch it now, tell me damn it, but you never know the answer.
I am the adventurous kind, never know what I might find.
I am the adventurous kind, ever know what I might find.
I am the adventurous kind, never know what I might think.
I am the adventurous kind, never know what I might find.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
You sing a bit of a song of Gooni B-Wid, Knee Bassie,
Thank you so much for filling in for the Toddster amazing. What a factory over there in Jersey
All right, so definitely a food bar Friday
So a kind of a food bar last thought then just you know going back to
Thinking about how we indeed mind of convinced ourselves of this global warming thing
This global warming crisis and it may not be true at all
Yet four billion dollars a year of government money is spent on research on global warming each year in the United States alone
So I think we have to look at this as uh, perhaps possibly a classic example of
The game of telephone and I think it was Thanksgiving that I played in this last and it had been quite a while before then
But even grown up adults sitting right next to each other can't reliably pass off information from one to next because by the time the original message
Comes back round full circle
Obviously it says something completely different and it could be quite the opposite
Particularly if prompted by administration such as out of that sure so
Try and see that if you will and that will be my final thought of the week
Okay, daily source code calm that is working. Thank goodness
So that's where you can find the show notes for today's episode and hopefully by well
I can I just check during the song
Gmail likes to update once an hour on pop and it brings in 200 messages at a time so sometime
In May you'll be able to email me again. My everybody football
Another pod show podcast stick it in your ear
The best and the brightest
Subdupt daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering pod show and limelight