This podcast is brought to you by Pawn Show and GoDaddy.
The show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
GoDaddy.com
Delta Sierra Charlie 680
$16 million worth of airplane straps my ass.
To the next generation free new content in my ears.
We don't need most heat increase in it.
I like to think I'm flying into this journey.
Testing his battery.
It's foggy and California, my friends.
Good morning.
How you doing?
I'm drank a lot of time to kill them in me of your face.
To buy your house for the million time today.
But I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over.
And I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and
I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I'm over and I
I'm just a man, just a man, just a man, now I'm over it, and it's been too long, and I wonder how this whole emptiness I've got it.
I'm just a man, just a man, just a man, now I'm over it, and I wonder how this whole emptiness I've got.
Hey everybody, how you doing? Welcome to the Curry Condo.
No, then California. We're in San Francisco. It is the Daily Source Code episode number 680.
Kick it off with Valley Lodge. I'm so over it.
Great. Bring it home boys.
There's a morning. It's very foggy outside. The condo, it is bright and early.
How you doing everybody? Almost didn't do a show this morning.
Had all kinds of technical difficulties, we'll get into that later on.
Nice to be in California. Nice to be in San Francisco. Nice to have my friends welcoming me back to town.
Good evening. Hey, Adam. It's Ranger Craig on the Rock. Hope you bring a shock mouth to your microphone while you're in San Francisco.
We have a pretty good little shake last night, 5.6 with about 30 aftershocks.
Any case, just what I'm saying, hey, you have the Halloween. Enjoy your stay at San Francisco.
You know how to reach me if I can be of any help.
And I actually have a favorite to ask you.
Yeah, but we'll leave that for another time. Greetings from the Rock.
From the Rock Ranger Craig.
Check it in. He's Ranger Craig. He sits out there on Alcatraz,
which there's no way I can see Alcatraz today. Let me tell you.
I can barely see the Bay Bridge.
And in fact, I can't even see the top of the Tower of Death.
My goodness, this thing is so unbelievable.
You know what they've done up there. And by the way, thanks, Ranger Craig,
for the for the warning about the earthquakes.
Well, we have almost a 6.0 the other day here. Oh, man.
Can't believe I missed that one.
The Tower of Death that is now nearing completion across the way from the condo.
Apparently at the top of the building,
they have this like whole water construction, like a huge water tank
that is supposed to counterbalance any, uh,
supposed to counterbalance any earthquakes.
All I can see is I'm going to be really fucking wet
if that thing kills over.
I'm going to get that water right on my head.
Oh, yeah, I need to say something nasty and Swedish.
Hi, I just thought I'd show the drunken Londoner and I couldn't resist.
So here's it. Here's it. It isn't Swedish.
I don't carry it. No, not a. Yeah, yes.
So no, not a.
That's the nasty version of Yelskadi.
Oh, boy. I got to tell you so many things happened yesterday.
Of course, got to brighten early, uh,
hopped on, uh, on the virgin Atlantic upper class to, uh,
to ride and over to San Francisco.
Of course, completely un-eventful as, uh, as usual.
I did watch, um,
Michael Moore's new movie, Sickko on the airplane.
And, uh, I hadn't seen this movie yet.
I certainly encourage you to see it.
You know, I have very, very mixed feelings about this.
If you haven't seen Michael Moore's Sickko,
uh, it's essentially it's about health care in America versus health care in, uh,
in other countries. I'd say, and, and I'd have to say,
it's a beautiful piece of work.
It really shows the differences between, um,
the general health,
and health care in, uh, in the United States.
And it compares it to, uh, Britain,
and the kingdom and, uh,
who have the National Health Service, which is a socialized medicine,
and it, uh, compares it to what else, uh,
to France.
And I got to tell you, I have been in many of these countries.
I've lived in the UK for the past three years.
I know what the NHS is,
and I did not think the movie was very accurate.
Um, in fact, well, what it didn't do is it didn't, um,
show any of the problems that these countries have because of the way
their medicine is socialized.
Um, and although it looks fantastic,
and it is, of course, fantastic the NHS,
because you basically pay nothing as like six pounds you pay for medicine,
you know, instead of the hundreds or thousands of, uh,
of pounds or dollars in other countries.
Um, in France, uh, you know,
it's like, wow, what a well-hala.
But what Michael Moore doesn't do is he doesn't show the huge problems
that are going on with the NHS right now,
or the huge problems that are going on with France in general.
Economically, financially, or economic, or economic kind of the same thing.
Economically, socially, culturally.
You know, there's lots and lots of problems with socialized services.
Not to say that it's a bad idea, you know,
uh, I like the, I have a, my wife is ill, you know,
it's a, I pay huge amount in an extra insurance,
in case anything happens.
The real core of the problem, which I feel wasn't discussed in that movie,
is that the drug companies,
and of course a lot of the private hospitals, or for profit hospitals,
and it's just gotten out of control.
The pricing is just out of control.
That's really the problem.
Uh, you know, there's no discussion of the billions of pounds
that NHS is costing, how many people are really pissed off,
computer systems that are a billion pounds over budget,
aren't working, uh, people dying of the super bug,
you know, maybe that wasn't really apparent at the time this was made,
but I don't know.
The one thing, the one thing that I, the one quote that's stuck out from this movie
that I really, really liked, um,
and was these expats living in France, you know,
and boy, they were living it up.
That's for sure.
Um,
the quote was,
in America, people are afraid of the government
when they want something changed, they're afraid.
But in France, they take to the streets and they protest.
And that I thought was a very good point.
And, uh,
and something to think about, something, uh,
I will be touching on in the next couple of shows.
I don't want to get too deep because well, mainly it's, uh,
not even seven o'clock in the morning here.
It's kind of tough.
I cannot wait to tell you what happened when I landed in San Francisco,
but first, I had, uh,
you know, those technical problems I was telling you about.
It's almost as if my, my lovely son,
Sony Vio, knew that I'd receive this voice comment
and was actually contemplating looking into it.
Hey, Adam, this chip was top of the populate.
And, uh,
I was listening to your last show and you're talking about getting
back up and running again.
And, uh, the only thing you were really wanting
Windows for was you could all, uh,
cast laughter, which, uh,
with my PC,
I was talking about using love and,
and if I ever am on the road,
not using my PC laptop,
then I will definitely, uh,
use it and recommend cast laughter highly.
However, uh,
you might know that, uh,
I switched over to Mac at home,
and really had been enjoying it a lot.
And, uh,
the first things I did was start to mess with a garage band,
as you know, I have a band too,
and you play my music before,
so I really appreciate that.
Uh, you know,
I was talking to Matthew Ebel on an interview on my show,
and then he was talking about how he made his whole beer,
and it was a coffee and cigarette.
He was, uh,
on his, uh,
garage band.
And so I thought,
well, I'll give it a shot.
I'll get a Mac and try to start eating
garage band.
And, first practice song I did,
is a matter of fact you play on your show,
because it was a...
That's right, remember?
Yeah, but they've a boy song.
Yeah, heroes.
You can be curious.
And, although,
I did struggle
and play all the guitars and all the instruments on it,
and learn how to use and send it to you,
and you did play it on the show,
with the lady Patricia present.
You told her that it was a karaoke version
with me saying,
oh, sorry.
And I will have to say,
um,
who's right now.
Fuck you.
Yeah.
You're the fish that you are.
Sorry.
I don't know what's going on with the sound today.
It sounds weird.
Yeah.
So the point, sorry, man.
I didn't mean to,
to harsh your mellow with that.
Yeah, the point being that, um,
Uber Castro hadn't looked at it in a long, long time,
and it's come a long, long way.
And so I started to install this on the,
the MacBook Pro,
and I was indeed quite impressed with one small problem.
There's a delay in the microphone channel.
So I, it's like impossible to speak,
because you hear there's delay,
and then you start to talk like that.
So I got to figure that one out,
until then it's a trusty cast blaster.
And cast blaster didn't want to start up this morning.
That was nice.
You know, like,
running around at 630 in the morning,
freaking out.
Bye.
Okay.
So hey, guys.
Guess what?
All of this talk that we've been having about,
the constitution and skull fuck the rotting corpse of the TSA,
and all those fine things.
The Ron Paul interview.
I'm on the list.
Oh, yes.
This already happened to me once in Chicago,
and I wasn't quite sure if it was just an anomaly.
That was the last time I was in the States.
Yesterday I arrived at San Francisco International Airport.
Had a nice little chat with the Customs officer.
So hey, Adam, yeah.
We used to watch an MTV.
What you doing?
Yeah.
Living in the UK, cool, man.
All right.
Well, have fun.
So let's me go.
I go through to get my suitcase.
And about, before my suitcase came off,
so maybe only five minutes after I'm standing there,
the same guy had apparently come running from
his little cubicle there.
I said, oh, Adam,
can I just have your customs form for a second?
Yeah.
I got to write something on it.
And he writes on it, baggage check.
And I say, oh, why is that?
Did you just all of a sudden decide you wanted to check me?
No, I don't know.
Something popped up in the computer.
Okay.
So I had to go in the other line.
And waited for about half an hour before it was my turn.
And the Homeland Security Officer started asking me some questions.
And I said, oh, he did my passport.
American citizen.
What are you here for?
I have a business here.
I live in the UK.
And oh, you're a so-you're on business.
Yes, I am.
You have a business card.
Now Patricia had made me wear a different coat when I left.
And I was pretty low on cards, but that's where I keep a stack.
And so I hadn't transferred that stack over to my other pocket.
And I said, oh, shit man.
I don't know my wife made you wear a different coat.
So I have to look for one.
I don't know if I have one.
Well, I really need to see a business card.
I'm saying, and this is where I've, of course, made a mistake.
And I said, excuse me.
Isn't my passport enough?
Well, this, of course, was the wrong question.
Well, if you don't want to stand here for another two hours, you better show me a business card.
That was pretty much the response.
And then, of course, they proceeded to open up all of my business.
I had nothing.
You know, no contraband, no bad stuff, no nothing,
but thoroughly searched.
And finally, I found a card of James.
James is our, he runs all production in the UK.
So we'll look, man, here's a company card.
It's not mine.
But here's the UK address.
Anyway, so for some reason, that seemed to be sufficient.
But I'm on the list.
I am most definitely on the list, and I'm not quite sure what it is,
but it's not a pretty one because I am going to get ripped apart every single time I come into the states.
And I'm just not going to buckle.
You know, and I'm going to give these guys shit when they,
tell me that I can't enter the United States without a business card.
That's horseshit.
I was actually, I was pretty angry about this yesterday.
I'm much calmer now, but this is how it goes, I guess.
And I told Patricia, he says, you know,
it's just, you know, you've got a big mouth,
and you're just not a likable guy.
That's the problem.
You see, you've swamped keys.
Hey, you know, does anybody ever push the button to try to send you effects?
Does it ever happen?
Yeah, it does.
Hey, about this female guy.
You've just said his name.
I was just listening.
I don't remember what I mean now.
The way I heard it, he got promoted.
Oh, that promotion you were talking about, he was up for it.
That you didn't think he got it.
Yeah.
He got it, like right after that big press conference.
Like somebody would buy it.
He had a good job of that wag the dog incident there, son.
He got promoted.
But then, like, more up or happen,
and I guess as I said,
to me, he got, he got shit can, he's out.
But the dog knows it's only because some attention got
to some light got shown on that situation or whatever.
Yeah.
The only way in the Bush administration that you can get promoted
is to be incompetent and proven.
Just as, uh, just as Brownie.
Yeah.
Fuck you out.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
I got to work on these voice mail, uh,
on the quality of the sound.
Something's going wrong with the trans coding there.
Yeah, of course.
Okay, it fired.
He actually got promoted.
Of course he did.
This is the guy who set up the fake conference.
A lot of red pill running through my veins,
my friends.
That's for sure.
So I'll run Paul on the tonight show.
That was pretty cool.
Uh, not so marginal anymore.
A.
And Hillary, you know,
comic strip blogger.
You keep telling me that Hillary is a shoe in
for the Democratic nomination.
I don't know if you saw the, uh,
the debate, which was on two days ago.
I don't think so.
Oh, yeah.
It's still anybody's race.
And in the infamous words,
Ron Paul on the tonight show.
Hey, you know,
there's a danger.
I could actually just, like,
kind of win this.
Comic strip.
So, of course,
with me now being on the TSA shit list.
Comic strip blogger is timely as usual.
Adam Kerry.
This or your comment.
It's not about your opinion on as usual.
Okay.
It may be disturbing to you.
This is your last chance.
Stop listening to this or your comment and
delete it.
Delete it.
If you don't want to be disturbed,
the comment will end.
And you will wake up in your bed.
And believe whatever you want.
Okay.
This is a comic strip blogger's red pill blue pill.
I think.
Hello.
See you as be.
So, do I stick with me?
Yes.
You prefer?
Yeah.
Red pill, my friend.
Red pill.
Bring it on.
Okay.
You wanted it.
So, first listen to this.
It is an airplane with which I flow.
Last weekend.
Oh, sounds like a...
Sessner.
172.
Maybe even a 182.
Definitely a like-coming engine.
As an airplane-hit test.
What airplane was it?
It's a like-coming engine.
I can hear that.
Yes.
It is just not airplane.
But it is not the point.
Now, listen to me, Adam Boy.
Tell me.
Do you seriously think that you can fuck with various interests, groups,
without endangering yourself?
Don't you think that some groups may send a contract killer
to eliminate you?
Adam.
You have changed.
I knew you at the time when you preferred to fool around about gadgets
and see the fun things like sex, drugs, and rockin' out.
Now, you got political.
You got serious.
You fuck with more or less secrets and dangerous groups, Adam.
I am afraid that once upon a time,
we may find out that your chestnut airplane had some accident.
And we will know then that they have reached Adam.
But then we will be too late.
Adam, come back to your silliness and stop that political crap.
Ignorance is please.
Fuck you.
Yeah.
Fucker.
Yo.
Alright, I woke up.
I still got the red pill coursing through my vein.
CSB.
Yeah.
Patricia said something very similar.
You know, and I have received a lot of emails about this.
People saying, hey dude, you know, you should really be careful.
You should watch out what you say.
So two points to your statement there.
CSB one.
You know, this is what you guys are talking about.
I mean, I'm trolling my email.
I'm trolling my voice smells.
I'm looking for feedback.
I'm not getting any naked pictures.
I'm not getting any gadget stuff.
All I'm getting is political stuff.
So we're kind of going with the flow.
It goes both ways, right?
If you want to talk about something else,
if you want me to pontificate about my MacBook Pro.
I'll do that a little bit more because I am going to get some version of
Uber Caster up and rolling.
But I will not be silenced, my friend.
I'm sorry.
And yeah, you're absolutely right.
And when you said this about the airplane, I'm like, yeah,
as someone could absolutely sabotage the aircraft.
And what's the worst thing that could happen?
I think failure, I guess.
I guess that would be possible to sabotage it.
You know, it's in a hanger.
I'm not around it.
It's marginally protected.
There's lots of people who have access to it.
So it could someone do something.
Yeah, absolutely.
Am I going to be afraid of that?
No, apps are fucking loosely not.
I will continue to say what I feel is on my mind.
Because that is my right.
And if you hear about an engine failure,
then you'll know what happened.
And the first thing you need to do
is seal off the area, call in wing commander William,
because he'll know exactly what happened.
But I'm just not, you know, I can't live that way.
Comics are blogger.
I can't live in fear of what I say.
So as much as I appreciate it.
Just going to leave it the way it is.
A little concern.
I have a fantastic rant.
Listener called up that I want to play for you.
I hope it doesn't sound as shitty as the other ones.
I might have to wait until tomorrow to play it for you.
I'm going to be able to shop because it's a great rant.
It's two minutes and it's just really, really.
It's a great rant.
Check it out.
Hey Adam.
Hey, this is Mark and Los Angeles.
I'm not trying to get on your show or anything.
I just wanted to respond on show 679,
DST.
I don't know the caller's name,
but he had a comment about putting candidates on your show
or getting candidates on your show
to talk to the DST listeners.
And you've got a great audience.
Obviously, I mean, I'm very conservative.
And I love your show.
I love listening to the range of people that are on it.
And if somebody doesn't have the ball to get on your show
and tell it like it is and be able to talk
without, like, quote, talking point to being positioned.
And just, you know, your audience is an audience that's worldwide.
And it's an audience that ranges to an elected people
that are real.
You know, none of this can crap.
And maybe that's what we need to do is get these people
from, you know, given us the crap they think we want to hear
in tell us who they are, what they're thinking.
And get show a little nuts.
You know, get out there a little bit.
And risk something.
I don't know.
If I was a bummer right now or Edward,
and I wanted to try to do something different.
I'd be on your show at a heartbeat.
I'd be on it.
I'd park straight out as it is.
And I would sit there and say, hey, look at, you know what?
This is what we want.
This is where we're going.
And this is what we can be.
And you don't have to settle for this stuff.
And the only person that I got that, and I really enjoyed it,
was Ron Paul.
I mean, I could not even think about voting for a Republican before.
And Joe, I listened to Ron Paul.
And I started listening to him and his passion
and his who he is.
What he thinks.
And then it is that if there's anything we need more than anything else.
And this damn world that we're living in right now is people we think.
And you can talk to anybody at any time and tell, you know,
we need and we need another Kennedy.
We need some intelligence.
And you know, we need something that says, hey,
you know, let's face it and push down a great job.
We need something.
Hold on, better than what we've got.
Oh, man.
Thank you so much.
And everyone listening should thank this guy because that's right.
You guys are awesome.
The audience of the Daily Source Code is freaking awesome.
I get up at 630 in the morning because you guys are awesome.
Absolutely.
Anyone's welcome to come on the show at any time.
After I get these voice mail fixed.
Sounds like shit.
All right.
I got so much to do.
Though, yeah, homework for you, which we're really talking about
in the next couple of days about black water, I do want to talk about that.
If you haven't seen it, Eric Prince, by the way,
is from Dutch descent.
It turns out his parents as grandparents were Dutch.
Very, very wealthy, very influential.
He is the guy that founded and is the CEO of that private security firm
that has so many forces in Iraq.
You've got to see this interview on Charlie Rose because,
and you know, this guy, all right, you can call him a war prophet here.
You can call him a successful businessman.
You can think he's shady or whatever.
And that's not the real problem.
And I listen to what he said.
And he was answering, I think, appropriately.
The point is, did you know that there are thousands?
I mean, like thousands of private security firms that are working for the United States,
all over the world.
Did you know this?
Were you aware of this?
I mean, our army is just a small part of,
of the, of the manpower that is being,
it's almost like it's a commercial draft, you know?
We can't get enough guys, so we're going to, you know, we'll do,
we'll bring in some commercial guys.
And this guy's mission is to do what,
federal expressed it for the post office, the US mail,
to do that for the armed forces.
I can't really fault him.
And I think barking up his tree is the wrong one.
Probably smells a little bit of dog pee at the, at the base anyway.
So I think that's the wrong way to go.
What is just surprising and astounding, I feel,
is that no one really knew that all of these private security firms
were doing all this war work for us.
It's known as the, what is it though?
The war industrial complex isn't, isn't that what it's called?
Hey Adam Jason from San Diego.
I'm, I just wanted to give two cents about the black water thing.
I was for a consulting firm that there's a lot of government contracts.
Yeah, I'm sorry, this sounds like shit.
Well, we'll deal with that on Monday,
because I don't want to do it tomorrow on Friday.
His point is there's tons of contractors.
I didn't, yeah, of course I knew that, you know,
commercial firms build the, the machinery.
It is the war industrial complex.
That's really what's going on here.
And a lot of our money is going in making a lot of people rich
and making a lot of people dead.
And I'm not not.
Let's play something that we need to play at every time this year,
because it is the first of November, my friend.
The first winter snow outside my window.
Feels like at that time again to me.
The mistletoe, a Christmas show.
And the lighting of that famous Christmas tree.
People are shopping for them loved ones.
I'm making plans for a Christmas feast.
But it all goes by.
And the rain goes by.
And then we have to wait.
Another year.
What if every day?
Christmas.
What a wonderful world.
This would be.
It would never feel blue.
We make all our dreams come true.
With Christmas we're everything.
It was time to bring out the good people.
I just look around now and you will see it.
Everybody's nice and full of light.
And they give to those who are in need.
What if every day?
Christmas.
What a wonderful world.
This would be.
It would never feel blue.
We make all our dreams come true.
With Christmas we're everything.
It was time to bring out the good people.
What if every day?
Christmas.
What a wonderful world.
This would be.
It would never feel blue.
We make all our dreams come true.
With Christmas we're everything.
What if every day?
Christmas.
What a wonderful world.
This would be.
It would never feel blue.
We make all our dreams come true.
With Christmas we're everything.
What a wonderful world.
This would be.
It would never feel blue.
It was time to bring out the good people.
I would never feel blue.
That would be.
It would never feel blue.
This would be.
There's Christmas to the body.
Some of you who are new to the program won't know about that.
I think this is the third year running that we're playing it.
That's right, three years ago.
We created this song.
It's Podsafe for Peace.
It's a whole list of Podsafe music artists.
You can find the link in the show notes.
Of course, a dating source code dot com to find out more about the project.
It's for a good cause.
It's fun to play this now, third year running and it sounds just as good as the first
time.
Before I go, I just want to say that I was watching the Democratic presidential debate and
they were talking about the drum beating going into Iran, Iran, bad guys, nuclear weapons,
Iran, Iran and I realized, we've got to really be careful.
With the way we're talking about Iran, there are a fucking people who live there.
Like 90 million people and they're sophisticated and they've got internet and they can
listen to stuff and they can read web blogs and they have web blogs.
Let's not just talk about Iran, like at some fucking clump somewhere, we're just can drop
a bomb and all problems are solved.
I'm embarrassed.
I am absolutely embarrassed, not about the conversation, but the way we're talking.
I mean, it's crazy, I know there must be someone in Iran who listens to the show.
Please call the voice mail line.
Please, you know, I remember I put up a video.
I'll see if I can find it a video of some teenagers, young people, like 20 year olds, having
a party in Iran.
Guess what?
It looked just like a party in San Francisco in New York or London or Berlin or Amsterdam.
It was a fucking party.
It's like these are like people like you and me.
Yeah, there's something really seriously fucked up with what's happening here.
Oops, I just got on to another TSA list.
Can you hear it?
I can hear the pen scrunching on the paper.
So I apologize.
Our leadership or assholes right now, we're working on that.
We're trying to fix that.
And the meantime, please, if you're in Iran and you listen to the show, give me a shout.
Let me know, okay?
Because I need to hear some humanity here for a second.
I just can't stand this Iran talk.
And it's not like these people are fucking desert bunnies, okay?
It's like sophisticated cell phones.
They got iPods.
Geez, Louise.
All right, tomorrow we'll do a food bar Friday.
And we won't go too deep.
So I'm looking for stuff to talk about gadgets, looking for stuff to talk about chicks, naked
pictures, and hey, if you want to see us, we'll do some political crap.
Adam and podshow.com, dailysourceco.com, I'll see you tomorrow for a food bar Friday.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest, served up daily by the sharpest minds and content delivery.
Podshow in line light.