The Port City PD, the number one online police drama series, is now available.
The pod father had a cameo in the season 1 finale, who will be making cameo appearances
in season 2, you, me, get in on the action, portcity.podshow.com.
This is Bob Locksworth and we're here at the location of the UFO's sighting with Mr.
William Henry.
Mr. Henry was apparently taken into the spaceship and able to capture some audio of the
aliens.
Mr. Henry.
What did you find?
Well, I was abducted, and this is what they said.
Well, I'm glad they didn't see six horns.
It's dazzling, startling indeed, oh my, that is audio from the UFO.
Almost for Hensley.
You said that they proved you, where, where, where did they take you?
Where did they probe you?
Uh, up to butt, up.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Just take hits from the head and carry.
Are you crazy?
I'm calling for my phone.
I'm calling for your phone.
I'm party party party party tonight
Oh, there's no chance in time, but I can't find my food
Oh, now got so desperate that I sent a rocket to them
No, you're serious, I'm upset they saw you standing with me
But you're not a man, I'm not a man, they look like you
All the keeps on you now, this feeling's much too strong
My heart is ringing and I'm singing, it's fine for you
Because of like you, you're like you
And feel it so broken in your eyes
You're like you, you're like you
And feel it
Party party party party tonight
Party party party party
Cell party, I'm party party party
Cell party, I'm party party party tonight
Jesus, thank you for sending this money to me
That's a way to kick off a hum day, a short skirt
No, I'm the seat-o
I'm party, I'm party, I'm party
Party is a daddy
As we heard, the sympathy for the devil
And Danny Warhol's matchup a couple days ago
He said, Adam, you gotta try this one out
I'm pretty sure I've played this, I'll probably back at the cottage
But wow, you're here now
Delta Sierra Charlie
Number 640, everybody, how you doing?
No rain yet, my prediction still kind of holds true
It was beautiful this morning, nice and sunny
As I went into the second of several diva appointments
So that I have with my dental surgeon
Yeah, I'm getting everything rebuilt
One last, I think, you know, I was like, I'm halfway through my life
I hope if I'm lucky
So I might as well fix what I can now
I still have money and still give a shit
So when I die, I'll be nothing but just some beautiful teeth left over
Oh man, hey, it's good to be here with you guys
Thank you for tuning in once again
Yesterday, I feel really great for a number of reasons
We had a guy in the office yesterday in the London office
The UK Crashpad BT Pod Show
His name is Michael Bradford, he's an American living in the United Kingdom
And he works with people's energy
And obviously there's some interest here
We're looking at creating some programming with him
And he said, oh, Adam, do you mind if I just take a look at your energy
And he whipped out this
Some kind of like, divining rod device
It was beautiful actually, he was like beautifully crafted
Kind of very shiny bronze like
And it looked kind of, it had, you know, like, coils on it and stuff
And it looked a bit like a divining rod
He said, okay, well, all right, you only have one leak in your energy
Your crown chakra is blocked at 250 feet
And I said, oh, wow
Maybe that's why I feel so good when I'm flying
Because I'm above the 250 foot mark
And my block chakra is down there
He said, no, no, no, it's still 250 feet above you
I wish, of course, technically means it's illegally in the Heathrow TMA
That was for pilots, okay?
But he cleared me and I've got to tell you
I feel great, I went to the dentist today
And I knew I had to have some novocaine and stuff
It was in the morning, like 10 a.m. appointment
I don't, I'm not, why did I do that?
I was hating myself
But actually, I got in the car and I felt kind of good
And I went in and boom, you know, she started and did everything
And I just feel good, I feel really energized
So there's probably something to it
And that wasn't the only exciting thing yesterday
Yesterday was the full blown first day iPhone test
To see how it performed
I was most worried about the battery performance
Well, let me tell you, by its internal measurement
It actually has an internal clock
That starts ticking the minute it has completely charged
In fact, the minute it's charged, it stops charging
And then the standby time starts to roll
I got almost like seven hours and 50 minutes
Almost eight hours of pure usage time
That was a lot of it was on the phone
A lot of it was spent using the Wi-Fi
Wi-Fi is continuously on, of course, always searching for signals
I used a little bit of the quote edge network
The GPS stuff, I try to stay away from it
Because of the cost, lots of text messaging
And really, it lasted throughout, you know, my day
Is definitely longer than eight hours
But a lot of it is spent on the phone and using the phone
Using the browser at least
And yesterday was a particularly heavy text message
Candyman Luke, man
You know, it's like he knows I'm using the iPhone
And he likes to send, instead of emails
He sends me text messages
But they're so long they come in like five different chunks
And so beyond the phone with someone
Like the iPhones of vibrating against your head
So very pleased with that
The spelling correction, the opt-out spelling correction
Is absolutely killing me
This is, I do not understand why they make it an opt
Yeah, I understand when you're only doing English
But even then, you know, it's like
Who writes the Queen's English these days anymore
And we all use abbreviations and stuff
It's a pain in the ass
That's really dumb
But it did kind of make me realize
There's a lot of falsehoods that were running around
About the iPod, all these so-called experts
And, you know, like, and gadget
And, you know, everyone who was supposed to know exactly
What was going on all the information
And one of the things was, oh, the battery life will suck
Sorry, it doesn't, it's fine
It's certainly comparable to my E61 eye
They said it was either going to be huge
Because they had a male model with big hands
And, you know, it's a great size
And I even heard Steve Gilmore say that, you know, the UI
And how beautiful and selected looked that was bullshit
Because it was done, you know, it was television editing
And when Steve Jobs demoted it had a wire
Coming out of it, of course, it had a wire
And needed some kind of video output
So I'd say everyone was pretty much wrong about it
Now, there are, obviously, some things that I'm not too happy about
Now, I use the mobile version of Google's calendar
But I have gone through the pain
of setting up outlook to sync with my Google calendar
And then that the sync with my iPhone
And actually, that does work pretty well
But it's not handy because, you know, I don't want to take my laptop
Everywhere I go, so I'm not getting the most updated information
My calendar does change regularly
So that's kind of a bummer
But it sounds like some other Charlie heads out there
Have their iPhones and a test in them as well
So let's do a little check-in
Hey, I have a message from Bucket
At Bucketpottest.com
Hey, Jen
I'm calling you from my iPhone
To talk about your iPhone
And I'm wondering if you found what I find
To be the most annoying missing feature on the internet
You know what, Jen?
I think you should drop by one day
And we'll talk about iPhones
Firephones
I found at the end of the day
When someone tried to
I'm going to say text message
A picture to me
It's not SMS, really
It's MMS
Multi-medium messaging
And I got this weird little message
But I had to go to ViewMyMessage.com
And put in a bunch of incomprehensible codes
Which I found to be seriously annoying
Because here I am with what supposed to be the slickest smartphone on the market right now
And I can't get a multi-medium message to my phone
So I mean, I know you can go into email and everything
And you can email pictures
I haven't figured out how to view email attachments yet in like Gmail
But I just, I found that to be a serious lack
So that's my biggest beef with the iPhone so far
Other than that, I'm actually really, really loving it
So if one of those is running into that, let me know
All right, bye
Yeah Jen, actually I think that was predocumented before the phone came out
We knew that it wouldn't do MMS
And I believe that, well that has, it's the very carrier dependent
But the MMS is all fucked up anyway
I know that Patricia tries to send pictures to Christina
And that's incompatible
And it's a mess, it really is
Here's what I do with pictures
I, you can do as you can email a picture
So what I found is it's really easy to set up an email address at flicker
That will accept pictures
In fact, you can even have two email addresses
You can send it to a different email address
And you know, put the subject line in there
You can even add some tags
And you can even create a blog post
And it'll close to right on the blog of your choice
So that's become a pretty simple operation
Whereas like I take a picture
And then I hit the action button
And I can email it
I email it into flicker and I forget about it
What is disappointing is that you can set it up to sync with a folder
Your pictures and that is a way to get pictures onto your phone
So I synced it with my pictures in my windows set up here
And if I drop a picture into my pictures
It syncs to the iPhone
But pictures that are on the iPhone don't sync back to my pictures
That I find weird
That just makes no sense
So literally the only way you can now get your pictures off
Is by emailing it out
It just doesn't sit right with me
But you know, at the end of the day
It's really the phone, the text messaging
And the browsing that I need
Hello Adam, this is Dr. San Diego
I hear you got your iPhone
Congratulations
I don't know if you've heard yet or not
But there's apparently a security leak
So when you are surfing on Wi-Fi
Hackers have been able to hack
Into the iPhone
And the phone and execute commands
Still your context
Or spam your context
Yes, why?
I
Yaman
Yeah, a lot of people told me about that yesterday
Hey man, it's not secure
Like what the fuck
So I think what has to happen
Is first that have to log into a particular access point
That is set up for this hack
Then it have to go to a particular webpage
So there's a lot of getting me to do things
And I think I've heard of this hack
With the Macbook Pro is before
And yeah, sure, whatever
So I have nothing of interest
Really, I don't
And then people in my contact
Well, it would be kind of interesting
I have a pretty good address book
I say I must say
And I have painfully
Painfully
Excuse me, hon, I'm in the middle of the show
Yes?
What?
Hold on a second
Come up here
What are you talking about?
I'm in the middle of the show
You have no fucking manners
What?
Come up here
What is the pill that you gave to?
That's the ibuprofen
I've never seen it like this
Hold on a second
I'll show you exactly
What does that say?
And that's what was in it?
That's what was in it, yes
It's ibuprofen
Oh, I've never seen it with little poles in it
No, could you?
No, tiny poles
What do you say?
I apologize
My goodness
Pardon me
And you know what I was talking about anymore
You have no respect
I get no respect
You don't listen to the show
You just break into the show
You're seeing it just came up to you here
No, I went downstairs and gave that to her
Oh, okay
Myself, personally
As you told me to do
Yeah
Well
Hello this nurse
Good morning
And you know what I was saying anymore
Ah
Yeah, yeah, goodbye
Rooting my show
Hey Adam Liam from London here
The iPod winner
I'm at work
So I couldn't phone in the comment
But I figured I'd email it instead
Throughout the promotion
I won exactly
Check this out
This is our Coca-Cola promotion
90 free iTunes songs
Mainly by getting everyone at work to collect their codes for me
Plus
I won the iPod
And 10 free songs to go with that
So
For me
100 DRM free songs
Is 100 pounds
200 bucks
Plus 230 pounds
Which is about 500 bucks
For a new 80 gigabyte iPod
I got about
$665 worth out of this promotion
Also the prize draw
Stop tomorrow night
That's Thursday
So remind everyone
To enter all their codes today
Or tomorrow
At Liam cool
I told you
People really do win
That shit really does work
You just got to pay a little bit of attention to it
Yeah
I'm out of it
I probably had some awesome thread going
That I've not completely forgotten
When I listen back to the show
I'll say oh shit
That's where Patricia came in
Let's do something different
Damn
It's anti-B
I just wanted to share the good news with you
I just heard
That the chill cast
The anti-B
Is nominated
For
Best produce
Podsafe Music podcast
For the People's Choice podcast
I'm totally stoked
I guess the voting opens
On the 28th
So we'll see how it goes
Wish me luck
Oh yeah
Also
You've been talking so much about your channels lately
I noticed that you have not yet added
The anti-Bvid cast
You should do it dude
And tell me how it looks on the iPhone
Alright
Hope to talk to you soon
Bye, baby
Oh baby
Congratulations
I can't
I'm thinking of coming to PMA
PME this year
If only to just hug Angie
Ah
Pacifico's Hellway
Also nominated for an award in the comedy category
Congratulations
Mark
George Martin M. Cough
I never get nominated anymore
That's why I hate awards
Cause I never win any
Never get fucking nominated
Something wrong with that
Yeah, maybe just people aid me
Adam
Allison here from Craftcast
Okay, okay, I take that back
Not everyone hates me
Hey, just want you to know
I'm listening
Listen in every day I'm out here
You are wonderful
Bedside Companion
As I was recovering from a little
Sheldir Surgery
So thank you
Very much
Learned a lot
Had some time to play and look at channels
And learn all that
All VDBD exciting
I also put into the email here a link to yesterday's article
In the Times and the Technology section
All about how to figure out
How advertisers are going to
Spend their money
How to figure out what to charge
And what software is in place for all that, et cetera, et cetera
Anyway, it's all very exciting when you see that
For me
Who's very interested in this
New media
Content
Arena
To see all that happening on the front page of the times
Business section
So and what else?
So I have a technical question
How do I get
My ad
In front of my show
So that no matter what show you click on any of the archives
That ad runs through
Where is that place?
Help girl out here
Who's trying to learn everything from bullshit?
I'm not trying to understand what you're saying there
What are you asking for?
Hold on, listen again
My ad
In front of my show
So that no matter what show you click on any of the archives
That ad runs through
Where is that place?
Help girl out here
Who's trying to learn everything
So you want your ad
Give me like a promo for your show
Or an ad that just goes
You have to explain now
I'm sorry
It's not quite sure what you mean
If you want control over what goes in front of your show
That is something that we plan on surfacing
I think that's what you mean
But I'm not sure
I'm both in boards and reading and you my darling
Anyway
Just wanted you to know
I'm out here listening
And
At least someone is
I was well
And that
Oh, the iPhone
Yes, love it
I'm jealous
I have to tell you something funny though
Eric, my son got one
So we're doing our normal video
I chats
And he wants to show me the phone
So he brings it up
To the computer to show me on I chats
And of course it causes major
Electronic mayhem
And everything crashes
So
Anyway, I thought that was pretty funny
The
The iPhone is not user-friendly
Right next to the
laptop
So
Anyway, hi
Big hugs
And I always look forward to hearing you
Bye, honey
Alright, how's it?
Thank you
Yeah, I've heard some other interesting things about the iPhone
If you put it into
If you put it into like a
What was I hearing?
Was that on Twitter maybe that I heard
Someone say they had an alarm clock
With an iPhone
Adapter on top
Or an iPod Adapter
Of course the iPhone fits in it
But then the iPhone has so much RF frequency
Going on with its
Yeah, with its telephone
Built in
It turns on the alarm
That's editing
And all hours of the night
Ah yes
Shit does happen
I'm exact the most man
And I'm on episode 75
Of the Rock and Roll
Keep Indicast
Check it out
Because you do an interview show
I'm thinking like a parody of your interview show
Like you said you do like
Confrontational interviews
I am Adam Curry and I'm on your show
Let's hear it
I have with me from the popular
Show of the Daily source code
And also co-founder of pod show
Adam Curry
Welcome to the show
Oh thanks
Come on
Yes, but you got to get some
What do you think started?
Do you do drugs?
Yeah, you go
You know I do that's part of my
That's one of the things me
And Patricia do best
Yes
That's it
Um
Okay, good bye
And I'm right
No
Nice
No, that's no
That's exactly how the interview should go
You should call
You should ask him one question
And say okay bye
That would floor him
He's never been done before
That would be a brilliant interview
Zach
It's okay
Bye
That would be a brilliant interview
Do you do drugs?
Okay, bye
That would destroy his ego
Man
This hair would fall out
Dude, that's the worst
Oh, that's brilliant
Brilliant
That's episode 75
If the rock and roll geek in the cast
Check it out at rock and roll geek.org
Michael
That's your broodus
I was that saying my hair would fall out
It's usually bald guys
Hello Adam here's Martin Judy from Judy's by size bonus
You've been talking a lot of news show about her deception on TV and radio and things in the past
And you asked us to confess our lot
Well, I do have a confession to make
Way back in the early 80s I worked on a regional radio station in the north west of England
And every somewhere we used to do the roadshow
We're used to go out and meet and greet the people
Different events throughout the north west
Knowing them days as you're well know we didn't tell things like
Sats like connections to the studio
Just far too expensive for a small station to afford
So what we used to do is we used to park the shumabiel
Near a telegraph pole
You know one of those telephones
And then an engineer used to come on from telephone company
And basically hook up our broadcaster equipment to the telephone line
It then dial out to the studio
And stay connected all the time that we were on the shumabiel
To the studio so we have a live connection if you if you will
So during the show time on the shumabiel
Which lasted for about three hours
I used to do five or six talk bags to the studio
Reports on what was going on the show
Advertising everything obviously you know trying to get people down there
Which are on quizzes and competitions with the crowd that was there
And this artwork's really well, okay
Once the twice we did plant the winners of the competition
And actually part of the production crew
If we can't find anything suitable really to go on the air
But it was always done live
And directly to the studio
So we used to have to mind our peace and cues
No swearing and things like this
But one particular show
We sat at the largest show we did in the summer
We was up to show ground called the Saint Helens Show
This is a big big show
In the north-west of England
Out Saint Helens like the name suggests it
And probably it's a couple of million people pass through the show ground
Over the two days of sits on
So we then were our show reveal
All set up and it's about seven o'clock in the morning
When we suddenly realised
That there's no telegraph pole by the show reveal
We've been given the wrong plot
Some sort of mad panic
We can't move anything
Because everyone else stands for all sets up now
We've got this 60 foot
Our show reveal is stuck with no tractor unit to move it anywhere
So we're stuck there
That we know way of communicating with the studio
One of the senior producers who was on the show reveal
suggested that I pre-record everything
My interviews were the crowd
And things like that
Using one of the journalists
Handheld real-to-reel reporting machines
I don't know if you remember these things
Used to sit at sort of they used to be strung across the show
Oh yeah
And now you're at real-to-reel
I remember my phone
So that's basically what I did
So as the show was going
I was walking out of the back of the show
And we were grabbing people there
And we called in the pieces
The tape was then given to all the sectors
Who ran down to the main gate of the show ground
Which is probably about half a mile from where we were
Jumped in a taxi
Took that back to the radio station
Where they played it as life
It worked fantastic
There had never been any of the difference
All the interviews were done
All the competitions were run at the show ground
Taking back to the studio by taxi and played as life
While you're well imagine
It was great to get that over and done with them
But
The guy that helped us purse strings at the studio
He suddenly said
Must have cost us a small farting for all these taxis
Back was in forwards
But when he actually worked out when it cost
It was cheaper than in that way
Then it was used in the telephone lines
So of course
From there on in
Every time we did a live show
From the show reveal
This was the method we used
Every time anyone heard anything
Live from the show reveal on the radio
It actually had been pre-recorded
Pulling an hour before
Taxed back to the radio station
And played there
That's my confession
Just a bit of kid oldie
And let's not fool ourselves though Adam
Podcasts
We're no completely innocent
We all tried to fool the public
One way or another
We and I have one major confession
If only switch the effects button on my mixer off
You'll see that I'm actually a woman
Like this
If you tell me exactly I'll get out my toy
Your voice is so sexy
I get wet when I hear you die
This has been GD confessing all
On Adam Kelly's daily source code
Catch me five days a week
From Monday through to Friday
And by sizeburners.potgeo.com
See Adam
You make me so juicy
I'm going to slide right off the chair
GD
Out of control man
Yeah
That's a great example
And oh man
Has the word live been overused
And incorrectly and used in deception
Really
And the thing is because it's not such a big deal
And you know it seems like kind of a harmless little thing
And it doesn't really make any difference to people
You know that builds upon builds upon things and things
And then you get to the level of where it doesn't really matter
If people enter the competition
But no had to had absolutely no chance of winning
Does it?
You know it's like an MTV
We do spring break
Or any location shooter
MTV
But spring break is such an excellent example
You can literally watch it happen
It seems like everyone's all party and excited
And all ready to go
But all that shit's all set up
So here's an example
I'm at the pool
I have you know I've got to introduce a video
And so there's everyone's behind me
And the producers yelling at everyone
Okay get ready for the big belly flop
And so got some guys supposed to be
You know the huge belly supposed to do a belly flop
And they'll count us in
And five, four, three, two
And then I start my
You know I start my rap and then
And then everyone goes
Woo!
And they're all excited
And the producers waving off camera going
Yeah!
And it's all being excited
We're crazy it's spring break
You know it's not that it wasn't crazy
But it just wasn't that crazy
So yeah
Trickery
Trickery my friends
Anyway
From the moment you started the daily source code today
You probably could already smell the cheese
Because it is time
My friends
Cheddar by the time
You hear the show should be out
And available
It's releasing this morning
We had a couple of delay
Well actually
Why am I even giving you the update
But I'm bumming other day
At the office
But I'm bumming just saying hello
But I'm bumming
To the game from HQ
And pod shot
Hey Adam
It's Andrew here
And joining me is Paulina Lue
Hello
And
Paulina Lue
Give all of your listeners an update
On what is happening with Cheddar
I'm sure they are eagerly waiting
It's
This is Andrew Gromad
And Paulina
Why do I think I have a met Paulina
Hmm
Sounds hot
Here it's on our
www.podshow.com
And we had
The best of intentions of getting
It live this afternoon
And
We're running a little bit late
We've had some very interesting issues
With the power
This has to do with
Which you all may have read about
I think the rumor is that
Some drunk employee went nuts
And kept unplugging
And replugging the
Powerswitch
Which isn't Paulina man
There's talent in the engineering department
I don't know about
It sounds better than those
Those witches over at scene
That's for sure
Nice Paulina
Welcome
For Cisco
Yeah
It's a great image
It's kind of an interesting
Each time the power went
Ah, you would hear these grow
And from the office
And it would be back on again
And off for five minutes
But we cannot fully blame
The fine city of San Francisco
We encountered a number of bugs
You know, not major deep issues with the system
But small things
Inevitable
Bugs that
Come up when you merge code
Between several different developers
And also lots of little finesse
As you saw
We lovely
White on orange
XML buttons
That appeared
So late in the game
Thanks to Paulina
So
So we also spent a good chunk of the day
When we did have power
Squashing out those last bugs
So the current status
Which I'm sure you've all been waiting for
As of today
We're just looking over the issues
There are a couple of
Essentially
Display level
Styling issues
That we're trying to get really finesse
And working across all the browsers
And the nice consistent way
But we are hoping
I just sent out an email
Which you probably saw at
Identifying the last couple of nagging issues
Pitching that we have our
Go-no-go meeting
That is just kind of a final say
On the status and stability of the build
And once we have that meeting
I think should slow up
So we're open for some time tomorrow morning
And I would just ask everyone
To keep their eyes on the site
And we're getting it up
As quickly as we can
Anything to add to that, Paulina
Nope
We're just trying to work out
All of the
There's always
There's always some problems between
The IE and the PC and FireFox
And that's kind of what we're running
That's kind of what we're running
IE
And it's always just like that
I've actually threatened
To people complain too much about the style
Issues and IE have actually threatened to
Make them work on a five year old
10 pound
Windows laptop
I've done it
And you're never going to make me do that again
You'll pry this pretty little neck out of my cold dead fingers
Okay
So don't even try
That update from HQ
We're like I said, we're going to push forward
And try and get this thing out
And a nice clean polished way
For everybody to get their hot little hands on
Sometimes tomorrow that would be
Wednesday
July 25th
Day to mark in history
So
Is that day to get their food
That's right
What was it?
What were we saying?
The cheddar was flowing like
Moulton lava
That's right
It makes your pot experience flow
Your pot experience
Oh
All right guys.
Signing off then
I will be listening to the show
And eager to hear everyone's feedback
Thanks
Thank you
Andrew Paulina
Two hot geeks high on cheddar
You know the you guys got to show there
Andrew you your your your
Your modulations a little low
Paulina you've got a fantastic voice
And you guys could talk geek
Paulina you could talk geeky stuff in my year all day long
But I'm bummer the day at the office
But I'm bummer just say hello
But I'm bummer to the game from HQ
But I'm bummer and pod show
Yeah, you thought that's always get from pod show
No, no, no, no because apparently
And this is pretty interesting
These guys I guess signed off on
On on the engineering and then it goes to something called
QA the QA department quality assurance
I presume
Headed up by shriek hunt now shriek
You got to kind of reset your ears because shriek hunt
Speak with an accent
But I love this
I love what he sent in
It's awesome shriek hunt you're up man
Hello Adam this is shriek hunt
QA got a pod show
Today we need Andrew mention that you want audio comments
For chatter from engineering
And Andrew chose me to do that
Which I think was a very long choice
Because you cannot get QA guy to talk good about anything
But I will try to
So this new feature we call it channel editor
Also term as pre-dater or chatter
Is a really cool feature
This feature enhances user experience
For channel creation and manipulation
That's it right there
It increases user experience for channel creation and manipulation
Spoken like a true QA god
A new channel will enable users to create new channel
Mentor items in the channel
Rear the items in the channel with ease and in a very user-friendly manner
User can just drag and drop the items from the collection
Out to 24 items into the channel
And they will get the instant channel
User can also define the depth of the playback
For episodic shows in the channel
The user can decide whether they want to play only
Let us episode or last two episode or last three episode
Or they can even decide to skip the show
From the channel without playing any episode
Nice
Okay, so that was a speech
Now I'm going to put my cue hat
And
Now comes the QA hat
Now he's going to tell us all the shit that doesn't work right with
Cheddar because I'm crude behind the lies
So this feature is not yet fully cooked
And still need few enhancements
First of all, we can handle only up to 24 items in the channel
Which means if user create a new channel
They can have only up to 24 items in the channel
Okay, let me just make sure I got this
So I have seen this
So when you're creating a new channel
You can put up to 24 items
That could be 24 shows
So I think it's going to be sufficient just for us to get started with
No idea why the limit
Certainly no idea why the limit is 24
But it doesn't matter
That's what tree contest for it
Point to point that out
Thank you
QA god
Well then that
Second
To the order of the item
In the old channel
Which are not edited using this new feature
And if the user tries to play the channel
From edit my channel GUI
Then the playback order of the items in the channel
We'll not be the same as it appears in the GUI
Okay, I got it
So if you already have channels in Pod Show
Their behaviour will not be affected by this cheddar release
I presume not until you've actually edited the channel
And to work around this issue
What user has to do is
Then it to open the old channel
Using new edit my channel GUI
Either we order or add new item to the channel
Which will force the channel to say
And then the items in your old channel
We'll also play in collect order
Right
So over the other two
So basically all you have to do
If you want to convert your old channels to new
Cheterize the channels with molten cheddar cheese
Then you have to go in and edit your channel
And presumably maybe just change an order or something
Or click on a depth setting
Or just do one little change it will save automatically
And of course then all your channels will have the default
Depsetting of one
All the shows in the channel
I think
Channel
We'll also play in collect order
So overall this feature is great
And thanks to Andrew and his team for putting this together
And also I would like to thank my Q8 team members
For doing such a great job
Thanks
No, thank you guys
It should be savanche recont
That's it
Because you guys truly are savants
I can't wait
You guys will be having your weedies
And I'll be sitting here waiting for the cheddar to come out
So it's happening today
I think we'll have plenty of time to be playing with that tonight
And talking about it tomorrow
Hey Adam
I'm the guy who called in today's go about the channels
And I just heard your reply
And whatever, my name is Steve
I don't have a really awesome handle
I don't know
Anyway
Yeah you do your savanche Steve of course
The action is I've got a stop calling in when I'm fascinated
I sound like a smack touch
Maybe you like that
You know my problem is that I'm still using juice
Maybe I'm just my issue
As I got to go back over to iTunes and use that as the pod catcher
I had a bad experience when they first released the pod
Podcast catching feature
I think it blew away but you might
I don't know
You did something bad
Stop using it
Went back to juice works
But it sounds to me like
That's my issue
Well of course
That seems to show that I
A couple days ago when I actually left the message
I kept listening to the show and you actually were talking about
The iPhone or the listening live and I suddenly realized
Well
Yeah that's it
It's just
Kering things around in a hard disk
Come on I pod
I think a lot of sense
If you could connect it to that full time
Then the roots of the whole issue
Yeah eventually
That's really the future here
That we're getting toward
Anyway
Later
Yeah I think we definitely will get there
Always on always connected
Wirelessly all the time
So you'll know that cheddar has been released
If you go to atom.podshow.com
You'll see my channel module right there
Front and Center in the page
And if it has a little
New drop down box that says
Choose player
And from that you can choose multiple players
There's also a put it on my iPod option
And you'll actually see a little
White and orange RSS button
That'll work for juice
Just copy that link right into juice
And your channel will work in juice
No problem whatsoever
Satisfaction guaranteed
If you and you can do that without a pod show account
If you do have a pod show.com account
Then you'll be able to go to your profile
Click on edit channels on your edit
On your channel module
Or in the master control
And you'll be able to edit your channels
Create new ones
And I would say let the fun begin
Out of a steal again
I just had an idea
And I'm wondering if you guys have thought about this
It's a long commute
I just sit here and think
Um
Do you plan to make it so that
You inspire
Importing somebody else's channel
Or going, hey, I like that channel
I want to subscribe to it
What if you made a template
Somebody else's channel
Used it as a starting point
Somebody getting into this
Might
Take a look at a channel
Take those shows
Look appealing or I heard this one already
If this is the rest, look at your single
I'd like to try that one
And then later me want to customize it
Is there?
I didn't hear it
I'd not heard you talk about that
To me that scene is like
A pretty likely way
Somebody might use it
So just to find
Yeah, Steve, you know
Brilliant minds think alike
I can't say that I'm one of the brilliant
Minds in this case
That will be a part of the get channel
Functionality
Which a lot of it is already working
But we're going to hold off on that
And first we're going to just
Get through editing and creating new channels
Seeing how that works
You know I have no idea how it's going to work for everybody across the board
So let's take it in little incremental steps
What will release right after that
Or maybe two weeks from now
Depends on when we feel it's right
Is the ability to get a channel
So you can subscribe to someone's channel
And you'll be able to do three things with it
One is you'll say just
Get this channel
And put it into my collection
So you can drag it into another channel
Set a depth and treat it just like a show
That'll be one way
There's another way
We can say get this channel
But don't get the channel
Please just explode the contents of that channel
Into my collection
So I'm subscribed to them
And I can put them into other channels
Individually
And the third which is what you're talking about
Is
Subscribe to this channel
So it will actually show up
As a template
In your channels
With the name and everything that
Was the original template of that channel
It's in fact exactly what you're talking about
Steve
I have a couple of questions about that
Because I'd like to have two versions of it
Both versions need to have attribution towards the
To the creator
Whoever created the channel
I mean you want to be able to find that person
That should be trackable
And the other one is
I'd like to be able
To subscribe to that channel as it is
Have it in my channel module
But have someone else
You know the originator be controlling it
So I don't have a copy of it
A template or a clone
It's really just like an alias or symbolic link
That is just sitting there
And that will change
Even if someone takes it
If the creator takes a show out
That will be reflected in my version of the channel
So that's all coming
That's all part of the get channel functionality
Baby steps my friends
Let's just start off with the big steps first
All right
40 minutes
On the long side today
But had a lot to go through
I got a wonderful
iTunes gift certificate today
In the email
From Brian Know
50% of the production guys
He MPed up
Are the production guys Adam
And here comes a quote
I get the news I need on the weather report
A song about a pilot
For the next time you're an NYC
From the society
For the preservation of the soundtrack
To our lives
Thanks man, I appreciate the present
It's a play that I'm done
But I know you're part of the more fun
For the next time you're an NYC
You don't want me, you don't want me
Have for the time to know, we don't know, we don't know where
You don't want me, you don't want me, you don't want me
Hey, you don't want me, you don't want me, you don't want me
You don't want me, you don't want me
It's pretty much the first album, the bridge over troubled water album that I
I wished for better technology
The pressing of that record was so poor, it was so thin, it got scratches and crackles after like 10 plays
Ah, presented to you under the fair use act by the organization for the preservation of the soundtrack
of our lives Simon and Garfunkel and the only living boy in New York
Alright everybody, enjoy your chatter, we'll talk tomorrow on another episode of The Daily
Source Code, DailySourceCode.com, adamantpotcho.com, bye bye
The best and the brightest, sub.daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering pot show and limelight