He had him, it's an issue for him.
One time they'll talk.
Niscuit them girls' body last time.
It was a blast.
What's the people going to be coming to see me from that one?
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Till we are the SC660.
Not to be presumptuous.
Or I was kind of expecting you to be reaching out to me.
To be a son on about six years.
I mean they'd do call my number right.
Just let me know when you want to get together for that.
And while you're in the state, I think it's down there away.
But we know we can do lunch.
There is this flame glow bugger doing this to die for.
Take care of Adam.
Have fun and episode 660 of the Charlie.
And I'll talk to you soon.
Ah, ah, ah.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I was lying in the kitchen.
Fantastic.
It's a matter of courage.
To talk to a baby, go to rehab.
I said no, no, no.
Yes, I've even played for when I come back.
No, no, no.
I can't got the time.
And if my daddy thinks I'll fly.
It's not a lady going to rehab.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
You know that love you.
You know that love your love.
You know that love love.
You know that love.
You know that love dear Matt wake up and let me play the peer.
So why don't you take me home,
Didn't get all out of your class
But I know we don't come
In a sharp glass
It's all of me going
I'm sitting in no, no, no
There's something right
We are perfect
No, no, no
I need a time
And if my daddy thinks I'm fine
Should I don't believe I love you?
I love you
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Just the power
Should I make it a match to me?
Yeah, I'm myself
I'm a fool, I'm a fool
No, no, no, no, no, no
There's something right there
I'm not a time
But I know we don't come
We're going to call you name
Girl, it's just a fight
I'm a fool
Tited, I'm a fool
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no
I'm being go through the mirror
I say no, no, no
Yes, I've been back, we are gone back, you know, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, and so on.
And somebody that got a pretty sudden middle for something, comes from my autobiography.
And somebody that had met him or something, this guy knows how to mash it up, doesn't it?
Why me?
projet.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Four top smashed up by Party Ben there with Amy Winehouse.
By the way, it's got to be a prime example of the spectacle of the society.
Would somebody please help that girl and stop just writing trash about her,
do something, pull her out of the shit that she's in?
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
It is a daily source code episode number, what is it?
60.
Oh, man.
Yeah, Lucifer.
We are going to close it in on you.
Right now it is 4.
48 AM on Thursday.
Today is September 6th, 2007.
Why?
So early.
Well, I woke up.
I woke up at about 4 AM.
I just came out of a dead sleep.
Actually, the glands in my throat hurt a little bit.
I'm not quite sure why.
Particularly on the left side, so maybe, yeah, if I tilt my head a little bit,
maybe, just hurt a bit and it woke me up.
But also, it's not been a very standard trip for me.
It's been an emotional roller coaster.
Of course, with the passing of our dear, dear pussycat Cindy.
Yesterday, you know, fox with you, what can I tell you?
Oh, I have to thank everybody.
So incredibly much.
You know, I said, if you want to send an email about, about Cindy, about a pussycat,
please send it to Patricia.
Hundreds of emails came in.
And I got to tell you, this was so incredibly helpful because, you know,
Patricia's family lives in the Netherlands.
So they're not next door.
They're very close or sister and parents.
I'm not there.
Christina has to go off to a two day I love white trip with her new school, kind of,
like a get-to-know-you type of trip, I guess.
So, you know, she's really lonely.
And she said, and I know my wife pretty well.
We've been married for 21 years.
But she was forwarding me several of these emails.
And she actually sent me a text message and said,
please, please, would you thank everybody who sent something in.
I have one who's listening to the show.
She said, it really, really helps.
In particular, you know, I was thinking, originally when I saved this for the show,
I was thinking of reading this, this email that Brian sent.
Brian from audioaditude.com.
I can't do it though because I know I won't get through it.
But what I found is that people would send in their own personal experiences,
sharing the grief because they understand it at a very deep emotional level.
And it's beautiful.
This is the kind of stuff that Tony Khan.
You remember Tony?
I'm sure he's still doing WGBH's morning stories.
I honestly have not listened in a long, long time.
And I haven't spoken to Tony in a long, long time.
But this is the kind of stuff that really turned him on.
And I gotta tell you, it makes me feel awesome.
Awesome to know that even though the word friend is used so easily these days,
particularly in social networks, you know, be my friend.
I befriended you.
Some of you guys really are friends.
In fact, probably all of you, even if you haven't called it,
I know you're on our side.
And again, thank you so much.
I really, really appreciate it.
And of course, I got tons of phone calls.
Hi Adam, this is Nora.
One of your Italian friends.
I'm so sorry to hear about to your loss.
I feel for you.
Just like, it took the wind out of you.
I would took the wind out of me.
I know a much of feel.
So you lose a pet or perhaps a family member.
I do feel having the same position.
My pet is health and strong, but like,
it's lost half in the past, and I know how much I feel.
So I'm sorry to happen.
You have all my sympathy and I'll make sure I'll send an email to Patricia.
Bye.
I know.
Luckily, it's time for me to let continue.
Yeah, indeed.
Here's the more.
Yeah, okay.
Indeed, life continues.
That's for sure.
And there were just scores and scores of similar voicemails.
Very, very touching.
And we really appreciate it.
I think the girls buried Cindy had a nice ceremony.
And now we move on, but it takes time.
And I recognize these feelings.
It wasn't too long.
I lost my mom.
Now, I don't want to compare the two necessarily.
But it's the same like just ripping your gut out type of feeling.
And there's other friends.
John C. Dvorak, who I did cranky geeks with yesterday.
And I had a lot of fun doing the show, by the way.
I think he kind of felt that I, you know,
Look, it's obvious, you know, even though I'm up and I'm positive,
and I'm very excited about what's going on in the company.
We got some great shit going on.
Absolutely great shit.
Now, you can tell, of course it affects me a little bit.
And so what he did is he took me out to dinner last night.
But when you do that with John C. Dvorak, that's kind of an experience all to all unto itself.
And we wound up going to this place called Flair Deli in San Francisco.
They also have a restaurant in Vegas at Mandela Bay.
And they've got some other burger thing going on.
But this is like high, high, high class top quality cuisine and wine.
And man, you guys know, I'm a smoker, not a drinker.
And I did not, I did not know that I could drink so much wine and then,
wait, well, first it was a, what did we have?
A Pino, Pino, Grigio, maybe?
I don't know. It went from white.
It went to red.
It went to Medira.
There was an apple teeny somewhere in the middle.
But, you know, like really top-notch French cuisine,
you know, and really all of the Somalier, you know, and John,
that knows a lot about wine.
And I was just sitting there.
I just, I should have recorded that.
It was just like, listen to these guys bullshit each other.
But they really know what they're talking about.
And I'm just drinking it.
And I had, well, like popcorn with truffle on it.
It was like an explosion of the palate.
And it was good.
So we just shot the bowl, basically.
And I had some awesome food and awesome drink.
And I came back last night at, you know, as I was in at 10.
And I just went straight to bed.
And maybe that's part of why I woke up, you know,
all these foreign substances coursing through my veins.
So yesterday, of course, was the special apple announcement.
And, well, I'm very happy, I should say.
Adam Richman, let's go here.
You're Wisconsin pilot.
Call of from Dawn Andrews.
Well, near back yard.
Hey, it's September fifth.
And I was just listening to 658.
And let me tell you, you called it.
Apple just announced a day that they're coming out with an iPod with a touch screen
and Wi-Fi access.
Congratulations.
You had it nailed.
And, oh, by the way, they are dropping the prices of their eight gig.
I phoned down $200.
Does it get me out to buy one?
Not really, because I don't have that kind of disposable income.
Your handle on the industry is just impeccable.
So, I hope your travels are going well.
And you're having a good time in San Francisco.
This is Richmond, Wisco, your Wisconsin pilot tailwinds.
Hold it.
Tailwinds indeed, my friend.
Yeah, not only that, but it has the Safari browser.
It's kind of, it's, and to say that I called it or predicted it is going too far.
This was a wish list.
I'm like, please give me this.
Thank you.
Yeah, I love it.
The details are still a little bit sketchy about what the device can do.
But this is the hacker's dream as far as I'm concerned.
This is a true web tablet.
I'm very excited.
And I'm not going to buy an iPhone.
No, no, no.
I'm going to wait until this iPod touch comes out.
I don't give a rat's ass about the iPod.
I want the Wi-Fi and the Safari browser.
Because it has the fantastic quick time integration.
All of those MP4 videos.
All of them will play.
They'll play live right off the net.
Our pod show channels look awesome and function perfectly in the Safari browser on the iPod touch.
This is, this is, really is.
It's a dream for me.
I wonder, since, you know, it pretty much is what I ask for is the iPhone without the phone.
So it looks like, you know, most of the stuff is in there.
I wonder if if they actually do not include the Bluetooth transceiver or if they would possibly
consider putting a proper, you know, Bluetooth transceiver that adheres to all the protocols in there.
Because I wouldn't mind having my little iPod touch.
Excuse me.
That could talk to my cell phone regardless of what it is.
There's a lot of capabilities in Bluetooth.
You know, it could, it could manage my, my SIM card by remote.
You know, it can, it can handle the audio back and forth.
I mean, it could be, in essence, I could just get a cheap-ass phone to slip into my pocket
with a Bluetooth or maybe even into my bag.
And, and it would just communicate with the, with the iPod touch.
Doesn't matter.
There'll be tons of hacks and applications coming out.
I think it's the right direction to go for Apple.
I'm very, very happy.
A little bummed out that I, you know, I was expecting the,
and it's for sale right now.
Unfortunately, that wasn't the case.
But wow, loving it, absolutely loving it.
And for those of you that, that call in on the, on, on the voice mail lines.
I, you know, just because your comment doesn't make it on the air.
It doesn't mean that I didn't hear it.
I listened to every single one.
But of course, if I actually put them all in the air,
that would be a show by itself.
You know, maybe there's a consideration here that I should just have a feedback channel.
That just runs.
Hmm.
That would be something interesting to put together.
Feedback channel.
Okay.
And we'll mark that one down.
But, you know, once in a while, I get something,
even though it's a belated happy birthday at this point.
It was just so nice.
I, I just got to share it with you.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you.
Hello Adam.
It's me again, Terry.
Or in Little Ren.
I wanted to take a moment and wish you a slightly belated happy birthday.
Last year, you did something very special for me on my birthday.
A mere three weeks after your own.
You played a song by Amy Ayers at the request of my boyfriend.
That was very sweet and it meant the world to me.
For the last two years, you have enriched my life
by simply continuing to advance your endeavors in New Media.
I have become engrossed in this new medium.
And I love it very much.
I now have two shows over on Podshow.
And as you know, I'm working on my novel ASB for Podshow Press.
You inspire so many people to do something different.
And yet for me, you inspire a desire to do what I love.
Every day.
Since the 80s, you have had an impact on my life in some form or another.
And for this, I sent you a heartfelt happy birthday.
And another sentiment from your listeners,
regarding your passing moment of weakness.
I personally look forward to the DSC whenever you put it out.
And the soundtrack to my life has become very pleasant.
Thanks to you bringing it to the forefront of my heart.
Now, I'm not going to plug my shows.
Just know that I proudly present them over at lrwh.podshow.com.
Although I'm still constructing it, it is wonderful to have everything in one place.
Thank you for all that you do.
And as your birthday is rolled one into the other.
Take heart in the happiness that you really do bestow unto others.
It has been a pleasure.
And by the way, the naked pictures from last year might be a bit outdated.
So new ones are yours if you want them.
And yes, FYI, I am a fold.
Happy birthday Adam from Little Reds writing hood.
Thank you.
Of course me, Terry.
Yeah.
Send them on.
Please, out of mypodshow.com.
You know, that's a very nice birthday present.
Whenever someone says you had an impact on my life,
holy crap, I think if someone said to me what is at the end at the end of this ride,
what do you want to be able to say?
I mean, it will definitely be that.
That I had an impact somewhere on someone's life.
So I guess I'm good to go now.
Well, that, of course, and, you know, I love the fact that, you know,
I can't even say it.
I'm not going to go there.
Hi, hi, hi, hi, hi.
Hey, yeah, also a happy birthday to Natalie Dalcante.
She was her birthday just before mine.
Actually, just after Christina's just before mine.
I'm having dinner with her tonight.
That'll be fun.
And I'm just getting re-acquainted with everybody.
It's been almost three months.
It's been out here in, uh, in no Cal.
That's a curry condo.
And there's also a ton of new people who I haven't met and, uh,
I'm getting to know them.
Gosh, I, I got to tell you,
when you see the new version of podshow.com and what it will do for you as an audience member,
in particular.
I mean, it's just imagine iTunes for the internet.
That's all I can really say because it's just no other way to explain it.
But what, what a great product.
I mean, it's something that, you know,
I'm really going to use.
It's kind of like, um, you know, when I was looking for the right set,
uh, to essentially have a, uh, a radio station studio in your laptop.
And I worked for months with the cast blaster mic on creating cast blaster,
which, of course, I still use to this day and recording the show on right now.
Um, it's, it's very similar in field to what podshow.com is going to be.
And, uh, it's, it's, it's so vastly different from what we have now.
And there's nothing else like it out there.
That, that I know for sure. There's no thinking going on like this.
Um, it's so vastly different.
I think we're actually have to bring up a separate site, uh,
port everyone's data over and then maybe even, uh, work with,
you know, small groups initially because it's just, it's so different.
And, uh, it's, it's, it's different.
Yeah, I think you've got to like it.
So, uh, let's see, uh, you know, we're still working on, uh,
the Lost Elvis Diaries, which, uh, it's going to be a couple months,
yet until, uh, until the production is done.
And when we actually start rolling out the episodes,
this is, uh, you know, uh, the Elvis's life in, uh, in diary form.
And, uh, I told you that for the production,
I was looking for a younger sounding Elvis.
And, uh, so far only one submission.
I thought we would do a little better than that.
Uh, how long was the curve?
Uh, what is he was looking for?
A younger Elvis will, I think, in the mind, um,
Mr. Kerr, uh, I believe that I've got what it takes and,
and well, I just, I just do, you know,
with my mom and I, she really didn't see what had been meaning.
I mean, I, I miss her a lot.
So, Mr. Kerr, if, if I'm your man, uh, at the end of this,
I'll give you a phone number to call.
I don't know. I don't know if this is the guy.
Maybe you can do a better, uh, younger Elvis.
We're looking. We're casting.
And before we have to resort to putting it on Craigslist, uh,
here's your chance right now.
Ah, you know what? I haven't done this in a while.
Let's, uh, let's play that horrible voicemail jingle.
And I'm a streamer.
Hey, I'm a streamer from hoddye.com.
And I have a really quick question regarding the podcasting
and new media expo in Ontario, California, uh,
coming up at the end of this month.
I'm just wondering, what does it benefit
in independent podcasts or such as myself, um,
especially in hip hop to attend and event like that, uh,
aside from maybe making a couple connections and seeing a bunch of
USB microphones, I could give a shit less about.
Really, why would I go?
I mean, it is a really that much to get out of networking at this event.
Um, and is there anything else I'm missing aside from the whole,
you know, I know you can do the, you pay the 300 bucks
and you get the whole educational workshops and all that shit.
Let's say you don't have the money for that.
Should I even bother going?
Let me know, man, I appreciate what you think.
Um, and, um, I hope you had a great labor day.
Talk to you soon.
Yo.
J-Mac.
J-Mac actually sends something with, uh,
with major, which I'm going to play tomorrow on the football
Friday edition of the show.
Which will be done on Friday.
Here we go.
I can hear the nylon just saying now.
We're promising.
It's going to under the liver.
Yeah, that's, that's a good question.
Well, this is, I think, year three for the portable media
expo sometimes also, uh,
misnamed the podcast expo.
Uh, the first year, uh, we, uh,
uh, so to answer your question directly,
I see no value for myself as in my position at pod show.
We see no value, uh, for pod show to do much there.
And we've actually never done anything there besides, uh,
the other part, which I do think has value is hanging out and, uh,
and networking, which, uh, you know,
that's kind of what all conferences are to me.
You know, I, I, I go to conferences not a lot.
Uh, I don't like speaking at them.
I don't like participating in them.
I don't really even like sponsoring them, uh,
because the benefit is usually for the, uh,
organizer of the, uh, of the conference.
Which is fine.
That's, uh, that's a fantastic business.
So, uh, you know, it's pretty much the same,
uh, the same kind of tracks, if you will,
and indeed, uh, that I don't think it would be,
you know, a lot of the fact that I get to see people who I only hear or see,
uh, on video or, you know, just to, to be there to hang out and, uh,
to be there and hang out essentially.
That's always a good thing.
And I don't think you can put a price on that.
Um, and we just had this discussion, uh, yesterday with, uh,
with Richard Brewer, hey, you know,
you will, and indeed, uh, that I don't think it would be useful, uh,
for you, uh, Jane Mack, because, you know, you're, you're kind of rolling.
And I think a lot of this is where people who are.
It's, it, it's kind of a, it's like a blogger conference,
you know, a, um, and I think with most blogger conferences,
it's, uh, you really, you know, what people take away from it from, uh,
you know, what, what, what the media they create out of it is probably the most interesting.
And that's usually just, uh, people hanging out and getting together.
It's also, it feels very much like Ash-Kosh, you know, for pilots, you know,
what is the point of going to Ash-Kosh? Well, you have to go, you know,
and it's on my list.
Um, it, uh, will anything, is it any real reason?
No, because I just want to hang out and kick some tires.
It's like hang or talk.
So, um, and I'm, by the way, I do want to come this year.
And, and the reason is because I know who's showing up,
and I just want to see these people.
I want to hug some people.
I want to say hi and hang out.
Generally, uh, there's, there's not much else that, uh,
that I can see that, uh, being useful for.
Um, next year, I think they're going to move, uh, to, uh,
a much bigger venue in Vegas.
You know, now you're talking, you know,
there's always a reason to go to Vegas.
All right, uh, one more song that I got for you.
This is from the Podsake music.
Now, where this is, um, from the Nigel pace, you know,
Nigel is, uh, I'd say probably the best example of, uh,
what an independent promoter in the radio business is.
He is to podcasting.
Boy, this guy knows how to promote stuff.
And, uh, he has a, uh, he got a track up on the Podsake music
network from, uh, Journey South.
Uh, Journey South are, uh, let me see.
So, first of all, their album is coming out in the UK on the 15th of October.
I just really want to read this because he sent me another email about it,
and I really want, I think they were, uh, what were they?
T-to-to-to-to-to-to...
Yeah, okay, so Journey South, they were finalists on, uh, on the X factor.
A couple years back.
It can only be two or three, I think.
And, uh, so I guess they got a record deal.
And, uh, it's not bad.
So, uh, what the heck?
It's, uh, very appropriate, by the way, for my, uh, trip.
It's journey south and what I love about home.
I'm down, and silence in my country side.
That's what I love about home.
I'm out on the road now, now the place we're all face past goodbye.
Stay out the window thinking back to where I sit goodbye.
We're done trying to picture all of the people I know.
There what I love about home.
Oh, there's a place where I feel I belong
Tell that the end of the room, we're on top
Close with our bodies, I'm on run away
Oh, my life, let's wear our skin
Come on, my wife, I'm on our way back now
That my mom's upset is just warm up to go
I get this thing feeling, we feel
And you're dead's as there's a love
So you know where
When you're lonely
You're always welcome to stay
That's what I love about her
All these places that I feel I belong
Tell that the end of you will be wrapped up
Oh swim my heart is so warm on the way
Oh my life that's where I stay
Well for sure this is going to be one to the soundtrack of my life
Journey South and you can find a link to that
at the pod save music network
podshow.com slash music
the link actually will be a daily source code
dot com to go and check that out
That's a beautiful beautiful song
Journey South
All right everybody 30 minutes perfect
I think we actually have a first conference call coming up in 45 minutes
So
Oh yeah
We're on the west coast baby west coast time
I will talk to you tomorrow for the food bar Friday
Drop me any mill anytime
And thank you for being my friend
Adam at podshow.com
Talk to tomorrow bye
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear