Hello, Gruscott, and herzlich will come in.
My name is Tannig Bulgar, I'm in Germany, and you hear the daily source code,
Oscar V. 500, 47.
With Adam Curry.
I need little pants.
From Pod Show, home of the world's most dangerous new content comes the Daily Source Code.
With Adam Curry.
About $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking greens in.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just in case I'm curry.
Thank God, it's...
One ticket please.
But Adam and Lucy are invited here.
And what's going on man?
Yeah.
She's at home.
Yes, she's at home.
Let's the new liquid.
I just want to bear it for night away.
Yeah, right here I am now.
I'm going to stay.
Oh, my God.
We got the new liquid.
Down until I feel the slavery has passed.
Basically, I give the names, it's wrong.
I'm out here in Heaven.
And still, I can't erase the flame I feel
The 10-letter of we use to share
Save like a floor, throw it at
I've got fire, was giving me a side
Let's music play
I've just walked in there for night away
Yeah, right here, right here
Well, I'm gonna stay
All I know
Yeah, yeah
That's a really play-all
That's a fear I feel that's never reached out
I'm over the kitchen dude
Keep the nils in stone
All let it play-all
Let it play-all
And let it play-all
And let it all play-all
We can go to the other
Ha ha ha ha
If I can make it through the night
All I know
I'll just pitch it
Here with me
All I know
That's a place I'll see
I know it's basically
But as I hold it up for me
That's a music play
I've just walked in there for night away
Yeah, right here, right here
Well, I'm gonna stay
All I know
Yeah, yeah
And let it play-all
Doesn't tell us the others never is
Go, go, go, go
Ha ha
If I can make it through the night
That's football, man
That's what it's all about
Barry White
Let the music play
Play-all
All the way to start a Friday
Daily source code episode 5-47
How you doing everybody
It is Friday
The Master of the Manor
Adam Curry
Coming to you from Curry
Manor
And the affluent suburb of Surrey
Known as Gulford
On the west side of G-town
Why am I playing Barry White?
Well, let me tell you
Last night, the lady Patricia and I watched
The documentary on sky
Like six or something like that
And it was about the life and times of Barry White
Post you mostly put together
Because of course this legend has been
Has been gone for a number of years
And it was titled Let The Music Play
And it was such a fascinating story
To hear how Barry White came from
Literally walked
From East Los Angeles to Hollywood
And started out as a drummer
And then an A&R guy and a producer
And then started making records
And just what a talent this guy was
And throughout this entire documentary
People are all talking about
How Barry's music will live on
And there's his ex-wife
And there's his daughter
And there's his writing partner
And Barry's music will live on
And I'm thinking
Yeah, shit, how's it going to live on
If people live over here
There's stuff
How are you going to discover it?
You typed in white
On iTunes
And all of a sudden it showed up
Which of course is how I got that track
Because I did buy it
And only a fraction of his
Catalog is available
Online
And you know, you can have to
Really search hard to find
His Catalog in music stores
For whatever music stores
I still left over
So you know, if you liked what you heard
And you want to learn all about
The love making skills of Mr. Barry White
And how they can affect you
And how you
But you know what the word
The word is legs
Go home, spread the word
Make babies with Barry White
I just got to play that stuff
I just couldn't stop
Last night
Patricia and I went straight up
To the attic
And started playing
Like 20 Barry White tracks
Which is pretty much everything
That's there
Then of course there's some love
And limited stuff
I just like, oh man
I got to share that with my friend
So it is Fubar Friday
Please don't sue me
That was out of the goodness of my heart
Ah
How to great day yesterday in London
Sorry that wasn't able to put out a show
I kind of knew it wasn't going to happen
Just because you know, I had to be in really early
It's president
Excuse me, you can still tell I got this
Ah
Various
A lot of people in London
Hacking in coffin as well
Um
Yeah, so we had some meetings with the
With the BT folks
BT vision
Which of course is there
There's that top box
Which is now available in limited quantities
And about pod show TV
And then had dinner
With two of the most powerful
Women at British telecom
Who control hundreds of millions of pounds
So I was really all cleaned up
And looking nice
I'll go see that
Sucking up
The best I could do
Ah
No
But it's great
Because it's two completely different cultures
When you come together
As pod show and BT
And it's really nice how we do fit together
We go together
Like shinglinglingling
Hey, I got a note here from Amy Mack
Adam, I know you're feeling crappy
And hoping to travel on Friday
Actually, I was going to travel Friday
But now it's going to be Sunday
So I'm going to cut you some slack
And give you this week
Assurcize free
Feel better
Hope to see you next week
Amy Mack
Yes
I will see you next week
And maybe you can do a personal
Assurcize
Speaking of body parts
Did you see this or did you hear about this report
The UNICEF put out
That said the best place to raise kids
In the entire world is the Netherlands
And they have some kind of
They'll have a very detailed study
And it's based upon a lot of things
I don't really understand
And they came up with some kind of index
And by the way, I'd like to disagree
It may be great to grow up in the Netherlands
But it's very hard to break out of the Netherlands
Once you grow up there
Very few seem to
Okay, so that doesn't matter
I'll take that
The worst country in the world
By far in a way
Was the United States
Which I also have my disagreements about
The second to worst was the United Kingdom
So I'm like, look in the survey
And I said, we definitely need better data
And I got it today
courtesy of the son
This is the son online
So I'll post a link to it in the show
No, it's a daily source code.com
British women have the biggest breasts in Europe
A survey revealed yesterday
Oh, yes
I knew it was in the right country
Here you go
The poll which is done for Brahmaker triumph
Also the manufacturer of fine motorcycles
Found that only in this country
Did more than half the women need a decouper larger
Our 57%
Including curvy model Kelly Brook
Put the rest in the shade
With Denmark second
On 50%
And then number three the Netherlands
36%
Third biggest houters of Europe
Belgium after that
Notice I've lived in three of these countries
France, Sweden, Greece, Switzerland
The Swedes in the Swiss
Have the largest number of acup sizes
At 14%
Fantastic fabulous
Fabulous survey
Very appreciative
Because I was just getting a little bit worried about
About why we're actually here in the UK
Oops
On the second
Pilot error
Hey Adam, it's dark from Sydney again
So let me get this right
You go to the toilet with your N800
I just
I don't know what you need to be doing with that
In the toilet
Yeah
Yeah, you can't fathom that can you
Well let me tell you I like to sit in my friend
I like to sit no matter what my business is
In the toilet
I've completely retrained myself
42 years of horrible habit
So that we can keep the bathroom splatter free
Even though I don't have to clean it up
I do have to clean up my own shit in San Francisco
The condo
Yeah, of course I've got to
My interior engineer
Christinaizer name coincidentally
Who comes by before
I show up in after I leave
But still you know when I'm there for a week
I have to clean crap up
Not just crap
Yeah man
That's what that's what the N800 is
Fantastic for again yesterday
Went to London
Took this
There's Nokia internet tablet with me
Walked into the pod show
Shortage crash pad
And
Immediately
It found I'd taken it there before
So it found the network
It had already connected me
Didn't have to do anything
I was doing my email
And I didn't have to log around a laptop
So that's basically what you know you use the laptop for
And I actually got some stuff
I used it on the train with the
With the modem from my phone
Um
And I've I haven't had a lot of time
In the past two days
To really mess around with all the
I'm going to talk about that later in a free
Trinity update
To mess around with all the
The python scripts
But it's a fantastic device
I'm I'm actually
Getting back into a little bit of programming
Learning how to
To a now address the
What is it the gtk?
I guess that's graphical
Toolkit or something like that
From python so you can open up windows
And and file
File dialog boxes and
Put some functionality into some scripts
And once you really get into the zone of
Scripting and something
It really goes quite fast
And you should see this development
Environment
I got to make a screenshot of that
So that's all right
Just a little geeky stuff for a second
So I'm SSH
In
To the device
To the N800
From my laptop
So I've got a
A terminal window open
And then I have VNC running
Next to it
So if I program a window to pop open
Through the python toolkit
Graphical toolkit
I can actually see that appear
Without having to have the device
Right next to me
It's really it's a lot of
I got a delia
I
Love the tinfoil hat moments
Hi I'm in CG here again
I'm really pleased that you picked up my suggestion
For it's some things
And you're getting some
Now getting some ass exercise as well
In order to encourage more people to take up this
I mean just for those of you just joining the show
Just so you don't confuse about ass exercise
And whatever he just said in German
This is about the sits and
sits and pink on
In other words
A movement
A movement to have all men sit down
When they pee
As I can't say it any other way
Sit down when you do a number one
Because it'll you know
It'll save a lot of hassle and nastiness
For the person who has to clean the toilet for you
Practice
I really think that they need to ask
The person who does the cleaning
And that is
What benefit there is
After they've tried it a week
If you like me
And you're being down on your hands
And these
With a scrubber
And the bottle of bleach
You really get to see what
Spray about
Just for now
Thank you man
Hey great news
And I got this this tidbit
From tons of people
Of course
Quoting
From several sources
Now that Google has more computing muscle
Sarah J. Bryn
So the company will start selling additional storage capacity
To email users with extraordinary needs
Google still hasn't figured out
The specifics would bring indicated the email storage
And fees will be introduced later this year
To be similar to Google's photo hosting service
The charge is $25 annually for 6.25 gigabytes
And $500 annually for $250 gigabytes
Hello
Yeah
Love it
Oh they finally heard me
Fuck you Jason
Not only have I been talking about this
Since the inception of Gmail
And as you know
I'm already deep in the
Conclaves
The Enclaves
The Catacombs of Google
Because I got the
Special 4 gigabyte limit
Which of course I've surpassed for a year now
And keep floating at 98.99%
But look at our board of directors dude
Maybe that'll give you a clue
Is to who really
Really insticated this
So let's just mention
Featuring the best of all genres of the electronic music
I know you give me a lot of spiles
And I'll host this at the Chilkance
I'm Jim Noe
For the idol of music podcast
Hey, this is Joanne from In Over Your Head.net
Hey everyone, this is Macedonia
Of the Radio BFF podcast
Hey everyone, this is Thomas
The host of Yolala as a French hot pot guest
That Yolala.org
I'm going to read from the 1st electronic night day
And the 16th podcast
My name is Neil
Greetings from Attenborough.net
And Scotland.
With you there please
Up with together the almond present podcast
Yeah, this is Mr. E from the DJ class
Bringing you German base and beyond
Hi everybody, this is Pedro Bucanist
Coming to you from the Netherlands
This is Bizzoucajo and this week's edition
Of Solopsistic Nation features an exquisite corpse mix
It began with sending a song to a fellow podcaster
And asking them to select the track that they thought
Go after the tune I picked
The next podcaster had to choose a song based
On the previous track with the tune they dug
The process was completed until the mix was complete
How the mix unfolds will be just as much as a prize for us
As it will be for you
So please join us on Solopsistic Nation
Where we play the very best of electronic music
If so we want a TMI
I still see nation.com
So Lipstick wait a minute, I got to spell this for you
Because you'll never be able to get it from the promo
Solopsistic Nation
Okay, here we go, ready got a pen
Sierra Oscar Lima
India Papa
Sierra India Sierra Tango
India Charlie
November alpha tango India Oscar
November dot com
That's a good idea
I like that it's kind of like one of those
Party games you play at the table at a dinner party
You know like passing on
Yeah, I word association
I like that that's very cool
I've not listened to the show yet
But the promo definitely
Definitely did it for me
Like this one too
That's just the riff of a new song
I'm working on Adam
It's David of Belito
That guitar man from Central Park
And Lisa from I love the company
And we're just letting you know that we just finished
Show 200
Actually show 200
And one
That's right by time you get this
But time you play it
On a daily source code we're back
We got back from Mexico
And so now we're getting back into the swing
And things again new show
On high love the company
Every day Monday through Friday
So make sure you tell everybody about it
David I like this groove
Cool, you know what I just
Truthfully I just kind of kick this thing around
Some new funny songs
So this is a new thing
I'm just kind of kicking around right now
So as soon as it has some likes
We'll send it your way
And oh listen
Let us know when you get to New York
Yeah, maybe we'll go to London
Maybe we'll go to London
Maybe we'll hang out with you guys in London
Alright so listen Adam
Keep up the great work in them
And we'll see you around the pod as fair
Yeah, yeah
I David the lovely Lisa
Yeah, I know
You're episode 202 already
Because I think I got that one last night on the train
Did I get on the train?
It was the morning that I saw a show up
200 was great and congratulations
And yes I'm going to be in New York
I'm going to I have a
Oh I'm appearing in a production
I don't know if I can actually mention it yet
So I won't say that
But it's being done in North Carolina
I think I think it's North Carolina
And it's acting
It's a real stretch for me too
It's something that's kind of fun
It has to do with pod show
And you can't really get there from here
So instead of flying for nine hours like Atlanta
And then taking another plane
And I was like why don't I just go to New York with Virgin
Which I love you know
I just love Virgin Atlantic
I can't help it
I would rather stay at night in New York
Just to fly the first leg on Virgin Atlantic
So I'm going to stay one night in New York
Which I think is going to be Friday
Or Saturday Saturday night
The
Ojipu
I'm thinking the 10th or 11th or something like that
And then I'm flying out Sunday
And then I think that that week
Anyway shit
I'm coming to New York
Okay, I got a lot of stuff to do
But I would definitely love
I would love to hang with you guys
Maybe that night when I arrived before I go
To North Carolina the next day
Maybe we go hang out
I'll be a little jet lag a little bit tired
But I would love to hang out with you
And the lovely lady Lisa
I'm feeling mighty lonesome
Haven't slept a wink
I walk the floor and watch the door
And in between I drink
Black coffee
Love is a hand me down the road
I'll never know a Sunday
In this week they rule
I'm talking to the shadows
Wanna collect your phone
And load house below the moment's go
When all I do is phone
Black coffee
Since the blues cut my eye
I'm hanging out on Monday
My Sunday dreams
To dry
Now man is born to go
I love him
A woman's born to wait and for it
To stay at home
And tender of him
And down her pastry the rest
In coffee and cigarettes
I'm moaning all morning
Moaning all the night
And in between it's nicotine
And not much hard to fight
Black coffee
Feeling low as the ground
Recognize that tuna
From a couple days ago
It's driving me crazy
You're waiting for you baby
To come around
Black coffee
Fultures with splendor
If you must know
Stephanie Hardger
Hardger
I think it's Hardger
Of course that was the soundtrack
The chef Mark used
And his valentines concoction
And I sent me a note
That's great
What a great track that is
Thanks, Chef Mark
For letting me know that was on the podcast
Music Network of course it was
Yesterday
Second episode of Textra
Launched Natalie Del Conti
Who is now doing a multi day
Technology show
For Pod Show
I'm really liking it
I think you should go check it out
I had a
Had a really good conversation with her
Just before we started the series
And
I have to say
This young lady is a true, true, true feminist
And every sense of the word
We were in discussions about her doing a show
Now she's a very accomplished writer
And she's written about technology
For a number of years
She has degrees
And all kinds of really impressive stuff
But she's also beautiful
And no one can deny it
And she said, I really want to do something different
With this show
I really want to be girly and feminine
And sexy and still talk about technology
I don't want to have to hide my assets
So to speak
And I want to
It should be possible
It should be a combination of both
I know she went on cranky geeks
The other day I haven't seen the show
So I don't know if she talked about that
But I'm so proud of her
As a woman myself
I'm just so proud of what she's doing
And everyone who's watched the show
seems to just love it
So there's a new one up today
Textra, T-E-X-T-R-A
Textra.podshow.com
With Natalie Del Conti
Mark Yoshimaru and M-Coff
Not a pretty good idea actually
Maybe it's something for the Fubar
It's something
If there's enough what do you call it
If there's enough people that want to try this out
I'm totally game for it
The idea is
Bringing back the guitar solo
Guitar solo
It's almost something of the past
You know, almost something of the 80s
Yet you know that
Oh crap
Hey folks, listen to serious stars 102
Go get your own guitar
Get out your axe
Because we'll be talking about it
Download the whole show
DailySourceco.com
Before we find out the rest of this story
I think that there's still lots of people
who love to just pick up the guitar and just riff
And I think that there's, you know, we've had
Air Guitar Contest
But actually, I think that
Audio podcast like this one
Maybe a good place to bring back the guitar solo
So if you've got a guitar solo
Or if you want to record your guitar solo
Send it to
House of Tone at gmail.com
House of Tone
All written together
T-O-N-E House of Tone
At gmail.com
Mark and I are going to see if we can get something going
Now he actually sent it
He claims this is his guitar solo
He says the guitar used for this
Was a bright yellow custom-made
Strat body with EMG pickups
I have, if Mark, if, well,
Listen to this
This is apparently a guitar solo
Download by Mark Yoshimoto
Nemcock from Pacific Coast
Hellway
Number one with the bullet shadow falls
Yadi Adi
Where's my fucking latte?
All that stuff.
Small penis, here we go
1-Sport
Mark, if that's really you
Stop podcasting
We just fucking stop
Go play guitar
I don't know if I, I'm looking, I think for guitar solo is that don't have rhythm
section behind it. Just, you know, just let me hear your sound, man. And let us know what
gear you're using and just play some. Just fucking riff away. Let's see if we can do that
because I like listening to guitar solo. For a while we did drum cadences and then I guess
we just kind of ran out of material after a while. But guitar solo as man, you can pick up your
right. In fact, I have, I got four guitars here. I love Christina's boyfriend Andy. He
re-strong every single guitar, cleaned them all up, tuned them all. Nothing I can play or anything.
Hey Adam, this is Stella from California. I just wanted to tell you that I truly enjoyed
the show with you and Patricia. It's just so wonderful listening to both of you, the honesty
and sincerity. It's not corny to me because I've been married for almost 25 years and for you being
together 20 years and still being so in love and such kinder spirits. So thank you and hopefully
Patricia will be back again next week or maybe not next week because she'll be in San Francisco.
But anyway, have a wonderful day and just a day. Just beg, I want you to be be gay with my wife.
I would make me really happy. John Kits says, Adam, be a little gay. Make sure the kids are quiet.
Ah, those were the days when men were the master of the manner. Is Ivan still available?
I think Patricia's sister. I'm telling you, man. Actually, I did listen to the show I
did with Patricia Valentine's Day. Man, I'm a lucky mother fucker. Vadim Zaliva.
He, now I'm just going to switch gears here for a second to a little bit of tin foil hat moment
back to the Nokia N800. Not just the Nokia. I was talking about the light. That's what it was.
The life blog software that is in the series 60 phones. I had that on. Oh, I have it. I have it on my E61 and
was it the N95 or whatever. A lot of phones have this. It's a really nice piece of software.
Well, second. What's that? Screw up. It's like the Dutch gossip magazines are calling me now. How
they got my number? I don't know. Anyway, so I had a story earlier in the week. I was talking about
the fact that they support the Atom ATOM, the Atom API, which is a way to get content to metadata
from one device to another across the internet. And I was saying basically the MetaWeblog API,
which is built on top of XMLRPC, or is an XMLRPC version. I don't know what the hell you call it.
But you know what I'm talking about, which is really so simple. Even I can make it work. I even
made it work on the N800. And I really want Nokia to implement an Atom on XMLRPC with a MetaWeblog
API, which so far I've been striking out on. So Vadim sends in a comment, which I thought was really
interesting. He says, uh, heard your comments about Atom versus XMLRPC in the Nokia Life blog.
He says, I assume by XMLRPC, you mean the MetaWeblog protocol? Oops. Yes.
Working in mobile space, I can understand why Nokia is reluctant to do what you want. It's very
difficult to get new software into headsets. Fuck. I'm going to play that voicemail, whoever that was.
It requires extensive testing of multiple devices for where upgrade sometimes even legal
paperwork in some countries. Yeah, I that I understand, but that was not what I was told. I was told,
hey, we've got the Atom API. Why would I implement something else? On the other hand, it would be
quite simple as Vadim to implement simple proxy from Atom posting the Life blog flavor because
they do use some non-standard extensions to the MetaWeblog. This could be an external module running
on separate machines. This way, you didn't do not need to modify anything at Podshow,
and yet have it working with Nokia phones. It's a fairly simple project. Probably only take a
couple of days. And I'm very interested in this. Think about, I mean, what a what a fantastic
web service that would be. Wow. Okay, here's an idea for your Vadim. Here's an idea.
So if you made a simple web service, basically where I sign in, I register and I say, okay,
I'm going to be sending you something from my Nokia phone or any Atom related protocol.
But let's just say the Life blog. And here's where I want it to go in XMLRPC. So you have kind of
like a translator. You know what? I would even be happy to have a little link at the bottom show
of Automatically that says, you know, this post was TransMorgaford TransFarded. This post was
TransFarded. Thanks to the Vadim translator service or something like that. I think there's a
fuck, I pay for it. You know what? That's awesome. Awesome Vadim. Let's see if we can get some
together on that man. I really like it. Okay. So let me just see here. These these jibronies, man.
They've been calling me for the past two days. What they call up and they say, hi, we just want to
see how everything's going and how's your new house? Let me say, I'm going to put this on the
speaker phone. I recognize the number immediately as show news, a television rag.
Do you want to be eating? You're a message from Anna?
Uh, why do I have to listen to that? Hold on a second. I don't want to listen to that. That's
like really old messages. Oh, I hate it when singular does this. Hold on. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
save. Oh, this sucks so bad.
A crap. All right. Let's play some Jersey Todd and then I'll get this hold on a second.
You know, I know you're with me now anyway. Hey, yeah, hold on. Let me save that one.
Hold on. It's like a fucking million years old.
Oh, singular. Can I just say that your voice mail service sucks major ass. You should be
giving me the new messages first, not the old messages. Hold on. Yeah,
re-saved. Okay. Finally.
Okay. Well, that was really fucking unsuccessful. Hold on.
Okay. Those of you who live in the Netherlands will understand how stupid that is. Hey, just call
the see how you're doing. See if, hey, why don't you call in live on the show tonight?
Whenever there's technical problems, I'm just really happy he's nearby.
I had a prolific program. I'm proud of you, man. You're learning. You're correcting yourself.
You're taking your time to speak. Let's go. I had a prolific program in San Francisco again.
Take your time. I posted some of the Google Earth output that you requested on the news group
on my blog as I put in keyhole mark of using Python. Have a good night, cheers. Okay.
So prolific programmer is on the case. What are we talking about? Well, we're talking about
ramping up for free Trinity. That love day for you, everybody. Let's see if we can get this some
bitch on the road.
Driving across the USA. Open and make a good time today. I feel like I've been watching
go. Letting everybody know that this is going to be the better way.
Little cowbell, everybody. The Trinity, Trinity, because of central luxury, Trinity, Trinity,
left the bio, diesel, set your brain, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity,
right out. Okay. I got a lot of work to do this week and catching up on the free Trinity
group. I've got a proposal that I have to still review from Paula Walto, podcaster, Barbara, who's
gathering all the information I want to run the project. I've got to kind of figure out what
the entire project is. However, the techno heads are surging ahead and I really, I just haven't
had time to sit down and parse through it, but it looks like we got a lot of code that I'm going
to start to implement this weekend. So prolific programmers, he just heard he's set something up now
so that GPS coordinates are output in a KML file, which is the type of file Google Earth uses,
so you should be able to track Trinity's progress. Okay. I've been thinking about
thinking about where to place the black box, which I'm pretty sure is going to be a Nokia
and 800. That seems to be our development platform. I'm thinking that it wouldn't be cool
if we use the onboard camera and we kind of position the thing on the dashboard, so you can always see
who is driving and then I saw something yesterday on Dave Winner's weblog. You have these wireless
cameras, these Wi-Fi-based cameras, that as long as they can connect to a Wi-Fi point somewhere,
they basically send back their IP information to home-based and you can not only look at the
picture, but you can control them from anywhere in the world. Maybe it makes sense to have a couple
of these hardwired in as well, so you can either, so we could perhaps record a video stream,
make it interactive. I got to get one at my hand, I wanted these devices, I got to order one off
of Amazon, but that could be something very cool as well. A multimedia experience with Trinity.
Okay Adam, after listening to the DSC for over 350 shows, I'm finally sending in an audio
comment. My name is Dan Lin and I produce the RoseDrop Media Circus podcast available at
RoseDropMedia.podshow.com. Our show features local Portland Oregon Performing Artist,
answering interview questions, playing live, and sometimes featuring cuts from their CDs.
We've been doing the show since September 2005 and have posted over 100 shows of all original
material. We just moved from our first venue, have always recorded our show live in public,
and would love to have Trinity stop by on her cross-country tour. Join the circus,
and we'll take you out to a nearby biodiesel station. We also stream our live taping into
second life. I've played many live music dates in SL as RoseDrop Rust, and we can show the
audience in real life clubs, the second life podshow live music venue. Please come to Portland
to be our guest. This would be a wonderful and valuable prize for our listeners.
Haven't missed a show since I started listening, and yes, I told all the staff, of course.
All right, dude, thank you so much. Yeah, absolutely. We'll put her on the map, and that would
make a lot of sense. I don't mind going up or down before we go to the right. If you're looking
at Trinity's starting point, lots of other smart companies jumping in on the action because
it's going to be a lot of fun to be had with Trinity. Hi, Adam. It is all the same on from Holland.
Well, I listen to the daily source because only almost on the regularly basis daily. I love
the show. I even love the Trinity concept. In my daytime job, I'm a marketing guy at the company
Vogels. We made a product to mount these these player or small 70C in your car at the head
of Phonti. For the back seat, I can just enjoy a movie or show the web. I'm willing to
sponsor the project with a VV doc product. And while we're even a couple, if you want to
give them a chance, I would put the values of prices. The product is on www.Vosal.com, slash VV doc,
and I will send you an email with my contact details if you want to know more about the
VV doc. Okay, it actually straps on to the back of the headrest. That's pretty interesting.
You have other docs here available as well. Let me see, when else they have. They have sound on
their website is what they have. LCD wall support. Dude, thank you. That might be pretty good.
Yeah. I wonder if you can still bolt the box to that. I don't want, well, it's kind of a
trusting. If we send Trinity off and we have this box, this nice tablet, it's something that
could be easily stolen. If you take it out of the car, it could be easily dropped. We may have
to have a little more a fixed solution for that than what it was called, DV doc does. I like the
product though. Is that your own invention? Is that a Dutch product because it's pretty cool?
Alright, please join the Free Trinity Google Group. I predict that somewhere in the next,
well, I'd have to say by maybe April 1st, but hopefully before that, we can get around the road.
It really depends on how much the technology we can get together, but I feel we're getting pretty close.
I just got a jump into the group and start participating and maybe help organize a little bit
and see if we can get some installs and stuff just kind of works.
The address to join is groups.google.com slash group free Trinity Trinity Trinity,
luxury Trinity Trinity, let the bio diesel set your brain, Trinity Trinity, Trinity Trinity,
free Trinity, you save the world, you win valuable prizes. Trinity.
Hey Adam, it's Kate from the UK again. You were just lamenting on DSC 545, I think,
but no women were calling you, so I'm calling you again, and you were also talking about smart
hot women, so I thought you might want to try me out for sites, I'd say, on five to seven,
reasonably slim and blond, I've got blue eyes and I've got a HD in biomedical science.
Is that the, yeah? Oh yes, that does mean, that's all I've got to say,
this is what you have to go on times day, and oh yeah, I think I've caught your illness through my
earbuds, I feel horrible, I don't even need a pot saw that. Oh no, can I come over there and kiss
it and make it better without help? What do you have a degree in? Yeah, and I think that's all
I've got to say, and then to which one? Why, why not stay in biomedical science. Biomedical science.
You know, just the other day, it's, it's really unbelievable. Ron Blumini, we're saying to each other,
wouldn't it be fucking awesome if we could have a video show about biomedical science and
we're looking for a host, I mean, I just can't find one anywhere.
Suddenly naked pictures, paint, I'll set them back up from us, crack it up,
charging in the house, to make a motion, to watch this bother our hearts,
to turn his ball around.
Hey, how are you doing? It's Jersey Todd on Fubar Friday. Yo, what's up, AC? I've got a band for you tonight.
Hailing out at New York, New York, the city's so nice and named it twice is one of my new favorite
bands. Yeah, they kind of sound like a cross between the strokes and Freddie Mercury, but I'm
loving them because they just sound like something completely unique. The band, well, of course I love
the name, the band is the attorneys and the song is on a whim. Hey, have a good food by Friday.
Everybody, I'll check you next week. Turn this up loud.
Got a good back, good back to you. I know it's been a long time, but I don't know what to do,
but my time and my mind is a fantasy. I know it's just a dream girl, but it feels so real to me.
I know we'll have to relax the reason to be fun telling you not to fear stress of our worries.
I'll be ready to show you, I know we'll have fun.
Checking my watch it's nine o'clock, I know I'll take on too long
But it's not like I've forgotten
What you'll need and the same did we like to share I know it's not the same dear
But at least we both were here
Oh no, wait
I've got back to relax and be by the bed
Do it side to just face
Oh my work please
And I'm too new, so I'm not
I'll come soon by too
And all I'll be saying once is that please remember my answer
Only once will the set of you say
And I love you more than a doubt tells us questions
So stay with me just one more night as my name
I finally home now the work is done
I know it's been a long time since you and I had any fun
Together we measure just what love could mean
I'm in love with you
I just would love could mean
I know I want you to know me
For the rest of what may be
I'm in love with you
I come back to relax
Bring the lips of your face
Oh my worries
I'llyeon to you
I'm in love with you
I'll come straight back
To you
Once again Jersey Todd delivers the goods the attorneys on a win from the pod save music network
Through the magic of the internet to your ear buds via the pod safe music network links
In the show notes a daily source code dot car. It's Friday
Monday Tuesday Wednesday Thursday food about Friday at a final fun of the week
I'll have no one of these in a while until we've almost had a complete week of shows and I'm feeling a little bit better
I did just want to say one thing about what I learned in this past week my final bot for you
I learned yesterday that a husband of a woman that Patricia and I know pretty well well acquainted with has cancer
And his terminal has one year to live and he's very young she's young
It's something that is just fucking shocking
And of course I've been confronted with this on my own personal level as well
You know this past week we celebrated Valentine's Day and it's the one day out of the year
That guaranteed we're going to be nice and romantic and send flowers and make love
And just you know have a nice overly commercialized day
And when I hear you know how very vulnerable life is I just think to myself you know
Why don't you get up every day and think today is Valentine's Day
Fuck the fact that your eyes are opening in the morning you should just be grateful for that
Really
So here's my suggestion
Run don't walk run to your iTunes or your Napster or your whatever Yahoo music service
Buy some berry white and tonight
When you and your loved one are together just flip that one on
Of course you'll have to slap the laptop into the bedroom because the iPod or unless have an iPod dog
Anyway, play that and
Let's make every day just a little bit of Valentine's Day
All right, that's it for this week traveling to San Francisco
I'll probably do a show Monday, even though it's President's Day
If you guys promise you'll listen I'll do a show
And today's show notes will be chock full with all kinds of links and stuff as discussed in this very program
As daily source code dot com and if you want to send me anything it's Adam at podshow dot com
Have yourselves a great weekend
Make love to very white
Take care everybody
Have another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear