You better be careful out there on the next couple of weeks you hear me?
Let's close the room.
No.
Two sides.
Soon or later, either you're gonna be with us.
I can be with the nearest one family.
All the places you gotta come to my place.
I'm done with you!
Walking Phoenix, Mark Wahlberg,
on October 12th.
Oh, get down!
Two brothers collide.
Maybe you could be killed.
Right?
We own the night rated R.
Once again, it's time to ask.
Where in the world is Adam Curry?
Perhaps we'll find out on the DSC 667.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Been the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm strong.
Yeah, David.
I'm Curry.
Do you name it?
What's up?
Get it?
Can you see it all over my face?
Uh-huh.
I try to hide it.
But I kept it in the cupboard in case.
Case I liked it.
I got a green light.
I'm glad we had the party in your place.
Oh yeah.
It did feel right.
Turning back to Amber Red Light.
Red Light spells a danger.
Maybe you name it?
TVC's on the team.
Maybe I can't TV.
Lady Trump.
How can make your baby cry?
If you killed FDP.
Baba D's and most MPs.
Me.
I'm on the K.
The street.
Maybe you name it?
You name it?
Desit on the ceiling.
Desit on the floor.
You name it like it.
More and more more and more more more more more.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
You made me like it. They are from a thing Scotland. Everybody how you're doing it.
It's a daily source code episode 667 and I don't know where you are. You may be just waking
up Saturday morning at the podcast media. It is officially now the podcast media expo. I believe
hold on. I'm trying to get my sound right here. I'm set up in the hotel room and boy, it was
last time we spoke on Tuesday. Oh fantastic. Another two-show week. Fuck. It's really frustrating.
There's been a lot going on and I have been taken notes so I can bring you up to speed.
First, I'll tell you about the setup here. It's a very interesting hotel. We're in the
in the Sheraton, the Marriott, which is closer to the actual convention center and a lot of the
action is booked up fully, well in advance. I'm sure. Of course, I only knew last minute that I was
going to come out here. There's actually this is like a round glass dinner table in my sweet here
on the non-smoking floor. We almost got everything right for Adam with the bookings except for the
non-smoking floor because you know when I come out to the to the to the expo or anywhere that
there's people who listen to the show. Man, I get hooked up left and right and I deserve it. It's the
end of the of a long week and it's going to be this way for I told you up until the new year. It's
really the time to hustle and move ass and get some shit done. My week started Wednesday morning
flying to Chicago. Great flight, you know, took Virgin Atlantic and it was beautiful as always. I must
say though, I'm not quite sure if someone was trying to do me a favor or what was going on but
when I got off the plane it'll hair. They made an announcement would you please have your
your passports out and ready because you know instead of you normally expect to go through
customs right and there's a line etc and all that and then there's a non-residents and residents and
so but right at the end of the jet way we had to show our passports and I showed mine and there's like
four homeland security agents and lady took my passport to say oh yep here you go and she gave it
some other guy some forgot his name agent something or other and he said come with me and so you know
it's like all right and so we're we're you know we go around through a secret door and
I don't have to stand in the queue or anything like that and then he waits for me to get my bag and
I'm like is it's a hookup from Virgin you know what what is this like VIP treatment like
and it was I guess not having to stand in line but then he said you know because you know
of me taking you through here I got to open up your suitcase and so then he proceeds to open
everything up and he asked all kinds of questions about you know my you K address my address in San Francisco
and I don't know luckily I wasn't carrying any contraband my goodness I'm so lucky
anyway Chicago I was there to speak in front of about 250 300 people at OMD which is
probably the world's largest digital agency and Pachod does plenty of business with them
and I'm always looking for more you know me mr. opportunist so I did a keynote
which is fun you know it's a man I I wish I was a video of the one I did at IMedia because I think
you'd really enjoy it I think that there might be one that was made so if that becomes available I'll
be sure to put it up online man it looks like my levels are a little low here hold on let me just
crank up the mic a little bit how's this and my more in your ear now is that better
then in the so I did the keynote in the morning and it was it was a little bit messed up because
when I got to Chicago I called Patricia and she really was feeling poorly and that really sucks you know
I was like fuck I left again and now you know she's not feeling well she's okay but she just you know
just not feeling just over tired I think from a number of things and also Christine is back in school
so we're all getting up really early again my wife she flourishes beautifully in spring and summer
and in winter time she really cold weather just does not agree with her as long as I've known her you know
she really goes into hibernation mode and around January she starts to freak out and she really
needs the weather to get warmer that's usually when we book our trips to Jamaica
anyway so did the keynote and then there was a panel moderated by cool guy Nick Johnson
who I think he said he's like head sales Weasel over at mbc.com
smart guy and so you know as a panel of me and a guy from Google got from Microsoft guy from my space
another woman from mbc.com and between her and Nick I was like man you know either
either you guys coming to work with me or I'm gonna you know we have to buy nbc
those are smart people and so it was cool and so thanks to Sean Finigan Bill Gorsky and above
all Cory oh man I hadn't met Cory Cory I don't know she she's like some head hunch over there but
kind of she probably hate me for saying but she kind of looked like like Tina Fey you know I
considered to be extremely beautiful and she yes she really had a Tina Fey look which she was five
months pregnant and wow she was just incredibly sexy she had me mesmerized throughout this entire event
she was running around and then taking care of business it was awesome totally lover anyway so jump
on jump after literally ran right off the panel into a waiting automobile and sped off at about 15
miles an hour to oh hair airport it was bumper to bumper traffic all the way so just barely made it
onto the flight TSA no problem for me at least this time of course I didn't have any hair products
in my bag I did have the usual transmitters microphones wires all kinds of devices multiple cell
phones lighters you know all of that stuff that of course is completely safe and they're not looking for
we'll talk more about that later and a sat next to and actually usually I you know I fly a coach
when I'm flying internally in the US I like jet blue a lot as you know and I've tried out virgin
and so this was american airlines I think someone must have used their miles or something but they
hooked me up with a first class seat which was nice I wouldn't have made that much difference it's
short flight you know four hours not that bad set next it's lovely woman who and I said she she
she looked like mid 50s probably and you were talking about TSA she said oh tell me about it you
know I have a pacemaker and she says you do really think that that having TSA feel me up
every single time I go through the metal detectors can make your flight any safer as you just
the lovely woman lovely nice chat was one of those you know it wasn't an uncomfortable type of
seatmate chat it was it was nice it kind of felt good and and then upon arrival at John Wayne Airport
Orange County California had yet another escalate with tinted windows waiting for me to whisk me
away to the Sheraton hotel in lovely Ontario California and we had our traditional
unexpo party going on which we did with the extreme pods and rumour girls and yeah those are the
main the main sponsors I think we took care of all the drinks which was basically you know that's
all you need here is you just need some drinks and a room and we're good to go and it was packed it was
absolutely packed and it was just amazing to to see everybody oh man I can't remember
although I must say I've gotten much better at recognizing the faces now that I've seen them a couple
times in a row or you know I've seen them in the past the previous events and just getting to know
people more women this year because you know this is totally a middle-aged white guy geek fest to be
quite honest I'm not even sure what we're doing here other than to absolutely hang out with each other
and that's working that's totally working for me but it's so good to see women here and so of course
Angie B and God she's such a she's a flirt man she drives me nuts and I got my big hug and she
gave me a big kiss on the lips and you know her lips were really sticky and uh to my
one like sticking together I could barely talk some kind of lip gloss thing I hope and pizza babe
as she kept hugging me Marcus couches wife you know she's so lovely and there were some of the
sex podcast women were walking around and and of course the rumour girls Karen and Carla and I was
just I was completely I don't know it's it was just a series of events you know I think it started
with Cory and then Anne on the plane and then I just built up and I'm like looking at all these women
and that just all beautiful all in their own way and I don't know I was totally I think I
propositioned Karen from the rumour girls yeah so I want to play it song for the girls all the
girls and all the women of the world because I truly love you
really good sunshine in the head
I love things we know love things we show got to be where hey girls the sunshine in the head
the person that it was girls ever we were
I love the things we show got to be where hey girls
I love the things we know love things they show got to be where hey
oh yeah baby
moments in what knots girls from the soundtrack to my life thanks to the organization for the
preservation of said soundtrack to my life we're able to play that on a fubar Friday I do have
kind of maximum music for you but there's a lot of there's a couple topics I do want to run through
but just finishing up you know being being here so the party was was fantastic and it was great
because security and the cops came to shut us down just before everything got out of control
and the booze was pretty much done by that time as well so that was outstanding I would have to say
a very proud of our pod show a presence here to kick off of the festivities at the portable
media xways I guess it is officially podcast and the new media expo
so then it was pretty early 12 12 o'clock I was back in my room you know
tried to do a little bit of email of course bandwidth is horrible at a convention like this
that is not really sitting at the hotels everything aren't set up for oh shit no hotel is set up
for the amount of bandwidth we're consuming that's for sure so got some sleep you know of course
I woke up at five woke up at six woke up again at eight and then London was up so they started
calling so long after I get so got up and basically had my double coffee breakfast
didn't even have time to order room service just one after another and yeah some meetings were
started to go on of course so we have the digital musical awards on Tuesday so that's why I'm flying
back tomorrow Saturday afternoon I'm flying back for a rival Sunday this is big and and this is
going to be the debut although it's kind of running already of the plus yeah this is original
higher I'm trying to watch the plus TV and an EVDO connection here and you might imagine
it's just not cutting and now it's wanting if there's any kind of adjustments that I can make
to this on my end so that maybe of a lesser quality so that I haven't been with trying to
watch on this wireless connection the idea is it'd be appreciated for the show yeah yeah man
so first of all you know your results are gonna be I'm gonna very for sure when you're trying to
do is stuff like that over EVDO now this is of course this is all pretty new to us and just to be
on the very safe side and we went with a really safe solution for the stream of course I know
we can do flash etc we've tried that in the past it wasn't great for everybody so we're going
with really just a very very safe solution right now which is well Windows media and that's being
distributed by I'm so that's you know that's a pretty safe pretty safe bet there I believe the
stream is only like 348 kilobits and I don't know if it's variable I thought that you would
be able to connect at a lower speed you might have to check the settings on your player
to tell it to vary according to bandwidth or something like that but I don't know if if we
have to do something on our end it's entirely possible that we do but again your EVDO that's kind
of tough a lot of talk about the plus TV which I'm very happy about because you know I've mentioned
it here and there but I've been working on this for nine or ten months and it really started
with just a plan I wrote up on a Saturday or Sunday afternoon and you know the idea here is
imagine what MTV would look like if if it were still on its original mission here today
in the the age of YouTube and and episodic content so yeah there'd be music videos but we'd have
some you know some wacky stuff like people shooting bottle rockets out of their ass and you know
why wouldn't you have you know five minutes of texture really a complete kind of channel just
in linear fashion and you know we we have the machinery to do it all we just really needed to
away to schedule it so I found this great scheduling software and we work with the company to
modify it so it's really meant for radio stations and so you know this is not like a playlist that
you put into Windows media player and where you wait for the next thing to buffer it's one continuous
stream and we have a lower third titles that come up automatically and you can see we're doing
stuff on the page where it shows you what's coming up next and it's all kind of stuff like that
so it's really been fun at least the errands has been running this all by herself man it's been
a herkulean effort so we're gonna utilize that for our live coverage or our coverage of
the digital music awards and it starts on Monday so Monday we start with all our pre-stuff and we've
got lots of recognizable pod show faces who are doing segments and introwing all this stuff and
that will be looking at videos from the nominees and stuff about the event itself and it's going
to be pod show style you know so I think it should be pretty cool let's see so anyway yes so
I met with you know doing some meetings with the folks on our network which is really one of the
main reasons for me to be here and then there was the awards the pod cast awards and I think
well I know the show girls won for best general pod cast whatever that means so I wanted to go
and you know clap and cheer for him and it was really weird because they're not doing it at the hotel
this year they're doing it at the convention center itself and the room is so big it's like an
airplane hanger but like a really really big one and this is bigger than wing commander Williams
thing it would probably fit in that three times it's just huge and even though they had a stage
they you know they had a couple lights set up and a backdrop and they were doing the awards there
and the sound was kind of shitty because it was hard to fill the room without booming and echoing
and just not not great acoustics and just weren't enough people in there to fill it up I mean
you need five times the amount of people and there were hundreds at least it was more like a photo
off you know it was it was weird it you know when you say a award show I'm like I want a red carpet you
know I want some fanfare I want an acceptance speech you know that's what you I want
fucking Joan Rivers to be there to create to critique when I'm wearing you know I was ready
it wasn't there anyway hooked up with the dawn and drew I love those two they came back to the
room here and we did an episode of the dawn and drew show which was fun I had never done that
with them before and we had a good time it was definitely a blast so I'm a little bit drained from the
entire experience but I'm as I said I'm here I'm having a good time I've got a skip G said
I bumped into him he gave me a USB powered lava lamp which I have right here on the table I'm
I'm set you know what you know what really make this complete right now this moment while I'm in
the vibe with you seeing it is it's a food bar Friday I would just love to have
young bullets hit tests
hey Adam this is a hit test number 89 and this is intro number one right
down a street like down a this is number two rolling stones you know is it
oh I can't remember it's maybe with Michael Jackson number three
all right my brain really hurts now young this is not good I have not done well my friends and
time's up and this is answer number one from 1982 this is weeks in company and you know how
to your world yeah yeah even though I got it wrong I'm happy to hear this song
rock your world weeks in company at answer number one
and this is answer number two which are 1984 the Rolling Stones
number of the night and number two the Rolling Stones and on the cover of the night
and this is answer number three and it's from 1989
oh righty the answers to this hit test and also the links to the music and iTunes so you can
buy these tracks can be found at hittestapacho.com and it's also the place to dig the show
next week I'll be back for a new hit test and it will be number 90 so until then take care and bye bye
hit test and she will.com info young bullet.com J&POLGT.com
young fantastic job my friend I got like half a star there I only got the Rolling Stones
right everything else I had wrong you know it's so tempting sometimes like me you know if I
just I could listen to this to the file you know and I could find out what it is but that I would
be like cheating he's so incredibly wrong okay here we got to talk about it's all kinds of
ends to wrap up a zeitgeist crap and TSA and I have some fun before the food bar Friday is over
and of course some awesome music for you. Hey what's up Adam this is major in jMac and
throw the staff over here at hoodhype.com got another track man that we featured on the show
before that I think your listeners would enjoy man this is the artist named Gazi he's out of
the San Francisco Bay area the name of the track is called remember check it out man yeah and
major does listen to the show yes I do 1976 I remember this on the time pass since
dwelling on an irony of how it all began how my men pop and like that they're again in the second
floor flat out in portrayal hill fairly tall enough to peer over the window sill and I can still
remember how I feel to ride my new big wheel what big enough to push it up the hill before I
knew the value of a dollar bill I was shung it wide out of roads and tie that's funny how
time flies and you don't even notice for your mama sick on the school help notice before I ever
thought about life in the business remember double touch girls around the corner down the
black belly knee high knee high playing hot touch breaking on cardboard hugging on my
crotch on a black totally hot couch getting to dark in my T.I. black suit in my Nike court
heads back in 1984 with Ronald Reagan was Chris and it think that was way back when
round 10 I found rap in the eighth minute same since then
just in that year my life yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we were so young and
hey yeah it's a tough y'all I put it up in between two and like in seventy three I've been
I knew I was going and I knew what I wanted to be and in two time I could tell you
line for line for the vocals that I spit I wanted to shine and time when I said it to my mama
when we credit but a wage on my music never stopped till I get it on some while out three
under morning studio session on some height to get in pain for all this aggression and time
I planed on my own maybe I just hit the road visit all the places and travel through all the
different goals I'm in a different zone and I'm feeling right at home you ain't gotta prove nothing
face me when you're all alone we had a pack when we cut it in blood we learn faster than an average
out of choice what we growing up we had it sold up now I sit back and relax say a damn if I could go back
yeah yeah yeah yeah thank you seventy six black child F.C. Pink white bridge projects I had to go
and I'm broke family medical valley childrens now the guy built it I'm living good in the hood
puff up my back foot rolling them old school cars we in the jaw remember wanting him my back y'all
I'm living good y'all yeah I just want a girl I just had a son I'm about to have a wife I'm about to
switch my life right and wrong wrong the right move wife me the house and my son need brand new
nights brand new bikes can't I like this at night satellite television watching the fight brand new
I just sit back you reminisce all the good times in the bed remember this for the cold weather
sky turn a sunshine and the things that we did man I blow your mind it was all good we were so young
we had the girls and the drinks man we dropped funds it's a new day now we got to move on I do it all
over again it's been so long
Ooh, you said that yeah, my love.
Yeah, you're, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
All that we did.
We were so young and yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's such a long, long time.
Guazan featuring Asia.
Remember, thanks to the hood hype brothers?
Nice, guys.
Thank you very much, it's beautiful.
I agree. I think the audience of this program will be somewhat turned on by
Nice sort of the M. It's kind of a weird Friday. It feels like 5 a.m. on Saturday.
Away to minute. That's what my body feels. Yeah, it's 930 p.m. here in Ontario, California.
And of course, 665 and 666 we talked about as I'd guys the movie and what people mistakenly
call my conspiracy theories on any conspiracy. I'm just following the money. I'm just looking
for just looking at, looking at for me, looking at for you, you know?
This is Tony and Haskell North Carolina. And I just wanted to thank you for bringing up the subject of the
zeitgeist movie. I had not seen that and found it very interesting. I've been wanting to
present it to other people that I know, but I think that the first part of the film with Haskell
really just slammed on it. A lot of people were not turned off and not wanting to continue watching it.
I've been introduced to these ideas, the conspiracy ideas. I think 30 years ago when I was
a teenager, I wasn't that old. And I kind of put it aside over 30 years, but I've
pulled it back to the, to the red bill moment that I think most of it's pretty accurate.
And I appreciate your perspective and I hope you've got to continue with your red bill
on the film subject. Anyways, thank you very much. Bye bye.
You know, so a couple things, first of all, yeah, I can understand where the religious
start of zeitgeist the movie zeitgeist the movie.com. I can understand where that is,
that might spark, I think they put it in there intentionally to also kind of titulate
and get people riled up and then maybe you're a little bit, maybe you're a little more susceptible
to information when you're emotional, which is how commercials work by the way, you know,
emotional, emotion could be happy, could be sad, could be angry, could be frightened,
and then the minute you're in your emotion mode, you can slip in all kinds of information
into people's heads. It's brain hacking. The other thing I noticed is, listen to Skyman.
This is awesome. You could totally be Elvis.
I appreciate your perspective and I hope you've got to continue with your red bill on the film
subject. Anyways, thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Do you hear that?
Maybe it is Elvis. How was could be out there listening?
Well, there are people who disagree, of course.
Adam, come on. I'm so sick of you being with this conspiracy bullshit. It sucks bullshit.
It is such bullshit.
They did not blow up the building. I'm so sick of everybody, but these conspiracy theories
and, ah, every podcast you talk about, they blew up the building. Come on.
You're smarter than that.
Oh, man.
It's all right, my brother. I know you're in a blue pill moment. It's okay. I love you.
Those of us swallowing the red pill love you severely.
Hey, hey, this is John from Dallas. First off, episode 66 Iron Maiden.
That's the soundtrack to my life right there, but I like what John does with the hit test,
but it's really a lot of dance music and stuff that I don't normally listen to.
So, hearing something like Bruce screaming on your show, nice, nice stage.
Second thing, all the stuff about these zeitgeist movie and the conspiracy theories and all that stuff.
Okay, I think listening to some of this, I think the truth actually somewhere in the middle.
I think they, because zeitgeist boys kind of went a little overboard with that whole chip thing.
But as far as following the money to find out what's really going on, yeah, that's definitely a valid idea.
I think anybody that has a pulse that can think for themselves in any way whatsoever,
can pretty well figure out that the crap we were told about the whole Iraq war doesn't add up.
And there's another reason behind it, and we don't know what it is because, you know, they just want to keep us stirred up about, you know, muslims and terrorism and all this crap in the real reason.
Is, is hidden underneath all that and trying to just be interested in getting a little discussion going about, you know,
I think we need to go stuff fires with the, you know, the one world order and the world government chips and all that crap.
I don't think, I think that's another smoke screen.
But what's really going on here, you know, I just kind of got me thinking about some things and really appreciate you picking it up.
All right, bro, talk to you later, man.
No, man, no, absolutely sanity there in the middle. Thank you. Very nice.
You know, and this is not, I play a game with Patricia all the time because she's, you know, she hears me, she hears me talking and she says,
Now I told you what she's, what she thought about Iraq, she said, now that was just something, you know, that was just,
Oh, no, actually 911. So that was something between the Bush family and the bin Laden family.
Something fucked up there. She said, that's just families, you know, who don't give a shit,
playing out their anger. And I trust my wife's opinion and viewpoint a lot of stuff and sometimes all things being equal,
the simplest answer could probably well be the truth.
So, but the game I play is just work backwards, okay. So, you know, we were in Iraq, why?
Well, was it because of September 11th? Well, no, because that was a sum of bin Laden.
All right, so you can already start asking questions there.
You know, some of the, what I would say is pretty good proof Alan Greenspan said, we were there for oil, okay. Why were there for oil?
Well, you know, now you start to ask questions again.
At every single step in this game is you work backwards.
You're going to have to answer certain questions and there's multiple paths you can take play it play it.
You know, so let's say why why did they go to Iraq? Well, because Saddam Hussein was a trouble maker, okay.
So, how did he become a trouble maker? Well, did we not support him as the US 10 years before that? Well, yeah, we did, you know, more questions to be asked.
I still recommend you go out and read Legacy of Ashes, the history of the CIA.
Tim Weiner, I think this is his name.
It's a good book. It's a tough one to get through, but I did finish it and it just shows you.
It just shows you how our government has worked for the past 30, 40 years with its clandestine operations.
And, you know, this is all the entire book is all from documents obtained under the Freedom of Information Act,
and then the guys are reputable writers, so I'm going to have to presume it's done properly, or at least pretty close.
So that's all I'm doing, man. Just follow in the money, listen to the story, and I think we all just need to keep our eyes open.
And remember, if America really wants troops to be withdrawn from Iraq or anywhere, we should be able to make Congress do that.
I don't know if we're sitting around waiting for something to happen, but right now is not happening. So that's kind of weird.
You know what I'm saying? Are we exercising our rights properly? It doesn't feel like it.
Maybe we're just not going about it the right way, but there's something messed up. It seems to me like everyone wants to withdraw or at least change something.
It seems like it's just not happening. It shouldn't be that way. There should be a way that our representatives take care of business.
Or maybe it's just not the majority of the country. That's what it kind of seems like.
And if you point on that, please, let me know. In fact, let me give you a phone number to call.
Gosh, I miss my equipment back home or at the condo. Nice compression.
4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 16, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3, plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 16, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3.
Actually, John called back and had some choice words to kick off the next conversation.
AC, hey, John from Dallas again. I left off one thing in my last comment.
Scott thought the writing corpse of the TSA.
Dude, let me listen to that again.
Oh, I went down the wrong dude. Oh, listen to that.
What is it? This is in my last comment.
Scott thought the writing corpse. Dude, what?
Scott thought the writing corpse. Nice.
You remember the whole John Walker American Taliban incident two years ago?
Oh, you want to know fly list?
I have to be traveling on that day by air.
I have never in my life experienced the kinds of things that I experienced that day.
And I definitely gained a new appreciation and understanding for how a people still
being racially profiled or any kind of profile.
Living on the US, I've never experienced that before.
And it was a real eye opener.
And once again, fuck the TSA right in the fucking ass.
Wait a minute.
Oh, man. I'm sorry.
Anger is a beautiful thing, isn't it?
Hi, Adam. I'm Janice from New York.
Hey, John.
If you want to rail against the TSA and what doesn't make sense,
there are two things that you fail to mention.
One is always flying from Europe left summer and seem to me that you fly from Europe.
You don't have to take off your shoes.
It's kind of an American today.
Yeah, it's totally.
When I flew to Chicago, it was really busy at the take off your shoe line
because at Heathrow first you go through the metal detector and your bags go through.
And then you walk into, you know, they trap you into the fucking duty free area.
It's set up that way.
So you have to walk through the Dolce Gabbana crap.
And that's where they have their shoe x-ray, a separate shoe x-ray.
And it was busy.
There was a guy that just stands in, you know, you guys can just walk on by.
And he was like picking out, you know, where I thought was,
it doesn't look like a shoe bomber.
So you can just send that person off the left completely stupid.
Doesn't make a whole lot of sense since the shoe bomber was flying to the US
from Europe not the other way around.
I flew from Israel last summer and knew how security conscious Israel is.
Yeah.
I didn't have to take off my shoes.
So anyway, that's kind of ridiculous.
The other is, I'm a high school chemistry teacher.
And actually anyone who's taken high school chemistry probably can tell you that
if you want to blow something up, you don't need to live with.
Anyway, thanks for showing out of the fight.
Hey, Janice.
So first of all, you should call in more often.
You sound like a really hot chemistry teacher.
Man, I would have taken chemistry if you were my teacher.
You know, I'd be like, I miss Janice.
Could you just help me out with my experiment over here?
And then, you'd have to lean over me.
I'd feel your breath in my neck.
Ah.
Oh, if only it could be 15 again.
Um, alright.
Thank goodness there's a red pill on this whole TSA thing.
This is good.
Hey Adam, this is Sean J.
I'm having some honest issues.
I'm going to leave you as the same semester.
I'm instead of the long-winded one that you probably just waited for.
Yeah.
I did, by the way.
We're going to the whole security, airport security issue.
Something that has never really discussed that has been bugging me for a very long time.
It's almost right after September 11th.
Um, deals with that whole issue.
My wife is a flight attendant for Southwest Airlines, which is domestic.
So when things had happened, we didn't worry as much because our planes just
They didn't hold it up fuel.
They weren't going long haul.
The censored censors.
We weren't really worried about somebody taking a Southwest Airlines plane.
Um, but the thing that nobody talks about is that it would be impossible today to take over
an airplane with box cutters.
No matter how many people you had on the airplane.
Um, the reason that they were able to do it before September 11th is that nobody had ever used an airplane as a weapon.
Now, I want you to listen to this guy really closely.
He is so right.
See, he's so right.
Okay.
This was the big difference.
No one had used an airplane as a weapon.
That's very different from bringing weapons on board or trying to destroy an aircraft.
So listen to this.
This is really, this is good.
I'm so glad he brought this up.
He used an airplane as a weapon.
And, you know, the world protocol for terrorists on an airplane was to let them do their thing.
Let them land.
Uh, they would let people go eventually or, you know, worst case scenario kill everybody on the plane,
which is yeah, it's terrible.
But nobody would ever fly a plane into a building.
Well, that has changed.
In fact, it changed so quickly.
The attitude changed so quickly that during the attacks of September 11th, one of the planes
was not allowed to shoot the weapon.
So there's no way that, you know, regardless of my fingernail clippers, even a bomb on a plane is yet terrible
and you could blow up a lot of people.
But it's not going to have the terrorist effect of destroying something like a national monument or building.
Yeah, you know, I am so down with that.
I think you're so right.
Because after pan and 103, we didn't have all this fucking TSA crap.
You know, and that probably was the last really big American attack on American citizens
that brought a plane down.
And you're so right, you know, that was, in essence, that was pretty much a failed mission because
you know, you could take proper credit for it.
I know that sounds really crass, but it's true.
You know, we found out later that some Libyan guy had done it.
Maybe Codafi did it himself, doesn't matter.
You know, it's like, you know, no heroes there on that one.
No lasting point except for images.
So absolutely, that was the, you know, I had forgotten about this myself.
That was the big game changer, like holy crap.
Here we are.
We've been, you know, walking people through airport security, which, of course, was a joke before 9-11.
And, and here's some fucker who's so smart, just like learn how to fly a plane in Florida.
You know, yeah, okay, they had box cutters, whatever, but they overpowered the crew.
That's not that hard.
Pilots are usually pretty wimpy.
And, and then they use the pole plane as the weapon.
No need to smuggle anything on board.
Yet, all of this personal security stuff has gotten really tight.
And you could not, could not nowadays take over an airplane without heavy, heavy artillery, essentially.
You can't get into the cockpit.
People aren't going to let you take over a plane.
And, to even search us and go through the whole thing, if you think about going through security,
imagine what you would feel like.
It's actually currently, I think, an active terrorism in itself.
Imagine what you would feel like going through security if you just have to walk through.
You know, put your change in the bucket and walk through and then scan your bag.
You know, you don't have to take out your laptop.
You know, imagine how smoothly and happy you would feel getting on an airplane.
Just walking through that, you're not going to worry about the airplane blowing up.
We never did before in airplanes blew up.
No.
People are not going to be able to use airplanes as weapons.
And that nobody talks about that anymore because we have to stay scared, I guess.
Yeah.
And it's really frustrating to hear all this.
When there's no way that it's, I just don't think that it's possible.
I knew if I'm going to have kind of been upset about from day one that people never.
Yeah, shit.
Then you ran out of time.
That was three minutes.
But that was one of the best three minutes I've heard in a long time on this program.
Thank you, my friend.
You're so right.
Red pill within the red pill.
You nailed it, man.
You totally nailed it.
That's it.
It's that simple.
You know, this has nothing to do with 9-11.
And yeah, I've heard all the threats.
But nothing has really happened in that fashion.
So maybe that's because of the security.
I don't know.
But I just like some consistency.
Yeah.
I mean, I can think of a million scenarios.
Dude, you can get a boat.
And you can get out in near JFK.
You can get out on the lake.
And you're too into fucking stinger.
Missile any aircraft at any time.
You know, let's open our eyes up just a little bit.
So while that was playing, I was surfing around.
I was thinking of playing, of winding up today's show with
the dead pennede's moon-over-main, which is on the
Podsight music network now.
But I'm in a different kind of mood.
Here's something that I had not played in a long time.
Typically, I played this song, or I've played this song
I've played this song when I leave somewhere, when I leave a, when I've left radio stations
or left a country, and it's not particularly a happier sad song, it's just something
from the soundtrack to my life, and it's, I don't know, maybe it's because of the camaraderie
that I'm feeling right now with the sort of the tribute to some friends of mine.
God, I love this, this is so good.
This is Jackson Brown with a loadout. Enjoy, it's long, but you'll dig it.
Now the seats are on empty, let the road east take us to, pack it up and tear it down.
The first to come, and the last to me, working for that little way, there'll sit up in another town.
Tonight the people were still alive, they waited in their mind, when they got up on the feet
and made the show.
And that was sweet, but I can hear a sound of swimming doors and full of cheers,
that the sound they'll never know.
Roll them cases out of them if they're mixed,
and haul them trussers down and get them up their ramps.
Just when it comes to moving me, you know you guys are the chance,
but when the last guitar's been packed away, you know that I still want to play.
So just make sure you got all set to go before you come from my piano.
But the bands on the bus, and they're waiting to go, got it dry all night,
and do the shopping to cargo, or to train, and I don't know.
With their soul many shows and low, and these towns all look the same.
We're just past the time in little hotels, and wander around backstage,
to those nights come up, and we hear that crowd, and they remember why we came.
I figured out why I went to the song, to be shared with you,
because it's my life right now.
I've got to do that show in Chicago, it is my life, now we got it.
Country and Western, all the buss, all the way, we got this room.
It attracts me, because that's the studio.
We've got a rural season magazine, and we've got truckers on C.P.
And we got a rich and prior on the video.
Time to think of the ones we love, while the miles go away.
The only time that seems too short, is the time that we get to play.
If you've got the power of what we do, you can sit there and wait for you to throw us through.
Come along, sing the song, you know that you can go around,
because when the Lord and Son comes speaking down,
you're on a wake-up in your town,
the bill is scheduled to appear.
A thousand miles away from here, people stay.
Still a little bit longer.
But we won't play in just a little bit longer.
What if don't mind?
And if you don't mind?
If you take a little time, and if you do all the hasn't,
why most are all what you stay?
Just a little bit longer.
Please, please, please, say you well, say you well.
Oh, what do you think?
Just a little bit longer.
Oh, yeah.
I love this song.
And it's really about you.
You're listening.
Paul and we're going to touch you.
You're on the network.
We're an advertiser.
We're all connected in one way.
Some in many ways.
I love it.
Thank you.
I'm going to have a fun.
Remember, it's not a dress rehearsal.
It's a real deal.
All right, everybody.
I'll see you after the weekend when I'm back in there.
Foggy, hold the button.
And I'll buy now.
Oh, yeah.
I love you.
This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your fruit-quick blog from GoDaddy.
The best and the brightest served up daily by the shoppest minds in content delivery,
punch-show and lightweight.