A domain registration is a gift that keeps on giving.
For all the peaks in your life, do your shopping at godaddy.com.
Listen to this podcast for a special code that you can use to get special discounts at godaddy.com.
You're traveling through another dimension.
A dimension not only of sight and sound, but of mind.
A journey into the wondersland whose boundaries are that of imagination.
You unlock this door with the key of imagination.
Beyond it, another dimension.
A dimension of sound.
A dimension of sight.
A dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land of both shadow and substance of things and ideas.
There's a fifth dimension beyond that which is known to man.
It is a dimension as vast as space and as timeless as infinity.
It is the middle ground between light and shadow, between science and superstition,
and it lies between the pit of man's fears and the summit of his knowledge.
This is the dimension of imagination.
That's a signpost of a head, your next stop.
The Delta Sierra, Charlie.
Five, seven, nine.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just in here as a free.
So I can play the role of the world.
You're safe, you're right, you're right.
You're inside, yeah.
You're mine, you're the loyal one.
You're down, down, and I won.
You're mine, you're blue.
I'm so down and down, and I won.
I promise that I've got to try and quit.
You're watching me just my way.
You're me, me, me, me.
Plus a thousand million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
You're playing those little monsters, hey, hey.
I'm lying down and down, I won.
You're blue.
The world is the world
Showdown in the sky
Made in the world
You're the world
And I know all
The world is the world
Sometimes a song could just say it all
Can it?
Back on the way
It's bubble
Hey everybody how you doing
Coming to you from
Beverly Hills
California
That's right
So Cal for a change
It's the Daily Source Code
Episode number five
Nowadays it's for you
It's Tuesday
Yeah
April 10
An extra day added to my
Stay out here
In California on the west coast
Wasn't quite prepared for it
Which of course means
You know I have everything timed
All right
Running on empty my friends
If you know what I'm saying
Very low
We're down to seeds and stems
Once again
Oh boy
Sorry about yesterday
Typical typical
Oh man
It started on Sunday
We had a video project
That the fabulous fat man
Was working on
With the
The Boise Mafia
In Idaho
Believe me it's all code
That people at Pod Show
And he felt ill
Which sucks
Sucks ass
Because something in his inner ear
And it's like vertigo
And it's really hard to do video editing
When you're not
When you get queasy
And just from breathing
So that meant that we had to gather
All kinds of assets
Burn them on a DVD
So most of Sunday
Was actually spent doing that
Didn't get to tell you about
About Saturday
Went out and bought some clothes
Yeah
Do you know how
Hard it is to find
34 waste and 36 in scene
It is almost impossible
The only thing available
Is either
Custom Taylor made
Which
I don't know
I'm not looking for that
I just want some cool pants
You know
What are my other options?
Well
They did have
36 34
That was presented to me several times
Finally
Yeah
I did find a store
What was the name of that store
Which I threw the bag out
If you're in San Francisco on market
You go past the mall
You go past the house
A blue jeans and you go past
Like all of a sudden
The neighborhood changes
And the street kind of gets a little smelly
And there was like
It's a men's designer
And I hung a left right in
And I was in the middle of
Hip Hop heaven man
I tell you
So I scored me some pants
That I'm sure Patricia will never let me wear
Never let me wear
And so not in my suitcases
There's 75 pounds in weight
It's just unbelievable
Anyway
Flu to Los Angeles
Sunday afternoon
Got in
And of course
Because of all this mess up
Had to start downloading stuff
Have you ever
Try to rely on a hotel network
I mean even the Beverly Hills hotel
Which is
Where we usually stay
When we're in
In LA
It just sucks man
I know that after midnight
When finally
Whoever was downloading porn
Stop doing it
I was able to download a lot of stuff
Pretty quickly
I had
Ten
I think at least
Fifty megabyte files
I was downloading simultaneously
And I know that
I was crunching the whole hotel
That works
So it was a little bit of
A little bit of revenge
That I got
But oh man
It's so horrible
When by the time you're done
It's like three in a morning
Get up at seven
We got our first meeting
And
I will tell you about
Some of these meetings
Rather interesting
These are all upon
Invitations
But first
An email from Cassandra
Hey Adam
On
Daily source code episode
Five
Seventy-eight
That was the Fubar Friday
From No Cal
You said it
And I just had to send it to you
Haha
That's right
How did I
How did I start
Oh that's right
It was the word phenomena
I kept saying phenomena
And then phenomena
And then I went into phenomena
Or was it
Manamana
Hit it
This makes you happy
Doesn't it?
A day just starts right
Manamana
When you hear this song
I know you know the lyrics
Let's go crazy
Manamana
hit hit hit hit hit hit hit
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
Come on.
Yeah.
Banana.
Come on.
Yeah.
Banana.
The Muppets, the Minamena, saw him.
Wonderful.
Bravo.
I love that.
I'll find the song on YouTube for a cell phone.
I'll put a link in the show notes.
To be found at dailysourcecode.com.
It was awful.
Come away.
Boom.
I missed those two old guys.
Yeah.
Sorry for breaking the podsafe code of conduct.
Oh, speaking of which.
I just saw that today.
The famous A-Lister.
Tim O'Reilly.
Let me just see if I can find this link for you.
Actually suggested a, you know, this thing that's been going around ever since the Kathy Sierra.
Configuration.
He suggested a code of conduct.
And this thing just it literally had me rolling.
About the things we we should and should not do.
Which include don't say anything online.
We wouldn't say in person, please.
We connect privately before before we respond publicly blah blah blah.
When we believe someone is unfairly attacking another we take action.
This is like it's like the king is dead.
Long live the king.
You know, it's like what happened to the the anarchistic part of the web.
Believe me.
Believe me when I say, oh, he's never even as a badge.
Civility enforced.
It's pathetic, dude.
This is not the way it's going to go.
It's going.
I keep saying it's going to get a whole lot worse before gets any better.
Because we're just exercising these muscles would just figuring out that the old
added really is true that the pen is much much
Mightyer than the sword and free speech.
You want it.
Dude.
You've got it online.
Now, of course, that doesn't mean that you can go and threaten people.
But this is what happens.
What happens when you get your 15 minutes.
Everything is going to come true that these guys predicted from Andy Warhol.
Right down to the the pen is Mightyer than the sword.
Who wrote that?
Mark Yoshimura Namkov.
I think.
So I have to DJ here from Australia.
Hey.
All my songs are up on the pod save music network.
And whenever a song is played on a podcast, I download the show that it was played on and have a listen.
And I'll often subscribe to that show.
Well, is one that came through just a day or two ago.
Have a listen to it.
Interactive issues.
Yeah.
I don't know what language that is, but it's not Russian, but sounds very similar.
But made me think of you.
Anyway, have a good one.
I do.
I sounded like a Italian.
I'm not sure, but that burp.
I definitely influenced that.
And I'm damn proud of it.
Listen, because the guy actually he burps.
And then he says something something podcasting moment.
Which can only mean that this is a true sign of a real podcast.
Turn this on.
Do it.
Let's hear it again.
I'm a dickie.
Yeah.
podcasting moment.
podcasting moments.
Funko popular.
Fantastic.
I got nailed it to airport security.
Gosh, it's been going so well with my lighters.
I don't know if you heard me lighting up the match.
Beverly Hills Hotel, man.
They give you like a book of matches, which is really fancy and stuff.
But it only has like 15 matches in it.
And they're really high quality.
Yeah.
I usually put my lighter behind my creative labs.
PC, PCI.
I was a PC card, which is my external sound card, which I plug into my via.
Whenever I'm going to record a show, which of course leads into cast blasts or
does all that beautiful stuff.
Because when you place the lighter behind a piece of electronics, they can't really identify
it.
And that's been working for me for a couple of months.
And they'd certainly nail me at SFO on the way to LAX.
And they knew it, man.
From the minute the scan happens, like, lighter.
Oh, shit.
So not only down to stems and seeds, but down to wood and sulfur, it's getting pretty bad.
So we were here upon invitation.
And we're staying an extra day because there's a number of people we want to meet.
By the way, the last I forget at the top of the show, Sharon Bam.
You know them as the producers and share, of course, as the host of the Rock and Old TV show with the song Holly
would down and out and Hollywood man, just perfect song.
I love with those guys.
They do it under the Moniker bubble.
There's a link in the show notes to that at dailysourcecode.com.
So I'm here in my room.
And if you can hear it, I don't have the my normal processing stuff.
So you can, you know what?
I have quite a long wire.
We haven't done this in a while.
Let's see if I can take it outside.
I'm carrying the hot.
Now this is about as far as we'll go.
The high LPR 40.
I'm now standing on the balcony.
See if I can pick up any sounds for you.
So quiet here.
It's fantastic.
I'm overlooking the tennis court.
You can hear a little bit of road noise off in the distance, but just barely.
It's really nice.
I'm on a good side of the hotel this time.
So despite no ban with this pretty good.
We hear an invitation from two talent agencies.
Creative artists.
Agency and the William Morris Agency both.
Want to represent us.
And you got to understand how Holly would work.
The guys that do the packaging.
So it's not like we're going to get an already fly shirt type agent who's going to
run around and teels for us.
But let me explain how it works.
So a company like Creative artists represents represent a lot of people.
They represent Steven Spielberg.
They also represent Hasbro Toys.
And what they do is they'll say, let's see.
We've got Hasbro Toys.
Hasbro, what do you guys have coming up?
We've got this, this, you know, we've had this pretty successful line of toys.
It's called a Transformers.
Oh, that's what we got Steven Spielberg.
Why don't we do the Transformers the movie?
And then they go and they get the script and they get the writers and the readwright and
they get the funding and they put it all together.
And so the things that that we've been talking about.
Really threefold, I guess.
One is how can we help our shows and our producers.
They can't export and syndicate into other avenues.
And how can we get some of their clients?
And they have between the two of them.
They have just about everybody in Hollywood.
How can we bring them into our world?
Because we know they want to come and they're telling us that.
Not not not not the Hollywood celebrities and superstars.
And I'm not talking just about actors and TV host.
I'm talking about authors, comedians, people who are on the talking circuits.
I mean, there's just tons of people who are extremely interesting and
really want to break into independent media.
Realize that the kind of money they may be used to or they think that they can
command in the traditional world is at this point probably not possible.
And independent media, but they really want to go for it.
They just want to go with a company that's got their shit together.
And so it really surprises they call us.
And tomorrow at tomorrow we're just going to hang out and meet with a couple of people.
I've been trying to get a whole of these g-living dude.
Have you ever seen that show?
G-living live?
This green stuff, man.
It's really, really taken off.
That's such an incredible industry in the green living space.
Speaking of sucking.
Comic strip.
I found the jingle again, can you tell?
Hello, I'm Kerry.
Hello.
Here is comic strip.
Blogger from comicsstable.com.
You know, you know it very well that you are surrounded by escises, brown noses.
And these people are blinding your view to the reality and the real problems of podcasts
and so on.
And also everybody is sucking up to you.
Yes.
So I have to tell you.
Fuck you.
If you're kind of helping in this issue, this issue is there.
Let me tell you.
This is the approach that my parents taught me as well.
This is the way to get things done in life.
You set someone up and say, look, your ass is being kissed.
If you don't help me, fuck you.
You've got my attention.
I have purchased a domain for a new podcast that I would like to make.
And I have sent you the name of this domain.
And also I have sent a question to the support of Podshow.
So shortly speaking, I have a domain, internet domain.
Something something something cast.com.
And now I would like to host podcasts on Podshow.com.
Your service, but I would like to have this podcast to be on your own domain.
Something similar to your daily source code.com.
Daily source code.com is serviced by Podshow.com.
And I have sent the DNS service for this domain to ns1.com
and ns2.potshow.com.
And in the control panel in Podshow.com, I have sent the two children to this domain,
but it is not working, please.
Please help me out.
You help me.
See you on May 8th.
Hopefully after I've helped you.
And at the time, show it to me this day.
Yeah, I do.
I think that's going to work out CSB on May 4th because the lady Patricia is going to be going
all that week.
So I know I'm going to be in the UK.
I'll just have to clear it with the lady Christina with the pod daughter.
Let me just check this man because that's supposed to work.
I'm not sure what the problem is.
But from the very beginning, we made sure that you could map a domain name to your podshow
show site.
Let me just see.
Is it under show info?
I think.
Let me just check.
Yeah.
I think you're not supposed to point the domain name service to our servers.
I think.
Let me just see if it says anything about that basic information.
And description.
I know it works.
Oh, here it is.
Do you have a shit.
I'm sorry.
Just click the way from it.
Let me just read what it says.
Here we go.
Do you have an existing website for your show, indicate the full URL here, and then you
have to add a domain.
I'm pretty sure you have to point it to our servers, but not to our DNS servers, CSB.
But I am looking at this.
I know when you sign up.
And when you create a new show that it is explained.
In fact, you can even buy a GoDaddy domain name with a discount when you sign up to podshow.
And it'll map automatically.
But I can see here that you're right.
The askcissors have done a horrible job.
What they have not done is they have not made it clear when you go back and want to add
a domain name.
Okay.
I'll look into that for sure.
And we've got this big move coming up.
I already hear the data slip that was supposed to be the Friday, the 13th, the 13th of April.
This coming Friday.
The day coincidentally when I go on vacay, leaving for Tanya Rifei going on vacation.
It's slip I think until maybe Monday.
So everyone's crazy busy.
They really are.
And you joke about it CSB, but these people are really fucking smart dude.
And you'll meet a couple of them in the UK on May 4.
Comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip.
Have you ever heard of the whispered Peroles podcast Michelle?
As Blasque I think, host of that show.
It's a very sensual, very erotic show.
She has a fantastic voice.
And she's really, really made my day.
Hey Adam, she writes an email.
What's this crap about you never receiving naked pictures?
Obviously the ones I sent you never reached you.
So here they are again.
As I said previously, now you've seen all the nipples from the whispered Peroles girls.
Hopefully this will brighten up your LA trip a bit.
Cheers from Michelle from whispered Peroles.
Michelle, this did not only cheer up my day a little bit in LA.
This told me that podcasting has arrived when I can create a show on my
Dinky laptop and get naked pictures and return for it.
This is true.
Showbidden this baby and I'm loving it.
And what we need now to end this Charlie is a Hollywood ending.
She's gonna come through, but you can spend your whole life pretending it.
Gonna go let me for you too.
Cause only you.
I'm gonna go let me for you too.
Cause only you know our secret heart.
She doesn't need to be unkind.
And the waiting is not so hard.
What's a little more.
Time.
We are.
For this was something.
I'm smarter than this.
Oh, swallow whatever you like.
We are.
For something.
She's your loveiest weakness.
She was my longest goodbye.
Hey, I know just where you are.
It up, every last word.
And you swore you never let it get this far and you never get hurt.
Hey, I know I can't change your mind.
Like you can't change your heart.
Hey, I know the cliché.
Love is blind, but whom it could be so dark.
We are.
For this was something.
I'm smarter than this.
Oh, swallow whatever you like.
We are.
For something.
She's your loveiest weakness.
She was my longest goodbye.
A heart is trying.
Don't you just love Hollywood and day in the naked tire.
She's gonna come through but you can spend your whole life.
Forstants of today's show brought to you by Tylenol P.M.
Sorry.
But you're done.
You're done.
It's off the hook.
It's like I know that we've been promoting it and promising it for months and months.
We should do that more often.
We should just delay the release because man, everyone just jumped on this thing.
First episode is a smackdown between the satellite repairman, PW Fenton and CC Chapman, a fantastic episode.
And the sponsor, the prize sponsor, no surprise for the prize, is Nokia and the winner of the Bond contest.
Walks away with a Nokia and 800 Internet tablet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Do you heard how that came together?
Christian Leonard Quail said, Adam, I've had my N800 for quite a while now.
I simply love everything about it.
I could give you a list over why I love it but that list is getting too long these days.
Without you I'd never have heard about this fantastic product.
I felt it owed to you to say thanks even though we can contribute to cluttering your mailbox.
Love the show keep on rocking Christian.
No man, I love it.
Thank you very much.
I appreciate it so much.
And as do our sponsors.
There you go.
Nokia, playing with us.
Thank you guys.
That's it for the Daily Source Code for today.
I'm not quite sure.
Yeah, I'll be doing Wednesday's show when I get in.
I think I'm getting in a little bit later than usual but we'll definitely crank out a show for you.
So tomorrow as I said, just some meetings and then then I'm off.
By the way, if you go to acurry.com, I have a little Twitter box there.
And I'm basically using it as kind of a broadcast mechanism and letting you guys know where I am in my in my travel.
Seeing if how that works for you if you get kind of a reality vibe, you know, some kind of connection.
Now that you know what my days are like.
And then you can actually follow along where I am.
So that's it.
Adam at podshow.com.
DailySourceCode.com.
No lighter click today.
So I'll crap it went out.
Talk to you tomorrow.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest.
It is served up daily by the sharpest minds and content delivery podshow in my light.