Dromatically reduce ambient noise by up to 85% with Sony's noise cancelling headphones
and work home or travel, shut out the noise and really enjoy your tracks, get yours at
Sony.com slash headphones, Sony headphones, your music never sounded so good.
I don't know if I'm gonna flip it up, but I'm going to blow it home.
I'm such a jerk of the band with the 70's penis, please come to the bar, because the band
with the 70's penis, please come to the bottom of me, thank you.
I feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it,
feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it
feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, expect it, feel it, feel it, feel to feel it, feel it, let it be, have that, then, hit, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel the feel, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feeling it, feeling it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel the, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel the feel, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it
episode number 694 last show for this week coming to you from the Curry condo in Northern
California. It's been a beautiful day today. It's been quite a busy week as you can imagine
of course. It's been the delayed, say, source code once again with only three shows pumped
out. I still not too bad considering the only two nights that I didn't do a show. Of course,
I'm doing them in the evening, which means it's still technically football Friday and Australia
by the time you guys are listening to this. The two nights I didn't make it as because I
went to bed at 9 o'clock 9.30. First night I slept until 6.30. That was perfect. And then
Wednesday night for Thursday show. I just got back from the office and I was like,
I'm sorry, not back from the office. No, no, no, no, no. There was Wednesday night for Thursday
show. That's right. I had dinner with Natalie Delcante. Oh, yes. And I was home at 9.30 and
one stretching bed alone. I wasn't so lucky though. I woke up at 4.30. So that was this morning.
It's just, it's been crazy. It really has. And of course, Friday, very special football Friday,
engineering. I think it's Kevin O and Pavel are probably Andrew Grummit. I don't know the whole
engineering team as far as I'm concerned. They're going to be presenting V3, V3 is the new version
of poncho.com, which now this is really an internal company presentation. So please don't get too excited.
It's not going to be until the end of January that we expect to have it up and running full and
it's in her full glory. But this has been months and months and months of work to get to this stage.
And it's, I know it's going to be spectacular. Maybe I'll sneak a screenshot or two just to mess
with everybody. Okay, let's start with an easy question for today's food war Friday.
Adam, you've to sell guy Germany. You. Adam, I'm standing in a traffic jam here. Just thinking
away. And I have a question. Do you need to get a separate private license for flying at night?
Or, you know, is it similar? Can you with one license, just fly at night or the flying at night
require a completely different skill sets? Just curious to know, big shout outs to Deep Mar of
Fork, my German colleague, who first got me to iPods broadcasting and all that other stuff. Bye.
All right. Thank you. Thank you. Well, that really depends where you get your license.
But at this point, it's been like six weeks since I've flown. I don't know if I can fly during the
day. I wonder, it's been, I mean, this is really one of the longest periods of gone without
flying. It's just been the schedule. It depends where you get your license. In the United States,
you have to do five hours of night flying for your private pilot's license.
So I did that for rotary, as well as for the helicopters, well as for fixed wing for regular
airplanes. I like night flying. I haven't done any solo. Well, yeah, I think I did two hours solo.
But you know, that's like doing circuits around the airfield. I haven't really done anything
across country any serious nighttime flying. Mainly because that's a lot better to do it in the
States. I would say in general, just considering the weather where we're where I live.
And in other countries, I think in the UK for the CAA license, it's an add-on.
You know, so it kind of depends where you get your license. Do you need a separate set of capabilities?
Yeah, absolutely. Absolutely. That's when I stopped wearing contact lenses. After I did
what my first night flight in the helicopter, and we landed at Antwerp Airport, and then we went back
to the the Curry Castle at the time, landing in the backyard. Then I took out my lenses, put on my
glasses, and I could not believe the difference. There was such a difference in just what I was
able to see, the sharpness. I was like, I never looked. I said, I'm not going to deprive myself
during the day by wearing, actually I did do that. When I had dinner with Natalie, I put in my
lightly blue colored contact lenses. Hey Adam, it's Callie from Geek Brief.
Oh, from one babe to the next. The question on the last DSC about Geek Brief being behind
on Tivo, so I just wanted to fill in the blanks. I've been talking to Potcho HQ about it. The
process is pretty labor and time intensive. On our part, it takes two extra hours to get an episode
Tivo ready and up to Potcho. Then someone at Potcho has to get it into the Tivo system.
Up until a few days ago, it was going through another process with a person at Tivo.
Now it's a little bit more streamlined, but we're still at the mercy of compression and uploads
the bane of my existence. I know you guys are working on it hard. We're working on it too,
and for Tivo cast viewers, I'm thinking it's just kind of a welcome to the joys of early adopted.
I miss you. Let me make it pictures. Did I talk too fast?
Oh, no. But you could send another comment and say that slow or semi-naked picture.
Welcome to the joys of early adopted. I miss you. Let me make it pictures.
Did I talk too fast? Yeah. I got like four different people sending the emails and comments
about this, about how, you know, I've got a comment. Was it last show on Boe Boe Boe, Wednesday show?
That the episode seemed to be behind on Tivo on the Tivo cast. And it is quite a process. I told
you, you know, we've got a, so Callie has to produce, you know, just as one of the shows,
we put as many shows on as possible. I think what we have going up there tonight,
Brian, no semi-neme, I'm about it. Anyway, I'll look for that in a second.
So in the case of Geek Brief, Callie Neal have to produce a, you know, a certain format that works
on television. So it really looks nice on television. That of course also has to be uploaded.
Then I think it goes to Brian, Brian then has to transcode or fruco-romos it.
After he puts in like the, I don't know, the leaders and the PG-14s and all kinds of stuff that
has to go in the Tivo. And indeed, there was another person at Tivo, actually had a part of his work
in the process. I think that's no automated. We're getting better. We're getting there.
But man, being a media company is hard work, isn't it?
Hi Adam, it's Matt from Games Weasel. On this week's show, we've got a review of Super Mario
Galaxy on the Wii. We've also got a little review of the game on the PSP called Deadhead Fred.
We chat to Jerry Seinfeld about his new B movie game and you can win copies of Unreal Tournament 3
for the PC. Check it out at gamesweasel.btpodshow.com.
Really?
Chat with Jerry Seinfeld. Interesting, Mr. Matt Cuddle.
nominated for a gaming media award, or those, have those already passed and did you not win?
I still like the show, like the video version too.
So it's almost hit test number 100. Hit test number 98 to be exact.
And Yon sent me a peculiar email. He said, Adam, here's the hit test number 99,
number 98 for the football Friday. And here is a video version.
So I'm going to play the video. I have no idea what I'm going to be seeing. I'm going to play the video
version and you guys just listen along to it. Because it is part of the Friday festivities.
I see. It's Yon in the studio.
Hey Yon, this is hit test number 98 and this is a special edition.
You look pretty. And let's see if you figure it out. This says intro number one. Hit me.
So, Chris Ria, come on. And it's like one of my favorite songs.
Easy. Yon, you look so interesting from this angle. Number two.
Isn't that Chris, Chris Ria as well? Isn't that Josephine or on the beach?
And this week's final one is number three.
That's on the beach. Oh, it's a Chris Ria special. Okay. So I think it was number one.
Was full of you think it's over. Then it was Josephine and on the beach.
Times up and these are the answers. Okay, hit me. Oh, and by now you can figure out that this is a special Chris Ria
edition of the hit test. This is an number one from 1978. Cool. If you think it's over.
Five, four, if you think it's over, let's just figure it out. Oh, Yon's number one.
Fool, if you think it's over. Yeah. And this is answer number two.
From 1985. This is Josephine. Straight. Straight on my window.
I know the lyrics. Thank you.
I send you all my love, Josephine.
Answer number two, Josephine. And this is answer number three from 1986.
Also, Chris Ria. This is on the beach.
Texting by, to the place, on the beach.
Answer number three on the beach. In this special Chris Ria edition of the hit test.
And it's number 98. So I think did you have them all? Every single one my friend.
So yeah, answers to this hit test. And also the links to iTunes. You can buy these
strikes online. Can be found at hitthest.potshow.com.
So I don't thank you for playing everyone else. Thank you for listening.
And I'll be back next week for number 99. So until then, take care and bye bye.
Oh, I wish you guys could have seen the video version of that. That was absolutely spectacular.
I'm sure young is going to post that at hittest.potshow.com or at what is it?
Yumpulet.com. Why is it so soft?
Oh, that sucks. I was going to be really slick and I was going to play that song for you.
All right, let me maybe if I try, uh, I'm using a new search function we have on on pod show on a sec.
I can't make it any louder than that. That's kind of weird.
Well, that's it. Something in the, no, it's not the connections.
How amateurish is this? Why it feels like a proper food bar Friday?
Oh, I'll see if this is louder. Why is it so soft? Is it something with the,
must be something with the volume control fucking windows, man.
Okay, here we go. It's over here. I found it.
I think I just have to play the song for a second.
We come back.
I just do one chorus together. Okay.
Oh, of course he heard me promoting the Sony headphones.
The new Bluetooth wireless Sony headphones, which apparently are completely awesome.
And you're concerned with sound listening. Your comment is pretty interesting.
I've heard about the new Bluetooth sound that should come in the 2000s, so I'm just curious.
But probably we can't Bluetooth headphones, but they use compression to get the sound into your ears.
And that's especially about with the already compressed sound.
So just curious to know if you know and tell your, or just to google pod breeze and of course,
follow up hell that they are the curry.
I think that was something nasty and Swedish.
You know, that's a very good point. I don't know what the Bluetooth standard is.
I'm not up to speed on that. I had no idea that there's like, you know, some kind of compression
issue or transmission issue and makes it sound crappy. I'd love to have more info on that.
I've refueling comic strip blogger might know.
Oh, man. It's going to be one of those shows. Let's try it again.
Yeah. Oh, how's it going? Adam, it's Jersey Todd, the official musicologist of the
Chacha. Dude, now that I've been the musicologist for a while now,
I feel like it's my obligation to keep my eyes out for some bands that I really want to get up on the
music network. And this week, the band is no exception. The band is semi-precious weapons at
a New York City and I've heard about these guys for a long time. And while they're finally
up on the podcast music network and the weight has been worth it. Check this song out.
It's probably got the best lyric of the year. I can't pay my rent, but I'm fucking gorgeous.
How great is this stuff? Check it out.
I can't pay my rent, but I'm fucking gorgeous.
I got that song that can kill your comrades.
If you want to try, you better come inside.
You can't pay my rent, but I'm fucking gorgeous.
Tell me something I don't know. Tell me something I don't know.
Tell me something I don't know.
I can't get to, can't get to um tutor.
I don't strangle, it's my heart is closed to the moment.
I can't let the fucus check thetes less and less
I know y'all want to be my
But baby, I ain't sick
Don't drag me
It's because my heart is closed
Oh
Tell me something I don't know
If you can't, if you can't, if you can't
I can't, if you can't
Tell me something I don't know
If I could clear the guitar, it would sound like that
Does any freshness weapons?
Tell me something I don't know
I can't pay the rent, but I'm fucking gorgeous
Thank you so much, Jersey Todd
Fantastic selection for the footballer today
Hi Adam, it's John here from Guilford
I don't know if you have any funny sound for Cisco
I've got a question regarding polisher channels
I emailed support, but didn't get him head back from them
Here's a question
I've got a load of channels, and I'm subscribed to podcast
And so by iTunes, I've just come home tonight, and I'm sitting here
And I'm clicking refresh refresh refresh
I know you've already released the SD-693, but I don't see it
I'm still clicking refresh nothing
So then I go to podshow.com, I go to my profile page
I go back to iTunes, click refresh
And right now I've got 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 9 podcasts downloading
So I choose to check every hour, I don't get them every hour
So what's up with that?
Let me know, because I mean, it's a kind of defeat support
Using channels, but I don't get my content when I want it
Cheers man, what must I say?
Yeah, yeah, I'm curry, bolder, red pan
I haven't got color, clearly what color pillar I am
It's nice, it's nice
Cheers mate, yeah, lots of people had this problem
It was very sporadic, so let me see if I can explain it to you
It should be fixed by now, it did take us many days actually
Because we had the thanksgiving holiday
And had like three or four guys jump it on this
Trying to figure it out, here's essentially what happened
So there's a couple of processes
Obviously there's a huge aggregator that goes out
And looks at all the shows that you're subscribed to
And it gets album art and does all kinds of stuff for you
To bring it into either your collection or into your channels
Then there's another process which updates the channels
Because these also all have to be checked
And you can imagine there's quite a few
So this is a couple of machines that do this work
I think I just dedicated to this work
So there was an update to some of the code base
Not quite sure what exactly
An update meaning like some software is upgraded
Whatever happened, these processes weren't started again
It's part of the normal, I guess the servers were rebooted or whatever
And so these processes didn't start or weren't started
It doesn't really matter
So the channels weren't updating
However the channels are engineered
That if you go look at your channels and you click on a channel
Then it's automatically going to update
The minute you hit that page, it doesn't update
So if the update script hasn't hit your channel yet
And it's not just one, it's a whole bunch of these things
If it hasn't hit your channel yet, then the minute you go look at your channels
It automatically does that so that you'll have an enjoyable experience
With the freshest content, the minute you click play
So I guess I don't know what the interval is
But it's not a long time
But since the update process has not been running for
Apparently several days
And it was very hard to troubleshoot
Because I, for instance, wasn't seeing it
Logically because I am always hitting my page, listening to stuff
Looking at what's coming up in my channels
So stuff that was loading onto the
Any 110, it was showing up because I just refresh my channel
But anyway, they move some more hardware in
They start up some extra versions of this process
That has to run through everything
And I believe all channels now up to date
And we're all caught up
Apologies for that
Just all part of the food bar
I added some from Bristol and UK
I'm listening to DSC 693
And it's about the iPhone and the reception
I have one theory, the frequency
That's used for GFM in the United States
Well, I was like, this is about the new story that the iPods
iPhones have poor reception in the UK
And my theory is that they had poor reception in the US too
But there's just less cell towers in the UK
Or more
No, I think in general, I've seen it
I saw it with my own iPhone
And it was the same carrier
It wasn't O2, but I saw it on Vodafone
I saw it on orange, I saw it on a couple different networks
I would put my SIM card in the E61
I would get three or four bars
I put it in the iPhone, I would get no connection
whatsoever, or would come in and out
Very briefly
So that's what this is about
It's another theory apparently
In the UK, we have two networks at 900 megahertz
Which is O2 in Vodafone
And then orange in T-Mobile
He's 1800 megahertz
So the main O2 frequency in the UK
It's going to be a lot different to the US frequency for AT&T
So although the iPhone is triple band
Or maybe it just doesn't work
So well, at the lower frequencies
That would also work if you're plugging it into the dock
Because when you plug it into the dock
You'll be giving it a bigger bit of metal
Therefore, making it antenna bigger
And the lower the frequency, the bigger the antenna should be
Right
That's true
Maybe there's a theory that
Anyway, love the show
Thanks a lot
Yeah, man, thanks
No, I think you're right
That is true
What I can recall, because I did a lot with the
With illegal transmitters and ham radios
Sideband
12 watts, PEP, blast and out
On the high jack upper channels
Anyone remember that?
You cut the diode leading to the chip
And all of a sudden, instead of 240 channels
You had, no, instead of 120 channels
You had 240 channels, because you had like this whole upper limit
Near the near the 10 meter band
God, I'm going back in time
Is a geek R9
Yeah, so if the lower the frequency
The bigger the antenna
Interesting theory
That really could be something to that for sure
Adam is a woman
Hey, Robin
Want to call and say, let's start talking predictions for 2008
I know it's early, but I'm starting early
All right
Okay
You're of the killer app
No, I want to talk about the killer device
I thought the apple iPhone was going to be that device
Which can get podcasts on it
And I can't download
You can
Oh, okay
Get it on your device
So that's me
There's not satisfying my needs for podcasts
I know there's podcasts
Ready, I know there's my potter
I know there's our tools
But I still haven't seen the device
And they did the Nokia
And I'd like to know more about what you talked about
When you're over there
And I hope it's not just about advertising for their device
But actually, if I'm giving them some input on what you would like to see
And what I would like to see
Oh, no man, it was all about benefit and money for pod show
There was nothing else
You think I'm going over there going to tell those guys something?
Nah, I'm just there to benefit
Robin Robin Robin, I don't know if it's the device man
I don't think it's the device
And by the way, it's always platform and content
The two always have to go hand in hand
First of all, my prediction about record companies
There was a great article, I will great
Not so great if you're time Warner
How they came in short
Lower profits
They don't get like five million dollars in profit for the quarter
I don't know if I was misleading that
But that was like, huh?
And that's on revenues of, you know, 700 million
It's kind of interesting
I'm not quite sure what's going on
But it seems like people are panicking in the traditional music business
And I'm not happy that they're...
Well, no, I guess I am kind of happy they're folding
But you know, it'll be interesting to see what's next
And what the fallout's going to be and how it's going to work
And are we at the nexus or we at the change?
Now when it comes to the killer app, I don't know
I think it's the networks man
There's a lot happening in mobile data
There's a lot of new frequencies coming up
The next five years will be interesting to watch
I don't think it's going to be anything happening in 2008
If you don't mind, I want to focus on getting ourselves a better president in 2008
He's killer device, obviously going to be the cell phone
And it's going to suck the big pipe and pull in all these podcasts over the ether
Right to the cell phone device
But right now, you've got to take the Apple iTunes or the iPhone
And plug it in to get any podcasts
Now I can understand AT&T saying
He goes on for another minute, Rob and I'm sorry
I hear your frustration, bro
I really do
And so the Nokia and 810 is that something for you
I don't know
For me, it is perfect
I use it as an iPod
Because it's small enough to fit into either my back pocket or my coat pocket
Even my inside pocket, it's a little on the heavy side
It's not an iPod by any means
But the media player
They've done something really good in the software
The media player is much more functional than it was
You can kind of create playlists
And there's an automatic playlists for recently added
So if you just load up a few files
You know, to take with you
And the way I do it is, you know, I just go to the dashboard
Because that all works now, all this flash stuff works
And you know, click on the shows that I want
And I click on download and I download them to the device
And I'm off and running
And it does multiple downloads really well
That's really improved this thing
And as you know, as you know
And it's a little too late for me to call
Chief Mega Head Sales Weasel Chris Jacob
We're going to be offering these to
Potual audience members at a great discount
And he assures me it's going to happen before
The end of the Christmas shopping season
It's going to be tight
But it's going to be in time
Now, of course, if you can't wait
A couple of you have already done that
They are available now
And there's a link at
Create.com and in the show notes at daily source code.com
When you can go and pick yourself one out
But it will be who view it in price
To wait a little bit
Adam Curry, this is Tom Wiley from Ireland
I'm just wondering about this any under any 10
The reason you guys are going to be doing
Is this going to be worldwide or just
U.S.
Because I am so pissed off with podcasts
But I'm just U.S.
What?
Oh, U.S. deals
Thank you
You're not the only one
Wondering that
I've been assured it is for Europe
And the United Kingdom
And for the United States
And of course, anyone, I believe anyone can purchase it
Worldwide
But they did have to come up with
Separate promo codes and coupons
And so I know that there's work going on with that
That's basically our waiting for
So that we could do
Territories outside the U.S.
So the answer is yes
And of course, I have no idea about price point
Although anything these days
You buy so much with your English pound
It's just amazing, isn't it?
Yeah, I'm a vapor here in San Diego, California
I was listening to DSC 69
Three I believe
And I've been appreciating with you sign off
That everybody's been giving you
I'm kind of curious for those of us
And I might have missed it
Because I've been listening for a couple of years
But I skipped out for a while
Coming back
You could explain the origin of the
Fuck you Adam Curry
But in any case until I get an explanation
Fuck you, ask Terry
Yeah, it started with comic strip blogger
Our European Union correspondent
He always end his reports
His official political reports
And other comments with your Fuck you Adam Curry
And I noticed
Because I think I said, hey, you know
Everyone should just end their comments
With a good old FU Adam Curry
And I noticed that the comment
Quality has gone up significantly
That's why I don't really want to stop it
Because I can hear everyone's really focusing
on what they want to say
And they're getting the message out
And you guys are doing great on time
It's in reasonable
It's not like five minute comments
That are useless to me
Because you know at the end
You're going to be able to say
Fuck you Adam Curry
I feel free to use your creativity
Come up with something else
Okay, my name
Stumble across this
In the top 10 for the week
On the podcast music network
American Athens real thing
I'm going to try to listen to what I'm going to make
I'm going to listen to what I'm going to make
I'm trying to listen to what I'm going to make
I'm going to listen to what I'm going to sound
The American Anthem's real thing from the Podsafe music network haven't uploaded a new song
and almost looks like two years, man, what happened to it?
Well, if there's still out there, just a thought, you could always enter in the audio
street.net competition, the battle of the bands at the grand opening of the new Hard Rock
Hotel on San Diego, go to audiostreet.net to enter for the battle of the bands, the winner.
I guess there's a big grand opening and then you get to perform on stage with Black Eyed Peas.
I guess you'll be opening act for them, which ain't too shabby.
Last night, I went to bed and I couldn't sleep immediately, I was really early and so first
I listened to traces of nuts from the UK side of the equation, BT Podsha, traces of nuts.bt
Podsha.com, those guys are fucking crazy, that's really, really funny episode.
And then I listened to Pacific Coast Hellway, Mark had Mike UC on, that's a great combination
of those two guys.
And I was literally giggling in bed, it was so juvenile, yet so delicious.
Hey Adam, Anning Booker from Leipzig, Germany here, I'm a long time listener since
2005, I think, and I have a comment on DSC693.com, they're coming straight blogger talked
about the beginning of World War II and he was kind of right, but as a student of history
advanced class in Germany, I can't help myself.
Oh, hold on a second, I think we're going to get a little bit of a history lesson about
the beginnings of World War II pay attention, because this is the shit you'd never
learned in school.
To give you a more detailed overview, but the situation in Europe in this time in 1939,
so there was this problem with East Prussia or Ospreysen, and a deep Germany had
great interest in building a highway or Autobahn from the main part of Germany to East
of Prussia, mainly because it wasn't that easy to feed those people in this part of
Germany and to provide for them.
So this was one of the biggest issues between Poland and Germany in this time, but it wasn't
actually the trigger of World War II.
As you may know, World War II started in the morning hours of September 1st, 1939.
I have to be honest, I was never taught that in school either.
I did not know it was on September 1st, 1939, but I will remember from now on as will
have thousands of people listening to this World War II started on September 1st, 1939.
And actually it was a pretty nasty strike by German propaganda, because they claimed the
German propaganda claimed that Polish troops would have attacked a small German radio station,
called Zendaglwitz.
Of course, there weren't any military actions taking place from the side of Poland.
So here's what really happened.
A high Nazi officer ordered a task force to kill several Polish people, then to put them
into Polish uniforms and to let the scene look like an attack by the Polish on this radio
station, on the Zendaglwitz.
So it wasn't, actually it wasn't an attack by the Polish, but by German soldiers, but
it looked like an attack by the Polish.
Okay, so it was a cowardly attack dressed up as enemy terrorists, a page book from history,
interesting indeed.
And then in the propaganda Hitler told the German people that actually Germany was only
defending itself.
Then the Bermacht, the German armed forces invaded Poland, and this caused the declaration
of war by the United Kingdom and France, because they had both an alliance with Poland.
So this was the long version, the detailed version of the beginning of World War II, the
story behind this, the Zendaglwitz.
So I hope I could help you in a way, and yeah, fuck you, Adam Cole.
Oh yes, nice.
Okay.
Yeah, thank you.
That was, well that was actually quite educational, who says you can't learn something
from this.
Hey Adam, it's Andy from Germany.
Andy.
Do you really want to make me believe you couldn't resist the smuggler-tyzing?
Smuggler-tyzing.
Come on.
You know how they manipulate you.
The advertising is inside the cigarette and gets inside your brain.
Oh no.
You can't resist it.
I mean, if you really want to, you can't stop.
Okay, how?
And I want you to listen to my voice, just relax and listen to my voice.
Can I touch myself?
I know you're safe when you see the fireworks, you will stop smoking forever, only the
splits are allowed.
I hope thank goodness.
And if it makes you go nuts, just tell us on the Charlie and we will call you and help
you to get through it.
Okay.
And remember one thing.
Here it comes.
Fuck you, Adam Cole.
Bye.
I take it all back.
You guys are just doing it to make me happy.
Hey, I know it's Gary Alexander from Las Vegas, it's going on.
I want to talk about the Republican debate on C, I think I saw on CNN or something as
I call it on the 100 channels.
Here we go.
There's someone talk about that a little bit and talk about Ron Paul and Giuliani.
Actually, actually John McCain seemed extremely frustrated in the debate.
I don't know if you were able to see it or not.
I think.
Yeah, you know, actually I was able to see it because I have, we have a, a TV at the
office.
This is pretty cool actually.
We have a TV set up with a sling box and it's set up so that, you know, a number of
us could, you know, check if the TV cast is working via remote.
I don't have the capability to have a TV in the UK.
So I could actually literally sit in my office and I can switch through, you know, hundreds
of, you know, up in the attic in the manner.
I can switch through hundreds of channels and I can look at, you know, the TV cast version
of the stuff that's going up.
So I just switched to CNN and I just thought of my desk, you know, had a little window
running.
Yeah.
And also I was able to follow most of it.
It was, you know, I read some of the reports and I was like, you know, lots of fire
and I thought it was kind of tame.
I'm, you know, honestly, I'm sick and tired of this format.
And I, and yeah, the YouTube videos are very cute and people do very creative stuff.
But it's show business, you know, you know, a politics of show business for ugly people.
You can't, you can't like try to make show business out of show business.
You know, we need some politics.
We need some real debate, some real disc, people talk, you know, do a whole bunch of
sit down interviews and fill your channel with that.
We need some real information.
This is all just sound bites and trying to make other guys look bad and get a laugh.
And I said, what was I watching?
What's maybe it was, uh, CNN later that evening, I can't remember or this morning.
I don't know what when I saw it.
They had a panel of people sit there with a kind of like a vibeometer, you know,
and if they liked what they were seeing or hearing, then they would, you know,
I apparently push a lever up or move a slider up or whatever.
And you could catch their mood.
I've seen this experiment done.
We've done versions of it, Ron and I in our previous companies for research, you know,
you sit behind the glass wall and watch how people react to stuff, uh, the, the one,
the one way mirror.
That was always fun.
And, you know, and you see people just, you know, it's the laughs.
It's, uh, it's a comedic fest.
So I just don't think it's, it's good show business entertaining to watch,
but just didn't really do anything for me politically.
Maybe you're a sense of this semester, but, um, I tell you, Ron Paul, man.
I'm, uh, I'm just kind of blown away.
The guy is, uh, the little guys, you have some calmness, you know,
and, um, Juliani, I'm, I'm really torn between this Republican party.
I got to be honest with you, the Democratic party kind of sucks at this point,
as far as what they're offering, um, I'm not really one over by Obama or Clinton,
uh, or any of the other, uh, people for that matter of Democratic candidates.
But Ron Paul is really kind of, uh, spark my interest over and over.
So I want to thank you for bringing him to light and, uh, spark my interest in the debates in general,
because without, you know, having the Ron Paul stuff on here,
I really wouldn't have watched, to be honest with you, uh, this early on.
So thank you very much, and, uh, keep doing the dude.
Yo, man.
Yeah, thanks for calling it about that, because I, uh, you know, I'm glad,
because you reminded me, uh, to talk about it.
I didn't think Ron Paul was, uh, was really strong last night, um, um,
some of the messaging, I think needs to change a little bit.
Just, you know, my, my personal, you know, my, my personal opinion.
Uh, he also got less airtime, uh, than a lot of the other candidates, which is always typical with stuff like this.
Uh, Huckabee stealing a little bit of his thunder, Huckabee, you know, kind of cool with Chuck Norris, cool, good idea.
You know, Ron Paul could use some of that, some celebrity, you know, maybe Hasselhoff,
just a thought there. Hasselhoff would do it, for sure.
And, I mean, you, I mean, you, I mean, in all honesty, who wins, you know, Chuck Norris or the Huff?
I mean, that's, it's a tough one, but I think the Huff might have the upper hand.
He's a survivor, you know, he's been to Helen back again, the Huff.
And, uh, good old Doug Pilgrim sent me an email on Mom, see if I can find it here in my, uh, Google Notepad.
He, uh, maybe it didn't say for some reason.
Well, he sent me a, a perfect inventory of the, uh, of the primary, and he said, you know, January 8th,
here's the hotel, you should stay at, you know, here's the, the universities you could go to.
And I'm thinking, what can we do, you know, to rally, I guess, young people, college kids probably
is the best market, and is that the best market? What can we do to rally them, you know, a day or two before
the actual primary to get them to go and vote and have them vote for Ron Paul?
You know, I was thinking maybe some kind of campaign like, uh, take the red pill, vote for Ron Paul,
which I thought might actually be kind of a cool slogan because, you know, anyone who's seen the matrix
immediately understands the take the red pill, which, of course, is why I use it here on the daily
source code. Um, and I, and I know that it will work because I sent an email to, uh, to Ray Lane,
uh, to the Clienter Perkins, one of our investors, and, uh, somewhere there was a reference to the
to red pill, doesn't matter, you know, why, but there was a reference in the email thread, and, uh,
and he, he got it immediately and he, he dug it too. I'm thinking maybe we can do something like that,
take the red pill, vote for Ron Paul. Yeah, that's, that has a ring to it. Take the red pill, vote for Ron Paul.
December 16th will be, uh, the second money bomb for Ron Paul, it'll be, uh, the, the, the Boston Tea Party.
And a verse over the Boston Tea Party, you're gonna go raise some more money. I can't
donate anymore. I gave my maximum 2300 bucks, um, which I was wondering, I'm wondering now,
maybe I should have split that up. I'm sure this is going to be another drive. But anyway,
I can certainly, uh, paint Ron Paul out to you guys and, uh, you know, I think, I think he is the right guy
for the job. I really do, and I'm surprised that I'm, you know, backing a Republican. I never really
expected that to happen, not, not this, naturally, not this easily. Okay, uh, so we're going into the
weekend, you know, I've been trying to get into the kid into the Christmas spirit. It's, that's a
little weird in San Francisco, although it must say Union Square. They've done it up beautifully,
the tree is fantastic. There's lots of really nice decorations. Uh, but, you know, I like, you know,
having a fire going and that snow or, you know, I like the kind of the cold weather, uh, you know,
for a limited amount of time, obviously. And of course, I don't mind having a nice crisp, cold winter day
with the sun shining with a, you know, completely blue sky, perfect weather for flying, by the way.
So, kind of I want to get you in the mood, and, uh, it is a footballer Friday, so I'm, you know,
I always put some extra work in the looking for the tracks for you, and I found one by DJBC. It's a
mashup. Oh, this is John speaking with his voice. But all very happy to be able to talk to you like this
on this little bit of plastic. This record reaches you at the end of the really game for us on
it's all due to you. I think you're like it. Imagine saying,
I'm a girl's coming at the wall, yeah, saying, I'm a girl's coming at the top, saying,
I'm a girl's coming at the top, saying, I'm a girl's coming at the top, saying,
I'm a girl's coming at the top, saying, I'm a girl's coming at the top, saying, I'm a girl's coming at the top,
I'm the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world, the world
the world, the world, the world, the world, the world,
But I'm not the only one.
I hope someday you'll join the world.
And the world will live this world.
I see you are my hero.
Oh, what a great song to wind down the week.
All right, final note.
If you want to get a great deal on a domain name,
I just ruined the vibe, didn't it?
695 used my promo code DSC3.
DailySourceco.com is where you can find the show notes to everything
spoken about, everything relevant in this program,
especially the music.
Thanks to everyone who contributed.
Thanks to everyone in the pod show office here in San Francisco.
I had a great week.
It's been great seeing you guys twice in a month.
A little, little wearing on the old man.
But it's just been good all around.
And I have no idea if I'm going to be back here before the end of the year,
or if I'm going to be in New York.
I might have to go to Washington.
It's still be kind of crazy busy.
But I'm sure I'll be back with you on Monday.
More than likely from the curry manner.
Remember, live your life with passion and enjoy your freedom.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Imagine headphones without wires.
Now their Sony's Bluetooth wireless headset.
A rechargeable listening experience with 11 hours of music playback.
So you and your music are free to move.
Pick up yours at Sony.com slash headphones.
Sony wireless headphones.
Your music are unplugged.