And now one of the best shows in NewMudia, the DSC, 670, with the Man the Mythal Legend, Adam Curry.
And now one of the best shows in NewMudia, Adam Curry.
Well, sorry, of course yesterday and no show, that's because left for Germany on Germany.
On Sunday, for a number of meetings that we had scheduled, our local guy on the scene, Dr. Will.
His name is Will home, we just call him Dr. Will. He is a, he's funny, in Germany if you have a title, if you have a PhD, then you introduce yourself as a doctor.
And so, so that's what we call him Dr. Will. He's essentially consultant who's skilled in helping foreign companies set up shop in Germany.
And so, wow, man, I was actually planning on flying out myself.
Sunday was perfect.
You know, the idea was to go to, uh, shown haven, uh, airfield, which is just, uh, to the south of Potsdam, which in turn is just to the, uh, south west of Berlin all within like a 20 mile radius.
And I was prepared, man, I had everything, I had my flight plans, I had my three GPS's configured, I had alternates, everything that mapped out because this was going to be the first time.
I was going to a foreign country to a foreign airfield because I've never been to the Potsdam airfield before, or shown haven.
And, um, you know, so, uh, a new territory. And, uh, and basically, setting out in a journey.
I, uh, discussed it with Wing Commander William and, uh, you know, he, he always just wants to make sure I'm prepared for everything.
And I was all set to go. And then I realized that, um, we actually get a lot more benefit out of it if, uh, if Ron and I who was still over here.
In the UK, uh, after the digital music awards, if we would, uh, you know, if we flew together, we'd have a little more time to chat.
And if I knew that if I was going to fly him in the Delta Sierra, uh, there would be no time for, uh, for business chat.
Because, you know, I'd be like, uh, trying to concentrate on, uh, what the hell I'm doing.
You know, I can't think of anything else, but flying when I'm flying.
Uh, so today, actually, I'm quite glad that, uh, that we turned around, uh, that swiftly actually decided to come back last night.
Oh, and, of course, I have some stories about airport security to share with you.
Oh, man. It's just as ridiculous in Europe as it is in the US.
Because otherwise, I was returning on that, planning on returning this morning.
Uh, probably would have left already, it might have been, uh, underway for at least an hour.
Uh, but the weather is quite shit, uh, across the channel. Um, and now, you know, clouds are not necessarily problem.
Low ceiling is not a problem. When you get thunderstorms, uh, that's going to be a problem.
Because, you know, as we've discussed, you do not want to be flying into thunderstorms just not a good idea.
So, uh, Germany, wow, uh, once again, a fantastic trip.
Hi, Adam. This is longtime listener, Michael said we're in need.
Did I hear you say pop stand in Germany? And at the third, six, six time?
I was just there a few weeks ago for a friend's wedding. And what a great town.
Uh, just wondering if jobless things for pod show, pod stand are going to be listed on podshow.com.
I went there and I didn't see anything listed for Germany or London.
Uh, love a show. Keep it up.
Y'all mom.
Uh, yes. Uh, so it will. We're not quite ready yet to, uh, to be doing open, uh, open calls, if you will, uh, for people to come and join us.
Actually, it would be a podshow Germany, uh, but I do like the idea of podstom, uh, podshow podstom.
We're not, uh, 100% certain that it's going to be in podstom, but I would say, I would say 95%.
We've seen real estate, uh, both in Berlin and in podstom. What I'd like about podstom behind besides it's, uh,
very historic significance throughout, uh, centuries, actually.
Um, the space that we're looking at is in this, uh, legendary, uh, movie, movie complex, studio complex,
uh, Marlene Dietrich, uh, didn't movies there. I mean, there's just a lot of history to the place.
Really, really like in that. There's one other incredible advantage, uh, that comes with, uh,
being in the Brondonburg area, which is where podstom is.
Listen to this, it's unbelievable. For every employee you hire the government, the German government,
in podstom, not in Berlin, but in podstom, will give you 50% of that employee salary in subsidy.
So if you hire someone for, uh, say 50,000, uh, euros a year, 25,000 of those euros will come right back to the company.
Um, and that's the cap, by the way, is the 50,000. So if you hired someone for 100,000 euros,
then you'd still only get 25 because the, the maximum is, uh, is half of the 50,000 deduction,
but it doesn't matter how many employees you have unlimited.
Incredible. Uh, Berlin does have something similar, but that doesn't start until you have a minimum of 20 employees.
And, uh, we're a ways off from that yet. And we, we don't even have the 15 yet in the UK.
Uh, so that's, uh, that's a pretty big incentive I'd have to say. This is how it works people.
This is how it works. This is how, uh, regions and countries and cities attract businesses and,
and get them to set up shop. Very interesting, uh, to see this type of incentive.
So, uh, had a great time. Um, there was, uh, there was also a conference going on in, um, in Berlin,
a, uh, what, I could forget the name of it. It was like broadband wireless, something conference.
Wasn't a big one, but it was a lot of IPTV, uh, representatives from around the globe trying to figure this shit out.
Seems like there's still a lot of technological issues that, that they're dealing with.
Uh, so I actually even sent, uh, a little, uh, a little text message to, uh, our Savant, uh,
comic strip blogger thinking he might be in Berlin, uh, for this conference, unfortunately he wasn't.
But of course, you know, whenever you tickled the comic strip blogger well, comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip,
Uh, if you tickle them, usually will show up. Hello, madam Adam Kahlo. So here is your European Union correspondent.
So, what's up lately, in your opinion?
Firstly, bureaucrats want to pass new e-o-3T through vectors without having getting public
popular vote.
Okay, wait a minute, so I just a quick translation there.
So what I understand is in the European Parliament, they want to pass laws and regulations
without a popular vote on said subjects.
US American dollar is now so fucking cheap with regard to euro currency and some other European
currencies that EU citizens are wiping their feds with US American banknotes.
Another thing, since now some new EU countries are joining the euro zone, so the currency
zone includes us as Slovenia, it was last year, it includes Malta and Cyprus that are
joining by the end of this year.
The new euro coins are being made now, where however, Turkey has been wiped out from the
map of Europe on this coin.
So, of course, it is because you've got some people, but I have to say that the French President
Circusy no longer is objecting to the membership of Turkey in EU.
So that's it.
Thanks for listening.
Fuck you, too.
I think all, whenever you call in, please, whenever you call in, end your call with
fuck you, Adam Curry, fuck you, please, it really makes me laugh.
And not just you, see us be anyone, anyone calling in, please, and that way.
I like it.
All right, so if I understand correctly, you tell me that European coins are being minted,
and the Turkey is not represented on the little map there, that's interesting.
I did bring back some euros, so they're probably older ones, but I'll take a look.
Even though, as you say, Circusy has no objections now to Turkey joining the EU, we will, of
course, follow the situation quite closely.
Wow, man.
The numbers are in.
Let me, here I go.
Telling you the numbers are in, shit, my mouse is stuck here with the hell, is up with
that.
Is that just a low battery on the Bluetooth?
My goodness.
Where is it?
Hold on.
Don't, don't go away.
I want to share.
Sorry about that.
Here we go.
Remember, we did backstage pass during the digital musical awards, during the, the actual
recording, the taping of the award.
The show aired on Friday here on Channel 4 in the UK.
I've got the numbers in.
These are mainly coming directly from, from Akamai, who did the, the, the big scale part
of our live stream, which, of course, is still running at
the plus TV.com.
You can get to it from the homepage at,
paucho.com or bt paucho.com.
Check this out.
Whereas it, unique stream views.
And these are just the rough, low numbers.
So it's probably going to end up a little bit higher.
But what we have already calculated,
850,000 unique streams.
So that has to be individual computers.
Over the 72 hour period of our, just let's just call it a broadcast, I guess.
850,000, that's almost three times the viewing audience for the awards on television.
Of course, that aired at midnight, but still, that's almost three times.
Overall, average viewing time, about six and a half minutes.
However, during the actual event itself, when we had all of our red carpet, so we had
our, basically, we, we broke it up into three parts.
We had the pre-amble, which was a full day and then leading up to the awards itself.
Excuse me, then we had the show where people were coming off stage.
We were interviewing them at our backstage, backstage, past pit area.
And then people, you know, then we had the wrap up and rewind is what we call them.
We look back at all the great stuff that happened.
So during that middle piece, during the awards, the average viewing time was 22 minutes,
22 minutes.
I mean, this, this thing worked.
People actually sat there and watched entertainment, streaming live on their television.
Hi Adam, it's Sam here and you, Ty, just that sort of London.
I just wanted to say, I've just had a fantastic evening of entertainment.
I've been sat watching the plus and, uh,
looking at some of the coverage from the DNA awards and man, I'm blown away by your content.
It's just fucking awesome.
Um, I've got one small criticism, Adam, Ace.
Alright, so first, let me wallow in that for a second before you go into the criticism.
I knew it.
If you just, if you, this is your MTV went right.
And this is what it would look like if they went left.
Keep with a short form video.
But it's not just music videos, it's, it's, it's interviews,
it's segments, it's episodes from podcasts from the video podcast.
It's music videos, uh, it's YouTube hits.
It's, uh, the best from daily motion.
All of this stuff.
That is exactly what MTV would have been today.
I don't think they can back into it.
So we're just moving ahead forward.
And of course, the beauty is we have this complete huge bucket of, of, of shows that we can
draw from to schedule.
It's, it's all on the network already.
So it's, uh, I'm glad you like it.
Uh, and of course, it's 24, seven.
It does not stop, uh, right now it's one feed for the entire world.
We're already thinking about creating a secondary feed for Europe.
And then maybe even do one for Asia, theplustv.com.
Alright, now now you can go ahead and, and break me down if you don't mind.
For sight, it's horrible.
Oh, so the out is in the ages to find it.
Yeah, alright.
Alright.
Yes.
That too is changing.
I've mentioned it several times before.
Uh, in November you should start to see some of, uh, some of the, uh, the third version
now of Pod Show site going to beta as we say here.
Uh, and somewhere, uh, either the end of the year or the beginning of the year, it'll be
launched full time, uh, live.
It is such an incredible difference to what we have now that we're, we're really going to
work very carefully on, uh, on the integration, uh, so that we don't break stuff that is
already working just fine.
Thank you.
Hey, Adam, this is Terrence from Texas.
I was checking out music plus the other day and I thought it was pretty neat thing.
Um, it's actually a really nice format to have actually one screen until, instead of a
five or six in at the same time, blaring.
But, uh, there was good music coming from it, but, uh, the last couple of days, I haven't
been able to find it, um, and there's, uh, advertises, uh, something about look out in
major tests.
Yeah, just listening to the beginning of that comment.
If you're looking for music plus TV dot com, then you're going to be disappointed.
I don't think that you were, you were watching the plus TV dot com or just go to
Pod, Pod Show dot com or BT Pod Show dot com, you'll find a link right on the home
page.
I think this conspiracy stuff is, is getting out of hand, but, um, anyway, I hope
nothing really serious is going on.
I hope to see music plus backup.
The plus.
Um, anyway, I was, uh, it's a third, but, uh, all the same, good luck with everything.
And I hope that, uh, the sites were stored soon.
So, uh, I look forward to it.
Have a good one.
Alright, man.
Bye.
Yeah.
So, the site is, uh, obviously still there.
Uh, one thing that we did have to change, which, uh, we're working on feverishly.
Bisiony, we had all these interactive bits where it would show you what's coming up next.
And, um, uh, I'd also, so you can get this show immediately, the one that's playing.
We've had to turn that off because it's just been too much traffic.
And this was running on, uh, on a separate server.
It really, the whole thing was still proof of concept.
But it took off.
And, uh, until now, we're, we're reinforcing everything with steel beams, uh, post launch.
Uh, so that'll be, uh, up and running again as soon as we can get it rolling.
It's, there's a lot of excitement about this.
I'm totally flabbergast at how many people tuned into watch this, theplustv.com.
Hey Adam, start from Chicago.
I called, um, a couple of days ago in the plus TV cranked out, but, uh, uh, uh, the U.S.
answering machine was, uh, must have been full and booted me, man.
I just, uh, and I'm listening to Super Friday and I said, nobody called them to the UK.
So I'm like, dad, damn it, I'm going to call it to the U.S. line and, you know,
I don't think that's, I mean, that's fabulous.
I've been, I've been checking, uh, you know, since it kicked off with the DNAs and all
weekend and everything and, uh, by God, man, you are kicking ass and taking
names, man.
That is just, just beautiful.
I definitely get that, you know, my, uh, JJ kind of Allen 105, you know,
grassroots MTV early days.
Beautiful, um, hey, so congrats, uh, and, um, Natalie's a county man.
She, but, man, she's, she's awesome.
She's going to go places.
I got to tell you, um, there are people over here who have not stopped talking about
Natalie Delcante and her performance, uh, during the digital music awards, particularly
on the plus, people really, really enjoyed what she was doing.
She was asking the musicians came up to me.
The guy from, uh, Caducan, fucking guy from Caducan, okay?
A band called Caducan, says, hey, I, I really enjoyed what Natalie had to say.
She asked me some serious questions about digital rights management and was the first
kind of question that was really, you know, really good all night.
Right, uh, man, that's my girl.
And if you, uh, look at, uh, I was watching, it came through on the plus yesterday.
This is also, by the way, the way that I watch all of our shows.
Instead of, you know, uh, going through all my subscriptions, uh, it just pops up, you know,
I know that a new texture will eventually air on the plus.
So, eventually I'll see it because that's, that's how we roll, um,
Natalie packing her gadget bag for her trip to, uh, to London.
You've got to see that episode.
It's, it's the most natural I have ever seen Natalie be on camera.
And she's, and, and actually it's not very far from where she is when she's focusing on the,
on the tech news on camera.
It's just so personal.
I forget it.
I could gush all day.
Yes, I agree.
She's kicking ass.
So, this talk from Chicago meant to that, you know, I knew you're in town.
You blew through and, um, yeah.
No, I apologize about that, dude.
I did blow through town, uh, on the, uh, when I was, uh, going there for, uh,
for my presentation, I know you, you reached out to me and I just didn't have any time.
Uh, even if I, I did, you know, I was on the phone with Patricia back home who was feeling really
not well at the time, uh, so I just had no time to hang out.
But I promise you, I will come back.
I mean, I know your busy man, but, uh, hey, anytime you're in Chicago, please,
can't be podcast on the guy.
Yeah.
For Canada, here, actually I miss.
You could probably cruise out of here on American.
I should've looked you up.
Anyway.
I did, you're wrong.
Keep it up.
Rock and Bestie, uh, um,
challenge, folder of all that could stuff.
We'll fill out that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I like red.
You really.
I'd rather thank you.
There you go.
Lots of, uh, comparisons with the, the plus TV dot com to, uh, to old MTV, uh,
uh, but done in the, in the new fashion way with, uh, and you know what?
But if I had said today, oh, let's just start this, you couldn't pull it off.
We had to back into the big content pool, the big cesspool that is podget.com, and it's
working.
I'd love to hear more from you, check it out.
Let me know what you think.
Hey, Adam.
So, I'm Steve.
Quick and TV question.
When you guys were actually on TV, seeing the George Michael video for the first time
you were just mentioned the other day.
When you're hosting, you're on the watch and TV at all.
Do you watch the other guys?
Did you watch it just my curiously?
You know, just to see what the other guys were doing?
Did you actually watch it because you liked it?
It's curious.
Well.
Red pill.
Yeah, good question, man.
So, when I was there, of course, this doesn't happen anymore.
We had segments, and we had days where we'd do a 12.
I'm sorry, a 24, and days where we'd do a 48.
So, on Monday, we would typically roll in and we'd do a 48 right off the bat.
Which meant we would pre-tap our segments.
Our segments only for Tuesday and Wednesday.
So, now we had facilities.
We had the VJ room where you could watch all the videos, prepare for your show.
We had research there, and that's where you'd sit with your associate producer and get ready
for your segments, and decide on what you're going to say in each segment.
We had a schedule.
So, we know, okay, I'm coming out of commercials going into, let me see, of course,
some new kids on the block.
I got to play some new kids on the block, I'm Choneson.
And then you sit there and you do segment after segment after segment, and so you'd pretend
that you had seen what just played, and you'd pretend that you were about to watch
what was coming up.
And we had an internal video system, so basically we'd schedule it in order, so if I
happen to be doing the afternoons, I'd come in, probably around 11 a.m., and I could
watch Julie Brown, or China, Canton, or Kevin Seale, or someone else, do their segments.
And so we definitely were able to watch each other.
We did a lot of that.
And then when I went home, of course, I turned it on.
It was back in the day when it was kind of like wallpaper, so of course, of course.
And then we had our new music Tuesdays, and when the new videos would come out, and
we'd all kind of huddle around, and we'd look at all the cool new clips when it was still
cool to go back in the room, and say, hey, man, I got the new aerosmith video, and we'd
all marvel over it, and the record company executive, where the promo guy or gal would
be there and be all proud, and we'd be excited.
So yeah, that's one of the things I've really enjoyed about the plus, is there's music
videos on there that don't just, that aren't just there because they're great songs,
but they're innovative and great videos as well.
So a grand experiment, so far so good.
My name's Matt, this is Game's Weasel, and on this week's show, the two biggest titles of
the year for the 360 and the PS3 go head-to-head, that's right, and Heavenly Sword is
taking on Halo 3.
Listen to what I thought of both of those at gamesweasel.btpodjo.com.
Hey Adam, I'm just listening to the DSC669, and I've got to tell you, mate, it sounds like
you're blue pillinous. I'm listening to your show, and it's like, you have that big
and of these awards, man, and big at P.U.A., it's always like a very big time to get
UK people to call up. So it worked, I'm calling you, blue pillinous.
Of course I'm blue pillinous. I do that all the time, are you nuts? I appreciate
it, man. Okay, so Friday, I believe I asked you to follow the money as your home work for
over the weekend, and of course I added a Monday there for you just to help out a little bit.
And really, you know, I'm trying to figure out how best to approach this subject, but what we
really need is people who are experts in finance and world governance, and well, like a
comicster blogger helps us out with the EU. There are some very interesting things going on
in the stock market. Gold is at a record high, yet being written about in mainstream
press as a bad investment. See what else is going on? Well, of course it's now $1.40 to a Euro,
which is just an outrageous, outrageous difference to just weeks ago, it seems.
You know, could this have to do with keeping the dollar the most attractive monetary unit for
for oil? I mean, there's so many different questions that come up, but there is a much bigger,
much bigger picture I believe. And Madeland did his homework, and he plucked a couple of audio
excerpts from Michael Moore's sicko, which I have not seen. I think I heard of it somewhere,
but I really don't know too much about it. I presume it's very similar to his previous projects,
but there is a great excerpt here that I want to play. Listen to this very, very carefully.
This is about following the money and how you can enslave people through debt.
I think democracy is the most revolutionary thing in the world, far more revolutionary than
socialist ideas, anybody else's idea, because if you have power, you use it to meet the needs
of you and your community. And this idea of choice, which capital talks about over time,
you've got to have a choice, choice depends on the freedom to choose. And if you're shackled with debt,
you don't have a freedom to choose. It seems that it benefits the system if the average working person
is shackled with debt. And people in debt become hopeless and hopeless people don't vote.
She'll say, you should ever answer vote, but I think if the poor in Britain or the United States
turned out and voted for people who represented their interests, it would be a real democratic
revolution. Now, I just want to stop that for a second, right there. Did you hear that?
When people get into debt, they become hopeless. Hopeless people don't vote.
Poor people don't vote. And I think the poverty line in this case is not about being able to eat,
just despair. Middle class, I would have to say, you can't just doesn't vote because they're
hopeless. They've given up. And I've said it time and time again. We have to use our system,
which I'll talk about in a minute, because the American system works in a very particular way.
I don't want it to happen. So keeping people hopeless and pessimistic. So I think there are two ways
in which people are controlled. First of all, frightened people and secondly, demoralize them.
An educated, healthy and confident nation is harder to govern. And I think there's an element
in the thinking of some people. We don't want people to be educated, healthy and confident,
because they would get out of control. The top one percent of the world's population
80 percent of the world's wealth. It's incredible that people put up with it. But they're poor,
they're demoralized, they're frightened. And therefore they think perhaps the safest thing to do is take
orders and hope for the best. There you go. It's been used time and time again. And I would have to say
the times we live in today look very similar to previous instances of using that type of strategy.
But of course, we're not really demoralized and depressed. We're fucking alive. Aren't we?
You open up your eyes. You've got another day. Even today where it's just raining down in buckets
from the heavens above. You've got to be positive. You've got to be hopeful. You've got to be
ready to take on the world and make a change. Every single one of you try and make a change. And
we clearly have a wonderful alternative media source to do this. So if I can get close to a
million people to tune in to some form of entertainment over the course of three days, I'm pretty
sure that we can start messaging people, appropriate world, if not life, if not world saving ideas.
So I certainly intend to do that on the daily source code. Now I don't get a million people a day,
but it's enough I think that can make some form of difference. Let me see. Where do we start?
All right. First thing, I'm starting to follow the the presidential race a little bit closer.
This is taking place now in the states. There's a great website. I'd like you to take a look at
opensecrets.org. You can find out for opensecrets.org exactly who has donated to each presidential
candidate and how much money. Of course, there are legal capsist to how much you can donate to a
campaign. I think it's just under $10,000 like $9,200 to $9,600. Now go to Hillary Clinton
and take a look at who's donating. And just do anything over $1,000 because the list will be too long
otherwise. And you'll see it's like 50 people from Morgan Stanley. It's all bankers. It's all
bad. The list just goes on and on and on and on. Which of course, to me means like, okay, Morgan Stanley
is basically backing Hillary Clinton and they're using either friendly employees or you know,
you could construct all kinds of conspiracies around why so many Morgan Stanley employees. It's listed
that way. Why they're donating to Hillary Clinton's campaign. Now let's go straight back to
look at the state of the dollar. Look at I'll just have to call it a bailout or semi bailout if you
look at the interest rate and how that's been working of banks on the credit crunch. It's obvious.
Now in the United States, you need money to become president. Hillary Clinton has already raised
75 million dollars. She projects to have $100 million by the end of the year. That's almost a
full year before the election. What is it used for? Advertising. Advertising. It's a marketing
exercise. It is about marketing the new candidate. You know Barack Obama falling behind, you know,
that his campaign isn't quite, isn't quite firing in all cylinders. Why? Well, because he only
has $45 million. So I know through the power of the power of numbers, if we needed to raise
that kind of money for a candidate. I'm pretty sure we could if we all got behind a candidate.
So I believe I have to endorse a candidate for the U.S. presidential elections. I'm not quite sure
who yet, but I'm going to be following it very closely. Interesting that Mitt Romney
has put in so much of his own money. And what's up with that? I mean, he doesn't know how to
raise the money or no one believes in him. I just want you to understand that the American president
is chosen thanks to advertising. It's how we buy our washing powder. It's how we make decisions
about buying our cars. It is how we decide who will be the next president. And in effect,
still I believe, um, leader of the free world hate to say that, but it just seems to be a fact.
Ah, fuck it. Don't even don't even get back to me on that. That's probably not true anymore.
So we have to continue to follow the money. I'm going to be looking at opensecrets.org
to look at these donations. By the way, Barack Obama, all like individual small people,
interesting enough, a lot of people who have no occupation homemaker.
You just got to wonder about this stuff what that means. So as a part of keeping us in control
by terrifying us, the TSA, and I have to say airport security around the globe, apparently,
as it is in the in the United Kingdom and in Europe or Germany, is just as fucking useless as TSA
in America. Hi, and I'm hits Thomas from Arizona. On that sad story of the woman who died,
just a little fax to back up what. All right, well, let me just put some contacts in this if you
haven't heard about it. This is the woman who died in, I think, Phoenix Airport. She missed her
plane. She got really angry. She was detained. I thought by TSA employees, but it turns out it was,
well, you hear, it was actually Phoenix Police. And within like 15 or 20 minutes, and this is just
according to the fax that I have, she died by suffocation in her cell. Very, very strange circumstances.
Background to the story. It was actually the Phoenix Police who had her in custody, not TSA.
So, well, you can go on about your TSA related brands. It really was a separate agency who had
her under custody and whose responsibility it was. The other one point would be that she was actually
on her way to Arizona for drug treatment because of at least she was addicted to substance.
Hey, let me ask you a question. Why do the Phoenix Police have a holding cell at the airport?
That's kind of interesting. It's what the local media has been saying, and that's why she was flying
out. But her family didn't have someone along with her if she was in such trouble, you know,
that kind of didn't make sense to my family and everyone who had heard the story around here was,
you know, how do you send somebody who's in that kind of messed up shape on a plane flag without
somebody along to keep an eye on them. And you know, if your family member or friend just kind of
seemed a little sad all the way around. Yeah. Take care. Yeah, I've been following that story
in the I too have read this. I think that's just the distraction away from the real question.
Yeah, sure. Okay. So mentally unstable on drugs, whatever. You know, the family should have been
responsible. Bullshit. I watched cops almost twice a week. I see it somewhere on TV. I see
drunken drugged out motherfuckers thrown into holding cells for 48 hours. You don't hear about a
lot of them suffocating all by themselves because of their handcuffs. Okay. Certainly not women.
So I just really did that that whole thing really, really reeks. You know, TSA did
did completely fuck up my bag again. Did I tell you that? It's unbelievable. They're able to break
a a supposedly indestructible to me bag. Oh, yeah. I've got my TSA lock on it. It says TSA lock
and they snip it right off. Oh, man. I really pissed me off. Luckily, I'm not alone.
Hey, Adam is direct from Sinia Australia. My friend just came back from Germany and while she was there
and Paris and a couple other places in Eastern Europe. While she was there, she sent this email
just before she came back about how pissed off she was at the airport security. And it's just
subject to the email is if you don't like a abusive language, you should probably get a church after
this. So I'll just read, I'll try and, you know, refrain from tuning F words and it's, you know,
capital letters and all kinds of crazy stuff here. But she's really pissed off because she just
heads the airport because and she just wants to explode. Her luggage was 51 kilos and that's when
killer over what you're allowed. So she's like, oh my god, what a big deal. But I do. Are you
in the bathroom taking a leak while you're recording this list? That sounds like there's water
dripping in the background. They had to pay $600 Australian just to send one of them, one of the
luggage, one of their suitcases back and it's going to take almost two weeks because they have to
send it back rather than because they're not allowed on the plane. It's freaking ridiculous.
Her mum, she writes, when they're in Germany, in the airport, they bought 125 mil bottle of
perfume, which got 70 US dollars and you're only allowed 100 mil liquid of anything on the plane.
So they basically just had to throw it away and it's just, it's a power trip thing. It's just like
the guys just like, yeah, fuck this, we can do whatever the hell we want. Yeah, um, don't
fucking care what it is, whatever. And it just doesn't make sense that you buy it in the airport and
you can't figure it on the plane. Freaks. Yeah, right on to that man. So we took easy jet, right?
And leaving London, the airport has determined how big your carry on can be. And basically it's
the size of a lunch box. And ladies, please don't think you can have a carry on and a purse. All right,
it's for Boughton. So I had to check it. I mean, of course, I'm going for one night, right? I've got
my hand luggage and like, oh fuck, all this crap. It doesn't fit in the nice little rack. I mean,
I've got a sizeable carry on bag, but it fits perfectly in the overhead of every type of aircraft
that that I've flown. And I guess really it's just the inconsistency that really erks me. So
here we go. We're going through UK security. So I'm not allowed to take this big bag. So I take a smaller bag.
Now, all of a sudden, it's take off your shoes and the line next to me. I see people don't have to take off
their shoes. That would, uh, prove me to say the least coming back from, uh, from Germany, from Berlin.
Easy jet said, oh, no problem. Uh, you can, uh, you can put that through. That's, uh, that's a good size.
It's just one piece, right? Yeah, one piece. And he liquids. Yes, all 100 milliliters. I came prepared.
And I have them in a fucking plastic bag. So of course, uh, I have to open up my bag.
And, um, the German security officer is pulling everything out and just looking at, uh, looking
at all the sizes. Even the hairspray, 100 milliliters. And I said, I'm making a joke, right?
Said, isn't that just a troche? It's 100, look at my hair. How can I get buying 100 milliliters a day?
I need at least twice that amount. All done. You can take two, uh, two hair sprays of 100. Yeah.
Thank you very much. I understand. So it's 100 milliliters. She pulls out my, uh, my, my colon.
And on, on it, it's 150 milliliters. But it's half full. I said, look, it's only half full.
Oh, okay. Now, that really pissed her off. Because then she looked at my deodorant once again.
Uh, but this is 150 milliliters. It doesn't come in a smaller container. And it's a little aerosol,
links, right, which is acts in the US. No, you can't take that. And even worse, I had to go back
out to the other side of security, throw it into a, especially marked bin, which, of course,
these cock suckers probably empty at the end of the day and take my shit home.
Had to go through security again, just to get on the plane. Oh, by the way, didn't have to take
my shoes off. Could we at least get some consistency in this story? It's really fucking pissing me off.
It is so incredibly stupid. Consistency will make a believer out of me that you're serious about
security. I'm about to start smuggling illegal shit on the plane, just to prove that I can do it.
Because I know I can do it. I know I, I, I, I, I'm going to start doing this. I just have to because
it is making the absolutely fucking crazy. This is not making us say for it is making us a
afraid. We're in debt. We're afraid. We're being managed. We don't fucking vote. Wake up people.
You've been, um, and she's like, it tells me to stand pretty much soon. We're not going to
bring computers on planes. Because it's got numbers and letters on it. And then we were being
bringing a hand luggage. And in fact, you can't even bring your bones on the plane.
All right. I got to stop because he's just going to make me crazy. That's right. We need to come.
We really need to start protesting this shit. And I don't care what any politician says.
Let's do a job review of the TSA. Let's call for that. I would really like a job review.
Is that okay? We pay these cock suckers. We pay, and you know what? And it's not the people
individually. I'm sure everyone gets up in the morning. Goes to work and thinks, okay. I got a job
to do. I want to do my job. I want to do the best I can. But the supervision of it is so shit.
It is so inconsistent that it cannot be safer for us to travel this way. And by the way,
why don't we have that same shit on the train? Did they not blow up a fucking train in Madrid?
Did they not blow up buses and tube stations in the UK? Why no security there?
Where actual terrorism took place? Why? Because you're full of shit!
Hey Adam, Jason Sandiego. Comment on your clairvoyant. As always, curious on why clairvoyant
never talked to Jesus. And people think they're crazy already for talking to dead people.
I just want to go out with the bang and talk to Jesus, or if you want to go that eye, you know,
those are Abraham, uh, bunch of pilots, these are anyone of those guys.
I forget I'd like to talk to one of them. Any who.
Many who. All right, so what? Thank you. Thank you for changing the topic because I was
getting really out of control there. You're referring to Gordon Smith, spirit messenger. We're launching
his show, um, hopefully either this Sunday or next Sunday, but at least in the next two weeks,
we've already shot the pilot the first episode. And this is bone chilling. Now Gordon Smith is not
a clairvoyant, okay? He calls himself a grief counselor, but he does literally speak to the dead.
And when you see this show, it's fucking bone chilling. I'm telling you. How good he is at,
um, you know, not only passing on messages, but describing this person's personality,
just a lot of information without any prior knowledge, of course.
And I have to say that if it's really possible, this guy is doing it.
Uh, it's certainly very convincing to me. Gordon is subject of a lot of discussion right now in the
in the UK. And this is quite interesting the way this came together. You know, I've been talking
about Gordon Smith for, uh, if not several probably even two months now. And he's a subject of a
lot of discussion in the UK, particularly in the press because the McCain family, uh, have apparently
reached out to him, asked him if he would like to see if he can get in touch with, with, with Madeline,
with Maddie. Um, and he says, well, look, you know, if, if she's really dead, uh, and the parents
come and visit me, uh, she'll tell me exactly what happened and where she is. I know I can do that.
No problem. Boy, wouldn't that solve a lot, huh? So I'm presuming that they're actually going to do this.
Uh, you know, I'm presuming these parents are innocent, um, before proven guilty, obviously.
Um, so why doesn't he talk to Jesus? Well, I think there's two reasons. One is it's very hard,
you know, there's no, there's no other party involved. There's no one who actually knew Jesus at the
time, uh, and can, uh, and can say, yeah, you're right. And, you know, this is his personality. That's,
that's a good description. Um, same goes for any of the other people you mentioned. So it would be kind
of unbelievable anyway, but quite honestly, quite honestly, uh, isn't the whole point of Jesus that we
can't talk to him because he came back from the dead and he's not actually dead. Get him a question
for another show, perhaps. All right. One more song from the pod save music network before I head out
here, got to go to London today. I heard this one on the Jersey Todd show. And the director.
It's going to be a bit of TSA energy out there. Crash a bit, baby, baby, baby.
All the way you say, but Joe stopped recording until, month beat, huh, you want
to stop. Stop doing that week. Don't stop. Take it all the way.
Baby, baby, baby, come out and show me what you got baby!
Oh no, I don't cry.
This is so good.
I want to take it off.
Yes, we're scared, I'll open my bed.
I want to penetrate, but don't stop.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Tell me how you want me to stop.
No, no, no, no.
Take it all the way.
Baby, baby, baby.
Come on, and show me what you got.
Don't stop, honey.
Red or spring, and I'm trying to create it all alone.
Tell me just what turns you on.
What did you want?
Baby, baby, baby.
Come out and show them what you got made there, made there, made there
Come out and show them what you got
Don't stop honey, what I don't promise
I'll try new places, I'll let it all
Tell me just what you do, what you do, what you do
Come out and show them what you do
Take that stick, that new TSA crack pipe
100 milliliters of bond water
It's good to be alive when you hear something like this
I don't hear that shit on the radio
Go tuning your top 40 station for that
And never after
Before I cut out just one more TSA comment because it's so wonderful
You know I feel completely stupid right now
I feel like I completed it
And this is Scott by the way from the Alaska pod show
And it's I'm really tired right now
So just bear with me here
But if I just been this stupid this long
If I just been taking it and just completely brainwashed
Because you know I'm listening to this TSA stuff
I'm listening to raise conversations in the stories
You know and we're coming back from this from this shoot
Down in Southeast Alaska and I'm going through TSA and they make this big deal
About this 4.3 ounce bottle of lens clear camera lens cleaner
$7.99 since plus shipping and handling it's my blast bottle
And then we'll let me bring it on a plane
I can't even begin to convince them to let me keep it
This is a joke, it's a joke, it's refined bullshit
This is good as it gets
You know because I'm flying it at cruising altitude
And in first class and this is the first time I've flown in first class in a long time
Since 9.11 it's been a long time
Oh man how do you survive
And I'm flying along and I'm just like I'm really hungry
I get smaller food and they bring the food in front of me
And I'm getting a couple bites and then I look down at my hands
I'm like my god
I've got a metal fork in knife in my hand
And real dishes ceramic
Sitting right in front of me
I don't think I need to explain it much more here
But can't these be used as weapons?
And didn't they just make a big deal about my 4 ounce bottle of lens cleaner?
Oh man I just feel like it completed it
How do I go on?
It's a human being
Just to think that they think that I'm this gullible
I don't know
Hey I miss my daily daily search goods
But and I know you're busy man
Gotta pay the bills
I gotta pay the bills
So I look forward to the shows all the time and the brain food
And man
Something's gotta be done here
This is ridiculous
Take care guys
Bye
Scott man
You totally made my day with that
And I like that processing by the way
You sound a great on that
That's right
We're all fucking stupid
They're laughing at us
Someone is laughing very loudly at us
My friends
Follow the money
And we'll talk tomorrow
Another pot show pot guest
Stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering pot show and limelight