This is Chef Mark from Remarkable Palette and Jennifer from Food Philosophy.
We've got the perfect recipe for seasoning your pocho experience to perfection.
Start with a network full of informative content and talented podcasters.
Add a heaping tablespoon of great listeners who can make the experience even better with their feedback.
Perhaps your dashboard isn't mashing or you're having trouble locating that fantastic podsafe song you heard.
Pocho wants to know how you want your entertainment served.
Just head on over to survey.pocho.com and register to add your own spice to the dish.
And we like it spicy.
Okay, we know you have the DSC 625.
We only want to the show.
So come out nice and easy.
Playing the DSC 625 with you and no one will get hurt.
It seems that using the waterclaws it based on our infrared scans.
And that's the only use of folders so it may take it as a while.
Okay, after you wipe your bum, bring out the DSC 625.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Here is the one we're on.
I should've known who it was along.
This region.
I keep finding you.
This dimension always keeps me finding something.
But try to avoid your wrath.
We've got some changes to my path.
I thought I had it all figured out.
But even when I was above,
I turned around and there you are.
This region.
I keep finding you.
This generation always keeps me finding something new.
I can't walk you the way from you.
It's true.
The chase is what it thought we can do.
So I guess I should get used to you.
This I should get used to you.
But I know who it was along.
I turned around and there you are.
I keep finding you.
This dimension always keeps me finding something new.
It's kind of got the California sound, don't you?
John Hoskinson.
This rejection.
I guys don't we all know it.
Daddy source code episode number four hundred and twenty six.
I ended kind of nicely.
Didn't that.
Oops.
Oh man.
Who's calling me?
Where are you?
Where's?
I'll just have to wait.
Is the Nokia saying who it is?
Ah, yes.
It is the sales weasel extraordinaire.
A to the B.
We have an A to the B on the sales team.
Forget it.
Come into you from the affluent suburb of Surrey known as
Gilford.
We're on the west side of G town from the curry manner all the way up in Adams attic.
This is the daily source code.
Oh boy.
Sorry about yesterday.
I tried to post the show before I had to go to London and something was wrong.
I don't know if it was cast blaster or something on the network.
But I tried twice to upload before I had to leave and I left it for a third
time to upload and just never made it.
So I didn't get back until nine 15 last night from from the UK crash pad.
It was very busy.
First of all, the road was busy.
That sucked.
Although the trip in and I take a car service in if I'm going later in the afternoon.
Well, if I'm not going first thing in the morning because of course nothing beats the train at that point.
And it's nice because all the way up the what is it the A three and twenty five
God knows what I'm driving on.
You can really see the cloud formations and it's been quite spectacular this past week.
You might have read that we had severe flooding.
Yeah.
No, you left a voicemail.
We had severe flooding of north and I still have to take a trip up north to to Gerro.
I was planning on doing it this week.
That's where Christina's pink mini is located.
It's like 250 miles north right near Newcastle.
Luckily, Newcastle has a fantastic airport.
So that trip is planned for this weekend.
Saturday or Sunday when the weather's just a little bit better.
And I can take someone along who knows the area.
Anyway, yesterday, let's see two well besides seeing everybody and hanging out and shooting the shit and coming up with great ideas,
which is usually what happens when we're all altogether.
The new episode of O.J. Borges Show, 11th Commandment.
You've got to see, you've got to see this new show.
You can find it at 11 dot podshow.com, ELEV and 11 dot podshow.com.
And he's basically on a quest from God who has given him an 11th commandment,
and that is the whole show not be boring.
And he gets into, he interviews this,
was at MMA type cage wrestling, ultimate fighter dude.
And he does the interview while basically being pummeled.
And you know, O.J. is not a puny guy.
I mean, he's muscular and he's got some meat on them bones.
And he got, in fact, one of the, you left to see it for yourself.
But one of the fighters said, I can make you cry like a girl within 30 seconds.
And O.J. is like, oh, yeah, sure, sure, sure.
I think it was 17.3 seconds.
He was already warning like a baby.
So that's up today, 11 dot podshow.
11 dot BT podshow.com, if you will.
Then one of our investors from the DAG group was in London vacationing,
so he dropped by, he had never seen the crash pad,
and it lived up to his expectations completely.
And that was always fun to meet with our investors,
because these guys are just so out in the stratosphere when it comes to smarts.
And understand a lot of different marketplaces that were not as well versed in.
So it was great to catch up with him.
And then a guy came by and this was a hookup.
That's actually probably what the sales we used to land was calling about.
It was, let me just, Anthony Holden is his name.
I don't know if you've ever heard this name.
But he wrote a, well, he's, he is an author.
He's written a number of books.
Some of them about the royal family, actually, to make it even crazier.
But he wrote a, a cult classic about poker called,
Oh, Jay, let me just see.
This is great, great show prep curry.
Holden, I'll tell you exactly what his name was.
What his, what the name of his book was.
He wrote one of them, which I think sold over like a million copies.
He had big deal, that's it.
And he wrote a new one, recently called, a bigger deal.
And it's really more about the culture of, of poker than about the games themselves.
But this guy is, is quite a celebrity on the poker circuit.
And in fact, he's on his way.
I think today or tomorrow to the world poker tour in Vegas.
And he was really interested in, in turning some of his books into audio novels.
He wants to do, you know, one of our classic formats, which is a roundtable of experts about anything.
Which we've discussed on this show works extremely well.
And he would love to do that.
I was like to do some video stuff.
So it was really enjoyable because this guy was so knowledgeable and fucking sharp.
But he also had a total poker player or a bottom.
He came in like a cloud of smoke, literally.
And just every, out of every poor of his body was oozing smoke.
And he's like, yeah, I like places where I can smoke.
That's why I'm going to Vegas.
Hey, man, we'll put a deal.
I'm talking like he was American, but he was actually proper English.
No, we'll put, we'll put in agreement together.
When I come back from Las Vegas, or if I win, we'll do the deal in Las Vegas.
Like, all right.
So that was good.
That was, it's fun when you meet people who are really into something and that there's
a real marketplace for it.
You know, poker is booming booming.
So look for a poker channel to be erected soon.
Project Cheddar still going very well.
Andrew and Devon has promised me to deliver updates as they come along.
There's really nothing.
The probably won't be anything to report until sometime next week.
And hopefully we'll be surfacing some of this stuff live.
So you can see it.
There's a good healthy discussion going on at daily source code.com in the show notes,
comments, as well as at curry.com about what these channels are and what they do and how they work.
And so far, we're seeing two groups of people really, really enjoying them.
One is audience members and advertisers, interestingly enough,
for also really gravitating towards the concept of channels of package content.
So we'll just keep plugging away.
Also had a chat with the Chris McIntyre to know as many to many known as the Firf.
And the Firf has taken a very important role now in the company.
You know, of course, he's the Lord and Master of Podcast Ali.
But he now is literally sitting inside the developer group.
And he'll be managing our APIs and developer relations.
Yeah, we have right now, I think is fairly simple.
It's based on XML RPC.
So in the next week or so, we'll be adding new, this is just for geeks.
We'll be adding new APIs.
I think we're a rest interface and JSON and there's maybe something else.
I don't know, but he'll be calling in regularly to let us know as well.
And I'm sure at least one person will be happy with us.
I think, bro, winner, at your command, it's the role of the program.
That's right, from San Francisco, California.
I add them.
It's a prolific program.
I hear from San Francisco.
I noticed on DSC, whatever the show was, for Tuesday,
June 26th, you were talking about Gordon Brown.
I am British and I believe he and Blair are two things the same back side.
And that's the same kids.
Two, what of the back side?
Maybe men, two sides of the same coin, what was that?
You know, I believe he and Blair are two things the same back side.
And that's the same kids.
Two cheeses of the same size.
I can't understand a prolific program.
But I do appreciate it.
By the way, I forgot to thank Ed, who sent me a couple suggestions for some music to play on the show.
Where's Ed from?
Suitcase full of dimes.
Interesting.
Suitcase full of dimes.blogspot.com.
Yeah, very good.
Very good suggestion, dude.
Totally appreciated.
A couple more suggestions and recommendations that came in.
I want to actually play a music video for you.
Because the song is so awesome.
And I think it's pretty much a mainstream license.
Probably has a record deal type song.
I've never heard of the artist before, but I'm sure many of you have Rodney Carrington.
And this is obviously a copyrighted video that's up there on YouTube because it's from some kind of television special.
And I'll put a link to it in the show notes.
But it's something that I think you'll enjoy listening to the lyrics for sure.
But then when you go back and look at the video, you will not be disappointed.
So if you close your eyes and imagine, I'll try and give you the setting.
It's probably like a 700 to 1000 seat venue.
It's a nice stage.
Guy with a cowboy hat, blue jeans sitting on a stool with a gift fill with his guitar.
And he is singing a song called Show Them To Me.
And well, listen along and you'll get the general, the gist of it.
And then when you go back to watch the video at home, you'll be smiling even more.
I don't know if I love you, but you sound like somebody I could love.
Drought and horny.
And I love that.
Oh, it seems to mean this whole world long crazy.
There's too much hate and killing going home.
When I see the bare chest of the woman, my worries and my problems are all gone.
No one thinks fighting when they see your topless girl.
Maybe if you'd show yours too, we could save the world.
Right, so you get it.
Now the audience, we see the audience and the audience is lit up.
And there she goes.
God bless you.
I don't care if they don't match your arms, but you're in the other.
You can show me one.
And I'll imagine the other.
Even if you're really old, there's nothing wrong.
Don't be saggy, boobs ain't bad.
They're just a little long show them to me.
Them down to me.
Little sleepy star, to let the whole world sing.
Just like this round show with your body like that, pal.
But he got us cheeky.
What you Spanish for, Tittet Records and nothing we listen to,ש tittets.
Them down to me.
I've made a lot of them, but another one I've hated.
Even if you've had 13 kids and you think they look deflated,
there's no such thing as a bad breast.
I believe there's much is true.
If you're a big fat man, I would tell you if I hadn't,
I'd love to see yours too.
And everybody now.
Oh, no.
Another guys showing their tits.
It's kind of rough.
Yeah.
Show them the name.
Just like the girls don't wild don't TV.
Just lean back and show your act and I'll be in ecstasy.
If you've got two customers, so now to me.
Come on baby, let me see.
All the world I live in harmony.
It'll be a good little game it would.
We'll make history.
You love your country.
Yes.
It's got the flag up now.
I'm going to say one more time.
I say we love your country.
Dallas, Texas.
Do you love your country?
Yeah.
We stand here as much as everybody can to me.
I love that.
I need a gig like that, man.
What an awesome, awesome song to play live.
I'd like to shake your daddy's hand.
Never damn nice.
Thank you, sir.
We're riding those to this country.
It's been a damn pleasure, sir, for them.
Rust, if you have to be ashamed of yourselves.
Our men and women fight across C.C.
But you're fucking freedom and you can't whip out a tear.
Oh, man.
Fantastic.
I'm telling you, I need a gig like that.
Ladies, ladies, listen to this show right now.
Show them to me.
Go ahead.
Yeah.
There you go.
Just pull them out, whatever.
Oh, you've made an old man so happy.
Thank you.
And thank you, St. Clair, for sending me the link to that.
Of course, I'll put that in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Some other cool news that came in on the email.
This is from the candy man.
Now, you know, I'm a big fan of the Nokia N800, the Internet tablet, which I use,
particularly when I'm in London because I have the cloud.
So it automatically connects the network, almost wherever you are.
It turns out now.
Let me see.
Here's the announcement to EarthLink announced that Nokia N800 Internet
tablet customers can now access EarthLink's Wi-Fi service at no additional charge on
this municipal wireless networks and select cities throughout the United States.
Nokia N800 customers will be able to securely connect to EarthLink's Wi-Fi network directly from
the device to get started users click on the EarthLink Wi-Fi logo in the connections menu.
Hmm, I wonder if you have to buy it through buying it through EarthLink then.
Hmm.
Okay, so cool.
I know they have a similar deal with the cloud in the UK and that works throughout Greater London.
In fact, there's even a Wi-Fi point for the cloud in the in-gill for actually a couple, I think.
I said, I wonder if it's the same deal. I wonder if it's interchangeable.
So if I go to San Francisco, can I hook up to the EarthLink municipal Wi-Fi?
Awesome.
Oh, let me see.
Simon Powell, I add them listening to the Nylon's comment, Charlie 619er.
Is it just me or is he sounding more and more like Madge Weinstein slash Richard Bluestein by the day?
Seems to be trying to wind you up all the time.
And now what's with all that mysticurium watching you stuff?
Hmm.
On a totally unrelated note, why does the Delta Sierra have a US registration when it seems to be UK slash NL base?
Just wondering if it was bought and registered in the states and then brought over here somehow?
Well, by definition, the the make and model of the of the Delta Sierra is of course manufactured in the United States.
All good airplanes, the consists of sheet metal and rivets, they come from the US.
The sheet metal and rivets guy, by the way, I'm not a composite wing dude.
Not completely convinced about the serious in that regard.
So the registration is a very interesting thing.
And the main reason why mine is an N-redge, which is US based, is to fit with my license.
I have license by the FAA.
So I can fly an N-redge aircraft as piloting command, solo, etc.
I think there are different rules for G and a Dutch registration would be PH.
Not quite sure what those subtle differences are, but I do know that it's a hell of a lot easier to have an N-redge aircraft.
And in fact, taking it through to a G or different type of registration, I believe it's a process that sucks.
Or as they say in aviation, the process is done when the pile of paperwork falls over of its own accord.
It just makes it a lot simpler for me to do anything I want with an N-redge aircraft on my FAA license.
Oh, I immediately go into pilot error.
Hello Adam, it's Martin.
Hey, GD.
I've got a bonus podcast.
Just wanted to relate to that little story to you, something that happens to me over the weekend.
And we see the text message from two friends of mine, who are wavering for the weekend,
down in Grastery for the festival.
Thought to their knees in mud.
And they were welcome on a Saturday morning by my voice.
Now they knew for well, I wasn't there because I'd already spoken to them on the Friday night,
but Crystal could hear my voice.
Now this is about eight o'clock in the morning.
As you can imagine, they're not feeling very healthy.
At that time in the morning, freezing cold still went from the night before.
And my voice is booming out.
So they pop the hell out of their tent and tried to figure out where the sound was coming from.
And we realized it was coming from the tent next to this.
It wasn't me in person, of course.
Suddenly, in that tent, was playing on a podcast.
Nice and loud in the middle of the campsite.
A glass tree.
How cool is that?
Now this just shows that podcast is really taking off here in the UK.
The kids at Grastery, they know their music.
And here they are, away from the weekend, see some of the best bands in the world on the stages there.
And what's they playing to entertain themselves when there's no bands playing?
That's right.
GD's by size bonus.
When my friends went into do some sales to the people next door and said,
We know GD, they actually text me and asked me to send a photo message to them to their mobile phone.
So they could prove they actually knew me.
They actually got chatting with these people, they had a lot in common.
So GD's, you know, 18 the world, not only in music, but in French, as well.
Yes.
And this is just one more step forward for podcasting.
It won't be long before I have my own stage at Grasterbury.
Until that day comes, of course, you can catch me five days a week,
monthly through to Friday at biteousbonus.podshow.com.
Oh, and one more thing, drink coke.
Yeah, drink coke, please, please don't mess.
When you buy coke, do get music.
You can win an iPod or free songs on iTunes.
As Cool GD, I've had a moment like that.
And I agree with you that this is definitely catching on in the UK.
And of course, it's not hard to think that eventually we're going to start, you know,
bursting through and little pockets of interest start to pop up and people are catching us.
So to have that happen, it is awesome.
I remember when I was driving from Amsterdam to Antwerp, and I was actually recording a show.
And this was in 2004.
All of a sudden someone was honking next to me and it was Raymond,
our buddy Raymond Port, who then held up as iPod and said,
Dude, I'm listening to today's show.
And I'm like, dude, I'm recording tomorrow's show.
It was another one of those fantastic moments.
Yeah, we got, we got reach, man.
Absolutely.
And the kids, of course, they're always going to be looking to find the coolest.
And I think that, you know, in a in a strange,
perverted kind of like Herman Monster Way, you're a father figure to them.
I hope they came out right.
A couple of emails from people who say they're very familiar with Barry from Wattford
who called him to the show yesterday.
He actually has a, has his own website, Barry from Wattford.com.
And he's been on the late edition with Marcus Briggs stock.
A couple other, that's on BBC Four.
And I thought he was on some television some morning show as well.
And yeah, he's pretty funny.
So he's been, and I do recall now, I actually met with him.
And he was thinking of joining the show.
So I guess that's a good sign that he's, that he's on the way in.
Oh, my goodness.
It's going to be pretty busy today.
We're scheduled to talk to all of our top shows and producers over the course of the next few days.
So I got to hurry up and prepare for that.
It's, you know, it's time to just give everyone a call.
See everyone's doing see what the gripes are.
There's always something going on.
I'm always something we can do to suck less.
And I would encourage you if you, if you'd like to make what we do better.
And I'm not just talking about this show, but any show that you listen to.
We are doing a massive survey.
I would like you to join the super panel.
This is a part of that whole suckless campaign.
Go to survey.podshow.com.
And sign up, fill out the survey.
I think it's one a month and you're going to be, you know, it's really like doing new movie surveys and stuff.
So you'll be asked to, you know, to listen and to watch different types of advertising and give your feedback and host endorsements.
And really it's just trying to figure out what we can do to make the experience better.
We've already learned one important thing and that has something to do with 60 seconds of stuff.
But we're, you know, happy Monday, Adam.
What do you mean happy Monday?
It's hum day dude.
It's Wednesday here.
It was just wiping my ass when I thought you had fuller scruncher, hit her formal pull.
Nice.
I'm ready to declare winner.
Holders.
I have a new question.
Do you standard you sit?
Let me start.
Adam and the folding standard.
I have one other experiment I would like to do.
www.gotnate.com.
Do you think I should have updated by vlog or even paid good editing for hosting before sending this in?
To talk.
And again, happy Monday.
Thank you.
It's Wednesday.
I think you should check out code dsc3.
That'll certainly get you some mileage.
Go dead daddy.
What is this?
When it's cold outside, I've got no complaints.
I guess it's for you who said what can make me feel this way.
I want to come to my hotel.
Maybe I will need you out.
Me.
I'm feeling the way you carry yourself, girl.
And I want to get with you because you're the dude.
So if you want to come to my hotel, all you've got to do is how to edit me.
If you haven't, I have some party.
I'm knocking out six in the morning.
On the morning.
On the sun.
Oh
We the new car tells all tell when the kid
If you mean start acting up acts for him or acts for me
You see we could look at the crack it, but you know what the habit we'd be under the troubles making love to be clever
I got the double hit once the sleep on the other one to get my free on this off
I walked for the lady hit them off for the lady she just laughed for the lady my heart
Talked up for the lady pop up for the lady. I got love for the lady
You want to come to my hotel
Baby I'm gonna give you my room
I'm feeling the way you carry yourself though
And I'm gonna give what you cause you's a kill
So if you want to come to my hotel
You gotta do it for a baby
If you haven't had the authority
Checking out six in the morning
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh
I've got so
I got us with a s Chef
Yeah, you say you can make me feel this great, so great
If you want a party night till late, oh I will do a good thing
Say, oh, just come to my hometown, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Maybe I won't make it, no, I'm feeling the way it carry yourself there
Then I want to get with you because you's a kid, no, if you want to come to my hotel
You've gotta do it, tolerate goodwill
Having an alcohol party, checking out six in my morning
I have to say that's about the perfect mashup for a Wednesday
Nice smello
Some old school built in DJ
To reset my girl hotel, mashing up the temptation of my girl
And of course, Cassidy featuring our Kelly with a phone tape
I'm gonna keep it short
So I'll leave you with that for today
Please check the phone numbers at datasourceco.com
And give us a call
Get your hands up
Oh boy, and get your submissions in for Fubar Friday
I'm saving up for it to be another rock and show
I've got a new mode Jones will be playing
And of course your request as well, so make sure that gets in
Adam at podshow.com
DailySourceco.com, talk to you tomorrow
Y'all
Show them to me
The other podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest served up daily
By the sharpest minds in content delivery
Podshow and Livelight