Hey, man, that was a great party last night, man, I had so much fun and whoa, dude, you're
not looking so good.
Yeah, I guess I should kind of confess to somebody, last night when I got home, I was
so drunk, I blew chunks.
Hey, man, that's cool, everybody, you know everybody throws up sometimes, as long as you
hit the toilet, it's okay, man, it's no problem.
No, no, man, you're on your stage.
That's, that's sick, that's football, that's like DSC642 football.
In a world where TV networks, movie studios and record labels still think they can
govern what you see in here, one man has the power to return control of entertainment to
the masses and make big media corporations wet their tiny little pants.
In Pod Show, home of the world's most dangerous new content comes the daily source code
with Adam Curry.
You know, I remember back in the day, back before Adam was, I don't know, making cheese or
whatever the hell this cheddar project is, you knew what day a DSC was going to come out.
He wasn't that busy and pretty much this was what he did all day, sat around, checking his
email, pulling down audio tracks and getting ready for the DSC.
And now it appears he's gotten a little bit too big for a daily podcast, so he's going
to put out for a week and you're just going to have to figure out what days they're on.
So I don't know if it's going to be a food bar Friday or a meaningless Monday or what
day it's going to be, but this is the daily source code 642.
It was $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation
renew content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this genre.
Just like wich is a black mass in it.
Oh, people, minds and blood is structured.
So far out of debt's construction.
Oh, even the feet of bodies burning.
As the warm machine keeps turning.
Oh, there's a big kitchen in the sky.
Oh, poisoning their rainwater.
Oh, water.
Way down.
Far down.
That's an opener.
Black zeppelin.
It is the daily source code episode number 642.
How you doing everybody coming to you from the swanky server.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, it was apologize, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
I think I have every single one of them in use so we'd have to go get a new one and I swear to God
He said, oh, you know, because I can't use the power drill. If I don't have the extension cord
I think all of Geoford is sold out
I just because I love because he does awesome things with the with the power tools
So whether once again looking pretty nice today
We have I think we'll probably have about 70% of the day will be sunshine and lots of people sending in comments about
a good friend who tried to explain El Ni単o and La Ni単a
Paul Shepherd
Clarkson says, look, let me just tell you how this works. To understand the complex El Ni単o
La Ni単a phenomena, you must know the following and pay attention because when you look at the weather report tonight
You look at it in a whole new light and by the way we gloss over weather reports so easily it affects everything in the world
As you can see from recent news reports particularly here in the United Kingdom number one all weather is driven by the sun
This is really important when the sun has its activity and you know the sun is not a stable source
It you know, there's bits of sun spots and explosions and extra heat here and there
It does affect the weather and it is the primary source of what affects the weather
And it's not really the other way round, but that's a whole other global warming question
Number two, the sun heats the earth's atmosphere unevenly
Important to understand unevenly is not one consistent source wind is moving air
And air moves from high pressure towards low pressure areas
You'll see this on the chart tonight when you look at the weather report high pressure air masses are cooler
than the low pressure air masses
Low pressure air masses are less dense than high pressure air masses
And low pressure air masses can hold more water vapor than high pressure
Air the high pressure air masses because there's more space between the various air molecules
Which of course means you know clouds they can hold a lot of rain, right?
So that's the the real fundamentals weather is an amazing thing pick up a book one day and take a look at it
It could change your life. It really good
Of course then we have good old GD Martin for a green dragon from the bite-sized bonus podcast to btpot show.com
He always relies on the the old string barometer hang a piece of string from a nail on the shed if the string is swaying
It's windy
If the string stand sideways it's very windy if the string is wet it's raining if the string is dry
It's not raining if the string is stiff it's freezing if it casts a shadow it's sunny if it casts no shadow
It's cloudy if it's invisible
It's nighttime and if the string is smoking well your sheds on fire
Once again time to open up the extra microphone because she's here to tighten my buttocks any nice exercise
Famie that
I can think of a single move for you this week, so I think we're gonna have to improvise. Okay. I'm I'm game
Stand up
And squeeze
Those cheeks
Relax okay, squeeze again deep breath and
Sweet
Please
Like I like oh can I look relax. Yeah, thank you. Oh deep breath and last time
squeeze
And relax
Is that it? Well there you have it until next time
That's what I call phoning it in Amy
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Doesn't matter how I love you
Fantastic
Amy Mac
She's gonna be our first VJ on the plus TV which I can't tell you about yeah because I don't wait to find it until it's ready
We still have some technical stuff going on. It's gonna be 24 hour a channel of like just the best video shit
You can think of not only from pod Joe, but from around the globe my friends
um
Let's see so what should we launch into there's a couple of things I want to talk about one is the iPhone
I want to keep you up to speed on that because I am of course an X-pat with an iPhone in the UK
And I've used it now for what four five days something like that
Consistently okay, let's talk about this first of all
The bad real life
Although good for a cell phone without a doubt it does not
Just doesn't cut it compared to the E61. I I could use that thing
For hours and I mean my days are 12 hour work days
Really full-time work not just you know being around but phone calls etc etc
phone calls and email I say and calendar and yeah, that would be it
I did not use to listen to many shows
Excuse me
on the on the E61
Because you know it doesn't have a dual headset it just has you know you can listen to it on speaker
Or you can listen to it through one little earbud unless you get some kind of adapter thing
In which I didn't want to carry
But that battery would hold out
longer so yes the iPhone gets just about eight hours of full-time usage including your iPod usage and your your browser
etc, but it does not make it through an entire day of one of my days
I'm still way completely down with the browsing experience. I think this is the way to go
You know it's going to be virtually impossible to convert the entire web
You know to work on mobile browsers and you wouldn't think it's just a lot easier to
Really focus on the technology and make the browser on these mobile devices better and I think that that you know Apple has set the bar right there and and that's just the end of it
It's fantastic. It's
Fantabulous if they had flash nothing not not for YouTube videos, but you know just for some basic flash stuff
Which I think the phone could handle it would be even better, but I don't really miss that
And I love it got to tell you love it
the
Well, you know
Let me let me play this comment to your first. This is uh
Can always expect it from your family. This is from my sister in Italy. Here's Willow
You traitor you you I feel like CSB
Era
Convincing everybody to get the E61 I including me your sister. I was also happy. I got it three days ago and I'll happy and then what do you do?
You turn around and go get an iPhone
With a battery life. It's so good and the screen and the browser and everything is so cool
There's only one
problem with the iPhone you have to synchronize
The worse you need iTunes
I am against iTunes. I hate synchronizing. I hate iTunes
So I'm gonna stick with my Nokia. I've been with Nokia since
1995. I love my Nokia. I love my new Nokia and I can just grab the podcasts out of the air without synchronizing
Okay, I have to admit the podcasting application. It's very basic. But it works. It's functional
The player definitely needs improvement
But I'm gonna stick with an Nokia also because I spent a lot of money on it and
iPhone I don't think this is a road. I'm gonna travel with you
Anyway, that's all. Chop it or that. Chop it or whatever that means
Oh man and that was that was the the nice version of what she told me on on the phone when we spoke a couple
days ago
You know, but
Really I think we should look at an analogy. Let's look at the road
The road being the network
Road system and let's look at cars the cars being the the devices you connect to the road
And you use the road with you know to to travel across it
You know if there was just one car that would work for everybody we'd have you know
It'll be driving Volkswagen's you know that would have been that would have been Hitler's vision
Or we could all be driving fiat 500s or the douchevo or you know there's a million a million different types of
Examples of people trying to say okay, you know, this is the one this it has everything
It's it's just not gonna happen that way. There's trade-offs everywhere. So it's not as simple as saying
I only need one mobile device
It just doesn't I don't think it works for anybody you have different mobile devices
For different occasions really which is why I believe the whole SIM card technology of essentially, you know
There's your your little card and that contains
Your personal information so your phone number it can of course can contain a number of standardized
You know contacts it can't contain all of my contacts because I just have too many
But it can contain a lot of the the ones you can just you should be able to switch from phone to phone for different reasons
I have also been using the N800 over the weekend all that also has its advantages, you know, so it doesn't have a cell phone built in but
You know, it has a touch screen. I like navigating with my fingers that that works. It has a I have to say the
The touch pad keyboard is better
I feel then than than the iPhone's not in in visual cues, et cetera, but it's spaced better. It's it works better from my fingers
You know again all of this is personal preference. It's by the way. You should be able to change that on the iPhone
We're on any virtual keyboard not every keyboard works for everybody. You know, I have the Sony via which has just about the largest keys
You've ever seen in your life
When people get on the on my laptop to you know to use it to type that's the first thing I say
Oh my god these keys are so big in this or widely space. Well look at my hands. I get the boy's got big hands. What can I tell you?
Yes, it is true
Um
So I believe that there is no Jesus box. There is no magical machine. There is no, you know, God's gadget that has everything
But you have different you know different material for different missions. It's just like airplanes. It's exactly the same thing
You know, could I get a jet?
Yeah, I could get a jet, but you know, it would cut my my missions in half. You can't land at hill versus airport in a jet
You know, you can you can barely land in a in a twin that has to be a you know one that's
Specified for it, you know grass strips are going to be a problem noise abatement all kinds of different reasons
Let alone the cost you know if I just want to fly across the channel it's a lot more efficient a lot easier
And I can get to where I want to go in the Delta Sierra you know it's all about the mission profile of what you need to do
so there is just no
no standard
No standard mobile device that is I think going to work for for everybody
But if you know I think in certain situations
I would trade off as well. I have been carrying all three devices. I'll let you know in my
Back I'm not taking my laptop the laptop stays pretty much at home and docked
But I'm taking the an 800 the E61 I and the iPhone and that's mainly because I can't switch out the SIM card
You know and just take the one device. I think I'm going to be needing for that particular day
The other thing the iPhone does extremely well
Better than than Nokia it's just fucking better is switching between the mobile network and the Wi-Fi networks
You know I have a cloud
You know the cloud dot net in the UK it's it blankets most of London most of the city with a white with Wi-Fi coverage
And I've been a lot of cabs recently in the city and you know, so I can be you know doing my mail or looking at my calendar or going through
You know my news reader which I use a Google reader for that the mobile version which is just fantastic and I can literally see
Switching between networks so I'll it'll go real fast right and and I'll so I'll be on the cloud and then I might get into a dark spot
Or it's trying to switch over
It'll immediately pick up the GPRS access and then it'll switch back once it has another Wi-Fi spot that stuff
They did extremely well
So
It's no such thing as the best the better
But as always, you know with with with Apple and and pretty much everything else the experience is just lovely is just a nice
It's like a greasy smooth
warm
Yes indeed almost almost a
Sexual feeling
Can't help it it's the truth
I've missed in co-ordinate cutter that's for those you just tuning into the source code thing what the hell is going on with this cheese
Still
Chitterbee cheese cheddar kind of sounding like channeled or if you say it fast a couple hundred thousand times which I said
Certainly these bad many times in the past few weeks
Channel
Editor
Channel editor
Top editor
Chudder
No, Chudder channel editor
Channel editor channel editor channel editor channel editor channel editor
Oh
Welcome to daily source code
Uh-huh
Yeah, I saw about a thousand channels created over the weekend people starting to try it out and I noticed something really interesting on the iPhone if you and you know we have the RSS link now
Next to every single channel so you know you can play it in a variety of ways
If you if you're using the iPhone and you know a patch out our com looks looks great in fact the channels page is just
Look awesome on the iPhone if you zoom in and you click on the RSS link it'll then bring up
That channel
Through it's interesting. It actually goes through a dot Mac like proxy, but it doesn't matter how it does it
It actually brings up a nice page which you can bookmark
Which becomes
You know the the channel page on your iPhone and if you're connected you can get any of the content in you because most I would say most
Independently produced
Video these days is is done in quick time. Yeah, it has the pew has the pew Institute done a study on that please
Yeah, I would have to say that the original fire material most of it even the stuff that winds up on YouTube is probably created in quick time
I could be wrong
But I have a sneaky suspicion about that so of course
You know the quick time is integrated very nicely into the iPhone and it works man
You pop it up and because you know I have it all set to I think every single show in my channels
Like my on the go channels all set to one to poop out one show at the end so it's really clear all of a sudden
Instead of all these episodes mixed through each other you can't really tell what's what now. It's you know
It's obvious. I know what I know I can see what what these shows are and I see if I've played it or not. It's
It's really nice. I also messed around
Using a couple of freely available widgets
To create channel widgets some examples of that at curry dot com really excited. I've not
You know I'm actually enjoying now that I can manage this stuff a little bit better
I'm actually enjoying shows that I completely forgot night subscribe to
Because they were coming out so and frequently that they were pretty much pushed down to you know the bottom of the list and I never really get to them
Or never see them and so all of that's changed and I really I've also gone through a little bit of you know
Reorganary management of of my media and can't wait to start building some dynamic channels stuff that
Pod show will build out of connections that your channel makes because remember you know if if you have a a show
In one of your channels and someone else has that same show
In one of their channels. Well, that's going to make some kind of connection there that we should be able to surface
A lot of that is kind of like LinkedIn. I like the way LinkedIn does that we run and I worked on that over the weekend and
You see how these connections are made that's basically people
I think that there's a connections in relationships between people in media and media media and people and
Where I think we're coming up with some pretty pretty interesting stuff and that'll all be reflected in the new UI
Which is being worked on very hard as we speak and only two more weeks and that's off to the states for the big curry family reunion in an upstate in New York
Actually an armunk
It's gonna be awesome
That's where I'm gonna see willow of course and the kids and and Uncle Don right this is it's actually now Uncle Don's house
So finally we're gonna have the big Uncle Don interview
Which will probably mainly focus on North Korea, but I think we can talk about George W and the guy has a lot of experience
You know he was in multiple governmental organizations and is now the CEO of the
Korean society so I think he had a quite a large hand in the in the most recent negotiation so looking forward to that
Then of course nice weather here in the UK
You know Adam
Cameron eat from Australia
Is it getting here I'm not I don't understand here. I'm actually from New Zealand
I'll just listen to
Do see 641 in you talking about
Some nice looking people in Australia and some nice looking men mate the second place is full of bad
I believe in people that need a bath and I'm sure if it's quite a few family trees that don't fall
Can this town either
They just go very cool because there's a lot of children's marrying and a lot of brothers and sister seven six
They're actually nice people about our people at least some real fucking he'll believe down here
Lepa show
I don't believe you. I've been to Australia. I only saw beautiful people. I didn't see any ugly people
You know hey for those of you it down under semi pictures of your girlfriends and wives will ya?
I'm I'm certain that it's pretty people down there
Please and if you want to send them you know as naked pictures that's okay, too
I am it's the candy man here
Sorry about all those long-text messages
I look the candy man from Nokia. Yeah, look look look look look look look like you know
It's that I barely respond to email these days because I'm just too busy
So now he sends me text messages and they get broken up into 15 parts
Hey question for you
Has to BBC you'd become evil
Today they launched their online video service which they call I play or I think and
apparently it uses
some kind of X
Controls there so you can only use it with the internet explorer and you're not able to use it with
Mozilla or Firefox or
Hopera or even Safari so has to be the sea going from this kind of open and friendly company to an evil
Deceptive media house
Let me know what you think thanks. Why I may be a little bit harsh there Luke, but I there is a lot of talk about that the BBC has released
Stay what they call the eye player and it is kind of their version of podcasting
You know they they're trying to walk the thin line between
Don't let people keep stuff and use it or reference it or go back to it. You know make it disappear after seven days
So they can it's a catch-up service not it's not an alternative distribution with that's kind of the offensive part
And the reason why they chose Microsoft
Technologies because of the digital rights management, you know
It essentially will handle all of that stuff for them. So that's not evil. That's just the choices they make as a license
Payer as a pair of for the TV license saying about 136 pounds a year
I feel that they should have done a little more investigation and probably made that a little more accessible to people indeed with
You know if people said windows 95 I don't know if it will run on that. I think you explicitly have to have
Who still has windows 95 with the fuck am I talking about no one as we know
more maybe
It was it's a professional edition 2003 or whatever
But no max no Linux no alternative browsers
So I don't think that they've done their homework properly and they've they've rushed to get something out just to you know quote
Compete with what's happening with video online
Honestly, I think it's a shame. I hope they don't get rid of all their podcast links because I think that stuff is awesome
I I consume BBC
Programming all the time you can see it in my channels go look at my on the go channel you see the daily
Breakfast which is a compilation of stuff that they put together of a video show in the morning. I love it, you know, and yes
I'm willow. I'm
Once again roped into iTunes, but it's it's okay, you know, it hasn't crashed on me yet
knock on wood and and when I sink the phone up in the morning it's it's got my shit on there, you know and and other stuff
I'll just find through through the web browser
channels
So I hope they keep that and I don't know
From a competitive standpoint, yeah, it's great because you know, they're just not gonna be getting the same type of traction
I registered for the eye player
It appeared to still be in beta or beta as we say here and and I was waiting for confirmation email didn't receive any so I'm not sure if it's public
If I'm going to the wrong link or I don't know it doesn't seem like they did it really is simple release something that's easy to find
oh well hey
Since I missed the food bar Friday, I have hit test number 80 queued up for you
haven't heard it obviously
But it is one that young created just before
He got the the terrible news that I talked about on Thursday and
And Gary sent in a message which he said you know didn't necessarily have to play publicly, but I do want to because uh
Young and his wife Victorian went through a really bad experience
Or she miscarried their child and
Oh, here's Gary Alexander from the ultimate podcast and mind you this is the guy
Who's into ultimate fighting and cage fighting and stuff and oh, he's a softer side to him
Hi Adam is Gary Alexander from Vegas
Listen, I just listen to Thursdays episode and that would be this is basically just for for you and actually
I don't have it. I really don't know much about y'all pull it
This is what I hear when you show, but this is actually
You know something that maybe you could just tell him that you know
I don't know so let me know how to get touch with whatever. I've been in the same boat. We are my wife and I have lost
Two babies one as a miscarriage and one is a steel birth that eight to have months and
Actually there was a there's a beautiful story because along with my daughter Bella that
We lost it eight and a half months
Wonderful butterfly story is just a beautiful thing and I
I really can't help but to have my heart go out to this guy and I'm sure that there's been a lot of people contact him and tell them that they've been through the same thing
too many people have
I do a lot of work for the march of dimes and I'm very appreciative for all that they do for children and
development and research and
Kind of the big thing much of the arms is a huge huge huge supporter for for that kind of
Up tragedy so
You know, let them know that the next donation that I make will definitely be
in their name and I really really do
Just feel for them because I know all too well
So
That's my time. Thanks
All right man. That's so beautiful. Thank you
And I love the fact that you you called it a a butterfly story. I think that was a reference to my mom so
I appreciate it very much
No, students
Recording this on my Nokia 770 that I got for a grand total of
Great British
Anyway
Cheddar
Got a small problem with it. You can have a look on my
Daddy Dows at poncho dot com on daddydows dot poncho dot com
My little feed of gone there which is called freaking cheese F or iKKI and cheese
I've put some feeds in there including the DSC one of one of my favorite episodes from Tiki bar where La La
Shets her snakeskin
Yeah, it's too best of you cute
Um, which were really good but they're not showing up in my feed and I choose
I wonder if you can explain that one because I can't I've tried adding it taking it out
Having it taken it out no doesn't work
So yeah, good concept as you know I understand it but yeah that one doesn't work which is a bit of a pig
Just me all right. Yeah, you figured something out all right
So the the YouTube stuff
Is flash-based and that's really where your problem stems from because
Excuse me
I don't even have a sponsor to tip tip tip tip today do I that way I'll I'll pimp cover girl
They're launching with it is blibromouth up yet blibromouth TV
Blibromouth dot com I think it is blibromouth dot poncho dot com anyway
Um
Those are currently not being put into the downloadable feed if you were to play your channel in the mashboard
Which is a selection right there you can say play channel or just select play and mashboard from the drop down
Then they will show up
But obviously
If your phone well, I I don't know does your I guess your phone does understand flash so
We could put that in we could put the actual flash files in I'm not sure if they're going to play properly
This is where you get into a whole bunch of problems the good the same goes for pod safe music
You know the the whole point of the pod safe music network is we're not making them these songs freely
Downloadable for anyone to just go and grab but they're you know
They're available for producers to put into their shows and then promote the songs
So again if you get an artist on podshow.com
You will be able to play that artist songs
In fact, they will play nicely in order through the mashboard, but they're not downloadable and that's because
We don't have the rights to make them downloadable if we could change that. Oh, man that would be awesome
And of course the question is
I mean, I know I know the immediate answer, but there's there's maybe ways around it. What if
You know there's a best of YouTube
There's a YouTube clip that's put into someone's channel and we were to transcode it back to say mp4
So would play on an iPod or just you know playing general if we just
Transcoded to age dot 264 or whatever the norm is these days
That is of course theft
Because you're you're taking someone's content and transcoding it now we can report that back through technology quite easily
We could tell the YouTube server. Hey, you know we got a download of of this video so out of view count
But that still doesn't remove the whole idea that it has now been been downloaded onto a device and it's kind of free so
I don't have the rights to do that James so it's not that we technically can't do it. It's that
Well, we technically legally can't do it
Uncrafting casting with Adam coming
Hey Adam
Are you ready to be stumps bring it on?
He's the new test
Yes, we've got a problem. Let's do it. Hey Adam. Are you doing this great is it does number 80
And we're going to start right away. So here we go. This is intro number one
Easy easy easy
Do we lose ham the news that would be the power of love from back to the future?
I know I got that one right number two
I'm going to have to say I'm stumped on that one. I did not recognize it at all and today's final intro number three
I'm doing that far out of the I know that one
That is Mick Jagger. I think with Michael Jackson and state of shock an awesome collaboration between the two and times up in these hardy answers
And to number one from 1985 he will lose and the news
But it's a power of love
From 1985 he will lose and the news and the power of love
I happen to hear we lose and this is answer number two the Meg band roses are red
Oh
And so number two from 1988 the Meg band and roses are red and this is the third and final answer from 1984
This
Answer number three
The Jackson's together with Mick Jagger you come you come you come me in the state of shock and state of shock
And that's it for it this is number 80
I
Must tell you that it's a real challenge every time to
Edit those tracks back to about 30 seconds and well one tracks better than the others
Well, it all depends on the track itself
It's a kind of fun to do
That kind of stuff, so I hope you had them all and you enjoyed this one Adam
Info about this hit us the answers and items you can be found and hit us the partial dot com
Next week call the back for hit test number 81 so until then take care and bye-bye
Yo, y'all my man thank you so much
You know that that's second one
I you can play that for me again and I still won't get it but man I love hearing the Jackson's with Nick Jagger again
Gosh, and what are we your combination when you think about it? Can you just imagine those guys in the studio together?
Red pill blue pill moment a lot of people sent me this and and I know Patricia and I have talked about this on the show a couple of times
about the and it's not just the
Penelope cruise laurel commercial which is
For mascara and if you haven't read this of course, I'll put a link in the show notes
This just shows you you know how incredibly
Deceptive advertising is now for four years Patricia's been saying this and I'm sure
Several times throughout those years she's mentioned it on the show she she really despises these
mascara commercials the same goes for Kate Moss with Rimmol and in fact in this article you say they'll even a loot to it that it's a
Industry practice to essentially put fake eyelashes on the women who are demonstrating the wonderful
long-lasting lash extending mascara which of course is crap
So finally
Who is it the advertising standards authority?
Have called them out and said this is misleading
in particular the
Penelope cruise laurel commercial who said right here it's common industry practice to use artificial lashes
That's such a harsh shit oh
Man
Particularly cosmetics and what do you think photo shop is used for?
You know go look at Vogue magazine tell me everyone looks that beautiful. I
Yeah, it's unraveling right before I very eyes my friends. It's happening. We're too smart
We're figuring all this shit out and we're calling people out on it and it's gonna
Cause for a lot of confusion. It's gonna get a lot worse before it gets better, but it's gonna get better
Hello, hi Adam
This is Shane and Amy from a year at the wheel back
Yeah, this is Shane. I am not Shane and Amy. I mean guys are like in the and only one speaker
All right
We've got to work on your audio set up my friends if you're gonna take Trinity out on the road for a year
Well, I'm Amy. No, I say people adjust you from now on as Shane and Amy you like that. Yes
Especially because my name comes first
So we've been mulling over the
Reasons the tour should start in Chicago. Yeah, and Chicago is the place to be isn't that we're all the politicians
Come to win the Midwest and when they win the Midwest they win the election
True. How about the Democratic National Convention the riots that Mayor daily same we preserved this order here
Was that the 68 one? Yeah the night. Oh, yeah the 1968 Democratic National Convention exactly and that's where the
Hamarket riots were what the hell does that have to do with anything? Wasn't that we're the
Anarchy party was born? Oh, well, okay, we'll talk about that on a podcast on a year at the wheel
But also Adam, you know, I have a lot of surprises for the listeners and the viewers out there and one of them is
I scheduled a free the West Memphis three kickoff here in November fifth
Since we'll be in Chicago starting November fourth for ten days
As one of our 20 host cities
We're going to do a free the West Memphis three
Concert on November fifth as part of our kickoff. We're host of it. So you think they'll ever get free
Free free as in
podcasting is free to the people yeah
The West Memphis three free. Yeah. No probably not
But anyway Adam Chicago's where it's at pizza hot dogs
Good for right and we have this. Oh, did you hear about this press conference? We're doing November fourth
With Adam Curry. Yeah, he's gonna be in Chicago. We're hoping that we're gonna do this press conference
That's right there. It'll be exciting Adam Curry's gonna be there and it's the center of the country
That's right. All right. I'm convinced already. Oh wait. We're talking Adam. We didn't tell him he's gonna be in Chicago in November fourth
Yeah, I'm so there see in November fourth in Chicago. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm so there. You kids you wacky kids
yeah, so why don't I get
Doug
Doug and his son to drive Trinity from San Francisco to Chicago and then we'll kick it off
Just before we get and and I guess I'll ride maybe I'll ride with him. I don't know
I don't know we want them to have their father son thing. Okay. November fourth press conference in Chicago
We got to have a lot of people coming. It's gonna be fun. We'll throw a party somehow
I like it he kids. We're now working out budgets
It's gonna be uh it's still a big project even though it's it's not a big project it is a big project
Because I want to make it rock you know I want these guys to be comfortable on the road and I want them to be able to
You know get us as much material as possible and I really really like the idea of this changing year
People looking at alternatives not just for alternative energy, but just alternatives in general. It's an election year
I think it's a really good tie in and and let's talk to people
Let's find out what they're thinking on a day-to-day basis. It's gonna be pretty darn awesome
I got like five or six audio comments left. I'm gonna save those for tomorrow and
Play a song that I found on the podcast music network. This has been getting a lot of pod play
It's one of the most played songs at the month actually
It's from a suspended mind
different California
Track of this is years from now it starts off a little slow, but
I kind of grew on me and I dig it
Exclusively on your daily source code
You
Thank you so much for watching this video and I'll see you in the next video, thanks for watching and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see
you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video
and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I will see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next one and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you just in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and need!)
One, two, one, four, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
You
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, God, Yeah, God, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah take that, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
It's so lovely, I'm gonna let you know that you know
Don't know, don't know, don't know
Beatin' down the head, you don't know
I'll never tell you that I'm alive
Hip, hip, hip, hip, hip, hip
I'll try to make you do it as the first and foremost
It's falling at the above,
tears tears all
And I was supposed to
But I didn't yet understand
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ah oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh you know oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh no
oh no oh oh oh oh oh oh oh yeah no confronted
seven minutes worth no way I can just hear the program directing now I can fit two
songs in there and five commercials holding the summer of oh seven four
men ripped rock roof and see that an orch you between got speed like emperor
dream theater and Jason Rodd as they say they're sure there's some
Mormons put jizm stuck in there as well as they like you're right long and epic
song
taking it man
years from now winding up today's daily source code after one last
comment that just came in which is a promo for a channel hey guys welcome
out to take trying to sound hello how are you this is Derek
to bad it it's Friday night dance party we host Jeff Hines this is the
week and dance so podcast
the electronic a channel electronic a channel dot com and science to DJ dot
pod show dot com a collection of electronic music podcasts handpicked by science
to DJ and powered by pod show channels if you're into electronic music
it's the only video and a need electronic a channel dot com
dude what an awesome idea I just went to it cipsters electronic a
channel love electronic music this is the only feed you'll ever need brought
to you by Australia cipster DJ and pod show channels this is awesome man thank
you so much this is great so we this page I could just click on this in
it and it would let me just see what's in there hold on a second let's see
so he has a cipster DJ so I click on this and let's see what it
brings up check it out let's see what shows are in there okay we have
cipster space and then we have progressive house mix oh seven so lip
stick nation Friday night dance party dude this is awesome this is like a
complete collection of awesome shows the play electronic music which of
course I hate that's not true I'm just not completely into it Christina's new
boyfriend Jake he's into that stuff so I have to turn him onto it thanks dude I
love the fact that you're doing that promo and that you know that's what a
great combination you know go to go daddy of course to use check out code dsc1
to get a great discount and then just map that to your channel awesome to your
channel page or yeah in this case he put up his own little page there with
just the RSS link you know we could probably do some more links there and
really what you want is some kind of widget that's the next step we're gonna
work on all right tomorrow show will be in the afternoon I think because I've
got two meetings in in the city one with was it the daily star and one with
okay magazine okay magazine same in the states and you know they want to do
some content stuff with us I'm very excited about that and I'll fill you in
Wednesday full show Thursday taking the lady Patricia to to the Netherlands so
that'll be an afternoon show for sure because I won't be back until around
three or four in the afternoon and Friday that who knows maybe we'll get a
food bar out of it you never do know daily source code dot com for all the links
and stuff I talked about in today's show adamant pod show dot com if you want
me send me a message have you have a talk to tomorrow bye another pod show
podcast stick it in your ears the best in the brightest
sub dot daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering pod show and limelight