This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your fruit-whip log from GoDaddy.
I've got it.
DSC 604.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm testing DSC battery.
Hey!
I told you that it's for my body.
Yes!
It's my entire time.
Look at that porn on a dog.
She never was watching.
To see what you do.
Everything's looking like you.
Oh!
Everyone's wondering
We'll come out tonight.
Everyone's trying to get it right.
Get it right.
Everybody's working for the weekend.
Everybody's watching.
Everybody's grown with our plastic bags.
Everybody's needs a sack of chips.
Oh!
She want to be so mad.
She barely got who's known.
She want to be in the show.
Come on, baby.
No!
Everyone's looking.
To see what you do.
Everyone's watching.
Everybody's working for the weekend.
Everybody's watching.
Everybody is watching.
Everyone's watching.
Everybody's watching.
everybody's watching.
Wow, I got back from London because I was in relatively on time today to pitch some business.
Actually, it's for the Manchester International Festival, a Sony PlayStation is sponsoring that
and they had asked to come up with a proposal. So beautiful weather in town.
Ah, you know how much I love London when the weather is hot and the English women just
started throwing off their clothes and everywhere. There were two young women from the
advertising agency in this meeting and they were like, like, dress for the beach. It was fantastic.
Ah, yes.
New segment for the football Friday.
Hey, Adam, this is Chris over at PlainManus.com. The PlainManus podcast is my new show. It's all about
aviation. I'm also a pilot too and I hope you come over and check it out. I really like your show
and I know that you like to fly as well and being a flight instructor, I thought, well,
one of the things I'm going to start doing on my show every week. Since flight instruction is so
expensive nowadays, I'm going to go ahead and offer what I call my five second flight lesson of the
week. Okay, so here we go. This week's five second flight lesson. If you're flying along and you get a
bird strike in the tail, you need to add power.
All right, it's it. This week's flight lesson. Hope you like it.
And then I love that. It was awesome. Send me another one next week.
Good old artists back.
Let's see you people left. People put the power in the air.
Get down to the ship. I'm a people. I'm a new one. Yeah, this time it's all coming to you.
I want to get shot. I want to be shot. I want to get this piece to get shot. It's down to
big time. I lose the light on the red. Some morning talk to talk to rock that village.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah,
Once again, some of the very finest match available for mashuptown.com.
That's from Art.
It's even listening to the Charlie for a while, you know, that Art for mashuptown used
to send me the good stuff.
And he's back.
I got the inside track.
If you want, I got it right here.
DJ Moll, of course, links in the show notes to all about him and the track that he's
done.
I love it.
It just feels so good to do these mashups under the auspices of education, of course.
As we continue on our football Friday, I've been talking about this for about two
weeks.
Now, finally, it's, it is upon us.
The launch of the official podshow.com, suckless zone.
It's at suckless.podshow.com, so that's suckless with the hell I'll spell it for you.
Sierra Uniform, Charlie Kilo, Lima, Echo, Sierra, Sierra.podshow.com.
There's a little video there that part of this will be very familiar to listeners of
the Daily Source Code home.
It's not going to actually going to open this up directly from suckless.podshow.com.
Let's see if it'll play properly.
We're always trying to improve, and this time we need you to help us suck, what?
We're creating a special place called podshow suckless zone at suckless.podshow.com.
All right, well once you're there, you can join the super panel, give us your feedback.
Earn points and get valuable stuff.
It's fun.
It's easy and best of all.
You help us suck less.
Not to imply we suck to begin with.
Yeah, soccer girl is in this promo, forget it, don't even do anything at the suckless
zone.
Just look at soccer girl, and then you'll want to do anything we ask you to.
That's pretty cool.
Of course, I'll put the link in the show notes, but it's pretty easy to remember.
Help us suck less.podshow.
You're outer, I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out.
You're outer, please don't bang that gavel.
You can try this cowbell out, let's all give a nod.
To the hardest work in law here, it's just a tiny bag, yeah.
It's just a tiny bag, yeah.
You're outer, what do you say?
You might even get the veld one in this case.
It's very easy to suck, yeah, yeah.
It's very easy to suck.
Yeah, how's it going at him?
It's jersey time, the official music college is all of the chacha.
Dude, everyone's in the wild.
There's an album that comes up on the pot safe music network that I absolutely get addicted
to.
And that's happening again this week.
The singer is Emerson Hart.
Now, the name Emerson Hart should ring a belt to some people because, well, he is the former
lead singer of the band, Tonic.
In 2003, they had two Grammy nominations at a number one hit, they had a platinum album.
Yeah, they were a huge band, well Emerson Hart is now in the pot safe music network.
He's got a brand new album called Cigarettes and Gasoline, which is just absolutely fantastic.
The song that I'm going to play for you, if you're going to leave, it's just I love
the slow build to it.
It's just a fantastic, fantastic song.
And the best thing that I can say about Emerson Hart is, of course, he's a jersey guy.
Check this out.
It's Emerson Hart on the pot safe music network, on the Fubore Friday.
Maybe I'm the Joker, maybe I'm the fool in your eyes, maybe I'm the weak one, maybe
I'm a lion just cause, maybe I'm angry, cause I'm the one who's always wrong, and
maybe I'm not the one who's so strong, did you think about it, did you put it in the
wallet out, could you live without me, did you ever really have a doubt, but do you
want to stand it baby, when you say it's over and start, maybe I'm not the one who
says it's over and start, maybe I'm not the one who's so strong, I'm the one who's so strong,
I'm the one who's so strong, I'm the one who's so strong, I'm the one who's so strong,
we can fight about all the things, this isn't forever, this is small that I'm ready,
but do you want to stand it baby, when you say it's over and start, maybe I'm not the one who's
so strong, I'm the one who's so strong, I'm the one who's so strong, I'm the one who's so strong, I'm the one who's so strong,
yeah, you better start around, because I always do, no more time, oh, did happen,
the things that you wanted, we in the front, how did happen, yeah,
just look all right baby, someday you might need a friend, so if you're gonna leave,
yeah, you better get going, cause I ain't always in no more time, that we did, what we did is it would be calling,
yeah, you better start around, cause I ain't always in no more time,
it might ain't always in no more time, one might have been, all right according to Jersey Todd,
he is from the Garden State currently living in California, Emerson Hart on the daily source code,
the Fubar Friday edition, we invite you to kick back relax and enjoy the maximum music and call in once in a while,
I don't understand, I know you don't make an arrangement from the car, but it really is the only place that I can contact,
yeah, in my schedule at the moment, stop it small and absolutely fantastic, makes one really,
I'm a small guy, I was small and 40 days for about 15, 15 years, and my little boy came along and I decided to sing that I gave up,
what made you this heart, it was so awful.
Well, you know what, this is James is talking about, that I stopped smoking at what 48 hours ago,
and I gotta tell you, James, the physical addiction is really not a problem for me, it's the self-medicating factor,
but that I really, really miss, particularly when you have scheduled stuff you gotta do, like, you know,
doing the show, so you do the show, you want to be in a certain mood, and I kind of miss that, I don't drink,
so a lot of people do something like that with alcohol, but the only time that I've really missed smoking in the past two days is when I'm doing this show,
and otherwise, not at all, in fact, I'm enjoying kind of feeling awake, it's a boy, open still fun to listen to.
And for you know, it is, there will not be any gestures you know about it, but it's just trying to help people for this new smoking band coming in on the first July of 15 July, or it is.
Although it would be, you know, you know, you know, you're, you know, you're, you know, you're, you're, you know, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're,
you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you are, you're. You're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, and you're, you're,
And I watched that and she was a smoker, and you know, I'll tell you what the problem was of course
Yeah, I should have quit immediately and having seen my mom go through that horrible fucked-up process
Just inhumane
She had only quit smoking a year and a half or maybe yeah a little under two years before that
I think I was actually afraid to quit thinking that that's the moment I'd get lung cancer
I may have it. I don't know
But I if yeah, I told you I got I got the the warnings from the angels
So I guess I got to take that seriously. I really really will
I do not intend to go back to smoking tobacco and again
I can't smoke anything during the day if it's pure stuff because I just turn into a
Frick an idiot all right now Tommy open your last present
Oh, a puppy. I always wanted a puppy. I'll name him Mr. Snuggle face. We all looks forgot
We still have to sing happy birthday bring Mr. Snuggle face
Happy birthday to you happy birthday to you
Happy birthday
All right, hey everyone down on the fucking ground. What did we do?
Hit him with the taser
On the ground it's this the year twenty thirty one. Huh is the copyright expired is it?
No, no, it is it
You seem happy birthday public you pay royalty time war. I didn't think you think you can just rip off time
Warner and to a lesser extent the hill sisters who stole someone else's melody and then there's some more
Expect the RAA not to bring the hammer down huh take the balloons the banners the cake the presence
Grandpa's dialysis I need that you come this little concert and the dog
No room for the dog destroy is destroying the dog
The recording industry is association of America would like to remind you that we are
Fucking around anymore
You
I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend
I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I consider myself a friend of yours to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to send me my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be your friend, I want you to be your friend, I want you to be my friend, I want you to be my friend. I want me to be my friend,
understand the word they're saying and but it is just kicking my butt every
tasting single time I hear it. Mapa putsi is the name of the group or band or
dude whatever and mungamonga business is the title of it. It's a YouTube video so
of course I'll put a link in the show notes so you can check it out for yourself.
Didn't that just like drive man?
I'm out of it.
Friday morning, it's you from Ferris, you're kind of.
Thanks for the proud last week. That was fairly amazing. My colleagues are still
laughing. There was really amazing being on the show like that and well if the
part show thing doesn't work out there's always a job for you as a salesman
with that network map. Okay I'm 100% with you on this fitness thing. I went
to have a big checkup. Earlier in the week and they told me exactly the same
story so really.
We want to joking fucking around the out the field.
The very track it. That's pretty scary.
Be in crap whether this week so I know why you're staying at home, but catch up
you soon.
Yeah a few thanks man. Yeah it's like 42. I should have done this a couple of years ago.
Probably around the probably 30 I should have gotten serious about that but now I am and
yeah man I'll come jog with you because it's fun. We jog right across the apron right
of the runway. We'll be dodging a numerous vehicles as they are incoming. Hopefully
crap. I won't be flying for another week or so sure and as I look out the window no one
may be flying this country for another week or so.
Hey.
Do you smell that? Fucking smells like we didn't hear.
Straight from the streets and to the limousine started off with just his bullet holes
in a big dream hooked up with them and them and Dr. Dre. Now he's got his own fucking video game.
What you trying to say what you trying to say what you trying to say 50 cent is a pussy
50 cent is a pussy. Yeah bitch what I'm fucking calling you out. You're about as
gangster as the chick from no doubt. You try to step with your gee unicru, my true-to-life
woman's a kick this shit out of you. What you trying to say, what you trying to say 50 cent
is a pussy. I don't give a fuck about your gangster party. 50 cent is a pussy. You should
quit without a bappa party. You got shot nine times. You got shot nine times. You better
you're not a dumb bitch. You got shot nine times. Some dumb motherfucker can't shoot a properly.
50 cent is a pussy. 50 cent is a pussy. 50 cent is a pussy. 50 cent is a pussy.
50 cent is a pussy. And if you want to know who sang that. WWW.
That's nice. Peter. What day is it today? It's Friday.
It's Friday. It kind of came as a thought in the middle of the week as the messages came
to me that I'm basically been killing myself. So the final thought of the week is just
for my benefit so that I can listen to this show one day in the future thing. Oh yeah,
that was kind of a turning point. That was pretty good. Total be yeah. I'm not really
grouchy or I'm hungry all the time. I don't know. I guess I'm no one to preach. So there's
nothing we can say about it. But I'm not going to be for myself that I finally figured
out that I should at least stop the thing that's really going to kill me to quickest.
Oh no, no, not flying. And time to get a hyperbong or something. And really I figured
it all out. It's a whole oral fixation. That's really my problem. And I just don't think
it's acceptable if you have an oral fixation to walk around with a cock and a year
mouth. That's why I was smoking. I don't punch you. I got to get out of here. DailySourceco.com,
Adam at podshow.com. Have yourselves a great weekend. I think I'll be talking to you
from New York on Monday. But hey, experience the unexpected. Another podshow podcast. Stick it
in your ear.
The best and the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery,
podshow and lightweight.