This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
The show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
Welcome to DSC 6-7-8.
But it's not a food bar Friday, isn't it?
Not that we're better or angry?
Welcome to DSC 6-7-8.
We're happy it's here.
We just wish it was a food bar Friday, like you promised.
On 67, right Adam?
Welcome to DSC 6-7-8.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
A train on a hero's in the fire,
cos it will go super close.
There are always the ones that love you,
most love you most love you most.
Your love alone is not enough,
not enough, not enough.
It's what you've felt.
It's what you said, what you said, what you said.
You said the sky would fall on you,
on you, on you, on you.
Through all the pain all right, stay blue.
They say blue, baby blue.
But you love alone, say no more.
You look at the secret of the universe.
Despite all you made it worse.
It left you lonely.
And it has to come.
You stole the sun.
Sweet from my heart, from my heart, from my heart.
We've no excuses.
You fell apart, fell apart, fell apart.
Know you won't make a mess.
I've been messing me, messing me.
For your respite, messing me.
I can't be, I can't be.
I could just sing for miles and miles.
I couldn't make you feel alive.
I could have placed us in the sun.
I could have ridden all your life.
I could have shown you, I could have shown you.
I could have tried.
If you love alone, say no more.
I could have shown you.
Yeah, that's the soundtrack of your life.
Man, it's great creatures, they're from Wales.
How would be in the United Kingdom as well?
Your love alone is not enough.
If you live in the United Kingdom, you've probably heard that song before.
It is now officially on the Podsake Music Network.
It was, isn't that the girl from the Cardigans?
This has been a big hit over here in the UK.
Now officially available for your own independent productions to the Podsake Music Network.
It is daily source code, episode number 678 coming to you from partially overcast
Guilford, that is of course the affluent suburb of Surrey in the Curry Manor.
I hope you had a good weekend.
Yeah, I didn't get to the Friday food bar festivities.
There was really food bar.
It had to make a quick trip to the hospital, which delayed the whole day.
Luckily, it had already completed the first episode of No Agenda with John C. Dvorak,
which is at noagenda.podshow.com.
The show is exactly what it sounds like.
No Agenda.
But people are already tuning into it.
That's pretty cool.
And by the way, don't ask me to put it in my daily source code feed because I think that's
a mistake.
I've tried that over the past several years.
People don't like that.
It's got its own feed.
Or if you subscribe to Curry.com, you might have gotten the episode automatically.
So has this ever happened to you where you wake up on a Sunday morning?
It's a weekend.
And like, okay, what time is it here?
Oh, man, we slept until 10.
30.
This is pretty late for us.
Pick up the Nokia E61I.
Turn it on because, of course, I want to lay in bed there leisurely.
Listen to the Sunday morning love songs on BBC Radio 2.
This probably never happens to you, actually.
And John, the phone, I'm like, this is weird.
The phone is saying it's 9.30.
But it's 10.30.
And it took me about an hour to realize after resetting my clock,
then turning back on the network auto time update feature only to find the time was 9.30 again.
Or at that point 9.40.
What the hell is going on?
Well, of course.
We fell back into the daylight savings time.
So I said the Patricia said, hey, you know what?
We got a whole extra hour.
Why don't we go into London?
Let's go, let's go hang out.
Let's go to let's go shopping.
Ladies, don't you love it when your man says that?
And I actually said, let's go to herids.
This of course was all, but a sli-ploy to sneak by
235 region street to the Apple store, which is not far from herids on Brompton.
Is it Brompton?
It's Brompton.
To pick up, yes, I was going to make today the Big Mac is back attack.
To pick up a MacBook Pro.
And today I was actually planning on running a cast blaster on Windows on my MacBook.
Of course things never go.
Let's expect them to.
And I've been somewhat disappointed.
First of all, we had a great, it was kind of like rainy, not really rain rain,
but that little fine mist that just kind of drizzles down on top of you
that makes you just as freaking wet.
We had a really nice time in London, just the two of us.
Oh man, you know, at herids.
And if you've never been to herids, this is an amazing department store.
They have every massive major fashion brand known to man in this place.
And although, you know, I'm marginally into this.
Of course, it's the female version of my Mac porn.
And of course, we went to the Apple store first and you had to order it.
And man, are they just like handing this shit out there?
There must be a thousand people in the store.
As outrageous, they can't sell the shit fast enough.
Anyway, so if you want to hear a memory upgraded, then they have to do that in the basement.
So, oh, I said, I'll come back at the end of the day and get it.
And that was my version of porn.
Although I don't like having my porn with so many people in my proximity.
And that was off to herids.
Man, oh my goodness.
You know, I, uh, I'm forcing, I know how clothes are made and what it really takes to do it
and how fashion operates and, uh, what a rip off.
I couldn't believe it.
The shoes.
Now, I understand where you can get, you know, if you get a pair of Prada or Jimmy
Choose or, um, you know, Chanel or, uh, you name it.
You know, there's a, there's a brand there.
You're going to pay a premium.
And, uh, look, if you're going to, if you, uh, want to buy those types of shoes,
you got to expect to spend four to 500 pounds.
It's like a thousand dollars for shoes, which, by the way,
my, my wife rarely does.
She hates that she can't stand it.
Now, I can understand when you got a brand like that.
And, you know, this shoes, you know, I held in my hand at looking around.
It sniffed a little bit.
Uh, you know, you have the shoes with a red bottom, which is another thing
that everyone has to be wearing these days.
Uh, the sole is completely red.
You know, it's, um, I, I understand you pay the premium.
But even for brands that I, that I'd never heard of,
shoes, three, four, hundred pounds.
Sandals.
Just a slab of leather would like a toe strap on it.
There's 350 pounds, 700 bucks.
What the fuck is going on?
That's how, that's how outrageous.
And it's not just the, the, the brands that, you know,
that unsophisticated guys like, like myself know.
I mean, there's all kinds of new brands that I've never heard of.
Even the harrow's house brand shoes are 400 pounds.
What is going on?
Uh, maybe that's a topic for Noah Gendus,
something I can, uh, can run by, uh,
Dr. John C.
Anyway, um,
So, uh, came home and Patricia did buy a couple things.
She brought the new, uh, new trendy, uh, elbow high gloves.
That everyone's supposed to be wearing and some new pants.
And yeah, we had a, we had a good little shopping trip.
That was really nice.
And, uh, of course, you know, I unpacked my porn.
I'll unpack the, uh, the MacBook.
And it has, uh, 10 OS 10 dot four installed.
So then you have to do the upgrade.
Probably three hours really configuring this thing.
You know that, you know, you get your fresh Mac and first you got to upgrade to leopard
and you go through that process.
And then you got to install office, or at least I have to because we really,
you know, the power points really have to kind of be the same with the same font.
So we, we do a lot of, uh, power points stuff for presentation to presentation
to advertisers.
Uh, there's a burp coming, but it's a wet one.
So I'll hold it in.
Um, yeah.
I installed the, I work, um, you know, uh,
did a little search to figure out how to synchronize my Nokia, uh,
E61 eye with eye cal, and then there's an eye cal with G cal,
seeing.
So I'm doing all this stuff.
And then, of course, I plug in my time machine backup drive.
Everything's rolling right.
I'm like, okay.
This is great.
So everything's installed.
I've got everything set up the way I wanted to be.
Uh, okay.
It's a time.
Oh, and of course, some, some updates ran in the background.
You know, at least a 400 megs of updates, uh, to the OS,
which I'm thinking I'm probably should have installed those updates first
before going to leopard, at least that's what I'm about to attempt now
because you guessed it.
Uh, when I rebooted, um, even though, you know, everything
had been installed, it kept coming up with the setup assistant.
And I could not get out of it.
Even if I completed the setup assistant again,
it would start over with the setup assistant.
I was like, fuck, you can't put Cooper,
you know, you're disappointing me again.
What a lousy experience.
I don't know.
I'm sure I was just trying to do too much at the same time,
but, you know, there's not like there's any instructions
in which order you're supposed to do this stuff.
So this morning, I tried to recover.
I could actually, I know a little bit about max,
so I get into command line and see what was there.
And it seemed like I just couldn't figure out
how to get past the OSX assistant.
In fact, it was bringing up the 10.4 setup assistant.
So I did what any other brave man would do, fuck it.
Just erase the whole drive, start over from scratch.
So I've got like 20 minutes left on the leopard install.
Then I'm going to reboot and see if it actually
will go through that sequence before I start installing all my stuff again.
Ah, luckily though, I got the dot max synchronization setup.
So I think everything that I had already imported
because you know, you have to import your address.
Hello.
Can I help you, babe?
What, hold on a second.
What?
Yeah.
When I'm done with the show, I hope.
Bye.
No one cares about the show.
You don't care about the show.
Okay, about the show.
Okay.
I'll help you later, babe.
She needs to send off documentation for a passport.
And I have in the first passport for a driver's license.
Oh, whoa, is me.
My kid's going to be driving an automobile.
And it's time to change in my friends.
You know they are.
Forget around the world.
Well, the winds have changed to blow in my friend.
It's time to elect a president again.
I'd love a spirit of debates.
So I'd be ready for a wait.
Let's get at them to get the candidate online.
Come on, Adam.
Get the message on the line.
I really want to know what this stand for.
I really want to know what the mean.
Don't you crack the internet and rip it wide open.
Know it's your vote and it's mine.
It'll all be okay.
If I had my say, I'd love Adam to get the candidate online.
Come on, Adam.
Get the message on the line.
Yo.
So the winds have changed our blowing through this show.
Even I'm getting a little tired of the political talk.
I do want to say a couple things.
I got a whole bunch of responses to the Ron Paul interview from
Daily Source code 677.
If you haven't heard it, you might want to go check it out.
Here's just one I want to play for.
This is Kevin and go from Florida.
I just heard your interview with Ron Paul outstanding.
Listen, here's the problem.
I'm going to have red pill you my friend.
Okay.
The problem with Ron Paul, which isn't a problem, is that we're used to being sold to.
We're used to being manipulated.
We're used to being promoted, pushed.
And Ron Paul's not about that.
He's just laying it out there for you.
He's, I guess you call it a data dump.
He's not pushing.
He's not selling it.
He's not promoting it.
He just is.
It exists.
And it is.
And it always was.
And he's just putting it out there.
And that's why people are having a hard time accepting his message.
But man, I'm right on.
Because I hate being sold or promoted to.
I mean, that's the deal.
It is what it is.
So hey, take care.
Good interview.
And have sex with you now.
I'm not going to do that.
But.
Yeah, I will.
And November 5th, of course, I'll be donating my funds to the campaign.
Interesting.
While I was installing all this shit, I was actually watching the GOP debates.
I think it was someone posted on YouTube.
And there was also a kind of like a compilation, which I don't like.
I hate it when people do compilations about one candidate because it's pretty skewed.
But anyway, there was a compilation of Ron Paul on Fox News after the debate where they had the results of their poll numbers.
And Ron Paul, like stood above all candidates.
Something like 35% approval in this poll.
And it was so funny to watch the Fox News guys.
It's like, well, the poll is obviously fucked.
You know, the poll isn't right.
Or, you know, the deck is stacked because Ron Paul supporters are calling in more often than others or whatever it is.
And I was like, well, because clearly they don't manipulate these polls.
Otherwise, this couldn't have happened.
But it was funny.
And they were really doing everything to marginalize it saying the results were off.
It was no good.
And then Ron Paul got on.
He's like, I love your Fox News audience.
They're clearly very intelligent people.
I was quite funny.
I did learn something though that, you know, when they say,
Well, how come you don't show up in the national polls?
And apparently he's at least in most of them.
He hasn't been listed as a candidate.
But as a candidate that people can respond to.
So I don't know, man.
I think he, again, I think he had a really clear message.
And I think that the Republican Party outside of, you know,
what was in the audience in Florida, which apparently included,
it was like 3,000 people.
Giuliani got 1,000 free tickets.
So a lot of Giuliani supporters.
This thing is all, what this whole system is messed up, man.
It's really messed up.
But you will be advertised to about Ron Paul,
because that's what it's going to start doing with this 5 million
box.
It's going to start advertising.
So hopefully he'll do it with the message.
And for you, my friend, just called in,
maybe the radio isn't for you.
Maybe radio advertising isn't for you.
Maybe you should just be sticking to independent media.
Hey Adam, Rob Cohn from Western Canada.
Just commenting on your view, the world rugby championships there
as my old rugby coach.
Yeah, you know, this is, this is my amazement that England versus South Africa
in the world championships for rugby.
England lost even though there was a try,
which is the equivalent of a touchdown or a goal.
That did not count after a video review because the player was out of bounds.
But everyone kind of, you know, it's like orderly.
All right, shit, we lost.
That really sucks.
We're devastated.
We're guided.
But no fighting in the stands.
You know, no one's beating each other up.
So what did your coach use to say?
rugby is a barbarian sport played by gentlemen and soccer,
aka football is a talent sport played by barbarians.
I just thought you might enjoy that.
And of course, fuck you Adam Kurt.
God, thank you.
Yo, you know what I got to say that I think probably a lot
of the England football supporters are also England rugby supporters.
So what is it about the game?
What is it about the situation that changes that?
Very interesting to me.
I even though I want to stay away from a lot of the political talk today.
When this guy calls in, you just can't ignore him.
Let's have a word with the nylon.
Spreading the news with the smile on where the roll is right.
So you'd think, of course, that the nylon would call in be completely
contrary and say all kinds of shit about the Ron Paul interview about me about
the show about how much I suck and you know what?
You're right.
Hey Adam, it's the nylon backed by unparalleled demand.
Let's go to the chasing here with Dr. No.
There used to be a day when, you know, you'd walk into a bowling
close to curtain, pull the lever and walk out and no one asks you what happened
back there.
Let's go back to those days.
I don't really care who you're interested in.
You're mind that your opinions aren't relevant to me.
Maybe just some of the listeners and they're probably relevant to your new
so-called listeners from the Ron Paul campaign.
You know, that is a good point that nylon makes there.
I recall back in the day when I was just a young girl.
Come on, sit on Grand Paul Adams knee here. I'll tell you a story.
When I was, I don't know, 5, 6, 7 years old living in the States.
I recall very vividly that people would not talk about whether who they were going to vote
for or what party affiliation they have.
That definitely changed over the years.
I don't know if that's a good thing or a bad thing.
I think debate and talking about stuff is always good.
And, you know, if you have a viewpoint, I guess it's going to match up with a candidate
or you'll bring in a candidate.
I don't know. I understand where you're coming from on that nylon.
But I think it's kind of good that we're all talking about our choices and our ideas and our thoughts.
And it's, you know, we're from the outside.
It may look like, oh, there's a red state blue state and sometimes inside the United States
as a red state blue state vibe.
But in general, no one gives a shit.
Who are all just Americans?
Who are found a willing sucker in you for their version of one rest of the charts?
I guarantee you, if you stop supporting Ron Paul, stop supporting Steve Kobair,
which I'm sure that'll be the next thing.
You'll lose those listeners there.
Look, first of all, I don't, you know, I don't make this to gain or lose listeners.
I presume people listen or they don't listen.
And you, let me tell you, I'm a big fan of lots of shows, lots of radio programs.
You just can't listen to everything.
But this, you know, I'll never listen again.
Fine, man.
I don't buy any of that.
And this is not about winning or losing listeners.
It's about doing my show.
And by the way, Steve Kobair is actually more internet savvy than Ron Paul.
So let's move to that one and bore me.
Now, don't worry.
No danger of that.
So, by the way, this whole thing about bummer is to chill it.
Let's get over this.
First of all, bummer is the chart.
What are you talking about?
If you're talking about November 5th, that, you know, Ron Paul supporters are all going to start donating money on November 5th to move the needle.
Which I do believe works.
I said bummer, I said charts.
It's, I don't, I don't, I hope they're not calling it that.
Boy, as you know, Joseph Jaffey invented that.
Didn't move.
You're still counting the payments to get WPP or Coke or Johnson Johnson with your time and all as your sponsor.
And you know, I find the army is that before bummer's to chill it, you have sponsors for your show.
Since the needle moves, you have no sponsors.
I think you might want to reevaluate that nylon.
I got plenty of sponsors.
Both in D-gap and fun of the show and inside this program.
However, I will say that I have turned down quite a few because, or we've not come to terms because of the,
fuck use at the end of each comment.
Interesting how that needle moves.
By the way, the needle doesn't need to move from me.
Okay.
It's not about me.
Please understand nylon.
Back to Ron Paul.
You two need each other.
He calls about 1% of the vote.
And I gather this about 100 million iPods out there and you get about 1% of those downloads.
So you two, to me, are the new 1%ers who need each other to try to get to 2%.
And Adam, you're really starting to sound like a cheap, drive, time, talk, radio host.
I like people better when you're signed sell to the podcast about nothing.
To me, you're losing relatives.
Fits your brain.
Anyway, good luck.
And I'm hoping you and Dr. Ron have a good time.
Bye.
Oh, man.
That would be quite a step back to go to 1%.
But I understand where you're coming from with your sorted lack of knowledge nylon.
Fantastic.
With Adam Curry.
Hey, Adam.
For you ready to be stumps.
And I'm going to use the hypnotastic test with young problem.
Hey, Adam.
This is hit test number 93.
And this is intro number one.
Are you kidding me?
I'm going to come run to you.
Let's try an Adams.
The Cougar from Vancouver.
And number two.
Oh, wow.
It's...
Could that be my wife?
Who's that lady with my man?
Either that or it's...
And this week's final one is number three.
That's tough.
Didn't anyone want to go want an in my handman?
Algebraus.
Uh...
Moose garden?
Moose garden.
Yeah, moose garden.
I think I've got at least two out of three, huh?
And times up and these are the answers for you.
Yes.
Number one from 1985.
Brian Adams.
You and Dad.
Dad.
I don't want to see you.
Yeah, I don't want to see you.
Cause when they're feeling proud, I'm going away.
I don't want to run to you.
Run to you, Brian Adams is answer number one.
Got that one.
And this is answer number two from 1987.
Oh, man, I'm lucky I got this one right.
Yeah.
And Adam, don't tell me you've fucked this up again.
I don't know.
This was your wife from 1977.
Patricia, bye.
With a great song.
Thanks, dude.
Who is the lady with my man?
But final one.
Oh, my god.
Number three.
Algebraus.
Is it?
That's it.
From 1982.
This is Roof Garden.
Oh, I'm gonna go on a walk.
Same in the night band.
Does anyone wanna go back?
Something I'm not a bro.
It's a loop.
Yeah.
You're a stepway fast.
You took a step.
Same on one.
One walk.
Same in the dark.
What happened to Algebraus?
I'm saying.
One walking dance.
On one.
And some number three.
Algebraus.
And Roof Garden.
That's from here.
Number nine.
B3.
Yeah.
All right.
The Adam.
How did you do?
Three.
You had them all.
Yeah.
Leave in the second one.
The one by your wife.
Yeah.
I got it.
All right.
The answer to this hit test.
And also the links to iTunes.
So you can buy these tricks.
Can be found at hittest.potshow.com.
Next week.
I'll be back for hit test.
Number 94.
So until then, take care.
And just one final thing.
If it's still done.
Adam.
Fuck you.
Bye.
Respect test.
The old pa ll
Where?
Teac expansion.
I don't have sponsors.
Adam Hey,
Stage checks for musicians because in
I'm listening to dsu
671.
You just said.
Yeah.
And I thought, are you ever going to like, when you're 60, are you going to like sit back
and write like the Adam Curry autobiography?
Because you got so many freaking stories that you just breeze over and I'm glad as you gave
the whole, you know, blow on a knife part of that, which was kind of cold, but I'm just
sure there's more to it.
I just ever wondered, have you ever thought about writing a book?
Just curious, a fit from your favorite scruncher, and of course, fuck you.
Yeah, you know how many times have been asked about that or to do that, I can't count
them on two hands anymore.
And of course, I'd love to write a book, but I think I need to wait another 20 years
at least, because when I go, I'm going to really go all out.
I'm going to tell everything, because I need to cleanse myself before I die.
So I'll have a couple more, you know, well, hopefully more than a couple of years and 20 years
from now.
By the way, Jack Sauer sent me an email, Adam was listening to DSC60, 675 on the
bus today.
That was two Fridays to go.
Hit test came on.
Every little thing she says is magic started playing when you said, you know the word
sing along.
I completely forgot I was on the bus and started singing out loud.
After about 30 seconds of singing, I realized everyone on the bus was staring at me.
Only you at him could make someone start singing out loud in public, keep up the
great work.
I would have to give some props to young pull-out there, because he does know how to
pick him, how but pick in my wife's song, trying to trick me up again, you bastard,
you bastard.
Adam is Jason Jarrett, call it this and this November the fifth thing you're talking
about wrong calls, can't say, you might not be aware, but remember remember the fifth
of November.
I'm going to had a treason and plot.
And, lady, the terrorist link is to do with die force and why he didn't name them
on November the fifth.
Who knows, take care, Beth, he'll find out.
Yeah, I got a lot of feedback about that people saying, you know, that was probably what
the controversy was about donating money to the Ron Paul campaign on November 5th.
I think it's pretty genius actually, so they need to do some jingles for November, remember
remember the fifth of November gunpowder treason and plot, they'd need to come up with
a new rhyme or something like that.
Hey, Adam, this is Sean J, just have a weird thing happen, sitting at a stoplight, I had
both windows open and a butterfly flew through my car in one window and out the other, and
maybe think of your mom.
So, uh, just send out some love to you, um, keep up the great work, Dr. later.
Oh, man, that's a, that's a beautiful, thank you.
It happened to me the other day when Patricia and I were walking, uh, where were we?
We're on the island of White, and all of a sudden, and it's pretty late in the year
in a butterfly flew past.
Uh, yeah, you know how I believe in that kind of shipment.
I really appreciate you sending that in, makes me feel good.
So, Adam trees from San Diego, uh, been listening to you for quite some time, and now
I'm listening to you trying to open up my mind, make to make a left, and when I shouldn't
make a right, well, I took your advice, I made three less, and I was late, so you know
what that means?
Fuck you.
That's a, how do you fuck me?
Yeah.
No longer fuck you out of, fuck me.
Hey.
I'm telling you, it does work, it's really good for your brain to do something out of the
routine.
Particularly those things you do with incredible routine, like picking up your tea cup,
pick up with a left hand instead of the right hand or right if you're left handed.
Uh, I'm sorry, I didn't make it, didn't want to make it late, did it work though, did
you feel that better?
Did you do it?
It's a lie.
You must have felt someone better.
First cause roll, now Gina Villalobos, somebody saved me.
Is next door, I think I'm gonna move on, I've been done with you, but I'm the CEO, you can't
move on.
I'm telling you, it does work, it's really good for your brain to do something out of the
routine.
I'm telling you, it's really good for your brain to do something out of the routine.
I'm telling you, it does work, it's really good for your brain to do something out of the routine.
It's really good for your brain to do something out of the routine.
I'm telling you, it's really good for your brain to do something out of the routine.
I'm telling you, it does work, it's really good for your brain to do something out of the routine.
It's really good for your brain to do something out of the routine.
I'm telling you, it's really good for your brain to do something out of the routine.
I'm telling you, it does work, it's really good for your brain to do something out of the routine.