I'm gonna have to change this, it's gonna let's stop for a second.
Okay, let's do it.
Two, two, one, bye.
I'm gonna have to change this, it's gonna let's do it.
Two, two, two, one, two, check one, two, two.
Okay, two, two, one, two, aw, what do you say?
1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2
2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2
1, 2, 2, 1, 2, 1, 3, 2, 1, 2, 2, 3, 1, 4, 1, 2, 1, 1, pushing,
I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the
ways I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way that I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the ways I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I'm going to change the way I want to change the way I'm going to change the way
So I'm in my beauty
So I'm in the beauty
Check 2, check 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1
2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1
2, 2, 1, 2, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, well like that!
Hello!
You
I really don't know what's going on.
I think my right ear got blocked up, busted, two, two, two.
Two, two, two, two, two, one, two.
Okay.
Well, we'll just have to use this one for a little while, see if that does the trick or not.
By cranking up the sound from the underground, everybody, everybody.
Daily source code, six, two, zero, daily source code, six, two, zero.
Oh, yeah, one, two.
Hey, everybody, this is not by your favorite alien, and you're listening to the daily source code.
Oh, yeah, well, Monday, enjoy the shower and carry.
Daily source code, six, two, zero.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Okay, let's do it.
Let's see if you've played a little bit.
Let's do it, let's see if you've played a little bit.