Another pod show pod guest.
Stink!
We interrupt the show for a special announcement from Pod Show HQ.
Attention podcasters, viewers and listeners, Pod Show needs you to help us suck the lads.
Help us suck the lads, help us suck the lads, Pod Show needs you to help us suck the lads.
Hi, it's Jade, I like Matt Pod.
Pod Show needs your help, so we are creating a special place.
The pod show suck less zone at suckless.potshow.com.
The best pod show dive call!
That's right, and once you are there, you can join our super panel.
Give us your feedback, earn points, and get valuable stuff.
It's fun, it's easy, and most of all, you can help us suck less.
Now, back to the show!
Hey, I've been even, I've been just hold on a minute, just hold on a minute, I got another call, hold on.
Yeah, yeah, Danny. What do you mean you're lost of?
What? What?
He's seven feet tall, he's got blonde bushy hair, it's like tracking big bird down man hat,
and how could you lose him?
Would you understand that we're not going to be able to listen to the DSC on this Thursday?
That's missing a show, that's not going to work, Johnny.
He got to find Adam. We need the DSC 615. Before you know, it's going to be football Friday.
Just do it, Johnny.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Head in back to London, get my life all track again.
Though my stop off is made.
Then you see, and I would date, I'd work in your bar.
In the States, in the student's area,
finally went to far.
When I left, I'd keep your car.
Goodbye, New York.
I'm going to walk you made it.
So be easy to decide.
When I turn a bit to summer, I'll just 25.
Now I barely feel alive.
Goodbye, New York.
As you die, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
I mean, perfect, it's not a pot-safe music network.
One search term from New York and you come up with the shakes, you would find New York,
we are leaving by the time you get this letter on this podcast, I'll be back in London
town.
Okay, it's almost perfect, but I won't be in London.
I'll be in San Francisco.
I'll bar Friday everybody, episode number 615 of the Daily Source Code.
It's a maximum music for bar Friday with lots of stuff to wrap up for the week.
A new music, Andreas Wiser, like I should do.
Yeah, but I won't, then I won't be there.
Wanna stay and maybe I won't go home.
But I won't, then I won't be there.
Stick around because I don't know.
If I love you, like I should do, and if I'm gonna treat you right, if I love you, like I should,
do, and if I ever go to make you mine.
You said come on now, oh, because I don't know I, this is taking too long.
And if there's a problem now, then we can work it out.
Tell me it's something wrong, and I won't, and I won't, and I won't, and I won't,
and I won't, and I won't, and I won't, and I won't, and I won't, and I won't, and I won't.
And I won't, and I won't, and I won't, and I won't, and I won't, and I won't, and I won't, and I won't.
If I love you, like I should, and if I'm gonna treat you right, if I love you, like I should do,
If I ever go on, make you mine
It's hard, baby, I know it's hard
There's if I'm gonna ride you
I'm gonna love you forever
If I ever go on, make you mine
It's hard, baby, I know it's hard
Tell me where this guy is from
The name kind of gives it away
Doesn't it there?
Like I should do, the guy's got three songs in the podcast
Music Network. It was really hard to sign
Which one to play? He's from Sweden 21 years old
Awesome, brand new to the podcast
Music Network, I think he is
Let me just check you, let me see, yeah
Uploaded in May and in June
Hey everybody, wrap it up a week in the big apple
Another beautiful day, I just got down from the rooftop
The Grammarcy Park Hotel
Of course, I didn't tell you what hotel I was in
Because while we were able to do that a year or two years ago
I can't do it anymore
Because I could cause in the middle of the night
So I'll be leaving today
Hold on a second, let me just
The mobile setup is exactly what it should be today
And it's warm, it's already past the 80 degree mark
It's still relatively early in the morning
I gotta tell you, the Grammarcy Park Hotel
There's something I really, really like about this hotel
And there's something I really, really hate about this hotel
The rooftop terrace, I think, is a stroke of genius
I'll see if I can find a picture of this thing
To put it up online so you can take a look at it
But they have this wraparound terrace
Roof top
And they have retractable roof
And just tons of plants all over the place
Isn't he in Shreger Hotel
So it's one of those like
You know, kind of way too hip for itself
Bullshit hotels, but that thing
That rooftop is just spectacular
Really, it's too bad I don't smoke anymore
Because you can sit up there and drink and smoke
And you know, just lounge around
It's awesome, totally awesome
Now, the hotel rooms itself
You know, as I said, it's one of these
In Shreger Hotel, so you know, they got like all kinds of weird furniture, weird dimensions
Interesting colors
Totally a designer's wet dream, I presume
But in the bathroom
They had to go all like
You know, funky cool on the lighting
And it's so incredibly stupid
They have a string of lights hanging down the left hand side of the mirror
Okay
And you know, it's like, you know, naked light bulbs, intertwined wires
You know, it's supposed to be cool looking
And it looks cool
And it gives off a great light
The problem is it's only on one side of the mirror
So you don't, you can't even when you're shaving
You can't, I can't even see my side burns on that on that side
So you like try to turn into the light
And it's stupid
Stop it
The internet's okay, though, which makes up for a lot
Because these days
I definitely make my decisions on
Where I'm going to stay based upon
Internet access
And ability to shave
Help us
To suck less
Suck less touch
Oh, Angie
Angie, Angie
I played that
You're going to start hearing that
As one of our D-gaps pre-rolls
Nice and short and sweet into the point
But Angie, be hearing you sing that
I'm like, maybe, you know, I love what you do with love spirals
But you may want to consider
Trying out an evergreen classic
Because I think you've got the perfect voice ward, baby
Hello D-S-C, this is Charles
Your drunk Londoner, long time no show me
I have no idea what's going on
Still on the D-S-C
I have absolutely no idea
In the last month I've had so much happened to me
Part of movie flat and having no broadband
Or phone line or anything like that
Can't get online
So I'm not allowed to download the B-S-C
However, one fabulous thing that happened to me was that
Our illustrator, leader
Big brother, podge, pod for the himself
Adam, Terry
Sent me a beautiful raid
I pod nano
He was given
By Virgin Atlantic
And this is a phone call to say
All hail
Sir Adam of Curry
Thank you so much
Really
I'm really touched by the fact that you've sent it to me
And as I said before
I'm planning on
Saving up some money and getting myself an iPod
And so I can maybe auction this one off
At a later date
A genuine Adam Curry artifact
So as and when I do that
I will let you all know
And you can all do it on it
Or you can do a composition of something
Who knows?
Anyway, that was it really
Rambling on
There was another thing
But I can't remember what it is
Of course I can
Well, thanks for listening
I will be downloading the GSD
When I can and I will be chewed in
And you guys can all
Feel me in what's going on
Alrighty
Thank you
Charles
The Drunken Londoner
A little bit sauce today
Clearly and he's obviously received
The Red Virgin Atlantic iPod Nano
That I sent to him because you know
This is a guy who contributes to the show
On a weekly basis
Often several times a week
He got completely jacked
His computer is iPod
His cell phone
His entire life was basically stolen from him
And I felt really shitty about it
So at least now he can somehow
Listen to the Charlie and continue to
You can find a phone somewhere in the UK
I'm sure Charles
So apologies of course for the
For the low output of episodes this week
It's been just absolutely nuts
You have to understand that
When we go on these quarterly
John's to New York
We're going to Madison Avenue
We do it basically three things
We go to
We go to Madison Avenue
We follow up on campaigns that have worked
And as an example
Universal McCann is an agency
We've done a lot of work with a lot of the Johnson
Johnson products
The Splenda campaign
The KY campaign
The
I'm still pissed that I didn't get to
Participate in the KY campaign
My show was rejected
I don't know why
Yeah
Then of course there's
New business that we're following through
And then there's a lot of education
We're still educating and learn something really really interesting
Because a lot of
A lot of podcasting these days
Is video and people
I think advertising in general
It's like the easiest path to
Understanding oh I can see this video
I understand it's not
It's also very difficult to present audio
In a meeting
Because you're all kind of like
Steering at your navel while you're listening to something
So it's not the easiest thing in the world to sell
However, we know to something very interesting
With a number of buyers
And I'd love some feedback from
From the audience and in this case
Definitely from some podcasters as well
It turns out
So the way it goes is an advertiser
And actually advertisers are so incredibly smart
They know exactly who they want to target
They know like between 50
And 53 years old
And I want them to be making
More than $60,000 a year
And it's very very targeted
And of course with podcasting
When it comes to interests
Particularly interest in niche groups
We can help advertisers
Talk directly to the audience
They're interested in and the relevance
Should be there because it's
Yeah, it's like games
For games show some real simple stuff
Health and food and sports
But when they hear the word podcasting
They're like, hey, what I'm not sure what that is
But when they hear internet radio
They say, yeah, go, I'll buy some of that
How interesting is that
So is the definition of internet radio
Does that have to do with the delivery mechanism
Because traditionally we talk about internet radio
A streaming radio streaming audio
But is there any difference with a podcast?
You can basically stream it
You click on a play button somewhere
And it starts streaming in
The only difference is you're hearing it from beginning to end
And you have some control over it
Versus a stream where you fall in the middle
And you don't have control over
Forwards and backwards
Is there a difference when it comes to just the enjoyment of audio
And calling it internet radio versus podcasting
To the advertiser
When they hear a podcast and you tell them it's internet radio
They dig it
So something very, very interesting we learned
And of course I'll follow up on it
And let you know what happens with that
So but it literally is like
Get up at 7 o'clock
8 o'clock it's the first breakfast meeting
And it just continues on until
At least 8 or 8 30 in the evening
But of course it's New York
This is where shit happens
The pace and everyone's just moving
And we have goals we know what we want to do
And it's the whole city is just vibrant
I've seen every single time I come here
I say the same thing
And I really love being here
And of course I also like Lee
Hey Adam this is Lisa from I love the company
And the awesome podcast
Hey rumor has that you're going to be in New York City
This is coming weekend
So just wondering if you're going to make it out to central park
To see David and Bluto play on the hill
Listen man, we'd love to see you out there
I'm going to send you a track from
For my soon to be released CD
Everybody else just check out
I feel like shit now
I should have been able to stay
For some day when David and Bluto's playing
Is a park
Fortunately, I'm going to miss it
Yeah, again
Next time round buddy, I promise
On my screen
It is eyes that I've seen in a smile
So invite him
Got five damn fantasy fighting
Now so hot
That she's steaming
I know I must be demon
So I run home in a evening
I'm checking in and seeing she's real
I've got a flying
She's got me out of my mind
I don't even know her
But I can't stop thinking about her now
I got a flying
She's got me out of my mind
I'm always getting a little bit crazy
But now I'm chasing a dinner that can't you baby
Sweet pain every time I
Realize she's not online
I realize
That therapy
Is a definite possibility
I walk through this city
I see faces just as pretty
But I run home in a evening
Still checking in and seeing she's real
I've got a flying
She's got me out of my mind
I don't even know her
But I can't stop thinking about her now
I got a flying
She's got me out of my mind
I'm always getting a little bit crazy
But now I'm chasing a dinner that can't you baby
Could be that has happened
And I finally off that deep end
Could be the way things are
I've left reality far behind
This obsession
I'm left with the same damn question
So I run home in a evening
Just checking in and seeing she's real
I've got a flying
She's got me out of my mind
I don't even know her
But I can't stop thinking about her now
I got a flying
She's got me out of my mind
I'm always getting a little bit crazy
But now I'm chasing a dinner that can't you baby
I got a flying
She's got me out of my mind
I don't even know her
But I can't stop thinking about her now
I got a flying
She's got me out of my mind
I'm always getting a little bit crazy
But now I'm chasing a dinner that can't you baby
Now I'm chasing a dinner that can't you baby
So if you're lucky someday in Central Park you'll see
Check it to our guy
From Central Park
And also check out his podcast
I love to come back
I love the company
I was at iLTC dot pot show dot com
Oh
I'm pissed about that
Hey, you know one other
Plus of the Grammcy Park Hotel
They have
Big finished David
They've got to HD television
And you know on home I've got the HD skybox
I've got the HD DVD player
I've just been too lazy and been doing too many things
To pick up the HD TV that I want to get
It is on the list too
So I've actually enjoyed watching HD TV for the past week
And you know what it's it is so sharp
When you when you watch like a like the morning program
So I was watching the like the today show
And good morning America
And you can see everything
I mean you see the studio floor
Which looks like shit
You see every single bump
And in
In in perfection
If you will
Of the of the people on television
I think
That once HD really is is
You know completely rolled out
And I'll take years
I'm sure before all the sets are converted to HD
I think it's really going to affect the way people perceive their their television heroes
And it's it's it's I think it's
I think the quality is just too good
I don't want to be on TV anymore
Although I will be on Bloomberg television
I think it's this coming Monday
I did the interview yesterday
With Mike Schneider
Who used to do the news on good morning America
I know Mike I met him several years ago
She's almost like a decade ago in the in the mid 90s
Nice guy and we talk for half an hour
This is a show called
Believe it's night talk
It airs in the evening on Bloomberg television
There's a couple times thing at 8 o'clock
9 o'clock in 10 o'clock
So you're bound to bump into it
But he's had some great guests on it
Russell Simmons on the other night
And so it was cool just to sit down
And and channel a little bit about
About podcasting about pod show
And it was also really nice to
I have to admit as much as I like sitting here at the table
In the hotel room with all my wires
My spaghetti factory of mixers and boxes and stuff
It was also really nice to sit in a completely
Climate-controlled air-conditioned soundproof studio
We're just like the sound is so dead
And the breeze of the air conditioning is just kind of
Wafting through the air
And you can have a really nice non-distracted chat
I do have to say if you got the money to build the studio like that
It can be very, very nice
Games, please
With that come
Hi Adam, just like you know on Gamesweasel
This week we're looking at virtual tennis
3 we're also reviewing the last
Medal of on a game for the PlayStation 2
And we've got copies of World of Warcraft Expansion
Pack the burning crusade together way
If you need more info on that head over to
Gamesweasel.btpodshow.com
Yeah, what's up Adam, it's jersey time
The official musicologist of The Cha Cha
So what I've got for you this week I'm really excited about
Because it really shows the synergy going on between podcasters and musicians
The artist's name is Jim Armstrong
Yeah, yeah, he just did the jersey time theme song just there
But he's so much bigger than that because he's got a great new album
Finally up on the podcast of music that we're called Mudtown
It just got released on Sonic Deli Records
And Jim Armstrong really really understands the power of podcasting
His last album just did great brown bag lunch
And I've been a fan of his ever since
I thoroughly addicted to his new album Mudtown
And I think that you're going to be too
The song I'm going to play for you is called She Spins Around
It is absolutely perfect for a food bar Friday
Turn this up loud and enjoy man
This is some great stuff from Jim Armstrong
Rocky roll bangin
She came with a couple friends
That's how the host of the games
I look away when I come
Lookin at me
She spins around
Just like a hurricane
Nothing can ever
She's running around away
And I'm okay with how the cram
Just counting the freckles on the skin
She was breathing out
I was breathing out, I was breathing
We're gettin' really raced, get on
The hot summer breeze
She turned this ball into a man
I've been on it in the cloud
And my face
And my wrong way
My scratch
My shabby me
She spins around
Just like a hurricane
Nothing can ever
She's running around away
She spins around
Just like a hurricane
Nothing can ever
She's running around away
And I'm okay with how the cram
She spins around
Just like a hurricane
Nothing can ever
Bring the damn she's right there on the way
I'm okay with how the crowd
Once again right on the money jersey time official music college is done
The shots chance to rail
For a maximum is a full bar Friday
Jim Armstrong she spins around from the positive music networks
You can find links to everyone play today on the show
At dailysourcecode.com
You know something really spectacular happened while I was away
I have back home in Jolly Oden, England
Oh yeah Richard Branson added again
Yeah then this is Richard and playgate
Just come across a little story that might be up your street for a biodiesel movement
Which is virgin your favorite travel company
Virgin trains infecting the UK
Lortzness first
Train powered by a biodiesel tomorrow
They're launching in London
It's going to be a used in station at 11h4 on Thursday 7 to 2
In the morning and
I'll search and stay in the head of a biodiesel train before
So just like I might not typically fancy
Bye for now
Darren, thank you very much
Thanks for the info
Sorry I missed that one
That's pretty cool
I of course I'd like to know what kind of biodiesel is it
I don't think that there's enough
Processing plants of the of the vegetable
I put into Trinity to actually make the trains run
But fantastic nonetheless
And once again showing that there are alternatives
To our independence upon foreign oil
As the president now himself is saying isn't that amazing
Brand new sponsor on the show
Sponsoring the hit test for today
Of course it's the football Friday
So that means young poletta standing by
He of course is along with myself
One of the charter members of the
Organization for preservation to the soundtrack of our lives
Better known as upsole
And of course upsole.org will soon be live
Young and I have it a good time with this
Today's sponsor the hit test is Lexus
And as I was thinking about the company and the car Lexus
I realized the last time I actually drove an Alexis
And I didn't even drive I sat in Alexis
Was during the MTV Beach House series
Bill Bellamy member good old Bill
And by the way I kind of lost track of Bill Bellamy
Because we used to hang out a little bit
And we'd play ex box and place
And we did a lot of that at the MTV Beach House
And so I've been looking into some of the materials
You know me I'm always interested in gadgetry
These Lexus is it Lexus is or Lexi
I wonder the Lexus is like
Well these automobiles
They got a lot of technology in it
And so of course going through their site
And looking in some of their cars
I saw that they
You know I actually remembered
They have that auto park system
So as they're trying out podcasting
Which of course I really appreciate
And they're jumping in head first
I think we should try out their car
Has anyone as any of you guys
Ever driven that that self park Lexus
Do you own one have you have you
Try it out the the self park the auto park feature
Please send me an audio comment
Adam and podshow.com
Or of course you can always call the voice mail feedback
One, two, one, six, two, five
Six, three, five, seven
One, two, one, six, three, five
Six, two, five, six, three, five
Seven, eight, six, three, seven
Adam, here we go
One girl in casting
With Adam Curry
Hey Adam
F***ing ready to be stumps
I am good
He's the good test
With young pullback
God!
Adam hit test number 73
Three short snippets
And then three answers
So let's start right away
This is number one
Oh, y'all, come on man
He's trying to insult my intelligence here
It's a Holognox man, either
I recognize that one in any circumstances
Number two
I love this one
Yes, human league
Don't you want me?
Good songs, y'all
But not all that hard to recognize
And the final one, number three
I know it
I know you're sitting there with your buds
Jambed in saying
It's the patch up boys
Uh, type of the song I forgot
And that's it
This is answer number one
Boy, she comes
She's a man, either
And she's number one from 1982
All I know, some man either
I got that one right
And this is answer number two
Of course I had it right
Don't you want me?
You know I can't believe it
And I hear the truth
See me, don't
Don't you want me?
You want me?
And so number two from 1982 as well
The human league and don't you want me?
Number three
And this is the third answer
Today's hit this
All time, what's the call for?
West
West name girls
I've been to boys from 1986
I've got to have a point for that
Sometimes you better off say
It doesn't come in here
I've sent
You're wasting time the damn world
You're wasting girls
You're wasting boys
And so number three today's hit this
The patch up boys from 86 and western girls
Well, that's it
Again, hey, hey test with a good music from the 80s
Absolutely
Alrighty
Hit test.partshow.com
It's also up and running
And in the posts of the hit test
There will be a link to the answers
The hit test answers
And also the iTunes links
Also you can check them out
And also buy the tracks
Well, Adam, I hope you like this one
I love it
There will be a new hit test
So until then
Take care
And bye bye
Bye
Back to test at gmail.com
info
youngpalent.com
J&POLDT.com
Thanks once again to youngpalent
Hit test brought to you by Lexus this week
And check out hittest.podshow.com
Okay
Yeah
From mash up town
Good old art
Sent us yet another perfect track for the maximum music
Food Bar Friday
DJ Magnet
With some more of the patch up boys
Lower it into this one
You're going to love it
Love comes running up that hit
DSC 615
Doesn't hurt me
You want to feel how to feel
You want to know that it doesn't hurt me
You want to hear about the deal
You want to make it
You don't want to hurt me, but see how deep the bullet lies, unaware that I'm tearing
me with thunder, there's thunder in our hearts, baby, so much hate for the ones we love
Tell me we both matter, don't we, you know, love will always come to me, you know me, love will always come to me
love, you know me, love will always come to me, love will always come to me , love will always come to me and steady all of a thing
get out in this warm, warm place
as it says astation and not a humility
we're going on a bad road for the BB
1A that fell down
is only Christ
I don't know what
is for a kameravan
Come on, darling, can we steal some more from you now?
It's just when it looks like it's been too late
We run up that road, run and I'm back
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You'll find your link to this track.
That is sourcecode.com, taking you to mashuptown.com.
It is DJ Magnet.
He's from Denver.
A beautiful mashup of placebo's cover running up that hill.
You also heard the original Kate Bush version in there along with the Pet Shop Boys.
Mashup for today's Daily Sourcecode, the maximum music Fubar Friday edition.
Of course, one other thing happened this past week which really made our schedules nuts, not just here,
but throughout the entire pod show organization.
We had a hack attack.
For those of you who haven't heard about it, a guy who calls himself monkey,
spelled backwards, got in somehow into some of our system.
And although most of our security measures locked him out, locked him in, isolated him,
he was able to send out basically a hack message to a significant number of email addresses that are associated with our members.
Now, when something like this happens, I got to tell you, this sucks so incredibly bad.
It's really, what a waste of energy, of time, of money.
Because, you know, well, if you're a really small company, then, you know, that's one thing.
But, you know, we're reasonably large.
We have over 100 people right now, worldwide.
And this shouldn't happen to us.
Of course, it shouldn't happen to anybody really.
And I've been through, you know, the past 20, 25 years.
I've been through this before.
Only never with a large base of customers.
And essentially, every single listener, every single podcaster, everyone who is working or using pod,
you're working with, they're using pod show, of course, is one of our customers.
So this really, really sucks, major league ass.
The entire engineering team has been working on this for the past few days.
They could have been doing a lot of other really productive things.
One of the things that we just really, you know, that I wanted to bring in a security expert.
Now, we've got guys who are very well versed in security.
And, you know, we did a huge move of all of our stuff to a new,
a new co-location.
And actually, you expect stuff to happen during a move like that, but this took place later.
Now, of course, I do know some of the details of what took place, which I obviously can't discuss here.
What we'll be happening is, you know, as I said, we're just going to have to get a security experts in.
That's the best thing we can do.
Have them do a full audit of the system compared to the audits that we have compared to all the,
and you still can't always get all of the information.
And it's just sad, you know, it really blows.
And it's just, it's counterproductive for everybody.
And by the way, I'd like to say to the, to the monkey guy who did this, you know,
complete amnesty dude, if you want to come clean and want to help us and lock up any holes that you think you see or anything you could exploit.
You know, you could do it in complete anonymity and, you know, we're not going to do anything with you.
But, you know, you really fucked this up and it would be nice if you could help us turn some of that back.
Because there's just a shitty perception. I really, really hate it.
And although it's, you know, this is probably the end of it.
You know, nothing, you know, there's like two philosophies.
Back in the day when I had MTV dot com.
People, you know, it was the perfect address.
I was maintaining it myself.
And there was no way I could thwart any of the attacks that were coming in.
So I just left it open.
And everyone you think people would come in, they'd roam around.
And of course, there was nothing on there, really, of any interest to them, except, you know, just basically some files that you could see publicly anyway.
And often what would happen is they'd say, hey, you know, I opt to someone we're hacking to that it was a headless sun three computer that hack it and they say,
Oh, you know, while I was in here, I tightened up some stuff.
I put a new release of whatever software, you know, and that was cool.
I don't know.
I wonder what big, are there any other examples of big companies that have been through this or big or medium size companies?
Now, of course, the, the only thing of any real value to someone rummaging around our system would be, essentially, are our user names.
Our user name database.
And, of course, any information that's associated with that.
And we protect that with our lives and we encrypt that and we keep that in, in what I'm told is the, is the appropriate manners.
So there will be updates coming throughout the week.
A lot of you have questions about that.
And all I can say is we're incredibly sorry.
We're obviously a victim of this along with every, every customer of Pod Show.
And we're just going to, you know, being as open as we can about it.
You can't always communicate everything, as I said, for obvious reasons, security.
But I guess the best thing to do is, you know, have a independent audit done.
Take some recommendations from them.
And we should be hearing that I hope over the weekend, actually, that there will be able to send out an email to explain where we stand and where we're at.
So far, though, it seems like the damage is pretty limited.
Nothing has changed.
I use her pages.
Nothing has changed on the site.
Nothing has changed in our, in our core back end.
But through the mail server, a lot of emails were sent out.
Not everyone got them.
Some people got 20 or 30 emails.
And, um, man, that's, that's life.
Isn't it, though?
It's not all you had the chance to travel every major road in the USA.
Ever wondered what the real face of America looks like that's not from a glossy and fake manufacturer perspective?
Can't afford or don't have time to travel as much as you would like?
Come along with me, as I show you the more obscure parts of the USA and high definition Apple TV 720p video.
Check it out at trucker-tomhd.com, where HD stands for high definition.
Yeah, that stuff trucker-tom does is very cool.
You should see, it's like music videos, um, only of this beautiful country of ours.
And now that it's an HD, a lot of people do an HD.
Cali Lewis do an HD, room of girls doing HD.
I'm just seeing HD all over the place.
And I see a lot of people setting up separate feeds for HD versions of their shows so that it can go straight into Apple TV.
And other people who want to enjoy the HD experience.
And it really is pretty awesome.
Of course, we've, and we've had to up the limit of, of storage.
I think that's now been pushed through if not, you know, correct me.
But I think that you can now upload, uh, quite a mess load of, uh, of, uh, megabytes, uh, in order to facilitate all of that HD material that's coming out.
But it's cool, man, because it's HD stuff.
It's clearly where everything is going.
Well, Swagadam.
That won't swagadam.
The Sheren.
Delah.
DevaCast.potcho.com.
That's a couple of things.
When a Shweather shop, so povoo.
It's by Celine Mastorelli, and it's brand new to the Pod Save Music Network.
It's called Jiffa Passefois.
Oh, Jiffa Passefois.
And it means I don't want to know.
See you later.
So, Fubar Friday.
Oh, wow.
My little divaCast.
Huh.
What's the story?
Yeah.
It's from the Pantheon Music Network.
You know, you just don't hear enough French songs under radio anymore.
So, man, it's what put it on the Charlie.
Jiffa Passefois, Celine Mastorelli.
Oh.
I don't want to see you again.
Even if it's true, you're a piece of shit.
I don't want to see you.
You're the Fantas, my little divaCist.
You love my own color.
It's not good for you, my little divaCist.
I don't want to see you, you don't want to see me.
Before I went
Shouldi'd trade like Go
Choose bad stuff!
sounds messed up
I don't want time, I don't have the burn
I don't want to suffer
but you won't see me
I'm not afraid, I'm not afraid, I'm not afraid
I'm not afraid, I'm not afraid
I'm afraid, I'm not afraid
Thank you to the divas from the diva cast, diva cast.com for turning me on to that one.
I love the france of shansong.
Again, you just don't hear enough of that stuff on the radio.
But you can hear it all over what we call podcasting, pho shizl.
Podsame Music Network is where you can find that dailysourcecode.com, of course, where
you can find link to that in the show notes.
Well, let's see into the interview.
Yeah, it's Friday.
It's Friday.
Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, full about Friday and a final fun of the week.
Personal thought of the week.
You know, my mom passed away, July 2nd, 2006, one cancer, it was fucked up and not a nice
way to end.
And, you know, I have a lot of friends who listen to the show, who really helped me get through
that period.
And, you know, it's kind of coming up on the one-year anniversary and so you start to start
to think.
And it was my mom's, it would have been my mom's birthday a couple of weeks ago.
And I got a lovely card from one of her best friends, Brenda, who lives in New York City.
And it was just really nice, you know, I met her when I was like six years old or something.
And so I can vaguely remember.
I do know that she paid a visit to my mom before she passed away.
She traveled over to the Netherlands to see her.
And today I'm going to repay the favor.
I know she lives in New York, I was able to find her phone number and we're going to be
meeting for lunch today at the Harvard Club, which was her choice, that's very nice.
So my final thought of the week is really just going out to my mom.
And I want you guys to have a fantastic weekend, enjoy it, whether the weather is good,
or whether it's crap, just have a good time, you and your family.
And if you don't have your family near you, call them up and tell them you love it.
And on my shit, let me end the thought first.
Yeah, exactly.
I will talk to you on Monday.
I'll be in the Curry condo San Francisco for the next week.
We're going to have a lot of fun and we're going to just, we're going to have fun.
I promise you, meet me Monday.
Bye.
The best in the brightest, served up daily by the sharpest minds and content delivery,
Pajo in Line Light.