I can get through this, I can get through this, I can get through this.
Hort City PD, the number one online police drama series is now available.
Subscribe now and get the entire first season on your iPod.
And get ready for an action-packed season 2 coming July 2007.
Hort City.podshow.com.
Wow!
It is Friday, the 13th today.
And you are listening to DSC, 634.
The Fubar Edition, similarly like myself.
This day was fucked up already before it even started.
And now, ladies, all the ladies, let's talk about channels.
All right.
For $60 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking, couldn't you?
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I don't care.
I'll be asking you a matter of theory.
Give me another slide, I can't get through this.
I can't get through this.
Oh!
People are all you ready!
Let's start the show.
You sure are a cup-up man and then the one behind the hood.
Put it on for you.
It's like that thick and won sweet fish.
Come in out the door, and you're a group, we go, make it all happen right here right now
I want to welcome you all to have some beer now, we eat it
Let's cook the chocolate, make it to my new weekend
So take your time, grab a drink, a week up and see it
Let's make it to my new weekend
We'll see my name with some more, make it to my new weekend
Let's make it to my new weekend, make it to my new weekend
Let's make it to my new weekend, make it to my new weekend, make it to my new weekend
Let's make it to my new weekend
Let's make it to my new weekend, make it to my new weekend
Dr. Art Ruthy
We're if you missed it up for us, we're brought it back
Feel a bit of bangers a mess for the NCT incluso back, and black mashed
up with late sports calling out kicking off a foodbark frody on the daily
source code from swanky cereal everybody from the west side of G-town
it is the daily source code episode six hundred and thirty four
Beautiful day, we've got blue skies, we've got a little bit of wind
We got some clouds, but right now locally, it is fantastic.
I've got maximum music, full food bar for you,
all kinds of cool stuff coming your way.
And of course, apologies for the non-family safe
opening the other comic strip blogger.
But hey, who am I to complain?
Yes, because we've got one and only Amy Max.
Mm-hmm.
Amy.
Hey, Adam.
Hey, Amy.
Sorry about last week.
Once again, I was confused on my days.
And then I was going to send you one on Friday, four Friday.
And then I figured you're already done recording.
And then you didn't put up the food bar until Saturday.
It's so okay.
Amy was just not on our side.
Don't worry about it.
Don't worry.
Did I mention that I had caffeine today?
Uh-oh.
Anyway, how are you?
I'm good.
Thank you.
How about you, baby?
Everything okay?
Good.
Yeah.
So, I think you're going to love this week's exercise.
Oh, yay.
Okay.
Since you've complained last time about it being too easy,
I haven't been easy for you.
Okay.
Does anyone say doozy anymore?
All right.
Sorry.
I'm going to be on the floor.
So go ahead and get yourself situated.
How long am I back?
You're going to lay on your right side and you're going to prop yourself up with
your right hand.
Now straighten the right arm.
All right.
Make sure that your hand is in line with your shoulder.
Yeah, it is.
Your left leg should be stacked onto your right leg.
It hurts.
Is it woodwork?
Okay.
Are you a triangle?
Now, DSC kids, don't try this at home.
Okay.
Take your left leg and lift it up.
Crack.
Now bring it down.
Oh.
Take it forward.
I'm going to get the mic close.
I'm going to bring it back to center.
Forward.
And then up.
Yeah.
Or is this top?
And back down.
It's really hard.
Now to the back.
And then to the center.
Up.
One more time.
And down.
Don't tell me how to do on the other side.
Deep breath.
Great.
One more time.
And then we're going to switch sides.
Up.
Forward.
Down.
Back to center.
Up.
Down.
To the back.
Back.
Center.
Up.
And back down.
Come down.
Another deep breath.
I'm sweating.
And switch sides.
Okay.
I'm on left now.
Up on the left side.
Okay.
I'm on the shoulder.
I'm straight.
And the right leg goes up.
Down.
Front.
Center.
Up.
Down.
Out.
To the back.
And center.
Again.
Up.
Down.
Front.
Center.
Back.
Up.
Down.
And back.
And center.
Great.
Take a deep breath.
It's been fun, hasn't it?
I'm sure.
All right.
Until next time.
Oh wait.
Hang on.
Not yet.
What?
No.
I'm not going to tell him about the health of Venice channel yet.
Because it's already.
Did you want to tell him about the channel editor?
Really?
Wow.
What?
All right.
Well, you guys heard it your first.
This is Amy Mack.
What?
You guys heard it your first.
This is Amy Mack.
What?
You guys say your name.
It's ridiculous.
Until next time.
Thanks, baby.
The one and only Amy Mack plays a gentleman
Our ray of sunshine through the clouds of anything.
Amy.
I didn't feel anything in my ass.
Let me rephrase that.
I didn't feel any muscle pull in the glutamus maximus region.
Yeah.
And my arms hurt and my legs hurt.
Nothing else worked.
Health and fitness channel, huh?
Hmm.
I wonder if we'd have that channel editor coming out soon.
Hey there, Adam.
It's pretty Mason.
You're a virtual girl fan.
It's just checking in.
I was hoping you'd like to play a game with me.
You like games, don't you, Adam?
Now there's no handcuffs or feathers involved in this one.
But you seem to know an awful lot about ancient 80s music.
Geekboy stuff like HTML.
Pop this and pop that.
But do you know your pop culture?
Are you ready for it?
You know what I mean?
I got to stop.
Brittany.
What happened?
Something's completely full barred.
I'm only hearing you through the through one channel.
Send it again.
Well, yeah.
Because I definitely want to test my pop culture knowledge.
Maximum music's full barred.
I'm the Danny source.
Come to everybody.
Rockin' it out for the pop team.
Music Network.
Health and digital.
Sweet system.
Now we're freaking out.
You system.
Dayo being gone.
Yeah.
Now we're free.
Really have to fall in.
Now we dance for your life.
And I'm beecontaining my points.
I'm just gonna dance for your peace of mind.
I'm going to sing your voice.
Guess what it's like.
Enough.
That steam must've been to read me life to teach you the mine.
Brittany's gone.
You know you're gonna be insane.
See you soon, now we're waiting outside
We're waiting outside
Get more and more ready now
See you soon, now we're waiting outside
So many nights
So many nights, the time is up
Yeah, I wanna tell you, it's me
You're getting down, pushing me out into this town
Guess I've had a dream for the young dead news
I've made a man who's hoping to break me free from mine
Will be for you to keep your stay in the law
I've rubbed me through the nail
I've never had a roll all day
We don't hear well, so many hours to forward
So many nights, the time is up
We're waiting outside
Yeah, I wanna tell you, it's me
You're getting down, pushing me out into this town
We're waiting outside
Yeah, I wanna tell you, it's me
You're getting down, pushing me out into this town
I've made a man who's hoping to break me free from mine
Yeah, I wanna tell you, it's me
You're getting down, pushing me out into this town
Now we're waiting outside
So many nights, the time is up
Yeah, I wanna tell you, it's me
You're getting down, pushing me out into this town
We feel good, you know you're probably saying it
No way now seems to nails, now you're real real real
We feel good, now you're out of my eye, now you're real
We feel good, now you're real real
All right, I'll give you one guess where they're from
Think about it, it looks, it's guns and roses,
Motel crew, speed row, and fuel
You get it yet?
Of course, they're from Sweden, where else?
Hell and diesel!
Hell, hell and they're from Sweden
From the pot safe music network, link to that in the show notes at
Kicking ass of the Mexican music bar Friday
Shea were maximum music, but there's still lots of stuff
Coming into the phone numbers, now that I actually know how to get all the messages
It's almost overwhelming, but there's so much good stuff
Got him, hey, who is this?
I don't want to get my name, it doesn't matter
Listen, I happen to have about this music thing in the copyright board
I happen to know somebody who works
It's a executive at one of the very top level music streaming companies
You know the name and a heartbeat of your heart
Pandora
And just so happens, I was at a little Shindig with the guy
And I'm asked how's the company going
You guys gonna stay in business
Let me just stop for a second
For those of you who don't know the context of this
This is about this coming Sunday, July 15th
When the new royalty rates go into effect for streaming internet radio
Which I've discovered is really two things
It's either radio stations who are broadcasting their signal on the internet
Or it's playlists of music
That are being streamed
Like live 365 Pandora last FM
Even to an extent, Napster and another online music services
Where you rent music
Those fees are going up significantly
And will be calculated on a per listener basis going forward
Actually, there's some of its retroactive
So I guess the question was that you pose to this executive of
And I love the fact that you're calling me anonymously
The question you pose to some exact of a big streaming company
Was are you gonna guys stay in business
And so this is about the regulation that kick off in July
July 15th
So the mood and at least at this particular company is not good
And he told me something that I don't think is widely known
There has been legislation, both in the Senate and the House
That would overturn this copyright board decision
Well, not entirely true, wouldn't overturn it
But it would certainly delay it and provide for some
Some breathing room for people to get their act together
And everyone to figure some stuff out
So it's not a complete overturn of the legislation
But it is a block of the legislation that's absolutely true
And I think that has been posted relatively widely
However, if you notice, you haven't heard me say about that, right?
On a mainstream
Well, a couple of weeks ago or so
Apparently of the heads of all these companies that would be affected
And the RIA and these are a couple of executives represented
And you're all brought into a room with some big monkey mucks and cops
Don't honestly know who it was, I don't remember
But it was like, you know, kind of a committee, some big guy
And this guy just sits and down and goes, all right guys, look
We are not going to legislate on this
So wait a minute, so we got Congress together
With all the the mucketing mucks of all these streaming radio companies
And Congress said, we're not going to vote on this
Boy, does this take me back to everything I've been saying for the past two weeks
You know, don't just write your congressman with some bullshit plea
Threaten them, that's the best way to work
They threaten you, threaten them
If you don't vote for what I want, if you don't vote the way I want you to
I will not vote for you, I promise
Guarantee, I'll get you out of office
It's the only thing that works, cut to the chase
You don't have to be nice and political about it
And just story, we don't want to have to vote on this
So we're not going to
So you guys are going to come back in a week
And you're going to tell us how you're going to work this out
You will do this
Now I haven't heard what the result of that was
It might have just been a bunch of FUs and that was it
And if the congress isn't going to vote for
Why would the music industry bother to make a deal with anybody
They force their concerns to help make you just go away
Yeah, they won
You know, we can go back to the 1980s with CDs cost 20 bucks
Um, anybody had to buy them, right?
But anyway, that's not widely known
And that is a God's honest truth as I understand it
Um, and things are just simply not looking good
Last SM sure those guys got bought
But there are a lot of other resources that are either dependent
Or part of another corporation
A lot of lines, those guys are not going to want to spend the money
To stay in business so
I don't know if it's interesting to you or not
It is great
Oh, cool
Holder folder folder folder folder
An anonymous folder, ladies and gentlemen, appreciate the info
Do good intel
Yeah, that's not going to get overturned
That's clear unless it all of a sudden happens today
Um, so I doubt that
And there you go
It's clear there's only one direction
And it's very topical for me because I've been in conversations with
A large European independent record company
And we have a couple of them on the network
It was so great because
As I'm talking about having this company put all of their back catalog
On to the pod save music network and there's some awesome stuff in there
Um, and in fact, I can say it's red bullet
And uh, they have golden earring
You know, I've played some of this before because I got permission
So golden earring
Uh, focus, uh, shocking blue
Um, but his, uh, the sun has his own, uh, his runs a spin and records
Which is a big dance label
Anyway, we had email conversation
And he brought in, um, his buddy Hine
Who is, um, on the board of epitaph records
And, you know, and I said, well in that interesting
Uh, Hine has over a hundred tracks
Uh, epitaph has over a hundred tracks on the pod save music network
So what's happening is this 25% of the music business
Which uh, is made up of independence
They're seeing the light, my friends
They are seeing the light
This, this, the whole conversation was in Dutch
I wish it could translate it because a lot of it just doesn't carry over
But one thing, um, uh,
Villam said Villam is the owner of the record company
He said
Essentially he said, what the fuck?
No guts, no glory
And I love that so much
Right, he's absolutely right
And we're just going to route around it
You know, this whole music thing, this whole license music
These, you know, the 40 most popular
You can't even name 40 most popular songs of the day
Because you probably only can name
The top five or the top ten, if anything
It's the spectacle, it's part of the spectacle
You know, we've been talking about the society of the spectacle
And the, the business works perfectly
Um, you, uh, you create, uh, you've got a star
They have a hit record, uh, then the tabloids jump on top
And then there's all kinds of scandals
And it has to stir around, to wher around
And if you're, timely enough to be out with the tour
Or the album, you can benefit from that
And then of course, the artist self-destructs
And maybe we'll make a comeback later on
It's all about the society of the spectacle
I'm, uh, this is Mark Elso, Los Angeles, California
Listening to 633
A long time listener of, uh,
Well, basically, to Charlie and other podcasts
And, uh, I gotta tell you, you're right on the money
Uh, when it comes to mainstream music
And, uh, when it becomes pot-safe music
And when it becomes, in alternative
For people to listen
And, um, it's just, uh, just bear with me a little bit
Because I haven't thought here
You know, in the States, NFL is really big
And baseball is big, but interestingly enough
They're charging a lot of places right now
For the NFL network to be able to watch
The NFL
And, uh, so all your favorite bars
And stuff like that
They, they got restrictions
They don't have the, they don't have the, uh,
The games you want to see
So, basically, people go other bars
And stuff like that, but
Oh yeah, well, it's, it's no different from the music business
I mean, sports rights
Oh man, sports sports rights
That's the, that's the big deal in television
That's the big draw, that's where all the money
In fact, that's not where all the money comes from
Drawing audiences
And, um, and because, you know,
A showing this in your bar
Is essentially a public performance
And, of course, that is prohibited
You know, you can do it, but you just have to pay money
Um, and believe me, they've got a force
Out on the ground that goes to every single bar
And they get charged for the music
They play, they get charged for the, uh,
Uh, the television they're showing
It's, uh, hey, it's not illegal
It's not wrong, it's just, you know,
They're basically forcing their customers away
Uh, and their customers, in this case, uh,
Right now, our bars and, uh, public places
And, places where stuff is performed
Then use as well
So, uh, well, they're squeezing out every, uh, last drop of revenue
Which again, is, there's nothing wrong with it
It's what the organization has to do, you know
That's, that's the way the beast operates
They're losing money on sales
So they got to make it up somewhere else
Uh, excuse me, Coca-Cola
Um
What was the point I was going to make about that
Ah, I don't know, what's continued listening
Oops
Where the, uh, here we go
Uh, uh, there was a point I was going to make
I'll come back to it
I'm seeing, and one I'm predicting here is the rise of soccer
And, um, and it's just funny to watch it
Basically the more you control and try to control people
And the more you, you push a bunch of rules on things
People find other
avenues and, uh, as much as, believe it or not
I'm not a soccer fan, but dammit
I just watched Argentina beat Mexico
And somebody was explaining explaining to me
I don't know why, but how I was watching it
But dammit, it was exciting
And, um, and, and that's taken from me
Somebody would never even think about watching soccer
So, if, if you could put the same kind of logic in there
Just the idea that people will actually
Listen to other things
And, uh, it's, it's funny
Because whatever you want to call it
Big media or big paid media or whatever
Restriction media you want to call it
There's always going to be an avenue for other people
To enjoy and it expands itself and it creates
Other opportunities for people out there
So, yeah, big go
Right on man
Yes, indeed, in fact, uh, I noticed something very early on
When you've heard a pod save song
Which, of course, by definition, is not mainstream
Not a hit, it's not being jammed into you
Over and over again, but you hear
One or two times on a different podcast
You start to recognize it
You start to be able to sing along and I realize very early on
Oh, sounds like, wait a minute, this feels just like a, you know, mainstream
It's like I'm sing along to the hits
It's just, it's different hits coming from different places
Absolutely. Now, why do you think we have
Such a beautiful arrangement with British telecom here in the UK?
It's really simple
Just like, um, every, every media company
Um, basically has the same offering
You know, you've got your BBC channels
You've got your, uh, your, uh, your ITV or channel 4
And you can get the same offering
And of course, it's all the triple or quadruple play
Right, so you get your internet, your telephone
And your television
Uh, all through a box
So virgin media has a box, which comes through cable
We have sky, which comes through has a, they have a box
Comes through satellite
And then we have British telecom
Who have just recently put a box into limited release
Called, um, BT vision
And it's IP TV, so television over the internet
That comes through the DSL cable
Um,
Now, all of these companies
Basically go out and spend millions
On the same thing
So they spend millions on getting some movies
They spend millions on getting some, some rights
To some, to some sports in Europe
It's traditionally, uh, football
Or soccer as you would say
But it's all kind of the same thing
You know, there's no differentiator
Uh, unless of course you think of the concept of pod show TV
So that would be something very, very different to have on your box
Now wouldn't it? So that's really the main reason why why we're here
And why it's so exciting, uh, because, you know,
We are there to give people an alternative
Something cool to watch or to listen to
And they're coming
You know, people are secreting out
And in a certain point, it's just like it's not going to be seen
You know, not be labeled as alternative, but just
Good shit
Or maybe not so good shit
Who knows, maybe maybe I might become a big soccer fan
If that happens, it just tells you that
Uh, that those that are trying to control people
We'll find themselves in the loot short end of the stick
Yeah, and uh, maybe it's the same thing with music
Uh, absolutely meant, absolutely
Totally
Totally agree. Of course the whole shame of uh, of the music part is
Is that we're actually being restricted
And we are um, no longer able to share
The soundtrack to our lives
You don't hear the soundtrack to your life anymore, because it's not commercially viable
Because it's not a huge hit and can't be, you know, programmed in
To be shoved down the very thin tubes that traditional mainstream media has
If you're talking about radio
They just don't have time to play all the songs that are part of the soundtrack to your life
But we've got a solution to that, my friend
Hey Adam, how are you doing?
Right, man, how are you?
So hit this number, 78. I'm ready. Again, three very short clips
And the three answers, so you know how everything works
Oh, this is number one
Oh, please, John
Steven to me one more time
Frankie goes to Hollywood
Relax
That was pretty easy. Come on, crank it out baby
Give me some tough ones
And number two
Let the music play Shannon
Oh, yes, 1984
And number three
I think you got me on the third one there, John
Of course, I'll be saying oh crap when I hear it
And times up and these are the answers
Number one
From 84, Frankie goes to Hollywood
This is relax
Relax
When you want a second to it
Relax, don't do it
When you want to come
And so number one Frankie goes to Hollywood
I know what this is
So number two, also from 84, Shannon
We started
Yeah
Oh man, that was the jam back in the day
Yeah, what was number three
And so number two, Shannon and let the music play and this is answer number three
It's with me, Houston
Oh
Okay
Oh, yeah
Whitney Houston from 1987
As handsome number three and so emotional
And that concludes hit test number 78
Well, Adam, I hope you had them all and you did well
Um, I had fun
Creating these answers
It was difficult to bring these tracks back to about 30 seconds
But I did it and it was kind of fun to do
So
Um, the answers and iTunes links can be found at hittest.partsio.com
And I'll be back probably next week
With hittest number 79
So until then, take care
Bye bye
Hittest at gmail.com
info.com
www.gmail.com
Alright everybody, how about that for a Friday
Fix from the organization to the preservation for the soundtrack of our lives
Everything used under the fair use doctrine
Just thinking about Shannon let the music play
Just a personal anecdote about that
When I went to West Virginia to go to college
And I was planning on studying communications
And so I'm in BF West Virginia
Actually
New Clarksburg
And
And my roommate is Ty Hamilton
Ty is from Trenton, New Jersey
Black Kid and I was from Holland
I wasn't really a white kid
And we'd never met each other
So we're in, you know, in a relatively small dorm room
And we're kind of like hey man, how are you doing?
Like scoping each other a little bit
He pulls out his boom box
I pull out my boom box
And that was going to be the defining moment
You know, I'm sure he expected some incredible
My boom box instead
I clicked it on and played a tape
From the radio station that I had been working
At the pirate radio station Amsterdam
Called radio decibel and the song that I played
Was Shannon let the music play
And then he showed me how to
How to a body pop
I know it sounds real 80s
But it was a very defining moment in my life
I have to tell you
Y'all pull that, thank you once again
Body brought to you by Coca-Cola
This summer when you buy Coke
You get music
You can win an iPod or free songs or nightchains
You're outer, I'd like to make a motion
To rock this mother out
You're outer, please don't bang that gavel
You can try this cowbell out
Let's all give a night
To the hardest working lawyer
You're outer, what do you say?
You might even put the finger in
You know, how's it going
Adam, it's Jersey Todd
The official musicologist of the Cha Cha
And well, the hardest working lawyer in podcasting
Yeah, that's the new title
But listen, I've got a great, great band
And a great, great story for you
I got somebody called The Seed Dragons
And I got a great, great story for you
And I got a great, great, great story for you
I got somebody called The Seed Dragons
And I got somebody called The Seed Dragons
And I got a new York city
Actually, it's really just one guy
And some other guys went like all bands
But it's Darrell Thurston
And Darrell's been around for a really, really long time
He was a session artist
He was heard on HBO Showtime
He was heard in Madison Square
Garden when the next came out
And he's really been around for a long time
But he finally got back to writing songs on his own
And he's come up with a great one
That's up on the pot safe music network
This song is called Sweet The Lion Island
And I'm absolutely loving it
It's just kind of got this great kind of bird's feeling to it
And it just kind of really, really works for me
I think it's going to work for you too
Check this out
It's The Seed Dragons with Sweet The Lion
On your Food Bar Friday
Check this out
Oh
Walking down the dirt in the street
With the sunlight in her hair
Seed with the nipples
She pretends that she don't care
Now I'm Caesar
Now I'm Notre
When she's back in home
Life is Life
When she's all alone
Sweet The Lion Island
And you know it's getting better
And we can save the Lion
And now I'm Notre
When I'm Notre
When I'm
When I'm Austria
When I'm Notre
Sweet and I love it, now it's getting better every day
And no one else can make me feel this way
Now it's getting better every day
Now I'm not gonna make me feel this way
What can you do?
What can you say?
Sometimes you just want to run away
Sweet and I love it, now it's getting better every day
And no one else can make me feel this way
My thanks as always to the official music colleges of the Charney, Sir Jersey Todd
See Dragons and Sweet Delilah, you need to wake me up in the middle of the night to give me a sound like that
That's 60s kind of
I would call it the era of the pirate ships in the North Sea
Those of you old enough to know what the hell I'm talking about
Nice, really, really nice
Oh man, I'm not even halfway through my list of stuff to do for you today
Already at 36 minutes and that's without a check 1, 2, 1, 2 at the beginning
Today, if all things go according to plan, I can't promise it because it's not my call to make
But if all goes according to plan, we may be able to push cheddar live
Which means we'll be able to be messing around with channels all weekend long
You'll know how it's there
If you go to, if you have an account on pod show, you go to your profile page
So mine is adam.podshow.com
And at the top there there's a box and you click on my channels
And it'll look the same
Only there will be different options to play the channels
And you'll also see an edit channel button
That's really all that you have to look for
I don't know if I do anything better than you, but this is the way I see channels
This is for your call, I had to know what's what our control is
In your iTunes, you've got your podcast feed
So you've got your list of big busy news, daily source code, blah blah blah
Your channel is just an RSS feed, that's all it is
Put in the channel manager on pod show website
You're actually controlling what gets dumped into that feed
Oh James, I love it when you're on the money
Regardless of what it is, it does not have to be described
Somebody else's feed, it does not have to be described
XML or RSS, it's just it's
It's as easy as dragging a dropping an icon into a box
That's exactly what it is James, you don't have to know about feeds or anything
You just say, hey, here's an episode or here's a show
I want to put it into the channel, drag, drop, done
It's the files that you will top of yourself from other places on the network
I like that top up yourself, yeah
RSS feeds, so I can get for my wife, for her podcast channel
On iTunes, which she never updates, I can now create a channel for her
And drop in the favorite YouTube best of YouTube video
Or a favorite daily source code or an accident house
One episode at a time, all the entire feed
Do it, for example, I'm going to take 2-10 of best of YouTube
I'm going to drop that into a little bit, that's my feed
Then the next time my wife opens a iTunes and syncs a iTunes to podcast
It then goes to that feed, the one that I've created
Which will now call the channel
And it will pull them, what I've dropped in that book of media content
James, hold on, let me give you a boing
Oh, yes, I love it when you're right on the money, dude
So I control the RSS feed from within potential
Yes, does that make sense?
Yeah, even better than that, as you're roaming around pod show
If you find a show or an episode you like, you can just click get it
And then you can add it to the channel right from there
You can just say, oh, okay, I'm just going to add this to the channel
Just pop it right in
One after even go to the channel manager, you can just add it as you're surfing along
And any channel
Sound like what it's after
The reason that it works so well as far as I'm concerned
It's because I can take instead of going to my friends and send them an email
Go and check the send them a net download this download the other
I just give my friends my RSS feed
And see, stick that on iTunes
And every time you want iTunes all sent or I don't get it
You get all the stuff that I wanted to show you today at work
But instead of me taking 20 minutes out of the way to tell you all about this
You just download it anyway
Off you feed
And that's all it works
Because it's so all in comparison
You wear
And then the RSS starts getting complicated
I can take their feed and put them into one for me
Swat and take bobs and jones and clairs and sanders feed
And put them into one feed for me and don't let in my iTunes
So I don't have to subscribe to each individual one direct in iTunes
I just put all their feed in my feed
So now I've got my wife's feed and my friend's feed
And they will come in the iTunes
Yes, where it's complicated
You can stick those two in the one feed and pull that in
Put that right
Yes, that's right
That's right
James, I was smiling from just a shit eating grin
From ear to ear when I heard that
Just before the show, exactly James
And a couple caveats to that
I think when we push cheddar live
We won't have the get channel
Functionality live yet
Because we really don't know how that's going to work
We really don't know what the result is going to be on scale
You know, if
Who knows
I really just don't know
So we want to make sure that we're not going to bring the site to its knees
If everyone's putting channels and channels and channels on the first day
So it's all beta and it's all going to be ugly
And it's not about the interfaces about the functionality
We're not going to promote this heavily
It's just you and me guys, essentially we're going to know about this
And one other thing I wanted to say
In our philosophy
Which, by the way, is not far from the philosophy of Apple
When it comes to operating systems and formats
But that's a different conversation
What if you had a channel of PDFs
Do you think those would play in the dashboard?
Could be. What if you had a channel of pictures from a gallery
What if you had a channel of blog posts
I mean all of a sudden you're seeing that you can mesh together
Feeds of all kinds of different content
And you can become a broadcast or a producer
A distributor of information
Extremely valuable stuff in the interconnected world
And I've been talking about this all week
Hopefully that'll go live today again
You'll know if you go to your profile page and you click on my channels
You'll see that there's different ways to output it
Not just to put it on your iPod James, but you can also say, hey, just play it right here
So if you're not near your iTunes, you can just log into your account
Any web browser and enjoy your channels on the dashboard
Right from poncho.com or put it into Windows Media Player
Or some other player that'll handle everything
It's a big one
I'm really excited about
Hey podcast business
My name is loosegagging and I'm inviting you to my Los Angeles Music Awards showcase
Well, I've got nominated for best alternative song with my track what I
And if you're in the alley area, Sunday July 15th
Come on over to the parliament
It's a 3, 3, 8, 7, motor Avenue, West LA
And from more information and tickets, you can go to my website
Which is over at nooshscalgan.com
That's n-o-u-s-h-s-k-a-u-g-e-n.com
And see it show you my teeth
This is Busy Kajou and each and every week on Solipsistic Nation
I play the absolute best from all genres of electronic music
This week we'll delve into grime and dubstep and their love child grime step
We'll hear a music from focus, tecmatics, DJ Flex and much much more
Plus interviews with Leo from grime step international and the lads from the UK connection
Quick rapping with like the electronic hip hop sounds that's based in some sort of Jamaican groove
It's really hard to explain it without using the term grime
The drum sculpt is made of a blue bric and it's brought it back to the room
The past is made of kind of bad enough
The drum sculpt kind of just brought it back in with these blue grimes
Cut them out and I'm feeling it messed up
I think it's just being in a back to the room
Join us at Solipsistic Nation.com
For mix of grime, dubstep and grime step
With base frequencies so low you'll fill it in your bones
So we want a T.F.I.S.A.A.C. Nation.com
What's up together?
The page nine and you're listening to the daily source code
Look in for your mind's eyes
Hell yeah
Marcus Kaos checks it
Bring us another page nine
Mark the pussy
I'm from our front end
Laced in transmittions of anonymity
There'll apply's wasted space in my vicinity
The picture holds all sorts of vast ability burning up
Do the arms up, but they're never near
How many of you let the pussy down
You might know from a minute
Then you'll be thinking in time
This will work as I don't know
That will be up to let the pussy come down
Ha ha ha
I'm not in a fair night
Say it anyway
The other time I actually must talk for there we go
That what excuses will you know is not that scary now
It's only my mind about you to take care of you
But he's a jet that I can fight
I'm good for you
I'm not in a fair night
Then you'll be thinking in time
This will work as I don't know
That will be up to let the pussy come down
Ha ha ha
I'm not in a fair night
Say it anyway
I'm not a little bit, I'm never, I'm never, I'm never, I'm never, I'm never, I'm never, I'm never, I'm never, I'm never, I'm never, I'm never, I'm never, I'm never, I'm never, I'm never, I'm never, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not,
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'll't, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not anymore, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not. I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm
is that you've knocked you on the ground agnag recipe?
Yeah that's right well you'd rather talk to my wife but you know we just
called we wanted to call you the pod father and announce our a year at the
wheel podcast video cast and you know and we're gonna drive around for a whole
year and talk to people and videotape them and podcasts. Yeah exactly and
you should go on and explain the adamant that said I'm creeped like I'm an
gateway. It's because you watched how you were coming from Stanford so
yeah I think. Anyway you know I year at the wheel.com. Yeah check it out it can be
so much fun and hopefully we won't get arrested anywhere. Yeah we end up
watching a DC November I'm super Tuesday November 4th and we're gonna go
like to stirge his bike rally and the Republican National Convention so we're
mixing it up because we're gonna cover the election for a whole year. And you
know podcasting is basically ruined our life so we just thought we'd go
with it you know we've started we've been podcasting for four years we got thrown
out of a town because of it and no embrace the hate. Okay look this is such a
long message okay bye yeah Mr. Curry. Thanks thanks for making me feel old
at the rear very in there. Okay very interesting. The reason of course why I
find this interesting is I think this is a perfect tie in for the one and only.
If you recognize the tune sing along. Okay you kids now I'm not quite sure
about you getting thrown out of a town and in fact that only kind of enhances
the appeal to me. I like rebels. I think this is what I've been looking for and
just hit me just before the show that I'd like to make you guys an offer. Now
let me just play a little open kimono here on the free Trinity Project.
A whole lot of water under the bridge. I see it as a very very complicated
to do with multiple people and you were the first ones who well you're of
course you're not offering this to me but you're going to be on the road for a
year. Now I've been trying to get this Trinity Project set up and I know that
it's going to take money and resources and effort to really pay it off and make
it work and we want to have lots of people involved. They need to have expenses
covered or at least that because it's a big deal. It's driving a car that can
fall apart easily. So we went searching for some sponsors. We got some
interest from Nokia and due to all the talk about that Tom Tom go became very
interested in fact that they come out with their new summer GPS products. So
they come out with their new products, the GPS products in the summer and
believe it or not we also got some significant interest from Mercedes Benz who of
course love the whole idea that they're car or they're one of their models as
being used. Although not entirely representative of the current Mercedes Benz
line I might add out point out. So here's what I propose to you guys. I would
love nothing more than to have you spend a year at the wheel in Trinity and
here's the commitment I'll make. We will make sure that she stays on the road.
Either we'll do it or we'll do it withheld from Mercedes Benz who may have to
provide a sweep up van pick up all the bits behind her but that should be
relatively doable. I think the engine will hold together just by every single
part has been replaced so that should work. To cover your expenses not just the
expenses of what you're doing but really for producing the content I'd like to
compensate you. I'd like to pay you to do that and that's where I'd like the
community to kick in and help you guys determine where you're going to do
where you're going to go. And can you imagine how awesome it will be to have a
biodiesel car show up on super Tuesday? I mean it seems so logical to me.
So there you go. I think we finally have something. I don't know if I can get
the sponsors in but I will commit if you guys will commit to staying on the road
for a year and doing it in Trinity I'll commit to keep the car on the road and I
will compensate you guys for doing this and for let's see actually I'm looking
at the year to wheel.com see sponsored you guys have any sponsors yet no
not yet. Okay so if you're interested let me know because I think we finally
have something and we can still you know hit all the people who are interested
in participating because you'll just stop by say hi to everybody and we'll
create podcasts and video stuff and we'll cause a ruckus and we're going to get
noticed. I know we will and it's all about independence. You too seem like
very independent spirits. So and apparently you know you can do this. You can
f off for a whole year and drive around. I'm insanely jealous. So that's my
thought. I'd love to hear from you guys open kimono time really appreciate the
feedback. All right one more song for today then. One of new black lab
comes out you can't help but play it. No I'm saying I mean guys are such friends
of the Charlie. Don't know if this is up on the PMN yet but Neil sent the
to me so happy to play it.
And I'll make you sad. I won't give up and don't mind waiting. I can't wait
another day. I won't give up and don't mind what to do but I can't walk away
because I lost myself. I lost my heart. I won't mind but you crush my heart.
I know that I've got one last chance to show you the real you.
So will you stay still a little while? Everything is easy when you love me
and see you smile. I'll go down down before it's through. It's not the secret
that I wouldn't do feel. I won't give up and don't mind waiting. I can't wait
another day. I won't give up and don't mind what to do.
And I can't walk away because I lost myself. I lost my heart. I won't mind but you crush
my heart. I know that I've got one last chance to show you the real you.
So will you stay still a little while? Everything is easy when you love me
and see you smile. I'll go down before it's through. It's not the secret
that I've got one last chance to show you the real you. So will you stay still a little while?
I'll go down before it's through. It's not the secret that I've got one last chance to show you the real you.
So will you stay still a little while? Everything is easy when you love me
Black Lab brand new and of course big friends of the show.
Man it's almost been an hour. It's been quite a ride. It's been a very vocal aggressive maximum music
full bar Friday. I'm almost fatigued from doing all this today.
It's Friday.
Well the final thought for this week is all about the society of the spectacle red pill blue pill stuff.
So let's just say that we all are caught in the society of the spectacle and whatever
the spectacle of the day is the spectacle du jour. We pay attention to it and get completely sucked into it.
So stuff like the earth is going to explode and die. We're going to die of horrible diseases.
A Britney Spears is the best thing since sliced bread. And Paris, Hilton going to jail. These are all spectacles.
And of course what's really happening is that people are starting to basically take the red pill
and unhook from the matrix and they're finding alternatives. They're finding different music, different programming,
different media, different people, different connections, different contacts, mainly throughout the internet.
And that is really the revolution.
And you know, revolutions aren't just one single event. They often take many, many, many events
and many, many years to finally push through. And I think that we're kind of in the same situation.
So instead of trying to convince people to unplug from the matrix, instead of trying to give them the choice of taking the red pill,
I think we have to create our own spectacle. So things like a year at the wheel with free Trinity, that's a spectacle,
things like bum rush the charts, that's a spectacle. You know, we have to create these spectacles to get people to say,
Oh, wait a minute. There's another spectacle over there and jack into our matrix.
And then it's very easy for us to slip them the red pill. You know what I'm saying?
So keep that in mind. Oh, and there's one other thing I was thinking about last night.
It is time for me once again to post a link to the Zen TV experiment.
I've done it probably about twice a year for the past three years.
And it's time to post it once again. If you really want to know what television is doing to you.
Right down to the heart of this whole flap. I don't know if you were following it. The BBC had a trailer running for a documentary about the queen.
And Annie Leibowitz and one scene was photographing the queen. And she asked the queen if she could take the crown off.
And the queen made some remark cut to the queen's storming off. Well, it turns out, and I love this.
It turns out that that was a setup. The queen didn't actually storm off.
In fact, they took footage of her walking into the room and made it seem like she got pissed off about the question and walked off with a photo shoot.
And they had to apologize to the queen because it didn't happen that way. Oh, gee.
You mean you're telling me that television lies? No.
You're not actually going to tell me that they fake stuff to make it more interesting? No.
You're not going to tell me that happens through video editing. Are you? No. Oh, my gosh.
There's gambling going on here. No.
So you take this as MTV experiment. And then you tell me. Next week when you call and you tell me,
if you don't think that you are completely blue-pilling yourself when you're watching mainstream media.
And that my friends is the final thought of the week.
Today at resourceco.com, Adam at podshow.com, I want you to have yourselves a fantastic weekend.
And I'll be back here on Monday. Please join me. Bye, everybody.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.
The best and the brightest.
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering podshow and limelight.