Port City PD, the number one online police drama series, is now available.
The pod father had a cameo in the season 1 finale, who will be making cameo appearances
in season 2.
You, me, get in on the action.
PortCity.podshow.com
No excuses. No BS. Delta Sierra Charlie's 633.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Do you know what I mean?
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
You know, I mean, you know, I mean, I like to think I'm trying to get this shit.
You're gonna have to hold my chest and kiss, and I'm curious.
Like I picked him on week, please smoke him.
You sure are a birdie man at him to bounce.
You sure are a birdie man at him.
You sure are a birdie man at him to bounce woman.
I'll have something for you.
Don Hennelian, pullin' over in there.
We call it not that great.
Agro-1, Mash is it up, it's big time.
Needles, hotel California versus the Hustle Athletics
taking it as noisy as San Francisco.
You can find it at agro1.com or force through Mash of Town.com.
Everybody, Delta, Sierra Charlie 633,
the Danny Soros code coming to you from Swanky Surrey.
That's right, G-Town.
It is the curry manner.
Sorry about yesterday.
It was one of those days.
I just didn't have the energy anymore.
I had to leave early in the morning,
had several meetings at the crash pad in London.
It was great.
I've been going to the crash pad a lot,
which, of course, makes production of the show a little bit tougher
because of the commute and everything.
But Jill Mills was there from the ICAST
and just lots of activity, excitement going on.
We had super-aging Keith and Alan the Face Kingston
dropping by and we're working along on all kinds of stuff.
And, of course, go figure, there was a bomb scare
just down the road from the crash pad.
Now, we are on Charlotte Road right off of Great Eastern Street,
which is in, what do you call it, a shortage.
There you go.
In not so Swanky shortage.
And on Old Street, just down the road,
there was a bomb scare.
So you can imagine that it funny though,
not even reported anywhere,
not on BBC websites or in the news.
But it was, you know, so probably it was someone's valleys
or suitcase just laying around and they probably had to go
and blow that up.
But it was a very indicative of the times we live in
because I immediately observed everybody
because Alan the Face came in late for the appointment
that he had with me about an hour late
because the tube station was closed off.
I think at Old Street.
And he said, well, you know, there was a bomb scare.
And I looked at everyone in the room and I was like,
whatever, you know, don't really responded.
And I was ready to roll out the line again.
You know, if anyone doesn't feel comfortable,
they want to go home.
It's not a problem.
What the hell was that?
Oh, what does that, is that this?
I don't know where that sound came from.
That was kind of frightening.
One of my devices is burping at me.
So that made the commute home horrible.
It took me two and a half hours to get home.
I was on conference call from most of it
because as we're working on sucking less,
there's a lot of things that are happening.
One of the most exciting things, of course,
is that tomorrow, I think we'll be able to roll out
cheddar.
It's the new channels editor.
And you'll be able to use it tomorrow.
So there'll be some talk of channels
in today's Daily Source Code.
Also on Sunday, and this is something really exciting.
We worked out this week.
Dr. Cockney, our official international sex therapist,
if you've never seen him, just you got to see Dr. Cockney
show international sex therapist.podshow.com.
Just to make it easy, we don't want too many people
finding it.
Or just go to podshow.com and type in Dr. Cockney,
or any of those terms, you'll love this guy.
He will be featured in the news of the world on Sunday.
This is a huge newspaper.
It's totally a low brow, which I love.
I love.
It's, I think it's affiliated with the sun.
It's probably a Murdoch paper.
So there'll be featuring Dr. Cockney, his most recent episode.
We're going to do this for a couple of weeks.
I'm very excited about it.
And this will be about four play.
How long, I think the question is, how long should you wait?
Oh, no, how long is appropriate for four play
before the actual deed?
And Dr. Cockney's in and about,
I think the London this time asking people that question.
So that question will be printed in the news of the world.
We're also going to run this episode on the news of the world
website.
So we should be introducing a whole sh-boat load of new people
to what we're doing, and I'm very excited about it.
Hi, Adam.
This is Justin from San Francisco, Long time listener
first time calling on all that.
The reason why I was calling was because you've got
some dude copying analog to MP3, but what about your old podcast?
I was looking for the first show that you were talking about
the official biographer, Tom from Down Under.
Yeah, he's, he's indeed digitizing analog.
What are you, what are you looking for?
We're just, Christina, remember, you were standing in the kitchen
of the cottage, and asked us if we had similar issues
with our kids, and you got all anxious because she was running late.
Oh, my God, classic memory for me.
Yeah, I remember.
And I wondered if you had it hidden on a server somewhere.
How that would really be great if you had that.
And I want to thank you also for messing up the other day
because my cousin and I started a show.
And if the pot's harder could screw up that,
that would make it a sweet ass of themselves.
Then, you know, it's not that bad if we mess up too.
The red tilt choice.
Testing one, two, one, two, test, test, tickle.
Well, you should be able to find that through search.
I'm trying to think if that episode, if that was uploaded to
the podgeo system, if we had podgeo even in use, then I know exactly
which episode you're talking about.
It was when Patricia was in the Netherlands,
and I had the wireless mic on running around,
trying to get Christina off to school.
I'll have to look for it.
Actually, I could do the search for.
He's probably, if you just search for, I would say,
D.S.C. and Christina, you should be able to find it.
Let me give it a shot.
OK, let me just see what happens.
Because we also track show note episodes,
and soon we'll be tracking what you call it, contextual stuff.
So actually, what's being said in the show.
Man, for some reason, everything seems slow.
It's interesting.
Almost like, let me see, D.S.C.
D.S.C. D.S.C. 12th of June 2007,
May 2006, no, no, no, no, no, well, maybe it was in that one.
What is this?
Let's see, this is a, this is the best stuff, Charlie, I think.
I don't know, man, if that's going to be easy.
It seems like it was earlier than 2006.
Let me see, this is from, where was I here I am?
Sixth of May 2006.
Yeah, but this is a rewind week, maybe.
I'll see if I could find it.
If not, anyone else just to shove that into the comments,
it would be greatly appreciated.
I'm thanks for bringing back the hip test.
Is it a one-to-week thing?
Should we go camping, pay for us?
Great.
I love it.
I think it's back to your days.
I don't care.
Two out of three is wonderful.
I mean, I got another great one for tomorrow.
Young already sent it in.
I haven't listened to it.
Of course, that would ruin it if I listened to it.
But yeah, indirectly, it isn't deed sponsored by Coca-Cola.
This summer, when you buy Coke, you get music.
You can win an iPod or free songs on iTunes.
And ever since I've drawn your attention to it,
people are indeed winning songs on iTunes.
And we had, yes, the other day we had a guy
won an iPod, so it does work.
And indirectly, yes, it is, of course, sponsoring young,
because I can't have young do this for free.
It's a lot of work that he has to do.
So he's being paid a producer fee for producing both the hit test
on a weekly basis and keeping the site current.
And I'm putting the links to iTunes, which is very important.
That was a prerequisite from the organization,
for the preservation to the soundtrack of our lives.
Very important.
We put links into the people can go and buy these things
of which you hear just a very small snippet all under the fair.
Hey Adam, this is Eric Port-Norgen.
At Red Till Blue Bay,
Bill thing reminds me of Sammy Hagar, the Red Rocker,
and I've got the sun there, it's here in front of me.
And here's the first little, uh, first few words.
I've read it all, it's black and white.
The spectrum made of shade I like.
The crimson rays are ruby red,
technicolor light, red.
I want it red.
There's no substitute for red, red, painted red, green,
a mean compared to red.
Give me that red till brother.
We're going down the rabbit hole.
I do, I appreciate you picked up on that.
That was, uh, from, uh, actually, I really liked the show that I did.
The, the, the 632, we were talking about the society of the spectacle.
This book that Brian knew, uh, 50% of the, uh, the production guys at Pod Show sent me.
Uh, from Guida Boa, and, uh, it's a translation.
He's French.
It's, uh, the, when it first came out, this book caused quite a stir.
And, um, and so I actually, uh, let me just, uh, go to a daily source code.com
and read the, the comment that Brian put in there.
So what I did do is that, you know, based on a couple of comments that came in yesterday,
um, that really, we do live in the society of the spectacle and, uh,
and there was a whole list of things like a bird flu and, uh, uh, uh, a global cooling from the 70s
and all these big spectacles that we just get sucked into.
And, you know, really, that is the matrix, um, it's communication.
It's television is radio, but also blogs and, and podcasts and independently produced media
definitely propagate a lot of that.
Um, so it is, you know, we're all kind of on a blue pill trip and, and we're just enjoying things
and letting the information feed in and now we've become information and content routers.
So we, so we, so we hear something, read something at our comment to it, post it on a blog, say it,
uh, somewhere in a forum and, uh, and, and so the, the matrix expands by more nodes.
And the red pill, what I'm referring to and what you just heard referred to is, is really about
breaking loose from that. Here's a Brian knows that he said, you got it.
The spectacle sucks us into the matrix of unreality.
We have to choose to wake up and connect with life, to interact meaningfully with others.
We have to work out it.
Deboard also points out the connection between the spectacle and the global economy.
One makes the other possible and necessary.
The way I applaud good intentions, one, oh, so now I go into the life first thing.
I don't want to get into that, uh, because, uh, that would distract me.
That would bring me back to that horrible thing.
So what I liked about this comment is, dude, you completely reciting the lyrics.
There's no semi-hagar, definitely a friend of the show.
In fact, it was semi-hagar who convinced me to take the offer from MTV in 1987 to go work in the
States in New York when he was on my show in Holland.
And I hadn't told anybody that I'd been, uh, been giving this offer.
Because yeah, I was working like I was working on it.
I was, you know, the top post on the, the only music TV show I think at the time that really
mattered, it was, you know, I was riding high, things were fantastic.
It's like dude, you know, what's up with this MTV gig is, is that, uh, is it worth it?
And he said without a doubt, Adam, you should do it, uh, and, you know, you'll, you'll, you'll
kick yourself for the rest of your life if you don't try it out.
And I have to say, I think he was completely right.
And since he is a friend of the show and since I know he'll vouch for me,
dude, let's put some music to those lyrics.
You recited so cleanly from the red album.
Here saving heart!
I've read it, all this black.
Black and white The spectra made a shade I like
The crimson rays are ruby bright
Technic color light
Out of breath, out of breath
There's no sun to come in
Black and white The spectra made a shade I like
You don't know what it does to me
My crimson shinning density
I'm hopped inside the mystery
Oh mystery of breath
Man, not so thin, soft like a hot
My love, got it covered
My drama, got it covered
That's one of the things I like to say
I'm on the bed
Now it's like a bit of hay going on a Thursday.
All right, those of you in the Potsay Police, please don't worry, Sam is going to vouch for
me.
I don't have a prior permission, but I'm sure it'll be okay.
And by the way, I had to buy the entire Red Album to get one track, and Napster wouldn't
let me just download and buy one track.
I had to buy the Album for $9.95, so I invested in this, Red.
And of course, I expect all of you here on the Charlie to absolutely be swallowing the Red
pill.
So this Saturday is it's black, black Saturday.
Mm-hmm.
It's when the copyright royalty board approved vote goes into effects, and all internet
radio on July 15th will have to pay fees for music played by the person.
And this is, so there's a lot of news about it cropping up today.
Jack Myers report, which I read religiously, says this promises to put many broadcasters
from mom and pops to Pandora out of business.
See live 365 of which I'm a card-carrying member.
Let's see what they say.
Hold on.
What are they going to do?
They have no plans to go dark, and they also currently have no plans to pay the increased
fees.
Okay.
We'll see how that works out.
There are a lot of people sending in questions about this.
In fact, here's William Peachman.
If you're listening to your show, via Sirius, my son and I thought that it might be
fun to put together a podcast.
Gee, how many of your fanletters start out that way.
So here you have a mixer, three mics, and this is an extension to our other hobby amateur
radio.
Send me a QSL.
Uh, you can see our little studio on our side, but we can never foresee legislation
such as going to an effect in going into effect here in the U.S. come this Sunday.
I'm sorry.
The 15th of Sunday.
As you know, via the copyright royalty board, we do not understand what happens when
a source from music has via the podcast music network, nor how creative comments works
here in the U.S. are creative comments, agreements, recognized under U.S. law.
Uh, well, I think we've proven that they certainly work under international law.
If we only use music on the podcast music network, what impact does this law have upon us?
Do I have some sort of record keeping burden, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Okay.
So here's the deal.
Um, if you are creating an internet radio stream, then just the fact that you have
the channel, you are obliged by law, so this is like taxes.
You have to pay $500 a year.
This does not count for podcasts.
This is for streaming the streaming version of internet radio.
Um, so you have to do that no matter what no matter what music you play.
In fact, if I was going to overturn anything about the copyright royalty boards, uh,
decision, I would say that would be the thing to overturn.
Take away the $500 minimum payment.
That's horseshit.
Because it states very clearly in this compulsory law, uh,
mandatory, uh, what is the, um, what's the word I'm looking for?
Uh, not compulsory, not mandatory.
Statutory.
There you go.
Woohoo.
Um, which means, uh, guys who one day will have a statue,
erected for them.
For sure you pay this.
You are allowed to play music royalty free if you have a prior arrangement with the artist.
Well, you have exactly that.
If you're a member of the Podsake Music Network, it is a license.
You have to check the boxes.
You have to agree.
It's completely valid.
You have the right to play that and not pay anything.
Now, the record keeping part.
I'm not too sure about, um, the easiest way to do it, of course.
Again, Podsake Music Network, music.pot show.com is to just tick off the box when
you've played the song, which is the agreement in which you are obliged to do by the terms
of the license.
Anyway.
That's your record right there.
And how many people listen?
Well, you know, you guys, you might have to hand over your, your download request if someone
comes asking, but I'm pretty sure all your streams or Harvey, you do that.
But I'm pretty sure that, um, that it's not going to be too tough, uh, to prove what you're
doing.
And, um, you know, it's kind of up to see who's going to be first, who's really going
to go all Podsake and then, uh, and report that as such and say, look, I don't know
you anything else, but my 500 bucks, and that again, really, I think if any bill is going
to be created, that is the thing to overturn, uh, but as far as, um, uh, all legal opinions
I've received, I am not a lawyer, of course, and we're just at the beginning of all the
crap that's about to happen with this, um, uh, I think you're in pretty good shape.
This is only just, you know, there's so much going on right now, uh, you, you've probably
seen that EMI is considering, uh, a bid from a, um, hedge fund for, I think, 2 billion
pounds.
It was like three or four billion dollars from a outrageous amount, and they keep saying,
and look, they have, uh, you know, like Madonna on their label, wow, um, where is the
shoot?
I thought I would save this for sure.
Anyway, you know, Australia, uh, the Australian version of, uh, I guess could be Ask
at BMI and the RIA, it's all kind of the mainstream music industry.
They have decided to raise the rates, uh, for performance rights in bars and clubs, and
I'm talking about significant, uh, rate increase, like 50 cents to three bucks.
So the way they do it, just so you know, this is exactly how the music business works.
If you have a bar, if you have a cafe, if you have a, um, uh, a dance, uh, hall, if you
got a dance, if you've got a dance hall with the lunches, and that's how I'm system.
If you got any of that, you have to pay by the, by the capacity of people that can fit
in there.
Well, of course, you're probably, if you got a, if you got some kind of rave set up,
you know, you're probably not playing anything mainstream, and it's all self-created
beats.
But still, you know, there's, you have to have, you know, all kinds of proof that you're
actually playing the stuff pod safe, and, you know, you have the agreement, so I think
the pod safe music network will help there as well.
Um, and this is what's happening.
And by the way, there are plenty of people in the music industry who really are in it
for the music, and really do love the music and love getting music out to people and just
love music.
And I know lots of people at record companies who, um, who really feel that way, but
this is the work of the lawyers, and they really run the show.
Yeah, geez.
Was it two years ago, Ron and I were at, uh, Sony music, and I reported back that the
carpets are all afraid, and there's only suits walking around with, you know, legal pads
and stuff, because it's become a lawyer business.
So while they're, you know, look, if you have to prop up a two billion pound valuation
in your EMI, well, you better show that you can get that money somehow, and the way you do
it is by raising rates everywhere.
And of course, that will end.
There's going to be a number of people who can continue to pay that, but at a certain
point, we're all just going to snap.
This is what happened with us in independent radio.
We snapped a long time ago when we started the pod safe music network.
That was, for me, that was really, look, fuck it, there's lots of other great songs out
there.
I'm just not interested anymore.
You have a very limited selection mainstream record music industry, guys.
And there's so much more out there, which I love.
I love your stuff, too, but, you know, if you're going to make an impossible, then so
be it.
It's just going to be impossible.
People will snap.
Bars will snap.
It will just become impossible to, to make money.
So either they go out of business, or they switch to an alternative source of music.
And of course, I would recommend the pod safe music network because it has all the shit in
there that we need already.
If the music that you like isn't in there, then help get it in.
Go find some.
Go find your buddies.
Tell them to put their music up.
It's great promotion, and it does move product for the artist.
Unbelievable.
It's so easy for us to walk into this gaping hole that's being left open.
I predict within the next year that will be a chain of some sort.
Some retail chain is going to go completely pod safe.
Easy for me to predict because I'm actually working on that, of course.
Yeah, this is Steve's Sacramento coin.
I got two questions for you.
What ever happened to the format change, you're going to do, like, weekly or daily geeks?
Uh, yeah, it's a vans.
Yes, well, here's what happens.
You know, my life long dream is to just sit here every single day.
And if I had the time, I'd do it seven days a week and just talk crap and play songs
and have fun and noodle back and forth to you guys.
That's what I love doing.
It's what I do best.
It's really what my career has been.
Um, so there's all this other stuff.
You know, in order to enable that, well, we have to have the infrastructure.
We have to have a pod show.
We have to have the pod safe music network.
All of that takes time.
We're working on two continents at the same time.
I'm usually on the phone until 11 or 11 p.m. or midnight because San Francisco is still
in the middle of their day, um, you know, but there's also a whole day over here.
So I get up early and, uh, and get my stuff done.
And somewhere in between all of that, I fit in making the show and really, I just
don't have the production time to pull it all together, um, then I apologize.
It really does suck, but one day, you know, that, that would be my immediate goal
is one day to have this company running so smoothly.
And so well, oil that I can step back from, uh, well, constantly fixing the gears
and and putting in new, uh, new catalysts and then carburetors and fuel injection pieces.
And, you know, and just kick back and do the show.
So I apologize, uh, just hasn't paned out, but also I have to say the savants that we
do have are doing quite a job of keeping the savant quotient high in the program.
Don't mind, as though I like to keep with the original format and then people
going to ask you what happened to, uh, CSP, what happened to that, uh, second life avatar
check.
Can't remember named Brittany, you think?
Thanks, man.
Yeah, you mean, um, Brittany Mason?
That's right, Brittany Mason.
Well, she kind of runs, uh, the pod show island in second life for me.
Um, I do have to reconnect with her.
Uh, while you were saying that, here we go.
This is one, there was one more thing that I wanted to put in check this out.
Hey, Adam, uh, Bob Evans from Birmingham, uh, so your messages are coming through against
that.
I thought I'd leave another one at the repeat of when I left earlier.
You've been promising a conversation with your Uncle Don and some of which I'm sure was
going to include his thoughts about the original George Bush and the current.
Man, I'd love to hear that interview before George W. Bush leaves office.
So get on it.
Anyway, um, with listening to this show and thought I'd call in, uh, if you're interested
by the way, this is coming in from an iPhone, which, uh, is the same device I was using
worse into the day we source code on.
So I just said, ah, gotta talk to Adam, you get the button on the phone and it stopped
the podcast and now I hit the end call and it'll go back to the podcast.
Yeah, later.
That's beautiful, man.
So it worked.
One device does all you were listening to me and you could use the same device to call
back.
Ah, it's loving that.
Yeah, second week of August, we have a curry family reunion in New York, upstate
and Armank, uh, where Uncle Don lives with Aunt Meg, uh, Aunt Meg is my dad's sister.
And it's going to be the big to do.
It's going to be a boatload of people.
And that is when I'm going to nail down Uncle Don.
We're going to do a nice, long sit down chat.
I hope to be able to do enough for two or three episodes.
And I think, uh, I think it will blow you away when we really get into, uh, and I think
he's going to be pretty darn open, you know, he's, um, he's now 80, I think he's close to
it.
Uh, and the guy is still just, you know, in New York every day and he's, you know, saving
the world.
It reminds me, of course, a lot of my grandfather, my grandfather was at his Remington
typewriter, you know, banging out letters to his congressman every single day and night.
Uncle Don was in the midst of it all, uh, and the midst of the Bush administration.
And, uh, had some very poignant views on the, uh, the current Bush administration.
So, uh, yeah, you can count on it for sure.
Adam, hello.
This is a bit of a sound scene tour.
I'm on Shostown, we have a UW-1.
Shostown, we have a new W1 in the heart of London.
So, hope.
I'm sitting outside and laying his arm with the, uh, terrible.
You mean, lemme's rabble.
Terrible production has been going for too many years.
It's all of your lovely, uh, Americans' factories seem to adore so much.
I guess because it has a, uh, post-face, little girl on fun.
Anyway, hey, yeah, that's a sound of, uh, back all the past nine in the morning and
the half past, can't remember.
I just want to say, um, Shostown, you're always on the money, uh, really enjoy listening
to the CSB, uh, comments, um, and in contrast to that, as Adam said,
you can try to review from, uh,
what's his face?
No, I don't.
Oh, I really enjoy listening to him too.
I don't know if I'm going to get so well now, up by him.
What's your problem, guys?
Back out, chill.
Um, and the issue of, uh, Americans being ignorant and, um, what have you that, uh,
that, uh, prolific programmer, sorts of that.
Um, I think you're being a bit ignorant yourself.
Okay, you can't judge a nation on one or two people.
Um, and, um, and what I'd say to come to Shostown is, uh,
and I'm going to post a program and say you're a great guy, but he doesn't,
but he can get in.
All right.
You kind of lost it there at the end, but I understood what you were saying.
Yeah.
I thank you very much.
I was waiting for someone to call it and say they actually are a fan of Nylon because, uh,
uh, you're right.
Contrarian views are extremely important to me.
Um, it's, uh, it is, you know, if you want to feed me the machine, then you got to say something
completely the opposite to what I'm thinking.
Hello.
He's Nylon.
I'll spoken to Beatriz.
He's in London, but he's from New York.
Whoa.
He's Nylon.
Contrarian views.
He's in London, but he's from New York.
Come on in Nylon.
Hey, Adam.
It's the Nylon.
Whew.
After a week of battering, um,
I'm still standing.
But here's my points today.
Um, a lot of personal comments and very little discussion and dialogue on the issues.
Let me get to a couple of things.
No.
Nylon.
Welcome to show business, my friend.
Of course, no one's ever going to address the issues.
It's all about the spectacle.
Not an actor.
I'm not on the part show payroll.
I'm a successful executive with a successful,
working for a successful company living in a wealthy suburb just like Adam.
Okay.
Dude.
I appreciate it.
Just for once the next time you call in,
if you tell us what you do.
Um, so that's me.
Now for about 8,000 of you who attend to have a lot of comments about me.
I would like you to also have a full disclosure when you call,
particularly when you criticize me,
others or actually support Adam.
And therefore, I would like you to say also,
um, to let us know if you have any professional,
contractual or financial interest in the part show.
Dude.
You're so misguided.
Nylon.
I wish.
I wish I had the whole company listening to this show.
You know, hard it is to get the people in the company to listen to this program.
Let alone call in.
No.
I can tell you right now.
Not a single person who's ever said anything about you on this program.
Has any financial business,
professional, etc.
relationship with Pod Show with me or this program.
But that sort of disclaimer you would have in any other arena when you're making comments.
If you do have any sort of affiliation with Pod Show,
give us a chance to then understand if you buy it or there's a self-interest involved in your comments.
Now, about the comments.
If you think I'm an asshole because I'm discussing product push versus marketing lead strategies.
Well, then you've already never worked in any major company because every company deals with that.
So tell me why that's an unreasonable perception.
Let's talk about that issue.
If you think I'm unreasonable for thinking that hiring a print journalist who hasn't like any invention in the last five years.
Okay. Now, I'm just going to jump in here.
Nylon, you're doing okay.
But then you say such blatant things about John C. DeVorac.
I think you should back that up because DeVorac.
Let me just give you one thing.
The reason why I really want to DeVorac is cranky geeks.
When I saw cranky geeks and we've got a show for you, man.
You have no idea what we're putting together.
It's going to be awesome.
He brings credibility.
I don't have to explain that.
He doesn't have to be innovative.
He just has to go with the flow.
For him, for him just going with the flow is innovation.
And he's fine with that.
So it's not, it's not about, you know, any innovative.
He's been a print journalist for 25 years.
He's also been around the block.
He's seen the hype.
He knows how to dissect it.
And he's still here.
Kapish.
To transform a technology channel.
Is it unreasonable perception?
Please talk to me about that.
And also tell me how many times you've downloaded tech files.
And if you think the commercialization of Trinity is a ridiculous observation,
can be my ride.
Well, let's talk about that eight months on.
And I'm still waiting for the announcement six weeks ago.
You promised to add them.
Yep.
So anyway, I recognize your entourage.
I believe you have a new Ron Hubbard of the new wave, new media world.
Let's just understand.
I'm a listener.
I'm a listener who disagrees sometimes.
It's probably makes me, among the most engaged listeners.
Yes.
But just because I'm a listener doesn't mean I don't circulate.
Right, nylon.
nylon.
nylon, dude.
I love you.
Of course you don't have to drink the cool light.
And please, let's take a contrarian view to something new.
Okay.
Let's get off the Devorex subject and let's move on.
Let's have a word with the nylon.
Spreading the news with the smile on where the roll is right.
Ringo for light.
Let's listen for a while.
And the nylon.
Let's one, two, one, six, two, five.
Six, three, five, seven.
So if you've got yourself a cell phone, put that number in.
And whenever you want to say something, the minute you hear it on the show,
you can pick up the cell phone.
It may even be the same device you're using to listen to the show,
i.e. an iPhone, or even the Nokia's can do that.
And call me, please.
Hi, Adam.
It's DJ.
You've gone point users at org.
As usual, in traffic.
And I was listening to your daily source code.
So if it's as usual in traffic, then you must be from Holland, dude.
Subscribe on the N800.
And I figured out myself last week that when you crank up the main volume
on the internet tablet.
And then crank up the volume in Skype.
It gets a lot better.
It seems that the two volume slides are not hooked up together
for some reason or the other.
Yeah, I noticed that as well.
You know, a lot of people have been calling in about,
about me talking about Skype on the N800.
So that might help.
Something else.
You should definitely get yourself a contract with notes.
Because, uh, stupid me.
I've got an E60 online now on the way.
So I've played with that later on as well.
And something you want to check out for that maybe is true phone.
Tango, Romeo, Uniform, phone.com.
And these guys basically give you a voice or write the application within your Nokia
that allows you to receive calls and make calls when you're on Wi-Fi.
But when you're not on Wi-Fi, the mobile number you get from them gets forward
to your real mobile number.
So you have just one number and they either forward it straight onto Wi-Fi
when you're on Wi-Fi or onto your phone when you're not on Wi-Fi.
We're checking out at least.
Yeah.
That's it.
All right.
Yeah, so a lot of people said, dude, you know, this is pretty cool.
We've only heard a little bit about Skype on the N800.
And I have to say it's really completed the box for me.
Now, of course, I had Gizmo, which gives you voice over IP.
But really, and this is just a cultural thing.
My and really pod shows entire IAM architecture is Skype.
So we use it for instant message.
We use it for conference calls.
We use it for video conference calls.
We use it for a lot of different things.
So I'll excuse me.
It's a live.
It went down the wrong pipe.
So I really, I've really been waiting for this.
And I'm surprised that there hasn't been a number of articles.
You know, out now, basically comparing the iPhone to the N800.
Because I feel there are comparisons.
Yeah, just take out the cellular network phone part for a second if you don't mind.
And just look at it as an internet tablet.
The iPhone is a fantastic internet tablet.
And of course, it has the iPod in it and it's interface,
which has a lot of advantages for first-time users.
And for people who just want to have music on the go.
And it's a beautiful interface.
And not that I have one yet to be able to actually compare it with anything else.
It's coming Wednesday.
But you know, some people actually said, why don't you demonstrate the Skype on the
on the N800?
Nothing has a pretty good idea.
Actually, I'm taking one of my jacks.
I'm going to put it into, there we go.
It's now in the N800.
And oh, by the way, the jack, any headphone jack goes in the N800.
You don't have to have some kind of special thing from Apple in order for that to work.
So they have their own headphones with microphone built in.
So it's a three-prong works beautifully.
But it also works just fine with a regular headphone jack as I'm about to demonstrate.
So let me, I'm going to bring up the dialing interface.
Okay.
And I'm going to call my cell phone.
Hold on.
Okay.
You can actually hear it.
Can't you?
Luckily, it's not the actual tone.
So you don't get my cell phone number.
Okay.
Let's hit call.
And let's just see how that works.
So the volume is always at 80% by default.
I like to crank that up a little bit.
Let's see.
Okay.
Volume's up.
It's, it says it's dialing.
There we go.
There's my cell phone.
So you can hear it sounds like it's real, doesn't it?
Okay.
I'll answer.
All right.
Hello.
Let's see.
How should I do it?
I'll mute the, yeah, any 100.
So I'm talking to my, I'm talking to my,
61.
Sounds pretty good.
Doesn't it?
And I'll mute that one.
And I'll unmute the tablet.
I'll put the E61i up to the microphone.
Can you hear it?
So it sounds pretty good.
Doesn't it?
It just works, man.
I've been using this for our conference calls, which is an 800 number.
So that's completely free.
Loving it.
Oops.
Let me just put that back in there.
Okay.
In fact, I think,
Nokia, Nokia is,
I guess what Nokia should do.
If I was Nokia.
I would say,
who needs the iPhone when you can have the guy phone?
This is without a doubt a guy phone,
because we don't need no stank and 3G crap.
Two and a half G, actually.
Edge.
No, no, no, no.
Now, we've got the guy phone, man.
We just, we got the clown.
We've got internet access everywhere.
We've got Skype.
So we're completely reachable.
We can be walking around.
Listen to tunes.
Watch and video.
Have Skype interrupt us.
Yes.
The guy phone is for you.
Hey, Adam.
It's Father Roderick aka the Catholic Insider.
You know,
you're shove it down to throat strategy for the pot show channels.
Really works.
At least for me.
I had to try it out.
So I said down.
And in only 10 minutes was able to create two channels.
One for all the podcast that have to do with the world that
Tolkien created the Lord of the Rings universe.
And then I created a second one,
encouraged by my success on the first one.
And that is a Harry Potter channel with the best Harry Potter podcast
out there.
And this week is very important for Harry Potter fans.
There's a new movie.
We're all waiting also for the final book in the whole saga.
So it's very cool to be able to bring together to create a mashup of all those podcasts
and easily transfer to iTunes.
That's for me, the coolest feature.
Now here's my question.
How do I publish the link to those channels?
I'd like to put them on my website.
I'd like to distribute them in blogs.
But how do I do that?
I just couldn't figure it out.
Perhaps you can help me.
Absolutely my friend.
So I already posted this at curry.com.
And thank you, Father Roderick, for jumping on board with us.
It's funny because yesterday we were in one of our big off-site meetings.
And I was, this is the one I was in the car on the phone.
And we said, you know, look, we've got this two-to-fronts channel.
People are catching on.
And then I think Ron said, well, how about a Harry Potter channel?
You know, this is the biggest thing coming out.
You know, it's surely we've heard of the book in the movie.
And boom, the next day there's Father Roderick with a Harry Potter channel.
So I posted the RSS and the iTunes links at curry.com.
So the whole problem with what you're witnessing, Father,
Beloved Father, is that we don't have the,
you know, we don't have that piece deployed yet.
The piece that is known as cheddar, cheddar has two very important parts.
So one is the ability to edit your channels with much more complexity
and much more power than you're able to do now.
The other is there's actually going to be a drop-down box on each channel that says,
play it in the dashboard, click.
You play it in the dashboard.
Play it in real player, play it in Windows Media Player, put it on your iPod.
And this could be a box that could also say put it on your Nokia,
although Nokia doesn't have a spiffy iTunes link the way iTunes has with ITPC.
You'll also be able to get this channel.
Now, that functionality isn't, I haven't seen that work yet,
but we're going to get to that as we go along with these cheddar updates.
So tomorrow I believe we'll be pushing this live and you'll be able to expose that.
So people, you know, so you'll be able to find the links yourself.
People who just come to your channel will be able to find those links.
And we'll be able to just put it on the iPod.
But even better, you'll be able to determine if you look at, you know,
if you, and of course, I put it in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
If you look at Father's Father Rodrigues Harry Potter, Lord of the Ring Channel,
you'll see that there's a whole bunch of episodes in there.
You'll have control over the order in which the episodes come out.
And as John Walker says here, Adam, you've got the interest did.
I started messing with the channels.
Looks like a pretty neat feature question.
Is it possible to filter a show that you've set up in a channel,
so that you can block stuff from that show's feed from coming into the channel,
based on keywords such as a title?
For example, say I want to set up a channel of Mark Yoshimode,
an MCOF stuff except I don't want to see dire of a madman.
Well, he typically dumps everything into into the PCH feed.
I don't like everything Mark does except
a dire madman in my, the hell.
Anyway, so I understand your question.
That will not be available when we deploy tomorrow.
However, if Mark were to create a channel, and this is really the way he should be doing it,
instead of dumping everything into his PCH feed,
he'll create a channel which is a collection of all the stuff he does.
So if you look at that channel, it'll have Pacific Coast Hellway.
It'll have number one with a bullet.
It'll have dire of a madman.
It'll have the badlands.
And if you don't like one of those shows,
you'll be able to suppress one of those individual shows in the channel.
So that is kind of how it should work.
Looking forward a little bit,
and we discussed this yesterday as well on our offsite,
you'll have a search capability where the results of the search can be,
a show.
So whenever that search will run continuously and whenever it hits against your keywords,
or negative keywords, I guess that's also possible.
So I want this and this, but not that.
It will then pop in the episode that's relevant right into your channel.
Oh man, it's going to be so exciting.
I got a lot of work to do today because deploying this is very, very scary stuff.
We don't want to do as mess up the work you've done on your channels already.
Yet I would like to give you the capability to edit the channels you have now,
to reflect the behavior that you can now put into it,
such as order and number of episodes coming in from show containers.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
Oh man, it's been a long one.
What happens when we get busy, eh?
Fifty minutes already?
Well, we can tack on another three and a half.
Because it's a rave dive.
It's always, it's rave dive.
It is.
Hey.
It's rave dive.
So where is this place, anyone?
Well, it's in a circular motion.
You just got to ring this number.
Right.
It's going to be there.
Right on, aren't you?
So what's it all about then?
It's a rave dive.
It's rave dive.
It's just as if people were to move.
Spreading laugh and listening to shows.
It's rave dive.
So what's going to do then?
It just has a lot of fun.
Stand around.
On the head right up and down.
Stop your face upon the ground.
To the camera.
To the side.
To the hand.
To the camera.
And my friend will such you out.
That's what brings him roll about.
They dive.
See that bird.
I wear that.
Be shaped.
Propynise.
Definitely once it's over.
I'm going to dive, Dive.
Which will make my dive dive.
Dive.
Life, it was my life, I'm feeling strange, yeah we're having sex around time, it's right
time, it's right time, it's right time, it's right time, just as a people in a room, spreading
life, listening to church, it's right time, so what do I have to do? Just have a lot of them stand around,
what they hate, round up and down, it's not your fate upon the ground, it's you who can't
jump as it sounds, you throw your hands up in the air, and maybe give a little shake, go to the
bar, and get a bit, go speak to that, who's over there, and then my brain will search you out,
because that's what brings you to the ball,
can chill out here all night,
one stop until it's life,
lala la la la la la la la
Come on inside, let's go and write, all of these interesting things come on now,
oh god it working morning, eeeit's going on. Oh yeah we care, yeah, what have we
Yeah, what a knife.
I could so see this being the summer hit of 2007.
I just blasted out of stickers and trailer parks everywhere.
I have a diet holiday camps.
It's a rape-dave potsafe.
You'll find the link to the page
of the Potsafe Music Network at dailysourcecode.com.
Tomorrow, Fubar Friday, it's going to be a great one.
Get your songs in, get them in Swift and early, please,
because they're already stacking up,
and I want to play as much as possible.
Adam and Potsafe.com, if you want to send me anything,
data source code that can for the comments and I'll see you tomorrow.
It'll be Fubar. Bye, everybody.
Another Potsafe podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best and the brightest.
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content,
delivering Potsafe and limelight.