This podcast is brought to you by Pawn Show and GoGay.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Log it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
You need hard press to find two bigger gentlemen that cover Ville's Brian Emmett and Zedcast Bruce Murray.
So you think you can beat me?
Well of course.
Me, I think not so much.
I believe.
After teen crumpets of course.
Shall we have a go?
Quite.
Here, here.
One tram on Fred.
I shall kick your arms.
But get these two on trivia games show.
Bone and watch the fetters fly.
Oh, I think since he was into pain, it's probably dentist.
Let's go with the meta couple.
Oh, that's gonna leave a mark.
Tell you how to pivot on here.
Okay, this for Todd. We're rolling. Go ahead anytime.
Okay.
Where's my drink?
Hello.
Mark.
Adam?
Are you okay?
Mark, I don't feel well.
Do you need to go to the hospital or anything?
No hospital.
I'll just rest on the couch.
Dude, you think you should call a doctor?
No.
It happens all the time.
Hey, is there anything you need a water?
A blanket?
A fat split.
I can't roll you a joint right now.
What are you on anyway?
More fun with the demoral chaser.
Mark, I'm so broke.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
Um, you have a 16 million dollar airplane.
I know.
I just told it for three bags of weed.
What? What the hell are you thinking?
I was so high.
Where are you right now?
I think I'm on the highway.
And I think I smell poop.
Dude, that is foul.
I hope it's not mine.
Come to think if I hope it is mine.
Adam, you got to get home.
Come.
I have no home.
I'm haunted.
This biased.
Leaving like an animal.
The jungle is my home.
But I feel sure the world that I can be it's master.
I shall perfect my own race of podcasts.
A race of atomic superpodcasters.
That's for a comfortable world.
Okay, then.
Good luck with all that.
Hey, listen, before I go,
I want to ask you about the blackberries you were going to get this stuff.
You know, I want to know if I could get a sidekick instead that said
Nemkoff.
Sidekick.
Fuck you.
Nemkoff doesn't deserve the smell.
My shit.
Okay, so blackberry is then.
Well, anyway.
This has been fun.
You know, I got some things to do.
Uh, so I'll catch you later, Adam.
So I'll bring up Nemkoff.
You think it takes talent to do BCH?
No, it's all makeup and cursing.
Count this in a slat.
You're listening to the daily source code with Mark Yoshimoto-Namkoff.
I got it.
Starts like a whirlwind.
Thinking about your girlfriend.
Making lots of time.
And you've been down there.
You've been on a ride a song.
Been working on it long.
And so we get mix it down.
You can't be free.
But then you come to learn from the man.
He was to slap a little steak on your plan.
Just be little words.
Don't you know it to work anymore.
We want it to be like we want it to.
We want it to be like we see.
And you can't lock it down.
You can never put it down.
Shout it out.
It's never music free.
I've got it in my pocket.
I've even went and bought it.
I didn't steal it.
No, I never would.
I said don't make it look like.
Just another crew.
Because I'm doing what you said that I should do.
Oh.
So take a deep breath now my friend.
Take your first step and walk right in.
To 21st century.
Welcome to the way it's going to be.
We want it to live like we want it to.
We want it to.
We want it to live like we see.
That you can't lock it down.
You can never put it down.
Shout it out.
It's never music free.
We like it to see you.
To anything yet,
To anything unless we all stand up.
We want it to die.
And it's not that not as nobody around.
Everybody's not enough.
No.
So take your deep breath now my friend
I'll take you first step and walk right into the 21st century
Welcome to the way it's gonna be
It's the way it's gonna be
We want to tune like we want to
Break it while we want to
Break it up so everyone can see
Let your can't lock it down
If you've never put it down
We shot it out and set the music free
We want to tune like we want to
Break it while we want to
Bring it up so everyone can see
Let your can't lock it down
If you've never put it down
We shot it out and set the music free
Set the music free
Jeff Smith set the music free
The Jeff Smith saying fuck you DRM
I love it and you can get that song at music.podshow.com
Hey everybody welcome to the daily source code episode 5-8-5
And yes it is for 20
You know what that means
You know what that means Mike right
I do know what that means
Actually I'll talk to college
Mike and I we are very glad
To be back in LA
The bangers and mash thing I was confused about how that works
Yeah, I can't tell you why Mike and I had to leave London so quickly
But it involves a duck queen Elizabeth and the jar of gasoline and a spatula
And I think it was a spatula through it over the top
Yeah, that was that was a little too far
Yeah, but I'll tell you that that queen
You you saucy minks you she's a gamer she is and the carpet does match the drapes
So
I mean you know in the living room
You know they're very cultured people
What did what do you think I meant?
Did you think I meant that dirt
No because it doesn't match the because she shapes so it totally doesn't match
That's the spatula it's the spatula exactly so
Who who knew who knew you know you drive on the left hand side the road and you would
Who wow whatever
I don't know but
You know at the airport though when we landed on on our flight
You saw the right who was in first class it was that actor
That the one that you look like she she'll a buff the buff the beef right
Like a buff yeah, yes, yes, he was there and
Yeah, he was he was like hanging out and I got it. He was wearing some really tight pants
And
Go ahead
I was gonna say I was not impressed now. I was not impressed either and and the funny thing is that
I realized that
His name Trent the way you translate isn't she yeah actually is the is um
Well it means oh where where where is
She'll a buff so means is and name actually translates to where's the beef
It's obviously not in his pants, but that's a whole other story exactly so yeah check the flicker pin
Exactly so
You know, I wanted actually I want to read this email right up right off the bat. So Charlie Row
Sent in this one he says I love that the pale wookie
Give you his show while he's on vacation the pale wookie
I just thought and he said I thought I'd give you an update on what's happened since the Christmas contest well, you know
Charles Rivera is the guy that basically won the
You know we put an episode of PCH host an episode
Basically it wasn't really an episode of PCH, but
Get into our time slot on serious be a series DJ for a day and we put it up for auction
All proceeds going to the David Foster Foundation
So we put that up around the holiday season and
Charles A he basically
Charles A rovere I'm wondering why he calls himself Charles A so I'll just come Charlie Row Chuckie Row
So Chuckie Row
one and
you know, he was
We put him up on serious in the serious slot and he said I thought he'd give you an update on what's happened since the Christmas contest
MSB podcast.com is now a multi national multi linguistic phenomenon since I found another MSR and Amsterdam now
It's a podcast now he's a podcaster with MS
Which is to me. I think is pretty amazing because
You know he's got MS. I mean he's got a monkey scrote him and
Not a lot of people can podcast with a monkey scrote him and
It's hard to still that long. Oh wait a second. You know what this is a different MS. I'm sorry. No, no, I'm
I'm thinking of the of Jersey Todd's MS. This is no he's got multiple sclerosis
So he he actually started out with one sclerosis and he invested heavily
In sclerosis and now he's multiple. Yeah, he has he's the Donald Trump of sclerosis now
Wow and so he said
So he's got the MSB podcast.com which is not about MS. He just plays a lot of great tunes and stuff
He says because of the focus of my cast it was possible for me to get her to start her own podcast and for me to provide the wire
I can tell you that's a freaking thrill
You give up control, but you get back so much in return
So I'm Charles A from the MSB podcast.com. So see see how it worked out. That's awesome. I'm so happy
But I see it's touching the masses
Exactly in it again in an appropriate way this time
Exactly, yeah
About fucking time. Well, you know court orders and all that so
But I love the fact that
I don't really care about what happened to his show so much. I just love the fact he caught no
I love the fact they called Adam the pale wookie
That that's pretty good. I love like that. Oh, so I guess I guess if Adam's the pale wookie
That makes me a job of the butt
And that makes you are too dildo
Excellent and let's see that would make let's do jersey tie can be princess lay a burg
And let's see and comic strip blogger is specimen jar jar banks
So there you go
Oh, yes, it's Friday
It certainly is how can you tell?
So it's so speaking of CSB right?
So I yeah, we had that call with CSB
And yeah, yeah, exactly and but what what really happened the true story behind it
It you know, we did it over Skype because God knows where he is
And
Two blocks away, but
So Skype fucking crashed the first time of course like fucking Skype does it just locked up
And uh, it's
I tie it it really it really annoyed me so because we had a great call going
But it it locked up like Mary Kate also in at knife point so but
We we have a transcription because I have the text calculator plug in for Skype
So it transcribed the whole thing I actually have a ticker tape machine that it transcribed it all too
So what I figure we do
Is Mike have you and I we should why don't we reenact?
Okay the conversation
Okay, so
Basically you want to be well how about how about if we since it's gonna be a and a reenactment right?
Why don't you play me?
And I'll be I'll be CSB and you know, well, uh, well, you know
Well basically try to make it seem exactly like it would have been had we recorded that first
ill-fated phone call
Try to figure out how to sound like if I squeeze my nose and say fuck a lot
Perfect you got it
Bingo okay, okay, all right, so okay, so ring ring ring ring and I go hello
Oh, he's this it's Mark you'll show out an app cafe CSB what what the fuck happened hey
Cock suck hair. I told you to call me earlier
And now I am I am too busy beating off. I cannot talk to you. What do you a fuck do you want?
I just have a couple more questions
What what the fuck is your real name?
Mike my real name is Cheryl
But that is not that is not a concern of yours that is no concern of yours
Oh, oh people want a fucking know what your real name is
I just have a couple more questions
What's it like I have fucking sex with your grandparents?
It it is it is all right. There is no shame in having sex with your grandparents
They the grandmother's bosom is warm and soft and smells like soup
So I there is nothing wrong with that
Did you do both of them at the same fucking time?
But maybe maybe I did maybe I did maybe I did it. I have not telling you yes, baby
I guess I did okay, so what oh?
How the fuck are how old are you are your grandparents still alive?
Hey, well, that is not because any concern of yours
Maybe maybe maybe sex with my grandparents involved they shovel in some digging, but that is no concern of yours
Cucksucker mother fucker. I hate you
Well, I I fucking hate you too. Hey, aren't you really for peccipsy to maybe maybe I am oh
I mean maybe I yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, maybe I am
So one one one last question. Is this Kevin Rose? No no comment and
And seen
There you go. I think I nailed you I think you did too. I think that was a perfect imitation of you
I though you meant that way
Well, yeah, I see I still don't know what happened the other night after we went to the pub and had the bangers and mash
So what do you think the spatula came from? Hey, myocard stericons didn't he end it's free by Friday here already and
Well, I was listening to DC 584 and that that was in tents with CSB. I was waiting for
I don't know I don't know he had to get thrown across
I don't know how far away he is from the curry man over there, but
Oh, I was holding my breath at he was nuts, but you know, it was laughing as well
I yeah, I that's my reaction anyway, but
Get it up on the book publishing podshow press that that just sounds wicked
My my god something that I've had you know just sitting around you know tucked away
You know not not how I had him touch that that's that's a comment for another day
But I've had this story called war plan. You know just sitting
On let's spend online, but you know I haven't really talked too much about it until now
You see it's a short story fictional that I wrote a very long time ago, but I decided to you know
Give the podcast novel to go so you know I you know rewrote little bits of it and stuff and made it into like a little short story podcast
This five really short chapters you can find them at warplans.com and
And I've had the idea well say you want to be a writer as you know anyone can pretty much be one
We've podcasting anything like that, but you know it takes a lot of effort to think of ideas and you know
Creating cover art and everything like that so what I thought is everyone can get together as a community and submit ideas
And it can become a fully like ginormous novel like
Scott singular type of novel, you know probably not that big, but
Everyone can combine their ideas and hey don't be like the basically the cover will just be
Tiny little text of every single person's name who's an author on it
So do you think that'll be just an awesome idea just combining everyone's ideas together if you want to
Listen to what it will plan calm, but if you want to send a contribution to one of the chapters or something
Email warpland at gmail.com
I just I just think it's great idea and if anyone yeah go and check it out
Lastly on my other podcast the pod show about nothing Monday world out that was just an awesome day for me
That was just basically speaking to my idol and you know
It's not too often in life you think you get to do that. I mean unless you some years reported you know interview someone
You're telling you been doing this. Yeah, some boring interview
I was on Skype with JC Hutchins the author of seventh son, which is JC Hutchins.net
And I spoke to him, you know for an hour. We'll just chat and think in a crazy ideas of how seven thund can
Is going to become a film and stuff and you know
I don't want to give too much away, but that interview is going to be on the podjab
And I think in the next week or so it's going to put all the it's it's like an hour long
You know, it's going to have to maybe cut it in a bit. So I think I'll just throw the whole thing up there just you know you can listen to
DSC 584 which went for like two hours on a phone call with some Russian
You can listen to it giddy up interview with JC up ease just awesome and you know
I I just can't say enough about him checking out JC Hutchins on it
I'm going to go get food barred right now and I don't know jump in the Pacific Ocean or something like that
I'll catch you later. I don't know if I'm a follower or a follower or a
I'm bringing
From the standard
Just catch you later
This is DJ Raspi from the Brookhaven Chronicles. Hey, this curve from the Brookhaven and creepy sleepy show and we're we are bringing you this special public service announcement
That Friday
Is 420 and you know that we know that people are inevitably going to end up doing drugs on that day
If you do don't be stupid
You know hey do you know you really smart about your drugs now? Do you know what from being on drugs?
You know they're moving Africa to Oliver Australia
I mean I really love that. I love that new move Brookhaven Chronicles
Dr. Creepy Sleepy calm you can come sell on our boat anywhere the Brookhaven Chronicles
You're talking to me and DJ Raspi this curve coming out yet
And we out
No, you know what what it makes to all my listeners. I want to tell you. I want to thank you for all all
Paging into me and paging in the DJ Raspi
The program
Hello Mr. Nemkov this is believe I mean profound program
I was listening to your DSC
I've 82
On bomb hit Tuesday and this has needed by the prospect of smoking catch it
My cat produces an endless supply
So I would probably have enough to sell so I decided to try it right now
I've ground up some really nice cat foods and I have them in my bunk and I'm going to try it right now. Hold on
I
One oh two listeners both of you. Yeah, well, you know what you're gonna have to go download the rest of this show
at daily source code dot pod show dot com because this window
This opaque serious window is about to close so how's that so how's that for you that you're missing out
But we'll get you later
Yes, but by now
Okay, anyway
Now we can get to the real show
You know every week every week I get two emails from the same two guys in Ohio that listen to my series show
I love that
I think there's the only two they work in a they they work in a bakery or something
No, what I'm a long haul trucker and the other ones a security or figures exactly
Yeah
Love that every week that I get two letters nice
I got I got an email actually from a Jeff uh Chikoney
Jeff Chikoney who uh or maybe it's Chikone
Jeff Chikone who said he said CSP is a fucking idiot
No, but he but he qualifies it. He doesn't just make a you know
Right, he says he says
To ask you why you say fuck all the time and not realize that is because you're from Philly
Makes him a fucking idiot
Wait wait wait wait. Do people in Philly say fuck all the time you think so
What you do
So he said loves that love the show uh keep it up
Jeff from Philly. Thank you Jeff. So
But I love that and I got this email. I got a bunch of great emails. Let me just read a call a couple of these
Mostly because we have to fill time. No, I'm just kidding. We got this email from
Says deer Narcassie Mofo Dumbkov on behalf of both of
On behalf of both well-adjusted heterosexual listeners of the daily daily cold sore. I would like to bestow upon you the anal
yearly Don I'm a sword for pubic service
It's only because of your tiresome efforts that we who assume and spit out the RIA laden
The RIA laden come can be fried my head is off to you from the bottom of my bottom
Long may you rain long may your rain be in your hands keep the stiff in your upper lip
Sign Eve Kersky I'm Siberia Russia
Yes, my friends Veta is shaved, but she does not have razor burn
Do you think she uses American mock three razor?
We want you to come see who I'm to Siberia this winter to put the the goo in our log
for
Gulag are you man enough to do this thing?
I am supplying picture of me in Prague so that you can see Eastern European men are not interested in having me
We are having so many women who need to have a big bottom boom that is why we
Always like men from the United States we have so many orgasms that go on fulfilled
Thank you. Thank you. Eve
Kersky, so so we're going to progress. I guess we're going to Prague
I'm thinking that's CSB's cousin so
Maybe or Simon's twin possibly
And let's see here we go Andrew heron writes in
Love what you've been doing with the hijack DSC. I only listen to 583 because I didn't get to download it before the server move
I couldn't pick your previous fake savants, but the prolific promo
Another note you might oh, I managed shadow falls bubble. Okay. No, I'll actually I'm going to write to Andy back because there's some stuff in here
Some personal stuff just me and Andy
They talked about some stuff that I know the rest of the DSC listeners don't want to hear this point
But he's talking about the you know shadow falls number one with a bullet and God forbid
I should you know plug my shows any more than I do, but you know
So according to CSB
Why do you plug your shows? Why do you plug everybody shows?
Maybe because I want people listen. Okay. I don't know I don't know tired of my dog and I sitting here listening
What exactly so anyway, but thank you. I Andrew. I appreciate that and
I got to tell you that was a thrilling email. I'm sorry. Yeah, I see I should screen this stuff before
All right, there that's well, you know like I got it
It's probable it sounds like mice oh my god
Bite me FCC dot com
That's right. You see radio positive. That's right
So it's it's probably about is well, you know what's what's even more interesting is that in the mail yesterday
I open up my mailbox and along with all the crap that's there and you know credit card solicitations
I got a piece of someone else's mail
And yeah, this is almost like I couldn't believe it because you know
I've gotten mail before for you know people across the street or whatever
This is literally a piece of mail for someone who who lives
Maybe six or seven blocks away and
They have the same house number, but it's a different street
But what makes this piece of mail so interesting is that it's the
Newsletter
For the national right to life foundation the April
And I was like oh
Thank you god
And on the cover is the national right to life convention for
2007 in Kansas City June 14 16 so pack your bag like
Oh, man, we're going so you can do some live in
Or semi-life oh my god, so it's like you know and it's amazing because
It's like you look at the sensationalistic nature of the way they cover their quote stories in here
You know and it's like a
President and congressional democratic leaders face off on embryo killing research
That's the headline on the front page, you know, it's like they have to use like embryo killing and
It's just that's a good term and
And you know there's an interview with bioethicist
Wesley J Smith
You know and it's just like
See the sad things that they probably know who that is yeah, and that that's the thing is tough means well he's a bioethicist
You know what is that exactly that's that's a fucking made up word, you know
Much like podcasting so it's
Kind of you know and then and it's just it's amazing to me
I haven't really looked through it yet because I'm afraid to touch it
But it's
It seems to me ironic this shows up in my mailbox the very same day that
The I don't I don't know if maybe my postman's a PCH listener DS elistner, but
entirely possible I guess but the very same day that the US Supreme Court issues a ban
Unpartial birth abortion
Now, okay, I'm not gonna claim to know what partial birth abortion is
I'm not sure I want it. Yeah, yeah, it does sound a little a little kind of gooey. Yeah, actually that's
So I was gonna say chunky, but gooey's probably gooey's probably better
And that's the thing, you know, it's like here's here's something that has been legal in this country
I don't know a partial birth abortion is but it's a procedure that's been legal in this country
You know for like 30 years
I get you know what I think the thing is isn't this like the 30th anniversary or roe v Wade or something or 40th or something?
Yeah, it is and so they overturn this procedure and
It just seems to me it's like all all the
Advances that we've made in personal freedoms over the last 40 years from civil rights to you know women getting the right to earn less than men
You know all those freedoms that we've gained in this country
Um
We're about to lose them
Because we have this conservative Supreme Court
You know a spanky in the White House there or Sparky what do you call?
What do I yeah
Spanky so spanky the bush my sister spanky. I'm sorry. I was looking at partial birth
Okay
I'm listening
But you know it would be better if you looked up partial birth abortion with your pants on
It would make me feel a little bit more comfortable
Probably true. So anyway, so spanky, you know a point a bunch of fucking clowns to the Supreme Court
Who you know a bunch of totes and he was gonna appoint this Harry and Myers
To the Supreme Court you remember that whole thing yeah, I do I mean, come on. Here was a woman who's qualifications to be on the Supreme Court
Or that I guess she perfectly fit underneath George Bush's desk
So you know she should be on the on the Supreme Court
Underhead was right and the same thing with the guy that they made chief justice whatever that fucking smiling
Gonzalez, I don't know the chief justice. Yeah, I can't even remember that
Yeah, it doesn't really know he always had that smile on his face like you know, yeah, I'm getting away with this
Yeah, I'm getting away with so it's the same grin the bush monster has yeah exactly like oh, yeah
It's kind of like that can fuse look what I got away exactly. That's exactly the look that's the look that you and I had on the plane
After we ditched the you know the the bloody glove in the spatula
So
Anyway, anyway, okay, you know looking looking at partial birth abortion
It ain't pretty. Yeah, I can't imagine as I can't imagine any abortion procedure is pretty, but but the thing is you know it's like
It's one of those things where it's to me. It's like the issue of flag burning
Now
To me and call me crazy, right?
There if you're in a country that
Professes freedom as the main tenant of its existence
Right there is no greater proof that you have freedom in your country than the ability to criticize your government
Right there's no greater freedom in your country than to basically take the symbol of that country
And the file it right to set it on fire
I'm not saying wipe your ass with the flag
Right, yeah, but but to set the flag on fire to me is almost like yeah, I mean I wouldn't do it
You know
As much as I criticize the government in this country and would probably criticize any government that was there because they you know
All governments do fucked up shit. They all suck, but you know, it's like well, what's what's the saying on UC radio
Pacho suck less more offense
Yeah, so you know we would like to have that happen in Washington, but
Yeah, good luck
But yeah, so to me it's like the same issue, you know, it's kind of like when you start to say well you can't do this
And you can't do that
Then are we really a country based upon freedom or
Convenient freedom, you know, it's like oh well you can do this, but you know this might disturb some people
So you shouldn't do it and you know, well actually make it even worse than shouldn't you can't do it now
Yeah, that's a good term convenient free. Yeah, and and that's what we're turning into because it's a country of convenient freedom
Just because you know somebody's feelings might be hurt
Well the whole thing with flag burning just I mean to pick that issue
I always kind of thought of it as like a three-year-old throwing a tantrum. It's if you pay attention to it
They're gonna keep doing it and it becomes an issue if you just kind of let them do it and ignore it
It'll stop because it doesn't really mean anything. No, it doesn't mean anything and that's that's exactly the point
It's not like somebody is like burning down the flag and the White House
You know, that's what that's wrapping it around a body and then right exactly exactly that's the point if you were wrapping the flag around nuns and orphans and then burning it
Then I have it right exactly so
Especially if the nuns were hot, but that's that's a whole other topic for a different day
But anyway, so anyway, you know, I'm not I'm not gonna pry it on about this, but it's just
Amazing to me the kind of funny stuff that ends up in your mailbox
That that's pretty lucky. It is it was at a total stroke of luck. I couldn't believe it because I said you know what
I can kill 13 minutes a daily source code time
This this is bought me 13 minutes of programming
You know, let me ask you a question about your mailbox. So when you open it, do you open it standing off to the side and kind of covering your face?
You know what I do? I actually have a remote control switch that pops open the front
So I
Send my Layotion house boy out
So open it
I don't know the name of this one because you know they all
They just come out. I don't exactly
And that's M-A-I-L so yeah, yeah, but anyway, so
Yeah
Hey, did you want to a gulfard angle and quick test please
Just a Lewis Carroll the author of Alice in Wonderland is buried in gulfard?
No kidding. I did not know that. Yeah, he actually he actually wrote the book
Alice in Wonderland and looking through through the looking glass while living in gulfard. Wow
Yeah, he's in the Mount Cemetery right there. Wow. Well, let's see. You want to know another question?
Okay, let's see uh this is a this is an important one the gulfard police force has
1,921 officers which is a down 33 officers from last year
Okay
That's what I do here. I find the fact. Wow. Let's see that's interesting. See I wonder how many of those officers actually take the time
To patrol the area around the the glory hole and the wall behind Adam's house
Yeah, I didn't see any
Yeah, well, you know as because I spent so much time staring through the glory hole, but
But anyway, so but I'm I'm glad to be back on your soil. I'm just glad to be home
We'll jet lag, but I'm glad to be home because I was starting to pick up an English accent
You I figured fucking if Madonna can do it. I can yes, so tell you
I hope hip hip in all that jolly good
I've dropped my ages now so everything's like an omen in early and I got to get em now. Oh mow
Yeah, you know mow
So anyway, and so when we landed right
I was actually I've surprised to find out that they voted San Gio off of American Idol
Did you see that? I know it's hard. I'm going to drink
Yeah
I didn't see that and I
I'm actually
Relieved
Because I was tired of hearing about it. Me too. I really was too, but you know, and I love the fact that you know, everybody was claiming
That
San Gio was staying on American Idol because well not everybody, but people were saying that was because of the efforts of a website called vote for the worst
dot com
And they were prodding they were saying vote for San Gio because he sucks and we want to undermine the whole idol thing
Which is what what they claim they did with the fucking gray-haired guy
Oh, yeah, uh the guy looks like he's having a seizure. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it looks like joke cocker young version
Yeah, so I was looking on vote for the worst dot com and
You should see the the hate mail they get it's fucking amazing
You got to go to vote for the worst dot com just to see the hate mail
Yeah, yeah, let me read something this is from the mail bag update
Was this April 10th? I just picked one a random because they're all very similar
This is all sent all in caps, okay?
You know good and trusted come stains you made my favorite go
I guess there's some her favorite go vote up in case in case built like all one word
Your why oh you are two t-o stupid to know which one I mean
Gina glocks and she was by far the best this year how dare you send her away when that pony hawk asshole San Gio stay
I'm reading this verbatim
This is warm other fuckers. I will be contacting my lawyer to sue your ass
Stearns, I guess you means Howard Stern and all the members of your evil cult cult oh with an exclamation point in an eye
That's because it's called I will revenge Gina and you all will be poor living in a cardboard box if box if
Box if San Gio had a brain in his head he would sue you all also for mental stress and slander
See you in court
Dave and the rest of you dogpugs signed
Candence her name is not Candace Candence Candence
So where's she from it doesn't say where she's from and then
And I love the next one. I will indeed yeah exactly and there's another one
This isn't a right website. You should delet d-e-l-e-t this website
I am going to protest to have you delete this website and send it to you. I will get a hundred names on the list and send it
signed l
l-l-e
So I mean
This is what it's come yeah and you know it's amazing because it's obvious these emails are from
you know
Pre-teen girls
The vote for the worst has angered
Pre-teen girls and young teenage girls. I mean obviously the most annoying demographic on the planet as it is
If you if you you know, and now they've got a rally exactly if you've ever been to a movie theater at the same time as pre-teen girls
You know exactly what I'm fucking talking about
yeah, and
So it should be legal to slap pre-teen girls who talk in a movie theater
There really you know we were sitting in a movie a couple weeks ago and these two girls were in front of us text messaging each other during the movie
Yeah, each other
Text messaging each other during so so there you go, so for the right I just wanted to slap the back of their
Don't grab their hello kitty berays and just smack their heads together
Yeah, exactly so so for the rest of you who may not know what it's like to be around American pre-teen girls
This this may give you an example, so so so American pre-teen girls are all up in arms and all pissed off about vote for the worst dot
So well, I'm just glad Sanjay is gone
Really, I mean, I don't watch American idol. I just don't care, but I'm just tired of hearing about him
Yeah, I am too really, but I just I just love the fact that they've angered all these young girls to send these emails
And yeah, well, which is actually
It's not too unlike
Some of the hate mail that we've received over the week
Yeah, doing daily source code. I won't read anything verbatim, but
There was there was one. Oh god. This is a great one. Oh my god. You got to go to um daily source code dot pod show dot com
And some some guy because you can see his picture name
Renee and
Hello in in America Renee is a girls name so
Said basically I love this he he's so pissed he said I have temporarily I've temporarily unsubscribed a daily source code
It's like something like nemcoff sucks and I've temporarily unsubscribed a daily source code
You know, and I will never listen to Pacific coast hell away
And I'm like oh Renee say it eight so please come back come back to PC age
Like this guy ever listened to PC H to begin with
Like this is the kind of like douche bag that we have in our PC H demographic
Our new specs are totally yeah, exactly we have a totally different group of douche bags
It lives into us so
That's too much I was missing a download. Oh my god. So oh, man. So yeah
So yeah, so yeah, so he might maybe he missed a PC H at 583 so I don't know
But yeah
So it's a shame, you know, I think there was a there was a problem with the feed
Actually, you know Adam said there was a I guess was he had a radio user land feed he has like three or four feeds
So it was a problem with a one a one or two of the feeds
Um and I think
One or two of the shows this week. I think 583 didn't get out to I got a bunch of emails from people like the jamcast guy
Said he didn't get 583 or something
You should just put it up on the PC H oh
Fucking fucking great idea gold star for you. You know what I'm gonna I'm gonna put PC H or the NTSC 583
In the PC H feed what yeah, why not exactly so you can get it on iTunes
But we got that and there was like some other thing like of course comic strip blogger was like he was like ragging on you like oh
You're you're your guest to say they are skissing and blah, blah, blah
And then and well, that's me. I mean, yes, exactly yeah
You're the PC H yes, man, so
Exactly
See you just agreed
I did you agreed again
Yes, you keep agreeing with me
I
Then what I love is that
So after comic strip blogger the same thing happened like a couple of days in a row that right after him some other fucking like
some useless cut rag fucking
types in
You know agreeing with the all this socks and all that and I'm like
Guys, this is a fucking podcast
You don't have to listen to it
But I love the fact that this one guy who's like
Digital dildo or something like that whatever is fucking
Handle is on pod show
This is fucking jiz bag. He fucking hated Monday show, right?
But then he also hated like Tuesday or Wednesday show as well and I'm like
That just I love that that he listened to it again because he knew he would hate it
Yeah, I get email like that but see that perfect people bag on me and then they keep listening to the show
What do you do you cannot ask for anything more than that people who listen to you because they hate you?
That's fucking awesome
They get a little gold star when it shows up in my Gmail like god just so I know who they are
Yeah, so a digital digital douche nozzle or whatever you are
Just you know hey just saying hi to you today so anyway
Yes, all right
Um
I think we're done for today. Oh
You know here. I'm gonna do my um, you know a final thought for the week. Oh, yeah
Yeah, so
You know what I need some music. I think you need to like hum or something like that
What do you want? Um, I don't know uh
I'll girl for me. Okay
Me me
My final thought for the week. Oh, you know what you better not that's that's probably not pod safe
Yeah, well, but I'm probably not humming it right. Oh, okay. Yeah, so change it change it around a little bit
So I can home stop foot at one. There you go. Humps um stump foot at one man
Okay, oh, let's see stop foot
Now that won't work. I'll change girlfriend you can you okay
Why not so the final thought for the week
I first of all. I want to thank everybody you hung with the DSE
for this week
Hung being the operative word
I'm so distracted by mics humming, but it's okay
And you know it I got to tell you podcasting is all about choices. It's about making
choices of what you want is your entertainment and whether you listen to something because you love it
Are you hated you're still making a choice and you're saying you know what fuck corporate media?
I want to listen to podcasting and that's to me the most important thing
About what we're doing here in new media. So I just again. I want to say thank you to everybody and
next week
Um it reverts back from the daily cold sword to the daily source code when Adam comes back from his gender reassignment surgery
And um I guess he'll talk to you then
Yeah, I didn't really have anything good. I was just rambling so
But I
I have no idea
It was nice by the way. It was nice. Yeah, thank you. I used to be a jazz singer. So I went to the next shows when the three o'clock
So no, yes
To drink minimum. He shows today
Hey, so happy for 20 everybody smoke him if you got him and
Mike why don't we get out of here with a song and I know
That there's something you want to play today
I do I would love to play come around by moxie sweet
They are a new band out of San Diego. They're album just dropped on on the 15th
And it's just really good stuff really good stuff. I've been playing them a lot lately. They gave me a world exclusive a worldblood
Exclusive for about a month
So I've been playing them a lot, but they're up on the PMN right now. Oh
Very cool. They're there. Yeah, check out moxie moxie. Oh very cool and uh, yeah, so play it come around
You know what we certainly will and actually as as you were talking there
I I was I zoned out because I saw that I got an email from Jerry who he sent me a little um
He sent me something when it insert in the show so Jerry just want to let you know that well
Actually I'm going to insert in the show before I talk about Jerry so it's almost like a day-chavu kind of thing
So anyway, all right, so hey, so this is uh, what's there song again?
Come around
My moxie and you can find it music dot pocho dot com and remember next week
The fun keeps on keep keep on keep keep on keep keep on keep on keep on keep on keep on keep on keep on on
That's yeah, oh god
No more blow no more blow vis from me on the daily source code and
Check out Mike show you see radio pocho head bite me FCC dot com
This is Mark
This might catch you later
You would feel I love the kind of boy
What a girl like me
Never let's do love your words to know the danger you could be
If you come
Wow
We get back I should have seen you again
But then when you were finally
And I know I'll never trust you in the way
But what am I to be?
Because if you come home
Now I won't be here
And if you come home
Now I won't be
And I know I'll never trust you in the way
And if you come home
Now I won't be here
So I'll never trust you in the way
And if you come home
Now I won't be here
Here
Mark
What's going on then?
Ben Patterson here
Yeah, I'm sorry to get you cut off in the last couple episodes
You see when I said I was resisting my captors and dancers
I didn't mean that it relevant to you expect that more
That guy is kind of irrelevant
You wouldn't know where to find a podcast
Actually I was resisting Adam's advantages
You see I guess somebody left the N800 in the closet with him
And he's been calling in
So that was Adam beeping in
I guess he's trying to find people to join him in the closet
I guess he kind of likes it in them
I don't know
That's his business
Anyway
I really enjoyed the comments
By the gentleman Jonathan Billock has following the comment yesterday
A sister of the cultural cool man
As a late great electric lester bang one throughout in
Autotic reactions and coberator done
We're all being sold a culture of cool
Every piece of culture, every piece of art
Any piece any product we buy
We're buying an extension of ourselves
We're expressing ourselves through what we buy
How we dress the culture we create and consume
There's nothing necessarily or inherently wrong with that
But John was dead on with that comment
Especially about independent musicians and making it big
So anyway, I'm going to go before Adam calls again
Don't tell him I don't want to join him in the closet
And Doug Morris
Good luck finding me man
There you are Mark
Hey Mark, it's Noah from Santa Barbara, California
I was just kind of to tell you that I was going to do a source code today
And you're going to do with comic strip blogger
Man that guy's full of fucking shit
Let me tell you, he's asking me questions like
What have you ever created?
Jesus Christ dude
Let me just point out that I've been listening to the data
To specifically grow cell ways
And another one of six or one or nine or something like that
So it was a lot like two years
And they don't need to do my days
All the time, it means the work can be used to school
Fucking love piece of shit
So do stuff out on every day
Number one with the bullet
Fucking awesome
Okay, just in the shot up and I'm glad that I got it at the end
So I didn't have to wait for week to week to download it
Because I was just going crazy
Doomsday club on chapter 11
But I just bought it on Amazon because I can't wait week to week for it
So I'm just going to read from chapter 11 on like eight blocks
Just some great deal on Amazon
And also a bone, so listen to that
I just don't know, I don't want to steal what this guy's talking shit about
He just sounds like a fucking idiot to me
And yeah, so anyways
I like what you do with the daily source code
Really funny
Come back to PC it soon
Yeah, just a lot of shit man
You turn me on the podcast and actually turned on man
I don't mean like sexually but actually sexually from my ears
Yeah, anyways
So yeah, I'm going to keep it up
And when it's done how this shot out to my friend Derek and Minnesota
You got fucking clear
And yeah, he actually told me the other night that he had clay
You know, there was some massive shots and
Ryan C. Crescent has a chance
We're going to clear anyways
Okay
Yeah, I wanted to drop a comment regarding
Yeah, really industry
Good champagne and all the other conglomerate assholes that are
Fucking out what should be a decent industry
But anyways
Yeah, the big champagne stuff
Talk come they don't share the entire research with
Like everybody just approved their flight
And that's just the RIA
Is it only because they're being paid by the RIA
I mean, when somebody drops like 30 bucks to see the entire report
And maybe that wouldn't satisfy people to reduce their number of downloads
Probably not, so I need this to say
You know, where's open disclosure
That's I guess that's really my point
Everybody knows that the whole music industry
It's been, you know, basically ripping off the public
And C.D. sales anyway
And a lot of people don't even remember the fact that the RIA
And the sales are sued by the federal government
For protecting the price gouging that they were doing
Remember when C.D.s were 20 dollars now that they're keen
That's a reason for that
Anyway
I kind of dropped that message
Oh yeah, this is like we're kicking bearer
We're the indigenous people's music podcast
We're at www.native-wezig-podcast.com
Hey, thanks a lot
See you later
Bye
Another pod show podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest served up daily
By the sharpest minds in content delivery
Pot show and lightweight