This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
The show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your fruit-whip log from GoDaddy.
We have some order in the house, please.
Dalman, ladies, please allow the congressmen to finish.
Thank you, Mr. Speaker.
I'll speak briefly after which I will yield the balance in my time to my honorable colleague
from the great state of Nirvana.
After much deliberation, discussion, and debate,
I believe we have crafted a resolution which please is all concerned parties
and have settled on language which is clear, concise and complete
and I now submit for immediate consideration,
cross-resolution Delta Sierra Charlie 677 which in its final form states simply
fuck you at a burry.
Well, the winds have changed to blowing my friend.
It's time to elect a president again.
I'd love a spirited debate, so I'd be ready for a wait.
Let's get at them to get the candidate online.
Come on at them, get the message on the line.
I really want to know what this stand for.
I really want to know what they mean.
Don't you crack the internet and rip it wide open?
Know it's your vote and it's mine.
It'll all be okay.
If I had my say, I'd love at them to get the candidate online.
Come on at them, get run, Paul online.
There's $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm fasting, fasting, fasting, fasting, fasting.
I've read it in the news to dig it.
$6,000 on the way.
I'll take another cut in bed.
I'm here.
Guess I'm just a lucky one, you think.
Well, would you run the road?
Spive on something.
Know now the faster chance is to get to the man.
You're the conscience of a nation.
You're the one nearer girl.
So here's the country man.
I'll rest my glass up to you, your name.
And the world has text us in that.
Set you around that together.
And you know I can't help but now to know everything.
I'm another lifetime, all my way, I've been step by.
You're the conscience of a nation.
You're the one nearer girl.
Me now alone.
Come with me.
Come, Come with me.
Cute and beautiful.
Your one nearer girl.
We're here to the content of the nation, so now I'm in here, here we go.
That's a young America singing to you.
The Alexander the Soul of America from the Podsafe music network.
He's from Texas.
Coincidentally, we'll be talking to a gentleman from Texas in just a few moments.
His daily source code episode number 677, a really important one for me.
Today, we're scheduled to speak with Dr. Ron Paul.
He is the Republican candidate from Texas.
He's a congressman.
He's been a congressman for 10 years, over 10 years.
I believe he's been in politics.
Also a medical doctor.
Everyone likes to always say he's delivered over more than 4,000 babies.
And we're going to talk to him today.
And as places many questions before him,
that have arisen on the daily source code in the past couple of weeks.
Since I discovered Dr. Ron Paul.
And I've got to tell you, I'm not nervous, but I'm kind of anxious because, you know,
politicians, no matter, you know, they're really trained at answering questions.
And always very protective.
So, you know, my strategy for this is first, I'm going to really suck up to him,
although it's meant and hard-filled.
Then I want to get a little background on just a constitution in general, I think.
And then ask a, you know, some questions about the issues that we've been discussing here.
And then, you know, all the other things that actually, you haven't sent me all that many questions I have to say.
Although, a lot of you have requested a discussion specifically about a couple of,
a couple of topics like the second amendment, like Roe versus Wade.
So we'll do that.
And of course, I'll try and ask some personal questions as well.
Try to sneak those in.
So, I want to second.
I'm doing this through Skype.
Patricia's not home.
Christina's not home.
It's three in the afternoon as agreed to the reason I'm saying they're not home.
So they can't be sucking on the bandwidth and make my Skype mess up.
Well, they're watching porn or YouTube video.
So, let's, let's, let's second.
Here we go.
Hello.
Dr. Ron Paul.
It is.
Hi, it's Adam Curry.
Good.
Dr. Ron, first of all, do you mind if I call you Dr. Ron?
Is that okay?
That's fine.
I just run.
Okay.
Well, I kind of like Dr. Ron and sounds.
I just want to give you a little background on myself, my audience before we start,
which is the audience is about 500,000 in size spread across the entire globe.
60% in the United States.
I myself am an American citizen.
I've contributed millions in income tax, corporate tax, capital gains tax,
employ thousands of people, including giving them health and dental care.
I've only lived half of my life in the United States and therefore have a lot of experience with other forms of government.
But most importantly, although I have no party affiliation, I come from a very long history of Republicans.
Many of whom have served in government.
So I know very well what the sacrifices are that that brings.
So to start off, I just want to say very sincerely.
I thank you for your service to the United States.
You are a true patriot.
Anyone who does this is a patriot.
So I want to thank you for that to start off with.
Thank you.
And so in independent media, Dr. Ron, you know, there's no top of the hour, no news.
We have as much time as you have.
We don't have to hurry along.
I want to give you the opportunity to really delve into a lot of questions that my audience is as
bring to the table today through me.
And I personally, I just love you as I see as a man of dichotomy.
And which is really how I was introduced to you and the platform that you stand for and that you represent through the Internet.
Of course, you know, where you have a Republican who's against the war that grabs people's attention.
You know, a medical doctor against centralized health care.
Those things really always grab attention because because you have a platform.
I believe you stand on the platform of the Constitution, right?
Correct.
So what I've noticed is you have this knack of relating every single issue that people are talking about, particularly in these elections.
Back to the Constitution, which actually I've seen in the debates usually goes uncontested, which is pretty interesting.
So I'd just like to take a couple of the top issues that the audience has talked about.
And maybe you could explain your position on each one.
And if possible, take it down to the constitutional level so we can really understand where you're coming from.
Does that make sense?
And and and really and this is this is kind of a really a really weird question.
I believe that there's a huge misconception about the form of government that the United States is based on.
It would be fair to ask you if you could help American to forgotten or have not been educated and certainly residents of other countries to understand the difference between.
The democracy and a republic just so we can set some very basic understanding of how America is supposed to work.
First, the the republic means that things aren't dictated to us by a majority vote.
If you appear democracy is one of the worst types of dictatorships because the majority can rule over the minority.
The majority protects minority rights and you take your government and decentralize it and you have representative governments.
You don't just vote on everything and you don't have arbitrary definition of what rights are all about.
And it's supposed to be held in check with a contract which is the constitution.
And it was designed to establish a republic, not a non a democracy.
Today we we have a democracy where majority dictates against the the minority.
And in the process we have lost a concept of the decentralization of government.
Everything is centralized not only at the Washington level but even at the international level because now we're working on international government through the UN and WTO and the regional type.
And government so it's going in directly opposite direction of what was intended by the founders of this country to establish and the end of constitution they republican form of government.
Did somewhere alone along the way did in the past you know over 200 years did something at high jack how did this happen that that we've gone from this concept which has written down and to be followed to what centralized government large government has become today.
And it was gradual in in cities and it probably started immediately and the debates at the convention the constitution convention really dealt with this you know when you had the Hamiltonians argued for a strong centralized government where Jefferson argued for the decentralized government.
So immediately after they started moving in that direction but it really didn't move dramatically away from the concept of republican republic until the 20th century.
I think in the early part of that that century we changed our foreign policy toward empire rather than just protecting and dealing with our own republic.
We changed our attitude about money.
We changed our attitude about taxes we had income tax imposed on us as well as if they central bank.
And throughout the 20th century it was continuous and in cities and of course we've had a lot of problems since we've had the century perpetual war.
And business cycles that become more.
More rampant all the time and now we're in a midst of a problem dealing with our dollar today.
This is an all consequence of the natural tendency of some people who want to rule over others and also fade into it by a lot of people who like to be taken care of.
And then they become negligent of the principles of the law and the principles of individual liberty.
And we get careless and sometimes the prosperity that comes out of a of a freer society and more republican form of society tends to.
Some people think only about the prosperity and forget about the principles and that's where we are today.
We still have prosperity but it's based on borrowing.
Not on the fact that we're a free people producing a lot of goods and services that the world wants.
So as this was a gradual process over maybe 50, 60 years, maybe 100 years or quite a long time.
But it would seem almost logical that we can't reverse that overnight. I mean, is this something it can even be reversed in a single or or double presidential term.
It's going to be difficult, but the thing you did good on this path and knowing the wrong path is of course not very not a very wise thing to do.
And it is difficult, but if we don't do it, we will have a reversal or something much worse because this is the last little collapse.
And do you think that's imminent within our lifetime the collapse of the system?
I think the foundation is gone, but there's still a lot of facing confidence in the system that really doesn't have a sound foundation.
The world still does a large degree trust the dollar less so every day and of course that's why the dollar is going down.
But if the dollar is rejected and our house comes crashing down, we won't be able to maintain our empire and the welfare system collapses too.
But a lot of people will suffer from it.
But there is a way out of this and it's merely returning to what was originally intended by the Constitution.
It will be the Constitution live within our means, bring our troops home.
And we could reverse it, but it is not easy.
It's so well ingrained in the special interest control of the control of the system because the government controls the wealth through the taxes and through the inflationary process.
And therefore, since they control and have the wealth, everybody has to go to Washington to get their parts either trying to get their part back again or getting to try to get control of it.
And that's what's going on.
That's where all the energy is spent today is trying to recover or steal from the Naples and their neighbor just through the political process.
So when you speak like this, which I think is very eloquent what you just said, do you talk like this at Republican Party gatherings?
Do you even meet with other members of the Republican Party?
And what do you call the power brokers think of this?
So what is the response?
Because it is what the Republican Party should stand for, I believe.
Well, I don't go to any of the major parties and you know, functions, they national party functions.
They probably wouldn't want to hear this message.
I mean, I run as a Republican.
I've been elected as a Republican for 10 times.
I go to a rally, go to rallies in my own district.
And every political talk I ever gave is always the same thing.
And I'm able to get elected and real elected in my own district.
But not many people knew me outside my district up until this campaign.
So it is a bigger testing grounds.
You're able to overcome it in a small district to overcome the status quo of the Republican Party.
But it's a bigger challenge now and it's pretty clear when you see the debates that the other candidates aren't very comfortable with what I'm saying.
Yeah, I think there's a lot of Republicans and most Americans who agree with me.
Let's talk about it.
I do want to come back to that for a second about the party and your affiliation to it.
But I'd like to just go through a couple of the issues that all candidates are talking about.
But yet you have a very different take on them.
If you wouldn't mind, we just go through a couple of them.
And the one that has been big debate on this program with the audience is the second amendment, the right to bear arms.
There's huge misunderstanding of the amendment.
There's all kinds of different interpretations.
And and that is I believe the basis for your willingness to bring back not just troops from Iraq, but troops from all around the world back to the United States.
Could you just delve into that and hopefully as we peel the layers away, we'll get down to the actual amendment itself.
So so we can understand your your take on it.
Yeah, the founders for rather clear in the Constitution not to give the authority the or imply that we have a responsibility to deal with other countries in a military sense or get involved in their internal affairs.
And that's what they preach and that's what they followed.
We don't have a authority to do it and the advice is it doesn't do much good for us to get involved in nation building and policing the world and being involved in their affairs.
And yet that's what we've been doing and that's how we've gotten ourselves in the trouble and that's why we're on the verge of a of a bankruptcy.
But in the same sense, we both have a strong national fence and the founders believe the strongest defense came from the individuals being armed.
And they were very clear about it and the purpose of having individuals being armed was their right to organize locally into malicious for the protection of their community and actually protection against.
We're bearing federal government. It wasn't just to worry about an invasion.
But it was also they went to people to be armed because they knew what it was like under the British that the abuse of the military and the British military was such that they didn't want that to happen to the people again.
So the second amendment was written for that purpose.
And obviously it was in context of a foreign policy that we weren't supposed to have an empire on the world.
So many people will say this amendment is outdated by today's standards. What is your stance on that?
It's probably more important than ever before.
I mean, we're living in dangerous times and with the threat of terrorism.
And that is pretty vague, but people who commit violent acts and these are criminals, these aren't governments that are invading us.
So it becomes a lot different than a military approach.
I don't know if it was like in the Cold War where we were frightened that the Soviets might attack us and maybe even invade and really try to do great harm to us.
That was different than it is today. So terrorism is done by individuals who are distraught and don't have there's anybody's weak people because they don't have a political base and they don't have a military army behind them.
And one of the best things to do is for people who don't properly be able to protect against individuals like that.
So the immediate reaction to something like that is, oh yeah, but not 11 was different. Look at what they did.
But it was the lack of respect for property rights and understanding of property in the lack of respect for the second amendment, which permitted that to happen.
The government was already supposed to protect us from hijackers on airplanes. We weren't to have, the pilots weren't to have guns and you weren't supposed to resist.
And the airlines weren't in charge with the government was in charge and they did, you know, had all the rules and regulations of screening.
So strong emphasis on private property rights and emphasis that individuals can use guns to defend that property which many people do, individuals in most homes in the country.
Most of our chemical plants and manufacturing plants are protected that way. If you have to have an armed car business falling money around, it's you that are responsible and not the government and that's where the greatest safety comes from.
So I think today it's more important than ever to understand this. And if you look at the great harm done in the inner cities, they especially take the guns away from the poor in the inner cities.
And those are the individuals who are most likely to be killed by violence because they don't have a weapon to defend themselves.
So if you had to proper respect for the second amendment, just because you were poor and lived in an inner city, you wouldn't be denied this right to defend yourself if somebody was coming into your home.
So those are mainly external threats. Do you feel that with the state of the union as it is today and being on the verge of being bankrupt as you say?
Is it getting dangerously close to exercising our second amendment rights against internal attacks and mainly against the government?
There are some in this country who believe that and are prepared. I'm not one of them. I'm working hard to try to prevent it. It's conceivable.
So we now have government agents over 100,000 of them actually carry guns.
They can barge into our property and retirement combination now with the authority that they've got and to spoil everything that we do.
Coming to our homes without warrants. I mean, it's a real mess. And if we have a financial crisis and there's a breakdown on the economy, there we're going to have a lot of violence.
People will be a lot less tolerance of the IRS agents and the FDA and everybody else and the A agents and the ATF and when they come around, there's going to be more violence.
I believe I'm working to try to prevent that and devise a transitional system where we don't have to do that, but it's quite possible where it could come.
Let me ask you one other issue. Rovers is weighed, which I think is also grossly misunderstood. It seems that there are a number of rights in discussion here.
One is you're in a relatable right of your own body as with your own right and created by the given to you by the creator as well as a pro choice issue.
That's the pro choice issue and then there's the right to life. It seems very complicated. And in fact, my head is hurting right now just thinking about it.
Particularly you'd be a medical doctor. It seems like you know what you're talking about. Help me through this.
Well, it is one of the more difficult issues because it's unique. If you have a truly libertarian viewpoint about your life and you can run your life as you choose.
This is pretty easy and I sort of take that position and I talk about it all the time.
It's your life. You can take your own decisions. If you want to build your body or your mind or your soul, you do it. But you suffer the consequences. You can come to the government or rob your neighbor to help me out if you messed up.
But all of a sudden this becomes different with pregnancy. So the issue to me isn't privacy at all. I think that's a red hearing.
I think the issue is, is there a live human being that deserves legal protection within the body of another person?
And I've come down on the side of saying yes, there is a legal human being that deserves protection.
And because I'm very much aware of my legal responsibilities as an OB doctor, if I ever get anything to enter the unborn, I can be sued because I've entered a human being.
If there's an accident, you're liable. If there's been a violent crime, you're responsible and can be hauled in the court for killing somebody.
So you've no doubt there's a live human being that has rights and inheritance rights or establish it's time of conception, not at the time of birth, a father of an unborn is still has responsibility through inheritance laws.
Now to that unborn child, if it's a proven child of the individual. So to me, it's absolutely illegal person.
But it's still difficult because there are difficult terms. You know, one day after rape is that the same thing as one day before birth.
And the more difficult these problems are, the smaller units of government I think should deal with it. So therefore I don't want the federal government involved.
And robbers who's weighed happens to be in the trussies ruling, not only because it legalized the killing of any unborn, in any trimester.
And over road, they over road all the state laws and said the state can't do anything to protect.
There was a violation of the concept of the republic and states rights. At the same time, they called as a privacy issue instead of a life issue.
And they made it so much worse. So my goal would be to turn this back to states or get rid of rovers as weighed.
And if there is sometimes a very, very difficult circumstance that the state has to deal with that.
But the Supreme Court literally dictated medical procedures that were different in the first second and the third trimester.
But they actually legalized the killing of a viable unborn in the third trimester. So that's something that we should even, even if somebody endorsed abortion on some sort of
limitations, they should find this a bit support to think that a two or a three or a four pound infant can be literally just destroyed.
And with the argument, it has no right to live.
Well, then let me ask it this way. And I don't think either of us are qualified to discuss the female reproductive system because we don't have one.
So it's, I find it very hard to give an opinion on something. I'm just not schooled on you. Of course, literally our schooled on this.
But as a politician, the right to your own body as a woman, do you not have the right to put in or take out of that body what you want if I want regardless of what it is?
Of course, you have responsibility.
I'm with the exception of right. You have the responsibility of the consequence of having in a course. So therefore that is the decision.
If you care that argument to its logical conclusion, I also think you have the right to your property at home. Your home is your castle.
I don't want any cameras any of that. Nothing in there. You know, some parents might kill their children.
We don't put cameras in there because we don't take away rights of parents because one out of 14 million are billion might kill their child.
We don't remove any their rights. But if we know there's some parents in a home just murdering their children, all of a sudden this becomes very important.
So the sanctity of the home is does not permit the killing of the children.
So I think the analogy is reasonable to say that yes, there is a child. It's in the womb and it deserves some protection.
But to say that it deserves done leads to some very weird things because if a patient comes to me and I'm doing abortions, I can get paid a lot of money to do the abortion right before birth.
But if I do that one minute after birth, I go to prison from murder.
And one time there was a case where the abortions did the abortion, but the baby was born alive, so he drowned the baby.
And he had to go to, he had, I think he was convicted of a crime.
But if he had only killed the baby sooner, that's why this partial birth abortion developed.
Because you didn't ever want the baby to be born alive, then you're a bad guy. But if you can just kill the baby immediately before this, this is not something that should be brushed off easily.
But there, to me, there's one time that I think that it's a strictly immoral issue.
The first, you know, in very, very early pregnancy, you know, it might be five or six days or so.
There's no way you can prove a crime is committed because you can't prove pregnancy by chemically, chemically legally, or by ultrasound.
And one of them may not be pregnant, and so how can you prove a crime was committed?
She takes something to make sure that pregnancy doesn't take.
And then it becomes strictly immoral choice.
And I don't think you can legislate in that region.
But you certainly can think more about what it's like in the third trimester, right before birth, whether or not abortion or done for convenience.
Let me switch gears, Dr. Ron, to two things I just like your input on.
If, if you're elected president or perhaps you're already working on these issues now, global warming, your stance and what you think if anything should be done about it.
Well, I don't have any answers for that. I read everything I can and I'm convinced that if you get close to where everybody knows something is so.
I think there's room for being a contrary and especially in economics and in finances, that's always true.
When everybody knows what's going to happen tomorrow, you can burn.
You can almost bet on it that the general information is wrong.
So I've read that I think it's pretty good stuff on both sides of this argument.
To be concerned at the same time not to be overly concerned and that they're having cycles.
There's no doubt there's been cycles in temperature change and throughout the history of the Earth.
And there's proof of that sometimes the Earth gets cold and sometimes it gets very warm.
But I do think that pollution is a serious problem.
We should not ignore it.
It properly writes approach means that you have no right to prove anybody's error in water and we should be cautious.
I came up with a statistic the other day that I think is interesting.
But if you look, if you were to see a two-emission emissions, you might look at who's doing it.
There are two-emitting countries in the world.
Our Pentagon is 30-fifth in line of all those countries that burn oil.
I think it's supposed to 400,000 barrels of oil a day that our Pentagon burns for something bombs endlessly.
And allowing depleted uranium to be lying around in the various countries.
So that's something I think we could do something about without pretending that if there are some natural weather changes that occur
that changes our temperatures over thousands of years.
I don't think this is a whole lot we can do about that.
And the things that we can do something about that I'm all for.
Excellent.
Are you familiar with the net neutrality issue, Dr. Ron?
Yeah, pretty much, pretty much so.
Not in ultimate details, but just generally so.
Any comment on that?
Well, I'm taking a position on, I'm not for it although a lot of people in the, in the internet industry.
They love what I do except that position because they think that it might hurt the market.
And my argument there is that we don't need government regulate.
If you accept the government regulating in a favorable way on the internet, then you've considered the authority to regulate in a negative way or even even go into taxation.
So it's it's difficult, but I think some of the advantages some of the providers have have become about because of monopolies that they've had in the past.
And I would deal with this in a different way rather than just regulating some protection.
A couple of general questions about your campaign.
The main one being you've, and it's funny because I see mainstream asked this question all the time.
I presume because they know the answer, but there's never any follow up, which is if you're not nominated for the Republican ticket that you will not run as an independent.
Which is correct, I presume.
That's correct.
Why?
Is this like a Ralph Nader situation where it could split the party and the Democrats who win by default?
I haven't thought it through.
It's probably just personal and there's a lot of energy that goes into the essence.
It's not like I haven't tried that before.
You know, I did run as a libertarian, you know, a while back and it's really very tough.
I mean, the whole system is so biased against an individual that's independent or a third party.
Ross Perode did pretty well, but he had spent a lot of money, so unless you have a whole lot of money.
Today, at least there's some recognition that I can get into the debate and I've made inroads this way.
But if I've been doing this outside of major parties, nobody would know my name.
And it's a very, very difficult to do.
It's a difficult and I think that I have to put on my energies into what I'm doing now and there's the possibility that the people really want me to be president.
It's going to come about this way, not by me following up and trying to do it in an alternative way.
The big news about Ron Paul, Congressman Ron Paul, is that the internet has clearly embraced your message, which I think is logical because the internet is basically one big copying propagation machine.
And when you put something on it that catches fire or has legs, it travels very, very quickly.
That can be a funny video of someone shooting a bottle rocket out of his butt or it could be the message of freedom and the constitution.
What are you doing to play into that form of communication?
Because it appears to me that presidential elections, it's still about who can get the most money because that means you can advertise more or more effectively.
Do you see it as two separate places or do you see it as one and as one influence the other and what do you, what is your main strategy for communicating with the constituency through online?
Well, we're doing it all the time and it's almost sometimes at the beginning it was in spite of ourselves because we knew it was important and we hope we could tap into it.
But actually the internet tapped into our campaign once the message got out that I was running and I knew the message that came to us.
We got groups just started growing and now there's over a thousand of them.
So it feeds on itself because they come to us, they volunteer and it ends up they send this money as well.
While we're getting free advertisement and free support over the internet, we also get the funding that will help us do the ordinary campaign through television radio.
That's what we've started to do and we'd like to say that it was all because we were so smart and we were able to harness the internet.
But although we knew the importance of it, I think we were just really astounded and how popular the message would be and how quickly it would spread.
So I was very impressed with this.
May I give you some advice on that point, Dr. Ron?
When you're interviewed and when the mainstream media brings this up because you know it's like the internet phenomenon and your answer is pretty much what you just said is well you know the internet kind of found us.
Could I just make a small recommendation which is it's not lying but it's kind of it's it's a tactic.
Maybe you could consider saying yes we've cracked the code of the internet.
You don't have to explain how but that just will put so much fear in everybody.
That I'm so frightened of you because no one has been able to do that.
Well that's what some of the users you know when we when the when it pulls you know after the debate they think we have cracked the code.
We can we know something they don't know but if it were just money in organization the rest of the characters I'm sure we're doing the same thing.
In the course we haven't done it but I see it's almost like a fun thing to do that would really cause them to get a little bit excited.
Well yeah I mean yet you have to kind of you know play along with the game I think a little bit which brings me to the advertising.
I've actually heard some of your your radio advertising and what was interesting to me is that it was a very different kind of message than what is propagating so quickly on the internet it's very much.
I'm not like this guy I'm not like that candidate I voted this way as opposed to that person sound so incredibly traditional.
Who actually does is your media advisor do you have an advertising agency that buys the the time do you have someone who manages that specifically are you involved in that process.
Well we're all involved I'm very much involved because I've been in this for a long time and I'm always afraid if I just turn it over to a company.
That they would be too conventional and I don't want to lose the message so the last thing I want them to do is to do as they we got a appeal to the Republican base and that means we have to soften your stand on the wall or.
Or stopping your stand of civil liberties I didn't know way that's my trademark and I will not have that so I keep very close tabs on that but we use various people in the if the people in the campaign aren't.
You know that a professional you know political people but there are people who are dedicated for the philosophy and the pandemic experience and they help a whole lot and working on these.
I found that personally I found it's much better when someone else says this guy is great instead of yourself obviously or or kind of like a.
A dark voice announcer guy something else you just might want to consider is there's plenty of people who have I've seen on YouTube alone I've seen probably 10,000 different.
Television or video commercials I've heard tons of audio versions that could easily be used on radio.
I'm just saying you might want to consider listening to some of those messages or have someone see if there's anything that is is usable because that message is sometimes so much stronger than what I've heard from.
From the radio commercials just to just.
Yeah and I think as to our radio commercials our song starting off you know to talk to people who've never heard my name before not to talk to people who know me on the internet and I do watch those.
As in those videos on the internet and some of them are very emotional I think they're very powerful.
But I think as time goes on we'll get close to that.
I like to make one other suggestion that I have a few more minutes I could take a few more questions but I'm going to have to go shortly.
Sure thank you and I really appreciate your time so right now I'll just fire off a few right now there's a major push online for November fifth I don't know if you're familiar with this.
There's a and it's just traveling through the internet you can't start it or stop at these things and the idea is we call it kind of a bum rush the charts it's been done very successfully in mainly with music purchasing and book purchasing.
I believe that everyone's going to start donating on one day specifically to really make a big jump.
I have heard that that is not necessarily endorsed or even desired by your campaign do you want to comment on that.
Well I know about it I hear about it and it certainly wasn't originated in the campaign but I don't know how anybody could want to get too far from you know if somebody wants to raise a lot of money and have a surprise and have a media event that on one particular day that we raise a huge amount of money.
I can't see how anybody with that it's a bad idea.
Excellent.
Two more questions nine eleven conspiracy theories do you buy any of it Dr. Ron.
Not really not the kind that I say well it was all conspired by our government and and that they get it for this purpose of ushering in this war on terrorism not a believe in that.
I believe because it's very very clear evidence that the Neo Conservatives in the way sort of welcome the event because they even wrote about a Pearl Harbor type event that they might be able to use to promote their cause and they and they certainly have.
Where where some of the stuff gets overlapping confused is that I don't think the nine eleven commission investigation was worth a whole lot because I think it was mainly designed to cover up mistakes and endless of government not so much to cover up or hide a conspiracy or a plan to do this.
The whole thing about the government I think that the evidence was there that if we had you know some really sharp people watching what they and the information they accumulated they would have known there was something very big coming on and yet they.
We haven't really arrested or fired or blamed anybody for the toe and that this is allowing nine eleven to attack so I think those are two different issues.
So you're saying possible but definitely not enough information on the table.
Well I don't think there's any information say that the government planned the event what I'm saying is that they had information buried in the accumulation of all these files that they didn't pay enough attention to for instance there was one FBI agent that.
The dozens and dozens of time reported to the series that somebody was trying to fly airplanes that not land them and he was totally ignored.
I don't think they did that.
I think I was in happiness rather than a conspiracy to allow it to happen.
Well Dr. Ron you I've said this before on on my show you you take all of the boxes that I'm looking for I wholeheartedly endorse you and I will be sending you money today to back that up and signing your endorsement form.
I really appreciate what you're doing I'm 43 and I'm tired I can only imagine how tired you are.
It's a very tiring business particularly beyond the spotlight like that and so it's it's greatly appreciated.
The final question I have for you which is extremely important are you a folder or a scruncher.
I'm a folder or a scruncher.
There is a scruncher.
Yes so when you use toilet paper do you fold it or do you scrunch it?
Well I think I think this is getting off of the target a little bit.
Is there a proper way to do it Dr. Ron as a medical doctor?
No I think everybody's independent minded into each zone.
Fantastic.
Dr. Ron any time you want me to help you with the network of independent producers that I can speak to please feel free to give me a call.
I'll be happy to contribute to the calls.
Thank you very much Dr. Ron.
Bye bye.
Who?
Why don't we decompress for a second?
We'll come back and discuss.
Who are you?
I've been waiting for you, and I've seen a massive victory
Are you the best of you ever after all?
But nobody knows you've been waiting for you, baby
All you've been is all the one thing you've missed in my life
From all the way, please
The storming on me, of America
Don't over~)
That's let it back, that's the whole team
You're grown r of death, now you're buildin' us
They're struggling to make people who die
racist, so dare you lest you hear me
I have a home on the Wallmanup spot
Do it on the America
Come on up and let it go
COME ON UP and let it go
Go my shoulder kalk
and stop
Fight your Pat procedure
for you
and fight you
Come on up and let it go
I know ain't enough of mine
Those are not bad, I can't go
To make you laugh
Don't know if you're gonna go
I'm sure that people aren't
That I can't break all new things
I can't go, I can't go, I can't go
Don't know if you're gonna go
Those are not bad, I can't go
I'm sure that people aren't
That I can't go, I can't go
That's the Dingo Brothers
Collectively notice to Dingo Pie
The Dominion of America
Of course, also brought to you from the pod save music network
Links to that song in the show notes a daily source code dot com
So I hope you understood what I was trying to do
It was basically get Dr. Ron on record on the most of the things that we've talked about
I didn't go into real debate
I tried to ask some follow-up questions
We're appropriate but I really wanted him to just speak until he stopped speaking
Which I think we kind of captured
So one thing I know for sure
I have to listen to the interview
Myself in order to even really comment on it
Because I know that there's things I missed and didn't hear
Because I was thinking of the next question
That's always a bit challenging
Again, this was what a great pleasure
To be able to do this and really have a conversation
Not be hassled by a producer telling me to stop
Ooming and I just get on with the next question
So we talked about second amendment
His answer I think was he's really trying to stop
The potential bloodshed
That was interesting
Rovers is weighed
Early termination would be a moral issue
Since the crime cannot be proven
Wow strong language there
And I just jotted down some notes here
He felt there was room for a contrarian view
He's concerned we should be concerned
But not overly
Net neutrality didn't sound like he really knew that much about it
But he has a pretty clear stance on
The fact that any regulation of the internet
is not a good thing and he does
It sounded like he has some form of a plan
It's to how he would attack that
Particularly the telcos and the monopolies
Which I think is very encouraging
And then if he's not on the Republican ticket
Then he won't run it all
And when I asked why
I think he said I don't know
Although he said personal too much energy
He's tried it before
I was quite interesting to hear
It's like wow
Someone would actually give up
But I can understand
Hey did I get him to laugh
Like almost like a high school girl
About cracking the code
I really hope he does that
Wouldn't that be funny?
Actually he said he said it would be fun
He said yeah we've cracked the code of the internet
Let's see if that turns up somewhere
We talked about the advertising
He met some valid points there
And maybe I just gave him an idea
That he could use some alternative creative work
Maybe I should have mentioned creative work
I was hard
November 5th
That's what I'm going to
So I endorse that idea
Now that I'm going to
To give it what I think the maximum of
$2,300
I'm going to do it on November 5th
And I think it's a good idea
That'll be fun
Let's see if we can make the needle move on that one
9, 11
I thought he said something
I wrote this down that the new conservatives
In a way
Welcome the event
Wow strong mojo there
And of course huge disappointment at the end
Where he would not devolve whether he is a scruncher
Or a folder
But apparently he makes no difference
Because you can do with your body
What you wish
Okay, homework once again
If you haven't seen the constitution classes
Do yourself a favor and check that out
Because if you didn't already
Get a better understanding of this presidential candidate
You probably will
By going through that
And it's important
If you've got Americans in your life or in your country
Then you should know what they stand for
And what the rules are
Anyway thanks to the campaign
The hundreds and the thousands of people
Who helped and put this together
And I look forward to your feedback
And I'm sure this conversation will continue
What do we say we meet here for Fubar?
Deal
Hey enjoy your freedom
Live life with passion
Another pod show pod guest
Stick it in your ear
The best and the brightest served of daily
By the sharpest minds in content delivery
The best show and live life