Hey home fries, it's CC Chapman from accident hash, encouraging you to check out
botod.tv slash battle.
It's one of the coolest battle events out there and you can only find it at botod.tv.
Let's see if I can fix Adam not doing daily source codes on Friday for Fubar.
Hmm, I'll hack into curry.com.
Password Patricia is hot, okay.
And let's find the code for Fubar Friday.
Alright, and we'll edit it to make it when Fubar equals bar and results to day of week equals Friday.
Then do show equals true.
Alright, that should have fixed it.
Now we're looking forward to the DSC 649 on Fubar Friday.
It was $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking friends in it.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Fantastic, this battle curry.
Well, it's Ubar Friday and what could be more Fubar than having Matthew we will say.
Pete, put your pants back on. This is the daily source code 649.
You're a birding man, Adam.
You're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a bird
you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a bird, you're a birding man, you're a bird, you're an you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding man, you're a birding
Don't do it, when you want to say it to it
Lay it up to the moon, lay it right up on their hands
And do it, come on
I'm just it wasn't easy
Chained in rock and roll with my hands
The paper can shake in
I thought I'd have to leave it behind
Oh, I know it's so much better, it's so much better
I'm from getting out and get out of your way
But I'm not all loose at feeling
You know I won't
I've held all the money so many years
When they were best of us and you
And we went to the moon and just wait
We didn't make up some part of turn around
We went to the moon and just wait
We lied so don't do it, when it wanted to It
We lied so don't do it, when it wanted to
Come!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Show me your way to the secrets Oh, up your soul
Show me your way to your deepest Tell me the secrets of your soul
Show me your way to the secrets Oh, I really want to know your heart
Really want to know your soul And that's what I've been living for and now
Tell me what you think of me Kissing up me thinly
I don't know what I would do without you without you
Gotta know your soul Show me your way to your deepest Tell me the secrets of your soul
Show me your way to the secrets Oh, up your soul Show me your way to your deepest
Tell me the secrets of your soul Show me your way to the secrets Oh, up your soul
Never gonna make your heart Never gonna hurt your soul
But let me in and hold me back and now Show me what's inside of you
What you want me to do Don't ever wanna live without you
Gotta know your soul Show me your way to your deepest Tell me the secrets of your soul
Show me your way to the secrets Oh, up your soul
Show me your way to your deepest Tell me the secrets of your soul
Show me the way to the secrets Oh, up your soul Show me your way to your deepest
Show me your way to the secret
Once again attract from the 99 entertainment hitmakers in Switzerland
I've been waiting for them to put some new stuff on the podcast
Music Network and they have come through
Girl stuff is back
You're secret
I love it
I don't know, it's a screw the spice girl's man
It'd be girl stuff
And where can I find pictures of them?
And yes, you know what kind of pictures I'm talking about
It's right everybody that could only mean one thing
Yon Polat in the house
Oh my god, you're casting with Adam
Hey Adam, are you ready to be stumps
Because he used the human characters with Yon Polat
Hey Adam, how are you doing?
This is hit us number 82
And it's the first one after all the stuff happening here
After a moving to a rice bike
And after the miscarriage
The day after I moved
So we were in the middle of all sorts of boxes
And we couldn't find anything
And then the tragedy happened
I must tell you that the amount of messages of sympathy
And stuff like that really supported us a lot
And helped us cope with that situation
Well things are getting better every day
So I want to thank everyone who
Well, send us a message or call us up
Or left a comment on the website
Thank you very much
It was really overwhelming but really hard warming
So thanks again
All righty to hit us
Here we go again with three intros
And this is number one
It sounds like
I have no idea
It sounds a little bit like Billy Joel teller about it
I don't think that's number two
Yeah, I know this one
That's a whole young every time you go away
Where is Paul Young?
Actually he's gone away I guess
And number three
What?
A wild guess man either hall notes
I have no idea
Talk this way
It's time's up and these are the answers
This is number one
From 1983
Joel and teller about it
To accept our real
Teller about it
To roll the crazy trees
Let's have no argument
Billy
Good to write a song
Joel is into number one
And this is into number two from 1985
This is Paul Young
Hey
We can still get it longer
Can't you sit
We've got nothing going on
Come on
Every time you go
Away
You take a piece of me
With you
Every time you go away
By Paul Young
You're sent to number two
And that's not number three
Also from 1985
Steve you wonder
Come on
The letter
You made it
From one of the two we want
With Paul Young
Love her
Come on
We wish you could meet
You passed me by
Don't even speak
No one can speak
Paul Young
With Paul Young
Parktime lovers
Answer number three
To our memory by a Steve you wonder
With Luther Vendros
As a backup singer
Alrighty
That concludes hit this number 82 for this week
Next week I would be back for number 83
But I hope you liked these three songs
So Adam
Hope you had them all
And Paul
And I think those can be found at hitest.potshow.com
So until next time
It's supposed to be next week
Until then, take care
Bye bye
Thanks Young
Hit test at gmail.com
And Paul Young
With Paul Young
Today's hit test brought to you by Kmartz
Check them out at back-to-school.potshow.com
The Savon Specials
Okay, it's a time for our Savon
From our series of The Circle of Savon
By the Sultan of Savon's Savon's
So
I think I'm going to be able to get at least
Once a month and episode
There's a fast forward button on there for a reason
And I hope to be able to talk to Savon
Every single day
Savon
And by the way
I want you to know that this format change
Doesn't mean that I don't want to make it pictures
Make it pictures
By the Sultan of Savon's Savon's
We present information and intelligence
About Iraq's legal Iraq's legal weapons programs
It's attempts to hide those weapons from inspectors
And it's links to terrorist groups
Georgie Porgie puttin' and pie
Picked some boys and made them die
In his playpan in the White House of lies
Sad around with all of his friends
Told him all on him to depend
Boyle is one, all of a sudden
The American have it with you
There's a place that we're gonna attack
For their oil and for daddy Iraq
Georgie Porgie made up a war
Told some lies about what it was for
Now you're baby, his out in Iraq
Do you know if they're coming back
Oh mama, how wanna come home
How wanna hear your voice on the phone
A straightforward, just move on the side
Got to find somewhere to hide
Oh mama, do something for me
Oh my kids, kids, my family
Tell them I'll be home in a while
But I don't die today
In a small town, something like here
Something's grown, something called the ear
Who's our phone, who really knows
Just be careful, where your vote goes
This November will be the true test
Can this country get out of this mess?
Boyle rich liars continue to rule
Come on people, let's stop being born
Oh mama, how wanna come home
How wanna hear your voice on the phone
Every day, one of the stars
Do me the deal, believe your life
Oh mama, do something for me
Oh my kids, kids, my family
I'll hope that I'll be home in a while
But I can die today
And die today
Come, die today
Your enemy is not surrounding your country
Your enemy is ruling your country
And the day he and his regime
Are removed from power
Will be the day of your liberation
You thought protests songs went out in the 60s
Uh-huh, they're live and well
And you just don't hear this shit on the radio
It's where it belongs right here
On a football Friday, daily source code 649
As Linda Finkel and Georgie Porgi
Put an impi, pick a few boys, send them to die
I gotta tell you man, we got a lot of cool people working at Pod Show
Checkin' in today
In just a bit from talent orders relations
Richard Brueher, hey, but first
So the one and only Oggy Doggy
Yo yo yo, Mr. Curry, Mr. Kirby
What's going on my brother?
It's your boy, Oggy Doggy contacting you from Part Show
Headquarters out in California
Yay, yay
Man, how's everything going out there for you
And the UK, my man?
Nice, nice
Well everything is going well over here for me
Another day, another dollar, life is beautiful
You know how it is man
So listen, just wanna check in with you
Let you know that I enjoy listening to you
Show yesterday as I always do
And I agree man, it's going to be a great, great, great, great thing
When part safe music is played out and retail stores out there
Man, that's going to be a big bonus for everybody
Yay, yay
Well, I did an episode on Cronk Rock Radio
And the episode is called
Bling Bling for you, ding ding
It's crazy man
I know it sounds very crazy
But the show is crazy, it's fun
And it's fun, he's guaranteed to put a smile on your face
So go check it out man
You can find it at crunkrockradio.pacho.com
Check it out, let me know what you think
I did a freestyle at the end of the show
And I know I'm not a rapper, but I try, man
So I also heard you're going to have a family reunion
And just hope all that goes well
Say hello to the family for me
And God bless you, God bless your family
God bless everybody out there in the UK
And two times for all the single ladies out there
I'll give you a love for your baby
Yay, yay
All right man
Much love and much happiness
I'm out
In a world where TV networks, movie studios and record labels
Still think they can govern what you see in here
One man has the power to return control of entertainment to the masses
And make big media corporations wet their tiny little pants
From Pod Show, home of the world's most dangerous new content
Comes the daily source code with Adam Curry
It helps to keep us young
Whether city on the affection of our sense of love
To who we are to be
A new way to love for me
I wish I didn't want you see
Has it drawn into the sea?
How are we to the sun?
The road to place where we can't forget where we're from
But the truth gets in the way we want done
But we are on the road on the run
And the answer only makes us numb
I send full of
To who we are to be
A new way to love for me
I wish I didn't want you see
Has it drawn into the sea?
To who we are to be?
A new way to love for me
I wish I didn't want you see
Has it drawn into the sea?
I wish I'd have been a summertime moon
I went to the sun and no walking.
They hail of course from nowhere else, but New Jersey.
Excellent.
From the Podsate Music Network at music.podge.com, or if you just want to see all the cool
pretty pictures in the music, and you don't want to join the network, then go to
Podge.com slash music.
Yeah, man.
I'm ready for some, well, that really vacation.
Because, you know, I'll be doing the show.
We've got the family reunion.
But we thanks to Chef Mark.
We got hooked up with an awesome beach house on Fire Island.
And, you know, I wanted a big place because Willow, my sister,
and Italy, is coming to the reunion.
And, her husband, Alessandro, can't come because he's got to work.
And, so she's bringing her two kids who are darling, by the way.
And I said, well, why don't we get like a big house?
Well, I'll hang out and we'll cook Italian.
And I actually try to get my other sister to come, but, unfortunately,
she's her son has to go to school.
Unlike the Wednesday after the Monday after the reunion.
So that just didn't work out.
Because, I thought it would be fun.
You know, have the whole family.
And so Willow was like, oh, this looks really cool.
And she looked it up.
I think that she Googled her.
She did a Wikipedia search, I think, on Fire Island.
Yeah, it's going to be very interesting.
I have a feeling that I will have a pretty big party with the locals.
Hey, today wouldn't be a football friday or wouldn't be a complete football friday
without at least one cranky savant calling in.
Come extra.
Hello, Adam.
Here is me, the CSV.
So I know that you will sell but show component to the highest bidder who offers more than
100 million US dollars.
Come extra blogger.
100 million got to be a lot more than that, my friend.
And you don't give a monkey.
What monkeys?
Let me say.
But let me tell you that I hate two things in putshow.com.
I guess if we fix these two things, then someone will buy us for 100 million.
That was the second CSV.
Do you don't you get it by now?
I'm doing this because I want to.
Firstly, I hate that there are no RSS feeds to comments.
Secondly, I hate that there is no method for doing upload with the resume after
interruption in outoring API of putshow.com.
A very very important feature for wireless applications.
Please tell your code monkeys to code it.
Or I will be very angry monkey myself.
And I will have to say.
Fuck you.
Adam theory.
Instead of the usual.
You.
Yeah, I know.
The comments on RSS.
I don't know.
I got mixed feelings about that.
You know.
It's a free and well.
I mean, you post almost every single show CSV, which by the way is appreciated because
I don't even know if anyone has heard the show until I see a comment by you show up.
I kind of want people to go see the comments.
And really, and be right there and ready to post.
I don't know.
I'm pretty sure that it's very simple to put that into place.
Now, the resume will upload from mobile applications.
Yeah.
Obviously, the best protocol, I guess, is FTP.
I don't think it's trivial.
You know, the way we set everything up.
I don't know if it's simple and how that would work.
But I'll certainly certainly look into it because I wouldn't want you to say fuck you.
Adam, curry.
I want you to say yo.
Hey, Adam.
This is Suzanne from the devicast.pacho.com.
Adam.
I have been itching itching to talk to you.
The devicast just had the most riveting interview that I can just ever imagine.
I wanted to share it with you.
We just interviewed Roland Haas, who has just come out with his book entitled Enter the Past
Tense.
My secret life as a CIA assassin.
Adam, I could not put this book down.
I think you will find it so exciting.
And he's very articulate and well spoken.
This book is just an absolute must read.
He's a must interview.
You're going to be peeing green within being when you hear our show.
So you have to go to the devicast.com.
Show number 59 and take a listen.
Adam, this is Robin, the producer for the devicast.
I read the book too.
And yeah, I had a hard time putting it down.
Very hard time putting it down.
I was over in Germany, flying the 810, right at the same time.
Roland Haas was over in Germany doing his business.
So it was right at the height of the Cold War.
And this sort of filled in a lot of the interesting pieces that I was aware that it
was going on.
But I, you know, I never knew exactly what was going on.
It was a really cool book.
And I think you'll enjoy it.
And I think it'd be a great topic for you to ask your uncle about.
Yeah.
When you go see him because I'm sure he has some insights.
I know he was on the other side of the world working in Korea.
Yeah, right.
Definitely have some ideas and some inputs on some of these things that went on.
So check it out.
Thedevecast.com.
You heard it here first.
Adam.
I'll talk to you soon.
Bye for now.
You tease.
That's all you are.
I know what's going on with you, Suzanne.
Okay.
Roland Haas.
Cool.
Yeah.
Amazon probably won't be able to get it to me before we leave.
But yeah.
Oh, man.
I wonder if I can get it to the airport.
That would be a good book to read before I talked to Uncle Don, which is.
Oh, crap.
Okay.
Guys, thank you very much.
I'm going to see if I can get a copy of it because I think it would be just perfect
homework for the big interview.
And we haven't actually, you know, there's two things I want to do.
One is interview Uncle Don.
It's a told you he worked for the CIA and he's now the president of the Korea Society.
Very involved in all the negotiations with North Korea.
But there's also, I recall when I was, I think 10 years old.
We had a previous Korean family reunion and we buried a time capsule.
And I remember, I distinctly remember where we buried it.
And so it's at the place.
It's still at the homestead, if you will.
And I think it's time to go dig it up.
And I remember with, I discussed this my uncle Don and I think it was, I think it was probably
winter or something.
We said, you know what?
We'll dig it up on, you know, that Easter or whatever.
And this is probably 10 years ago.
We just kept, you know, keep forgetting about it.
But by now, this time capsule, I think has been in the ground for about 30 years.
So I want to do a sound seeing tour of us digging it up kind of like an alcoholist vault.
Seven, I guess, a staking place this weekend.
Last night, everyone started arriving in Seattle.
And fortunately, I can't be there this year.
Of course, we do have a delegation from Pod Show up there.
up there, including our very unriched brewer hey from talent artist relations.
Hey Adam, it's Richard Cohen, you have here from lovely Seattle.
It is actually, let me think now, 10 o'clock for me.
So six in the morning for you on it'll be parts.
Fubah, hey, happy Fubah.
I made it up here for Nondex, as you know, and it was actually kind of fun to get up here.
I don't know if I told you the whole story behind it.
But John DeForek and I talked a little bit about speaking with Chris Purello, you know, as you know, who puts on Nondex.
I think he was actually the keynote here a couple of years ago.
So 200.
And John had said that he was flying up today, and that he wanted us to,
I mean, sit down with Chris and talk about the possibility of Chris doing some cool things with Partio,
which I know Chris has been wanting to do for a while.
I just haven't had a chance to connect with him.
So I booked my flight and got my hotel, got a rental car.
And I got an email from John about five o'clock yesterday afternoon saying,
the subject line was sorry for confusion.
And then when I opened the email, it said,
I think I might have said I was flying Thursday.
I'm actually coming up Friday.
John.
Thank you.
So John doesn't have to get here to tomorrow,
which point I'll order to be flying back to HQ.
So I managed to get with Chris on my own.
And I heard a very good meeting.
He's just fine coordination over there at Pod Show.
So you're up there without John, but the time John arrives, you'll be gone.
I love it when it comes together.
So I'm glad we had the meeting standing up.
He's a pretty animated guy.
Let me tell you, as you know.
Stop standing up.
I got to see some interesting people on the opposite under the spectrum,
as in not animated at all.
I did get to fly up with Steve Gilmore, which was a joy.
Let me tell you.
And then I also bumped into Brian Wall from cast fire.
Cory Janice from my order was their usual folks at a Metz.
I had a very good conversation with Chris Redlinger from GoDaddy.
She's been coming here ever since.
For quite a while, I see some sort.
Yeah, really.
I've been putting it on.
And then of course, the lovely Cali and the lovely meal together here in Seattle.
They've been driving all over the country by the sound of it.
They called me from the border of Canada coming back from Vancouver.
And they were stuck through customs.
They had two and a half hours getting into the country.
Uh-huh.
They just wanted to feed up Cali.
I know how that goes at the border.
They actually watched them in time movie on their DVD player in the car as they were
waiting to come across the border.
But we got to have a cocktail of two, as you know, Neil likes his general.
The only gin they had was beef eater, which was disappointed to him.
So he had his vodka tonning.
Um, HP sponsored the reception.
And which was a good thing because they apparently had good taste and beer.
They, uh, they had the Alaska Amber available.
So it was a good, uh, good reception.
I was impressed at the number of people.
I, you know, obviously, uh, who's who of, uh, dogs and geeks.
I would have loved it.
And, uh, I did.
Um, and it looks like it's one of your great show.
I was really amazed at the numbers.
It was a packed house down there in the water.
And I couldn't think of a better place to do it.
It's a lot warmer than expected.
Women in San Francisco.
That's your update, uh, from, uh, Seattle Pot Show.
All right.
You got cut off.
It's exactly three minutes.
There is a time limit, you know, Richard, that I can allow you to call in.
And he had another message he said.
Oh, I got cut off.
All right.
There you go.
You report from Nome Decks.
I hope they're doing a live stream again this year.
Because I do kind of enjoy that when there's conferences going on.
You can kind of listen in, uh, and since, uh,
Nome Decks is a single track conference, um, you know, you, you won't miss anything.
So I hope they're doing a live stream.
Think they're doing a live stream.
Oh, so they're doing Parillo?
Chris Parillo, um, I'm sure he will.
Yeah.
He does live stream when he's taken dump.
So we made it.
Expecting to do it from Nome Decks, Nome Decks.com.
What were you on?
Adam's first chin, I put.
Yeah, I haven't done this one in a while.
Let me just, uh, break out the old first generation I pod, you know,
the one with the really almost mechanical click wheel.
And we take, you see, um,
God, I connected.
Okay, we're going to give her a spin, I am going to put her on the summer playlist, see what comes off on Adam's first Jedi pop.
What's playin' on Adam's first Jedi pop?
Oh, what's this?
Can we guess it yet?
It's a summer song, that's for sure.
Oh yes, oh man, imagine the luck.
Alright, this takes me back to 1974 and 75.
Bobby Goldsboro, summer the first time.
Hard afternoon, the last day of June, and the sun was a demon.
The clouds were afraid, one tin in the shade, and the pavement was steaming.
I told Billy Ray in his red Chevrolet.
I needed time for something.
I was just walking by when I looked in her eyes and I swore it was waking.
She was 31 and I was 17.
I knew nothing about love, she everything.
I sat down beside her on her front porch.
You wanted what?
You're coming, that would be me.
The sun closed her eyes as it climbed in the skies.
And it started to swell too.
Sweat trickle down, the front of her gown.
I thought it would melt too.
She threw back her hand, like I wasn't there.
She said, don't let you live.
Her shoulders were bare, and I tried not to scare when I looked at her too.
When she looked at me, I heard her softly saying,
I know you're young, you don't know what to do or say.
I would stay with me until the sun's gone away.
And I would chase the oil in you away.
And then she smiled, then we talked for a while.
Then we walked for a while to the sea.
We sat on the sand, and the more it took her hand.
But I saw the sunrise as a man.
I had made dinner, but whether I had heard it or not,
Her muels were like a mont King.
When she looked at me, I heard her softly saying,
I looked in her eyes, but the memory may go.
I go back in my mind to the very first time,
in the touch of the finger.
Was a hot afternoon, the last dear dream,
and the sun was at the end.
I did a version of this song, got to play for you some time.
I think it's probably even better than the original.
From my first generation iPod, Bobby Gullsboro,
and some are the first time.
Adam, I know you don't want me to call him from the car,
but I can't help it.
I'm listening to the DSC number 647,
and you keep saying, foot and mouth disease.
Yeah.
Coward don't have feet, it's hurt, and mouth disease.
You're killing me.
Hi.
You can go in.
Oh man, I'm telling you that over here,
they say foot and mouth disease.
That's what they say over here.
I can't help it.
I agree that it would be hoof,
because it doesn't look like a foot,
but they call it foot and mouth disease.
Can't help you there.
Third outbreak now registered near Gillford.
It's going to be a mess.
This is really not good news.
Tomorrow, if the weather holds up,
and I haven't even told you how beautiful the weather is today.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
The God has just given this to us.
Thank you.
Thank you, Lord, for this beautiful day.
Give me another one tomorrow,
because I'm going to fly to Antwerp.
It's time for the 100 hour inspection,
and maintenance on the Delta Sierra.
So fly over hopefully.
If the weather's nice,
everything works out according to plan.
I'll be able to do some helly flying tomorrow
with the wind commander.
So don't look for me over the weekend.
And, you know,
it wouldn't be a football Friday.
If we didn't have someone who's just so angry at Pod Show,
and it'd me and it how football everything is.
Adam Curry, this is the skipper from the boatvirtions.com,
which is hosted by Pod Show.
I have addressed this issue with your tech support
more than I can count.
I cannot fucking log in to my account,
and this keeps happening over and over again.
This is my final comment that I'm sending your tech support
on the Pod Show website.
Message.
This is the last fucking time I will write in on this issue.
I can't fucking log in.
How many fucking times do I have to get you to address this?
I pride my password, it doesn't work.
I get a new one sent to me, and it doesn't work either.
This is a continuing problem that you fucks won't fix.
How am I supposed to get to my podcast that you host to add to it?
To check my stats, to edit, etc.
If I can't fucking log in, why does this continue?
And what are you going to do to primarily fix this?
Adam, the last time I will call in,
the last time I will send a comment,
and I will host my fucking website, my Podcast, somewhere else.
I'll get it fixed.
Oh man, I feel so bad.
Ah, Skipper, don't worry, man.
I'm sure it's just some anomalies.
I haven't heard anyone else with this complaint.
Oh, yep.
But it's good to get it out of your system.
How many times did you tell them to fucking not fucking do this fucking thing?
When I awake in midnight,
I lay in your shadow once again.
I wonder where you have been.
If I'm secure to you.
For the size I greater,
why don't you come out and say your peace?
And put my mind at ease.
I'm waiting for you alone.
Tell me you're wrong.
Tell me that my fears have gone too far.
Tell me that I've been here for a while.
You and I,
you and I,
just let it do now.
So tell me that I'm wrong.
Never say who I am.
Why can't you tell me why.
The house in Christmas tree
would've hold you till he's gone.
Run out of ways to save us
Run out of ways to save my place
Why are you just saving this?
I'm trying to save my mind.
Tell me I'm wrong.
Tell me that my fears have gone too far.
Tell me that I've made a role on your heart
You and I as live as the two love
Tell me that I'm wrong
I've been wrong to think that you've got something more to say to me
Which I need you still care as I know
You're true and hurts and you're a scene
You know, see inside my heart that your breath will never be
For the sun is a goal
I'm sorry I was right
Your spirit shakes me in my sleep
If I was wrong you'd be with me tonight
I tell me I'm wrong
Tell me that I've made a role on your heart
You and I as live as the two love
Tell me that I'm wrong to think that you've got something more to say
I'm thinking I heard of this guy before when I saw him pop up on the podcast music network
His name is Nelson Bragg
Turns out he also worked on Brian Wilson's
Smile album that project that was in the works for like 30 years
Nelson Bragg on the podcast music network tell me wrong
Why didn't up to daily source code episode number 649 on a football Friday
It's Friday
Monday Tuesday Wednesday Thursday
Food about Friday
Adam's final fun your phone
We're going to make it really sweet into the point today
Lady Bird
I'm sorry the hell am I talking about
Who barred
I'm going to leave you with a quote of the day that I ran across
I'm actually subscribed to this. It's the motivational quotes of the day RSS feed
This one's from Eleanor Roosevelt
Fine
Fine first lady
Was that a first lady
All right here comes. I just like the quote forget about her you gain strength courage and confidence
By every experience in which you really stop to look fear in the face
You are able to say to yourself I've lived through this horror
I can take the next thing that comes along
You must do the thing you think you cannot do
All right 45 46 minutes perfect everybody Monday
I'll be back remember we're traveling Wednesday
So you may not get a show then I'm not quite sure what time we're flying and
But Thursday Friday and from the curry reading you read re reunion in upstate New York
And from the beach house on fire island with all of our friends
There is source code calm Adam at podshow.com
Have a great weekend everybody
Hope you have great weather
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear