With $60 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
For the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't mean us.
We can get rid of you.
I like to think I'm trying to make sure.
Autistic.
It's Adam Curry.
Dr. Doctor, do you think he's in a make it?
I don't know what to mean, but there's a few things we can try.
First, James Earbuds and his ears real tight.
Now, crank up the DSC 570.
All right, I can do find this picture in the current time.
I'll just open the basket and see if he'll come around.
That guy's coming right in, look.
That's good.
That's good. Keep it up.
Keep cranking the DSC 570.
Of course, he'll picture the current time I always have.
I will look for my eyes.
The wind's coming with my help.
You might have come up from the war.
He will have supper that I put to be moved.
He that keep it be will not slumber.
Behold, he that keep it is real.
He'll tell me they're slumber.
The Lord is that keeper.
The Lord is that I shade upon their right hand.
The sun shall not smite by day.
We're the moon by night.
The Lord shall preserve thee from all evil.
We shall preserve thy soul.
The Lord shall preserve that going out.
And I coming in from this time for it.
And even for it ever more.
The Lord shall preserve that going out.
I've got to say kind of to me by surprises as well.
Here in the whole thing for the third time, I'm liking it.
It is, of course, the Shakes from the pod and set music network.
I want a better life.
This is the Dr. Remix.
I put up two remixes yesterday.
And something about it just like, yeah.
like yeah. Awesome. Can wait to hear this one in the
clubs, fellas. Everybody how you doing is daily source code
episode five hundred and seventy five seven zero coming to you
from the affluent suburb of Surinone is gulford the west side of
G-town is represented for you. It's the curry manner up in the
air and Adams attic more a more iteration for you perhaps it
is a beautiful day outside. I'm so hoping that the weather keeps
up for tomorrow because there's a sixty percent chance that my
aircraft will be returned which means you probably won't have a
daily source code tomorrow morning because I'll be in transit. If you
don't have a daily source code by Thursday then you'll know that
something didn't go well with the English channel navigation
solo flying you know what I'm saying. Lots of thoughts today
about bum rush the charts lots of bum rush thoughts that
listeners in the UK please do not be alarmed I know that you think of
something different when I talk about bum rush.
Speaking of bum rushing hold on a second let me open up the other microphone.
I think something must have gone wrong with uh with my email and Amy Mac last
week because well I've quite frankly I didn't get to ask her size.
Make it to the other mic.
Hello. All right there we go.
Amy, thank you so much.
Adam, hey, Amy Matt. Hey, Matt.
How you doing today? We're doing tiptoe squat.
Tiptoe squats okay. I'm sure there's a more masculine name for him but I like this one.
Yeah there's no masculine name for him. You're going to start standing tall with
feet facing out in a diagonal away from you and hands on hips okay away from
that. Nowadays up under your tiptoe's and then squat down as far as you can
keeping those heels off the ground. Taking them like with me.
You want your head shoulders and hips to all be in a straight line.
So no sticking that booty back. It's hurting into the right hands.
Squeeze the butt as you come up. Coming.
Come on. Good. Now you have nine more to do.
All right all my tips. This is really good for your core as well because you have to keep your
balance on this one. Yeah you do. It's going to nasty or don't hold your breath.
You always remind me to breathe and I'm so happy you do. Stay up on those tiptoe.
Yes yes yes. Oh that squeeze the butt nabs. It's kind of weird. Good job.
Makes me want to have a great weekend and until next time.
I think I I was a little premature with the exercise.
Pre-missue or a ascertainization. Yeah have a great weekend as well. It's only Tuesday where I'm
living. I'm sorry. I'll let me close the other mic there. That's the lady Patricia's mic.
Ugh. That's really weird. You should try that one. This of course is in the continuing quest to
tone up my ass because I sit on it most of the time. Now that I have the sit down studio instead
of the stand-up studio. The whole office is sit down for Cry 6.
Let me just catch my breath. I should try that tiptoe thing.
Because when you go all the way down to the ground it feels like you're squatting like you want to do
something nasty. Let's see what my condition is so shit. Let's see what's coming on the
voicemail comments. Of course, no milk cast complete without a comment from Eric Burgund's mom.
Hey Adam. Alice in the ear. Hey. By the way. No hummer. Rapcast.com.
So I had to call in and say something after listening to my son's speak and after talking
to him in great lengths last week. That would be Eric Burgund calling it about bummering the
charts. Hold on a second. Now did I already play this for you? I don't know. If I already
played it just fast forward. And I got to say something that the two of you left out that I think
is really important, which is how you feel and how empowering it is once you do something like this,
that it's not about getting a song to number one. It's about being heard. It's not about
well, do we just pick a song? We didn't really care about the song itself. We just wanted to show
we can do it. Like you said Adam, yeah, that is what it's about. But even more importantly about
that, it's like having that experience that you can do it because what happens next is exactly
that. What do you want to have next? Once you realize that you have the power to change something
like that, it's freeing. You just know, okay, what am I going to do next? How do I get heard more?
It's no surprise to me. In the times today, there's an article written by Jeff Leeds called
the album, a commodity in disfavor with the tagline underneath, with CD sales falling,
label-seek new deals with Apple. Here's a quote from the article,
executives maintain that they must establish more lasting connections with fans who may
well lose interest if forced to wait two years or more for their favorite artist,
releasing new music. Well, there you go. I mean, that is what podcasting and everything has
over everything. It's why I started craftcast. I realized that loved all the crafting networks,
but when they went into repeats, there was no new information you had to wait months.
And here is a format where you can put out information every day. I know from the subscribers
and people who write in who listen to me and how my fanbase is grown, that people want to be
able to have that kind of content that there's a need for it. It's very exciting. It's really
the bottom line. I can barely wait to hear what the next bum rush the chart type of that is,
because it's just it's being on the frontier edge here. It's just all unfolding and it's really
exciting. So big thank you to you Adam. Love your show and love all the discussions and look
forward to what's happening next. Naked pictures. That's what's happening. As you say unfolding around
unscrewing before I very eyes, I didn't quite catch it. Yeah, bum rush the charts has it has a
different meaning for every person involved. And that's what's nice about it because it didn't
have really one central drive behind it. But it is of course an audience exercise. And I've thought
about this. Remember yesterday, I just thought started popping into my head. This is exactly what
happens to hip hoppers. Whenever they receive an award, they always thank God for putting those
lyrics into their heads. It's exactly what happened to me yesterday. And I want to share those thoughts
with you. But first to continue in the bum rush thoughts with some other typical griping,
it's our friend. You know, we need a jingle for this guy. It's the New York Londoner. It's the
nylon. Hey, Adam. It's the nylon. The New Yorker in London. I can just hear Jeff Smith's brain
crunching what he can do with the nylon. I know you're in a little budget there. You can't
employ a sack check, checker. So, oh, yeah. Oh, nylon. Why do you start off like this? Yeah.
I know you want a little budget dude. You can play a trick tricker. No, that's what I have
you for. You're my fact checking bitch. Corrections and then a final word on bum rush to talk.
All right. First, the reason why you probably don't know about the E.C. 50th is that
it's actually the European economic community that's somewhere in the 50th birthday. And that
consists of Belgium, France, Italy, Luxembourg, the Netherlands, and West Germany. It wasn't
sort of master treaty in 92 that what we now know is the European community came into force. So,
it's only about seven countries that actually were part of that gum celebration. I'm signing back
in 1957, I guess. Second. Okay, before we go to second. All right. Well, thank you very much for
the correction. That does explain a lot if the U.K. was not in that region, in that treaty from
1957. Then this is what I mean. It's so confusing. We've got the European economic community. We've
got the European Union. It's complicated. Why can't it? Why can't it just be easier to understand?
And yeah, you're right. I don't have fact checkers for that. If I had to fact check everything,
I'd be like fucking mainstream media dude. Of course, I do expect comics to be blogger to check in.
He is the official EU correspondent. Is you mentioned the powerhouse of A.D.M.
Ambro and the Dutch and such. Let me maybe be behind your F.C. But if I'm likely in 90 days,
that A.D.M. will be a Dutch bank to allow the British or American bank. Well, obviously,
I understand that. I could read newspapers too, Nylon. I know that A.B. and Ambro was for sale
due to underperformance. In fact, I think I even alluded to that in what I said. I was very careful
to say it still is a Dutch bank. It's not even a fully owned Dutch bank, of course.
It's part to talk now because you've got me in this whole fact checking thing.
Yeah, I do read the newspaper. And by the way, that's a big part of the discussion going on
in the Netherlands right now is, you know, Unilever has already been partially sold off.
In fact, what does the Netherlands still produce after A.B. and Ambro has gone? What's their main
industry besides tourism for tulips and fucking bicycles? Nothing. All the great industry
has been sold off or moved on or consolidated and sold off.
So anyway, thank you for pointing that out. There's made a bit as you know, and probably
city bank will come in. So mine is a collection there. And by the way, Nylon, I'd like to know a little
bit more about what you do exactly. You're in the financial sector. Are you a trader?
You know, a manager or maybe IT manager, banking, of course, is largely an IT business.
Tell me a little bit about you if you don't mind. You're so credible, you know.
On second bank, F.C. again, actually, was that Twitter made the front page of the F.C. at least
here in the UK? Yeah, that's uh, I think I said that as well. That's the reason why I brought it
up is because in on the front page, there was a whole article about Twitter. I think at
line, I'll see what you're saying. So be interesting to see how this new little phenomenon has hit
the front page of the Wall Street Journal without even a bummerous, the on-challenge sort of
promotion. Oh, please. Has nothing to do with bum rush the charts? It's completely something
completely different. Podcasting was on the front page of the, it's continues to be on the front
page of the F.T. Twitter is a phenomenon. And again, I'll say that there's really only two parts
who would want. I believe that the United States is now finally discovering the simplicity
and reliability. I'll just say quote reliability of SMS text messaging. And they're loving it
because it's a very personal communications channel. And of course, the the cool thing about it is
that it's opt-in. So it's a published and subscribe mechanism. I think we'll see several of these,
but this is a very, very obvious one. And I think Twitter is really catching on more in the states
because the whole idea of text messaging is now dawning upon. I think a very important group of
influencers and early adopters. So curious thing to watch. And finally, I'll say the topic,
bum rush. Yeah. This is the short version of it. Is that it sounds like a promotion or was
a podcast is for a podcast of the benefit barcasters. If there is a bummer chart version 2.0,
make it customer centric. Make it where me, someone in the outside, not like you, someone in the
inside, look at it and say, okay, as a customer, I see what this is doing for me. You need to expand
the audience, not preach to the converted. So my constructive comment is version 2.0,
bum rush discharge. You've got expand in your audience, not preaching to the converted patting everyone
on their back. You need to get that 1% who download a 100 million iPods out there to 5%.
Then I think you've moved the needle. It's about customers. So not to criticize it, but
constructive comment. And last thing. All right. So first of all, I don't take that as criticism.
I think you're you're right in in many regards. I'll let you finish. I see you've got like nine
seconds left. So whatever you have to say is gone. Oh, why do my ass? Since you always like my ass
on the radio show after I'm done. Why if you're asking me to talk about scrunching and holding.
Cheers. Do keep calling. Okay. Whatever you do, don't
stop and don't turn nice on me. But that last comment you made makes a lot of sense to me. I did
some thinking yesterday. I do my best thinking in three places. One is in the bathroom.
Dirling my morning break, which consists of the financial times. I take no technology with me
into the into the smallest room in the house. And by the way, we have a special room just for me,
which is off to the back of the pantry. So it's a and it's nicely heated and I've got my
ash tray in there. Because of course, you know, I have to have my morning tea and perhaps
something else to get my brain going. And, you know, I'll just sit there and I take a long time,
and like half an hour type of guy. I love it and I'll read the two sections of the paper that
I enjoy reading the most and I take the rest upstairs. So that's one place where I do a lot of
great thinking. I'm always inspired. I love the newspaper. I really do. In the shower is another
place where I just can completely zone out as if hypnotize, as if back in the womb. And the third
place is actually when I go to bed. When I close my eyes, I'll usually cement a problem in there.
I don't know if it's healthier not to do this, but I'll cement a problem into my mind or
something that I want to work out. And then often in the morning, the brain is done the work.
During the night and it all becomes very, very clear. Maybe the brain has already done the work.
It just has to sort it all out and put it into perspective so that my consciousness can
take note of it and act on it. So bummer us the charts version 2.0. I think should
become something completely different. What? In hindsight, looking at this, we used iTunes as
a validation mechanism, and really very difficult to validate against mainstream media. Obviously,
we want customers to, and when you call customers, what I call audience, to feel that they have
this power, to see how to use it, which works through posting things on web logs and calling in,
writing into your favorite podcast and using your my space to propagate the message, just really
the concept of the unlabel. What we have not had, and we have a lot of really good things,
though the massively important piece that we have is the pod save music network that allows access
to the free and clear MP3 tracks for producers of shows to use and the reporting mechanism,
the reporting back because that gives us a social media network. You find a song, you like,
you see what other shows who played the song, you're likely to find another song that you will
also like that that same show played. Also, we can compile charts. The sea dog is one of the
many people who do a pod save music countdown. So this is all extremely important in like a parallel
music industry universe. So what we're missing really is the accepted and approved. It's the
same thing, no matter what new media always comes down to a certain point, you have to be able to
compare it to traditional media. It's unfortunate, we'll get to other types of metrics, but we do
need to have this and the iTunes charts are obviously used a lot as as a means of justification
or proof. Regardless, we don't even know how the iTunes charts are put together. So here's the idea
because we've been talking to app as we being pod show. This is what I'd like to do. I don't know
what else is going to do with bum rushed the charts. I don't own it. We've been talking for
man over a year now, at least, about what we can do with iTunes music store and the pod save
music network. And I think I've finally got it. What we need to do is to enable, let me step back one
second. It's very hard for an individual artist to get their track onto the iTunes music store,
because it's really it's a huge backlog. There's, you know, the iTunes music store team isn't,
you know, isn't huge. And what they much rather prefers taking a weekly upload from aggregators
and these aggregators are, of course, record companies and a few other and independent labels.
There are a couple of these aggregators. So the concept for me would be to become an aggregator.
You get your song onto the iTunes music store by uploading your track, basically, with all the
appropriate information to the pod save music network. So a lot of you have already done that.
So all you have to do then is just tick a box, which says, yes, make this eligible for purchase
through the iTunes music store. Now, here comes the tricky part. What I'd, so the concept here is
that we use the purchase of these songs as, as the metric that they're traditionally used for,
in other words, we link, if you want to buy a track, and this is, it's very, very tricky,
because we already have a purchase function on pod save music network. If you want to buy a track,
and you want to have your vote counted through this, quote, official thing, which will be through
the, you know, the official metric that Apple uses for all of their purchase data,
then you'll be shuddled over to the pod save music to the, to the iTunes music store, your iTunes
pop open, you'll buy the track. I'm still happy to pass on all the money. I don't need to take
any money from the artist. The iTunes is already taking money, just like the credit card companies
take money if you buy it through the PMN. And then we should also enable you to automatically
download the, the MP3 version. Maybe it's an email with a link to it or something like that. You know,
if you buy it, then, you know, the whole concept is that you should be able to have that MP3
free and clear of DRM. So we kind of sort that issue out. Then what we have, literally,
is a bum rush the charts chart, which is open for anybody. So,
even if you don't have a podcast, if you just want to, if you're just turning people onto this piece
of music, this track or this artist, you can use a link, send them over there, depending on how many
people download, whatever the magic sauce of the calculation is. It'll rise in the charts when
it rises in the charts. That's when people get excited. You try to make it go higher in the chart,
and then there's really another tier. You know, you could break into the overall iTunes top 100 chart.
You understand what I'm saying? So this chart would only be of songs purchased through iTunes
that are affiliated with the pod safe music network. I hope I'm explaining this properly because
it's starting to gel in, in my head. And we're going to have a meeting this week and see if we
can get this going because it makes a lot of sense. It will be, it's almost like an independent chart.
I just had to shut up for a second there as the satellite listeners dropped off.
Hmm. So this chart would be only to be manipulated or changed by people purchasing tracks.
So essentially, you can start your own bum brush because it'll move the needle on our own chart
and from our own chart, of course, there's many other places it can go.
Does it place us as a second tier? No, I see it as a parallel.
But we're coming in as an whole industry as a label that has as an unlabel that has no interest
in the in the sales of the music. But does have an interest in making all this content available
and being able to produce, you know, a real network effect based upon a reward system, which is,
hey, look at that. It moved up. So of course, the sales are going to be much lower than, you know,
the mainstream efforts just because, well, we're learning how to use our network.
So that's why we have to have a separate chart. Something like that.
Hey, you know what I haven't done in a while? I haven't, uh, I haven't done a proper go daddy commercial
but, oh, let me, uh, you like this track? I found on the pod saying music network.
Let me just open this up.
I think it's Dan from Creepy Sleepy who, uh, who gave me this, uh,
just this regular read. He really thought about it too. So I'll provide the music and he'll provide, uh,
oh, it's like lyrics and music.
It's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it
is like, it's like, yeah, that's right.
But that's right, and if you use, uh, uh, I wish I knew the creepy sleeping code.
Well, my code is dsc3go onto creepy sleeping.com.
Find out what this code is and use that.
And he'll get a little bonus.
And you'll get a bonus discount.
That's fun the way that works.
So those of you wondering what's going on with the free Trinity project, I'll
tell you our um, We can New York and in London.
Interestingly enough resulted in some very serious interest to a sponsor the project so I'm kind of in limbo because if we get sponsoring in
And it's a whole different approach I'd like to take
Both with sending some finances on to save the world, but more importantly, we could really do something with the production
I've kept everybody in limbo
Kind of like in irons, if you will, I'm sorry about that
Particular apologies go to Barbara the polo Alto podcast, who's just also been kind of like sitting still waiting for me to
To go left or right. It is going to happen
I just want to give it another week or two
To see if we can
Up the ante a little bit so to speak
Remember it's all about independence and true human relationships
Jeff you got that. I'm gonna order a jingle pack as pretty soon
And of course this program has with many shows on the
Pot show podcast network has brought to you in part by folders the gourmet blends of coffee to be nicely combined
With the splendor splendor with the splendor splendor what's your flavor
My forgetting something. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Oh, I got to get Patricia up here. She had the only reason I want to get her on the show so she can
Do a spot for me for
Tylenol PM
Which is sponsoring Angie B's show on wine dot pod show dot com
Another interesting comment. I've been going back and forth with this guy for quite a while
We're supposed to hook up for an interview. I didn't really want to cloud the free Trinity
vibe with what he was coming in with but it is so interesting to me
And it's a real tin foil hat type of moment. So here it is Adam right Adam's here. You know the guy that wants to build backyard atomic engines
Okay, it sounds like shit. What's going on? It's a run out run atoms. I think it is and
He's completely into backyard atomic energy. I got to tell you that's tough does turn me on
It's wanted to call and say how much I enjoyed your last two-board Friday show
I think you have it about right the great thing about new media is it's a playing field that's then leveled a bit
By the wide open unconstrained access to the internet provides
Sure bum rest of charts was display of power the goal was to show the old guard that they no longer have as much controlled over the distribution channels as they once did
As time goes on the battle be a little bit more about talent and passion and about ownership of the scarce resource like radio airtime
How absolutely I'm all the way with you there buddy. I'm a big fan of independent action
I've been working for about a decade and a half as an indie atomic engine designer and builder
Our system is all about independence from control by oil exporters coal suppliers
large equipment manufacturers and gas pipelines with
1950s inches technology. I once steamed around the ocean completely divorced from the grid from months of the time
With current technology we think we have a way forward that will demystify and democratize atomic energy
You've said that you do not want to get into the atomic controversy or is that
Controversy it's controversy the topic is important in a world with constrained fossil fuel energy supplies and a growing
Understanding that air pollution just might be damaging the planet's ability to sustain human civilization as we know it
Just imagine some day in the not too distant future
It might be a clean emissions free reliable moderately priced
Adams engine supplying a new pod so data bar
Hey, dude. I'm totally into it. I'm totally interested
And you know that that there's a huge
pile of money that is being invested in this sector if you really got something let's talk about it
I can certainly make the right introductions for you
But if you please send in in some more info and do something about the recording quality because that was absolute crap
I don't know what you're using you can if you're not gonna do more than 10 minutes
Won't just go to casplash.com and download the free version. You can use that
Tell me what does need it what what has to be done? What are the the raw materials? Is it safe?
I mean these are all the questions. What about the the nuclear waste? You know that's the kind of stuff we get here to know
Remember these guys that came on to the network about month ago the brand new heavies all fired up from the pod save music network
on TSC
We've
I'm gonna try to grab the look at you
So I'm gonna grab the look at you
I gotta see what's in front of you
Set it free and lose the moment
You expect me to stay
Unless we just got caught up
In the game of love
Take a look
We just learned a page in the love
As we look and we get dead
We're happy there
We gotta try to find out
Bye for now
We gotta build this thing
To let's be the love of love
Oh, the sky
Oh, baby
Watch me see
Oh, the sky
Oh, what's in front of you
Haw, the sky
Oh, the sky
Oh, fight up, you gotta try, fall up
Try, fall up, fall up
Try, fall up