Hey everybody, daily source code episode 523, how you doing?
I got nothing but boxes.
Tiny boxes, big boxes, little boxes.
The only thing still standing in the studio here at the curry cottage is the desk, is
the podcast console.
And the big gree ugly green thing, which soon will be just a memory, as it has to go
into deep deep storage, since it will not fit through the doorway up to the third floor studio
in the brand new cottage, which summer now calling the curry tower, which I got to see
if that'll grow on me or not.
Anyway, a time for another best of charity today, as we are completing the big move of
2007, it's a mess, I gotta tell you.
And of course portions of today's show brought to you by Splenda, as well as by Stomp the
Yard, brand new movie coming out in just four days from now, yeah, four days from now on
the 12th of January, go to StompthePodcast.com to find out more.
And by the way, I have had some time to check out some of the CES coverage that's been
going on.
Pod Show is at CES as well.
At the AMD Live booth, as we're presenting the first demo of Pod Show TV, which is essentially
a version of Pod Show Plus on IPTV, and it's fucking cool.
So that's something we can look forward to to 2007.
I saw the Bill Gates keynote, I don't know what, I don't know what, I don't know what
it was kind of bland, actually.
And you know what the demos when Bill Gates does the demos versus a demo from Steve Jobs,
I guess what is it tomorrow or the day after tomorrow, we have another Mac world and so of
course we'll have another stellar performance from Steve.
Whenever the Microsoft guys do a do demos, it just doesn't feel right, it feels like, yeah,
you know, what's going on behind the scenes, they never quite completed to make it feel
like this will actually work at your place.
Anyway, it's still very happy with my Windows machine, but I, no one has convinced me yet
why I need to upgrade to Windows Vista, although I'm sure the next machine I buy will
have it built in.
Okay, so I'm going to use this best of Charlie since it is a musical theme best
of Charlie produced by PD Love, I'm going to use that as some packing music for myself
here and the gang from smart movers who are helping us out, I've been packing a lot of
my own stuff mainly because as we've gone through this before, it's my stuff.
So when else is stuff, well, that's just purely shit.
Hey, here we're in, but I, sorry, could resist.
Thanks DSC listeners, I am PD Love, the guest host of this best of Charlie, and I just
introduce myself.
I do several podcasts, namely Love House Radio, for showcasing a mix of pot-sake music
artists in genres, and the daddy cast, a podcast for the parenting community focusing on
advice for dads and stories of my life with my two boys.
Perhaps you've heard my voice a little bit on some of the intros for the daily source code
or way back when in the second life talks.
But other theme for this show for this best of Charlie is Music of 2006.
It's a review of the music that Adam has played over the course of the past year.
Basically I went through Adam's show notes and put together a playlist of songs he seemed
to enjoy based on the number of times he's played each song.
Put it together and based on my research, the best played song of the DSC in 2006 was
Liberty Jones.
So let's get the show started with the shakes and Liberty Jones.
Ever nearly Liberty Jones works in the shop that she owns.
Lessons to music like swing.
When there's no customer's in, just because she don't like to drive, takes us to see
you don't mind back to my face.
Music shows something, why don't you go for me, take me away and lie to you.
If I'm in the country
On the island
No one is the United Kingdom
Liberty Jones
You could find them on the podcast music network
Gosh, I love that
What a great song
Really, really good
So we're getting some shape done that isn't gentlemen
And lacking it very much
And keep the comments coming for Shadow Falls, man
People are loving this
Shadow Falls.podshow.com
And part of the appeal is got to be the music
Munk has really outclassed himself this time
Into a whole new level
This song kicks so much ass
It's Molly Steen
I am
From PMM
I'm just begun
I was dead
For us to be
That swings both ways
You've never asked my name
I am here
I am alive
I am there for a reason
I am here
I am there
You are asleep
I am live, I am live, I am live, I am careful of breathing, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live,
I am live, I am, I am rains, I am living, I am alive, I am alive, I ameker people, I am elated people, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live i am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am live, I am lives, I am live, I am
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
I am here, I am here, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there,
I am there, I am there, I'm here, I am there no more than I could do, I am there, mother, I am there Camara, I'm really glad I'm here, I am there, I am there, wife is here, I am here, I'm there, I am there, I am there, I am there,yes, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am here, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am here, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am there, I am here, I am there, I am there, I am
your 2007 with a little splendor. What's your flavor? Now let's change the flavor of our music
with a little Howard Jones and Kevin Reed. This is something that really, really tickled me when it
came in this came in yesterday morning. Hi Adam. I'm not going to say who, who, um, I'll skip one
fight. Hi Adam. I just wanted to say thanks for playing building our own future on your podcast
show and big in me up. Thanks for the help with the tour dates as well. If I can be of assistance,
best wishes. Howard, that would be Howard Jones. I thought that was so awesome. Um, because of
course, Howard Jones, um, I know him from the early 80s, I've played so many of his songs on the
radio, played so many of his videos. I know actually that people under certain age don't know who
Howard Jones is and they play the song form, which of course is in the pod sitting music network.
And go, yeah, that's pretty cool. And, and some of them say, oh yeah, I think, uh, uh, uh,
yeah, that's the one. That's the guy. So not only did you just fantastic that he sent that note,
but then there's a PS to it. PS, he says, I'm a folder. I never thought about Howard, but make sense.
Here's building our own future.
I'm crying out the sunbeams. There's a lot of people listening.
Time for us to sing down a song. Try to pull them on this and then.
yeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeye Yeyyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeveyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyiyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyyyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeyeye
I just know now, day by day, three, two, three, two, three, four, five, six, four, five, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six,
six, six, six, seven, six, seven, six, six, six, seven, six, six, five, six, six, seven, seven, seven, six, six, six, six, six, seven, six, six, seven, seven, six,
Guys, we're going to build a young future
Just from now on, day by day
We need to choose a life that's better than before
Sons and daughters, brothers and daughters
Always have been on the road, come to me soon
Guys, we're building a young future
Just from now on, day by day
We need to choose a life that's better
Oh mga !
Sons and daughters, brothers and daughters
While we need to choose a life that's better than before
Now on, day by day, we need to choose a life
He's a musical genius, I gotta say it.
First, it's a folder.
For John's building our own future, he's on tour.
Two or two dates will be, you can find those in the show notes, dailysourcecode.com, or even
on his own page at the Podsign Music Network, which of course you can find a link to in the
show notes.
I don't know how much of the production Howard does himself, but oh man, that snare is just
BAM!
It just slaps away so hard, I love it!
With $144 worth of MP3 players strapped to my head, and the next generation of radio content
being vibrated into my skull, I think I look like a dickhead in the pool.
Alright Tom, Podsign Music Network Kevin Reeves on the Daily Sourcecode.
It's as late as the man that's in kick-ass.
Throw me a line.
I don't know.
Is there any way out of here?
Is there some way to make this clear?
Because of you, I can't sleep anymore, since you walked up the door and you left me.
All I do is stare at the wall, and you know from to to all, sempre memory.
While you want to try to be insane, while you want to cause me so much pain,
I don't think I can't make it on my own, but I don't think I can't make it on my own.
I just pray that I'm not dying alone, but I still be silent.
Tell me that you'll still live with me, but I don't think I can't.
I can't feel so no darkness from light.
I don't know daytime from night, on the free set.
Isn't real?
Oh, I wake up from this, and I miss if you kiss and embrace it.
One day I'm in my sports room.
I don't think I can make it on my own, but I still be silent.
I don't think I can't make it on my own, but I don't think I can't make it on my own.
I just pray that I'm not dying alone, but I still be silent.
Tell me that you'll still live with me, but I don't think I can't.
I can't feel so no darkness from light.
I don't think I can defend myself.
I don't think I can make it on my own, but I still be silent.
Tell me that you'll still live with me, but I still love myself as if you said lie.
Oh, I don't think I can make it on my own, but I still can't.
I can't make it on my own
But throw me the fire
What a crazy life
My tag is wrong but long
But it's still inside
Tell me that you're still in love with me
What a crazy life
My tag is wrong but long
But it's still inside
What a crazy life
My tag is wrong but long
Hey man
That's a quality shape right there
Kevin Reeves throw me a line
From the Podsia Music Network
Link in the show on today's source code
Oh yes a great tune by Kevin Reeves
When next time you have a domain name
I'll help the curries pay their new mortgage
And use the DSC codes at GoDaddy
I actually had to move my
TheDaddyCast.com domain
And registered theDaddyCast.org
And theDaddyCast.net
To last week using GoDaddy
And it was really easy
And plus you can enter the different codes
See which configuration works best for you
What saves you the most money
Very good stuff
When this last song was submitted by Jersey Todd
And happened to be played on a day when Patricia was on the show
So take a listen to the unveiling of the wild bunch
Let's go up the way
Stop it
I think you get yourself pumped up
I did a little rush until you got a jump up
So time up
I gotta put the table on my back
To make sure that we win and break it back
Stop
Now let I know you in the building
Everybody may win in the children
We ain't gonna do the way
But more we gon' stop
Till we knock the bottom out of the floor
To the reader
We gon' make one thing real clear
So I'm a fucking damn right here
We gon' party like this
All these
So I'm a real patient
And a way more money
Just don't trade it
Everybody in the house
And you ready to party
And you know
Say it out
Out
Everybody in the house and you ready to party
Let me tell you something, oh, oh, oh
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop
Let's stop the lead out
Turn down the sun her wayей
Don't call to the alien's on the line
Let's take it all off, hold
Feel the bad pace to tools
So then I'll go through
Stop the肉 just singing
No one else
You're gonna hard to open your mouth
You know we been in hard
But what's taking the back up
And from the 20 yards
Pick on the ramps all
Give it up for the team
An some automanz
To the leader
We don't make one thing
We're playing real clear.
So I'm a fucking damn right here.
We go party like this all these.
So you know, there's an idea.
The way you're my just don't care.
Everybody in the house is really a part of the deal.
So you know, oh, oh.
Yeah.
Woo.
Oh, I love that.
I love that jersey Todd back with the vengeance.
Oh, each your heart, I'd black out.
Pete.
Yeah, really.
That was awesome.
I wish we had a better recording.
That was of course was an MP3 of an MP3.
I'm sure.
But that sounds awesome on speed.
Good.
That was good.
Well, that was good.
Wild bunch.
It was a good for you.
It was fucking great, baby.
Get him on the positive music network.
Cheers, Todd.
ASAP do definitely big, big, huge.
I agree.
I think that could be it's got everything big.
It does.
Doesn't it?
Oh, and you know, you're dancing right away.
Even me.
Yeah.
And you're not dancing.
I'm the honkyest white guy you'll ever see.
Did you see me dancing?
Yeah.
Woo-hoo.
Wow.
It's raining even harder now.
Yeah.
People would think I'm wearing the shower to get.
Listen.
There are a ton of other great artists that were played throughout 2006.
I'm not sure why we measured them by weight, but they were a lot.
And I couldn't fit them all in on this show, but we'll try to get another best of music
theme out before Adam gets back.
Also, if you like music, check out Love House Radio at Love House Radio.com, that's my
music cast.
I actually did a recap of the 2006 year on that show just a few days ago.
And if your parent or especially a father comes to the community for fathers and parents,
the daddycast, at thedadicast.com, like most ads, I can use all the advice I can get.
So, come help me out.
Adam thinks we're letting me host the best to Charlie with the music theme.
It's been a lot of fun.
And I guess we are nearing the satellite window, but always wanted to say that.
So we'll take it away and let PW do his mastery, but of course, subscribe to the Daily
Source Code at the DailySourceCode.pocho.com.
Thanks again, everybody.
We'll talk to you soon.
Bye-bye.
Another pot show pot guest, stick it in your ear.
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT Pot Show Media Network.
Controll your part in the show at btpotshow.com.