Delta Sierra Charlie 527
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass
In the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into the future
Interestingly, there's a small price back hit
Since I remember correctly the number is low
That pickup front to the manufacturer
Now I'll just get over it
Why do I miss this instrument
The carriers, these are Gabriel and Eccord
A shouts all together
One more, two more!
One more!
I'm calling the mixer
Fails all around.
I've heard that's me
Whiled for the deals
I like just as you were 7pm little late in the night
So I'm going to a place we get to dinner right quick
Holding doors, coming in full of the chair
When she sits in the conversations who likes at Morris and a gym
And I'm mentioning that I rips
She knows who I am
And I'm flat in cotton hair
I'm going to know who I am
I'm not even my ma, maybe not even my dance
So I compose myself for people my ego and check
Cause I'm having the time of my life
And it's barely starting yet, so give her a kiss
This is my cup of beer
I'm out of juice
And you like me, so let's have a little cup of water
We're up here to catch the two of you
You're out of juice, you're out of juice
And you like me, so let's have a little cup of water
So we live the cafe and take a walk down the beach
A little ice cream as we walk talk the tide
What's the theme?
To joke it around
We're in a brain and the same thing
So we're first grade
I feel like a kid again
She looks at me as miles
And I smile too
My heart's a kid, I'm a rink and naked
They can naked do
I love you in the morning
And in the afternoon
And on the beach it's sunset and underneath
The moon
The moon is not quite right
So I don't make my moves
We're walking home laughing
She decides to wear my shoes
We're out of front porch
And I'm looking for a sign
And she's playing hard to get
So maybe I'll stick my time
I look into her eyes
And I want to shoot that
I just give her a kiss
Just make her to bed for me
And I'm a new
And you like me
So let's go
Let's go
Make her party
Will let me
To rock the world
And I want to do it
Go
Just make her to do it
Yes
Yeah
Just make her to bed
Bye
So I'm leaning closely
Opened she won't back away
And I'm leaning a little closer
And she takes my breath away
I burn away
Slowly
First kiss in the way
I'm knowing like the bowl
And we're walking on those
Where it's going
A reach for hand
Open mind doesn't shake
I'm nervous to sound
So maybe that'll have to wait
But the butterflies inside
I'll run my fingers through her head
Brush it out for more hours
And tuck it back behind her head
The tent is kinda mom
And then your mind is really running
And she's looking at you
On a man you gotta say so
So you tell her
She's beautiful
But it's never right for her
Because she's gorgeous
Only sex is so much more than just the word
She leads a little closer
If she understands the word
She never stands
Who needs words
She whispers
We can make our consent
I miss it
When I miss it
You love me
You hide me
And you dislike me
When I miss it
Afterwards
They say it's the Sickest Sound
To Evercome From the Dorm Room
Well
It's from Illinois
For ourSad Boys
Let's have a little makeup party
party you can find that on the pod save music network um obviously there's some bits
in there that I recognize from a former celebrity big brother house made I think there's
a little bit of Leo Sayer in there you make me feel like dancing but uh I need to hear
no there it's a jam everybody how you doing this is daily source code episode 527 coming
to you from curry compound the curry compound I'm trying it out I'm just trying out different
names for size uh Scott uh sent that one and he said try the curry compound for a new name because
we've had curry kasa curry crib uh camp curry curry compound yeah curry cottage still has the
the real representation of of what this place is like although it's bigger than the other cottage
and the other cottage was the cottage you know what I'm saying anyway we got so much to do today
because I can do a full blown show today tomorrow I'm traveling to San Francisco so I'll roll
out of best of Charlie uh early in the morning before I leave uh or maybe I'll do that late
tonight before I go to bed because there's always plenty of stuff to do I'm sitting in total
darkness except for the windows which of course do shed enough light into the uh into the third
floor catacome here um catacome on the third floor I think that is an oxymoron uh the electricians
are in hanging up the chandeliers uh which is uh hopefully if I'm lucky it'll just be the
lights that go out and not the actual power because if the power does fail I'll have to pause the
recording because I'm using the uh the Yamaha digital workstation for all of my routing and pre-processing
all that crap I think I've saved everything appropriately now so if the power does go out and come
back on all my settings should come back otherwise it'll be very very unhappy little podcaster
oh my goodness uh where to start where to start let me start with last night or yesterday actually
I was in uh in London for uh good portion of the afternoon doing some meetings uh hang out with
everybody at the UK crash pad and short-itch which was uh fun as always and of course uh uh moody was
there uh he's uh he runs all production for pod show and he was in from the states crisper sheirs
was in except I missed him he left on Saturday to go back to uh the uh the boysy mafia he's from
Idaho um and uh let's see was anything uh just some some meetings where we reviewed some shows oh
dude um who's on it which is the the interview show that we have with OJ OJ Borge
and he had the shakes so I think the next episode which is coming up next week will be the shakes
fantastic interview uh waiting to see these they we had some toy instruments for them and uh
so they have oh you know you guys are so good why don't you try these out and they did and
was fucking awesome uh Rachel from uh in the attic he Townsend's girlfriend um and actually I'm
gonna play a song from in the attic from the new in the attic which is out uh what else did I see
I just you know with this stuff it's uh and and I have at least uh if I count them here one two
I have a whole bunch of podcasters who have joined the network who uh just want to say hi
world news mashup the news doesn't get any better now from our aggregator today's stories
orange continues around but love is the world situation as always is growing more and more desperate
but here's the really important news I just made a bundle with pod show hi this is Brian
no breaking character for just a moment here okay I haven't made a bundle just yet but I did just
sign an agreement making my shows such as world news mashup the no zone studio c and the frank truth
the most recent members of the pod show family of pod guests you can find them all on pod show
plus at noby dot pod show dot com that's n o e b i e dot pod show dot com and Adam thank you so much
for creating a kick ass company and for all the support encouragement and inspiration you give me these
past two years you are the best see you on pod show plus everybody
sucking up helps very good policy Brian just kidding man welcome welcome to the show
Brian has been we've been working with Brian for a while actually he's been writing for uh for
serious for serious satellite stars one o two for all the stuff we're doing over there and he's been
producing uh I just all kinds of stuff you hear him on uh on some of our d gap insertions for
for line line and for go daddy so it's a great to have him with his shows with his own creative
energy uh that he does outside of what we ask him to do to have him on the network welcome my friend
today by the way marks of the first time i'm using cast blaster pro um it's in beta right now you can
find it at cast blaster dot com uh in the forums and uh i'm really i was a little wary of installing it
because i have all of my stuff set up and and the main differences with cast blaster pro is it gives
you a lot more slots to put stuff in so i think i have probably 30 percent at least 30 percent more
slots to to cue stuff up and so i was kind of dreading going back and rearranging everything but
i finally did it uh so i've got what is it one two three four five six times what i have 24
slots for jingles which is really nice for jingles and effects you know the stuff like uh and uh yeah
that stuff and then i have one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven two
so i've and i have 24 slots for songs which and the buttons behave a little bit differently and you
can cue them up and stuff that's why i mentioned that uh but it has a nice big red LED simulated
read out for the amount of time uh recorded and uh i don't know if there's any other uh secret
stuff in here but i'm going to fool around with it but anyway the install one perfect i'm very
very happy with it and as you know uh cast blaster mic is working on cast blaster video and he wants
to expand the data testers group a little bit so again you'll find at the cast blaster dot com
forums you'll find i'll put this link in the show notes obviously uh so you can sign up to become a
data tester of cast blaster video it's a complete different experience if you if you're doing
anything with video if you're a vlogger or if you like to create well father rotary because using
it to put together his daily breakfast show um it's a it's very different concept then um then
any other application that's out there in fact it is very analogous to the way cast blaster audio works
you know you're doing it live in real time it's recording whatever you're doing um and uh well
in cast blaster audio we have a little bit of editing there but it's really it's really intended to be
pretty much alive on air type studio and with video exactly the same but the way it's done i think
you will love it i've had a blast messing around with it i've really had a lot of fun and once everything
is kind of set up here uh so probably by the time i'm back from Stanford Cisco and then give me
half a week uh to clean some shit up because of course this is the messiest place in the entire joint
when i get all that square away i'm gonna start doing some serious testing so again link to the uh
to your opportunity to sign up as a beta tester for cast blaster video in the show notes today
at dailysourcecode.com hi run this is Kendall if i want to please you find my brains off from
front lady box i just came out at chill world one what wait a minute no wait one i hear him talking
reading he never shuts his pie hole i think every mess with like the music that he plays
sometimes he's actually interesting to listen to so check out world's a link on world's a link
world's a way you know i really i really love it when you pimp out your kids
it to pimp your show for fun and profit use those damn kids
plus four four two oh seven six eight one three seven five three plus four four two oh seven six eight
one three seven five three not quite sure what number you would call if you were dialing in from
Ecuador. Adam how are you okay i'm Pablo from Ecuador it's 2 a.m. in the morning i was just
giving a message to say that you are giving us some thanks towards at this time uh
great work we love your show bye don't i ma calling in from Ecuador i think this is a first time
that we've had so on from Ecuador calling um and when he said thank you for giving us strength
i was like what's going on in Ecuador so i went to Wikipedia which as you know i don't trust it all
but for this kind of stuff i figured that you know the big fact should be there it seems like a
like a pretty okay country i don't think there's a dictator at rule in fact uh
uh um uh oh Fredo Palazzo took his place in Romanian office uh until the presidential election 2006
which did not produce a conclusive winner until a runoff election election on the 26th of November
elected Raphael Correa his margin of victory 57% of the valid votes was the highest in the
Democratic period or inaugurated in 1979 after Jamie Hymie Roldos and sixthowed Duran balen
Oh, man, what a name that is, huh?
Little place there between Columbia and Peru.
Fantastic.
Well, I'm glad I'm giving you strength.
I'm not quite sure what kind of strength I'm giving you,
but you guys got any podcasts happening over there?
Is there something I should listen to?
Got to send me a promo.
I'd love to hear what's going on
in the Ecuadorian Potosphere.
1, 2, 1, 6, 2, 5, 6, 3, 5, 7,
1, 1, 2, 1, 6, 5, 6, 3, 5, 7.
For those of you who knew to the show,
you want to use that plus and the one.
If you're entering the phone number for the feedback lines
into your cell phone number,
because they no matter where you are, no matter what cellular system
and particularly no matter where you are in the world,
it will work, no extra codes, no necessary.
I just put up with the plus one in there.
This next caller, I'm not sure what he was thinking.
My call is the most incoherent thing I've ever heard.
Oh, thanks.
Give him some library.
I am dirt case.
There is number one, number one,
your podcast is on different times of day.
Don't talk, give up when it's on changing.
And number two, show me $5,000, number three.
Wait a minute.
Was this the guy who was my best friend?
And he says, I own $5 grand.
To govern number three, what?
Ha ha.
I've been a new year of dirt case library, child friend.
So show number 500 if it's just from all for 500.
And now be the one to get used.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
What?
Travel friend, buy library.
Bye.
Now, do you hear that at the end?
I think it's Mark Yoshimoto.
Then, cough listen.
What does he say at the very end?
Friend, buy library, bye.
Bye.
That's the way Mark Yoshimoto named cough talks.
I don't trust it anymore.
Hello.
Hi, I'm Tom.
It's Kashihye from Shushu K.
This is Liberty News podcast on the P.T.N.
A little bird tells me that you're a closet celebrity news addict.
Don't worry, I won't tell anyone.
We can keep it between you, me, and lady Patricia.
So get your comfy slippers on, scrap the gossip banks,
and switch your sense out on his time for a fresh brew.
Thanks to Pot Show Network, you can have your celebrity picks
with your coffee fix every week, and no one will know.
Hey, do you still want to borrow my filletos this weekend?
Huh?
Oops.
Are we still on there?
Don't forget to check out Shushu K. Pot Show.com.
See you later.
I'm sorry, I forgot to act in that bit.
It's just you, Kay.
It's that there's an enhanced version of the Shushu K, which is kind of cool,
because the pictures then rotate along with the stories.
Yeah, I love celebrity gossip.
You know that.
I came home.
So I took the train last night, of course.
I didn't get home until about 940, 40, and so celebrity big brother
was almost over.
Ah, man, I love that show.
Ah, I'm in love with Cleo.
Cleo was this girl.
Who was on the Kenny Everett Show.
And she said she's 44.
I think she's probably a little bit older now.
But man, she has such a beautiful personality.
And, you know, and enormous hooters.
But she has almost like a perpetual smile on her face.
It's this gorgeous redhead.
Anyway, after that though, there was this fascinating show,
which I'd seen promo all week long.
And I think it was on, I think it was on either E4 or more
four, can't remember which channel it was on here.
It was called the trial of Tony Blair.
And the hypothesis of this really, it blew me away.
If it was some great acting, some great writing.
The concept was it's set in the future where Tony Blair has given up the
prime minister ship to Gordon Brown.
And so he's coming into office as the prime minister of the UK.
And he and, and Tony and Shuri is very, is very much like a reality.
I mean, it's not shot like a reality show, but it's showing you
behind the scenes.
So they have to move out of number 10 downing street.
And you know, you see Shuri bitching and moaning in this box is everywhere.
And it, of course, it was very much like anyone moving.
So I was very much into that because that was quite realistic.
Now, at the same time in this future, the president of the United States
is Hillary Rodham Clinton.
And what's happening is Tony is obsessed with his legacy.
And he, he wants his legacy to be anything about the war in Iraq.
And he's, you know, he's writing his memoirs and they're, and it's, you know,
it's really taking the mickey to taking the piss out of Tony Blair.
No doubt about it.
I don't know the guy and I'm sure he's much nicer and much smarter than he's portrayed
in this particular drama piece.
But what was really interesting.
The hypothesis here was that the international community
through the United Nations was setting up a war crimes tribunal in the
Hague, specifically to prosecute those who had started wars illegally upon
sovereign nations.
And of course, depending on which side of the fence you stand on,
you could argue that George Bush and Tony Blair are both guilty of war crimes.
And so that's the whole hypothesis of the situation is that there's only one more,
the United Kingdom can veto, can veto this, this tribunal being set up.
And so of course, you know, Tony Blair's own party guy, Gordon Brown, has to either veto it
or go ahead with it.
And they come up with this rules, which is really nasty.
One of Brown's advisors, they just make sure that the representative of the UN,
the ambassador who was supposed to vote and veto this tribunal,
they make him miss the vote by, you know, sitting in the bathroom and whatever it is.
So he misses the vote and the tribunal gets set up.
And then everyone turns his back on Blair.
The property price is crashed by 20% the minute he's out of office.
Yet labor votes are up by 7%.
It really is a scary scary notion if your name happens to be Tony Blair.
And I don't know if there's, if you're available, if it's available for viewing anywhere.
Excuse me, oh, I said, let's blend it up.
You know, I'm sitting down now.
That's the whole problem.
I want my stand up console.
Anyway, if your name is Tony Blair, then you should be shit and bricks.
I hope you can see this somewhere other than in the United Kingdom because it was really,
really good and well worth taking a look at.
Hi, Adam, it looks speaking.
You know, Adam, we forgot to do something last year.
Last year we forgot to celebrate that this might 25 year anniversary of listening to
Adam Kirris, crappy shows.
This is something I started listening to you in 1991 or something around that time.
Well, I don't have any champagne here with me right now, but I have a nice fresh couple of Finnish coffee
in front of me and for this occasion I took out the president blend.
So Adam, stop playing with your gold-eddy, grab couple of scents,
put some splendour in it and raise your mark to another 25 years of listening to Adam Kirris crappy shows.
Okay, so thanks for the last 25 years and I look forward to many more good moments of listening to you.
Cheerio vibe.
Hey, look, that's really nice, ma'am.
Look from Finland.
That's right, if you, uh, let me think.
How long have I been doing this shit?
I started on radio, uh, pirate radio in Amsterdam when I was 15 or 16.
So that would be 24, yeah, so about 25 years. Damn.
Well, here's, I'm raising a mug of scents sale to you, my friend, and I'm very happy to hear that
after 25 years of indeed making crap shows and totally talking out of my ass, you're still listening.
I really, really appreciate it. It makes me feel good.
I just wanted to call the call out, uh, the Dignation Boys on, uh, on their authority.
I was catching up on some Calli Lewis Geet Brief TV episodes and I ran across this episode where,
what is it, uh, is it Kevin? Is that his name? From Dignation, where, um,
well, maybe I should have Calli Lewis explained it, but it's about the iPhone.
And this is before the iPhone came out and he was on his show, uh, telling everyone exactly what
the iPhone was going to be because, of course, you would expect Kevin Rose, right? You would expect him
to have all the inside dirt because he's so incredibly clued into what's going on in Silicon Valley.
Well, let's see if that's true. Have a listen. Kevin Rose from Dignation, number 74.
I have a little bit of insight information on the Apple phone. Okay.
Two batteries. Oh, two batteries. No, sorry. That's not correct. Roger.
One for the MP3 portion of it, and one for the phone.
Just say something! Two capacities for an eight gigs. Okay, that's right. I think we're talking
2.49 and 4.49. Like a pretty big price difference between the four eight gigs. Flash memory. Okay.
Slide out keyboard. Eeeeeey. I got keyboard. That's fancy. Anyone doing tech is gets tips.
But Kevin has a reputation for getting some important Apple rumors right. Okay. So there you go.
So much for the reputation. In a world where disability strikes 10% of the population.
Only one man has the guts to take on the powers that be and raise his voice in a challenge to
media demigagery and the tyranny of the mass market. That man is Charles Rovira and he can be heard
at MSBpodcast.com.
And I'm a buncher. I do my business on the throne. I'm a sitter. I'm a standard.
I'm a left-right hender. It's nice to know I'm not alone.
Well, it's not exclusive to the US, you know. We've got scrunches and folders and all parts of the world.
Including the United Kingdom.
I had them. It's Chris. Analyzer. From the aircraft podcast right up here in an authorist of England.
And we just wanted to let you know how fired up we are to be part of the pod show family.
Hey, and don't forget BET pod show. Oh yeah, it was quite exciting to see how show listed in the top
pick section. So for those people that haven't heard of us, you can find us us airpodcast.podshow.com or
a podcast at BETpodshow.com. You say we couldn't make it any easier for you to visit us.
So drop by to find out what two people living very different lives talk about when they're getting to a studio.
Oh yeah, and we're both folders. I never said you were a folder. I did. I said to you you
fold it like that and then I'm going to fold again. No, you're more of a scrunchie. That's good.
Welcome guys. Great to have you on the network. Yep. It's growing. We're building. I'm very excited
about what's happening in lots of people coming up to us with very interesting ideas. So for this new year,
I'm going to be spending a lot more time in London. I will be shuddling back and forth between
London and San Francisco more frequently. I tend to spend a full work week in SF,
come back to the UK for two weeks, then go back for a week and really try and manage it that way
because it's just too much going on on either side of the pond. I got a, uh, a forward from
Google reader from what's, who is this from from Shayna? Who sends me a links from time to time,
which I obviously appreciate very much. And she sent me a link about the movie, Stomp, Stomp
the Yard, which of course, as you know, we promoted the movie, been promoting it for two weeks.
I told you I promised you would be the number one movie. It was number one movie opened up this weekend
over $22 million in box office receipts. But this seems to be some controversy surrounding
surrounding Stomp the Yard. And it's kind of a funny one. What's this? Is this going to fire
up some video here? I'm looking at what is this page? This is on MSMBC.com. So the movie is set in the
world of black fraternities and their traditional style of step dancing, which is a part of,
a lot of the part of the pledging process. And I presume that the, um, that a lot of this movie
was based around Alpha Phi Alpha. But what's interesting is that Alpha Phi Alpha did not give
permission to actually display their, their colors or letters or anything in the, in the film.
And a lot of Alpha Phi Alpha alumni are going to the movie, not being very disappointed. And,
yeah, so there's a minor controversy there. That's, I guess that's kind of good to have
controversy. You know what? It's much better than controversy. That's why.
I had a full coin here from Beach House to the masses. Just a little message to thank you,
and everyone at BT Parcho for allowing me into the network. It caps off a very successful
and exciting 2006. The Vinnie Volk in the podcast Live gigs at the Purple Turtle in Camdered.
And we've already secured a monthly spot there, which is very, very good for not only the bands,
but also for podcasting, raising the profile a little bit and getting them as recorded.
And I think it's kind of cat-off two years of podcasting to make it all very, very bizarre
and to start with. And only just coming into, to get into grips with what we can actually do
in this incredible medium. So, he's to a great 2007. And I'd just see you again too.
Bye-bye. BFM.btparcho.com.
Right on. And also, welcome to the network.
We've got another great show, which I believe is launching, I wonder if it launches this week
or next week. It's a podfinder UK. We've brought the podfinder brand back and we're going to
do a video version of podfinder in the UK for UK-based podcast. Josephine is the host of that show.
I think you're going to love her. She's fantastic. I mean, I'm not quite sure what we found her.
She's not an actress, but she's well into, uh, well into pod casting. Hold on a second. Let me
see if I can find her, uh, her profile page. Mm-hmm. It'll be well worth it, trust me.
I'll just go to pod show and I'll search for people. I'm still on that vote of phone, uh,
the vote of phone, quasi-broadband modem. It's doing okay. I'm still definitely afraid. I'm going to
go over my allotted one gig limit before the month is up. Thank God I'm going to San Francisco.
You know, I've already checked all the machines. Make sure that there's no automatic system updates
that are in place. Uh, Josephine. Oops. Don't you just love it while you're
taking your time while I miss type shit. Okay. Click on Josephine, search under people,
and there we go. Josephine. Okay. What's her pod show? Plus you are, uh, Josephine Lawrence. Okay.
That makes sense. Josephine Lawrence dot BT pod show dot com. Or Josephine Lawrence dot dot dot dot
pod show dot com. And, uh, and you'll find a link there to pod finder UK with as let me see if
it's on the area. Is it on the air? See if the first episode is up, which is pod finder UK dot
BT pod show dot com. But check out Josephine met. She's awesome. Uh, no, does not have any episodes yet.
So, but I can already see this stuff that's featured. Okay. You'll like it. Episode one coming
up today, I think, or it should be up before the weekend. No doubt about it. Uh, why was I telling
you that? Uh, oh, the reason was because, uh, she all does she feature in the attic. I'm not sure
doesn't even feature the show. Well, anyway, so in the attic, I've talked about the show before,
which is, um, Rachel Fuller, uh, it's her concept. Uh, she is, uh, long term long time, long term.
I hope she's long term. Long time girlfriend of P. Townsend of the who. And, uh, while on tour,
she had an air stream trailer completely kidded out and she would sit in the back and do interviews
with bands. And we've had some pretty good ones. Magic numbers, Zutons, uh, Krike. I can't
even remember all of them. But all top notch bands and Pete will come in and jam with them. And then
sometimes, uh, in fact, I think there's an acoustic jam of Michael Jackson's Billy Jean in the
episode number seven, which is also going up this week. And whenever possible, Rachel, who is a
performer in her own right, she'll do a song. And, um, in, in this most recent episode,
see, this is a little, I'm playing this directly from the video. She does this beautiful song,
uh, acoustic, she's sitting behind electric piano in the air stream trailer. And the song just
blew me away. Her vocals, fantastic. It's almost angelic. This is Rachel Fuller on the daily source
clip. Check all the rooms to see if you're home. And I close all the doors, because if I'm alone,
I can't fly. And nobody knows this secret is mine. When I fly,
my happiness shows all at the same time. You wouldn't believe the wonder of me.
Would you see how light is my heart, how wild and how free,
when I fly, from heaven to fear, in the blink of an eye, and I can fly,
there's space in through time, and everything's fine, in my sky, invisible wings,
and possible high when I fly. And nobody knows this secret is mine. I can fly,
my happiness shows all at the same time. If there's a place,
we're lonely in the streets, this angel will fall, without faith,
how can there be grace, but until then, I will fly. And nobody knows this secret is mine.
When I fly, my happiness shows all at the same time.
God is not beautiful. Oh, was this the end of the show?
I do hope you enjoyed. Oh, I'm in love with her. What a voice. Let me just just see if I can
find that piece, it was with the foi vans, is that who it was? I think it's foi vans, yeah,
home on second. We find the Billy Jean bit. You're going to dig this. It was here it is, home on.
Are you have to listen to this? Totally not pod save, but it's so fucking cool.
So it's Simon, Pete's brother, Rachel, and foi vans, and check this out.
People always told me, leave care for what you do, you can't go wrong,
breaking young girls' hearts, but she's still right by me, and I smell her perfume.
Started to consume her, she let me to her room, and all I love was, but that she was never my love.
She's just a girl who claims that I am her world, but the kid isn't like a boss.
Oh, I'm in love with her, I'm in love with her, I'm in love with her, I'm in love with her,
I'm in love with her, I'm in love with her, I'm in love with her, I'm in love with her,
I'm in love with her, I'm in love with her, I'm in love with her,
I'm in love with her,
This is done live with just a couple of mics set up in the in the back of the Airstream trailer
You really I'm telling you you're gonna love this show in the attic dot
Pod show dot com or in the attic dot
BT Pod show dot com and either one will get you there
This is a fucking awesome awesome show and we're
I think there's a meeting today over at Elpye, which is the who's production company
Meeting to get Rachel's music up on the
Pod team music network. They're gonna do a compilation CD of all the songs that is with all the artists
I mean towns and sometimes literally sits down and and you can see him with his notes
It's a new song that he's never played anywhere public before. It is really really awesome
All right, well, I'm gonna what is 37-minute 38 minutes perfect. That's well within my 40-minute time limit
I'm gonna cut it out for today
It feels like I have a little less energy on the show because I'm sitting down
I don't know working on it. It'll be a couple more weeks until my father-in-law can come on over and
Enhandle the power tools unfortunately so I just have to deal with it
So tomorrow best of Charlie for sure because I will be off to San Francisco Thursday morning
I'll bring you a show from the Curry condo
Adam at Pod show dot com the email address to send me any crap you want to and of course show notes for today's episode for today
Show with all links to everything relevant a daily source code dot com take care everybody
Talk to you tomorrow
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT Pod show media network powered by Pod show and lime light network control your part in the show
You