Many people believed in the early years of 21st century that the greatest threat to this
world was to come from the microbes and germs that dwell on the rim of the humble toilet.
As you hovered over the seat, which had once been his throne, man cast out with all his
might and all hell was spread forth over the cubicle.
Meanwhile, on their tea break, the sanitation service providers slowly and surely drew
their plans against us.
Delta Sierra Charlie, five, four, five.
60 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
I want my fellow Americans at the bottom end of the economic ladder.
And that's exactly what I'm going to do.
I also want to go to Washington to get some drugs and alcohol.
This background is shady, grew up lazy with the money from his folks.
When off to college, was a frat boy, did his shit load a coke.
When in the politics, block his death.
With his ears and his friend, one on election, the election.
Maddy didn't even win.
He doesn't even know who we are.
I think he's doing a shit job so far.
Mr. President of the United States.
You are worthy of these days.
He comes on the TV and he tells us that we're winning the war.
People like Paulie, they are asking what we find in Paul.
He doesn't listen.
Maddy keeps on. He's got too much to prove.
Well Mr. President, can you hear this book?
He doesn't even stop to ask why.
He just thinks Jesus wants people to die.
Mr. President of the United States.
You are worthy of these days.
Try and do.
Mr. President of the United States.
You are fucking up these failures.
What happened to the audio on DSC 544?
I have a plane vanilla Mac, iTunes 7, and a 30 gig iPod set up here.
And I noticed that playback from my iPod stopped straight after ped up sting and before
the guest intro today.
It was about 19 seconds in according to my iPod.
I fast forwarded over that and listened to the show.
And about 11 minutes in, it sounded like you had a visit from Crichton Wheeler,
the radio presenter who suffered from splices disease.
I couldn't bear to listen from my iPod,
and so I used quick time to play the show in my browser,
clicking on the link from Carried.com.
Peter was missing, and so was the splices disease.
Why was there no ped up on the link from the show notes?
And why did that version not have the silences and repeated phrases
that the iPod version had?
Inquiring minds want to know.
Do we?
That's Dutch for us.
See ya.
Yeah, thanks for calling that in.
We've received sporadic reports of the show breaking up
or skipping ahead or definitely being corrupted.
And passed it on to end to Grummit,
who is now, who can't see anything at the top level,
who's now into deep debugging mode.
Here's one thing we have narrowed down.
First of all, you access the link.
You probably subscribe to the show through,
well, that's a good question actually.
Through the US.
So you would be receiving your file from the US server,
which is media.potshow.com or something like that.
And I believe it has something to do with the insertion
before the show.
Now, from time to time, when players change,
and I know that iTunes underwent some change recently,
things can get screwed up.
It's very hard to replicate these errors,
but I think it does have to do with the add insertion.
So we're looking at that.
The reason why you didn't get that from the link at curry.com
is because me being over here,
when I select a link, it's going to be actually the link that I post up there
is my media.btpotshow.com.
And whenever, whenever I'm in the UK,
I'm going to serve you up the UK version of the file,
which if there was UK advertising,
which there wasn't in this case,
that's why you didn't hear anything in front of the show.
You get served up the UK advertising.
When I'm in San Francisco, then you get the US advertising.
It's in a whole nother issue by itself.
But I think that there is something, indeed,
that's changed somewhere along the line.
It seems like it's happening with iTunes.
But not consistently, of course.
If you witnessed this problem,
please let me know.
You know, with some cool news,
looks like a Potio may be entering the German market very soon.
So all of this sits in Pinkland.
sits in Pinkland is very topical,
because I need to have a little more than my
bastardized Dutch to German communication skills,
when I'm talking to really important people in the,
in the German speaking marketplace.
So maybe you could help me out.
I mean, so far, let's see,
that got this, what is this from Fabian Fry,
who wants to interview me over Skype.
He's doing his master thesis on podcasting.
And he says, unfortunately,
you didn't get the endings quite right in your German lessons.
Let me help you with the words written out.
So again, this is for those of us who are now practicing
the fine art of sitting down
while doing anything in the bathroom.
And so in German, which, of course,
the Germans have, once again,
that leading the charge on this,
Germans are sitting down to Tinkle,
everywhere in the world.
So that would be sits in Pinkland.
That would be the act of doing it.
In sits in Pinkland.
And this is, this is something that I could just say
conversationally, as I'm talking to,
you know, big network owners and,
and government officials,
that each Pinkland in sits in,
or if I'm giving a speech somewhere,
I could just say,
each being in sits Pinkland.
Maybe you should help me out with a couple other things, though,
just to make sure that I don't make a fool myself.
Natalie Dilkante,
host of pod shows technology news video programs.
Textrah.
I have written for PC magazine,
variety magazine,
market watch, and tech crunch.
Textrah.
What's Google up to?
What in the heck is Web 3.0?
Those are the kind of things we're going to figure out together.
Textrah.
Get your extra on tech.
Oh yeah.
At starts today,
first episode goes up.
Natalie Dilkante.
I found her,
when I was watching an episode of Cranky Geeks,
which is a great show.
CrankyGeeks.com.
I think Natalie still appears on the show,
at least I hope she does.
With John C. Dvorak.
She's now going to do a multi show,
multi weekly show for pod show.
I think you're going to like it.
It's very rare.
I find in television that you can find someone
who absolutely understands what they're talking about,
because they have the journalistic background.
Natalie has master's degree in,
was it,
she has a BA in journalism,
master's in philosophy.
I don't know.
She's smart.
And she's beautiful.
How often do you see that?
Well, I tell you one thing.
I'm trying to get more of that for you at the podcast network.
You know that.
Happy Valentine's Day to you.
Happy Valentine's Day, Mr. News.
Okay, Adam.
It's me, Brittany.
Oh, baby.
You know, you're second life girlfriend.
Uh-huh.
I know.
Now, I'm not asking for any diamonds or chocolates or flowers.
Oh, like I didn't buy you that.
You be honest.
I bought you shoes.
I bought you outfits.
I bought you diamond earrings and necklaces.
And I bought you a whole island.
I just want you to be my virtual Valentine.
Okay, baby.
Oh.
And would you wish Patricia happy Valentine's Day for me?
Uh-huh.
So maybe we can, uh,
yeah, hook up just a three of us.
Adam.
Yeah.
Now, there's only so long a girl can wait.
Uh-huh.
Besides, I don't know how many more times I can tell Jersey Todd.
No.
Happy Valentine's Day, Adam.
And I hope to see you on the island soon.
Oh, man.
Todd trying to wheeze in on my babes.
Sir, Jersey Todd, I never thought he would stoop so low.
Oh, my goodness.
Yeah, happy Valentine's Day to you, Brittany.
That's the voice that you know here on the Brittany Mason show, uh, which is an animated
second, like she looks so smoke and hot.
Again, someone who looks fantastic and knows what she's talking about.
Check out the grid review.
She did another show today.
Haven't seen it yet.
Brittany Mason show dot pot show dot com.
And oh, yes.
You've heard this voice before, right?
I've heard this voice before.
All right.
This is the prolific programmer.
Uh-huh.
Who I really like because, you know, I'll say something on the show and immediately
on his blog prolificprogrammer dot com slash blog.
He'll immediately throw up some code and say, OK, this is it.
I've done it.
You know, I'm just like, OK, this guy I think is, you know,
is becoming part of the show.
Although it's almost impossible to understand what he's saying.
He's worthy of a Jeff Smith jingle.
I think boob and ever at your command is the prolific program and revenue.
Hi.
And I'm from the sergeant, just go again,
your vision to DSC five for whatever was today.
I think it's I'd go for or where you said you are interested in my rising
U. A elementary debut row.
I'm gonna go by teaching you look.
prolific program you've got to slow down man when you're talking you've got to slow down take
your time can't understand what you're saying uh this is this is the bridge I'm trying to
gap there is so much difficulty for communicators to actually communicate and build things with
engineers it's difficult you know we're both of the same creative ilk yet we speak
totally different language anyway prolific program or what I asked him to do is look into the
guts of the Nokia N800 which is this internet tablet to see if we can use the existing
applications with some simple codes so that we can actually strap one of these babies on the
Trinity as she goes across the United States and further on her world tour all it has to do
is send back GPS coordinates pictures and regular intervals and if possible some video at a regular
interval I'll even I'll even take the video for granted if we can just get the pictures I think
all of the elements are there it just needs to be scripted out so he's taken my task to action
and he posted some code and and I looked at it and I say well it seems like a lot of the
variables still have to be filled in and that's what he's responding to here
right away described on bugging tree I thought it was a preliminary invitation on my blog just a
out of kind of what is to be done you know if this is all right also I'm not a UI person and therefore
I would I would appreciate if you would work with me on the UI as you what you want and what you
don't want I'm really I'm really not good about so let me know cheers yeah man I'd love to work with you
on this and everyone said home we're like how does he want what is that and we want to talk to this
guy because this guy's a genius I can tell if you call yourself the prolific program right you've
got some balls right there and I think he on a absolutely understands what I'm looking for
so you know I don't even think we need a UI that would be a prolific program or speak for
user interface certainly not a graphical one I mean just start this thing up on a command line and
lock that puppy down you know that's about all that's needed again it has to send back GPS coordinates
I know there's it knows how to talk to a Bluetooth GPS receiver I know that that's baked into the
N800 that has to it has to send that back continuously whether it's connected to a Wi-Fi network or
if it can't find a Wi-Fi network like say within you know within 15 minutes it should then connect to
some GSM phone through Bluetooth it does that beautifully by the way the device so that
I would you don't have to do anything there it'll just happen and then same thing you know the
built-in camera just have that little stick poking out of some metal box that we mount this N800 in
so it takes a picture maybe it's just a picture of the of the drivers you know the who's driving
the car at that moment or maybe the driver's seat in a little bit of the left-hand window
something like that will be awesome and if you want to give me code I'll be happy to run it and if we
get to a point where you know I think you're actually on the something I'll get you I'll buy you an N800 absolutely
ladies and gentlemen our new friend of the cha cha
thanks Jeff speaking of Nokia it's kind of interesting I went through I never thought that
this would actually affect me Dave Winner who I think I'll be careful in saying I think he invented XML
RPC it's a way for computer programs to talk to each other and exchange data and ask the other
computer to do something with it you know you're probably more familiar with XML RPC than you know
if you use ecto even if you use cast blaster it's a way for an external program to talk to
basically a web server like a like a weblog and say hey I'm gonna post something here and here comes a
here comes a description here comes a title here comes a media object which could be a video file or could be an
audio file so there's a lot of programs that uses and a while back I'm gonna say what like two
years ago an alternative protocol I think it's a is it a protocol or a format and I think it's
protocol an alternative protocol called atom alpha tango Oscar mic was developed
which does the same thing as far as I can tell and but it seems to do a lot more and it's
seemed very complicated now as a non-engineer I've been able to implement XML RPC across many different
devices and I understand what it does and it just kind of works and it's something that I think is
I don't want to start any wars here on the show but I think it is probably even more widely deployed
on an individual basis than XML RPC is more widely deployed deployed than atom but of course
there are some big boys who use the atom protocol such as Google and Flicker and Nokia has a
an application called the life blog which is really nice because you can take pictures,
write text entries, take movies and with a push of a button you can send that to a weblog that
under or to Flicker by the way that understands the atom protocol so they literally have
built in you know upload your your pictures to Flicker and you know with your associated life blog posting
I'd love to have that be able to connect to the pod show network think about it you know
Nokia could could turn on thousands thousands of podcasters to using their phone right out of the box
all it would take would be for them to implement the XML RPC protocol next to the atom protocol
and it's unbelievable but the answer that has come back so far and I know people are working on it
is hey we have already implemented the atom protocol it works with Flicker I don't see why we need to
build in another one and that's exactly the point that I never really understood what day one
it was talking about but now I do for us as pod show to implement the atom protocol there's no
knowledge of that in the companies as far as I know so we have to hire someone we have to you know
it's a whole separate development track it will cost us a lot of money whereas for Nokia I think
it would be a lot easier probably one engineer would you know take the same amount of time
for them to implement it on their side and it would work for so many people I mean it just it seems
like a non-brainer if if you use XML RPC then you can use it with thousands of of independent software
services and with the atom protocol they're definitely limited so I'm working on that but it was
just interesting to see that something that the day was talking about two years actually happened
and then it happened to me and those of you listening to the show on serious satellite stars one
or two well hope you like that information just see some guy driving around this car
just pick up truck bailers Adam talking about Adam what is he talking about bring on the sexy girls
I had him eight to see from Dublin and I'm just listening to life or four on a mouse and here
because you're after getting your essays wrong again and the guy from the north and wrong is
not seamless or Shiva which is what I thought when I heard first it's Jay as an essay
think of it's not like SHA why no yeah but it was spelled S-E-E-M-U-S
it's supposed to pronounce that as shemes so I mean he's names bad S-E-A-M-U-S of shemes
and all the other thing I want to say to you was the artist has been pronounced the
country which uses the most toilet paper per head of population oh this is fantastic news
I'm so proud to be in the United Kingdom knowing that Ireland uses the most toilet paper per head
in the world this is great news sorting to some organization called the European tissue
symposium so there you are now you can move on I know from post posties too and
the amount of toilet paper is a people use okay all right then keep this on really enjoy the show
scruncher hi hey of course you're scruncher darling that's why you guys are using so much
toilet paper up there I do appreciate your call and I love it when women call in it gets so
boring with all these guys after a while thank you darling uh Tony schemes uh sent me an email
a couple days ago he says add them listen to the old DSC this morning on the PDA in the mini
Cooper on the way to work he played a song from a guy called Paul Durham black lab good song
but I liked it better when garbage sang it and called it you're only happy when it rains
if George Harrison was shun for rewriting he's so fine then what should we do with Jeremy
I guess that's my sweet lord he's so fine folder city that's where Tony's from and so I shot him
back an email I said well dude have you played these two songs next to each other that would be a
pretty interesting experiment uh so fast forward a few days and AC took me about 15 minutes on the
old violin to put these two verses of songs in question together first verse Paul Durham black lab
of course second verse garbage I'm only happy when it rains this is the new black lab by the way that
right uh played on the show uh not only is the guitar very similar in the vocals and singing the
same medley but it's even in the same key the courses are also very you know let's just listen to this
you know I'm not really convinced now you and maybe if you had done a
closer mix between the two I don't know I'm only happy when it rains interesting
well maybe you're right I don't know but I really don't care I think black lab is something completely
different and I think it does sound very different and you know you're talking about some very
basic melodies here basic rock and roll structure you know everything does kind of start to blend
together after a while um and just like a computer code you know why can't you build one on top of the
other ah we're all out to get our good from someone for some reason I guess huh yes that I played
the pod safe music network promo and I couldn't for the life of me remember who it sent to
to me it was uh Wayne of the worlds of Wayne podcast worlds of Wayne dot podshow dot com a lot of
people wanted to uh grab the promo want to play it in their own show I'm going to play one more time
just you know what I'm talking about you can go find the worlds of Wayne dot com or worlds of Wayne dot
podshow dot com play safety play pod safety with thousands of songs in all genres the pod safe music
network is the best place to find truly pod safe music for your show if you're a band or musician
looking to expose your music to a worldwide audience then look no further than the pod safe music network
showcase your music and let thousands of podcasters help market your songs and the best part
it's all free visit music dot podshow dot com and create your free profile if you're a musician or a band
upload your music if you're a podcaster then download the pod safe music network is easy to use
but the huge variety of music find upcoming unsigned bands or music from the hottest in your major
labels don't get burned by copyright infringement and don't get left behind by the new media
play safe play play the pod safe music network music dot podshow dot com
so um I don't know whether you've actually got around to look in a go daddy dot com yet Tony
no you haven't known but oh so a bit bluesy you've been nice yeah all right
oh no I strongly recommend that you do have a look at go daddy and um I am in a position talk about it
any of all this there's interested in the net and have a look at go daddy dot com they've got email
plans traffic blazer to re-do it more hit there is hosting plans you can set up shopping cards get
SSL certificates and you know what they are they can tell themselves yeah there's loads on there
and if you type in the order code punky one into the space provided what's that Tony one
and how's that spell but you NKY one can you do that in the blue star no fair enough come on well
you place up and I'll do it bluesy there's a load on there and if you type in the order coupon
kit one I said there's loads on there and if you type in the order coupon kit one
into the space provided you can get a decent no 10% off
it's particularly good if you're in the UK oh yeah
because of them exchange rate baby
they're fine a bit they're little they're little they're gone so go to go daddy dot com
for all your internet and web hosting is yeah that's how we should do it yeah we first started off
with we call host endorsements you know which is getting your audience involved in
uh yeah turning advertising to content I guess is basically what we're trying to do like
folders yeah how many messages a day I get people now saying they're no longer a scruncher
of folder but they're a folders yeah it's amazing it really is same for for splendid you know
people still stand standing in stuff the gofers do it all the time but you know the the
bridge like oh don't really understand what you mean by a host endorsement and that of course
because they really don't have that legacy uh the BBC as far as I know it's always been commercial
and the commercial stations here do have you know it's like spot advertising it's uh 32
commercials uh and even some shorter ones I think they have like 10 or 15 second pods I'll do
as well for 118 118 dot com but really I think they're actually rules against it
I'm not sure I'm sure someone will be happy to read me the off-com rulebook but I think they're
getting on to it now that was pretty good of course you you you you want to use punky one
let me don't even think of using DSC 3 you know I wouldn't want to take any credit for it where
I didn't deserve it hey Adam this is Dave from the Dave's lounge podcast over at
Dave's lounge.com I heard you mentioned on the DSC a couple weeks ago that you wanted to get
a Nintendo Wii for the curry manner and as someone who owns a Wii myself I can tell you that
definitely is the right choice it's a really cool console I don't I don't have a whole lot of games
for it yet I just have Wii sports and a couple of the virtual console games and those are pretty
much kept me occupied but the other thing that's really interesting about the Wii is the web browser
now of course the Wii as you know has built in Wi-Fi and you can download a web browser that's made
by opera for the Wii and it actually does a pretty good job at rendering pages the thing I find
most interesting about the browser though is that it comes with a built-in flash player now it's
an older version of flash slash seven so not everything out there works but it sounds a lot like
the same functionality the the Nokia and 800 internet tablet has it also uses opera with a flash
seven player is the the Wii isn't running Linux though is it I don't think it is but it seems like
a flash nine is coming very soon so that's your change I have poked around a little bit and I
discovered a few games that work and I discovered a few animations that work and I've discovered
that YouTube and Google video both play through the Wii web browser in fact I actually find that a lot
of my online video surfing these days is done with the Wii I found a number of BBC documentaries
on Google video and I've actually watched them through the Wii on my television set the quality isn't
stellar but it's very watchable and this got me to thinking if it's possible to play back video
on the Wii certainly it would be possible to play back audio right I mean think about it here you
have this console that's connected to your television it might be connected to your home theater
system as well you know you are so preaching to the to the choir here this is exactly why we have
pod show set up the way it is not perfect yet but we're getting very close because the same
information we're now exporting to IPTV which is a set top box version of television on demand
the same version is being ported to a mobile platform with flash and and by the way something that we've
been working on you've probably seen that we now have embeddable videos at pod show I'm pretty
sure that the way to go forward is whenever you upload a video show or an audio show for that matter
that the way you play it at pod show will be in flash so there'll be some shit going on in the
background and whether it happens on your computer or on our computer that's still up in the air
but it'll also be made available as a downloadable file almost like a feature you know if you
subscribe to the show you're going to get it as soon as it's up and if you go look at the show it
may be almost instantaneously but it kind of depends on how much horsepower and how we can figure
that because there's always some transcoding that has to take place but this will make it available
to any multitude of platforms because that's really what it is the web and flash I think the flash
web is probably where is where we're headed next although very very complicated because the technology
has now far outstrip with Ajax which as you know is what makes a lot of these web pages so interactive
with stuff like flash you know the metrics of paid views are blown to bits and it's you know there's
a lot of shit going on now with how stuff is measured and I don't think much of it really is
very accountable the one thing is accountable the we're doing is I like that is we're actually
sending customers who buy things to our advertisers door that seems to be working very well
advertisers like that by the way but yeah man I think you're right on the money absolutely this is
it's where it's going to go no doubt about it and whatever device is handy at the time just like
I'm using a multitude of you know it's like Gmail for me I use it on my phone I use it on my internet
tablet I use it on my PCs I use you know a lot of the stuff that is web based on any on any
device that happened to be using at the moment so absolutely that's where it's going Adam Curry on the run
lady Patricia here this is why he avoids Holland do you hear me everybody's looking for you
talking into the fucking microphone or get off my show I think you should I think we should I think
we should take it all the way I think we should say that I would divorce I'm living in San Francisco
you took all the money I have to change my location I'm still paying lawyers and accounts
and you just bought a new car and I'm in San Francisco in a broken down we're saying it's
300 turbo diesel station oh I'm very sorry to fucking say if anyone needs to find me they know
how to find him Adam I'm sure you'll come come on over here and get it boys
Mark on the linder how fuck you that's sonder podcast studio dot on our great production dude I love it
the curries on the run we're on the run they're trying to find us we're hiding out we're on the
lab my friends hey those of you down under have you ever heard of the what the Kembera times
this journalist sent me an email last week and it was like I want to interview when you're available
it was a pretty rude approach and I was like well you know what do you want well I want to talk
about actually I should probably bring that up and not paraphrase like that hold on that wouldn't be
very very fair of me let me just you know it's just one of those approaches that I really didn't like
and I have a point to this come on Gmail see there I am pontificating about Gmail and it's
taken forever to find this here we go Jenna okay my name is Jenna Price I'm a report in Australia
when would be good time to call you what is your number please a little bit straight forward I reply
hi Jenna how can I help she says I want to talk about why podcasting worked for which publication
I send back it was in the subject field the Kembera times which is the broadsheet daily in
Kembera Australia's national capital apologies if you already knew this but so many people don't a little
defensive there ah then we go assuming you feel like talking about podcasting good time for me says Jenna
730 or 1030 pm your time working I can contact you so go back and forth anyway so I talked to her on
Sunday and you know she's like how old are you 42 oh you're just a baby so how old are you 51 okay
you have a daughter I thought you were English thought it was English well yes I am can't you tell by
me I'm an accent that I'm from Manchester it turns out she hasn't listened to any podcast outside of Australia
but not even mind she called me up to interview me and she hasn't she didn't know anything about me
and you know this is such a respected newspaper and this is what all with this is why and I was
contemplating saying I shouldn't do this interview but you know I just don't do many of them because I usually
get disappointed by what show it shows up particularly from a so-called intellectual newspapers and I'm
sure you guys are going to correct me or let me know if the Kembera times is worth its salt or not
but you know and she just got into all this stuff but advertising and I explained in this
it but you know how can you ask these questions if you haven't even made the effort to listen to
what we're doing oh you have a company frustrating so let me know when that comes out
and let me know what you think about this Kembera times if I should have asked you beforehand actually
my bad and of course I will not judge the fine people of Australia based upon the genna
Kembera got an email here from Pete Hopkins Adam heard the interview spot you aired my song
I won't cry a couple episodes back when to thank you so much I'm totally digging this shit
I didn't exactly write that but I know what he says if you if you plan on spinning me again
before Saturday the 17th I've got a show coming up I'd like you to promote well yes Pete I'm going to
do that for you because I you know people have been sending me it doesn't happen often
people send me emails and I'm talking about maybe 20 people who said that Pete Hopkins stuff is unbelievable
I would have just the one of the first songs I really like that you played so here it is Saturday
February 17th at 930 p.m. in cranes Hollywood tavern that's famous cranes Hollywood tavern
1611 North El Centro Avenue that's between Selma and Hollywood Boulevard in Hollywood
California 9-WO28 free admission free show to come on out and have some fun let's check out some
options
as it does kick ass this has become from the pod save music network
my life's in this array is the way I feel it's just the way I feel but I wouldn't have it any other way
life has a funny way I think it's what they're saying yes what they're saying
her surprising you each and every day so let me sing this song and it won't take long for the
melody to wash over you and me then we can sing this song as a day is long and let's
learn the melody to set you free and it goes learn the la la la la la la there's a little more to learn from every
learn the la la la la la la no one has had the answer over
oh
just be not and become
boom yeah
so many things to do is the time enough and never time enough you need another year just to get it done
it's hard to overcome a fell on dreams yet live on dreams but happy human still we must
become some let me sing this song and it won't take long for the melody to wash over you
and me then we can sing this song as a day is long and let the melody set you free and it goes
learn the la la la la there's a little more to learn from every one
love love love love love no one has to have the answers on their own
so be loved there's to be stronger you can laugh away the pain like I've ever listened to the
song and we can sing this song and it won't feel wrong to let the melody
wash over you
learn the la la la there's a little more to learn from every one
love love love love love no one has to have the answers on their own
Pete Hopkins become from the pod safe music network and you can find the link to pizza page
at daily source code dot com of course you can always go to podshow dot com slash music we got our
spotlight page yeah you can see all the different genres what's being played in each individual
genre genre genre yeah yeah i'm just looking at the artwork for today show it's a beautiful
widget sent in by was it ben ben cast i think who keeps making great artwork for me it's a it's a
mac OS X OS 10 widget and i just went back to my email because i had a conversation with a guy
Scott who created this daily source code widget and he wants to sell widgets to podcasters
and uh like yeah this awesome dude and then uh i got him in touch with Andrew grommet
and he uh showed him how the api works so you could basically tie into your collection
at podshow plus you could just log in uh and up would come your channels you could just play a
channel right there in a widget and i haven't heard back from us like i don't know if we overloaded
it with information i was just looking back at the emails you said hey i'm not a developer but i'll
fit with it see what i can break i hope you didn't break himself looking forward to what you're
gonna come out with Scott all right everybody so uh oh that's not bad for a Tuesday show um
tomorrow will be valentine's day and uh damn it if i'm not gonna get the lady Patricia on the show
i wrote so you know just so you know i'm gonna get her on the show it has to be for tomorrow
and maybe you could send in a voicemail comment because since she never listens to the show
let people know how much i love her because maybe if they hear it from usual believe it
then i sourcecode.com adamoodpodshow.com take care of yourself everybody i'll talk to you tomorrow
bye bye another podshow podcast stick it in your ear
the best of the brightest sub duct daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering podshow and limelight