This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
The show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
The show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Whereup?
Delta.
Serator.
Five, eight, nineer.
In a world where TV networks, movies, studios, and record labels still think they can govern what you see in here.
One man has the power to return control of entertainment to the masses and make big media corporations
wet their tiny little pants.
From Poncho, polled up the world's most dangerous new content comes the daily source code with Adam Curry.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Do the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky drinks.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Autistic.
It's Adam Curry.
To take your phone so long, it was just as long way.
So long, it won't make me feel like you were once dead.
To take your phone so long, it was gonna save me.
I've never seen you again.
I've come to see you again.
We have so much to come and deal with.
We used to talk about all kinds of things.
I remember everything you said to me.
You made some problems with such things.
God keeps on being okay.
To take your phone so long, it was just as long way.
So long it won't make me feel like you were once dead.
To take your phone so long, it was gonna save me.
I've never seen you again.
I've come to see you again.
To take your phone so long, it was just as long way.
So long it won't make me feel like you were once dead.
To take your phone so long, it was gonna save me.
Something about the hand flap, it's almost like a child girl.
Just face.
Arthur Eurea, someone like you just is lonely.
This guy's got a whole mess of songs in the pod save music network.
And I listen to every single one of my, I think I added at least three to them to my special playlist
because they're all just that good.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
It's a daily source code coming to you from the Curri condo in Northern California, San Francisco, California.
It's episode number 589.
And man, what an odd deal to get ready for the show these days.
So I'm so definitely afraid of the headphone earlobe that I actually, I got to take a picture of this.
I stick like gauze with medical tape underneath my earlobe so that the headphone just can't rub against the sensitive, my sensitive areas.
You know what they are ladies, don't you?
And I was thinking it's like I'm like I'm ramming a tampon in there and then hit me.
That's actually what I need.
The tampon will be a great idea.
So tomorrow I'm going to try it.
And I think I need like the, the obese won't work.
It has to be like a tampax.
It has to be, I don't have to do long enough, but just something like,
and handy with a string I can wrap it around my ear so it'll stay in place.
Oh my goodness.
Good night.
I'm my host.
This is the right message service because this is a generic message.
I'm Darren from Melbourne, Australia.
I'm first time calling a long timelessness.
Quick coming about your headphone in your ear infection.
There's just a good chance that there's a bunch of bacteria on the headphone care.
And you just get some effect of those different things in life.
And keep them, completely clean.
And then you might not have much more.
Okay.
So it's over here.
All right, man.
All right.
First time call us or let you slide.
It was just so nice to hear from somebody down under again.
It dude, when you're driving your car or as you would say,
when you're back in the youth, that's not a good time to call.
It's very difficult to understand.
But you made a good point there.
And this is something Yvonne Patricia Sister even called to say.
And she said, you know, you really got to disinfect these pads on the earphones
because if there's any just dirt or bacteria or nastiness on it,
that could be causing the problem.
Absolutely.
But right now, I'm way beyond that.
You know, I've had pain.
I've had suffering.
I've had an operational procedure take place.
Oops.
Hold on a second.
I can see the virus softwares scanning.
That's not a good idea while you're recording.
I never really caused any problems.
But why invite Murphy into our lives, huh?
So tampons.
I'll try that.
Now Arthur, you're a by the way from the Houston, Texas.
Born in Chicago.
Great stuff.
Love it.
It's a hand clap song these days.
I'm not quite sure what it is.
So I'm late.
It is now.
What is it?
It's 1215.
Very late for me to be doing the show.
It's been going so well.
Of course, we have another, uh, savant.
From my circle of savants as I end the Sultan of said savants.
I'm going to talk about, uh, a very current topic.
Uh, excuse me.
Tylenol P.N.
Check out unwind and GB's show sponsored by Tylenol at unwind.podshow.com.
You will not regret it.
To why am I late?
Well, I've been promising for.
Oh, man.
Weeks that I would do a Skype interview with Eric Bergen.
Um, who plays Bob Godio in Jersey Boys.
Of course, uh, if you if you listen to the show, you know that he got me a ticket.
I want to check out the show.
I loved it very much.
And now the things are runaway success.
And I just can't say enough good things about it.
Really enjoyed it.
But we've never actually met.
He does a podcast called Green Room Radio.
And his mom does a scrap cast.
She does a scrap book, um, podcast.
And we've had a nice little email back and forth.
But he really wanted to interview me for his show.
And of course, I want to comply.
But, uh, you know, he's working a night doing the show.
And during the day, I'm working, you know, just to, you know,
to sit down and and do a, and interview, it's just hard to schedule that.
Particularly just when the other week's and out here is really busy.
So he's been sick for the past couple days.
He's actually been, uh, performing every single night for six months.
I think something like that.
And to some of he's, he had a throat ache and bronchitis.
And he wasn't feeling well.
So he, he took some time off and he deserved that.
And so yeah, so you know what, why don't you call me around nine o'clock.
I was working on all kinds of stuff.
We have a board of directors meeting tomorrow or today.
Actually, when you're hearing this, you know, we always look forward to that.
It's a great moment for us to check ourselves.
So we're going through, uh, through our regular, uh, quarterly procedure.
So it's busy.
I said call me nine, um, and he does.
And we talk for an hour and a half.
And I did know he wanted to do like, it's like, it was like,
it was almost as if we were doing an episode of this is your life.
But I kind of got into it, you know, and of course it was most of the energy that I intended
on spending on this show and it went into that interview.
But it was good at the questions and he really went back and he, uh,
and he had done his research, his homework and, uh, I appreciate that.
So, you know, we just talked and it was, and you know, he said he wasn't going to edit it.
And, uh, we were just having a very nice conversation the way that it works in, in our medium.
There's no rush, no rush for, you know, we don't have to hit any news break at the top of the hour.
We ever bought it.
And I told him, because, you know, I've been, I know what, so let me tell you what I told him.
But look, I had an erotic dream and you were in it.
And anyway, I just mentioned that, you know, me, I just mentioned that during the course of the interview
and he kind of like brushed it aside.
And the reason why, of course, is because I've had his name in my mind, you know,
thinking about, I've got to hook up, you know, I, I,
things I have to remember, I can put in my brain.
I remember them, they bug me and they keep popping it in my head.
So I was probably just having an erotic dream period.
And then his name popped into my head, whatever.
I don't know, he's not a bad looking guy.
And I'm just salacious.
So anyway, so we're near the end of this interview.
And his girlfriend walks in.
I would just, and he sent me this piece of the interview.
So I'm sure it's going to be on green room radio soon or, or as soon as he edits it,
I'm not quite sure what he's going to do with it.
I'll put a link to that in the show notes of daily source code.com.
But here's how the interview ended when his girlfriend answers.
Oh, actually, he's knocking on the door.
I guess she doesn't have a key.
And well, listen, you'll have, you'll have some fun with this.
Sorry about that man. Go ahead, what were you saying?
You got a booty call, didn't you?
I was my girlfriend walked in.
Told you, booty call.
Is she, is she moved with you for, is she goes with you?
Travels with you?
She's in the show. You saw her. She plays Franky's wife.
Oh, man.
She was in my dream too.
She was, you were an Adam Curry's dream.
Yeah.
But so you Eric, so I don't want to know about him.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh God.
Tell her, tell her, tell her.
I told her, you were, you were in the dream.
Put her on.
She's coming, come here.
What's her name?
Jackie.
All right, you can, you can hear?
Hey Jackie.
Yes.
First of all, I loved you in the show.
Oh, thank you.
And listen, how good is this?
Am I slick or what?
What I forgot to say is, I really enjoy your work.
Because that's what that, that's show business.
I forgot to say that part, but I really loved you in the show.
I mean, so I'm getting ready.
Really?
Well, I'm sure you heard it, but I was so blown away by just by everything.
Really, but you guys were fantastic.
And I just wanted to make sure you understood that I had this really weird erotic dream
about you.
And I didn't even know that you were a couple.
And it was really sexy.
Adam, I'm curious.
You have to tell me details immediately.
Would you be in that kind of thing?
Immediately.
Now, did you just hear what I heard?
Maybe the Skype connection wasn't good, but let me just replay that last little bit.
Would you be into this kind of thing?
And she says immediately.
I mean, tell me I'm wrong.
I'm curious.
You have to tell me details immediately.
Would you be in that kind of thing?
Immediately.
Wow.
I might get upset, but I definitely want to know.
So we're going to be in LA.
Maybe we could all kind of hook up in Los Angeles.
Absolutely.
That'd be fantastic.
And I could tell you about my dream.
Yes.
I guess we can't do that now or be a whole different kind of show.
Oh, man.
I'm going to have to...
Eric, you got to send me this recorded me because this is kind of like my show.
No, I love this.
This is rare.
This is...
I'm going to use my mother calling in with something.
Oh, wait.
I'm going to reveal that that's just awkward.
No, no, no.
We don't want mom getting in the way.
Yeah.
God.
Adam, I need to go now.
Oh, man.
You are so new to show business.
No, I'm not.
You mean...
You're just having me now as when the show gets interesting?
No, but didn't you get the handbook?
It's like we're all supposed to like sleep around together and stuff and do drugs.
And that's kind of what you're supposed to do in show business.
That's just me, man.
I don't know.
This...
This all has to go through Frankie Valley.
Yeah, go Jackie.
Did you hear Jackie in the background?
It's the scene, man.
Oh, yeah.
Look.
It's like we're all supposed to like sleep around together and stuff and do drugs.
And that's kind of what you're supposed to do in show business.
That's just me, man.
Yeah.
I don't know.
And this all has to go through Frankie Valley first.
Yeah.
I have to contact Frankie regarding everything.
Okay.
We'll give him my regards.
I will.
All right.
So this show is so successful that now the San Francisco cast after they're...
The show is going until September 30th.
So new cast is coming here.
And then this cast is going to Los Angeles.
And so Jackie and an Eric will be there.
And of course we've got business in Los Angeles.
I hope after Friday we may have a...
Well, you should listen to Green Room Radio.
I talk about that a little bit in the show as well.
So again, we have a Savand coming up.
We're going to be talking about a...
A news item.
Okurant.
But first, I wasn't even going to play this.
You know, Tokyo Dan called in a couple days ago, beginning of the week.
Basically complaining about two things about the positive music network.
And it's right that, you know,
our transaction system is weak.
But of course, you know, we are giving all the money to the artist.
And it was the best thing we had at the time.
And we really shouldn't review that and look at...
Look at something new there.
And he also said, our search sucked.
Just true.
But we're also working on that.
But it was a little bit of fence within me.
Because he said, you know, we've built this on the backs of the artist.
And now we have enough content.
Now we're fucking them.
We don't care anymore.
And that's such horseshit.
So, wasn't going to play his reply to that.
Word not for a brand new listener who called in to respond to Tokyo Dan.
So here's his second comment, which not really focuses on the money.
And then right after that, you'll hear the, a new listener from the Bay Area,
who's, who's, who's raising with his comments.
And some really smart, nice ones too.
Hello, Adam.
Tokyo Dan again.
How's your headphone earlobe?
Well, I must got microphone mouth because I still have some things I want to say
and response to your comments about my feedback on DSC587.
I agree that the pod show plus music section has really been upgraded,
but for listeners.
And we all know that advertising dollars chase audience.
But on the other hand, what's good for listeners is probably good for the artists.
Therefore, the artists are getting a lot of spins.
But are these spins actually turning into dollars for the artists?
There's probably no way to tell, but I wonder.
Maybe the most popular artists on the PMN are selling some CDs,
but I'm concerned for the artists that aren't so popular,
but still have some fans that like to buy the artist's music.
And for a lot of non-Engly speaking artists,
the PMN is the only way for them to easily,
and the keyword is easily, sell their music digitally,
to listeners in other countries.
But if the artists can't easily get the money that they are owed from the PMN,
then there's no incentive for them to put their music on the PMN.
This leads to my last comment.
The one I made about you are not caring about the artist
since you successfully built the Pod Show Empire.
Well, maybe I was harsh, and if I'm wrong, then I'm sorry.
But you have to think how it appears to me.
I have seen no progress on the Pod Safe Music Network for ages.
Maybe there's a lot going on behind the scenes,
but it's not apparent to podcasters and artists who have been
dilling of the PMN for a long time.
And in me, it seems that you haven't teased for gotten about the artist.
And I can back this up.
Go back and listen to DSC498.
On that show, we're comments similar to mine about the problems
involved in artists getting their money out of the PMN.
The comment was made by an unhappy manager of a popular ban on the PMN.
Well, I contacted that manager,
and we sent a few emails to the Pod Show about the problem,
but nothing ever happened.
So there you go.
Oh, and I'm not sure about this,
but we might have contacted PW about this also,
since that ban made his theme song,
and PW has a direct route to you.
Well, I want to say more,
but the microphone mouth is getting the best of me, so I'll leave it at that.
Hi, my name's Pam.
I'm a listener from the Census of Aary.
I was just listening to the ESC and Pod Get In,
and I'm about the PMN.
So my understanding was that the Pod Show Music Network
was all about artists making music available
to Pod Cats to be able to play those music.
And from my perspective,
it doesn't seem like it matters very much,
whether it's a good search interface or whether the
click-in-vide stuff works as well as it should.
It's a real value of the Pod Show Music Network
seemed like it's in the licensing agreement
and in the ability to use Pod Cats
thing as a way to promote music.
And I think it's unreasonable to think
that there's no value to an artist
just because search doesn't work as well as it could.
When it's enabling,
that doesn't seem like that's the value you're supposed to be getting
supposed to be the ability to have their music played on Pod Cats.
And you know,
you want to have a better search interface
for spelling music you should go run on iTunes.
And if you don't want to have Pod Cats
to play your music,
then you shouldn't be putting music on none of the PMN
of whether you want to sell it or not.
So that's all I see at some thanks.
I love that.
Thank you so much because I could not have put it better.
Tokyo, Dan, you don't be focused on the music sales.
That's never what we've been about.
It's been about the marketing of music
and exposing audiences to music.
And we've been very successful
that that continued to support it.
And really just the, you know,
the sales party,
we were able to do something.
It's not completely perfect,
but it's not our core business.
And he's writing.
If you really want it to be perfect
and segregated by country and easy for everyone,
then you need to do it through iTunes.
So let this be the end of it.
Please.
So tired of this.
By the way, Eric Burger just sent me pictures of his girlfriend.
Jackie.
Oh, oh, oh, man.
She's 28.
James Marino, Adam listening to the daily source code.
Do you see five, eight, eight?
I noticed that they,
I thought I noticed that they sounded the same
so I put them next to each other.
Last, I don't sound the same,
but they're phrasing rhythm are the same.
What's this about?
Ah.
Subject of the email.
Is Alec Baldwin,
Josel's boyfriend?
Okay.
I don't know who this is,
but stop fucking calling Josel, asshole.
I want to say something okay.
I want to leave a message for you right now.
Okay, I get it.
This is another link I should put on the source code.
Show notes from a Sinclair much.
Ah, there's a politician in,
let me just read you this.
Tanya Dervo,
leading candidate for the Senate of the
Nae Party and EE in Belgium.
Ah, has campaign posters of her naked.
It's like under political party right there, boy.
Adelia.
What is that?
What's their platform?
It's a nice platform.
The official campaign involves billboards,
featuring her in all her naked glory with a very seductive look.
And the text,
I promise you 400,000 jobs above her.
Wow.
Yeah, I bet you do, baby.
Okay.
It's a time for our savant from our series of the circle of savants.
Is I in the sultan of said savants?
Savants?
Right after I give you some important information,
because I'm working hard here.
I can't have you guys crap out.
I need you to call in, send in stuff,
and let me just give it the phone number.
On the phone with us now,
a true savant who I've known for,
I think, just about a year now.
And he's a savant in many ways,
because not only is he,
I believe, a yoga instructor.
He is a DJ.
I'm talking like in the club like,
you know, wheels a steel type DJ.
And he is also,
but the hell are you, Mark?
Are you our finance director at Podshow?
I'm the VP of finance at Podshow.
How come, though, you didn't get a CFO title, man?
Did you get jipped?
No, I don't actually.
VP is probably more purpose-wamen than CFO does too much work.
That's actually too little work.
At this level, CFO just sits around
and tells everyone else what to do,
but at a startup company,
you actually need someone who actually does work.
Mark Cierra is our VP of,
of finance, apparently.
He does basically take care of all financial matters.
And I got to tell you,
I've worked with a lot of financial people in my life.
And you would rarely wind up in a club with them,
just hanging out,
let alone having that person be in the club,
spinning the records.
Which, I just thought-
What are you doing yoga?
Now you are a yoga instructor, correct?
Yes, I've been teaching since 1996.
Oh my goodness.
Mark, now we got you,
we adopted you after you will recommend.
I think it came through our investors.
And they said, this is the hired gun.
This is the guy you want.
He's going to set your shit up straight.
You've been in the valley for a while doing this type of stuff?
Yeah, actually grew up in the Bay Area.
I've been working with high tech companies since
it's kind of embarrassing to admit since 1985, actually.
Yeah.
Took the startups.
And because I was at Apple for seven years,
and been working doing self-employed for ten years,
and I've been in Pot Show since August of 2005.
So, what made you actually want to hang around Pot Show?
Because you could have left.
You could have gotten out while the gun was good.
Well, I, as you may,
I came over from referral from quite a perkins.
I've been working with a couple of smaller companies.
Prior to my project.
Oh, and I was with self-employed for ten years.
Up to that point, and just, just, you know,
talking to, you know, to run, and then, you know,
hear about the story, and the team of investors,
and kind of what Pot Show was doing at the time,
and the future, I remember this,
over a year and a half ago, just sounded really intriguing to me,
and, like, the team definitely liked the space at the end,
and, like, entertainment and media,
and thought it would be crazy enough for me to join.
Well, we are very happy that you, that you did join,
and we're glad that you're still hanging in there.
I know you're going to leave us one day eventually.
But, fuck, I'm going to go back to,
what are you doing?
Playing hoops later on today?
That's right.
Hoops.
Correct.
So, what's really, you know,
why Mark is, is in the circle of the sabons,
is, you know, I really enjoy talking to him at the office
about all kinds of stuff, and, you know,
the topics are very quite a bit,
but when it comes to finance, Mark really knows his shit,
and he has the added advantage of having worked at Apple.
So, there's this big new story,
and all I read in the press and online,
everything I see on television is, you know,
evil options back dating, you know,
kind of this meme of bad corporate governance,
you know, and interestingly enough,
on the same day that Apple announces,
it doubled their profits to $770 million for the past quarter.
And the one thing that I don't read anymore
is what an option is.
You know, everyone's talking about this.
I mean, you can turn on the local,
the local, the local, the K, whatever news,
and, oh, options.
And you have just anyone understand what an option is?
I mean, Mark, could you give us a synopsis,
just so the Charlie listeners who were out there,
who would like to maybe get a refresher course,
just know what this is about and this option thing?
Yeah, I see if I can break it down here.
So, basically an option is the right to buy
some shares at a certain pre-determined price.
And the idea of being that you lock in the purchase price
of that at a later date or the same date,
which you can have definitely happened,
you can, you will make money on what's called the spread.
So, if you were to be able to purchase the shares,
it's a 10-dollar share,
and either that day or months later or years later,
it's at the current stock price of how the option is trading,
it's at 30 or 40 or 50 dollars,
then you'd make the difference as profit.
So, I think there's many shares as you own.
In the dot com days,
which actually the story is from, I think,
2000, 2001, options were used as an incentive
because you pretty much knew any company that started off,
that was public, that went public even better.
The share price would go up,
and if you could lock yourself in, as you said,
then you would stand to make a nice amount of money.
In fact, that's where a lot of the dot com millionaires came from.
Was this always used as an incentive,
or did options actually stem from something else
in the past before the dot com hype of the turn of the century?
Absolutely.
So, options, I mean, when I worked at Apple,
this was pre, it was pre, you know, dot com maybe.
This was pre wood when you worked at Apple, man.
Yeah.
It was Apple's 89 to 96, because it definitely was options,
but it was nowhere near the menu,
because Apple was posted,
so there was no, you weren't going to be getting options at,
like, five cents a share and being able to sell them,
and like, like, $200 a share later on.
But, clearly, you know,
even as a public treated company,
there's still lots of fluctuation,
and still way for executives to make, you know,
to paying him any shares, your options, you got,
you mean, hundreds of thousands, or potentially millions of dollars,
things went the right way, which they did for a lot of people.
But it was always an incentive-based instrument, clearly.
Absolutely. Yes, I was incentive.
Okay. So, what, what actually happened here,
and what, what is the story about?
Because you, you, there's one thing,
and so I understand that you can say,
all right, we're going to, I guess,
grant you set amount of options at a strike pie,
so if, if we did that today, I would say,
okay, you're going to get some options at today's strike price.
We're not a publicly traded company,
I'm kind of, some number that's on that,
and then you have the right to actually buy those,
and get the spread later on.
Take me back to those days of, of the dot com hype,
and, you know, when options were basically the currency that,
companies were using to bring in, quote,
smart people, or, that's another word for high price people,
that really didn't cost all that much in it.
Oh, definitely. Yeah, definitely not.
So, so back in, back in,
this time in terms of the, the startup company is basically the option
to be priced, basically any, you know,
10, basically 10 percent of whatever the,
the A or B or whatever they most current round
does it basically price the up to 10 percent,
you know, basically this 10 percent of that,
and obviously there was a lot of money to,
made later on when company would get acquired
or go public at a much higher price,
and whatever the A or B round was,
you know, so right away, I mean,
even if it didn't even use the soldier's shares at the,
at the round price,
you didn't make 90 percent profit just on that formula.
So what happened here? What, so there's the X CFO,
I guess Fred Anderson,
it was investigated by the SEC,
and he says, well,
these options were back dated.
Just explain the back dating to me for a second.
Yeah, so basically on back dating,
is what you're doing here in this scenario,
is you're saying,
we're going to set the price at a date,
a date further back from when the work,
you know, when it should have been based,
and the idea being that the price was a lower on,
on an earlier date,
and therefore there was more money to be made on the spread.
So it's basically what it refers to,
is taking the option price date further back,
and then it should have been.
So without,
without incriminating myself,
I'm pretty sure that,
because Ron and I ran a public company
back in the day,
squeaky clean, I might add,
but I certainly can remember conversations
where we would say, oh, look,
now our stock price really didn't do much for two and a half years,
so it was all kind of a mood point anyway.
In fact, our stock price,
we came out of went from $7.00 in a quarter
down to three.
I was very, very successful IPO,
but we did turn the company around
and I think when we sold it,
the stock price was in the 50s.
But the idea of, you know,
well, you know, we talked today,
but you know what,
we'll back date these options to the beginning of the month,
or something like that,
which may have,
I don't know if we actually looking at the stock price chart
at the time,
maybe I doubt it,
it was all kind of underwater for everybody anyway.
But it seemed like it was a pretty common practice,
where there are no rules against it.
Well,
I just wasn't as closely followed by,
you know, the, the SEC, I think,
and I think,
you know, I was,
since kind of the,
the surveillance,
obsolete kind of stuff.
It came result of, you know,
all the corporate scandals of the,
like say,
Andrew, I'm for example.
Yeah, so all the stuff is being much more close to monitor.
I mean,
suppose there was monitoring,
and it was relatively loose,
and they really try to clamp down
on some of these kind of practices,
where they just basically are,
you know,
giving much more,
income to these executives,
not doing any more work.
But, but Mark,
it's not just executives.
It's also,
it's employees, right?
Absolutely, but it won't work.
It's everybody,
but the thing that gets the attention,
of course,
is the executives.
I mean,
that's the one that really pops out.
Yeah,
agreed.
It is everybody,
but the one who makes out the most,
the guys,
the one that gets the publicity is,
is it going to have,
like,
when we're working here,
and we're more money at stake.
Okay,
so that's not,
now you mentioned Enron,
was stock option back dating,
did that contribute to the Enron collapse,
or,
to me,
this really has no other effect,
than that shareholders may get pissed off,
because,
well,
they're greedy,
it just has greedy,
everybody else, I guess.
Right,
because Enron was not about back dating,
back dating,
it was,
the one that seems to be getting the most attention,
as you mentioned,
it was really this,
this current case with,
with Steve Jobs and Apple.
You worked for Fred Anderson,
the CFO,
who was accusing,
or I don't know if it's,
it really is an accusation,
but what he basically,
an unfair phrasing said is,
look,
Steve Jobs knew about the back dating,
it happened,
it wasn't,
Steve Jobs didn't make any money off of it himself,
which I believe,
I'm sure he did it for however,
the new hires were,
or whatever,
you know,
they needed an option pool,
they needed to make it attractive,
it could have been any number of,
a factors like that.
What are the implications,
what does it say about Fred Anderson,
first of all,
maybe you can go to some background on him,
and,
and what does this mean do you think for jobs?
Well, I,
I want to be real clear about,
I,
I've worked for Fred for about his very first,
couple months there at Apple,
because I,
I was there,
I left in 1966,
and he was coming on,
in fact,
I was actually one of the first people
they ever met at Apple,
because of the time we were raising
a convertible debt,
funding of $650 million,
and that came in,
he came in with the CFO,
around the same time,
the new CFO at the time.
Who was that,
Emilio?
That was Gilimilio,
and,
and the contingency of the,
the investment community,
issuing the $650 million
that was the new management team,
being Gilimilio,
and Fred Anderson.
So let's just say,
by the way,
this all happened just around,
that,
you know,
so Steve Jobs came back and saved the company,
it sounds like they were pretty
dire straits in 1996.
Very dire straits.
It's basically,
uh,
Gilimilio has been very well documented
in some of the,
you know,
local high tech articles,
uh,
70% down in the S&D.
Jobs came in.
I'm going to say,
97-98-time chairman
as you mentioned,
just totally turn it around,
the stock price more.
I mean,
more else,
afternoon.
I mean,
just like pretty much every level.
And obviously,
as a huge impact,
financially,
market capitalization,
employees,
and obviously the iPod came later on,
and that's been its own kind of,
massive hit and its own right.
But,
.
So what,
what was right?
department and on sent a road really nice guy just just
been a brief pretty pretty pretty humble duty came over from i believe a
adp at the time
uh... just yeah we just we just sat in his living room and
kind of went through some of the stuff you know this is a four cast
just in the guys living room talking about half a billion dollars you know
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah you're in the lotus position right
spin in some uh... DJ chiesto tunes
exactly exactly yeah well at that time yeah i was just starting to do you get that time
actually so uh... yeah so just look really really nice guy and had a lot of
credibility coming into company and seem to can't keep his uh... and knows about the
fray and during during his whole time they're actually pretty pretty
solid reputation through the industry and i believe he's now with uh... the
elevation partners
the cc from jk believe it's well that's uh... you choose uh... you too with
bono exactly so uh... you know mark you know me well enough by now we found out
a bit and whenever a uh... multi billionaires and dire straits i love to come to
his rescue into his defense uh...
it did steve jobs do something really illegal in your opinion
well that's a talk about not being that close to the nation and it's hard to
say i mean
so i i guess the question is how much did you know when did you know it and uh...
or you know how to stuff that we can go straight to that because essentially
what front Anderson said if i understand correctly is steve jobs new about it
and you proved the uh... the back dating of the uh... this is like it seems to me
like Anderson did a big
either a cover your ass or perhaps a saviour ass deal with the cc by implicating steve
jobs that's what i'm getting from the media is that really what this is
if that's the case and yet if this uh... is this what is what is what is
fray is saying is true then uh... and clearly uh... steve something he's
going to be a little bit of trouble
and it may be even a lot of trouble
doesn't know that so
quantify that what kind of trouble
uh... basically knowledge uh... what kind of like maybe i kind of
market steward trouble right where he'd got a new something was going on and uh...
was was was complicit with uh... unknown uh... price that wasn't uh... that's
it shouldn't have been and when it had was it anyway we have maybe i don't
maybe some sort of you know
kind of equivalent of the collection inside of information thing where he might be
like like trouble like might be a pretty big sign for example
maybe so well that's interesting i'm glad you brought up martha steward because boy what
of what uh...
how that would be very interesting if uh... if what jobs is implicated of
you know got him in a lot of trouble but he didn't have to go to jail he could
buy it off whereas martha steward could have certainly paid
paid off any fine equal to the crime and she actually you know went to the big house
she actually because but on a pop culture no initially enough actually
part of the great thing ever happened i mean that much credibility now she has
uh... with her minions
i mean she's got a whole new audience people because she found she's got like
street cred or something she was not just doing doylies
she was doing doylies and she was doing doylies on the slamer baby yeah
yeah and a way that you know for more than you know
came to the side bigger and more i mean it's an interesting enough right because he would
i could have been worse than ever but uh... as a pop culture thing it's
i think it's made her more intimate more famous and i don't know
but i don't know i i personally kind of think it's cool for
it's a weird way she's not a very happy person so
she's not a happy no she's not this is just a general she's got a few
husband along the way we had we had an office in the same building in New York
years ago not a happy person but she can turn it on when i want to keep you
life so she can't oh yeah she's a professional so
i can't finish it so it jobs could be in the in real trouble but this is where it
gets interesting because uh... shareholders
who are the ones that are that the only ones i think in this whole game who can be
really pissed off it's not like this affected
the quality of the products in fact it probably made the products better because
people were incentivize and they were working their ass off to get the stock price up
and make the company perform better et cetera um i'm sure that uh... although
i don't have any documentation back at up i'm sure that this didn't only go to
executives but it probably there was an option pool
and it must have gone to other people as well who also of course you
lead lead the company um if they were to remove Steve jobs
or hurt him in some way that he couldn't perform his CEO duties for apple
that could actually have the adverse effect and it could really fuck up the company
because you know here's a company that just doubled their
they're profit in a quarter and this ipod as you mentioned is is you know the whole
just they're on fire right now so is this
you know is it a good thing for having worked there for seven years
yeah having worked there for seven years i mean i was there very uh... michael spinner
millio john scoli all these big name none of them could run that place none of them
i think during the ten year of all the three folks they destroyed more shareholder value
then uh... and the jobs with the with the fucking options right
incredible yeah so yeah so he's making out like a black abandon but at the same time
so is everything first is invested in out of the years during the time when he was the
CEO before he left back in the uh... the real eighties or since he's been there since
the late nineties very interestingly enough
so what do you think what's going to happen what's going to boil down to
i think he's just going to get a new i think he's just going to borrow part of the
body in his way he's going to display patience small uh... some small being relative
because the guy is by a multi-multi doing her but he'll pay a fine and get his way out of it
that's kind of my personal opinion so he should do a meacolpa and he should say okay look uh...
different times fucked up uh... and then well uh... here's fifty million dollars i and i think
it would be between fifty and two hundred and fifty million probably somewhere in there
and it's enough it's by not a big of a deal for him
it's not a scene
it's just wrong uh... it's just gave me the willy
right that you're on and part of it's part of it makes America great
so so the question is if uh... if you were to find yourself in uh... in uh... in uh...
anderson's position and uh... and run and i said look it's okay just back
date these things what would you do
with you guys yeah
oh man
i would uh...
i'd be hard to do man
it'd be hard to do okay you fired fuck you
by it i know it's the
and the open shit you know uh... all right marvellous night i appreciate you
let's see unless you're not here to really good deal inside or something you know
yeah i'd see all these guys man
always ready always in for a little game on the side i love it
will mark uh... you care my people i take your people yeah
look we're really happy to have you uh... on board man and you keep our shit together we
still have money left
we still got a bit of money left we're not okay cool so well we're working hard to fill up the
coffer and you know you've got a great team you've got to
john the hammer who uh... and uh... sendy lindi hopper
who by the way i've noticed the neither of them listen to this show so you might want to
you know have a little chat with them about that
it's a quanny any raise yeah yes
if they want their options back dated they should be listening to the show damage
actually particularly this particular this episode
all right mark thanks a lot man uh... appreciated and uh... i'll see you at the board meeting tomorrow
you gotta go
have a good night
you too buddy
day
dark
Tell me I know I need you to know Sometimes now or forever I need it to say in the impossible way
Sometimes through my window I want you to show how everything that comes
As long as I'll use the right and if you want me so You better tell me so
Because I want you to see the call of me that can let go Let me know
I need you to try as long as going by Sometimes now you'll need to
I never can say the way I wanted to say But do you ever do you?
So tell me I know I don't need you to know Sometimes now or forever
And if you want me so You better tell me so Because I want you to see the call
of me that can let go Let me know
Can you see the story that is Can only bring you down
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
But day after day I'll stop and say For 10 years maybe
Is it me all looking for?
I need it to try as long as going by Sometimes now you'll need to
I never can say the way I wanted to say But do you ever do you?
I want you to show how everything that comes
As long as I'll use the right and if you want me so You better tell me so
Because I want you to see the call of me that can let go
Yeah, I know I've played it before this week
And help it, it's such a happy song Makes me feel good
Fire aims, let me know
We'll have to save music, not work
Of course, the link to that fine musical band
In the show, no, it's a daily source code dot com
Just one quick thing before we end the show going back to Tokyo Band and Dan who was basically
Telling us how much we suck and that there may be stuff going on behind the scenes
But it's not apparent to artists according to Tokyo Dan
Yeah, sure do need you help
Well, you know, we haven't been sitting still entirely that Tokyo Dan if you
Tenant over to curry dot com, you can see in one of the blog posts
All the ideas and the war room and all the stuff that's been going on
We've been working on helping ourselves suck less and we've got some special stuff coming up
In the next couple of weeks that you can really help us out
With the mission of sucking less
That's it, I got to get out of here. I'll talk to you guys tomorrow
It'll be full bar Friday. I'm thinking no savant, but let's just rock it out with some music
Just a full show of music
So I need your suggestions and let's really let's make it flow
Let's have a great show that you're going to save on your iPod or whatever the hell you use
And you're going to just just to feel happy you're going to pull that episode up again
So more music less talk everybody
Daily source code dot com Adam at podshow dot com
Take care everybody
Stick it in your ear