You better be careful out there on next couple of weeks you hear me?
Let's close the room.
No.
Two sides.
Some more later.
You better be with us.
I can be with the nearest one family.
All the places you've got to come to my place.
I'm done with you!
Walking Phoenix, Mark Wahlberg,
on October 12th.
Get down!
Two brothers collide.
Maybe you could be killed.
Right?
We owe the night rated a heart.
Flare prop.
Delta, Sirator.
Six, six, eight.
In a world where TV networks, movies, studios,
and record labels still think they can govern what you see in here.
One man has the power to return control of entertainment to the masses
and make big media corporations wet their tiny,
tiny little pants.
From Pod Show, comb of the world's most dangerous new content
comes the Daily Source Code with Adam Curry.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplay,
strapped to my ass.
To the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic.
It's Adam Curry.
We owe the night rated a heart.
We owe the nights rated a heart.
years and he's got it in his little lots of claws and straight say say this and the
all-star jam as DJ loves to do so himself not since USA for Africa has such a
collection of mechastars been assembled for a musical cause of course acquired
from mash of town dot com the official mash-up supplier to the daily source code
after so number 668 coming to you from the west side of G-town in the affluent
suburb of seri known as gilpert in the curry manner
oh what a way to start off the week huh I felt really good I was really old school
we used to make stuff like that with cassette decks and using the pause button
he even has a real ending to it
okay the track of course say say say Paul McCartney Michael Jackson
a couple of friends along for the ride including Paul of course reanna nelly
frittado nine inch nails marie jay blige diner rosrick james and the temptation
saying hey everybody how you doing it is the daily source code it's a
Monday it is Monday afternoon I was intending on being in the London office
but the trains were all messed up there was some some anomaly on the rails
not quite sure what exactly has happened I've been looking at the BBC news
website seem to find out and things so far so well I kind of wait to see if
it clears up and if I'll go in and all I was like perfect I can do I can do
a source code because this morning I really took some time to catch up on email
of course I got back yesterday afternoon from the portable media expo
I left the swanky shareton was around 233 o'clock drove down or where drove east
down whatever drove over to Los Angeles to LAX and hopped aboard the trusty red and
white virgin Atlantic and it was good good flight now a lot of turbulence
actually the first two three hours of the flight but I kind of like that you
know it kind of makes reminds me that we're actually flying and that it
happens to the big planes too that's kind of nice and it was good and you just
to kind of decompress and chill a little bit because I had meetings right up
until I left and you know there's so many people that I didn't get to see
this year which is unfortunate but of course I only had you know like a
really a full day and then or no yeah like a full day and then half a day and
a lot of people didn't show up until Saturday so that made it tough pdf was
there pdlb fenton didn't get to see him I also heard that the the buzzout
load buzzout loud seen it's a podcast of undetermined length I listened to
that almost every single day I really would have wanted to meet those guys so
they weren't there but it was good I have to say in all pretty good show not
necessarily you know for the expo itself you know I did check out the
award show and and one of those parties and it was the the room was just
way too big for what was going on you know that was just a theatrical mistake
if anything so not that big a deal and of course next year the show is super
agent Keith yet's getting pretty busy because of course tomorrow are the
digital musical awards if if you haven't read it on curry dot com the plus is
now live we've got our pre DMA coverage running and this is really it
well I'll talk about the plus in a second and the digital musical awards
first let me tell you what happened when when I came back yes today so you
know I'd slept maybe four hours on the plane something like that and you
nothing too spectacular so you know a little bit groggy to say the least a little
bit jet lag of course it was only a four day trip out to Chicago then
you know to California and the from California back to the UK just a quick
turn around all in a week's work so it's okay I really want to take a shower
and wash my hair I hadn't washed my hair in four days you know we're
hair people so that that was just disgusting and so I'm in the shower and you
know I've washed my hair and you know our shower it's look these English
houses they're just not really tall in in the right places you know then I have
the ceiling height that I need their idea of a of shower space can differ
sometimes from that of a Yankee doodle dandy so now I'm taking the shower and
literally I'm so tired I'm leaning against the wall with my with my forehead
kind of like so it's kind of like in the corner between the wall and the glass
the showers there my cheek is pressed up against the press up against the
glass door and just chill on you know the water just running all over me and
I'm you know kind of you know vibe there and I I was probably under that nice
warm shower of love for 15 minutes maybe 20 just you know completely in my
element completely coming coming down from the trip cleansing my my outer and
and inner self and all of a sudden I hear Patricia like screaming and she's
running up the stairs and he's like what's wrong what's wrong and she's she's
like completely freaked out and she's thinking you know it's like there's
something wrong and I'm like and now so I'm pressed up with my cheek against
the against the glass and well here's what happened unbeknownst to me you know
Christina sometimes uses our shower and she had left all kinds of crap
all kinds of products and the lid of something I don't know what the hell
it was but it was a really maybe it's like a thing that's inside a lid of a
jar of some chemical compound had slipped on to the drain of you know of the
shower and so the water had come up and it started to overflow through the
through the door you know there's lots of lots of once it gets high enough
it can basically seep out now it's not that high to begin with so I you know
I don't have my glasses on and I'm vibing against the wall there so I didn't
notice it but water was literally streaming down into the living room into the
the the the den that we have downstairs which isn't really a den yet but it
still has boxes and all kinds of stuff from the move and the water is just
streaming down and there's water everywhere and Patricia is convinced as she
walks in she's convinced that I've passed out or you know something is gone
incredibly wrong and I you know and I'm just shoved up against the wall there and
she thinks I've had a heart attack or whatever and the water you know it's a
tip but it's a perfect scenario right you're sitting downstairs and also in
the water just starts streaming down you walk upstairs and there's your
husband's cheek pressed against the glass you just convinced that was a
garner so that was so that was like a freak out you know and I'm like
what was it going on and it was it was a mess it was like Niagara Falls coming
down that was really really bad now there was a silver lining to all of this
because in the in that den room there were a couple of boxes on the floor and
because the floor was just completely wet they were getting wet so and one of
them was marked books I'm like okay I got to take these books out so and these
are you know some of my my favorite picture books you know coffee table books
and underneath it is a jewelry box and Patricia for a while now she's been
telling Christina and I that she's convinced that there's a box of jewelry of
hers that was stolen somewhere in the move and of course that was the jewelry box
so I was really lucky because that really turned Patricia's move around
I imagine now she's been in the shit for almost two weeks one of which I was
gone even more than that actually with the the kitchen floor being redone
and all kinds of stuff happening and all kinds of dust and a big mess and I
was you know finally perfect and I came home and the candles were lit and
everything smelled nice and the whole house was nice and there I go and and
ruin a good vibe so needless to say no sex yet comic strip comic strip
comic strip so it's always good to come home to your friends hello Adam
hi everybody so I am your friend you know it so take what I will now say
notice criticism or here comes wishing well Adam yes you are sliding into
cannabis induced psychosis that may end up in your death oh no suicide through
some irrational dehumidness cannabis makes you susceptible to various
conspiracy theories absolutely they have their own
superstitious agendas that you don't fucking know cannabis is destroying you my
friend increasing your psychosis stop taking it ps yes comparing comparing
not American free trade agreement to European Union is a total bush complete
idiocy existence of European Union is a garanter of peace amongst its
members and americans should shut the fuck about it oh man okay yo yo yeah
who's high now yeah I didn't say the North American free trade agreement I
said the concept of the North American Union that's something completely
different of which of course NAFTA would ultimately play a part I'm not
I don't want to talk about that stuff on today's show the word enough comments
about it anyway kind of shot that word over the weekend or Friday I should
say let me think oh yeah this is excellent so of course you know I've been
on my rampage about the TSA division of the homeland security department the
transportation security agency or is it administration I think it's agency
and you know a lot of people sending me links and stuff and there's lots of
comparable stories and all kinds of nightmares obviously that go on and
I'm sure that was going on with airport security even before 9-11 but the
fact that you can't you know yell and bitch about it now without going to jail
kind of makes it like no fun you know and from the pod safe music network
there's a most awesome song that really puts me in a good mood about the TSA
who by the way you know what are they using to open up my suitcase these days
fucking crowbar I mean the zippers all ripped off and shit and this is a good
bag this is a to me bag it's hard to destroy those but oh yes they've been able
to do it this is Robert Lund part of the funk from the pod safe music network
there must be 50 ways to lose your luggage the problem is all the new
increase security that's what the oh here bag it's service set to me we
think you're gonna back since you took out your money there must be 50 ways to lose
your luggage I said again it must take rumples of your files I should wish
my missing bags received their frequent fire miles no doubt they've earned a
trip to the Polynesian Isles with all your 50 ways to lose your luggage 50
ways to lose your luggage just if the sky cap jack agreed to get
bump gump board in the dark mark or try to fly free got too much weight Kate
alright with the gate leg just make the crew cross Ross and get your bags lost
ooh pack too much shell mail close them with locks knocks fly when it's snowy
Chloe or boarding good sea that's gonna be snags bags so don't push your back
cuz I've got a feeling lean your stuff's in New Zealand
why must it be the most important stuff they lose I wish that carried on my
clothes and check the pills and boo I thought well I'll pour this place and just a
pair of shoes we'll notice anyways
I streaked through town to some policeman shouted halt and I believe he mentioned
something about a sexual assault and then he cuffed me but you realize it's really not
my fault it's cause there's 50 ways to lose your luggage 50 ways to lose your
luggage just pack lots of fruit new check it online climb fly Christmas Chris you
poor SOB if connections are tied dry or you're buffed to a night fly have fun in L.A.
gray your stuff's in bomb bay ooh pack too much liquid dick what joke about bombs
time carry on mace grace then lose your ID bring cans of rain jade
and then run when they're x-rayed if you're lucky just thinky twiggy it's shot to hell
regulations any piece against love unattended when we take it out to the torment and blow
up by me so I really hope it happens Robert Lund 50 ways to lose your luggage right on
fantastic I believe under the the parody clause that's allowed on the podship music network
but you can get sued for anything I guess cancha so it is a big big week for us here at the
London offices BT pod show where starting today actually it started this morning we're covering
the 2007 digital music awards we're doing that in conjunction with a launch of the plus the plus
tv dot com which is you know this is really a brainchild there you go I wrote up a document actually
I posted this on curry dot com I wrote up a dot you know maybe I want to just read to you what
I wrote a bit easier here you go I in September 2006 I wrote an internal poncho document there's a
link so you can actually read that a described streaming video station my underlying thought was a
vision of what MTV might be today had they chosen to stay on their core path of short form video
which today would include top youtube hits podcast episodic series and a healthy dose of talent
with an attitude we made a few different choices in our technical implementation but otherwise
came pretty close to the original concept over the past six weeks we've been testing the system
slowly scaling everything up in preparation for her prime time launch 72 hours of coverage of the
2007 digital music awards this week oh yeah now gone of course big props to Lisa Aaron's who is
pretty much single handedly implemented the plan borrowing resources from anywhere she could
stealing where she had to my personal thanks to everyone from the San Francisco HQ BT pod show in
Vincent's crew who have put in months of long hours of work to bring this project to fruition
what else do I say here our backstage past coverage of the DMAs has already started and
includes some familiar faces from our network and the fun is just beginning oh well from today
onwards you can discover great shows music and videos on the plus 24 seven live no jive
so yeah that's and it's interesting because we sent out a press release I think earlier
last week and there was quite a vibe about it people at the expo talking about it and everyone
seemed kind of excited and you know I've been watching it since early this morning and it really
you know actually let me see what's playing right now because you know now we've added
basically VJ segments we've got to OJ Jill Mills, Dr. Cockney I know Natalie Delcante is in the
London office right now doing some segments we're going to do it all throughout the
digital musical awards we've got our own private party area right near the red carpet
actually I've pressed play now come in isn't starting with the hell is this okay here it goes buffering
and you know and it's just basically going to keep going okay what's playing right now so we got
we got the format is really what's most interesting to me is we're setting up an automatic format
we just fill in all the stuff that that runs through podshow dot com it's a great way to
get exposure and if you look at the the plus tv dot com home page you'll see that it's really easy to
click into that particular piece of video whether it's a single clip video or whether it's a music
video or if it's an episode from a show you can click through it you can get archives and of course
you can subscribe to it so it's kind of cool I don't know what is this that's playing it's like
two bunny rabbits beating the shit out of each other cool it's a very angry music videos on this
thing I like it a lot though I'm just going to keep talking for a second see if we hit a VJ segment or not
cry probably not anyway so we'll be covering the digital musical awards you can check it out
live we have hope well it's the same video stream that you find at the plus tv dot com you know we
got to see if it's a second or a promo this is brand in the podshow intern super music video show
so and it's a great way for me to catch up on stuff because we produce so much and we have so many
different producers on the network that it's almost impossible you know to be looking at stuff
so now if I just keep the stream running in the background eventually I'll see something that I like
or I'll see something that I know I should be looking at that very cool very very excited go team good job
Jesus we've got part two of our star wars the force unleashed feature and you can win
copies of juice too for the Xbox 360 that's all on games rezoal tippy found at gamesrezoal dot
beatypotshow dot com excellent math thank you yeah so just one more thing about uh about the plus tv
you know I this so if you look at it what I'm hoping you'll see is that you know this is indeed
the path that MTV could have taken and then maybe they couldn't have even have taken it because
there was a really weird gap where music videos were ubiquitous and you know it would have been
very very hard for them to do the same type of business and increased ratings in less they took
the path I did which was you know more long form and of course eventually long form reality stuff
but I think that this this has kind of that that MTV vibe to it and you know the the way the
videos look are just as important as as the music so you know a lot of thought is going into it
and uh and a very small people are working very very hard to make it work um yeah I'm pretty happy
with it oh anyway uh so there's uh there's been a couple of uh mainstream mockery and fake
re-spottings and sightings and stories uh on both sides of the Atlantic Ocean let me start with the
US first Gary Alexander uh it's gonna tell us how reality programming is made hey Adam Gary Alexander
from the ultimate podcast what's going on um listen I wanted to comment on and I don't know why
I haven't done this before on um you know uh setting up reality shows and things of that nature
uh how the media are the TV networks are kind of pulled a little over I I was involved I was a
cast member on a show on A&E called um called Mary Dim Vegas where I performed weddings for this
wedding chapel here called uh people I think it's wedding chapel as Elvis and we need to hold
whatever motion and um many different other um characters as well and we were the show was uh on A&E
and they filmed a couple things and the first day of filming for some reason I was late
well after about a month of editing they came back to film a couple things that they needed to
like pick up shots well the pick up shots happens to be all of the storyline revolve around
me being late for the first five minutes of the show so they actually had a camera crew get in the
car with me and I just drove down the street and I did like I was on my cell phone calling into work
and during editing it looked like some guy with a camera was you know left my home with me and
traveled with me that entire day and it never happened never happened like that and obviously
that's reality television not the news or anything like that but it's very obvious to see what
goes down on the on the shows and uh I was part of of reality television on A&E part of the
problem you were my no and for fact obviously it's all bullshit so thank you again the ultimate
dot-pot show dot-com thanks late you know late as man late as Gary Xanna yeah absolutely good
it's exactly how it goes how real is that reality now it's almost as real as well forget it
oh wait what's this this is the the promo for the red carpet cool little Chris this is so funny
you know check this out backstage pass digital music awards 2007 yeah I'd love that Olivia
Lisa's gonna ask you one question to some like Deliberty from last year and the girl says yes of course
you can and and then she says who the hell are you yeah I'd love it
pass one to our one six to five six three five seven last one to our one six to five six three
five seven meanwhile back in Blighty more trickery and mockery of foot with the mainstream
I don't it's uh Mike here from Bristol, Elis and Go-Mem we've read this one recently
it's really said yesterday came out the BBC's being caught with its pants down again this time
on a children's television program called Blue Peter which is one of the longest running television
programs in the world they received children over a rig term telephone vote named over the naming
give up of a cat one of the pet's little pets on that program and it was over the naming
and the kids chose one name and the editor or whoever it was chose another name and the
yeah BBC and they've been caught with their pants down on it so you don't find that actually on
the BBC's websites and apparently they've got to find by off-com fifty thousand pounds over
which is probably not allowed many for BBC although that is public statement anyway
which comes from our license money for the year while you pay 150 years in effort television
is an UK think it is and I don't know I'm got to leave but I just a little point I think the actual
name for the cat was socks but they've been receiving all the children and their program was designed
for uh my laptop at 15 year old 16 year olds and it was a telephone vote we've created them
telephone numbers as well so they must make a lot of money off of that that's a little red pill
blue bell for me yeah man screw those guys we've got our own tricks to play look here's Jill Mills
this is so funny Jill Mills is going through all the all the nominees and with her Jill Mills
attitude it's very very funny I love this it's like a real station hold on we turn out
is that the real deal he makes me piss myself of it's a nice Jill fantastic okay let me see yeah there
was one more thing I wanted to play for you this is a really crazy guy that I found on the
podcast music network yeah his name is Waldruiro he's from Jersey of course check this out
influences Zappa Pearl Jam Beethoven Nobel who Matu Final Fantasy video games Paul Oconfold
Madlib the unicorns black Sabbath the John Williams Kojo condo video game music so apparently
this guy is completely nuts about video game scores and and he does all kinds of really interesting
classical stuff and I presume it's all synthesized although it sounds really really good and
I have to say it almost sounds like the real deal final bit here in his in his bio on the PMN
I'm also here I'm heavily influenced by video games films et cetera final fantasy games
cast Olania Castlevania John Williams Tommy Tolarico Kojo condo et cetera but I'm also into
Beethoven and the other classical composers my sound displays that I discovered the full orchestra
and never went back well damn straight this is uh the maple leaf rag just listen to the quality of the
shit
Yeah, they have some dynamics right there, boi, I'll tell you.
Walt Ribeiro, the Maple Leaf Rag, you can find a link to that on the podcast and music
network from the show notes for this program, dailysourcecode.com.
So tomorrow no idea if I'll be able to update, I think I have to go in pretty early to
get ready.
The show starts around 6 p.m., sorry, dinner at 6, it's like a combination of awards, dinner
slash show, it'll be kind of fun, they got some good names there this year, so you
can check out dma.podshow.com, if you find out want to find out more about the awards,
also watch the dma coverage on the plus dv, let's see what else, backstage pass.podshow.com
and of course the plus dv.com. So tomorrow maybe morning evening, tomorrow night late or Wednesday
for sure, we'll be back with more of the show another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.
This podcast is brought to you by podshow and go day. This show will give you a special
code to get great discounts at godaddy.com. Got something to say, log it with your fruit
log from goday.
The best and the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery, podshow
and lightweight.