Port City PD, the number one online police drama series, is now available.
The pod father had a cameo in the season 1 finale, who will be making cameo appearances
in season 2.
You, me, get in on the action, portcity.podshow.com.
Back from vacation, well rested, just uh, what a great week at the beach.
Of course, the problem is that I was unplugged the whole week.
Let's see what I've missed on the computer here, uh, boy, bunch of Gmail, uh, Twitter
having me keep it up with Twitter and whoa, the daily source could is up to 635, uh, I'll
be listening to this for the next day and a half.
Adam, save me, give me a recap.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, done the next generation
radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying heat to the future.
To me, got to be a yoga, just do what it's please.
Hold me, get shot and fuck you, hold me, get shot and fuck you, hold me, get shot and fuck you, hold me, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you, get shot and fuck you
survive, old Frank, get out, get the hell down. Don't prolong its knees, walk down here, and you can't feel it, get the hell out of me, hold me, pull me, pull me, pull me, pull me, pull me, Yeah I can't feel more pain you've gotta suffer me baby dope, put my heart yeah it's for you dont come to you baby, baby, get up, get up and fuck me you going to dope see you?
Herah! Lage! Oh, you Down! brutti, I'm dead as a Wan Scottish player and nothing else neutrimer thealet!!
Not a Eventually treble hereooo, holding my feko striped his heart 游땍
Hold me
Hold up
It's just about the hottest download on limewire these days.
Not only is it not hot safe, it's not even remotely.
It's also on YouTube, playing the straight from YouTube.com, it is the Beatles vs. 9-inch nails,
come closer together, it's got a fantastic slide show to go in it.
I just couldn't resist had the play at 4-0.
Debbie's Toursco at episode number 635, how you doing come to view from Swanky's
on the west side of G-town from the Curry Manner it is your....
Wow.
It's odd, to get together.
Dude, it's Monday.
And I'm a little bit fuzzy still I have to say.
What a weekend.
My goodness.
It was a Guilfest against given here in Gilford and unfortunately I didn't
get to go.
I had some other commitments.
called me last night though around around nine thirty from Gilfest and she said
Da da da da da da da. She holds up the phone. She's like, listen, it's madness. It's your boys.
Your boys are on stage. One step beyond.
So cool man. We bridging bridging a couple generations there. Patricia and I went to a
garden party yesterday, which was the weather. I mean, it was nice because the weather
did stay dry at the garden party. But this weather, well, I'll talk about the weather in a second.
It was the annual Ben and Halane for vine garden party. Ben for vine is the the CEO.
Do you see? Yeah. Yeah. CEO of British telecom. He's a Dutch guy before this. I think it was
at Lusant in the States. He's been at ITT KPN. I mean, he's one of the CEO guys that
definitely travels around from company to company. Of course, quite celebrated at the moment.
Because British telecom is doing incredibly well. And it was, you know, we had no idea what to
expect. It was just a little bit south of us in Hazelmeer. So a nice drive for the country side
only about 30 minutes. And had no idea, you know, I just like, you know, the the invitation garden
party. It's their garden party. So, you know, we were very curious. Well, it turns out,
it was us and 1199 other people who had been invited. I said, I kid you not 1200 people
at a garden party. And you know, and I did some work, you know, I'd look at the invitation.
And like, oh, if you take the train, they've got shuttle buses running from the train in a
station. I thought that's kind of cool. I thought that I could just drive right up to the house and,
you know, I found the postcode and arrived and they said, oh, no, no, no, no, no, no,
you have to go back to the station. There's no place to park. And that's before, of course,
I knew there were 1200 people who had been invited. So back to the station, hopped on the shuttle
van. And it was, it was unbelievable, this party. It was, it was more like a British telecom
partners, customers, type party. There were just, I didn't know a single person there because it was
mainly, I think BT salespeople. But there were a whole bunch of Dutch people. Of course, I guess
then and Helen have a lot of acquaintances in the Netherlands. And because of that, they had
brought in Dutch catering, who catered the entire Chebang, which was great because they had something
completely, typically Dutch, which no one was touching. None of the, none of the British were
touching it. It's a raw herring, herring with onions. And this is a, you know, it is a special way
of eating it. Actually, it's not entirely raw. It's been put in salt, I guess. So it is kind of cooked.
And you kind of slobber through the onions. And then you hold it, you hold it above your head
by the tail. And you just kind of suck the herring right off. And that sounded wrong, didn't it?
And this is a delicacy in the Netherlands. It did really only good once a year when you have the
fresh new herring. So Patricia and I hung out at the herring bar for quite a while. But they have a
good time. You know, talk to a bunch of different people. They had, you know, like celebrity tennis
match going on with, um, I don't know many of these names, but I recognize the name Pat Cash.
They had like all these, you know, ex-wimbledon winners who were playing, it was, it was, it was very
much like a, like a dot-com party, you know, from, from the, from the late 90s. It was quite spectacular.
So we had a good time. We had, uh, some good food and, uh, chatter with a couple of folks.
And, uh, then, uh, just came back to chill out. Now the weather, I had been looking at the weather
all day. Um, actually all weekend. Now, I'm looking at aviation weather. So I could pretty much
predict it was going to stay completely dry in that part of the country. And I was right.
Other parts of the country. It's been horrendous. And you have to know, uh, do you remember El Ni침o
remember, uh, when the El Ni침o winds were, we're flowing across the, the globe? Well, there's something
now called La Nini침a. I think it's La Nini, El Ni침o was what we had. And now it's La Nini침a,
like the ninja. And that's basically just swirling off the southwest, uh, to the southwest of,
of the UK of the islands. And it's just shooting all this crap up. You know, if, if you've been
following the news, you'll know that, uh, it's been, uh, it's just been horrific in, uh, in England,
Wales and, uh, and, and the northern parts of the country, they've had flooding. It's just been,
it's been bad. And I'm afraid that it's not going to get much better. Uh, we just may have a really
shitty summer as compared to, uh, the summer that we were, uh, we were promised. Well,
so much for global warming. I thought we're going to have beach front here in the UK crap.
More controversy about the BBC, uh, I think I told John Friday, the BBC, uh, were slapped
down for editing a, uh, a fly, what they call a fly on the wall documentary about the Queen,
uh, Annie Lebowitz was a photograph in the Queen Acid or take her tiara off the Queen protested,
cut to the Queen walking away angrily. Unfortunately, that was actually a shot of the Queen walking
in. I don't even think the sound is synced up. I don't know if anyone's looked. I don't think
you even hear the Queen, you, you hear her talking, but you don't even hear lips move. It was so
freaking fake. Now, there's a whole nother flap about, uh, something, was it news night, I think,
is it news night? I, well, anyway, another BBC news program, uh, that they edited this piece
about Gordon Brown, how he's trying to avoid, uh, certain members of the press and, and what they
did is they took footage, uh, over a course of three or four weeks and it made it look like this
was all happening in the course of a day or two. And so, you know, now there's these big investigations
going on. The BBC can't believe that, you know, all this must be, uh, just a, you know, it's just
an isolated one or two isolated events or incidents. And I'm thinking, dude, I've been in
television all my life. This is, this is what we do. It's how you make television exciting is you
edit stuff around. And of course, you completely distort the truth. I posted the, the XNTV
experiment to curry.com. I'd forgotten to put that in the show notes on Friday. So I'll try and
remember to put it in the show notes for today. Michael Hall sent me an email about it. Yeah,
Adam, the BBC lied with the allegation about the Queen, you're right. But this is the challenge
that the blogging and podcasting community has not taken up. The BBC corrected itself
when has a non-genitalistic blog or podcast ever corrected itself. You have on handful of occasions,
but most of them were grudging, grudging at best. When my paper makes a mistake, I guess Michael
works for a, for a newspaper in Canada. We published a correction period and we tried to learn
from a mistake because it's our livelihood. Look, uh, you're, you're misunderstanding what's going on
blogging and podcasting audio and text. It's not the same thing. This is manipulating images.
Every single time you see an edit, a zoom or some kind of technical event on television,
in essence, your brain has to fill in the rest of the formula. So, uh, it movies too. You know,
if, if you're looking at a scene inside, cut to outside, your brain fills in the entire piece
about someone walking out the door, opening the door, getting their key. You know, it's, uh, it's
a very different animal. And if this is a surprise to anyone that this goes on in television,
every single day, I would say almost every single program. You know, and, and now people are
getting fined, left and right, $50,000 to a kids program, blue, Peter, because they had some
kid from the audience pretend to be a prize winner. I mean, this happens all the time. You know,
if, if, if, if this actually, I think is the unraveling of of television, it'll, it'll probably,
it may go a little bit further. I think here in the UK, because the BBC is under tremendous
scrutiny, the whole point of the BBC and the license fees, because we pay like 춲150 a year,
which goes straight to the BBC, they apparently should not have the pressures to sex stuff up
that the commercial television networks have, because, you know, they don't have to sell to advertisers.
Of course, it's not true. Every single person looks at ratings. And the job security is based
upon ratings, even within the BBC, all public broadcasters have this. So it's a, it's a, it's a
fallacy to think that, uh, that just because they're nonprofit or not for profit or sponsored
by the people that they don't go through the same motions of sexing shit up, you know, to make it,
to make it attractive, to make people want to watch if this is, this literally is the big,
blue, blue pill stuff that I've been talking about. That is the spectacle. And if you've ever
been in a situation where you were at some place or at some event, or you were the subject
of something that was later televised, you'll immediately understand how much trickery,
fakeery, and sexing up takes place all the time. This is, uh, it's going to be quite a revelation
for people as more of more of these stories, uh, come out. Uh, let's see what, uh, this all kinds of
interesting email that I got. No, that's something I'll do that in a second. Um, big news, uh, on Sunday
as well, a couple things. First of all, a very own Dr. Cockney is now, uh, being featured every Sunday
in, uh, the news of the world, which is a huge newspaper. Uh, only comes out on Sundays. It's, uh,
of course, uh, let me just, let me just, say, put it this way. We only buy the news of the world on
Sunday for the sports, of course, not for the other content that would be in being there.
But nine million, million people read this. And so now the doc is, uh, is doing his great
British sex survey for the news of the world. It's on their side. And, uh, it's, uh, given
him a lot of exposure, it's very excited about it. But there was another, uh, newspaper that came
out on Sunday with something very interesting in it. Hey Adam, Dave, we can't just go here.
Question for you. I just heard that British giving away three million copies of a new album
planet Earth. And I think it's a UK I believe. And I'm curious what your thoughts on that are.
These, uh, record label is, uh, live it, as they said, and won't even release the album there
because what? That's a couple of findings, giving away a couple of findings in this day and age with
digital music rights and such. Love to hear your comment. Blue pill. Okay. Well, they're still
hope for you, my friend. Yeah, very interesting. Prince released his planet Earth CD through the
Daily Mail. Uh, it was packaged in the newspaper itself. And this is a, uh, it's very, it's a new model.
It's a new distribution model. Of course, Prince, as far as I know, uh, owns all of his, um, music
and the publishing rights. So, um, uh, he is, quote, record company are really only there for distribution
through their channels, through stores. And I presume, through things like iTunes, although I don't see
why Prince wouldn't, you know, go bypass the record company and go straight to iTunes for that as well.
Which he probably will. Um, so, you know, it's really inexpensive to do this type of distribution.
It only really costs about, um, I think Percy D. And it's, and it's, you know, that's not like you
get a nice jewel box or anything. I mean, it's just a cardboard, um, you know, like a fold of piece of
cardboard is the sleeve. No liner notes, no nothing, uh, not even a track listing. The track listing
is on the CD itself. It only costs like, you know, 40, 50 cents to actually, you know, work one of
those up and, and then there's some costs for the newspaper to inserting it. So they made a deal.
Real simple, you know, did he sell, did he sell each copy for, uh, for 10 bucks? No, he sold each
copy maybe for like a buck or, uh, maybe a little bit less. And for the news of the world,
uh, excuse me, for the Daily Mail, that just goes straight out of their marketing and advertising
budget because they do have three or four million readers. And they do this all the time. They do, uh,
DVDs of, uh, of classic, um, series like the World at War and stuff. So yeah, so Prince probably
made, uh, I would, I would think that he, he might have pocketed about a million dollars, uh, for
those three million that went out. And, you know, really, it's, you know, if you read the interviews
that he's putting out there, it's, for him, it's just getting the music out. Oh, I wish he would
put some of that stuff pod safe. All right. If I, you know, I've met the guy once, really nice guy. He's
not as small as you think he is, by the way, maybe I'm just used to Patricia, but really down to Earth
guy. That's not a hype joke. Um, you know, a nice and very informed and, uh, and not wacky at all.
And, uh, and he doesn't talk with that soft voice, uh, when you just talk into him normally,
that you probably think he uses all the time. Uh, so if we get about all that, listen to the CD,
not bad. I love the, uh, the track, uh, which has been getting a lot of play here. I love my guitar.
Um, there's some really nice jazz stuff on it. There's one track that sounds a little bit like, uh,
the controversy, uh, or controversy, um, uh, baseline, uh, some good stuff on it. Uh, I like it.
Of course, I'm a huge Prince fan. And I'll, man, I would do any, I would give my left, not just to
get that on the podcast music network. But this, of course, is the new forms of distribution
that we're going to see. Prince, um, you know, has a very, you know, he's, he's got a strong base to do
this. Um, but there's no difference to me, you know, for him going around the entire music industry,
uh, working with the Daily Mail, or someone going through Starbucks, or indeed working, uh,
with all of the, uh, thousand, tens of thousands of producers and podcasts, there's an independent, uh,
uh, radio and video, uh, programmers, uh, on the internet through, um, sites like the podcast
music network, where everything is just kind of taken care of with one mouse click and all the
rights are arranged. And it's working. So I applaud Prince now to get the guy on the podcast music network.
And lots of people are thinking about this. I told you, I'm working on, uh, red bullet in the
Netherlands, getting, uh, golden earring, focus, shocking blue. Um, I haven't seen their entire
catalog. More people are thinking about putting their catalog online. I'm really loving this shit.
Hey Adam, this is Chris Suspect from Washington, DC. I just got finished listening to, uh,
episode number six, 33 of the DSC, and which we're talking about, uh, the internet, uh,
radio streaming radio going dark. Uh, I think this is going to be actually a real big
balloon for a pot show and, uh, podcast music. Um, but what I wanted to say is, uh,
uh, it would I completely agree with what you have to say about, um, you know, the big labels
and the music. There's lots of other choices out there. And I think it's time to make other artists
aware. I used to want to label many, many meetings to go, uh, punk rock label at DC called
tourcrack records. And while we all have those to the couple tracks up there, some bands that
I have been in, I think I'm just going to post the entire catalog and that's 20 CDs. Um,
and, uh, some of those tracks on their future folks like David Grohl, uh, Brian Baker from
Old Miner Threat Currently with Bad Religion, uh, lots of good punk rock stuff. Um, and, uh,
I'm all of it's available through, uh, through music. So, uh, it's great the one time I
put some stuff up there for a band I was in called VPR. Um, we actually, uh,
let's end like three weeks. We sold like 120 dollars worth of merchandise just through, uh,
through podcasts. And I really appreciate what you're doing, what you're doing for music. And I think
you're, uh, writing the wave into the future. So, um, I'd appreciate it if you could play a VPR track
on the DSC, uh, particularly the one most people like is my girl turned into a lesbian. And I think
you'll find the lyrics funny. A little harder than what you normally play, but I play bass and
and I think half the song. So, you can hear that I sound like, uh, I'm not that great of a singer,
but the song is good. So, check it out and I appreciate it. So, thanks again for all you're doing,
and have a great day. No, do, do, do, do. Thank you so much. It's much appreciated. And even though
you're right, it's not exactly the type of song I'd play on the Charlie, I just got to play
it for you, uh, particularly the, uh, the title of the song, intrigue me. And remember,
there's a fast forward button for a reason. This is a true story.
I'm not getting it, I'm not getting it, I'm not getting it, I'm not getting it, I'm not getting it,
this is a phobic shit. Well, it could be, live a clean unfinished fight,
my go, otherwise go, I just can't deal with that.
My go watches minister on around, not getting it, not getting it, I'm not getting it, don't worry about
I'm gonna punch you all the time
I'm not gonna lie, I'm not gonna lie
We don't wear a dress, she says she's got a dress
She said my answer's too fat
My girl, she said she likes girls
I just can't deal with that
My girl, I can't deal with that
I'm not gonna lie, I'm not gonna lie
She says she got a dress, I'm not gonna lie
I'm not gonna lie
I'm not gonna lie, I'm not gonna lie
That hurt so good
VPR, my girl turned into a lesbian
You can find that on the Potsay Music Network
Of course, links to that in the show notes at DailySourceCode.com
Steven Palsmackers sent me pretty funny
I don't know we got this from
You know we have the in the United States
We have the concept of the terror threat level
Which I think is right now pretty much
Lodged at threat level orange
And the Europeans apparently have also
instilled their own threat level
Warning system against terrorism
As you know, the chief of homeland security
In the United States says he has a gut feeling
That we're in for it
That there's another big attack coming
That of course probably pertains to the US
But well, we have some upgrades here in Europe as well
The British are feeling the pension relation
To recent terrorist threats and of raise their security level
From MIFT to Pieved
Soon whoever security levels may have to be raised to
Irritated or even a bit cross
Londoners have not been a bit cross
Since the blitz in 1940 when T supplies all but ran out
Terrorists have also been recannigarized
From tiresome to a bloody nuisance
Last time the British used a bloody nuisance
Warning level was during the Great Fire of London
Of 1666
Now the French government also announced yesterday
That it had raised its terror alert level
From run to hide
The only two levels higher in France are
Surrender and collaborate
This latest rise was precipitated by a fire
That destroyed France's white flag factory
Effectively paralyzing the country's military capability
In addition to the British and the French
Italy has increased its alert level
From shout loudly and excitedly
To elaborate military posturing
Two more levels remain which of course
Are ineffective combat operations and change sides
Belgians on the other hand
Are all on holiday and the only threat they are worried about
This NATO pulling out of Brussels
Finally the Spanish are very excited
Their new submarines are ready to deploy
These beautifully designed subs have glass bottoms
So the new Spanish Navy can get a really good look at
The old Spanish Navy
One, two, one, six, two, five
Six, three, five, seven
Out of the synopsis of ont
Hey, I'm just having this random thought
You know, especially for us American guys
There is nothing better in the world than a cute British check
With an American, with a British accent
And I'm wondering, is it possible
That you guys could do something like
I don't know, is there a podcast out there
With someone like a Callie Lewis
Or a Carmen Tyler
Or somebody who's going to do it
A frequent show
And you see what I'm getting at here
And it's just going to do sort of a free form podcast
Because all I want to do is sit and listen
I don't even hear what she talks about although
You know, that could be interesting too
But God, I don't know what maybe you think of it
But I could just, you might have a real, real winner
There, I mean, just, you know, we've already got an accent
But you add a nice British accent
That's not that whole thing, man
You know, you might very well have, uh, who would it be
About 150 men?
Building an American guy is going
Us police, uh, just a thought
Man, well listen, I have the solution for you
Be horned dog
And I do know what you mean
I could listen to many British women
I could just listen to them read the phone book
Uh, let me see, I have some examples here for you
Well, we have, if you go to btpodshow.com
Bravo tango podshow
Btpodshow.com
Which, of course, is our, uh, our UK site
Um, you'll, right on the homepage
You'll find a number of cool links
The one I would suggest right off the bat
Which will probably lead you to other cool shows
Is podfinder UK
Hosted by the lovely Josephine Lauren
So it's not just audio of my friend
You can look at her as well
Hold on a second
I'll give you a little sample of it
I'm just pulling her up right now
Let's see, come on Joe
Talk to me baby
Hey, it's my, if I'm going to
He's all on the big
What the hell is that?
Oh, that's a promo
It's found a podfinder and of course
Joe, she's got a great line of a show
Okay, so this is not the sexy voice
I want to get a listen to
Oh, that is, again
Come on, give me Joe
Oh, here she comes
Oh, that's cool
We have a promo for games, we don't
Excellent, oh, let me do the code promotion while we're at it
You can win an iPod
Or free songs on iTunes
Come on in
Josephine
Hi guys and girls, welcome to podfinder
Oh, my name's Joe Lauren
So once again, I've got five fabulous podcasts
So there's that, then we have
UK celebrity news, Kasha van Sant
Let me see if I can find her
She's right here
Of course, there's the MNP show
You might want to listen to the MNP show
Let me see what else we have
There's the
On this week's show, things are really
Housing up in the world's celebrity
Temp is a friend, everyone
What I'm saying?
So there's plenty of stuff out there
My friend, just go to btponshow.com
And I, well, satisfaction guaranteed
Hi, I'm a serial presenter
I'm from the ultimate podcast
I am listening to DSC 634
I'm about 43 minutes into it
And I get it
I understand your channel concept
I understand the biobill
And how
Actually cool it is
And the gentleman, the
I'm assuming you can
That was that James, I think, James
Who really got it on Friday
I'm assuming you're from UK, obviously
Or
Yeah, but
Regardless, where he's from he
gave me a pretty good idea
Of what the channel concept is
And I get it
I get it, I think it's really cool
Actually
And he showed me the
You know, the ability to
The flying shows in poncho
And to add them to a
You know, a cold and cold channel
Or feed, whatever you want to call it
And then take that feed
Put it in iTunes
And then drop it on my iPod
So I understand now
When exactly what's to do it
I still probably will
Give it a listen to
You know, my shows a little differently
Because sometimes
I don't want them all in one feed
But I do understand the concept
And I think it's pretty awesome
And I want to kind of applaud you
That I really couldn't get my mind
Around it at first
But now
Well, you know what it is, Gary
By the way, Gary's got
Some super episode coming up
You want to check out the ultimate podcast
He's got some
Some awesome, like, fighter dude on there
And all this ultimate fighting
Cage fighting is really
Becoming all the rage
So we're right on the cutting edge there
It's really as hard as explaining
What Tivo is
Yet if you give someone a Tivo
You show them, you know,
Couple menus
They're totally into it
And you'd have to pride
From their dead fingers
To, you know, to take it away from them
So all of this, of course,
Is leading up to our brand new channel
Editor
Which we've codenamed cheddar
For a reason
One
Because I like cheese
Two
Because if you say channel editor
Channel editor, cheddar, cheddar, cheddar
Cheddar, it sounds like cheddar
And I was hoping we're going to release that Friday
I did jump the gun a little bit
We weren't quite ready
Apparently there's quite a bit to the
DB alterers and all kinds of stuff
That has to happen in order to make that work
Perfectly
And again, it's really beta stuff
So it's not like this is a big
Launcher exposure
It's really only for people
Listening to the daily source
Cokes, I don't think many other people will
Find it
Because that is a part of a much larger plan
That we're implementing now
Which, as you know, is
Turning our site upside down
Since we built the fucker inside out
And I want to apologize for
Saying that it was a, you know,
I didn't really give a shit
Because I didn't get it
No dude, not a problem
No need to apologize
What's the other
But now I do
And I think it's just another thing
That you guys are trying to be setting edge on
And I do appreciate it
Though, you know, it might not be for me
Messing so it might be
I just need to kind of get in there
And work on it a little more
So, you know, great, great job
I just want to say that I do understand now
And I like to think that the gentleman who
Call in and explain it
Because I get it now
So thanks
Call the publisher.com
Yeah
Red pill, I'm sure
Yeah dude
So the current planning is to release it
On Wednesday, that'll be Wednesday
San Francisco time
So that probably won't mean that
Unless you're planning on being online
Wednesday evening in Europe
Or even on the east coast of the US
You probably won't really see it until Thursday
And that's when we're really going to
Start hammering this stuff out
And start working on it
Because I have no idea exactly how it's going to work
What kind of things we're going to find out
When we basically feed the tail
Into the head of the beast, you know,
The whole idea of getting someone's channel
And putting it into yours
But in essence
It's just building upon, okay
I want to get a show
I want to get an episode
Or a channel
And now I want to put it somewhere
And that's going to really be the big
Oh well, factor is
How do I put this channel onto my iPod
How do I, you know, just grabbing RSS
So I can put this channel onto some other device
That understands that
I'm very excited about it
I really, you know, looking at the
Architects that we've built
I think it's going to be an awesome
Really do
All right, let's see
Three, two minutes
Yeah, I've been doing some long shows
Recently, so I want to
I want to try and cut this one
A little bit short today
Even though it's not all that short
I want to do it with a band
That I am just absolutely nuts about
They showed up in the top ten
For the month of pod play
From the pod sake music network
I was, let me just see if I can find
Real quick
The called natives of the new dawn
I used to play
It was going to be a good day
Which is one of my favorite songs
By them
I think that's what it is
Hold on
Natives of the new dawn
Shoot
Did they take the, I don't know
Anyway
They've got a new one out
It's called your boy
And it is completely
Natives of the new dawn
Kick an ass
Just sit back
Jam the buds
Indy
And enjoy
Natives of the new dawn
Kick an ass
Mama
Papa look at me
Mama look at me
Look what you're for
You're up to fame
Without you there been no me
I dedicate this to my family
I dedicate it to my mom and dad
Me and my brother
I'm glad you had
Respect to the people who
Has seen them birthed me
But when no one to be
But raise me safely
All the year influence
Today we're in the my panning
And I've been taught in piano
Jam is a lot more lake than you are
My point of light
And up to the change that family
My aunt to dodge
We go way back
Back and back to my baby
First brought them into the war
I fell apart then we would still be loud
Mama Papa born
Thank you for your love and support
For your watchful
I strong hands in war
Far weather
I was on pressure
What you pulled by surprise
And now I look to me
We ready to leave
Loving your eyes
That's friends
Topping out this under my shine
And not the could replace
These family times
What brother
Sister look at me
Brother sister look at me
Oh look at my brother
Who wants your brother
Hey
What brother
We're brothers and sisters
Who won beside us in the family
Pictures
Meaning you can be amazing
For your love and affection
Didn't I see you're done but now I see the connection you are my point at life
Enough to good change that family my aunt will brush we go
Wait back memories and take it up and write me down
Ink smears and cheek tears and that for now allow closeies memories of
Provin' up do we've been side me and everything we've been together
Hope you define me you walk beside me
Bit of my need the values temporary and the peak is wild a climb will be
We're born together
Partless in crime best friends
Copping out the sun to my shine oh my friends come look at me
All my friends come look at me you can be anything you want to be
You can be anything you want
Without you there'd be no me without you there'd be no me
I can see that you all my family my family my family my family
You walk while I walk while I walk I walk I walk I walk I walk in the name
I walk while I walk in the name
Well, look what you've called you up to bed
You've got your own hope to be
Without you there'd be no me
Bit of my need the values temporary and the peak is wild a climb will be
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Well, all my people people look at me
So you can be anything that you want to be
You walk
Without you there'd be no me
Bit of me
I can see that you all my family yeah
You walk
I'm a father
It is of the new joy
You're growing
I love what they put on the
Little bio here musical genres beware the natives have demolished all labels
It created a monster hip hop and soul funk rock and classic RB
Easy to love hard to categorize
Loose the gimmick shake your false pretenses raise your musical consciousness
Head nodding ass shaking high energy music damn straight
All right, we got a full ass week. We've got to stuff going on in the London office
We've got folks coming over
We're in we're an overdrive mode, but so that means we'll probably get four shows out this week
A daily source code calm adamant pod show dot com appreciate all your feedback
Appreciate your phone calls appreciate you contributing to the show and I'll be here to mark and talk to you
So join me. Bye. Bye
Another pod show podcast stick it in your ear
You
The best and the brightest
subdupped daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering pod show and limelight