Hey Peter, can I ask you a question?
Yes, do you?
Who would you say our calls important?
After 20 minutes of being on hold, I'd have to say now.
Please continue to hold.
Your call is important to us.
Yeah, it's very correct.
It's very important.
Then we'll hold music.
Unif I turn the cations.
Or I'll buy Cisco.
Now there's the DSC533 without Splenda.
Um, yeah.
Oh, I hate it.
I hate it.
Then there's the DSC533 with Splenda.
I love that show.
I love that show so much.
And not, yeah.
But of course, we all love the DSC533.
Food Bard.
Anyone can suck off my pipe anytime.
You never know what you're going to hear on the Charlie.
Kick up the music, AC.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding.
It's a hat in the curry.
One hit.
Three.
Got it.
Get up.
Be beep, beep, beep.
Got it.
I like it.
Been alive.
Come on, Patty, I'll post
Makein' plans, I'm up on it to camp, if we go
Can't happy face, it's endless, I'll need you again
Piles, number one for free, that's where we'll be
Better all, now you'll never find it
Lookin' bein' one, let's party for y'all
One from the corner we're spent by a tribe
Take all right in my, but we got nothing to hide
Make a start just one back to our ride
Never say that, but more, but they're wild
What do they want and they want and they want and they want
Come on, number one for free, that's where we'll be
Better all, now you'll never find it, you'll never find it
This is Delta Sierra Charlie, five, three, three
A hot cast of Adam Carey
And yes, the working week, once again has ended
Then you can start your weekend now
And enjoy some quality podcasting
But whatever you do, don't apply splendor-analy
Just put it into your coffee
Come on, number one for free, that's where we'll be
Better all, now you'll never find it, you'll never find it
Better all, now you'll never find it, you'll never find it, you'll never find it
Come on, number one for free, that's where we'll be
Better all, now you'll never find it, you'll never find it
Come on, number one for free, that's where we'll find it
Come on, number one for free, that's where we'll be
Better all, now you'll never find it, you'll never find it
Better all, now you'll never find it, you'll never find it, you'll never find it
Come on, number one for free, that's where we'll be
Come on, number one for free, that's where we'll found it, you'll never find it
Come on, number one for free, that's where we'll find it
Friday Thursday night, but I'm getting so many messages that people really love in the fact
that the show is ready in the morning almost all over the world except for Australia.
We've already been through that. Oh man, I'm so ready. I got some great tunes. I did the show
prepletive the office today. I did that for the last couple of nights. It's kind of nice.
You know, around six o'clock and I plug in the speakers and you know, people come in and
out and we're just playing tracks and people are commenting. It's cool. Andrew Grumman was
hanging out with me at this evening. And once again, you guys have done it. You've put
together the entire show for me. I don't have to do anything. In fact, all I have to do is kind
of move it along because there's so much to talk about. A lot of good emails, too, which of course
have to do with free Trinity. And by the way, I want to thank Doug, the originator of free Trinity,
for reminding me about Stingray, one, four, three. Of course, that was mentioned in audio
comment earlier this week. And of course, Stingray, I've played them, they started the cowbell
revolution. They revived it for me. So I've got a couple of things to just run through
quickly. Stuff we've been talking about this week. Then we're going to get into, um, let's see,
the naming of the new abode. And of course, free Trinity. Yeah. So let's, uh, well, here's something
new fresh. Hey Adam, this is Jen from Bucket. Now part of the pod show family at BucketSouthBodShow.com.
Anyway, I was just calling you about reality TV shows. I heard you say this, you like American
Idol. I know it's not about the singing and all that, but kind of feel that you're my people now
because I love, I love that. Anyway. So I know you're in a big brother. So I just saw it that I would
tell you that there's this show being talked about. I think it's coming out of the Netherlands,
actually. It's another reality TV show. Um, it's a reality dating show for visibly
district-figured people. So the idea of the show is that people who have visible handicaps,
it's going to be a dating show for them. I just, um, I just had the call you and tell you,
I'm going to, I haven't said to the link when I get to my computer. I'm in the car right now.
But um, you just, you have to look at this. I, I love to hear you talk about it. Anyway,
take care and I'll talk to you later. Hi. Not Jen. Thank you so much. So nice. Yeah. Isn't
a nice to be part of the family? Have I initiated you yet? I don't think so. Richard Brueher
will be calling you about that. Yeah. So let me, uh, yes, it is indeed a, uh, a show that's
being produced in the Netherlands. I've read about this too. I haven't actually heard about it
from any of my Dutch contacts. You know, we're on very different time zones. But I'm sure I'll
hear more about it. Um, two things about that. One, the Netherlands is extremely open about,
particularly visual handicaps. And I remember this, when we moved to the Netherlands in 1972,
I was a wee, a wee young boy, come on up on Grandpa's knee. I'll tell you a story, okay?
I we, uh, we moved there. And I remember there's a couple of things that really stood out about
the Dutch. Uh, the first one was they ate French fries with mayonnaise.
And that was pretty freaking weird. Something else that we noticed over the course of the
first couple of years and of living in the Netherlands, the Dutch have their wind their curtains
always to open push to sides. You can look into their window. Their windows are always
impeccably clean. I'm generalizing, of course. But that, that pretty much was the culture in
1972 to 75. So I'm sure some of that has lasted throughout the years.
And they love for people to look in and their window sills. There's always nice things displayed
and it's part of the culture. And we also noticed that there was no, and I, and I really recall
my parents talking about this. Uh, the Dutch don't hide their handicap the way other cultures do.
And I think probably, I think probably then, uh, we realized that, wow, the Dutch are
very more open or at least we see a lot more severely handicapped people. You know, just like
disturbingly so if you're, particularly if you're a kid, now that that was in 72. So hopefully
kids don't witness it that way anymore. That's kind of hard for me to judge. But I think the
Dutch really mean this. It's part of their DNA. It is part of their, of their, their cultural
to display this. And they're not going to be making fun of it. That's the piece that I believe
is being misunderstood. You know, it's like, hey, let's, let's give the, the lowest, the lowest,
uh, hmm, what am I looking for? The Dutch liked losers, complete losers in life to win.
And lots of cultures like that. You know, but this is more than the underdog. I think it's a very,
you know, that they truly mean it. Like, yeah, let's, let's have them hook up with a date. That's
pretty fucking cool. It's not going to be to be to make laughing stock out of them.
Now the other thing I wanted to say about that is we've been talking a lot about reality shows in
the past week. You know, I, I subscribed to a couple of RSS feeds, it's like motivational quotes of
the day and quote of the day. And I, and I always read all kinds of interesting quotes. And I'm always
thinking, well, I wish I could come up with a great quote that would live on forever. And I think
I have one. I think I've got one. And it relates to what we've been talking about
in the past week about reality shows and about the racism, a legit racism being portrayed in big
brother, celebrity, big brother in the UK and all this back and forth. And I was kind of
realizing that, you know, it's who we are. These are reality shows. The whole point is to show
you reality. And, and usually, and I'm just repeating myself, usually when people see themselves,
when they recognize themselves, they pretty much hate it. People who really hate reality shows,
I think they're probably seeing some of them, of themselves in those shows. So here was the quote.
I hope makes it into the history books as it be nice. No, Adam Curry. Reality is pornographic.
And that come on. That's a pretty cool quote, isn't it?
Adam, it shows in London. Nice talk. You haven't spoken to it at all?
Hey Charles, Charles, our drunken lunderer. Ah. Hammered again, Charles?
Is now Thursday, about 9.30 in the morning. God damn, I just got off the tube.
Apparently, he's had the tube in his vein now.
Now, wine, the tube winds up everybody. But, uh, not me. I keep kind of zen.
Oh, okay. It's not that kind of tube I get. I try to be a nice passenger,
but someone in just gets juice. And the fact that they put the prices up this new year,
George Dan, 27 pound 50 for a weekly 1-3 don't card.
Holy crap, that is a lot of money. What was that? It's quite some of this, uh, like 58 bucks a week,
just for a 1-3 zone card. I mean, can you even,
how far do you can even get that far with a 3-zone or can you? Yeah, that is very expensive, Charles.
My, George. Anyway, that's a little winch there. It's so weird how you seem to have
women call you in again. Hi, my name is Janet. I'm sexy. My, George, what a awful, awful radio voice.
Yeah, I want more of that. I want more women calling in talking really sexy. Shut up, Charles.
Please podcast. I can't even anything worse to listen to a middle-aged woman tell me about her
bit. It's been for yourself, Charles. Anyway, okay, first of all, you know, probably fourth point
by now. Sorry, family. Um, all right, racism. Regardless of whatever you think about the situation,
it's, I think, I agree with you, Jennifer should be applauded. This is, uh, opening up a bag of
worms, the cannerworms and no one talks about the institutionalized racism in the UK. It's always just
sort of accepted. If you're not around someone who's black or in the, you know, Asian or
of any sort of color or creed, that isn't political occasion. If you're not in the presence of
those people, it seems to be okay for whitey, just sort of mock. And, um, only, it's a very,
very, very few people have either come across to do this. But, you know, what, where does it,
if I ever met one percent of people that are done, that means that that's one percent of the
country that they're about. And, you know, if I was to do my own stroke, you know, I think every
culture, everybody marks some other way of speaking. It's just the way people talk and sometimes
it's funny, come on, lighten up already. Uh, you think that's not happening. And, but, you know,
look, I'm not insulted that people make fun of my accent and, you know, people do the same thing
with Madonna, by the way. Uh, you know, that is, if you're going to call, what's happening,
what happened to Shopa or it's happening to Shopa Shetty. If they're going to call that racism,
they can call it, it call everything racism, lighten the fuck up. It's realized that we're
doing it and looking how stupid it is. And then maybe next time, maybe next time, you see someone
like a Jade Goodie doing that, you know, like, damn, man, I don't want to be that person. I'm just
not going to do it. I think that's the point. And I think that's why Charles is agreeing with me,
the channel 4 and the mulch will be applauded when you see more of this stuff. Show it.
I don't, I truly do not believe it will be an example and people will start doing that, too.
I think it's just so embarrassing when you see it and it's not acted when it's real.
Reality is pornographic. So I'm in full full agreement. This shit makes me stand out, bullshit.
And I don't want to be judged for any reason, let alone my color. And I have actually been
the victim of racism despite being a blonde head blue-eyed. What do you remember?
Who's called a corn said? I don't know. I'm not as English as they come, of course, not because
being English makes us all hybrid just pretty much every European and international country.
In fact, there was a program on recently how English are you and people are saying that that's
people are talking about how they think they're English. And when they were actually
their genes were researched, it turned out they're far from it. Anyway, my other point was Trinity.
Where could you talk about it? I wanted to drive from San Francisco. I'm going to drive from San Francisco
down through like all of your nice, uh, difficult, high weight that 101 I think. I'm not sure.
Right. So then it cut off. You know, it has like, you can only talk for three minutes, Charles.
Okay. I should be enough, dude. So it feels like I've touched some kind of nerve, not like
a sensitive nerve, but I like it in the way Charles is explaining that. Is it for all I know?
Indian people could be making fun of Pakistani people's accents. I'm sure it happens, you know?
So look and learn. And by the way, when I say reality is pornographic, that really stems
from the thought that pornography, you know, people having sex. And, uh, I guess viewing that
pre-recorded or in pictures or whatever, that's pornographic. Well, isn't it just reality?
What we're seeing? Doesn't everyone hope they're having sex like a porn star?
I sure do. Hey, Adam. This is Chris Daley from the Pod Music Countdown. And I just got
done listening to this on the DSC. I know. It's something about, uh, well, you know, it's the
whole candle and night time vibe. Mains urban out or something like that. At least it's pod safe.
If not, unpronounceable. I want to be with Angelina Jolie. I want to be a word that touches
her lips and music divine that sounds in her mind.
What the hell was that? Come on, Adam. Here, I have a saying for you. Repeat after me. Friends,
don't let friends pick out music when they're stone. Wow, that song was terrible. It reminds
me of another friend of mine who every time he gets wasted, he breaks out the Ronnie James D.O.
albums over and over and over. That's all he plays. Bad idea. Adam, the next time you're stone
and you need some music for your show, do the right thing. Pick up the phone, give me a call,
I'll steer you in the right direction. And hey, if I'm not available, there's always the official
musicologist, Jersey Todd. Keep it real, Adam. All right. How about this one, then?
Questions of the daily source code are explicit in nature and not meant for sensitive ears.
And then you fight me.
I kind of like this life that spits me. I want to feed that hand that fights me.
I want to fuck you when you fight me. You want to fuck with this mask.
You want to fuck with this mask a kiss. You're in over your head, you're in over your head.
Show me what you got. I get here a worthy competitor. You want to fuck me. You want to fight me.
I want to fuck you when you fight me. I kind of like the boy that's fight me.
I like to feed the hand that fights me. I like it when it hurts.
Show me what you're worth. Show me. I'll feed this shit out of you.
Yeah. I want you to know that Andrew's ramen and I we talked it over.
So yeah, only because it's a good one, you know, I'll be doing it out of you.
I like it when it hurts. Disturbing.
That is so disturbing. It really, really is. Rachel can K-A-N-N fight me.
That's been to my playlist for probably two months. I've been looking at that song saying,
I don't know. I just don't know. Anyway. So I've been looking for a new name for
our new house because we had the curry cottage. Didn't really feel right to call the new
place the curry cottage as well. And I've received a lot of suggestions. Unfortunately,
most of them buy an email, which kind of sucks because, you know, I don't mind reading a couple out,
but it would take a whole lot of time to, you know, to really sort through them so I wouldn't
do a whole bunch of doubles. Let me just give you a couple. With this from John Glasscock.
Curry Kasa Curry Shelle Curry Ossedy Curry Favor Curry Crash Pad Curry Krakow's things.
Curry Curry Cave Curry Comerancy, which is a short-term dwelling, Curry Cabin.
Nothing really hits me there. A couple others. I added a mixture in from London just to get
back to the naming of the new curry residents in Gilford. Just a fool, but if you compare to drop
me a letteration, I'd pass it to an Indian restaurant the other day with his name on it and
thought my pursuit was called the Curry Villa. How does that sound? Curry Villa, I think that's pretty good.
You know, I take air, see you soon, bye. Yeah, it sounds like an Indian restaurant, you know?
Exactly what it was intended for. No, that doesn't sound right.
Yeah, I don't, I'd like the obliteration bed. I'd like the cook.
Of course, there's also a cook pit pit pit pit.
Hi, I'm David calling from Sunny Perth, West and Australia, but I think I'm just listening to
episode five to nine. It'd be one of you guys, sorry about that. You're talking about name
the new abode in England. Oh, I had a bit of a brain storm. Come up with the
pack, Palace, that's P.A.C. Patricia, Adam, Christina, the pack, Palace. How do they grab you?
Anyway, I'd rather all do well, love the show, keep listening. And I hope by now you've got
that bloody internet sort of had in the in the conduct. I'll keep listening and I'll hear from you soon
and I'll put you in my pack, Palace. Yeah, it sounds like a bad arcade game, you know?
I appreciate it though because that does kind of bring in, you know, the Trisha Adam Christina. That's
kind of cool. It was one that I liked. Let me see if I can find it. Who was this from?
Is this from Dave Pond Rios? Pond Rios? Hi, Adam. I figured with the connectivity
fun you're having at the moment. It would be better to shoot you an email rather than a voice mail.
Oh, well, yeah, I guess that's kind of right. When did you send this January 20th?
If you're still out for suggestions to Navy new place, how about Adam's Adam's attic? Adam's
attic. That kind of has a ring to it and he also suggested the curry crib. I think those two
names are kind of working for me. Love the show, keep of the great work. I think we'll stop with
Metro sexual moments. Yeah. Yeah, I think we kind of were kind of over that. But he's a quick one.
Check out the boss skin product line from Hugo Boss. While it may not be quite cheap enough for
daily use, it's great for a little pamper now and then that us guys so deserve. Plus, the ladies love
the subtle scent of it. Dave. Dave Pond Rios. Deep pan, he says. Okay. Yeah, man. Adam's attic. I don't know
the kind of my work. That does have a vibe to it for sure. Oh, well, let me let me let me just
live with it for the weekend in the trip home and I'll tell you on Monday when I think about it.
Okay, put your hands up if you go to movies. We go to a lot of movies. This is Robert and Toronto.
Join me in my co-hostsendia at our new podcast mobile movie located mobile movie dot pod show.com.
We get into our suit.pot Rod mini right after we see the movies, but the digital recorder on
talk about the movies. It's the best way to review a movie. We write them on a bag system, bags,
apart from that is remember mobile movie.podshow.com. Join us. You'll have a great time.
Hey, Adam, this is Doug Pilgrim. Oops, that's the wrong one. Oh, man.
Yeah. Oh, I'm sorry about that. Oh, yeah. How could I have messed that up? I thought I had it.
Oh, I hate myself when I messed it up like that. I was ready to get into the segment. You know,
we got the theme songs, so I might as well queue it up and intro properly. It's time to talk about everyone's
darling driving across the USA. I'm hoping to make a good time today. I'm feeling
I've been watching you go letting everybody know that this is going to be the better way.
Trinity, Trinity, the quintessential luxury, Trinity, Trinity left the bio diesel set
you're really, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity. Free Trinity save the world, win valuable prizes.
Trinity. We are attempting to figure out how to gain some attention for the bio diesel movement
because it's not an industry. It's a movement. What did I see? Did I see an actress last night on
Letterman? I think talking about the fact that she drove on bio diesel in her, in her, I didn't,
I just kind of caught the last the tail end of the interview. I think that she was on Letterman.
And she was talking about putting bio diesel in and that she was really sold on the fact that it's
smelled like a Korean restaurant, something like that. I don't know how she could tell. It was a Korean
restaurant. But, you know, it's, it's bio diesel. It's kind of getting some attention. You know,
people are talking about it in all walks of life. Hey Adam, it's Chef Mark here with Jennifer.
We've been following the free Trinity thread with great interest and wouldn't you know,
while enjoying chukru at the famous lay-all restaurant in New York City last night,
we found a great source of fuel for Trinity. Yes, we actually got to speak with
Philippe Lajoni, the owner of Lail, and I asked him about their recycling of cooking oil
from the stick fleet in the kitchen to pair bio diesel gals like our beloved Trinity.
So very simply, this company comes to the restaurant once a week. They collect all our oil
from our fires and they clean it up, they filter it, and then they use it for cars and
trucks that are diesel and they can run on oil. In fact, when I opened Lail in Tokyo,
in Japan in a few years ago, I had met a person who owned over a hundred Kentucky Fried Chicken.
So he was turning over a lot of oil. That's right, and he was doing a lot of
deliverings and pickups, and the entire fleet of vehicles was running on his own oil.
And he would not spend a dime on the oil yet on gas. That works all of the trans fat
problem in New York too. Yeah, that is great. So that's awesome.
That is like a furniture even doing it now. Yes, the oil, the clitorious.
I'm going to be funny if you just said that. I don't mean can you save the world and when
valuable prizes, you can also feed your car biodiesel from one of the top restaurants in the land.
Listen for the full interview on an upcoming food philosophy podcast.
And Mark will also have more audio from the Chukut Hall of Fame dinner on Remarkable Palette.
Be sure to include New York City on that free turnity tour at him because we can feed
her some top shelf biodiesel. But we're saving the Chukut and stick it for ourselves.
Ah, mercy, Jennifer.
I wonder if you put, uh, I guess depending on whatever was cooked in the oil, it may indeed smell
different. We should do some of these experiments. So, oh, man, let me, a lot of this came through
email, of course. So it just takes me a little bit longer to get through everything. But
I got a lot of these from Thomas Crosslon who writes at him a couple of things. How about having
Trinity stop to attend potsafe music gigs along the way? Although you just tuning into the
into the conversation about free Trinity, we're trying to figure out what to do here.
Doug Pilgrim was kind enough to offer to fly out with this son to San Francisco,
drive the car back, do a podcast every day during a week. And this is really sparked a lot of
response. And people, a lot of people would like to help along the way, a lot of people have a small
biodiesel based businesses that they'd like to promote, which I haven't all for, you know,
as long as we can document it, as long as we can, you know, actually create something. And I'm talking
small size things, you know, maybe three to five minutes, nothing too long. And, you know, the idea
of having, excuse me, I really didn't want to burp out loud. I wouldn't do that. That was a really
disgusting line. Okay, either stop to meet a podcast or attend a potsafe music artist concert.
And here's a map of biodiesel stations across the U.S. are already, you know, we've got mapping
information here. And these guys may be able that might be able to help you pin Trinity,
where does that love craft biofuels? Hold on, I haven't actually clicked on that link yet.
Let me see, what does it look like? Oh, they pimp, they pimp out. Oh, nice. Oh, man, the community of
people who are into biofuels is so incredibly fun. They just look like a bunch of fun. And they're
not all tree huggers, you know, it's just fun people who are just doing some amazing stuff. Okay,
so here's Doug. And thank you, Doug, so as I said, Doug Pilgrim reminded me that stingray, I've
actually paid a plate of a couple times. And he says, hey, Adam, how are you good evening? Here's the
here's the URL for the hemp car you showed interest in. Yeah, thank you. Second, passing Trinity
from podcast to podcast or sounds like a very cool idea promoting alternative energy, alternative
content, alternative independent music all at once. Wow, independent media about that, huh?
Independent media, independent oil, fuck, sounds good. It reminds me of the little white
bike project that was attempted in Amsterdam in the 60s before your time. Not actually the white
bikes, I think we're still around. They were just just about all the last of them. We're still
in Amsterdam when we got there in the very early 70s. Check with the suits first before you go forward
liability issues with all those non-employee drivers. Oh, yeah, luckily we got a suit, Brian.
These, he's been out sick for a couple. You know, a lot of people have been out sick.
It's like a flu bug going around, but it seems like two different versions of it. I think I've been
very lucky. I see people get really stuffed up, sniffly, start sneezing. Maybe that's what I had
the last time I don't know. And some people get a really, really hard, bad stomach virus, bad stomach
flu, moody. What is moody? Moody is SVP of production and programming. His daughter, like
for five days, is at high fever and severe stomach cramping and stuff. Yeah, it's crap, man.
It literally, it's crap. And yeah, you come home, you flip on the television. There's all these
commercials for like, what does this cold medicine bring down that high fever fast for kids?
Are these people shooting shit into the air? Or something that they know?
You know, they're media buys. They're pretty fucking on the money, aren't they?
Ah, third, how about going to podcasts or houses? I'm back to the Doug Pilgrim's email. Go from
city to city across country. Each night, going to a different club where a pod sick musician would play
a gig and all your listeners from an area could come together. Damn. Trinity could be parked
outside. Swag could be given away. Live music from the show could be played on the podcast the next
day with videos sound and interviews from the show are kind of rolling pod fest 2007, 10 days,
10 cities, 10 concerts, one big promotional bang all ending in say New York with brother love playing
CC Chapman, Jersey Todd as the MCs. If you dig this, you would like me to propose this as an
audio. Oh shit, man. Of course, you got to send this in his audio. Don't make me read this.
Well, Doug, first of all, I really appreciate the fact that you're willing to explore. You
had a damn cool idea to start with and it's really grown into something else. And so I appreciate
you being open to, you know, you're not being all pissed off about the fact that we're taking
your idea and morphing it into something else. That's cool. Paul Savi, Adam, I work with a company,
skyships. We make vehicle tracking devices that you glue onto the roof of a vehicle. The
device is completely self-contained, solar powered, no wiring or battery required and contains
a GPS and GSM mobile module, which period of who transmits the vehicle location by SMS text.
Small company based in town. What is it? Chowmsford? Chowmsford, I guess, in the UK,
whose main business is remote controlled airships. What is it? Skyships.co.uk. Paul, very interesting.
That's exactly the type of thing I'm looking for. I think I'm looking for something a little bit
more advanced and not necessarily, although SMS is, of course, freaking bulletproof, isn't it?
You know, I'm trying to get Nokia into the game here. Maybe they could trick out one of their
camera phones. So it could send multimedia messages and me look. Come on, someone's going to be
able to put this together. The guys who've got the box are Nokia, but we're going to charge them,
obviously. Otherwise, yeah, I'd like to promote skyships. Let's see, there were a couple more
audio things. Let's see, what else do we have here? Hey Adam, this is Dawn, just a listener from
San Francisco Bay Area. About the free Trinity thing, you know, instead of a strapping app,
I might want to try Google Earth. I'm much more interactive. I know there's people who've
done overlays and stuff on it. Let's check that out. Yeah, you know, right,
our man, how silly of me, of course. I do like the fact that we can show an image as well,
so we can get an image from Google Earth into a web page, and that's cool too. But yeah,
absolutely, because that'll give the mainstream media something to some graphics. They can,
yeah, they can, they love doing that. I see that all the time now in television. They zoom in
somewhere and you can see it's, it's usually it says Google Earth right there in the corner of the
screen. So, you know, we'll be able to give them actual rolling video of the path that Trinity is
taking. And by the way, why limit this only to the U.S. of A? Hey Adam, it's all in here. I'm driving
in just near the egg in the traffic jam, and I was listening to your, uh, the source code by Trinity.
I think it's a fantastic idea to bring it from one coast to the other. But why don't you put
it into a global initiative? And, uh, Shiverdale would have Europe as well. You can hand out
it with a car from Port Gostom to Port Gostom. We all think it's for this thing, rather than the
bonding between two people, what you do, bonding between hundreds of people, make it around the
room with any space. Why not? Good luck. Right on. Okay, that's the kind of stuff I'm talking about.
I'm sure we can find someone with a, with a container and we can stop, you know, just push
right into a container and then, uh, retrieve it on the other end. Absolutely. I know we can do this.
So, here's what I think we got to start organizing. We've got to start organizing a number of
stops starting in San Francisco, and we want to take it all the way to, uh, I guess you're good in New York,
and then we go New York to Boston. We could ship it out from Boston. That'd be kind of a nice
sendoff. We've got a lot of people in the Boston area. And along the way, we, we, so we need bio fuel,
and so we need, or, you know, and also people doing interesting things with, just bio
crap, let's just do the, it's Trinity, free Trinity poop tour. Um, so we need that, um, we want to,
this is a, this is a, this is a pretty big project. I'm game for, if we're organizing
it, if we can really get some people who are motivated enough to work on this, I think it's,
it's primarily tools, you know, if, if we can track this, so that's why I said frapper map,
just because it's easy to do. You can probably import something from frapper into, uh, into Google
Earth anyway. Let's just set up a frapper map, so we can start putting, you know, start mapping out a route,
a more or less logical route, and it doesn't have to be straight across the US. We can go up and
down, let's know, problems, visit a couple of states while we're on what we're doing it anyway.
And so, as I was working through all that, I get this email, now I really got excited.
This is from, uh, Michael. Adam, I really like the father, Sonny wants the podcast
from driving across the US. The concept reminds me of another amazing accomplishment that
started with telling a story about a journey. I'm a cyclist. I've written across Iowa on
Ragbry, which is an acronym, and it's a massive crossstate bicycle race across Iowa that is well-known
throughout the US and the world. The R-A-G-B-R-A-I, Ragbry, is an acronym for Registers Annual Great
Bicycle Ride Across Iowa. Does any points to a Wikipedia article about it? I started in 1973
when a register columnist wrote that he was going to ride across Iowa with a friend. He did,
and he wrote about it daily for a week. During the ride, his readers love the story so much
that they did the ride the following year and invited anyone to join. The ride went from a few
to a few hundred. In a few years, it grew to over 10,000 and attracted riders from every state in the
US and many from around the world. Okay, so that's basically his setup. Here's his pitch.
How does this relate to Trinity? Well, how about if you give Trinity to the nice father, Son podcaster
and let him lead the first cross-country drive invite anyone with a bio-fuel vehicle to join
even if it's a short segment near where they live. And of course he's thinking, Michael says,
I think the media would jump on a cross-country trek of bio-fuel vehicles that provide heaps of
personal interest stories with blogs, audio, video, participant interviews, background stories,
what also advocating the use of bio-fuel. So my humble suggestion is to apply your podcasting
in media ingenuity. No, I love that. In distorting the first podshow annual great bio-fuel drive
across America. Well, I think we can come up with something snappy other than that. Free Trinity.
Yeah, of course he says, you can find a better job at finding an acronym. Probably good luck.
Hope this can help promote the awareness and use of bio-fuel. Michael, I'm loving that idea.
And you know, when I'm hearing that, I like, yeah, man.
You know, I want to be there for at least a part of it. That's going to be a frickin' party.
So okay, so when you buy a few vehicles that stop off along
route that is tracked by a frapper map, and hopefully also tracked with some kind of mystical box
that brings us pictures and video and GPS positions, it's just cool if we can do that.
Come on, we're geeks. So when people, places to stop off at who can help us with bio-fuel,
have bio-fueled vehicle might want to ride along. And the evening, of course, we want to wind
up at a pod save music gig. So that, that'll take a map. We got to coordinate this so we can see if we
can really get people together. And then what else do we need? And enough, I think it's a good start.
Okay, we got the weekend to think about it in a lot of people are behind, but let's see if we can
get this together. And you know, whatever needs to be done, poncho is going to do it because
this is just too much fun.
Yo, what's up, AC? It's Jersey Todd, the official musicologist of the Chacha.
Yo, big man, this is why you absolutely need to keep me hanging around the source code.
Dude, I heard you playing Jeremy Roe yesterday. All right, that's fine. But this song in line
to die, that was put up this past summer. People don't come to a food bar Friday to hear the
same old stuff, they come to you the new stuff, the fresh stuff, the stuff that absolutely kicks
ass. Man, oh man, oh man, the people are just not going to stand for that. Let's see, I'm going
to need some help with this. Yo, Jeremy Roe, where are you out today? Dude, can you help me out with
this? Hey, Adam, this is Jeremy Roe. I'm just sitting here on a Fubar Friday, drinking a cup
of shitty raw sewage coffee, but you know what, it actually tastes pretty good because I've got
ten packets of splendour in it. Anyways, I just wanted you guys to hear my new single
in the shadows off of my new album, Where the Truth lies, which is up on the PMN,
Podsafe Music Network. So here it is, check it out.
How it comes, that's exactly how it goes, sometimes out of my control, that's exactly how
it goes, that's exactly how it goes, that's exactly how it goes, that's exactly how it goes, that's exactly how it goes, that's exactly how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how
it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's what it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes, that's how it goes we're
Take safely how it goes
Sometimes I'll own my country
That's it, take it, I will
And take it, take it
Take it, take it
Bring me all the way around,
You better tell us,
Yeah,
Yes,
Oh yeah, Jeremy Row, find him on the PMN, winding up a football Friday and another week
in Northern California.
The next time we speak, I'll be back in Blighty with the ladies to have missed so very
much.
DailySourcego.com, Adam at podshow.com, I got to go because Stearns on Letterman, hey,
I'm still a Jersey boy.
What can I say?
Take care, everybody.
Bye-bye.
Potshow Podcast, stick it in your ear.
The best and the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in Content Delivery, Potshow
and Lidlight.