Hey, home fries and CC Chapman from accident hash encouraging you to check out BODOD.tv slash battle.
It's one of the coolest battle events out there and you can only find it at BODOD.tv.
Delta Sierra Charlie, six five zero.
With sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
With sixteen hundred dollars left to my feet high.
And the next and the daily source goes to my ears.
I like the big home drive it up don't worry.
But the nail is door-toed in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
My heart, the perilous day.
So, when you're not stupid or stupid,
It's true I'm in your hands.
I may not be a Christian but I've done all one man care.
I understand of my throne,
but all the flowers are gone.
So, when you're not stupid or stupid,
It's true I'm in your hands.
Oh...
Took a sweet young fall in my gun.
And this lazy line is show right
It's nothing, nothing, no
It's ending
Without the rest of the whole
There you are, the day you break
The sun was the change
And such a star of the days and this
Beyond the ruffle layer
We'll do now sit there
If it's true, I'll make your head
I'm in a big Christian
But I don't want to make him
I understand him all the rule
What all it was is wrong
So we'll do now
Sit there
You'll be with your own
With your own
You know, I'll say music that work
Just never ceases to amaze a hero
Show up next
And we'll sit
And Elton John
You may do things to shut down the internet
Together and do it
We're to now see Peter
Do myself
And Wilson has apparently recorded her first ever solo
Records titled Hope and Glory
It doesn't come out until September 11
Already two tracks on the pot safe music
Network it'll be out on Zoe
Rounder records
Clearly some guys have got some vision
Who put two tracks up on the PMN
That is awesome
And I like the song
Actually she also released
An awesome version of immigrant song
Which I think they mixed in pieces of magic man
From the old heart magic man song
It's fantastic
You've got to hear it
Links in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
It is episode number 650
Of the Delta Sierra Charlie
And no one sent me an email about this
It did pop up on one of those today in music history sites
Actually I think it was a Dutch one
It's at August 13th
The very first episode released
Of the Daily Source Code
And I think that's right
I believe it was a Friday
At the time it was a Friday the 13th
I think
It kind of makes sense since it was three years ago
Three days ago
Yeah, we jump ahead one day each year
So yeah, it was probably Friday the 13th
As we rolled out Daily Source Code episode one
Damn, wouldn't it be nice if I could find that very first episode
You know what?
I've got another song lined up coming up a little bit later on
And I'll see if I can find it for you
It's a Monday
Two more days until we take off for the family reunion
But the portable mixer
And the via laptop are going with me
I will be doing shows from the road
Since we'll be set up in a nice beach house on Fire Island
So with Wi-Fi
They told me broadband
So it may be hard-wired but who cares?
I'll be connected
Because I can't get through a week
Without my hit test
Or
Without my ass or size
I got to get tone note for the beach Amy
I've got to give me something good
Just the squeeze exercise
Hey Adam, it's Amy Mack, how you doing?
I'm okay
I'm hanging it
Well today you're going to be lying down on your stomach
I'm going to use a hate this
Okay, I'm going to call it
Go ahead and switch your microphone
Get yourself all situated
Let me get there
Yes
Alright, you're going to extend your arms over your head
Now you're going to raise your right arm
And lift your left leg
Okay
And of course you're going to be squeezing the butt
Oh my goodness
Now bring those down
And lift your left arm
And your right leg
That's
Good
Now I'll do it quickly
Back and forth
Squeeze the butt
And breathing
Alright, my stomach hurt
Alright
Keep your head down
So you don't hurt your neck
Breathe
Keep going
Yes, yes
Are you breathing?
Yes, I'm trying too
And done
Very good
Holy crap Amy
Well that's it for me
My whole week has been through barred
So I'm ready for some great music
To go into the weekend
Until next time
He told me
She meant this for Friday
Sorry about your week Amy
Hope it got better
I'm going to close the secondary mic there
I don't get the fan noise
Somehow the combination with the first coffee of the day
And the assurse lies
It's just a bit much
However, I will say
I went flying over
This is dumb
I went flying over the weekend
Saturday was
Of course, a beautiful day
Someday wasn't all that nice
And knew that was coming
Now as we're leaving
I literally had about
Two hours and 15 minutes left
On the clock or the Hobbs meter
As we call it
In the Delta Sierra
For its 50 hour
Checkup
Every 50 hours
As a certain type of checkup
Done every 100 hours
And of course there's the annual
So it's time for the 50 hour
In the way it works
As I fly the plane to Antwerp
When Commander gets in
Flies back with me
Drops me off
Or usually have a nice big
English breakfast or lunch
And then he flies back
And then sometimes when I get back
From the States
After the reunion
He'll fly it over
And we'll pick it up again
And it was nice
Contalia
I mean it's fun flying with people
Sometimes just being completely solo
Just you, the elements
The aircraft
Of course the air traffic
Of course the air traffic controllers
It's really just this romantic
It's beautiful
And I got admit
Sometimes I dream of actually flying
I know it's sad
But I just dream of
Take off some landings
And flying over things
And going places
And it's
I need more time
And there's a woman
Never cut that call
And she's in the cockpit
7.57 on the ground
In Phosman, Montana
You've been talking about your absolutely stunning weather
What do you've had?
Phosman Montana
Two-Harmouth
Physicality
Absolutely stellar day
But I am so jealous
If you get so much flying
Over there
In Europe and your plane
Did have a nice approach
And to hear high
Type worked out beautifully
And I'm just sitting here
Look on a glider flying overhead
So
Man, I'm right there with you
Missed the flying
Off to do it with you
Someday
In the Delta Sierra
Tailwind
Oh man
Of course
Redpill
I look forward to a robin
This robin
From inside works
And the diva cast
And he is a pilot for major airline
And he just calls in from time to time
The cockpit
When he too is dreaming about flying
It's a gene thing
I'm telling you
It's something wrong with us
All right Adam
I was listening to your show the other day
And you and I have exactly the same problem
My old computer
Was set up to log into the PMN
Without any trouble
And then when I changed jobs
That computer was left behind
To PMN
And I had lost the password
So
I clicked the button that said
I forgot my password
I figured it was going to walk me through a prompt
It said
A temporary password has been emailed to you
There's only one problem
I don't have that email account anymore
I can't get text for it to help me out
So whatever you did
Could you do me favor
Could you tell them to come over and do the same thing
For Bernie's world on the PMN
Because
I've had to start up basically into account
In PMN
And now I got two different playlists
And it's a big pain in the butt
Is there any way you can help me out?
Thanks a lot
Yeah, Bernie
So there's a couple things that are going
A couple of threads here
So there was
An I rate listener who called in on the footballer Friday
Not just a listener but a producer of a show
Who said I can't get the
I get a new password cent
This is for podshow.com
It's not for the pod save music network
And it gets a new password cent
Then it doesn't work
Now I have my theories about that
And it might tie into the PMN problem
Here's what happened to me
It was a little different
My account just was gone
It seemed or
Excuse me
Kmart still got that back to school dot com special
Back to school dot podshow dot com
It seemed like
It didn't even recognize the email address that I had registered with
Let alone the fact that I could retrieve any email from it
So I did the same thing dude
I've created a new account
And started you know link and stuff from there
Which is not what I want
Because I got my whole playlist history in there
So I was reading through the email this morning
A couple of different things going on
One is
We had to or have been having
Intermittent problems with one of our
Server slaves I think
And you know essentially what each slave has to
Understand is you know stuff like
Login information
And if it gets stock or doesn't synchronize
Properly then of course it will still be looking for your old
Password and hasn't seen the new password yet
Or some weirdness like that
So that's I think that was like web two or whatever
So that's been pulled out and I think they're fixing that
The pods and music network seems like there was some other issue at hand
And the account logins just disappeared
And so there I guess it's being worked on I'm not quite sure what the
Resolution is everyone still asleep in San Francisco
So I just kind of jumped into the email thread and I'll hear more about it later
As the day progresses
But obviously yeah that does kind of suck I got a couple requests
From people who have exactly the same thing you they signed up in 2005
And they've moved jobs or the email addresses have changed
I don't really know how other companies do that
How they deal with that because it must happen a lot that people go through this
So if you haven't experienced with you know with the
It hasn't really happened to me but if you have any
Best of breed ideas as to how that how that can be solved
Or what people are doing out there feel free to drop me a line about it
But it does it does obviously suck a little bit
Let me see I'm going to make it a reasonably short show today
You know not like 50 minutes or a full hour like I'm doing other days when I've been catching up
Wednesday I think by the way we should be able to pump out a full show because we fly into the future
We fly westbound so we pick up a couple hours on the way
I think we leave it like 930 and we arrive at 1230
And we should be at the beach house by the afternoon
Oh man, I'm so looking forward to this is going to be awesome
I got an email here
Let me just see a little disorganized
Wait a minute, a couple other things first
Oh yeah, Gmail
Years after I've asked for it have now made
Additional storage
Available for a fee
I can get up to 250 gigs
Which is nice
Yeah, I've been screaming for it for a long long time
This was cool
Dylan Alfred Adam was really nice hearing you chatting with Christina on
Daily source code episode 648 it's been a long time
I have a five year old daughter and a one year old son
Every time I hear you on your show with Christina
I feel like I get a glimpse of my future
Oh and the Kmart promo worked
After listening to that little bit you did
I jumped on Kmart dot com with my daughter Caitlin
Who will be starting kindergarten in a couple of weeks
And we found this great backpack slash lunchbox combo for her
For only 1199 mark down from 1999
Which is more in line with the prices
I've seen for similar items elsewhere
Thanks as Dylan from Portland, Oregon
Yeah, well, dude, you know what
First of all, I appreciate the feedback
And it's true stuff just works
What's more powerful than a free roll
Or some other form of 30 second eye
This one sent in is something that's going to be on the
Pot say music network today
So let's check it out
David Usher and music
Just let's sail in this shot
Like the stars we're born and die
Like these roses we all feed
I can't see in the cars
On the free way below
Lost in the music
On the foolishness of all others
Dreaming out of control
Lost in the music
In the music
David, please don't cry
We can't out from your eyes
We can't share some of it
There's no one in us in here
In the mirror, you're perfect
Plastic flowers never fade
We all turn the grey
We've got to look close
On the free way below
Lost in the music
On the foolishness of all others
Dreaming out of control
Lost in the music
In the music
On the swallowing out of steel
On the swallowing out
And singing
The music
David, please don't cry
We can't talk from your eyes
We can't catch up on the bed
No one is sitting here
Bodies хорошing and shining
Like the stars we are born and die
Like these roses, we all feed
It's as we all feel
You can't see in the cars
On the freeway below
Lost in the music
All the foolishness of all our lives
Dreaming out of control
Lost in the music
You can't see in the cars
On the freeway below
You can't see in the lights
And you're no better
You can't see in the cars
On the freeway below
Lost in the music
And the music
All right, now I get it
Meal beer scent this to me
There's always hooked me up with black lab tracks
You always see so excited to tell you this
You got to check the sky out as name is David Usher
There's a sold more than 1.3 million albums worldwide
He's won 5 Junos
That's the Canadian Grammy
Including the 2002 pop album of the year
Also in Canada he has 10 different singles
That hold the number one spot on radio, 10 singles
And the top 10
He's also had top 10
And top 20 radio singles
And what a nice list
England, Germany, Switzerland, Thailand, Malaysia
And Indonesia, Poland, Russia, Hungary, Sweden, Austria
Czech Republic is real Greece, Italy, France
The Philippines, Singapore and Taiwan
But I guess that's what we're going for next
And he grew up right down the street from Neil
So we talked to him last week
Twisted his arm and now this track
The music from his album Strange Birds
It's pot safe, awesome, it should be up today
Thank you Neil, yeah, great song man
It's been three years since I started doing this
And look at what's happening
We're now playing songs from Anne Wilson, Elton John
David Usher
But also all the ones we've grown up
Within the past three years, shit's really happening
My friends, you know what?
There's no such thing as luck
It's just perseverance
I'm still looking through my old dot MAC accounts
Trying to find the very first daily source code episode
Unfortunately
In three years time
The one thing I've not been able to get out of podcasting
He's a good lead from it
Well, except for the lady Patricia
But I don't even get offers, you know
You know Adam, Kenny from Northern California
Regarding the DSC 648
Thursday, you asked the caller
The most important question was you didn't answer
I was getting laid because of podcasting
Like I literally know personally
Not only am I getting laid more
than I was before
I picked up a few tips
By listening to some of the sex podcasts
You know sex is fun or let's get naughty
And just the other night my wife complimented me
Saying I had gotten better at whatever I was doing
And I just told her it was a podcast
So there you go
It is working
Fuck you later
Not exactly
Not exactly what I meant
I think women who you already married do don't count
Oh man, I'm talking like groupies
There's none of that in podcasting
That sucks
Hey Adam, this is Nick from Naples Florida
You've been talking a little bit about the ZNTV experiment
And so I finally decided a couple of days ago
But I looked it up and that's I was kind of reading through it
I realized this is
Not unlike something that I do while I'm at work
We have
You know it's
Don't know how much in detail I really want to go
It's a casino
Basically
So the TV is on but it's on mute
And sometimes you have the closed captioned on and sometimes we don't
Notice this is the experience is very very different
We have the closed captioned on
Or I should say depending on whether or not we have the closed captioned on
Without them it's extremely
Disorientating
You really have no idea what's going on
And it affects everything
It affects everything
It affects the way you perceive
Even things that aren't going on
You're actually interacting with
With the closed caption you have a bit of a different effect
It's not
As disorienting
But it's still you still seem
Detached on what it is
It definitely affects the way you
The way you respond
To the TV show
And I don't know
I'll see if I can flesh this out a little bit
I'll call back another time
Wait
I think I understand what you're talking about
But what you really need to do is take the ZNTV experiment
I guess not to put that link in again because people are filing
Catching onto it and doing it
It'll really give you a whole different perspective on what television really is
And what kind of tricks it plays on your mind
And how hard your mind actually has to work
When parsing the information that television passes off to you
It's more work than you think
If you think you're just laying in bed
And relaxing watching television your brain is actually an overdrive
And you can tell what happens
Guy gets completely fostered
Can you talk anymore?
You had another one from the Podsame Music
That word Jersey Joe took this one up
Buttered up on line
It's Edmund's Crown
Keep Richard's is still alive
Now that you've been told
It's time writing lies on the fat through the door
It's clearly a don't know what thing about rock and roll
Oh
I'm sorry, but keep Richard's is still alive
This is show some self control
And we can stop putting stickers on trees like ours
It's clearly a don't know thing
About rock and roll
Now you may not agree
It just doesn't matter
If rock and roll the illusion to soon
To be shattered
It sounds the bottom of the way
But you need it as a taste around your gun
I'm sorry, but keep Richard's is still alive
So shut your life your whole
And stop writing what's on the fat through the door
It's clearly a don't know what thing about rock and roll
Rock and roll
Well, should be pretty clear
Keith Richards is king
Edmund's crown tells us all about it
They are on the pod safe music network
I must say that
Wait, wait, wait, first episode
Hold on a second, I've just been searching
Throughout the entire show
Seeing if I can find
Oh, ten, oh, man
Oh, crap
I just, no, I don't think I'm going to have any luck finding it
Let me say
One result stored on your computer
No, crap
Well, if you have that, give me a pointer
And I'll put it in the show notes
Okay, I don't even have my own shows
I need to produce her so bad
All right, enough whining for me
We're going to have a great week
It's going to be fun and jam packed
With all kinds of jet setting things
As we fly off to the east coast
Tomorrow, I'm leaving the beautiful weather in the UK behind
Although I think we'll have some
Maybe a thunderstorm later on the afternoon
It's going to heat up, I see some CBs forming
Enough about the weather
DailySourceco.com for the show notes
Adam at podshow.com
If you're desperate to need to tell me something or send me some checks
Or make a pictures, I'll be here tomorrow
Bye-bye
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best and the brightest
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content
Delivering podshow and limelight