A Domain Registration is a gift that keeps on giving for all the geeks in your life.
The newer shot hit GoDaddy.com.
Listen to this podcast for a special code that you can use to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
In a world where big ass voice guide Don LaFontaine does the intro for the daily source code.
Most podcasters would be intimidated.
Most of them will wet their tiny little pants, being afraid to create a new intro for Adam Kirk.
But not one.
One voice guide is ready to take on the biggest voice in the movie.
It's the daily source code that Adam Kirk.
Because there's no way you can be cuter than that.
Delta Sierra Charm 5-2.
60 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Welcome to the DSC 5-50 view.
No animals were injured when he making up his podcast.
Adam Kirk moved the hell out of some earth.
I never had much luck with girls.
They never liked to read and learn.
But I like to.
And if I could figure out the cause I know of your heart.
That be a good start.
Oh yes it would.
I never tried a date online.
Use everybody that's built to find.
I said that not that.
So if you look at this great.
Is there an unboss game.
You'll be my first place.
Because baby we'll be in the chat room.
On the IOC.
I'll have the big prom.
Star Trek costume for me.
Time in the time zone.
Go play.
TNT at baby.
It's upnerd to me.
You know what to say.
Let's get a nice opening on guys.
My face is going to set you free.
I'll be a fanboy.
And my star feeds you live on.
It matches the one ball.
But I never need more.
So baby we'll be in the chat room.
On the IOC.
I'll have the big prom.
Star Trek costume for me.
Time in the time zone.
Go play.
TNT at baby.
It's upnerd to me.
Be see pick up that guitar man.
Talk to me.
I'll have the big prom.
On the IOC.
Star Trek costume for you and me.
Time in the time zone.
Go play.
TNT at baby.
It's upnerd to me.
You know what to say.
Okay.
It works for me.
There's somebody out there.
It's going to like that song.
The fun.
Fox drug uniform.
Talk nerdy to me.
Speaking off.
Another week on the daily source code.
Everybody how you doing.
It is Delta Sierra Charlie five five two coming to you from the curry condo.
It is Monday only just though.
It's 12.45 a.m.
Back from Los Angeles.
It's a very interesting time.
Of course to be in LA and in Hollywood.
With the with the Academy Awards.
I'd have to say that's the part of Hollywood.
I don't like that much.
Or not.
I'm not that interested.
Yeah.
I'm just not interested in it as much as I am in.
The plumbing of Hollywood and how how stuff is put together.
You know how a movie like Seriana is is put together in package.
Great movie.
Real feel good movie.
Or how Steven Spielberg will do the new transformers.
You know, these are all amazing.
Amazing things that go on in the back room.
And which was also why it was there.
So of course I didn't actually go to the Academy Awards.
I don't get tickets to that.
Shit.
I don't get you.
I don't even get invited to the MTV Awards anymore.
So I watched those on TV.
I got to tell you it was I like the show.
It was you know, long as as usual.
It felt even longer than usual.
Perhaps Ellen DeGeneres.
I think she did a great job.
It was a very different approach.
You know, instead of real high tension, high comedy bits.
You know, it was almost like our TV show.
I like that.
That was that was kind of nice.
And it gave a very nice relaxed atmosphere.
And you could really tell that people there were having a good time.
Yeah.
You know, I think the takeaway from me from this year's award show is I'm pretty proud
that America is producing this stuff.
And even more so because if you were keeping count.
And I wasn't actually keeping count.
But how many foreigners?
And I don't mean that in a derogatory way.
One Oscars.
Through this magic making machine known as Hollywood.
I mean, that's pretty cool.
People are coming to United States to realize their dream.
And I think there are also some darn good movies that were made.
Yeah, it was good.
It was nice.
For me, it really felt like it was much more celebration of everything that happened.
It was just my perspective this time around.
I don't know.
But just, you know, the way movies are made.
What an amazing business.
I probably have a little bit more appreciation for it in the past year and a half or so.
We've been doing a lot of productions at Pod Show.
And I know what it takes.
You know, just to get a show like Textra up and running.
It takes a lot of people and a lot of hard work.
And yeah, the technology has improved and it's become much more affordable and much more efficient
without a doubt.
But you still need people who definitely know what they're doing.
So I'm going to run out a couple of things for you.
Quick you.
Let me see.
Oh, yeah.
I fixed my Wi-Fi problem.
Did I tell you that?
I don't think so.
Just inability to connect in in most spots throughout the condo to the to the Wi-Fi network.
Part of that without a doubt because there's just so many networks that I could get up here on the 24th floor.
It's outrageous.
Let me see.
I got a couple of the comments on that.
The first one was a prolific programmer.
Interesting.
He says I see a lot of the two fire Wi-Fi access points.
I've seen those two.
It's a number two wire.
According to a prolific programmer, those are SBC routers.
Interesting.
So they have some kind of wireless thing as well.
I had a, I think I had some comments on this.
A lot of people were, you know, very helpful trying to,
you know, come up with ideas and solutions.
What my possible problem can be.
And I'll tell you what I did to fix it.
But first let's hear some of the suggestions because I thought that they might be kind of handy.
And I probably ran into one of these problems.
Otherwise networks are you seeing where you live.
That's, that's an audio comment I wouldn't mind having.
In fact, all right.
So this is sneaker paid from Amsterdam.
The Western Nouns Courts of Amsterdam, actually.
And these are the names of the networks in my neighborhood.
De Vries.
We've got three speed touches with the strange extensions numbers.
We've got one Apple network.
We've got a 06 for dreams.
I guess that's a telephone number or something.
We've got a lot of week.
We've got two live boxes and one guy loving his
router and calling it sexy thing.
Hmm.
That's kind of weird.
Anyway, these were the networks from Amsterdam.
Show Adam.
So it turns out that there is an issue that I didn't even think of.
Having the same access name, access point name or SSID is its known.
Could of course be a tremendous issue.
Now, it's named Curry Kondo here.
But somewhere along the the routes of my testing,
I know I reset it and I said, okay, screw it.
I want all settings back to default.
And of course, then the access point gets the name default.
Well, guess how many defaults there are.
Hi, Adam.
It's Martin from Reading.
A couple of things for you.
You're wireless network.
You're having trouble with it.
It sounds suspicious to me, although I'm not an expert.
That's someone else has got a wireless network.
And they've set it up to the same SSID as you're wireless network.
And what is probably hacking is your machine is linking onto their network rather than yours.
And the password or the security you've got set up obviously doesn't match theirs.
And therefore, what you're getting is no IP address.
I can't really explain that one because normally, if you get a web key conflict,
we'd add my web key.
You usually get a nice address, but you don't get any traffic flowing, for example.
You could try just changing your SID, changing your web key,
or if you're using WPA or something else.
You could try changing that.
And turn off any bulkcasting you're doing.
And you might, if you could have other people's wireless networks and somebody really just
feel like constantly setting their wireless network to the same as yours.
You might need to do this several times.
So that makes a hell of a lot of sense to me.
And I did see that problem quite a lot where you'd get, you'd be connected,
but wouldn't get an IP address.
And of course, you know, I was on default.
I was just trying to set the whole thing up again.
I'm just going back to the basics.
But so many people don't change their access point name that they leave it in default mode.
And I guess that was conflicting.
So I figured that one out.
So I changed it back to something unique, which Cody condos seemed pretty reasonable.
And then I decided to download the new firmware or an updated version.
I still had firmware from like 2004 or maybe, yeah, 2004.
Well, whatever they changed, man, it made a big difference.
That's something I should have checked right out of the box.
Sure.
But this dealing box isn't that old.
Only bought it maybe 8 or 9 months ago.
So you could at least expect that they'd change that somewhere along the way.
So fixed.
It works now.
All my wireless devices connect.
Thank you all so much for all the helpful ideas and tips that you sent in.
Second thing.
Totally unrelated.
You commented the other day about people skipping over things in your show.
And it's always when I'm driving along in the car.
It's always frustrated me that in my car.
I have to hold down the fast forward button on my stereo.
And I'm playing the MP3 file.
And I have to listen to it sort of fast forwarding it.
So the double or triple speed.
And you have to just hit your finger off the button.
And exactly the right point.
Otherwise you miss what the next.
So the right to miss on the show.
And I noticed the other day I was listening to a podcast.
Which I found on iTunes called Dom Jolly versus the planets.
Now I'm not advocating this podcast because I actually listened to it.
And then I think I deleted it.
So if you played on the iPod as an MP4 and iTunes format file.
On the iPod it actually shows up as having little bookmarks in it.
Now I'm sure maybe the rest of the world already knows about this.
But this is a revelation to me because it means you can actually just by pressing the fast forward button on the iPod.
Or if you got the iPod connected to some of the device like a car stereo.
You can actually just by pressing the button that would normally skips the next track.
And it skips the next segment.
Now obviously simple.
And there's something you probably have to publish everything on Porto in the MP4A.
I'm not sure if you already do that.
But it just struck me as something that is a really good way as navigating a what could possibly be a quite a long podcast.
From anybody who's publishing a podcast.
So there you go.
Maybe somebody out there knows more about it.
And they can perhaps explain to us how it all works and how perhaps you guys could book it in.
But I think it'd be a great idea to implement on many of your shows.
Because it would wrap people to navigate through their shows.
So I'm going to stop ramping.
Yes.
I'll speak to you later.
Okay.
So I do want to respond to that.
Yeah.
Technically that's possible.
Bookmarking in the AAC format that is predominantly used on Apple iPods.
There are some different ways to bookmark with an MP3s.
And I don't really want to open that discussion up because it's something that we've, you know, we've had a lot.
Over the past three years.
And I really don't like bookmarking and not for if it's for the sole purpose of annotation.
Or certain type of content.
It makes a lot of sense.
You know, if it's a speech and you want to go to a certain section in the speech and it has to be indexed.
But this is not a speech.
You know, you're not listening to me for, you know, just to pull out nuggets of information.
If you are, well, tough.
I don't want to make it easy for you to skip ahead.
Now, obviously, the music, I put a lot of thought into it.
I don't just play stuff really nearly.
I listen, I get a lot of feedback.
I get a lot of suggestions.
There's a whole bunch of different reasons why I play stuff.
And, and I really, that's the one thing I continuously am trying to adjust to keep it fresh.
Keep it interesting.
So we all can learn something.
So we can enjoy something together.
And, you know, a lot of people skip through the songs.
But to make it easier for you to skip through topics now.
I'd rather you say that I'm just rambling and give me some other type of feedback.
But that's just too lazy for me.
No, no.
I mean, it's like, yeah, just skip around to the podcast.
And by the way, it is a hell of a job to annotate that.
You know, it's not like, okay, I'm finally done with the show.
I've prepped it for an hour and a half.
I record the show.
Now, I have to go back and annotate everything.
I need a full time producer for that.
You have a transcription department is what they have.
What they call that.
I don't have that yet.
But still, it's like, no, this is, this is my art.
Please, stay with me.
That's really important.
And you could miss a really nice gems if you fast forward through stuff.
And what should we do?
Just make it easier.
Get bookmarking and we'll put in some technology.
And I applaud that blows you.
I mean, make it really easy.
Yeah, I'm just applying from Parker in Colorado.
And I was just listening to DSC551 and walking out to some of the music you've played
a day, especially free ride.
That was awesome.
And the deafsmith, Jingle, totally made me think of it.
You nailed it on there.
He is so good at those.
Do you have a good work?
Boulder.
So I was talking about this with a friend of mine.
Because I really did enjoy just jamming out on Friday.
That was a lot of fun.
And I got a lot of amazing feedback when we go into some kind of musical archive
and play something from 25, 30 years ago.
People really seem to love that.
And so a new segment, hold on a second.
I don't quite have the, what actually, I started on some, some imaging.
It's not edited yet, but you'll get the idea.
Let me undo the plug here because I've got to put this one into my,
hold on.
I want you to actually hear the plug hold on.
Here it.
Okay.
That means I'm actually putting this plug live.
Oops.
Now you can hear it.
I'm putting it into my first generation iPod.
Do you have one of these?
Are you like me?
Are you a lazy bastard?
Who doesn't manage his songs on his iPod with that?
Incredibly handy interface known as iTunes?
No.
What you do is you fill it up and you buy a new one or maybe if you've traveled enough on Virgin Airlines, you get one for free.
And you just fill it up with more stuff.
This is the iPod that I used in 2004.
Yeah, 2004 when I was doing my, you know, the first testing with, with iPod or with my Apple script,
the first shows before they were called Daily Source Code, all kinds of material because at the time,
I literally saved everything because we were working on this technology and it was initially implemented through iTunes and the iPod.
So everything that I had pod caught every element, everything went on into iTunes and subsequently onto the iPod.
It is a mess.
It is just filled.
It is, I don't know.
What is this?
The 20 gig I think?
One of the first gen iPods.
It's filled with,
God knows what.
And in no particular order.
But on top of that, Napster was still, you know, he had open nap and stuff running at the time.
Well, what I would do is I built a little script that I could just type up a text file,
drop it into a folder and this script would go out and pull all the Napster servers.
And the script, of course, would contain band names and song titles.
And it would go out search things, pull them in, and then, you know, it would basically download everything that I wanted on my list.
And another little piece of, it was so cool back in the day when all the shit still worked.
I also had a way so that I could throw that list in and the minute it had downloaded at least a portion of one of the songs.
It started to play that.
And basically my playlist would just keep on going and, you know, throughout the day, maybe a type a couple more songs that I'd been thinking about,
thinking of and throw that into the folder and then those songs would magically be found and start to play eventually.
So it is kind of like what Napster is today.
I told you, I'd really like the Napster idea of paying 10 bucks a month or whatever it is and just being able to play anything you want.
Yeah, okay, I can't take it with me, but I don't, that's just not the way I consume mood music.
I don't mind it being only when my laptop is connected because I hope that up to my speakers and I get the same enjoyment out of it.
It's certainly $10 worth.
There's not a lot of things that only cost $10 that give me this much pleasure.
Oh, I can think of a couple that come close anyway.
So what I'm going to do from now on in every daily source code is we're going to play a track from Adam's first gen iPod.
Completely at random.
It's on shuffle.
I'm not looking.
Now, if I don't recognize what it is, I may have to just bend over and because it's on a different shelf here on the bake as a rock.
So I can take a look at it.
Hold on, let me, yeah.
To the next track at random.
Okay, I don't want to hit.
Wait.
Let's see what it comes up.
Let's see what this is.
Wow.
This is something called the barrage.
And sing, sing, sing.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
You know, at first I didn't really know why that would be my first gen iPod, but listening to that holy crap.
Man.
Oh, wait.
I'm not supposed to do any more tracks.
Only one per show from Adam's first gen iPod.
I think that's going to be the name.
Another track from Adam's first gen iPod.
Something like that.
I got to find out more about that track.
I have no idea how wound up on the iPod.
I don't have any backstory on it.
Of course, that is part of the game.
Sometimes I'll know how what it is, what this sound file is, or what it's about, or
I'll have some personal story, just not this time.
That's always a great way to start off a new segment.
That's it for our serious listeners.
They're gone.
That's too bad because they probably would have enjoyed this promo.
Hi, Adam.
This is Matt Detillow of the Matt's Today in History podcast.
I'm going to let you know how honored I am to be a new member of the Pod Show family.
You know, I started listening to the Charlie long before you were using episode numbers.
You're enthusiasm for this new medium.
And you're belief that every subject and pursuit under the sun needs a podcast.
Made me want to try my hand at it.
Thank you.
For you Charlie listeners, if you're a serious student of history or just a casual observer,
I'd like to invite you to check out my podcast, a Max Today in History.
In five to ten minutes, I covered an event that occurred on today's date sometime in the past.
From sobering to silly, from before the Roman Empire to the fall of communism and beyond,
I covered all the little at a time.
You can find me at Matt's Today in History.podshow.com, and wherever podcast congregate.
And I'm really glad that show is now a...
It's with us in Pod Show.
I've been listening to Matt's Today in History. I like it very much, and I'm just just been informed
that Peter was going to make an edit in that another track from Adam's first gen iPod,
so we can still fit Matt's Today in History, promo in on the within the serious satellite window.
Peter, you truly are awesome, dude.
Unlike this guy,
Adam, I'm one of these Nylons, a New York London guy.
Awesome.
But first of all, Nylon, I've not heard that before.
A New York London guy, a Nylon.
Hmm.
For the Wilmoton, and it's this Trinity thing that's got me a little farther,
because quite honestly, you know, I like to show,
but you should downplay if not eliminate totally the green aspect of it.
Because...
But before this guy goes on, I want to say something about this,
because I've received a couple of emails,
that in tone sound very much like this guy,
and I'm going to tell you what his message is first,
so you can be completely biased when you listen to him.
But essentially, he's going to say that
the whole Trinity project is not green,
and you shouldn't be promoting green with this project.
And, you know, I don't think I've ever used the word green.
The whole point is about independence
about being able to do something on our own without anyone's help,
let alone big oil or any type of industry.
It's fun, you know, and it's saying something,
and it's about people and about relationships,
and about doing something ourselves,
and in a way sticking it to the man, because that's always fun.
But I cannot recall one single episode,
where I ever said it was even in the entire discussions of Trinity,
that it was green.
Yeah, I'm still here,
it's still here my iPod bleeding through,
so I turn that off.
So I think that there's something a foot here,
and it's really interesting, because when you hear this guy talk,
it doesn't sound like he's been listening at all
about anything about Trinity,
my baby poo colored 1984 Mercedes station,
bio diesel station wagon,
but it's going on the road,
fueled entirely by biodiesel,
not ethanol.
Oh, I got a lot of those, too.
Don't you know that it takes more energy to produce my old fuel,
than it does, and then you get out of it?
No, that's not the case, because this is not ethanol.
This is shit we get from the Chinese restaurant.
The only energy it takes is a little bit of elbow grease.
So anyway, so listen to this guy,
and tell me that this isn't someone who is just,
it sounds like the guy's calling a list.
Okay, I gotta call this guy,
gotta tell him he's full of shit.
I don't know, listen.
You're the least green person probably out there.
You see your own admission on Twitch,
they had a million miles on version.
Okay, wait a minute, there's another clue.
There's no, he's on the least green person out there,
by your own admission on Twitch,
you have a million miles on virgin.
Okay.
Well, maybe the all are coming from Twitch,
all these letters, from Twitch listeners.
That's kind of weird.
All right, listen more.
I'm flying gold, so I know that's probably about 300,000.
It's miles, you've actually flown.
But hey, you steal two foot prints on the virgin,
and you're commuting every month.
How you want to company virtually?
That's a different story.
You then have souped up cards on in your house too,
and then you go flying on a plane.
You're on plane, mind you.
Three, so, and who knows how much electricity
you're wearing up there in the cottage mansion,
whatever it is?
So, yeah, you know, the turn of your thing is fine.
And then finally, I love the fact that you're going to have all these
sorts of there promoting Trinity,
they're going to be paying for it.
They're going to drive it 50 miles,
and how they're going to get back to their starting point.
Cycle run, probably not,
but they have a car, but it's a train.
So, they'll be adding to the CO2 footprint.
So, let's just keep Trinity of the car,
and you're given away a car, which is a nice thing to do.
And let's just stop the whole green thing,
because we like to do,
but you really have no license to be talking about green,
given the jack, virgin miles, your own flight.
These folks are going to drive 50 miles up and get back 50 miles.
It's not really the right thing.
Thanks.
Hey, I don't know who this is,
but stop fucking calling Disneyland's hole.
Really?
Now, I'm sorry, man,
but I have not played this as a green thing at all.
At all.
And this to me is just,
I think this is part of a group of environmental terrorists.
Now, I do plenty of green things,
but that's a whole different discussion.
This is about something completely different.
And if you're not listening,
and don't propagate the hate, my brother,
that's no good.
Now, I got an email from Drew Darmcus.
Hey, I'm not sure if you're familiar with the, I'm sorry.
I gotta blow my nose once I can hold on.
I didn't really blow it,
but I didn't want you to hear the other thing.
Hey, I'm not sure if you're familiar with the stand for project,
folding at home.
I doubt, of course, got my attention.
It's a distributed computing program similar to
City, which was the search for extraterrestrial intelligence, I believe,
which is distributed through a screen saver.
God, that was a cool application, wasn't it?
The processing power goes towards research for cancer and other diseases.
Oh, nice.
Go to dndfoldingathome.com.
Oh, man, another thing I got to install on my computer.
You had another little server, a widget thing.
It'll be rolling around in the background.
Ah, this was great.
Apparently down under the catch and on,
why do I always do the accent when I say down under,
I apologize, that must be pretty insulting.
Australian commercial on television.
This is a YouTube clip.
Oh, on a second.
Of course, I forgot to shut up.
I got to plug the computer back in.
There we go.
Okay.
This should do it.
Listen to this commercial.
It's tough growing up in a family of scrunches.
My parents of scrunches.
My sister's a scruncher.
And my brothers.
I'm a folder.
My great grandmother was a folder.
But she's dead.
I reckon I'll be a folder till the day I die.
If you're a folder or a scruncher, Australians love sobbing.
Oh, don't you just love that.
You guys are so smart.
And remember I talked about that.
It turns out it was a Lego, an automatic Lego machine.
That not only folds your toilet paper, but then cuts it for you.
I got a YouTube message.
And it's from Ed Hidden of the light source podcast.
StudioLighting.net.
And you said, this is a project that me and my friends built for school at the UC Berkeley.
It's made of Lego Mindstroms.
Is that it?
Mindstroms?
Sizzers and some scrap metal.
With all things considered, I think it turned out all right.
No, it does it fold your paper for you.
It also cuts it.
It would be the perfect accessory for a fancy high tech Japanese bathroom.
Really awesome dude.
I really don't mind doing the fold myself.
But I will put a link in the show notes because I don't know if I did that last time when I talked about it.
I love it.
At least now we know it wasn't it.
What do I think it was like an erector set turns out?
It's just good old Lego.
Hi everybody.
It's Ed O'Vat host of the Ed's Mixbag podcast.
Saying hi to all you Charlie listeners.
You've heard me before here on the DSE for various show promos.
But this time I'm here to tell you that after producing 70 shows,
I finally took the plunge and I'm now hosted by Pot Show Plus.
Yeah.
Find me at Ed's Mixbag.potshow.com
and get all the new subscription feeds at my show page.
Oh and Adam, just one more thing.
Everyone is invited to hear Whitney Steel speak a mind about
her recent involvement in the One Tree Hill TV show competition
in a recent Skype interview.
I had with this podcast singer songwriter diva.
That's coming up on Saturday, March 3rd, 2007.
But the full episode number 73 of the Ed's Mixbag podcast
at Ed's Mixbag.potshow.com
and by the way.
Hold her.
Yeah.
I figured as much.
All right Ed.
Thanks, man.
Welcome aboard.
Okay.
Last one for today.
Another awesome song.
I got an email from Andy Stone.
Adam just let you know I've released my EP in the coffee shop.
When, for download, you kindly played the title track in January.
Since then, I've made all four songs.
Podsafe.
And would be very appreciative if you check them out at my page.
I'm Pod Show.
Of course, I'll link to that in the show notes at DailySourceco.com.
It'd be more than happy to.
But the back and drink.
You walked in and a new plot.
Was introduced to me.
But what's that red blood from my head?
The letter said nothing to me.
Literally.
They've felt transparent on the edge.
I couldn't see.
I asked if you liked Oscar Wilde.
Drunk comedies.
But what were you like as a child?
And did you feel the green?
But what's your main job?
College major.
What you have and love the team?
To love the dream.
You say it'll bring us another love.
It's quite lovely.
The music melted through the air.
I love the shadowing of all the other people there.
It wasn't that the ring.
Though it's our next story.
This will all eclipse by me and you.
That's not true.
And yet I can't tell them about you.
I know it's not unique.
I know it happens every day.
When you be for me.
You say it's never been that way.
But never the right.
Even precise.
I can't see that point of view.
I believe it's true.
Cause there is no time for this love.
I can see you.
Thanks for really hoping one of these days.
We bump into the Beatles on Adams first gen iPod.
Andy Stone in the coffee shop.
When winding up the daily source code five five two from the Curry condo.
Northern California for a nice Monday.
Hi everybody.
Another couple days somewhere in the middle.
I'm going to I'm going to lose a show somewhere between traveling back.
To the cot.
Well maybe not Thursday Friday.
We'll see.
Now we can't miss football.
We can miss football Friday.
I'll do football when I get home Friday.
But maybe a little bit late.
Maybe a Friday afternoon football.
All right.
Adam at occur.
I don't podshow.com.
Sorry.
I haven't quite set up all the professional Gmail enterprise edition yet.
So keep it still the pod show.
And David source code.com.
Talk to you tomorrow.
Bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery.
Pot show and lightweight.