Oh, miffy, look, there's Adam.
Adam, Adam.
Oh, look, he's wearing those rose colored glasses.
Oh, per se.
Oh, Adam, boy.
I hear you're still doing that show, though,
dairy, saucecare.
You're up to what 540 shows now.
Two-shake good boy.
That's a great, great job doing that for little people.
And they're thinking you've got going with the car.
Very funny stuff, you know, shooting in the tank and all.
They just keep Henry from drinking too much and shooting in his ponds.
I have to go and sleep in the guest room when he does that.
Oh, miffy, look, you're having to wet the bedroom.
You've had a few too many martinis.
So, tell us Adam, what are you going with this posh people,
their pig skits?
It's very funny stuff.
But you don't really believe that, do you?
What?
Why would you say that?
You're really?
Well, I'm slightly offended, Adam.
Well, Gary, you should just go on and do your D.R.C.540.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
And the next generation renew contenting flight users.
We don't need no thinking.
I like to think I'm sorry.
We need to think you're in a good room.
I guess it's at a period.
I don't know her.
Maybe about it.
Could I justify all elevators who never have been cheated?
She don't remember.
Not a good inside.
So she picks a fight.
She's right.
And all this black and white at killing time.
She's a good girl.
She's good.
coming to you from the Curry Manor on the west side of G-town in the affluent suburb of
Suri known as Gilford. And it's another beautiful day. Captain Dan just called me and said,
we're on for Friday. So traveling on Friday going to visit Cas Blaster Mike. Of course,
I immediately said, can we have a day like today as well? Wouldn't that be nice? It's another one
of those blue skies. A couple of clouds, but it looks like the ceiling is relatively high.
So we could just pop up over it and I wouldn't be nice to fly a little bit.
Come fly with me, my friends. It's Tuesday in the United Kingdom. Yesterday was man, what a day.
It was like non-stop. And as you know, there was so much Trinity stuff. It's luckily I was able to take
care of a lot of that yesterday that I was severely behind. I had an appointment to speak with
Barbara the Palo Alto podcaster who you've probably encountered on the Google group for free
Trinity, you know, to talk through how she could help with the project. And I was like an hour
and 10 minutes late. I was able to email during the show and stuff. But that's, you know, when
I'm an hour and a half late, then most of the day is pretty screwed up. And I don't think I was
done until like midnight, something like that. Anyway, Christina didn't have to get up very early
this morning. So we all kind of stayed in bed to like 830. What a luxury. Yes. Yes. Wonderful.
I got to plenty of plenty of stuff to go through today. I almost don't know where to start.
Let's see. Yeah. This is a nice one. Tony Schins, I will listen Belgium.
You actually has a YouTube site where he records himself doing drum solo. It was pretty cool.
He has a Saudi via that he uses to record his videos. He uses a reason and so on. All the
all the lovely tools to do that. At the same ground loop problem with the funky Belgium 240
volt system, here's how I limited the ground loop. Remove the ground. Okay. That makes sense. I guess
most of your sound equipment in via have a three-prong plug. I use an adapter on these three-prong
plug level. Let me see. I don't even know if there's a... I don't think it has a three-prong plug.
I'll look into that, but that doesn't sound like the most logical way to get rid of a ground loop
problem by removing the ground. Isn't the ground there for a reason? Any ends up as email by saying,
by the way, in Belgium it's very common for the top toilet seat to fall down. Is that an
engineering design? Is that a feature? What exactly is that? We might as well get straight into it.
I've been doing some research on the quest for answers to find out whether push people are
potty pigs. It certainly seems that way, and I do have my thoughts about it now, my friends.
I think it's something it's an inner child in all of us, because of actually witnessed, well,
not exactly the same thing, but we have a teenager here. And, as you know,
to live in the house, she happens to be related, love her dearly, but sometimes she's a teenager.
And there's two things that it's very interesting to observe from my vantage point, to see Patricia
and Christina, in this endless loop, an infinite loop, if you will, from a
programming engineer's perspective, an infinite loop, where Christina makes a mess in either a,
her room, or b, the bathroom. Now, it's not like there's toilet paper on the floor and stuff,
but there's clothes and she leaves bottles and stuff all over the place. And, you know, it's always
like, could you please clean it up? If you ask her to clean it up, but I've, I've long figured out
the reason why it doesn't happen, because if she doesn't clean it up, Patricia cleans it up.
And so we've gotten into this habit forming, where it's like, it doesn't matter because someone's
going to clean it up, and it'll be done. If it didn't get cleaned up, or, as I say,
if I dump them in the toilet bowl and then through the monitor bed, she might get the
message, of course, I'm never allowed to try any of my ideas. But, you know, as a student of
Anthony Robbins, people run away from pain and run towards pleasure. And I think that the pain level
of this infinite loop of clean up your shit just isn't enough because the reward is so high,
you know, just leave it and it takes care of itself. And I think this is exactly what's happening
in public bathrooms, whereas probably everybody, but most surprisingly, very well-mannered,
posh people who would not do something like this at home are doing it in their office bathrooms
in public restrooms that just leaving the shit all over the place. Yes, or what, you know,
I mean, of course it happens that you sometimes you might just miss your target or something
nasty can happen. But why clean it up because it's going to be cleaned tomorrow? It's like magic.
I think that is part of the problem. But we're learning a lot about our fellow man in this
quest, my friends. Hey, Adam, this is Tokyo Dan. I haven't given you a feedback for a long time,
but this is for the our posh people, pig segment. Lately, in the last 20 years over here in Japan,
things have been proved a lot lately, and the Japanese aren't too piggy, even the posh people.
But one thing that does bug me, if you go to a public restroom, and you want to use the shitter,
right? These guys just, they stay in there. They're camping out in there and, you know, the stalls
are all full. You really need to go. And these guys are in there just, I don't know what they're doing.
They don't come in. Don't they live in there? Isn't the housing such a problem in Japan that
maybe they're just using them as, as they're peer to tear? Well, in the city, I live in Stahl 13.
Ma, are they, are they reading? Are they sleeping? Are they beating off? I don't know, but just
get the hell out of the toilet. No, it's a public toilet. It's not in your home. Other people are
waiting. Other people want to use it. They have no regard for the people waiting. People of Japan.
People of Tokyo. If Tokyo Dan or Brake will get that hell out of the stall, really bugs me.
One of the good things about it over here is a lot of the public toilets, especially in the department
stores and movie theaters. They have what we call Star Trek toilets. I mean, these, these toilets
have like armrest with all kind of controls on it. Today, hot air that blows on you to dry
off and you can actually adjust the pressure of the bidet, the hotness of the air and all this.
When you're standing up, taking a leak in one of these things, you have to be careful that
you don't hit the wrong button. I tell you, man, I've had one of those toilets and I love them.
I absolutely love them. And I'm thinking about getting, I mean, they're big. That's the problem
and the bathrooms in the manner. There's enough bathrooms, but they're, I don't know if they're
big enough for one of these basically snowmobile type devices, but I love them. I had them at the
the bunker in Amsterdam. In place we had there, it was so nice. You sit down immediately.
A fan starts, starts sucking away any odours. Not a lot of controls, by the way. It's not
necessary to have all those controls if it's a proper one. When you're done with your business,
you press little button, a little faucet comes out, turns up. Mr. Fires, and bidet of Fires,
your private area with a nice warm squeeze. Completely adjustable, of course.
Upon letting loose of the button, the blow dryer turns on. They are wonderful, Dan.
Because you might get a stream of air or a stream of water blown right into your face,
they have to be careful. Another thing is, the women's toilets I heard, as soon as you open the
stall, the stall door, the sound of flowing water starts playing. And this is just to cover up the
more embarrassing natural sounds. So, things are pretty advanced over here. So that's about the
only pet peeve I've had about the way the Japanese use their toilets over here, but oh no, it's pretty
good. Well if you want to hear more interesting things about Japan, check out the frustration
segment. On my, what's happening in Tokyo podcast at www.whi-to-k-y-o-o.info. And while we're on the
subject, I'm a folder. Take it easy, Adam. All right, dude. Talk to you, Dan, everybody. From Tokyo,
it's over to India. Greetings and salutations, Adam Curry. This is Parmac Pazwami from
Calcutta. And I want to talk about Pazwami people being pigs, because here in Calcutta,
it is not always Pazwami people who are pigs, but sometimes when I go visit a buy, a buy who
sets me my shoes. I step off the corner right into a big pile of Cal Puppy. And that is the problem
here in Calcutta. There is Cal Puppy everywhere on the streets. So, it is not just Pazwami people
who are pigs. It is the cows. The cows that are pigs too. So, please understand. It doesn't matter
if you are a Paz or if you are poor or if you are just a cow, you can still be a pig. Anyway,
keep up to go work, Adam Curry. You are doing a very, very good job. This is the point where
I would tell you that I am a folder, except I have nothing to fault. Thank you very much.
Ah, yes. Mark Yoshimaru Nemkoff, that is about the worst Indian accent I have heard
in a long time. But I appreciate the thought, my friend.
Ah, no, no, no, no. Besides, you can get in trouble for doing that, man. In the UK. Because
we are also politically correct now. Hey, by the way, there is something I forgot to mention,
just a little interlude here. About the Super Bowl, I was so happy that political
correctness seems to have dropped just one notch in the interest of fucking sanity in the world.
You know, there were two black coaches in the Super Bowl. So, over and over and over again,
in the media what you kept hearing was, there will be for the first time in history a black
coach who was taken a team to victory the Super Bowl. And I'm like, this is fantastic.
We're no longer stuck to the African American. And I love it. I really do. Hey, it's black, white,
yellow, red, you know, just get over and deal with it. It's fantastic. Let's just call it that way.
We're all people. But it was nice, you know. I don't know why that happened. If it has
something to do with the mechanics of the sport and how that's reported. But it was just
refreshing. Let me say that. In our quest to find out if posh people or potty pigs,
I want to know if women are bigger slabs than men. Hello Adam. This is Stella from Brisbane. California.
I know you wanted to hear from women as your guards. Posh people are potty pigs.
Well, I'm here to report that women are not any better than men. I do to work very early
in the morning. You start out at six. It is so wonderful to go in to clean bathroom and lock
her room. At your inclusive day, when I have to go to bathroom, well, seems like a hurricane
I just go through the bathroom and lock her up. There's hangers all over the place. There's toilet paper
on the floor. Mm-hmm. Sound familiar? Does it sound a lot like a 16-year-old little been
living there? I'm telling you it was the inner child. Paper towels. That portion of the reason
people miss the very large garbage can. That is there in the room for them to place dirt dirty.
Paper towels tend to be saying that it's so disgusting that some women, I don't know why
they know how they do this. This women who have their monthly career, they offer
them to date on the floor. I don't know. It's too much information. There's red all over your seats.
I feel sorry for the cleaning guide when I have to come in and clean after
during the disaster. I'm sorry to report that there's a lot of tissue women out there too,
well, how's it going? Something bizarrely sexy about the way you were phoned in that report.
Thank you so much. All right, so guys, part of this is up to us and this is referring back to
these bits and tinkland common from yesterday that men literally destroy bathrooms. I had a brief
conversation with a lady Patricia about this yesterday and she's like, let's do this show. We've
got to do a show because I have something to say about, okay, but of course you had to go to
the hairdresser today at 1130. So she can't be on the show, you know, much more pressing items.
But it is true. She says, you know, just from one guy in the house, pretty much me.
And I guess, uh, Indiana, Indiana, Indiana, Indiana, Christina's bow. My son-in-law.
That she says, you know, urine is just everywhere. It's on the walls. It's on the mirrors.
And she says, yeah, it's just, there's so much force. And of course, I'm quite tall. So when it
actually hits the toilet bowl, you know, it just splatters. And I'm very, you know, so here you go.
Here's the inner child thing. It's like, I'm not to worry about. It's something to clean it up, you know,
today's I will clean it up or Patricia will clean it up or maybe I'll wipe it down if I see it.
Now it's the whole running away from pain and running towards pleasure. And there's just, there's no,
there's no downside from me not cleaning it up. But I love my wife very much. And I want to please her.
So I have started a test. And I have to equate this to the Nokia N800 tablet. It took me a while
to get used to using the on screen keyboard. It really did. And now I'm pretty much hooked on the
thing. The via was not left the docking station for four or five days. I've been using the tablet
all over the house. But you have to get used to it. So I've been trying Zitz and Tinklin.
Zitz and Tinklin all a lot. Come on. I'm a problem. I've been practicing urinating while
being seated. And I understand all of a sudden this morning as I tried this out. I understand why
guys don't want to do it. You know, for for 40 years at least, I think I can't remember. I should
look at my baby book when I was potty trained. Let's say it's 40 years. I've been urinating
while standing. And sitting on the toilet bowl, my entire body and brain and everything about me is
condition that this is for a different delivery. This, you know, we're dropping the kids off at the
pool here. So all kinds of muscles and things get into spring into action. Whereas that's not the
not what I want to do. So, and I think that's why it feels very unnatural for guys. For women,
you sit down, you know what your mission is. You know, all the pieces move and function in the
right order and you're done. Regardless of what you're going to do there. For guys, it's like you're
sitting down. I wait a minute. The depose empty. But I think that within four or five days,
I will be able to completely have to retrain my brain and there'll be no looking back.
Our posh people of peace. Speaking of, uh, speaking of this, have you ever heard of the guys
called Dirty Sanchez? I don't know if it's OJ from who's on it. I'm letting you know that we've
got those guys from Wales. You know the ones that white poo in each other's faces. You don't know
I'm talking about it's dirty Sanchez. If you want to see how bad they go hot when they were telling
me about grandmother and stuff which quite frankly, you need to not be eating when you hear about it.
Well, go to who's on it's dot pp pod show dot com. Cheers mate. Hey, OJ. Thank you. My man.
OJ is a cheap ass man. You couldn't record a comment for me. You have to dial. He's
completely phoning it in ladies and gentlemen. The infamous OJ boards from pod show UK.
Yeah, you got to see this show. It's up now. Dirty Sanchez. They've done a movie. It's a very
jackass like, but essentially they do a lot with poo. Exactly. You can't help but laugh
when you see what these guys are into. I think you really like this though. They're on OJ's
red couch and while they're talking, OJ's basically give him a whole bunch of shit about being
from Wales, which is I guess kind of for the British is like, you know, the Americans are
say, well, you're from Canada. Something like that. And his grandmother rings.
Calls him on a cell phone is mobile. So you definitely have to check that out.
Hey, for the past two or three weeks, a PD love from daddy cast and the love house radio has been
providing fantastic openings. You heard the posh people opening for today's daily source code. Of
course, you're always welcome to send something in yourself. That's kind of stop that flow of
of intros. And whenever I have more than one, I'll use all of them. Unless they're like too long
or ridiculous. And so I just wanted to give the man some props for, yeah, for doing that for me.
Because every single day, it's like a wake up. I'm doing my show prep and like a big smile on
my face when I see that there's something from PD love. Where is it?
This is all the stuff that came from the hospital, but it's not here. It's got to be around here somewhere.
If you're new parent, I have some shocking news for you. Kids don't come with an owner's
main. Now granted, if you're a guy, you wouldn't read it anyway, but you know, if you're
having one of those days, you may need a little help. Or perhaps you've had a breakthrough
that you want to share with those who can benefit from your newfound parental wisdom.
Whether you are in need or you can help somebody who is, come on over to the daddycast at
thedaddycast.com. My name is PD Love and I am a father of two growing boys in the host of the
Daddycast. On the Daddycast, I share news, tips, and ideas that I have found, as well as suggestions
and thoughts from the listeners, with a few personal stories thrown in from time to time for
comic relief. So come join me at the Daddycast, together we can create a community for parents to learn,
share, and help cope with the complexities of raising good kids. You can find the Daddycast at thedaddycast.com,
or search iTunes, Potchope Plus, or any of your favorite directories for the Daddycast. That's the
Daddycast. Because some days, you just need a little hand.
Listen to my dad and say, I don't.
Fagers. That's right. It finally happened my friends. The official burp of the Charlie has now
been filled up with some Joe. That's a good one. What's your Charlie without some Joe? That's
right. Folgers coffee is now sponsoring the daily source code. Very happy to welcome them.
They're smart, man. They heard the whole Senseo thing. That's over. Last time you'll hear
about Senseo from me. Now it's about the Folgers gourmet selections, coffee flavors.
I have this at the condo. As you know, I don't have a capuccino machine at the condo.
And I've been using it. It's not I don't have the gourmet selection coffee flavors.
Let's see. They come in espresso roast. Yeah. No, I do have espresso roast. I'm sorry. I have that one.
Lively Colombian or Lively Colombian decaf. That's a dichotomy if I ever heard one.
Morning cafe. Oh, these are good, man. Morning cafe. Like body with a clean finish and a
delicate bright taste in a Roma or how about vanilla biscotti smooth vanilla flavor with a creamy
finish or the chocolate truffle creamy smooth and rich with an irresistible chocolatey flavor.
But maybe you want the rich flavor of hazelnut cream with an enticing aroma and smooth finish or
ladies a caramel drizzle a hint of creamy caramel flavor with a warm rich finish.
Also available in holding varieties. Hey, I'm really happy that they're that they're advertising
and that they've picked up a picked up where other coffee people didn't understand what to do.
And I'm also very happy that the folks at Syria stars 102 on the satellite were able to hear this.
We're going to leave you guys satellite window is closing. I'll talk to you guys tomorrow here on 102
and for those of you on the podcast. Yeah, I'd like you to go and try out the Foldiers gourmet
selections. In fact, you can get a free sample if you go to fulgers.com slash pod show
while supplies last so you got to hurry up
and let me know. Let me know which one you like. When I get back to San Francisco because I don't believe
the gourmet selections are available here. I'm going to look at the San'sbury
but that's it. I even broke up broke out the the old coffee machine here in in the manner.
So at least we have the espresso roast. I got to see if I'd like to try the caramel drizzle sounds kind of
interesting. So of course, whenever whenever I burp you're going to think fulgers
or whenever you burp you're going to think fulgers. Because what's the chacha without a great
cup of Joe? Hey Adam, I just wanted to let you know that you're driving me crazy with this whole HD
HD thing. Not all Brits say H. Some of us know there's no H at the beginning of H. Anyway,
while I'm here I wanted to say a quick hello and introduce myself. My name's John and I produce a
weekly video podcast about photography and digital photo post processing using Adobe Photoshop
and all that fun stuff. You can find my show at photo walkthrough.btpotshow.com. I'm just doing the
BTpotshow network and I'm loving the support you guys are giving to us podcasters. So thanks for having
me on board and I'm really looking forward to meeting some of you guys at the next boot up at the
London crash pad. So when's that going to be? Hey yeah, tell me if you're a folder or a scruncher
and we'll talk about it, my friend. I thought I had another burp. It's not coming. Good.
Now, warning the following song is explicit in nature and should be deemed defensive by people
of all religions. All right, dude, Sunday morning, wake and bake. Sorry. No room for you,
crews of faggot. Oh, you're such a yuck. Hey, ultra boy. Want some jesus too. Even if there's
suck dogs in hell. That's not cool. Your chacha is for homo. The intelligent design theory has been
just proof. Oh, wookie wookie. I just don't know what to believe anymore.
Think it's not cool to love our Lord and save you. Jesus Christ.
Damn, my lord. The ball. Jesus. Oh, Jesus. Holy shit. Who save us all from the shit from
brains. They call Satan. Make a freeze. Jesus tight. Fucking hell. God suck and tith fucking
piss. Chuck and ask fish and Jesus on a jet scale. Papa fucking cry. Yeah, yeah. Oh, man.
Jesus Christ. God. Thought you love a church of identical evils and pretty delicious.
As like every Tourette sufferers dream song you if you could sing along. That should be in
Tourette karaoke. Hey, that's a good idea. Tourette karaoke.
Ah, that showed up on the podcast and music network. Those are the same guys who did the song.
Hey, girl. Take off the t-shirt if you don't know any of the bands on it. I think that's a title of the song.
You know, I'm so pleased about about you guys as an audience because you really get into all the
stuff that I'm into and it's really it's so cool. I've been talking a lot about about Nokia devices
of course, you know, and I don't get paid by those guys. You know, we're trying to get some money from them,
but that's not the point. You know, about the tablet about the E61 and it's great because you sent me
email messages. I just bought one of those because I really like what I was hearing.
And so I I was looking for a way to get podcasts onto this pretty much open device seeing
as it runs a Debbie and Linux. And I got an email from Craig Meyer who says, hey, I purchased an
N800 for myself, awesome device. I did your X 11 VNC trick. I posted that on curry.com where I could
remotely control a Mac from the from the tablet and I could control the tablet from the Mac. That was cool.
And he's pointing me to some new applications specifically G Potter, which is a port of the Python version
of of iPodder. And I'm like, yeah. And so, you know, I tried to install it. And then of course,
and it is kind of the device is smart. It says, no, no, you need to depend on this. You need to put the
Python run time in. And I'm kind of lost now because for some reason, my application list or something
isn't updating properly, I'll figure it out. It just takes a little bit of time. But that's a fantastic
news that the G Potter is all, the, you know, the iPodder code, the whole concept is ported to this device.
And I guess we could, I, it probably has a pretty much a command line based interface. I think,
who knows? I haven't been able to get it fire up yet. It might have an interface. I don't know.
I can't wait to try it. I'm so excited. Let me see if there are a couple other, couple other messages
about Nokia. See, I'm doing the pronunciation right here, too. Hey, Adam loved your comment on
and Dick Chargers for new Nokia's couldn't agree more. Worst decision ever. See Miss Leverie.
Yeah, I hit home with that one, didn't I? Hi, this is Peter from Germany.
Since you're in contact with Nokia on a quite regular basis, I was wondering whether you might
ask them why they changed this fucking charger plug. Because this, there's maybe no technical reason
as far as I can see. Well, because there's an adapter that you can simply plug in all the older
accessories for charging that you have. And it simply, there's no point for me in having the new plug
because well, you have the accessories. And this was one of the point why I was buying Nokia
except from being patriotic for Finland is that you have this accessory, then you still can use them
for with every new model. So why don't you ask them when you're doing your turn at the
one, six things? No, of course. No, I already got an answer. It's due to
miniaturization. And by the way, all the new Nokia phones do come with a little adapter plug so
you can plug your old charger into it on one end and then the other end is one of those little
antique things. Yeah, it's a designed design decision made by engineers. I'm sure, as I said,
it's because of miniaturization. And I'm okay with that because all the new phones will just standardize
again on the new miniature plugs. All I'm was saying is that they're really fragile. And, you know,
if I can say anything that I think anyone who was had a Nokia phone will agree with these things
are in the fucking structural. I've dropped them. I've had cars drive over and Patricia has
dropped her into the toilet multiple times, multiple times. You know, hairdryer, things work and again,
so I've always enjoyed that. You know, oh, my phone fell on the ground. You know, and sometimes,
you know, the cover would explode and the keypad would fall off, but you could put it all back together again.
And it just works. You know, I really love the product. Not being endorsed to say that.
But now with the, with the small plugs, if it drops on the floor, with the plug attached, or if you pick it
up with the plug attached, whereas the plug would just kind of like tune, shoot out, or at least hold
its ground now at the end. Bricks off. That's a real pain in the ass.
Hot cap NYC is a free two-day uncomference dedicated to podcasting, logging, and other new and social
media. So come down, learn about these new forms of media, share your own ideas and conduct your
own session, meet other podcasters and listeners and attend our party. The event is hosted and
co-organized by the new school in Manhattan. This free conference, thanks to our general sponsors,
happens April 6th and 7th, 2007, for more information in the top 10 reasons to attend podcast,
log on to podcamp NYC.org.
Hey Adam, guess who composed that wonderful little song? That is of course the short version
from the Jeff Smith. It's Ray Anthony in New York City, and on DSC number 536, you play the song
by Pete Hopkins. And artist, I just so happened to interview last week for the next episode of my
podcast at radioguide.com. Here is just a sample, Pete Hopkins, talking about writing the song I
won't cry. Just a story, so, and it was on my mind, so the lyric part was easy. All I had to do
was just spit out how I was feeling about things, and the bass line, I think the bass line was one
of the first thing that actually, the music came, and it just had the sort of cadence to it,
and I had those chords that were like, damn, damn, and that sounded like in my head. I don't even
think about you. So I had that thing going. It came so naturally, it was just, all I had to do
was just pretty much follow my heart, even though I was feeling, and translate that through music.
In this world, and I'll find love a new dear, so don't you trouble your girl the girl's,
I'm not thinking about you, just stop pretending I'm home in my life waiting by the phone,
hoping my car say that you're sobbing, baby, don't be a fool, you will never that cool.
I won't cry, no tears in my mouth, I won't choose a cause of action to give you no satisfaction,
I got no hope, I don't even care, so go out and find another to take a loving, your loving if you dare.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, go away, מסob восп Kelvin, praiseful, every present, 15 seconds, 10 seconds, 20 seconds, 11 seconds, 15 seconds, 15 seconds, 10 seconds, 20 seconds, 30 seconds, 15 seconds, 10 seconds, 15 seconds, 15 seconds, 15 seconds, 10 seconds, 10 seconds, 15 seconds, 17 seconds, 15 seconds, 15 seconds, 15 seconds, 16 seconds
Yeah yeah yeah
Music
Oh oh cry
Oh cry
No sound is much like a northern sphere
Don't even care
Go out and find another
Oh cry
I think you'll agree with me that there is some kind of
Revolution of wood when you hear songs like this coming out the pod save music network
Pete Hopkins
Five four zero
That's a little bit of info a little
An interview there
Good old Pete
That's really what does it man is that relationship between the
Yeah
A producer of a show
His audience or her audience
And the artists
I love it
I just absolutely love it
Oh okay, let's see
Yeah
It's almost time for free Trinity update
Hi Adam
It's your favorite kentish girl
Josephine Lawrence
I am popping into the office to film episode four of pod find a UK
And I'd really like to meet you
So hopefully I'll see you there
Bye bye
I'll see you all I see you
I'll see you on
I'll see you on Thursday
Yeah, that's it because
I'm going into meet comic strip blogger
It's going to happen at the shortage crash pad
It's going to interview me and we're going to be filming the event
Traveling across the USA
Open and make a good time today
I feel like I've been watching you go
Letting everybody go
This is going to be the better way
Whoa
The Trinity
Trinity
Trinity let the bio diesel set you bring
As I said I had a great conversation yesterday with
Apollo also podcaster Barbara
And she's great
She's going to be collecting data
Presenting that in multiple forms
Of course we're going to populate our map
And that's how we're going to plan out the route
We're Trinity and I think we should get her going
In a week or two when I get back to San Francisco
I think we're almost ready
The Google group again you can find a link to that
It's a daily source code dot com
It's definitely filling up with
Heekly want to participate
I got to get Jeff Smith on the case
We got to get some more jingles and imaging
I got to get Chris Boshiers
To do some cool video bumpers
That's going to be awesome
Really is
And good news from Rosie
From podshow HQ
I got a little Trinity for a 500 mile journey
And she writes via email to me
Adam the trip was a success
She ran very well
Little slow going up hills
And also seemed to get a bit hot
But then cooled down right after the summit
I shot video on a cheap video camera
We have all transfer the files this week
And make an edit ASAP
I'll probably ask Andrew backster to help me
What length do you want me to limit the editor to?
A couple minutes, Rosie just show the fun you had
This is something else that
I think I've changed my mind on
Now that I've been reading through the group
It doesn't seem like a very good idea to hook up a trailer
It's a Trinity
Because it's only like 90 horsepower
Some very low number like that
I think it's bright
Maybe she comes right in a little higher
But after 23 years
So I don't think we're going to be able to get up hills
If we're you know, we're slipping around
gallons of
Unprocessed vegetable oil
And lie and all the stuff you need to make
Biodies also
I think we'll have to forgo that
Wonderful
Technology discussion though
On the Google Group
About how to
Use the Nokia N800
To send back
Pictures and video regular intervals
And GPS coordinates so we can track Trinity on her way
And it's really geeky
So I'm totally loving that
Moving out of
Newport again
Great one
Now Black Connect is the internet
Catching up on DHC
Catching up on the Google Group
I just wanted to ask Bondil whether or not
To use the code for Trinity dot watch
And there's no one going to
Smack that one before we use it for the
Posting content
Just so I mentioned that in case
That one's good for this mind
Yeah, thank you very much, New
Interesting because yesterday I did
I wanted to start a show free Trinity dot pod show dot com
And it was already taken
Like a crap
So I did like free Trinity project
Dot pod show dot com and I figured someone
It probably
Actually I kind of thought someone would have
Just registered it just to protect it like you
Suggest there
Of course it was Barbara
And Doug Pilgrim has been nice enough to
Regirect free Trinity dot com to curry dot com
Actually it would be nice to
Doug if you could redirect free Trinity dot com
To free Trinity dot pod show dot com
And what we'll get
We'll get the site up and running
Folks things are happening
As Barbara said this one's for the doers of the world
And there's a heck of a lot of you
And I really dig it
Programmer come on in
I am this is the prolific program
Again this time from Toronto
Chennai
And the thing I go from here
I'm for the e-week because
Oh, it's a good thing it's in the section
On DSD
539 I think it
Then one
Yeah 539
Was actually
Wonder if it would probably
Better to glue the other way
Diver up through Alaska
And close to during
Straight I do believe
And sing one
When the light is free
Of course then in that case
It makes for an interesting scene
I wonder if it would work with any
I believe it would be very
Straight up very deep enough
And if the ice freezes
The water to the level where deep enough
It will be able to cross with that problem
Um, hope you're here for me
Up to this place
It's some point on the show
And I also hope you got my
Us message regarding
Um
You could work with this
Just off in the UK
Uh, cheers
Yo cheers
Programmer from the Bay Area everybody
And Programmer
I'd expected you might be hacking the Nokia N800
By the way my my contact my deep-throed contact at the Nokia says
When you guys are ready
There are development sheet machines available
So you can really
Develop on the machine itself
I'm just saying you know
You might want to listen to that Programmer
Call in again
It took me a couple times
Yeah, I sometimes have to rewind him
And that's the reason why I put it on
He seems like a real character man
The Programmer I just love it
Just before I go and I do have one more song for you
Which is kind of wacky I thought it played for you
Um
They did a test
Uh, they put a number of uh, of test subjects
Into an MRI
That's uh, does a brain scan
While they were watching
Um
Super Bowl commercials
And there's been a couple of reports about him
Actually I found one in my Google reader
And for some reason I lost it
I thought I had started
But I guess I didn't so it's almost impossible to find it
You can't really search against your existing subscriptions
Unless I'm missing how to do that
Which of course is a flaw
Um
But apparently the way the
The media is taking this and I don't know if this is going to be very wide spread reporting
Most of the
Commercials fell
Completely flat
Let me just quote from a scene at article here
Uh, using brain scan images of people who watch advertisements air during some days
Championship game researches can show which ads triggered various emotions in viewers
Causing them to be fired up or emotionally flat
Federal expresses or FedEx's ad supposedly fell flat
The commercials that inspired the most engagement
Meaning responses of fear
Desire
Conflict and reward
Where Disney's NFL dreamers and CR missed airport security ads
According to researchers from University of California, Los Angeles
A manson, loveless, brain mapping center
And FKF applied research
Oh, that's a mouthful
Very interesting
Because it's a bummer
Because I was well, they posted the images in the data online which is nice
So going and reinterpret
But I didn't have time while prepping the show because there was this other article
Really explained each one in great detail
But just the paraphrase
Most of the commercials evoked
An emotional response of fear
Fear
And making men want to fight
And I thought that was very interesting
And the reports are saying, well, so they fell flat
They didn't work
I disagree
I really disagree
I think that advertising of course works best when associated with an emotion
Such as laughter
Sadness
When a commercial really tugs at your heartstrings and you well up
And of course fear
And fear is so easy to speak to
Now, I don't know if it's intentional
But I think if commercials are evoking fear
Well, bingo
And that's what the news uses to keep you watching is fear
Bird flu, you can die
Right after the commercials
Commercials
You'll never get laid
If you don't use art, is it cream
So I think that the analysis is wrong
I think it's fascinating though
That the
The commercials
Pretty much all evoked that same emotion
Coca-Cola I think gave people a warm happy feeling
But warm and happy doesn't mean that the commercial is a success
And I think that men, particularly men
1834 who were studied in this particular group
I think that they
They are angry a lot more often during the day
And probably when they're angry they think
I'm angry
I need a Budweiser
Something like that
I'll put a link in the show notes daily source code
dot com so you can take a look
At this interesting survey
When you have
Will be filled
The light
Because my must
On my cue
Tonight
That is going to love you
Like you're never going to cry again
That is going to heal you
From all that kind
I came
Here in my heart
Is where you start
Because my must
Gonna rock you
Tonight
Here comes
Let's find you home
He's begging you soon
To come dreaming with him
He's beaming straight
Into your bedroom
Because my must
Gonna rock you
That is going to heal you
And my must
Gonna rock you
Tonight
And if those little worries come along
They won't be staying around
Too long
Because my must gonna rock you
That is going to heal you
To all those tears
Have gone
There's nothing to do
But you hold on to
Love that belongs to you
Because my must gonna rock you
Tonight
Sleep tight
Don't let the bed
But it's bite
Because my must gonna rock you
That is going to heal you
Yeah baby
Mama's gonna rock you tonight
Yeah
Julie Slinn
The master mill for the pod save music network
Mama's gonna rock you tonight
I just thought I was an interesting
Voice interesting song
She's from the UK
Not quite sure where not all the details
I don't pod to music that work
Of course I'll point to that in the show
No state resource code.com
20 years as support
Support artists in various bands in the United Kingdom
Huh?
Interesting
Speaking of the United Kingdom
If you'd like to call in with a message
There is a phone number that you can easily program into your mobile
All right, I gotta get this show out
Gotta hit the bird
Gotta get it to PWFent
So I'm gonna close it down
It's been long for the past couple days
And of course it's because we have this regular recurring
Trinity free Trinity segment
Soon we're going to move the conversation over to freetrinity.com
Free Trinity.podshow.com
I'll keep you alert
But what I'm trying to do now is kind of after the 35 minute mark
That's what I'm doing all the Trinity stuff
So people who just really aren't interested
Or if you really are interested
You just know where to find it
Daddysourceco.com
Adam atpodshow.com
Remember, I just realized
We can do all kinds of scientific experiments now
We've got all these Folger flavor brain, flavor gourmet flavor
Coffee
Selections
That's what it is
The flavor gourmet selections
You can experiment by trying some
Splendaflavour blends
And do all of that while you're at godaddy.com
And use checkout code dsc3
For a great deal on a domain name
I'll be back tomorrow
It'll be hump day and send me some
Adam atpodshow.com
Take care everybody
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best of the brightest
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content
Delivering podshow and limelight