Hey there, Adam is here's blue, blue wittaker, you might remember me from when we went
school together here in West Virginia. We know Adam I've been listening to you show for
a while and I just had to take some of your advice and listen to them commercials about
Splimba. And you know my wife, Sue Ellen, was she been wondering about how to keep her
weight down. So we decided that we'd make the last batch of moonshine with Splimba. I
say what that tastes pretty good there and then I'm moonshine and you can't really tell
you not using real sugar in there. That's Splimba tastes just good and moonshine
in a world where he's using his passion. What, what Ernie said mash, yeah, I said
mash and now Ernie was here mash up. So you know, he'd been listening for a while too.
So if you take care now, Adam, you keep a rod in here and keep it at a 5.5.8, the DSC
5.5 A are rolling with some Splimba. The daily source code with Adam courage. It's my
art being able to choose the music that I want to play for you is virtually Nirvana.
It's musical for my voice. I love the cowbell on it. Oh, it's sweaty. It's really
want to look that leg and squeeze the butt. It's a good now. It's geeky goodness. I mean,
just start this thing up on a command line and then lock that puppy down. You know,
that's about all this need. It's low. You're supposed to be my trophy wife and I can just
see it now. And it's all for you. It's my job to entertain you. And if that means going
to jail, so be it.
I've seen a lot of the rings, seven to three times so far.
I've seen a lot of the rings. I've seen a lot of the rings. I've seen a lot of the rings.
I've seen a lot of the rings. I've seen a lot of the rings. I've seen a lot of the rings. I've
seven to three times so far. There's real induction in my radio. It does great thing.
I've seen a lot of the rings. I'm seven to three times hit in the middle of all.
I'm the section of my lady here that does great things with her
I'm getting nervous, but at least I'm learning how to run
But I was not falling in the data
Can't do myself to go with her
I won't ever think of her
There's a magic level in the barely heats up my suit
I just put it on high and I sit and watch my flowers drip
And the fridge works great and last year was something that's really cold
But just that he's on the break out every with my cracked cereal board
It hours and a phone didn't give a mad at him
Can't do myself to go with her
I won't ever think of her
It's a happiness, it's one in what you already have
But we won't all this crap
It might have looked good back in 1997
It's an obstacle for us, for a credit can sum yeah
And the end you are what you possess
You could be like a desert though
You could complete leaps, yes
Last night I let it sleep out of the colours up on the night
But when the mattress collapsed I decided to sleep on the floor instead
But I was enough on any given day
And I can't put myself to throw you away
I won't ever think of her
I won't ever think that I won't ever think of her
I have to hurry up now
I won't ever think of her
Alec Berlin, everything I want
Kick an off-dairy source code episode 558 coming to you from the Aflu and Suburb of Surino
As Guilford, West Side of G-town G, G-town represent
They do have a G squad or something according to Christina
Yeah, we got gangs here, absolutely, from the curry manner
My name is Adam Curry, how are you doing everybody? Welcome to the daily source code
For strange day, start off a little bit weird
I was up here
My regular time going through the email from San Francisco which came in of course overnight and sending out emails
Which I love doing because when everyone wakes up this morning in San Francisco my email will be on top of the stack
Worked out so well
Just I was just about ready to do all the
Serious satellite radio recording stuff which I also do every every single day and
Patricia says oh
What do you mean oh it's flowing? I'm like oh crap, you know
We've actually had some issues with one of our showers
It's a brand new shower, but something with the
Something with the tubes there's a series of tubes running through the manner that is wrong
And so I'm like oh man this is gonna suck it's gonna be completely flooded downstairs
What it happened was she had a nose bleed
Which is not a not a horrible problem of course you know and it happens very rarely and I've never
I think I've ever seen her get a nose bleed
No, I'm not that I can think of we're not there's just not nose bleeders really and
But because she takes all this medicine this cardiac medicine so she has blood thinners and
And stuff to keep her blood pressure low and
All kinds of fucking poison she has to take you know her blood is really thin and so it was man
It was like her her nose had been shot off. You know it was like I was watching
Crime scene after just paper towel after paper towel filling up with filling up with blood and oh
It was not okay
And it just wouldn't stop so I took her to the doctor
And of course when you're at the doctor's office and this has been bleeding like 40 minutes at this point
You know that's of course when it when it stops magically
But it turns out you know besides the obvious ways to stop and those lead which is first
So don't tilt your head back and I look this up on web and D dot com as well and the and the doctor verified
She thought my my medical knowledge was quite to vast
Don't tilt your head back in fact tilted forward a little bit and you really have to pinch the bridge of your nose
Quite quite firmly in fact for 10 minutes. I really doesn't help
But what does help tremendously if you just get some
Vix like sinus spray
I think was Vix
Synex or Vix a camera which one and it's just over the counter stuff you spray that in and immediately goes to work by
Shrinking all the blood vessels inside your nose which of course really helps stop stop the bleeding and and actually will keep it stopped
So
That's just a handy little tip from the curry manner and an exciting morning
In Adams attic
Yesterday I just might mention this you know I was going to go to my
My
mouth hygienist my dental health professional Beverly
So you have got Fiona who does all the heavy lifting and all the the crap work and who's actually going to be working on my teeth this summer
We have a little plan some things I want to improve
I'm not a really big hero honestly when it comes to comes to dental work
But I do like going to Beverly a Beverly
Clean's my teeth and you know what she said she said wow
Wow, I'm really impressed this is your mouth is really healthy and clean and and I said come over here baby
Prepare man coming after you
Making a rare appearance before the closing of the side like window PW Fenton checks in and what I talked about yesterday with juice
Or as I think I just have to call it by it's by its proper name. Yost from now and we're calling it yost okay
It's not juiced through that it's yost
If you're going to pick that name, I'm going to pronounce it properly
Finally a Dutch name and a product that is known worldwide and we're going to miss pronounced it no used it's juiced
Yost
So here was my hypothesis yesterday that because of the enormous amounts of bandwidth that this program
Gobbles up while it gives you a fabulous experience. I don't want to discount that because it really is quite amazing
It's they say
On the install it even gives you some tips and pointers and some warnings about the amount of bandwidth is going to slurp
500 megabytes per hour
Which is quite a bit and I think will be very strenuous on most DSL networks and even cable networks and in fact
Gobbling up a lot of bandwidth in direct competition with initiatives that the telco's
The phone companies who are rolling out things such as IPTV and cable companies who have their own digital strategies
And of course are able to move video quite efficiently over there
You have seen at work. I think oh I don't want to sound technically in a depth here
So a pdob checked in about the whole yost conversation and his experiences with it
Yol
I love the fact that
Comic strip blogger has his own sort of branding
He go at him. This is pdob
So far I've had a very different experience with juiced or yost
As you very well know because podshow pays for it. I have a huge pipe
All right, all right, I know what I mean
I get five gigs in two gigs out. Oh pdob you must mean megs. It can't be gigs
We've supplied you with far too much pipe if it's gigs and thank you should be supplying someone that pipe over here
Pdob past me your pipe. That's a huge pipe
I also have one of these super fast cord duo computers with the fancy video card
So theoretically I should be able to handle almost anything
So far every attempt to watch juiced or yost is just starts and stops stutters and glitches
This of course doesn't make any technical sense
I think you anticipated exactly what's going on here
My huge pipe is owned by time Warner
So my guess is that they're putting the squeeze on the yost stream
I normally can stream HD content
So this is the only explanation for yost not working that makes any sense to me
What do you think? Yeah, man, I think you may be very right. I think it's called package shaping
There's a way for for routers to look at the
different types of packets and then
Send it off a little bit. It's it's the net neutrality happening before you're very eyes and I have to say I'm not going to stand up and
Shout that yost is being screwed because I understand the the conflict here and I have a
I would think that as mainstream as the deals that yost is making right now that there may very well be several
Telco operators who have already licensed mainstream content to put into their network
Maybe trying to to work with yost to use their platform instead. It's very very possible
I'd keep my eye on that but it will be of course mainly mainstream content
We're still working on getting a pod show channel in yost. I think we have a pretty good shot
Well, I think about it, but it you know, it'll they'll probably only want video and not very much it's a very similar to a deal
We have worked out with Tivo where we're going to enable a number of of of of of or some programming on on Tivo
And it will come through in a real television experience mainly because we are uploading that an MPH2 to Tivo
And it gets stored at their head and then all kinds of crap like that so
But you know, when it comes to net neutrality, you focus on this one watch this one very closely because
Essentially yost is of course a mainstream content
Distributor or package or I should say it's probably better and
And they have licensed content and the same content perhaps even exactly the same content as licensed the Telco and cable operators
But yost yet yost is you know not centralized as far as I understand it's it's decentralized so it's appear to peer
Network which is why it's passing through about 150
Megabytes per hour of bandwidth onto the next person I guess
Food for thought food for thought for sure
We just check the
By the way, something I want to try I hope I can remember to do this I want to put one of my channels
I want to publish that now of course you can go to
Adam.podshow.com and you can see all of my channels
Right now we don't have an easy way for you to just click that and and put it into your into your iTunes or into any other
You know, maybe your mobile phone. I do that a lot. I have the Nokia podcasting a pod catching application. I should say
You could literally it's just an RSS feed so you can use it anywhere, but it's a very dynamic one because it updates from
Multiple sources and it's kind of cool, you know, then you'll be listening to the same thing. I'm listening to
And you'll get a little bit of a look into my mind
This is a pretty interesting story that came in from Ola, Ola Christian Valle who sent this to me
And a guy is now suing I think Microsoft I'm just pulling up the story here
Let's see Michael Allen Crooker currently in jail in Connecticut a fine-up standing citizen says that security features
Advertise by Microsoft and his business partner should have kept federal agents from accessing the files on his PC
In court papers filed this week in Massachusetts, Superior Court Crooker says that he suffered great embarrassment
as a result of Microsoft's failure to keep the FBI's prime eyes off of his computer and he's suing them for $200,000
Let me explain
Crooker purchased a compact presario
presarium PC
loaded with windows
I said presarium
loaded with the XP and I'd explore several security utilities in a 2002 at a circus city in
in Massachusetts
He says he felt secure in circuit cities claims of in penitrability and security
So what happened was the
ATF the Bureau of Alcohol tobacco and fire arms rated his home as part of an investigation
It's the sale of an air rifle equipped with a silencer
So of course you guys probably a terrorist right got a silent drawn at the air raffle
so they took his computer and
and
They were unable to crack the PC security features
So they sent it to the FBI cryptologic
you know cryptologic cryptologic and electronic analysis unit better known as the CEA
There they were able to access Crooker's files by making a mirror image of the hard drive among the files
They found a video showing Crooker and his girlfriend having sex his medical records family photographs and correspondent
Between Crooker and his attorneys. They also found internet history files that showed Crooker's fondness for pornographic websites
Man, I hope they never get a hold of my PC
He says he had internet explorer set to delete his internet history
Every five days any day beyond those parameters is supposed to be permanently deleted
So basically what the guy is saying is you know all this
You know you're safe and it's all packed away and it's encrypted and no one can get at it that turns out that at least in the versions of software that he had was horseshit
And I think he has a case. I really do I mean that's we should all be very worried about that
I totally use or in the past I have to say I got tired of it because usually it fucked up my hard drive, but I've used an encryption for
Not really personal sensitive documents, but
And I do delete some internet cookies
Just so that you know someone might not like be surfing along and seeing that it's already automatically registered and logged in
anyway
Speaking of wanking and such yo Adam this week on house of tone. We're going acoustic
At least mostly acoustic this track you got to check this out this track was sent to me by fill widows
of the folk cast I've got to be very careful how I pronounce that the folk cast of fullcast.co.uk
Which was described as the UK's first in premier folk music podcast covering the worlds of folk folk rock singer songwriter and roots based music
Sounds pretty cool. Well fill apparently wants to focus all up because he sent me a track called Fisherman's Priest
Which is also the theme song for the folk cast and I guess the best way for me to actually describe this tune is it's kind of like a cross
between river dance and
Frankie goes to Hollywood's
Hit single two tribes and I know what you're saying you're like what the fuck are you talking about
But trust me when I say I mean it in the best possible way
So Adam smoke him if you got him lay back and get ready for a nice hard fulking because here comes
Fisherman's Priest
Here comes the Frankie goes to Hollywood part
I
Let's sure isn't your grandfather's folk music I can tell you that much
The song Fisherman's Priest is all the work of folk cast co-host Ken Nichol who
Phil says makes a living out of spanking his various planks and apparently he has time to play the guitar as well
So very very cool and if you listen if you really listen to it you can really hear that
All those guitars were double tracked manually and I mean manually
Meaning that Ken laid the guitar part down on one track and then went back and replayed it
Note for note on another track and may have double and triple tracked it as opposed to some sort of artificial or digital manipulation
And trust me when I say that I'm an expert at digital manipulation
So if you're a guitar player, it doesn't matter if your style is metal blues jazz or you play some really
Fulking hot kick-ass acoustic send your guitar solo track to house of tone at gmail.com
That's house of tone all one word at gmail.com
And Adam thank you my brother for keeping the guitar solo in the spotlight because I can think of no
But her place to keep wanking a life then right here under your nose at the daily source code
So Adam I'll catch you later. Bye. Well folk me
Mark Yoshimoida and Kofky also keeping guitar wanking alive
What's wrong with your voice dude?
No, you can't spit you don't have to swallow
I pops up at the most opportune moments
Particularly when it comes to wanking
He sent a picture oh
Man, this is so wrong Roger and please don't use my name
I shop at Anderton's music and gillford. That's where I get all my cables and my compressors
That's where I got the TLA from the the 50 52 valve processor. Dude. It's so nasty. I can't
I can't you know, I'd have to Photoshop this thing in order to even
Make it put it up somewhere publicly
Well good to hear from you Roger and I appreciate you getting into the spirit spirit of things, but
The whole idea of a splash and dash
Too much for me my friend. Yo Adam not jersey taught this time, but jersey Peter
Here's a long time listener double digits. I think from the time right after you move from Belgium to the cottage in the UK
Glad to hear you and Patricia doing so well and I agree with so many other listeners
Patricia's so great on the show. Can't you get her on more somehow?
Yeah, I'd really like to
But she's too busy bleeding all over the place. She's got no time for us
Maybe tomorrow or maybe maybe Friday now tomorrow probably Friday is cleaning day
Yes, I'd like listeners. I'll catch you tomorrow for sure with without the lady Patricia
There's some parallels in our lives. I'm a Dutch guy living in Jersey and sure thing almost a joysy boy
The Frankie Valley show you went to in San Francisco. It made me look them up and buy some songs on iTunes
So much fun to be reminded of that music who know Frankie Valley was behind all those familiar songs
And thanks for the source code the other media that would include old-style radio broadcasts and cable TV
I've pretty much fallen by the wayside for me as they've become so irrelevant
But the Charlie has become embedded into my day
Perhaps the show also reminds me of the 80s when I grew up in Holland hearing you on the Dutch countdown and
Good evening on ankle. Great memories. So thanks for sticking around
You can check me out on indigored.com if you're interested check out the book I'm working on while raising my kids
Thanks again got speed at him. No, I thank you. I know past this on to the lady Patricia, so
Yeah
It'd be nice to get her on. Hey, um, you know Natalie Del Conte does a video show for us a couple times a week
called textra.txtra.com and
Every night before she tapes, she sends me the stories and they're like a show rundown because
I don't know why they put me up as executive producer. So I figured I'd look busy and
I'm not gonna read the whole story to you, but I do want to this is something you will definitely want to check out this this piece of news
I'm sure there must be a link somewhere online about this, but it's a very interesting the French
Constitutional council approved a law this week that makes it makes it illegal to film or broadcast acts of violence online or on TV if you are not
a professional journalist
Well, it's not interesting
That wouldn't go over too well in the states my frog friends
Oh man, I think you're asking for trouble with this one. That's like called what do we call that sense or ship exactly
I wonder if that's gonna be ratified through the European Union or it maybe you don't need any ratification
I guess you can do whatever you want, but
Holy moly professional journalists means your card carrying I guess
I don't know. I really don't know if that's a good idea
I think we're gonna miss out on a couple things there
Let me see some longer comments. I'm just gonna play some bits from
Item it's edros from pots with here. I've not listened to the SE for a couple of months
Do some health reasons, so also might need a bit of help knowing what's been going on since they're beginning of January
I have a bit of somebody to do a Trinity and you've got a nice knocking at hundreds and stuff, but just a few pointers as to
To what's been going on in your life might be nice. All right. We'll have to ask the govers to do another FAQ
So people, you know, I should make that a promo
If you stop listening for the past couple months, here's what you missed
But why? Anyway, um, did catch a few last week heard you talking about Wi-Fi sharing
Don't know if you know about a company called fawn that's fuckstraught Oscar
And no member
Nutsack you could say
Or we
Anyway, F-O-N.com
They have a Wi-Fi sharing community which sounds really fun. Yeah, you know this is this is about
About naming your Wi-Fi access point with your email address. You know there's so many dirt that you know sometimes
I wonder why if I seem to be so host there seems to be so many different things and competing
ways of doing things and
And the phone thing F-O-N
Yeah, I've heard about it, but you know that that the launch of that was kind of unfortunate
Because as I recall it
Apparently a lot of bloggers who were very enthusiastic about the service
Were incentivized somehow on the back end and that you know that stirred up a shitstorm and then of course
No one really focused on on the building of the community. I should check that out
There probably is something there, but I guess I have to get a new router or router
I don't know if I'm into that
The first thing I'm going that was cool. That was really quiet wasn't it the first thing or the next step in the free
Trinity
Promotion is
Is to get this this tablet up and running so we have the technology ready to send her on her way
Now you remember listening to Doug Pilgrim and his son who were totally into doing a part of this
And as we're you know rethinking the the drive the driver situation how we get people
Cued up, you know, I want to make sure the technology is right so I have this N800 which Nokia sent over
Luke from Nokia who happens to be a Dutch guy by the way
It's funny. We send emails back and forth. Yeah, I was like my BFF
You know we're emailing and and and testing voice stuff and it's kind of freaky
Anyway
There's the the sensitivity has a name Trinity is my
My baby poo colored Mercedes
Stationwagger from 1984 the runs on biodiesel better known as vegetable oil
So we got a name this tablet which actually is going to sit now I've started the configuration because I had to make a couple of user accounts
So first you have to get root and then you have to install the SSH server so that the you know a few
Engineers and
Technologists who want to develop this have raised their hands, you know, I'm gonna let them come in and
Basically violate anything they want on the Nokia and 800 because she'll have reports wide open for these developers wide open ports
I so of course
Yeah, this is a real thing, you know, it's it's alive. There's there's men inside this thing so I want to give her a name
And people are sending in some pretty interesting
Suggestions um the comics are blah, but blogger
Suggested we use the name Tariah, which is a very common name in Finland, which I think is a pretty good idea
Although then cleatus the Wayne sends in
How about to rock sand and he give me some lyrics here rock sand you don't have to put on the red light
Those days are over just need to open your ports for the geeks at night
I can hear Jeff Smith jingle happening already don't do yet Jeff because I don't know what the I don't know what the name is
Oh, yeah, so here's here's an email from Luke saying yeah, yeah, Tariah is a that's a pretty common female name in Finland
The president of Finland her name is indeed Tariah Hallonen
Hallonen yeah, and there's lots of Tariahs in his life, so
Okay, so Tariah might be a good one
We have some other comments about the N800 hi Adam this is Brandon in Tucson
Had an idea for the name of your N800
I know you went with Angelina
She is quite the prince of the darkness, but I think a better name might be Natalie Portman
Bet just a thought
It's yeah
Natalie Portman. I like that. Natalie. Ah, Natalie open your apartment
So when else said the how about
Sharon as in Sharon Stone because she flashed her ports on film and
For me that immediately is associated with Sharon Osborn, so it just doesn't really work, you know
Yes, I think this is for Adam Curtis
This is his neighbor
Sharon Osborn. Yes, it's the Sharon Osborn the one you to do was not sexy
Well, I'm your neighbor now and you know
Your apples are growing too heavy and fast and they're dropping all over our backyard and you have to clean it up
Okay, so
Tonight Oats Up by
That was a fantastic Sharon Osborn in personation. I have to say I was fooled from from the second it came in
Your suggestions for the N800's name
This lovely female device who will be opening her ports
Very wide for developers to come in and violate her internally. We'd love to hear your suggestions
Also talk to me yesterday about voice over IP
I got a lot of comments about that as I expected this one is kind of funny though
Let's listen to the setup and then I'll interrupt the call
Yeah, and it's false from my critical in Washington. I do IT support
Management my company does that
For various companies on the west coast and around the world anyway
Your voice discussion come my eye my ear as you said
We just did a voice install. We didn't actually do a real source of voice install
So come to help with IT solutions and
Okay, so so I'm gonna stop him here for a second. So first of all
This is cool. You know his company does voice over IP installations and he just did an installation
It's he's not it's not really pitching me on anything but he's he's interested in the conversation
He knows a lot about it
But here's what kills me as you listen to this comment you'll it starts to become completely unintelligible because I presume
He's calling on voice listen to this
See it's phasing in and out
I mean that'll that'll kill me if I if I have to listen to conference calls that way that would suck
Oh
And yeah a lot of people said that it's true
You know all these void providers. So you know basically the gizmo project is pretty much just a front end for the sip protocol
And yeah, they tie into a PBX which is I think an asterix
That's an open source PBX and you know someone there's buying minutes and switching stuff through so
You know the systems are pretty much in place, but it's stuff like that you know when the quality really degrade so
severely it becomes and the only thing you can say is you know you get what you pay for you know, which is kind of true
Now I haven't had a really bad experience yet
We're using using the gizmo project, but caller ID it just doesn't work
You know, it's because people are min from eight million different
Minutes providers and god knows what the connections are and the first thing to get dropped along the line of stuff in the protocol is the caller ID and it really really sucks
And I tell you until we get that stuff moved along it's just going to be second tier service. I mean people get used to that kind of stuff not just
You know voice mail sure that's important
But we need these other services and they have to work properly
You know the government's always focusing on you have to have emergency services like you know nine one one
Yeah fantastic give me fucking caller ID okay
I
Something else I was going to say about that
I can't remember what was talking about was talking about the voice over IP
The crap I can't remember now I may be able to come back to me during this
I
What
That is the best part
No
No, I want to listen to it okay
Oh
Love that
Okay, I remember what I was going to talk about it was about the cloud there's this provider in in
Certainly in Europe. I don't know if they're in the states as well, but in the UK and they have good coverage in London
And um, I think it's called the cloud dot net. That's how you get to it
And you can sign they actually have a special promotion for the Nokia and 800 tablet
Where you sign up to the service for nine pounds 95 cents per month plant pens per month, which I already did and
You you are automatically authenticated on any one of their hotspots and they have hotspots and gulfed as well
But they don't do it through a username password. They do it at the MAC address level
So the actual ethernet address of the of the Wi-Fi
Chip that's in the tablet or I presume in any other Wi-Fi enabled device. It'll it'll work the same way
So when you're in the proximity it'll automatically connect it'll automatically you know do whatever it has to do
For instance, it could reconnect my my Gizmo project client so that you know a
Potentially phone calls could come in but certainly some stuff could update like my new
My podcast aggregator. You know, it's a lot of that dream that we've been having of some kind of device that just sits in your pocket is looking all over the place for a network
And this one does it looks for open networks
It looks and I was looking for the cloud as well
Which of course will take preference it'll automatically log in and then it'll start to download stuff
You know, we're getting very close to that dream player and I got to tell you I got to tell you
I should be charging Nokia some freaking money for this shit. I'm way too enthusiastic about it
Oh
crap
I'm sorry. That was the wrong one. Well, now I just gave it away. Didn't I?
March 22nd is
Marked as bum rush the charts day now you've probably seen
The bum rush the charts logo on a couple of show sites
Certainly a number of pod show podcasts, but also podcasts outside of the pod show network or supporting this the idea is
on March 22nd to all
On mass and I'm going to ask you listeners on March 22nd as well obviously to go and spend 99 cents
to buy one song one track at
On iTunes
Because we believe that we can actually
Get this song to move up the charts and show that there is quite a bit of power in independent media
predominantly in podcasting
And the audiences that we
Have that are surround us essentially
And I love the idea. I think it's a very pirate kind of thing to do
It's not an official pod show promotion
But a lot of pod show podcasts as our participating in and obviously I hope the audiences will do the same
You know it's 99 cents to help out in an experiment of course of course
You know when you choose a band and the band that was chosen was black lab
The reason they were chosen is because they were on a major label and were dropped
So we you know that's kind of like a double whammy to say hey, you know there is audience out there
And they are motivated and they do care and obviously if you don't you don't give a shit about the song and don't buy it
If you hate the band don't buy it, please only if you want to and you want to help out
And it being the podosphere the podcast community and the blogosphere
Of course there's people saying well, he's that really that band chose to random
Like yeah, like we're trying to hype a band and this is some kind of hidden fucking promotion
That's so a fucking offensive
So of course, you know even though we didn't involve them officially or they're not involved officially as far as I know
Black lab Paul Durham
I has something to say about the bum rush the charts
Operation bum rush the charts and I think he's got a really good idea how we can just keep this on the straight and narrow and be focused and do what we set out to do
Hey, this is Paul Durham for the band black lab a lot of you may have heard about bum rush the charts a campaign by podcasters
And listeners to take over the iTunes charts by buying our song mine again on March 22
It's funny that a lot of people think that this is some kind of
Marketing gimmick on our part and I just wanted to take a moment to reassure everyone that
We're not that smart
In fact, we had nothing to do with planning of it
But now things are going crazy
So anyway, we just wanted to say that we are totally behind this effort to demonstrate the power of independent art and media
And we hope everyone will focus on the purpose of BRTC
Which is to make a statement about the power pod casting and to raise some money for a scholarship program
So on March 22 in addition to the iTunes affiliate money that is already been set up
We're going to be donating 50% of our earnings from the song to the scholarship fund as well
So thanks everybody and bum rush the charts. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. All right, so there you go. Thank you very much Paul
Sorted mate
Now let's farm rush those freaking charts
Oh
Can
Yeah
Nothing like a little black lab on a Wednesday
See the sun it's from the pod safe music network and don't forget bum rush the charts in March 22
I'll be for a different song for a minute give all right that's it for today's
Chacha, I'll be back tomorrow and I've changed my flight on Friday
So I'll be able to bring you a full food bar instead of traveling. I'll be traveling a little bit later on
So daily source code dot com Adam at poncho dot com talk to tomorrow everybody another poncho podcast stick it in your ear
The best and the brightest
Subdupt daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering pot show and limelight